Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather will come
fluttering down, swaying gently in the
air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
Wow! Our house is all fixed now!
Amazing!
Unbelievable! So this is the
full power of a goddess, huh?
You actually restored our house
and the whole city in an instant!
Well, I did cause everyone
a lot of trouble...
But...
Now that the Lord of Terror
is no longer a threat...
...my power is too great, so I'm
going to have to seal it again.
Belldandy...
Summoning electricity!
Oh, my. I guess Urd's playing
tag with Skuld again.
So this is the first thing she does
the minute her license is reinstated...
I've got you cornered, now!
What the heck is...
You're going down!
U...Urd!
Ah! Urd's Little Romance
Oh, man...slippery-smooth
and totally flat!
But why'd she turn into a child?
To live in this world, we goddesses
must draw on an energy supply...
...from Yggdrasil.
Oh, that's right!
The system crashed during the
Lord of Terror incident, so...
In Urd's case, I think that's how the
energy deficiency manifested itself.
So if she keeps on using her powers,
she's only going to get smaller?
Oh no, we goddesses have alternate
energy sources for emergencies.
Alternate energy source?
Ah, the heck with you! Goshdarnit!
Let me guess...could it be sake?
Huh?
Belldandy!
In Big Sister's case, it's sleep.
Huh?
I see.
She did use her full power
just now to fix the whole town.
Big Sister...
Come to think of it,
you seem fine, Skuld.
Oh, I'm totally fine!
Sure, because she has
no powers to speak of!
The grownups are talking right now, kid!
But listen, Urd,
I'll play with you later!
You've really got some nerve!
Is that a good idea, using your powers?
Urd!
Hey, why don't we do
something about your clothes?
But what kind of clothes should we
buy?
I know, we can get her something
at the neighborhood thrift shop!
Belldandy!
To conserve energy,
I've split off from myself.
Anyway, let's go get
some clothes for Urd!
Sure.
Urd's Castle
How do I look?
Hey, I think it rather becomes me!
You mean she actually likes it?
Looks like it!
I'm going out now.
Fine!
The Almighty!
This is cool!
Hey, it's really cool! Come on, come on!
There!
Hey, you!
Uh...my cram school class
has been canceled today.
It's not as if I always hang out here...
it's just a coincidence...
Sake's not for children!
Oh, no, it's not sake,
it's a video game...
Look, you've got it all wrong.
I told you, I'm not a child!
Drinking sake in broad daylight...
What in the world are
your parents thinking?
Well, they do like to take
the hands-off approach...
Come with me to the station!
Didn't you hear me? I'm NOT a child!
Don't be ridiculous!
Man, what a pain in the butt.
What should I do now?
Huh?
Hang onto this for me!
Hey, you!
Come back here!
Is she a friend of yours?
Uh...um...
Hey!
Oh, rats. I just used up
all my strength.
Are you all right?
He was nice enough to bring it to me!
But in any case...
Uh...listen...
Sake!
Huh?
Give me that sake.
Sake!
Ah! Nothing like a drink
after a hard day's work!
Thanks. I owe you one!
Um, no problem...
But really, you're a
little pushover, huh?
Running away with me like that!
Hey, but, isn't that why
you were able to get away?
Oh, hey, you're right!
By the way, what were you
doing just now?
Oh, nothing.
It's not like I was ditching cram school.
There's no class today, so...
I'm talking about the game.
Huh?
That's the one that
just came out, right?
Oh, uh...well...
This is it.
Hmm...how do you play?
This is Button A, and this is Button B.
And this is the Start button,
and here's Reset.
Want to give it a try?
Sure.
Here are the instructions...
That's all right.
I am a System Administrator goddess.
Huh?
All right, let's start!
I'm done.
Huh?
What's next?
What?
You don't have any more?
Oh, uh...um...
Okay, then...try this one next.
All right!
I had a pretty good time!
No way...how could you beat them all?
Anyway, I think I'll head home now.
Oh...
See ya!
My name is Shohei Yoshida!
What's...
What's your name?
Urd.
Uh...um...Uru?
My name is Urd.
Uh, hey! Will you be here tomorrow,
too?
If you're here, too!
Huh? What the...
Urd?
Look at the time!
I'm really going to be late
for cram school, now...
Hey...
Oh, cripes.
I forgot my sake.
Oh, whatever!
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Welcome home, Urd!
Are you going somewhere?
That's right. Great news, Urd!
Urd, we heard from the Almighty
after you left the house.
From the Almighty?
He told us that we should use
moon rocks as an alternate...
...energy source until
the system gets restored.
Right, they would definitely...
Hold on...how are we going to
get our hands on moon rocks?
We're heading out to make some.
The facilities we need are at school.
So we're going to
gather up the materials.
Urd, you only have to
hold on a little longer!
Well, there's no rush, really.
Being a kid is more fun than I thought.
She seems to be enjoying herself.
Yes, she does!
Hey!
What took you so long?
So what are we going to do today?
Today I've got some games that are
way more difficult than yesterday's...
Come on!
Hey!
Hey! Hold on!
A volcano, did you say?
Right.
Moon rocks are mainly composed of
a type of volcanic rock called basalt.
So all we need is to get some basalt?
Actually, Moon rocks have a slightly
different composition than Earth rocks.
That's why we have to
make them ourselves.
But once we do that, you two
can go back to normal right away.
Going to all this trouble for us...
I'm so sorry.
Don't be!
I mean, this is the one thing
I can do for you...
I'm...so...wiped...
But even I'm not that out of breath!
Buy me some sake.
Um! But listen, I'm still...
Huh?
You see...um...you can't drink
sake until you're an adult...
And I'm still in grammar school...
And even if it's a vending machine,
I still shouldn't do it...
So that's why...
I don't think I can...um...
Gotcha.
Come on! Let's go!
Yahoo!
Falling down isn't my thing, see...
Okay, then! In that case...
Come on! You can do it, Shohei!
You're almost there!
And don't look up, got that?
Don't look up!
What are you talking about? Most
people would say ''Don't look down!''
Rats, what did I tell you?
That's exactly why
I told you not to look up!
Right.
Thanks to you, I just got even smaller!
Huh?
Oh, nothing, just talking to myself!
I'm sorry I didn't buy
your sake for you just now.
Oh, that was nothing.
It's time for cram school,
so I'll be going now.
But it's still light out.
I've got early classes today.
Oh?
If you think you can't do something,
you'll never be able to do it...
...no matter how easy it is.
Come with me!
But...hey, wait! Hold on, Urd!
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
Uh, um, what are you going to do?
Okay, it's open! Come on, let's go!
What? Go? Go where?
We're going to climb it,
what did you think?
What!
Come on!
Hey, hold up a second!
All you have to do now
is cross over here.
No way can I do that!
If I fall, I'll be killed!
Then just don't fall.
Huh?
Didn't I just tell you?
If you think you can't do something,
you'll never be able to do it...
...no matter how easy it is.
But, saying that is one thing...
if I really do fall...
But you did it yesterday!
My sake...you brought
it to me, remember?
Come to think of it, at that time...
Why was I able to do
something like that then?
Right...I've got to go after her.
No matter what happens!
Whoa!
This is amazing!
Isn't it?
I mean, from up there, this was
the tallest building I could find...
Up there?
Oh, uh, nothing! Forget it, okay?
I think I might've
gotten too involved...
Shouldn't you be heading
for your cram school?
Oh, cripes.
Okay, I'll see you around!
Urd!
W-where do you live?
You are a foreigner, aren't you?
How long are you going to be in Japan?
Uh...well...
Sorry.
I'm not a child.
I told you when we met, remember?
That I'm not a child...
Huh? What?
Urd...
I'm home.
Look, they're done! The moon rocks!
You can turn back to your old self now.
Isn't this wonderful, Urd?
Let's wait...until tomorrow.
Oh, boy, so he did follow me home.
Urd, don't tell me
that you and that boy...
I thought I was just passing the time...
...but I guess I did something
that I shouldn't have.
Urd...
Maybe it's best that
I turn back now, after all...
TARIKI HONGAN TEMPLE
Can I help you?
Wait...are you a friend of
my little sister's, maybe?
Yes!
If you came to see Urd,
she's not here anymore.
Huh?
She went back to her own home, you
see.
And she probably won't
be coming back here.
I'm sorry.
That's not why I'm here.
What?
This sake...
Could you please give
this back to Urd for me?
Also, tell Urd that I said thank you...
That I'm going to stop
giving up before I even try...
That I know I can hang in there...
And so, when I'm all grown up...
...can we meet again?
Whoa!
Yes. I promise you.
So grow up fast, all right?
All right!
SKULD LABORATORY
Huh?
AUGH!
TO BE CONTINUED
Always believe in yourself and
your Dreams. You have a Wing!
I love you so much it hurts...
And it hurts me that
I can't tell you how I feel.
You and I have matching hearts...
So we must share the
same scars deep down inside.
But now that I'm in your arms,
I think I can catch...
...your pounding heartbeat this time.
Nobody else matters...
All we have to do is gaze at each other.
It's all right for your heart to flutter...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
Don't run away from happiness.
I'll always be waiting for you.
So come rest your wings anytime.
It's all right to cry...
anytime you need to.
I just want to see you again...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
I just want you to be happy.