Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather will come
fluttering down, swaying gently in the air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
Big Sister!
Good morning, Big Sister!
Good morning, Skuld!
Hey, let me help you, Big Sister!
I'll help! I'll help!
All right, then here...
Okay!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I call him Mitaro,
the All-Purpose Slicer & Dicer!
Now your workload will be so much
lighter!
Do your thing, Mitaro!
I'm sorry!
Thank you. That was a big help.
Big Sister.
It's all right.
Skuld's been latching herself onto
Belldandy for the past few days...
She was separated from her beloved sister.
You can't blame her for wanting attention.
Oh, listen to you! I'll bet deep down
inside you're jealous!
Huh?
You should let her mother you
once in a while, too.
What?
You're not going out somewhere, are
you?
Yes, I'm going to class with Keiichi.
All right, we'll see you later!
See you later!
Huh? Ah!
You stay at home like
a good little girl, now.
See ya!
Oh, come on, you guys!
Ah! Teaching a Lesson Called
Competition?
Big Sister?
Well, well! Good morning, Skuld!
Big Sister, are you going to that place
you call ''college'' again today?
Yes. There are so many people there
at college...it's a lovely place to be.
You should come sometime, too.
I wouldn't go there for anything!
I know! Big Sister always goes off
with Keiichi because of this thing!
Huh? What a primitive 2-wheel drive rig!
I can't believe he's making my beautiful
Big Sister ride this piece of junk!
First, this side car... Whoa!
What's up with this inefficient fuel pump?
Huh? Just look at that clutch!
It's absolutely pointless!
Oh my gosh, now that I can see...
there's no oil cooler!
Well, if it isn't Megumi!
Good morning, mister!
That bike you fixed for me the
other day...it's running like a dream!
You really saved the day!
Oh, don't mention it,
you're more than welcome!
It's my way of saying thanks.
Are you sure?
Of course I'm sure! You're
always such a big help, Megumi.
Well, then, if you insist...
The boss at the fish shop wants you
to take a look at his bike, too.
I'd really appreciate it!
Sure!
Morning, Kei!
Oh, it's you, Megumi. What's up?
It's so early in the morning...
I just thought I'd join
you guys for breakfast!
Oh, man...
Oh, come on! Here. I brought you a gift.
The grocer gave it to me.
You really do get around, don't you?
So unlike our Keiichi here!
Oh, back off, will you?
Hey, gimme some more!
Oh, it's you, Megumi! Good morning!
No way!
Belldandy. Can I join you for breakfast?
Stop it, Urd!
Please come in.
I did it!
To think that I made all these
modifications in such a short time...
...I must be a genius after all!
What did you do to my bike?
Oh, don't thank me,
it was a piece of cake...
I forgot I was going to take it apart...
...who knew I'd lose myself
in the joy of creation instead?
She's so cute!
Is this your daughter, Kei?
Are you crazy?
That's Belldandy's little sister, Skuld.
Hey, you!
Don't treat me like a kid!
I may not look it, but...
So you attached a turbo, huh?
A turbo in front of the carburetor...
Hey, I'm talking to you!
I bet you had a hard time keeping the
carb balanced on both sides, right?
It would be a no-brainer with
something simple like a car.
Oh, but you could always go
with a fuel injector, right?
But then there'd be the problem of heat...
You did great, making a turbo this small.
She's good!
But unfortunately,
now the body's off-balance.
What? Are you criticizing my work?
According to my calculations, it should
be 1.5 times faster than before!
Sure, it's probably gotten
a speed boost, but...
...it's too much for the chassis to handle.
Keiichi! Get on and prove me right!
Hey, stop that!
Good idea.
That'll give you a better idea.
Keiichi!
Oh, man, I knew it...
Who are you, anyway?
Huh?
She's Keiichi's younger sister.
Nice to meet you!
I don't care if you're his sister...
you're not getting away with this!
This is for whoever dares
to mock my inventions...
...the Skuld Bomber!
Now that's quite enough!
Hey! Big Sister!
Those who use such violent words end
up with violence in their hearts also.
Big Sister, give it back!
Belldandy to the rescue!
If you're going to compete,
it must be on equal footing.
You three must be sisters after all...
Yes, Big Sister!
Oh? Think so?
Okay! We got it!
Well, hello!
Monsters?
What are you two doing here?
Don't sweat the details.
Den-chan missed you since you've been
such a stranger these days, Morisato.
You keep your mouth shut about that!
Come on, you're too old to be so shy!
Um...so what is it that you've got?
It's this.
A Robot Battle?
These two will each build a robot,
and compete against each other.
A Robot Battle?
Rocket Punch!
X-1 Beam!
Cool!
I don't think that's what he means.
Who said you could look into my mind?
What's it gonna be?
Will you accept this challenge or not?
I think I'll give it a shot.
Megumi!
Well, building a robot sounds like fun!
All right, then!
I'll take you on, show you my power, and
rub it in your face!
Whoa, calm down.
I'll be looking forward to that.
You're treating me like a kid again!
Just you wait!
I'm going to build the most awesome
robot and cut you down to size!
Hey! Skuld!
So that's settled.
You can leave the rest to us!
All right, then... farewell, all!
Anything can happen with those two,
huh?
So let's see...
Basically, it's a barrel-collecting race.
The robot that gathers the most steel
drums inside that ring wins the game.
Steel drums?
It's so like those two to come up
with something like this.
You can use whatever materials
you want, and any number of people.
And it looks like you'll be allowed to use
equipment and facilities at school.
"Interference during the
game is also welcome.''
Those are my kind of rules!
All right! I'm going to start
designing my robot right away!
Will it be all right?
I think it will be a
good experience for Skuld.
I wouldn't be so sure...
Huh?
Urd?
I do understand the reason why
you fired up Skuld like that, but...
...that girl's more
difficult than you think.
Now then, I think I'll go explain
the rules to our little Skuld!
Urd...
VICTORY!
SKULD!
We are Skuld's groupies!
We're here to put our lives on
the line to support Skuld! Yeah!
We're the Megumi Morisato
Fan Club Community!
And together we're going to
guide Megumi to victory! Yeah!
What... what is this?
My, you two are both so popular.
That's not the point...
Well, this is all pretty crazy,
but let's both do our best, okay?
No way am I ever gonna lose to you!
Really!
Telling us we can use any materials
we want, and this is what they provide?
Behold, these are your materials!
What?
Humans are just too
uncivilized to be true!
Hey, look, there's Skuld!
I'm in the Megumi camp.
So you're with the enemy?
Since when did you go for that type?
Who knows what they're thinking...
Hey, it's Skuld!
Hey, Skuld! Good luck, okay?
We're all rooting for you!
Are those the parts for your robot?
Want us to help you carry them?
Huh? Um... you see... I'll be fine!
Boy, they gave me such a shock!
That's it, you can just bring that here...
this way.
Hey, thanks!
Use that pipe for reinforcement, okay?
Okay.
So she can't even build
a robot by herself!
If that's the case,
it should be a cakewalk for me!
Good work!
Thanks, that's just what I needed.
Skuld?
Hah! Take that! Take that!
Bam! Pow! Whack!
Yoo hoo!
Hey, what are you doing here?
I came to help out
my darling little sister, of course!
I'll be just fine on my own!
You heard her.
Isn't there anything
we can do to help you?
It's a lot of work for just one person.
I'll be all right. I can build
a robot on my own just fine!
I'm not like that Megumi!
Skuld...
She's late coming back, don't you think?
You're right, she is.
I'm sure she's wallowing
in the joy of creation.
I'm going to go help after all...
Just leave her alone.
Isn't that why you encouraged her?
If you go to her now,
she'll only be more stubborn about it.
Hey, so you're actually worried too, Urd!
Not a chance! That kid doesn't even
look up to me as her older sister.
Alrighty, I'm going to take a bath.
Belldandy?
Do you think I was mistaken?
Huh?
Skuld can be a little obstinate
at times, but I think...
...deep down inside, she saw something
in Megumi very much like herself.
So that's why she's had
such a chip on her shoulder...
But there's also an aspect of herself that
differs from Megumi.
That's what I wanted her
to find it on her own...
So you tried to make them compete.
Yes, because I was sure that those
two could become friends, but...
It'll be all right.
I mean, she's your sister
and Urd's, right?
Keiichi!
Still, we can't just leave her
to fend for herself like this...
...so I think it'll be okay
to help her out in secret.
Right!
I've made a lot of headway tonight!
So what do you think, Big Sis...
I'm going to call it a day!
What was that? Don't tell me it's a spy?
This is great!
It makes me happy to hear you say that!
But is it really okay to
treat us all like this?
All of us in the Nekomi Shopping Arcade
are rooting for you, Megumi!
Come on, everyone, dig in
and do your best for her!
Right!
It's Skuld.
Is she doing reconnaissance?
I don't care if she sees what we've got!
Hey, why don't you come eat with us?
She ran off.
I guess she really can't stand me.
I hear she's building
her robot all by herself.
She can do that?
Well, I wouldn't know, but...
By herself, huh? That's pretty amazing.
But the thing is, there are limits to
what you can accomplish on your own.
I'm going to win no matter what!
ROBOT BATTLE
Banzai! Banzai!
Banzai!
Skuld!
Big Sister...
GO! SKULD!
MEGUMI!
Thank you all for waiting!
The Robot Battle between Skuld
and Megumi Morisato will now begin!
First... in the red corner...
With Skuld wielding the controls...
a machine called Hysteric Wheel #1.
In the other corner...
With Megumi Morisato at the controls...
...a machine by the name
of Pot Shaker Dragon.
I've built a perfect robot! I wonder
if you can defeat my creation?
I'm impressed that you've built
a robot like that by yourself.
But I know that victory will be mine!
Ready... fight!
See that?
My Hysteric Wheel #1 was designed to...
...pulverize anything within its
spinning radius and then grab it!
She made that? I know she's my sister,
but that's terrifying.
And you two are so alike it's terrifying!
How can you be so relaxed?
What's going on here?
Don't you remember the last time?
It's true your robot has overwhelming
power, but it's not maneuverable enough!
Oh, no!
Megumi Morisato is on a tear,
collecting those cans!
Can she hang on for the win?
Okay, I'm just going to cruise to victory!
What are you doing, Skuld?
Take a closer look at the rules!
What?
"Interference during the
game is also welcome.''
Those are my kind of rules!
I see.
What an appalling rule!
Come on, both of you!
Your robot doesn't have
any offensive functions.
Just let me reduce you to scrap!
Oh!
Let's go!
Seniors! What happens in a case like
this?
Since she gobbled up Skuld's robot,
I'd have to say that means Megumi wins.
Hey, no fair!
There's nothing for you to latch onto
inside that drum... you can't destroy it!
No way, no way, no way!
This just isn't fair!
Okay, then! You asked for it!
A self-destruct device,
for crying out loud...
Wow, pretty wild, huh?
It'll be a lot of work,
cleaning up this mess.
Seniors! What happens in this case?
Tamiya and Ohtaki ran off! Get them!
It was a tie! Give us our money back!
I don't believe those two...
You did a good job.
Big Sister...
We're going to win next time, all right?
I want you to let me help, too.
Big Sister...
Now, I want you to make up with Megumi.
You built an awesome robot.
So did you...
Next time, let's build one together.
I bet it'll be a lot more fun that way.
Yeah, I think so too.
But...
Huh?
Skuld!
My robot was way more awesome than
yours!
Come back here!
What a little brat...
To think that's my own sister...
She's just like you.
What did you say?
Just how is she like me? Tell me how!
You know, in that way...
You'd better say we're not
alike right now! Say it!
Always believe in yourself and your
Dreams. You have a wing!
I love you so much it hurts...
And it hurts me that
I can't tell you how I feel.
You and I have matching hearts...
So we must share the
same scars deep down inside.
But now that I'm in your arms,
I think I can catch...
...your pounding heartbeat this time.
Nobody else matters...
All we have to do is gaze at each other.
It's all right for your heart to flutter...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
Don't run away from happiness.
I'll always be waiting for you.
So come rest your wings anytime.
It's all right to cry...
anytime you need to.
I just want to see you again...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
I just want you to be happy.
That which has been created...
it is called a ''Machine.''
A machine without a heart gains a
soul thanks to the goddess' love.
Next episode: Ah! When the Goddess
Steals Your Heart Away
How much is this thing's electric bill
gonna cost me every month?