Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather will come
fluttering down, swaying gently in the air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
Listen! This is a one-in-a-million chance,
so you've got to do your best.
If nothing comes of this,
I'll toss a thunderbolt at you!
Huh? But, wait...
I won't have it, I tell you! You lay
one finger on my Big Sister and...
...Banpei's coming after you
in Special Attack Mode!
Don't listen to her, she's a child.
Hey! Don't listen to a
wicked old hag like her!
Here...
Give it a read, and you'll
know exactly what to do.
No way! You can't do this!
How red you are! Do you even
understand what it's about?
You're such a...
Is something the matter?
Huh? No, it's nothing!
Since Skuld and I have to go back
to Heaven for about a week...
...to do maintenance work on Yggdrasil...
...we were just giving Keiichi some
pointers
about what he should look out for.
Right?
Really...these sisters
are totally in sync, huh?
Ah! If You're a Real Man,
Save the Goddess?
Sweet mattress...
sweet mattress...
Let's hang you in the sunshine...
let's hang you in the sunshine...
Just because we're alone together
doesn't mean anything's going to
change...
I mean, Belldandy isn't the type
of girl to get all self-conscious.
This thing and that thing only
happened because of the potion.
A whole week alone with her...
what are we supposed to do?
Actually, I mean...what should I do?
What is it?
Oh, um, nothing.
Sweet mattress, sweet mattress...
I guess I shouldn't worry about it.
Oh, man! Is this ever going to end?
Not if you don't stop
goofing off, it won't.
I wonder if everything's
going well with Keiichi?
I wouldn't bet on things
going the way you want, Urd!
But why not?
Because I fixed it so he won't
be able to get near Big Sister!
What do you mean?
How do you like Skuld's flan?
It's pretty good!
But I never would've thought Skuld
would be into making desserts!
She really wanted you to have it.
She insisted I serve it to you.
Here.
Thanks.
Darn that Skuld!
Hey, I'm not going to do anything.
Keiichi!
Hey, what's going on?
What the...
Don't tell me I've turned into a girl?
It looks like you have.
Looks like I have?
Still got it.
Thank God!
Hmm?
Dear Keiichi, You will remain a
member of that gender until I return.
That's what it says on this plate.
Oh, I see. So that's why
she made me eat her flan...
But from what I can see, it doesn't
seem to be doing any physical harm.
I think if you just stay that way,
it will wear off in about a week.
In a week?
What?
You mean I have to go
to class like this?
Um...would you like to come
with me to the ladies' room?
Oh, sounds good! But are you sure
you don't mind me coming along?
Of course not, Keiichi!
You're a woman, too.
That's right, so it wouldn't
be strange at all, would it?
Oh, good morning, Big Sister!
Morning, Megumi!
It's so nice out. Why don't we
all go to the public bath tonight?
Oh? Are you sure it's okay
for me to come along?
What are you talking about?
We're all girls here, aren't we?
But of course, you're right!
She's absolutely right!
You've got to be kidding me.
Is something the matter?
Isn't there any way you can
change me back right now?
Let me see...here it is!
It looks really bitter.
Don't worry, Keiichi. It's an ointment.
Ointment?
Would you please lift up your shirt?
If I rub it all over your chest area,
I think you'll go back to normal.
Rub it? You're not going
to do the rubbing, are you?
Yes. Is there a problem?
I think an oral medication
would be better.
You're right.
I know, I can just mix it up with...
With what?
We're going to pour in that liquid
and this seed at the same time.
Right.
Now then, I want you
to pour it in gently.
What's going on?
Belldandy?
Belldandy!
There was a virus in that liquid.
A virus?
Yes.
As an additive, it can have an extremely
potent effect, but if a goddess...
...like myself inhales such a
substance unblended, the effects are...
...just like that of a common cold...
Are you all right?
Sorry. It's all my fault.
Don't say that. I shouldn't
have been so careless.
Let's get you to a doctor right away.
No, the doctors here on Earth wouldn't
know
how to deal with a virus from Heaven.
I didn't inhale all that much.
So if I just get some sleep tonight,
I should make a quick recovery.
I see.
But there's still the matter
of your body, Keiichi...
Hey, don't worry about it.
I'll be fine, okay?
Since I'm like this, maybe
I'll try putting some makeup on.
It might be very becoming on you!
Do you think so?
Morisato!
Hey, Morisato! We came
over to hang out with you!
He might be out.
But she told me we should come over,
because he'd definitely be at home.
Who did?
Skuld.
Coming! Sorry to keep you waiting!
Welcome!
Keiko?
That's right. I'm a distant
cousin of Belldandy's, and...
...I'm a high school exchange student...
Do you know her?
Oh, boy.
Good thing I still had this
costume from that farewell bash.
She's hot.
Oh, and thank you for coming over,
but I'm sorry to have to tell you...
...that Mr. Morisato is
out at the moment...
He invites us over and then
goes out? That's really rude!
Are Belldandy and the others around?
Well, Skuld and Urd are
away on a trip, and...
But Belldandy's here, right?
Then it's fine by me. We're coming in.
Please wait a minute! The thing is,
Belldandy is still asleep, and...
Oh, so you're all here.
Belldandy...
And you really did try on some makeup!
No, see...uh...
Anyway, there it is. So won't you
please come in, everyone?
Thanks, we will!
Are you all right?
Yes. I do still have a little cough...
Belldandy's a babe, but
that little Keiko gal...
Yeah, she's an angel.
She's got a great figure too.
It makes me feel so inadequate just
seeing them stand there side by side.
I know I've seen her somewhere...
I'm going to go make
some tea, all right?
Oh boy...now what do I do?
Uh, do you mind?
Belldandy's not her usual self,
don't you think?
Now that you mention it, she seemed
a little unsteady on her feet.
Belldandy!
She's been sick since last night?
Yes.
We'd better call for an ambulance.
You're right.
No, that's all right!
Belldandy said she didn't want
to make a big deal out of this...
But...
Why would she say that?
Uh, because we don't have any money!
That's why, you see!
Money?
Use this money!
If you pool all our money, there should
be enough for Belldandy to see a doctor.
Guys...
Thanks a lot.
But if anyone's gonna take
care of Belldandy, I'm the guy.
Guy?
Senior!
''Senior''?
Megumi! Hasegawa! Thank you.
It makes me feel good to know
how much you care.
''Megumi''?
''Hasegawa''?
Hasegawa, when's your
next mechanical test again?
Actually, I can't say until I know
when the repairs will be done.
I ordered the parts the day before
yesterday, so you can get started...
...as soon as they're delivered...whoops!
No, what I mean is...um...
Look, you!
Ouch! Ouch!
What's up with this? It's not a wig...
Anyway, tell Belldandy we all
said to get well soon, okay?
But...
Do you really think we should...
Well, Keiko's being so adamant
about it. We can leave it to her.
Kei-chan, I'm pretty sure this whole
drag thing has something to do with...
...Belldandy's illness...
but this is your chance!
I mean, because now you can do
something for Belldandy!
Okay, then, good luck...Kei-chan!
Let's go somewhere else!
What does this say, anyway?
Star...Rabbit...Spear.
Damn, which one of these
is real medicine?
Maybe if I go into Skuld's room
I'll find a machine that will clue me in.
Oh...please excuse me.
It's been a whole night, but
she's nowhere near better yet...
The medicine we have on Earth
wouldn't work on a goddess.
No matter how hard I try,
I can't do anything for her...
Belldandy never shows how
she might be suffering inside...
...so if this is making her so sick,
it's got to be really serious.
I don't have any choice but to talk
to Urd and Skuld directly in Heaven.
It might have been an accident,
but my call did go through once.
I should have a chance, at least!
Hello, you've reached the
Tokyo Broadcasting System.
I'm sorry, wrong number.
I'm not going to give up!
This is After 5 Magazine.
This is Gentle Entertainment.
This is Bandai Visual.
Tanaka speaking.
I'm sorry, wrong number.
At the tone...
The time will be 7:38 PM.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
No good...
Hello?
This is the Goddess Eye Clinic.
Goddess?
Thanks, but we're not interested.
I'm sorry, Belldandy.
I can't do anything for you.
Not anything!
Deep down, I was sure
it would somehow work out.
That if I really cared...that as long
as I had faith...it would work out...
That as long as I had feelings for you,
you would stay by my side forever...
...that we'd be all right...
...that as long as I believed...
everything would turn out right.
But...
But that's not enough...
No, that's not true.
Because it all begins with the heart...
Because it all begins
when you believe...
Belldandy!
Right now, I feel so at peace with myself.
Because I know how much
you care, Keiichi...
Because I know in your heart you
believe!
Belldandy!
Holy Bell...
Right now, I feel so at peace with myself.
Because I know how much
you care, Keiichi...
Because I know in your heart you
believe!
She's right.
If I'm going to believe, then I have to
believe in any miracle or coincidence.
My call is going to go
through no matter what.
Belldandy will recover, no matter what!
Hello, you've reached
the Goddess Help Line.
Urd? Urd!
Keiichi? What's going on?
It's Belldandy...she's in trouble!
I don't know how you
got through to us here.
So? What do you mean, trouble?
What happened?
All right! Finished! I'm going back now!
What did you say?
It sounds like she's definitely
taking a turn for the worse.
Unless we do something now,
her body will be destroyed.
No way...what should I do?
Listen carefully to
what I'm about to say.
We're going to need some wind crystals
to concoct medicine for her.
Wind crystals?
Got it.
So I should have those ready for you
by the time you get back, right?
I'm on it!
Who was that on the phone?
I'm going back to Earth.
Huh? But wait, you're not done
with your work yet, are you?
If you walk off the job,
you'll be severely punished!
I'm doing it for my sister, and besides...
...I'm not afraid of
severe punishment anymore!
Sister?
Wait, don't tell me
that was Keiichi on the phone?
What's happened to Big Sister?
Hey, wait for me!
Belldandy...just hold on.
I'm going to save you right now.
Take that to the highest place
you can and hold it up to a fresh breeze.
That way, you'll be able to
catch the crystals.
The highest place I can...
There it is!
I love being up in high places.
Is that right?
Because it looks like everyone
in the world is groveling at my feet!
Okay, this is a good spot...
Wind crystals!
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
You can't come up here,
it's off-limits!
Well...no...
What are you going to use that for?
Come over here, it's dangerous!
Now then, a toast.
All right.
This is the highest spot
around here, isn't it?
Uh, yes, actually...
Keiichi! Where are you?
You mean that Keiichi?
There's another level up there!
Keiichi, are you here?
Skuld!
Do you have the wind crystals?
Yeah, I've got them, but...
Hey, what's a kid like you doing here?
Keiichi, you've got to jump!
Huh? But...
Just do it!
If you don't hurry up, you won't
be able to save Big Sister!
You've got to trust me!
Belldandy...
Shall we start over, then...
Keiichi?
Banpei! Activate System Catcher Mode!
This should do it.
Come on, Belldandy.
Big Sister!
We'll have to give it
to her mouth-to-mouth...
Keiichi, you do it.
Huh?
To tell you the truth, I was surprised.
You're the only one who's ever been able
to call Heaven and make the connection.
Is that right?
I can see you really do
care about Belldandy.
All right, hurry!
You can't let him do that!
Not to my Big Sister...
Skuld...
Just this one time, got that?
Belldandy...
What's this?
I...
Belldandy...
What's going on?
You have Keiichi to thank.
Keiichi?
Hey, Keiichi! How dare you put your
mouth against Big Sister's lips!
Oh well, since it made Big Sister better,
I guess I'll let it go.
Wait a minute...
aren't those bigger than mine?
These are at least 10 times
as big as somebody's!
What did you say?
I've got some decent...
What's this?
All I said was ''Somebody''...
Darn you! I hate you, Urd!
Just look at how red your face is!
You want me to make them bigger for
you?
If I leave it to you, I'll get a set
of vulgar, sagging breasts like yours!
What did you just say?
Thank you, Keiichi...
If you're jealous, then be honest
and admit you're jealous!
I am not jealous!
Always believe in yourself and
your Dreams. You have a wing!
I love you so much it hurts...
And it hurts me that
I can't tell you how I feel.
You and I have matching hearts...
So we must share the
same scars deep down inside.
But now that I'm in your arms,
I think I can catch...
...your pounding heartbeat this time.
Nobody else matters...
All we have to do is gaze at each other.
It's all right for your heart to flutter...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
Don't run away from happiness.
I'll always be waiting for you.
So come rest your wings anytime.
It's all right to cry...
anytime you need to.
I just want to see you again...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
I just want you to be happy.
Angels are the reflections of
a goddess's soul...her other self.
The struggles of Urd's little sister
remind her of her younger self.
Next episode: Ah! What Wouldn't I
Give for an Angel With White Wings?!
In other words, hard work is
the key for goddesses and humans.