Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather comes fluttering
down, swaying gently in the air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
Oh, I didn't get a wink
of sleep last night.
You can't sleep?
No...
When I think that you and I
are going to share...
...as many wonderful moments as there
are stars in the sky, I get so excited!
Hey, by the way, whenever
we can't sleep, we count sheep...
Did you know that?
So you do have mysterious spells
here on Earth as well!
I don't know if you'd call it
a spell, but maybe it is.
All right, why don't we
count sheep together!
Sure, then I'll start.
1 sheep.
2 sheep.
3 sheep.
4 sheep.
15 sheep.
16 sheep.
17 sheep.
Aren't you getting sleepy yet?
593 sheep!
594 sheep.
We'll have counted as many sheep as
there are stars in the sky by morning!
Probably...
Now then, let's keep going.
595 sheep.
596 sheep.
597 sheep.
598 sheep...
Man, to think that we're going to
start living together under one roof...
I wonder if I can keep up with her.
Is something wrong?
Sighing so early in the morning!
Good morning!
Keiichi!
Good morning.
Ah! Apprenticeship, Home, and the
Goddess
Since there's two of us, I want to get
a place with at least two rooms.
But I'll have to find something
that costs the same as my dorm room.
I don't want to go through the hassle
of explaining things to my folks.
I'll have to come up with the
deficit by doing extra work...
...and I'll try to get the
best deal that I can.
It's hard to get along in this world
without money.
I guess so. You can't pay rent or eat...
The fact is, without money,
you'll never get anywhere.
I see.
Then how about a little spell?
Spell?
Here is a wandering soul.
If you can hear my voice, provide
this soul with the Light of Life...
...with the sustenance he needs to live.
Big Brother!
Huh?
It's that little girl...
I can't thank you enough
for helping Hijiri yesterday.
Oh, don't mention it.
Thank you for treating us to lunch.
Hijiri, thank him properly, now.
Hey, Big Sister,
are you Big Brother's wife?
I'm so sorry!
Look, he's turning red!
He's turning red!
I am not his wife, but a godd...
God?
God, those glasses are so becoming!
Well...
You can't say things like that in public!
I cannot say such things?
My, how sweet that you two are so
close.
You know what? I've never seen anyone
wearing such frilly, flowing clothes...
...as you before!
Are they strange?
Not many people dress like that in this
country. Maybe you stand out a little...
Really?
All right, then...
B-Big Sister!
Is this better, then?
Big Brother!
You can't use magic in public like that...
Don't worry.
I can only use that kind of power
several times a day.
If people find out that
you have special powers...
...there's going to be a huge uproar.
And if that happens, we might not
be able to stay together anymore.
If that should come to pass...
...the System Force will take effect,
and there could be chaos.
Right, so I guess you're going to have
to learn all about living in this world.
Yes, apparently so.
Let's try and make this work somehow!
All right!
First of all, we've got to find
a new place to live. Let's go!
Okay!
Uh, we're looking for a
place for the two of us.
What kind of place do you have in
mind?
A place with a kitchen and two rooms
with its own bath and toilet if possible...
...and a parking spot for my motorcycle
for 15,000 yen a month or less!
I know I'm asking for the impossible,
but I thought I'd ask you to try anyway.
We do not have it!
Oh, man...
Reality is as tough as I thought.
A lot of hardship goes into leading
one's life here on Earth, I see...
Yeah, but everyone
goes through hardship.
That's why people work hard everyday.
Work hard, did you say?
If you're doing what you love, working
hard won't seem like such an effort.
Take me, for instance. If it's to fulfill my
dream of building my own bike...
...I can work hard for it.
I find that very appealing, Keiichi!
But the reality is that
everything takes money!
Right now this is my entire fortune.
So we have to find a place to live with
the help of that ''money'', is that right?
Yeah.
Then let me ask the Holy Spirit if there
is a place for the two of us to live.
Can you do something like that?
We are two wandering souls...
two souls who seek a safe abode.
O Spirit of the 2,000-Yen Bill,
bearing all the hopes of this man...
Reveal to us now the path
you would have us take!
Oh, crap! My entire fortune!
Let's go after it!
All right!
If we don't find it, having no place to live
will just be the start of our problems!
Keiichi!
Ah!
My 2,000-yen bill!
Tariki Hongan Temple
Huh?
Jeez, I came this close to
losing my entire fortune!
Still, I never knew
there was a temple here.
There are no evil spirits here.
It's quite a lovely place!
At any rate, I'd better take back my...
Take that!
No!
Keiichi!
M-My entire fortune...
Huh?
Last I remember, I got totally clobbered
over the head by somebody...
You're going to be fine, Keiichi.
No way...
The whole time I was sleeping,
my head was on Belldandy's lap?
Are you still in pain?
No, no, I'm okay now.
So you woke up.
Oshou!
I'm terribly sorry for what I did.
I mistook you for a thief
going after the offerings.
Even given my habit of jumping to
conclusions, it was a serious mistake!
Oh, no, I should apologize. What I did
was totally misleading! I'm sorry.
Don't give it another thought.
Oh, and...
As for this...
Let me return this money to you.
That's the least I can do.
Uh, could you let us pay for a night's
lodging here with that money?
We don't have a place to live,
and we have nowhere to go.
If 2,000 yen isn't enough, I'll do
whatever I can to make it up to you.
Please, sir!
That money is your payment for helping
me take care of this temple today.
Your food and lodging for tonight
will be provided separately.
You're going to enjoy working here.
Get yourselves ready at once!
Yes, sir! Thank you so much!
Make sure you get every
last inch of the floor!
Use your back muscles, already!
It's not that simple!
Take that!
Ow!
You need to follow the girl's example!
Huh?
Ow!
All right, take another lap!
Right!
The image of Buddha is any
temple's greatest treasure.
When you've poured
your entire heart into...
...its polishing, then it is
a true apprenticeship.
I can see everything begin to
gleam as I polish, more and more.
It's just like
I'm cleansing my own soul.
But what's this?
What is the matter?
Oh, uh... it's nothing.
That Oshou is one violent guy...
I'm sure he means no harm by it.
How are we gonna get
this temple tidied up?
The lawn's overgrown with weeds. It'll
be a major hassle pulling them out!
But if we do it together,
we'll have fun with it!
Sure, let's just hope we have fun...
Keiichi!
My name is Belldandy...
I call forth to thee in the name
of the autumn leaves. Heed my voice!
Deliver that man into safety!
Keiichi, are you all right?
Was that you... just now?
Yes, but I've broken my promise to you.
I used magic.
But you didn't have a
choice this time, right?
Besides, you saved me even though
it meant breaking your promise...
...that makes me happy.
Thanks, Belldandy.
Keiichi!
Hey, look, we better
fix that roof right away!
I suppose so!
That skill of hers...
That woman...
Who in the world is she?
I was sure she'd show her true self
at night if she were a specter...
However, I can't let my guard down.
I've got to keep watch all night.
Well, well...
Reveal yourself, Holy Bell!
Now then, let us sing together!
Restore this desolate land
to its former glory!
What! Don't tell me...
Blunder!
Where on earth is
this voice coming from?
Thank you, Holy Bell!
I don't measure up!
That guardian angel, that beautiful voice
that could capture anyone's heart...
Everything she does transcends the
level of enlightenment I have attained.
I still have a long, long way to go...
This time I got a good night's sleep!
Keiichi!
It's the Oshou!
Huh?
My Tariki Hongan Temple,
I bid you farewell for a short time.
Oshou!
Where are you going?
I still have a lot of
training ahead of me.
I must go on a nationwide pilgrimage
so that I can reach full enlightenment!
Please send me off with a smile!
But why, all of a sudden?
I was made painfully aware
of my own inexperience.
I must aspire to be like Belldandy...
...to one day have the ability to
send others to heaven by singing in...
...a glorious voice along
with a guardian angel!
Guardian angel?
Until that time, I am leaving
this temple in your hands.
Farewell!
What did he mean by guardian angel?
I think he must be referring to this...
Whoa! What's that?
Her name is Holy Bell.
She protects me, and is always
with me. She's my higher self.
So it was the Oshou jumping
to conclusions again, huh?
Still, thanks to the Oshou's kindness,
we now have a place to live, don't we?
I should fix that hole in the roof...
But isn't that one more thing
to look forward to, Keiichi?
Morisato Ya
I guess we'll have to
borrow the Oshou's stuff...
...until I bring over the stuff
I left at the dorm.
Yes.
I'm getting paid tomorrow, so that'll take
care of whatever else we need, but...
...we shouldn't waste money.
Yes, that's right.
Uh, I think I've put you
through a lot of trouble.
Oh, no. Since we're going through
it together, I'm enjoying it!
Oh...
What's up?
Look...
You know, if we had pretty cups
like these to drink our tea out of...
...it would taste delicious, wouldn't it?
You like tea, huh?
Yes.
Thanks!
Keiichi?
A moment ago you said we shouldn't
waste money, but you just did anyway.
It's just my way of thanking
you for saving me yesterday.
But isn't it strange? We went shopping,
yet we still have money left over.
Well, since we have more money,
we should've bought some tea, too.
And a tea service, too.
When we do, I'll make
delicious tea everyday!
That'll be great!
One day when I woke up...
A day like any other...
another one just beginning.
There you are, yawning...
your face is still so sleepy.
Because each peaceful day
we share is a miracle to me.
This is where my heart
will always return...
Forever...
There's only one thing I wish for.
I chase after the same dream,
wherever it may go.
The love I feel for you
gives me strength.
May tomorrow be as joyful as today...
That's my wish...
The Queen, one who reigns at the
highest level of the universe...
...leading the way with
her beauty and power.
The sparks are sure to fly
when these two meet.
Next episode:
Ah! The Queen and the Goddess!
Do you really have to come to blows
over this ''Campus Queen'' title?