Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather will come
fluttering down, swaying gently in the air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
Who are you?
Who am I?
I come bearing your doom!
That sure was an ominous dream...
This pulse...
It can't be...
Ah! The Demon Arrives and Wreaks
Havoc?!
What's the matter?
Nothing...what about you, Keiichi?
Didn't you get enough sleep?
Oh, well, I had a bad dream.
Aha! I bet you dreamed that you
got dumped by Belldandy, am I right?
I did not!
Please, Urd!
Now that's what I call a good luster...
Ah! You have a skilled eye.
That one just came in yesterday...
it's an import.
What's this?
A DEMON! A DEMON!
YOU WILL BECOME A DEMON!
What's up? Did you spot
a great bargain or something?
What is this...
What's going on, Den-chan?
A CD? What the heck
are we gonna do with a CD...
It's good...
Yes. It's good....
We'll take this.
I don't remember stocking
anything like that...
Huh? What's up with this?
Why would I have something like this?
Didn't you want to listen to it?
But... we don't have a CD player, anyway.
Well, maybe we should start by
coloring it black, just like a record?
Hey, good idea.
Where does the needle go?
Are you sure it's okay
to spin it at 45 RPM?
What the hell?
Damn those gods...putting
extra protection on the seal!
And who would stick a CD on a
freakin' record player, anyway?
What kind of a place is this?
Who the hell are you?
You want to know?
I am Marller,
Demon First Class, Unlimited!
And since you did release me
from that claustrophobic CD...
...I'll grant you a wish.
Spit it out, now!
Hey! What's the big idea?
How dare you intrude upon our sanctuary
without removing your shoes!
Just get the hell out of here!
Is that all you're going to ask me for?
I can't believe your lack of greed!
Your wish is granted!
Disappeared!
I wonder what that was all about.
It was probably a newbie from
the shop, trying to drum up sales.
What should we do with this?
Good question...
Damn, I left it behind...
But the thing is...
I don't ever want to set foot
in a place like that again.
No, right now my priority
is to settle that old score!
Just you wait, goddesses!
I'll get my revenge
if it's the last thing I do!
Gotcha!
You wish!
KO
She beat me again!
Isn't there anyone better out there?
Okay, then I'm next!
No, let me take her on!
Just get in line. You'll all get
your chance with me, so bring it on!
Right?
Belldandy?
What's wrong?
Keiichi! Let's go home right now!
Huh?
Disaster is headed for us...
I can feel it!
Urd?
You're history!
Really!
What's the matter?
O Blue Stone that wards off
evil and repulses demons...
I beseech you, protect us
with your white robe.
Barrier shield!
You'll be safe now.
Will you tell me what's going on here?
Earlier, I felt a certain pulse...
I believe a demon will be coming...
A demon?
Yes.
We goddesses serve the Almighty and
wish for the happiness of all humans...
...whereas demons, also known as devils,
lead them into corruption.
So one of those is coming?
Not only that, but I remember
this particular pulse...
With Urd's help, I sealed a demon
on the Almighty's orders...
...it's just like the pulse of that demon!
Excuse me! Registered mail!
Oh...I'll go answer that, all right?
Uh...
Keiichi, you mustn't
leave the barrier field.
Demons, huh?
Sounds like it's a lot more
than just plain hostility...
Right on the money!
Belldandy and I have
a complex relationship...
...impenetrable to the likes of you!
Who are you to talk to me
like that, you tanuki!
So you've forgotten my voice, have you?
You're from my... you were in my dream!
That's right. I am Marller,
Demon First Class, Unlimited.
Don't you ever forget it, either.
Excuse me!
Sorry to keep you waiting...
Hmm?
Registered mail... I need you
to sign for it, please.
But this is a demon's messenger!
I see Belldandy's as gullible as ever.
Now then, what am I going to do with
you?
What did I ever do to upset you?
Look, you... do you have any idea of the
trouble you're causing?
What?
Normally, it wouldn't be possible
to bind a goddess to Earth.
And you've got two of them!
In Urd's case,
it's not that I asked her to...
Shut up! Stop making excuses!
When goddesses loiter around on Earth,
the absolute quantity of joy swells.
If that happens, I'll lose my job!
There's way too much happiness
concentrated around you.
To put it bluntly, you're an eyesore!
Therefore, you'll have to
pay for this with your body.
But how is that fair?
If something were to happen to you...
...I'm sure it would bring those
blasted goddesses to their senses!
Cut it out! You demon! You devil!
That's exactly right. I am a devil!
Now I'll be free to focus on
my job without any distractions!
Marller!
You let your guard down because of
that barrier field, huh, Belldandy?
But how...
I snuck inside before
you threw up the barrier.
Thanks to you, I was able to
accomplish my job safely inside it.
What have you done to Keiichi?
You haven't figured that out?
He's right here.
Keiichi! How could you?
Please forgive me!
My powers came up short...
...and so you were turned
into this dreadful form...
No, not that. Over here!
You will change Keiichi back at once!
I'm ordering you as a first-class goddess!
I'm afraid I can't oblige you.
After all, it's our job as demons
to get in the way of you goddesses.
Be gentle when you
ride him, all right?
Come back here! Wait!
Marller?
I'm home...
I just saw Marller back there...
Urd!
Keiichi?
So that's the story...
Well, that Marller always
had an evil nature, remember?
Of course, that's probably
why she's a devil!
Anyway, you sure got your butt kicked.
But hey, being a bike once in a while
isn't so bad. You love bikes, don't you?
Urd!
Oh... hey, my bad.
Even so, it would be inconvenient
for him to stay this way, wouldn't it?
Don't worry, I promise I'll change
you back to your original form.
Looks like it's time for me
to show my stuff!
Now then, drink this and you'll be
rid of any curse under the sun!
Urd-Ade Super-Z!
But how can we get him to drink that?
Through here!
Now, drink up if you know
what's good for you...
Keiichi! You must calm down!
Oh dear...
Looks like it only works on humans....
Let me give it a try this time.
Guide this man back to his original
form...
To break a devil's curse, I guess
we're going to need the password.
But if we can keep chipping
away at it like this...
There!
Isn't it getting worse?
No, no, not at all...Take that!
I don't think it'll do any good
to give him an extra wheel.
No way out of it...Take that!
Sorry about that.
Never mind... one way or another,
we're going to have to get...
...the password to return
him to his original form.
Our only hope is to get Marller to break
the curse and turn him back herself.
But do you really think that
demon's going to just do as we ask?
Do you suppose Marller's angry
at us for sealing her?
Oh come on, we did that
because she broke the rules!
Still, Marller's the type
who never forgets a grudge.
But how do you suppose
the seal was breached?
Wait a minute! That's it!
The catalyst the Almighty
used to seal Marller...
I'll bet it's around here somewhere!
If we can just get our hands on it, then
she'll have no choice but to do as we say.
Keiichi!
The Eye of Heaven, the Eye of the Earth...
and the Eye of Water...
Reveal to us the location
of the demon's catalyst.
What the heck is this?
Huh? Keiichi, you know what this
means?
All right, then,
let's split up and look for it.
I'm going after the catalyst.
Belldandy, you try to hunt down Marller.
All right.
We'll return you to your original form...
we promise, Keiichi!
Okay, you're coming with me.
Excuse me, but I'm looking for someone.
A person dressed like this...
Thank you very much!
Put on a Helmet. Save a Life.
You're telling me to
put this on, is that it?
All right, all right,
I heard you the first time!
I can feel it...
What's that?
Over there?
I get it!
Women are not allowed to enter
this dorm! How many times do we...
Oh, don't be such a stiff!
Listen, guys, did you happen
to buy a strange-looking CD?
A CD...you think she's
talking about that one?
Oh, that thing?
We unloaded that CD on a
second-hand store ages ago!
Which store was that?
You'd better tell me, or I'll give you
the punishment of your life.
The used-record store
over on Third Street!
Oh? Really?
Thanks, boys!
What the hell was that about?
We'd better add a new dorm rule...
''no riding bikes indoors.''
I'll borrow some of that stuff
over there, all right?
Hey, let me have some, too!
No way! It's your own fault
for dropping yours, Junpei!
But you made me drop it, Hijiri!
I didn't!
I wish you'd just drop yours too, Hijiri!
Huh?
I'd be happy to grant you that wish.
Well? Human misery is a
joy to behold, is it not?
You feel the same way I'm feeling, aren't
you?
Ouch!
I do you a favor by granting your wish,
and that's the thanks I get?
Unbelievable...
This pulse...
It's Belldandy!
Found it!
This is all we need to...
Ma'am...
What?
Your money!
Keiichi, we need money.
Marller, please turn Keiichi
back to his original form.
You actually think I'm just
going to submit to your orders?
Surely not the orders of a goddess who
sealed me in such a horrible catalyst!
About that...
Why would someone like a goddess
attach herself to a lowly human?
Because I have a contract with Keiichi!
You can terminate a contract
with a human any time!
That's not true! Because I'm
staying here out of my own free will!
In that case, I have no choice
but to carry out my own duty!
I understand your feelings for Keiichi.
Basically, it's Keiichi's very existence
that's binding you to Earth.
So why don't I just
erase Keiichi completely?
If that happens, then you'll...
Marller, don't you dare go any further.
Oh? Then do you want to fight?
Wow, look at the special effects!
It's just like a movie!
Get a move on, now, Keiichi! Power up!
What's the matter?
Is that the best you can do as a goddess?
Don't tell me you're weaker
now than you were before?
I get it, so that's what's stopping
you from releasing your true power!
It must be inconvenient to be a goddess!
Please! Just do as I say and
turn Keiichi back! Or else I'll...
You still have the nerve to talk like that?
I'm sure you've reached your limit by
now.
If you break your contract and
go back to Heaven, I might forgive you!
I'll never do such a thing!
Marller, catch!
Urd!
As I recall, you've always been vulnerable
to good-luck charms, haven't you?
Here, we found it.
But that's the Almighty's CD!
That's right. The Almighty's catalyst...
paired with the Demon's catalyst.
It's what we use to seal away
demons who have sinned!
Marller!
Wait a minute! Stop!
Please, don't do this to me again!
Then please give us the password that
will return Keiichi to his original form!
Why? What makes you care about him
so much? He's nothing but a human!
Because Keiichi is... because Keiichi is...
...someone very important to me!
All right, I'll give it to you.
I'll give you the damned password,
so back off!
Guide this man back to his original
form... Ado Solia Helestia.
I'm sorry, I'll get you some clothes!
Sorry, Belldandy!
Is this all right?
You saved me!
Welcome.
Dammit...
Unless I get that catalyst back,
I don't stand a chance against them!
I've got to do something...
Really, now!
It's all Belldandy's fault.
Hey, are you listening?
Isn't this outrageous?
How can I be second-best?
I'd rather sell my soul to the devil
than come off second-best to that girl!
Did she say Belldandy?
One day when I woke up...
A day like any other...
another one just beginning.
There you are, yawning...
your face is still so sleepy.
Because each peaceful day
we share is a miracle to me.
This is where my heart
will always return...
Forever...
There's only one thing I wish for.
I chase after the same dream,
wherever it may go.
The love I feel for you
gives me strength.
May tomorrow be as joyful as today...
That's my wish...
The queen's slumber is rudely
disturbed by a demon's snore.
When these two meet in bed, it creates
a rift between the man and his goddess.
Next episode: Ah! Choosing Between
the Goddess and the Queen?
No, it's you I want by my side forever!