Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather comes fluttering
down, swaying gently in the air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
Good morning!
Is something wrong?
Uh, no.
It's just hard for me
to believe, you know?
A girl like you
making breakfast for me...
Oh, never mind, it's nothing.
Thanks for breakfast!
How is it?
Mmm! It's delicious!
Oh, really? I'm so glad!
Huh? Time to go already?
Are you going out now?
Yeah, I'll be at the university.
I've got to be there first period today.
University? Would that be the
place we visited the other day?
Yeah, that's right.
Would it be all right if I came along?
Huh? Well, but you see...
No?
That's not what I meant...
So I can come along!
Will you accept these?
Are you free this Saturday?
I'm sorry.
I've been invited to a yacht party
that day with my father.
Miss Sayoko! I managed to get tickets
for that concert you wanted to see!
Oh, thanks.
This is to prove my sincerity to you!
Hey, don't push!
What's that?
Not Sayoko again!
Her dad's the CEO of some hotshot
company, and she's so good-looking.
No one can compete with that!
No girl in this school stands
a chance against Sayoko...
Hey! Look over there!
Who's she?
The other day, I promised to take you
on a tour of the campus, didn't I?
Oh, my! I had no idea there'd
be so many people around!
It's not that I mind
being with Belldandy...
...but a girl this cute is sure
to attract a lot of attention.
After all, she is a goddess.
Who is that girl? I don't
remember seeing her before.
She's hot, huh?
I think I'll make a pass at her!
How interesting!
She's daring to mount a
challenge against me, eh?
Ah! The Queen and the Goddess
Wow, she's really cute.
Oh, jeez...
I just don't know what to
make of everyone around here.
Something might be about to
happen to you, Keiichi!
If something happens, it'll be to you.
We're just on a walk, and now this.
What is going to happen later?
Morisato!
How've you been doing, kid?
The seniors!
By the way, Miss...
Your address and your number?
Why are you asking for her address?
Idiot!
We'll send over the stuff you left
at the dorm to your new place.
Oh, I see.
Does that mean they're
shacking up together?
Who the hell knew?
The question is, why would
she go out with such a loser?
Sweetheart! You better jump ship to
someone who's actually worthy of you!
Don't break your parents' hearts!
What do they mean by
''shacking up together''?
Huh?
Oh, well, it's like when a
guy and a girl live together...
Here on Earth, do parents grieve
when a man and woman live together?
No, but living together kind of means
you're involved in a lot of ways...
Involved in a lot of ways?
Hey, no, not in that way exactly, but...
Never mind that.
Let's take you on a campus tour.
Come on, let's go!
Hey!
Morisato! I just remembered
I have an errand for you.
I need you to bring me
something from the club room.
Can't you...
On the double!
Yes!
S-Senior?
Yo. Den-chan?
Don't tell me this was caused by...
...the System Force.
You mean that thing that reacts
when something tries to separate us?
Yes.
I see. I hope it doesn't turn into
a huge headache for us.
Humph! Just you wait.
You'll learn about many things here.
Except this isn't really the class
I'm supposed to be taking right now...
No problem, I'm in this class.
Well, the last thing we need is for
the System Force to kick in again.
I have no choice.
Excuse me?
I'm sorry, but
would you mind moving?
That's my seat.
Oh, is that so?
But they never said anything
about assigned seats...
Never mind. I'll move to that side.
Just a minute.
I'm talking to you.
If you give up your seat, then
you'll be admitting defeat.
And if you refuse, everyone
will think you're a little bitch.
I've got you in a no-win situation!
You're quite right.
In that case, let's do this.
For real?
Yes.
Is there a problem?
She's no slouch...
She handled the situation without
sullying her reputation with the guys...
...and she slipped in a sarcastic remark!
Well, it seems we have
a full house today!
Excuse me, miss!
I haven't seen you here before.
Tell me your name!
Certainly. My name is Belldandy.
Belldandy?
She's an exchange student! She doesn't
understand Japanese that well yet...
Right? Right?
Absolutely!
Well, she must be if everyone says so.
Let's get this class underway.
So that's her story!
It should be a piece of cake, then.
Just you wait.
I'll never let you take the
title of Campus Queen from me.
That cat is the master of our school.
Really? Is that true?
What? What is it?
Is she a friend of yours?
Uh, yes.
This is Belldandy, an exchange student.
Belldandy?
Yes. I'm pleased to make
your acquaintance.
Ah...
Hey! Morisato!
Bad news, man!
The Dean!
Huh? You're the Dean?
Morisato, come with me!
Hey, what are you doing?
Keiichi?
Just come already! This is big!
There's no time to lose!
So what is the problem?
Professor Osawa heard about
Belldandy and he's investigating her.
You know, Professor Osawa,
who's always competing with Kakuta!
He heard some rumor about Kakuta...
...boosting his attendance by
planting a fake exchange student.
What are we going to do?
Unnecessary question.
We're going to hack into
the Student Affairs file server.
Can we do that?
Just hurry up and log into
the Student Affairs server!
The password's taped up
right there, see?
Log In Failed
A wrong password...
What the hell? They frickin'
changed it on us, did they?
You're going to get in
through sheer willpower!
Yeah, easier said than done!
How about this?
Man, that's not it either.
Keiichi...
Whosoever stands in our way,
I bid you, open the door for us now!
Provide us with the key
that will open that door!
Huh?
The password?
Great! We're in!
Rewrite the records!
Hah! Just as I thought,
no such exchange student exists.
What?
What on earth... She really
is an exchange student here?
Impossible!
I'm going to keep digging
until I find the truth!
He doesn't quit, does he?
Let's make the next move.
I feel so bad about all the trouble.
Why don't we just put an end to it?
Out of the question!
Now that it's come to this,
it is our duty to protect you!
Right.
I have a feeling it's more out of
a sense of mischief than of duty.
I can't get it open!
I will not be thwarted!
Dammit!
Now then, they must be ready
to expel that girl by now...
Was it all right to let them do that?
Um...
Don't tell me...
What...
Ugh, who gives a damn anymore?
No way...
Who knew that girl had it
in her to go this far?
Never mind. In that case I'll be
happy to take you on in person!
Since my junior high and high school
days, I've been called ''the Queen''.
Why don't I show you
how terrible my wrath can be?
Really? You don't say!
Come to think of it, I wonder
what's going on with Miss Mishima.
Sorry, but I'm not into
old-fogey stuff like that.
Something on your mind?
No, it's nothing important, really.
You were remembering
something that made you sad.
No need to worry.
Those who are well-acquainted with
grief will be visited by much happiness.
Belldandy...
Well now, I didn't think
I'd find you here.
Miss Mishima!
Professor Osawa was looking for you.
You'd better go see him right away.
All right.
Then I'll be right back.
I'll go with you.
Wait.
I have something to talk
to you about. Do you mind?
Huh?
You don't have to worry about me.
I'll be right back.
Um...
I know it might seem a little strange
to ask you this out of the blue, but...
Are you going out with her?
Not exactly going with her, but...
How can I explain...
So you're not seeing her, right?
Tell me you're not!
I'm so relieved!
There's that look!
That's it. No man has ever been
able to resist this tactic before!
That girl will be...
Sorry, but this is the girl
I've decided to go out with.
But wait, Keiichi!
Keiichi!
I'll humiliate her to the point where she
can never show her face here again!
Uh...
I'm so sorry!
You see, I've sort of had
my eye on you all this time...
Huh? But...
I mean, you know how you're always
tinkering with that bike of yours?
Uh, yeah...
My father used to work in a factory,
you see. So whenever...
...I see someone like that,
it just sets my heart on fire!
For real?
Listen...
Do you not like me?
Well, the thing is...
So you don't like me?
No, it's not that at all, but...
Of course, if you're any kind of man
that's exactly what you'd say!
Sorry! I didn't know
anybody was down there.
I knew the System Force
would kick in at some point...
Please.
Thank you very much.
I was hoping I'd get the
chance to talk to you.
How do you like our college?
There's such a mixture of various
emotions. I'm enjoying myself.
And there's a sweet little cat, too!
I see...
Are you all right?
Thank you.
You're so kind.
I don't think you should do that...
Why?
Because, uh...
How did it come to this?
Excuse me?
Professor Osawa was
actually taking a break.
Well... so? Are you calling me a liar?
No, that's not what I meant.
It's just that...
Why don't you show your true colors?
He's not around.
I know you're in a snit because
I made a pass at your guy!
In a snit? Are you angry?
Not me... you!
I'm sorry, I just don't get
the drift of what you're saying...
Man, you're so annoying!
Who in the world are you, anyway?
Coming to Nekomi Tech all of a sudden!
I am a goddess.
Well, listen to you!
You may be a goddess, but I'm
a Queen! You'll never defeat me!
You're a Queen? Queen of which
country?
Oh, never mind!
Just watch! I'll win over that runt, and
leave you to drown in your own tears!
Did I... did I do something to upset her?
Jeez, we had a long day, didn't we?
Do you think so?
I rather enjoyed myself!
You did? Well, in that case,
I guess it's all right.
All right, get in! I'll drive you home.
Oh, but...
I said get in the car!
But...
The System Force only reacts when
something tries to pull us apart...
...so if she's just giving you a ride home,
I'm sure there won't be a problem.
I'll go on ahead, all right?
But how do we know she'll
take me straight home...
Just get in the car, will you?
See you! Goodbye!
Uh, you really don't need to rush.
But the sun's about to set.
There's a beach with a beautiful view
of the sunset. Let's go for a drive.
I knew it...
ROAD BLOCKED
DETOUR
There was no construction
going on yesterday!
It's the System Force after all.
Never mind, I'll take another route.
ROAD BLOCKED
Why?
Oh, boy...
But why?
Not here, too!
Let's just give it up and go home.
It looks like the sun's
already set anyway.
Fine.
But I want you to answer one question.
W-What are you doing?
Do you love me?
What?
A potent System Force reaction!
This is terrible,
Keiichi's in danger...
Answer me.
Do you love me?
The thing is...
Answer me!
I don't dislike you.
But...
There!
Listen, about you and me...
Oh no! I can't get there in time!
The System Force...
Whatever it was that tried
to separate us is gone!
Look, I know you're not
really in love with me.
How can you...
You probably don't remember this,
but I got rejected once, awhile ago...
...by you.
That's why I can tell you don't
really mean what you're saying.
Not that it doesn't make
me feel good, though!
So do you think you can
put an end to this now?
I guess I kind of upset Miss Mishima.
I suppose so.
Wait, I left my bike at school.
Not that it doesn't make
me feel good, though!
I was so cruel when I rejected him.
How can he smile about it?
Who can that be at this hour?
Who's there?
It's Morisato...
What?
We made too much dinner, so...
Why don't we all eat together?
Oh, I don't see why not.
Come on in, then.
Thanks for the invite!
The seniors wouldn't leave without
trying some of Belldandy's cooking.
Oh yeah, the Dean told me
to give you this.
It's your student ID card.
Student ID card?
It means that now you're officially
a Nekomi Tech student, just like me.
Really, truly?
Yeah!
In other words...
That girl's going to stick
around 'til we graduate?
W-Why?
Why is this happening to me?
One day when I woke up...
A day like any other...
another one just beginning.
There you are, yawning...
your face is still so sleepy.
Because each peaceful day
we share is a miracle to me.
This is where my heart
will always return...
Forever...
There's only one thing I wish for.
I chase after the same dream,
wherever it may go.
The love I feel for you
gives me strength.
May tomorrow be as joyful as today...
That's my wish...
When two people of the opposite sex
live under the same roof...
...it brings their relationship
to the next level.
That goes not only for men and women,
but goddesses and human beings too.
Next episode:
Ah! Living Under One Roof Together!
Oh, man, am I supposed to live in
agony?