Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather will come
fluttering down, swaying gently in the air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
Hitchhiking, huh?
Yes!
So where are you headed?
To Nekomi!
So now I'm going to be a
college student, too, huh?
There's Honshu....
Kei's there somewhere...
Hey...
We're gonna be docking soon.
Oh, okay!
Ah! A Blessing in Every Bargain?
Three days to go before I get paid, huh?
That's right...
Here it is, my day off...
and I'm totally strapped for cash...
But you know how chaotic it's been
ever since we met, Keiichi...
I rather like the idea of
taking it easy once in a while.
Uh, sure... you're right!
I guess it is kinda nice,
sitting here like this.
But there is just one small problem...
Gotcha.
Unless we do something about this,
I won't be able to cook for you.
Don't worry about it. I can go
without eating for one day.
I'll just get a job that pays by the day
tomorrow. We'll make it through this.
All right, then. Why don't you
let me take care of this?
What? Take care of... how?
Can you conjure up money, too?
No. But I have a spell that will
bring good fortune to you, Keiichi.
Here is a wandering soul.
Provide the soul that resides here
with the sustenance...
...he needs to live at least until
the sun has risen and set three times.
Apparently, we have a guest.
Yeah.
Hello, anybody home?
Can you tell me if there's a
Keiichi Morisato living here?
Coming!
Huh?
Hello!
If you're here to see Keiichi, he's
right inside... so please, come in!
Keiichi... you mean, Keiichi Morisato?
Yes.
Belldandy? Who's that at the door?
Oh... Keiichi, we have a guest.
Kei!
M-Megumi?
I'm Kei's kid sister.
My name's Megumi Morisato.
Well! To think you've come
all this way to pay us a visit...
Thank you so much.
Aren't you supposed to be in school?
Really, now...
Who would've thought you'd be able
to rent a great house like this!
That's a really long story...
Not only that, but you're living
with such a gorgeous lady, too.
Man, that's so not you!
Didn't anyone ever teach you to have
a shred of respect for your big brother?
Hey, Kei... aren't you
going to introduce us?
Forgive me for not
introducing myself sooner.
I was sent here from the Goddess
Help Line, and my name is Belldandy!
Goddess... Help... Line?
What she means is...
she works for a volunteer group.
So her community service
includes going out with you?
Oh, shut up! Stop asking
those nosy questions!
You see, I have a contract
with Mister Keiichi Morisato...
...according to which I shall
be by his side forever.
It's a pleasure to meet you!
She's quite a character, isn't she?
I guess so...
Anyway, Megumi...
What the heck are you doing here?
Oh, yeah, that's right.
I happened to get accepted to
a college in the Kanto area!
What the...
My, my... congratulations!
So I decided to pay you a visit while I
was here looking for an apartment.
Hold on! What about those two?
Weren't they opposed to your applying...
...to a college on the mainland?
Well, I guess it just goes to show
how much they trust me.
But they were so against
my applying to college here.
I've got to get back in time
for graduation...
...so I was planning to find
a place today and go on home.
But since you've got plenty of room,
I guess I can stay for a few days...
...and take my time looking
for the right apartment.
In that case, why don't you
just settle down here with Keiichi?
Well, if I can't find a place I like,
that might be an option.
Just hold up a second!
You seriously think you'd have fun
at college living with me?
You'll never be young again!
Don't you want to spend it without
anyone breathing down your neck?
Can't you tell I was just kidding?
I mean, if I was around, it would
just kinda spoil things, wouldn't it?
Oh, if you're talking about me,
I have no problem whatsoever!
Uh-uh!
Megumi made the decision to come
over here and be independent.
So let's do everything we can to
help her find her own apartment!
All right, I'm behind you.
You're such a caring
older brother, aren't you?
Well, no...
We'd better find her a place before
she finds out who Belldandy really is.
I can't even get romantic with her
when there's no one else around...
...no way is Megumi going
to stick around here!
Remember, it's only until
you find your own place.
Kei, you're the man! Okay...
Then, this is my way of saying thanks!
My, how impressive!
What's all this?
I thought you might be craving
some home cooking by now.
I brought all this from Hokkaido!
You did, did you?
Man, you really saved the day!
I don't have any money
for food right now!
Then maybe I can get you
to help me out right away.
I don't know much about this city, so
I'm actually at a loss about what to do.
You can just leave that to me!
So what kind of apartment
do you have in mind, Megumi?
Oh, something like this, more or less...
2 six-mat rooms at the very least?
Private bathroom... Kitchen...
an absolute must!
A southeast-facing room with
plenty of sunlight... Non-negotiable!
No more than a 10-minute walk
to the nearest train station?
Built within the last 5 years...
For less than 15,000 yen a month?
Well, if worst comes to worst,
I'm willing to go up to 20,000.
What's so funny?
Are you out of your mind?
Look, you... you really don't
have a clue, do you?
Let's go!
Where?
Let's just say I'm going to
give you a dose of reality...
Huh?
Listen up, Megumi!
The best you can possibly do with your
pitiful budget is a place like this!
I don't think I could stand it.
A room that stinks of testosterone?
It is a very unique room.
I let half of my precious youth go down
the drain, jerked around by the seniors.
Do you think you could survive
a living hell like this?
A full-on workout, 100 push-ups,
100 squats per leg every morning...
Morisato!
Huh?
What did you say happened to
half of your precious youth?
Hey, Belldandy, who are these guys?
These are the members
of the NIT Auto Club.
Morisato, you've
really got some balls...
Not once, but twice, actually...
You dare to bring women into our
male sanctuary, so laden with tradition...
Hey, no, you've got it all wrong...
Not only that, but you've reviled this
sacred ground by calling it a living hell.
I hope you're aware of the
sheer enormity of such crimes.
Out you go!
Kei, you sure have some colorful seniors
running this club of yours.
Never mind that! You see where
I'm coming from now, don't you?
It's hard enough in Hokkaido...
But finding a place to live here
is a freaking nightmare!
Hey, listen, don't let it
get you down, okay?
Gotcha! Of course I checked out
the market before coming over!
But you never know where you might
find a really great bargain, right?
Yes, if we just look hard enough, I'm sure
that we'll find a lovely place for you!
Okay, so maybe I wasn't being realistic,
thinking I'd find a place in one day.
But just watch me! Tomorrow
I'm really going to pound the pavement!
And we'll do whatever
we can to help you.
Won't we, Keiichi?
Do you really think it's
going to be that easy?
Oh, boy, it's been ages since I
last got to hang out with you like this.
Listen, could you get real for a second?
We've only got today and tomorrow.
You need to get a grip on yourself...
I hope I find a nice apartment!
I hope we find someplace that
meets all of your requirements!
Yeah, I certainly hope so, too...
for god's sake!
Real Estate
Nothing.
Property, Buildings
Unfortunately, we do not
have anything available.
Rentals
Nope.
I mean, you really think we'd have one?
Oh, you're absolutely right!
Houmei Realty
Property, Homes, Apartments
No...
About the sunlight...
I can live without it...
Keiichi...
Belldandy?
Megumi...
Why don't you have some tea with me?
Uh... Megumi.
It's about your apartment...
Huh?
The way things are going, it doesn't look
likely that we'll find the kind of place...
...you're looking for.
Oh, hey, you don't have
to worry about that!
If I can't find my ideal apartment,
all I have to do is modify my wish list.
I don't want to make poor
Kei suffer any more.
I know what you're thinking, you're going
to ask him to let me live here, aren't you?
Yes.
I wouldn't do that, it's only
going to disappoint Kei.
You mean it would disappoint
him to have to live with you?
Don't you get it?
No...
Well, I guess it's because you're so
considerate that Kei fell for you...
Doesn't it wear you out to
be that way all the time?
No, not at all.
Well, what more could you expect
from the Goddess Help Line?
Okay, we've got a long day
tomorrow, so I'm going to bed.
All right, good night, then!
Belldandy?
Yes?
Look after Kei for me, will you?
Yes!
O dwelling that I seek,
you are at rest somewhere.
Please reveal your resting-place to me.
And I shall release you
from your slumber...
Belldandy, huh?
If angels and goddesses really do exist,
I wonder if they're just like her...
Real Estate
Oh, we've got one. An apartment
that meets all your requirements.
Do you really?
This is wonderful, isn't it, Megumi?
All right! This is amazing!
But I think you should pass on it.
Built 4 years ago. Has its own
bathroom, 2 six-mat rooms and...
...a 4-mat-sized kitchen. A 10-minute
walk to the nearest train station.
Has a room facing the southwest.
It's on the 1st floor of a 2-story complex.
The rent's 20,000 yen a month!
It matches my wish list exactly!
Hey Kei, I want to
take a look inside right away!
Good idea.
This room...
Wow!
Kitchen? A+!
Bathroom? A+!
Both rooms? A+!
I'm sold, I'm taking this apartment!
Well, it sure is a steal
at 20,000 yen...
Now that it's settled, I better
go sign the lease right away.
I'll be right back, guys, okay?
Hey, we'll go with you, then.
Oh, no... you two stay right here!
Don't you guys want to
be alone for a change?
Hey!
For god's sake, that Megumi...
Keiichi...
What's the matter, Belldandy?
This room...
Don't you think it's rather chilly
for a room facing the southeast?
Well, now that you mention it...
There's something here...
Did you hear that just now?
What was that?
Just as I thought...
I know you're here!
Show yourself at once!
Get out!
This place is mine, get out!
Keiichi!
Where are you? Why are you
doing such a terrible thing?
Belldandy!
I want you to stay
right there... don't move.
Keiichi!
Belldandy!
Keiichi! Keiichi!
Dammit, why won't the door open?
Damn you fool, for
refusing to heed my warning!
Keiichi!
Resign yourself to the
judgment of the gods!
Shield!
What the...
You're an Earth Spirit, 3rd Class.
Belldandy!
Why would you do such a thing?
Well, I never thought someone in
this dimension would recognize me.
I can see that your powers
have weakened considerably.
I don't want to fight you.
You must return to the earth at once.
That I cannot do!
Oh, no!
Belldandy!
That body of yours...
...I shall claim for myself!
I won't let you!
Arrest!
Such power...
You must be...
Impossible...
Goddess 1st Class, 2nd Category,
Unlimited License...
My name is Belldandy.
If you care to explain, I'm listening.
Please... please forgive me...
Thank goodness!
If he'd possessed you, it would've
taken three days to exorcise him!
Belldandy, who is that guy?
He is known as an Earth Spirit, 3rd Class.
Normally, one who controls the earth...
But ever since a stake was driven into my
Earth Power Line, I lost my abilities.
That's why you've been terrorizing
the occupants of this apartment?
To force them to move out...
That's right.
An Earth Power Line?
It's the path traveled by an Earth Spirit,
as well as his power source.
If this route is severed,
the Earth Spirit weakens...
...and in some cases the land
itself is destroyed as well.
Really... so that's what happens.
If the Earth Power Line is restored,
then will you resume your former duties?
I swear to you on my name.
I'll use some of the energy
from the Earth Power Line.
As you wish.
Transform the Earth Power Line into an
amplifier... let my powers be multiplied!
Shift the Earth Power Line at once...
I thank you, Lady Belldandy.
If you ever find yourself in trouble,
do not hesitate to summon me.
In that case, a friend of mine
will be moving in here.
Will you please protect her?
As you wish.
Now then, you may take
on your chosen form...
I'm leaving Megumi in your care.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Did you sign the lease?
I'm all set! See?
Now you can start college without
any worries. Right, Megumi?
Right, since this place
is close to school...
Jeez, I just can't wait until spring!
You said ''close to school''...
Come to think of it, which college
are you going to, anyway?
The Nekomi Institute of Technology.
Huh?
Oh, my!
The Nekomi Institute of Technology?
That's right. I'm going to be a
freshman at your school this spring.
You gotta be kidding me!
That means we'll all be
together at school, doesn't it?
I guess it looks that way. I'm
counting on you to look out for me.
You'll be my senior!
Why is this happening to me?
One day when I woke up...
A day like any other...
another one just beginning.
There you are, yawning...
your face is still so sleepy.
Because each peaceful day
we share is a miracle to me.
This is where my heart
will always return...
Forever...
There's only one thing I wish for.
I chase after the same dream,
wherever it may go.
The love I feel for you
gives me strength.
May tomorrow be as joyful as today...
That's my wish...
The human struggles, not knowing
what's in the heart of a goddess.
The goddess ponders...
...what on earth can she do to make
that one person in her life happy?
Next episode:
Ah! Where to Confess One's Love?
I know I love motorcycles,
but this is too much...