Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather will come
fluttering down, swaying gently in the air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
I'm resurrected!
Damn those goddesses...
Not only are there three of them now...
...but they also dared to
subject me to utter humiliation!
This time around I'll show you
the true power of a First Class Demon!
I can feel it...the throbbing
energy of your collective joy.
But all that will end today.
Soon, all you'll know will be
the agony of a living hell...
TARGET: MARLLER
ATTACK MODE: DEMON
It-It can't be...
What a peaceful day.
Yes, it is.
Ah! Misfortune Arrives,
and the Tea-Stalk Stands Upright?
Once again, I'm resurrected!
But for crying out loud...I can't
even get them to notice when I appear!
Curses!
Here I am, a demon, and I'm
up to my ears in misfortune!
To think that so much joy is
concentrated around this man!
I'll make him miserable.
Miserable beyond belief!
Mercilessly...undeniably miserable!
Keiichi Morisato...
Now that that's settled...
it's somewhere around here...
Aha! Found it!
Looks like the time has come
for me to put this to use!
With this Ultimate Last-resort
Weapon in my hands...
...victory is as good as mine!
Just you wait, Belldandy.
Not to mention Keiichi Morisato...
But even so...
Attacking them head-on will only
invite more outside interference.
Now, then, what should I do? Huh?
Mmm, that was delicious!
Thank you for another great breakfast!
Sorry I keep imposing on you.
Oh, no, you're welcome
to come over any time.
The one thing every girl should have...
...a big brother with a girlfriend
who's gorgeous and a great cook!
Look, Megumi!
Hey, you're turning red!
You'd better get a move on or
you're gonna be late for school.
Oh, I don't have class until
the afternoon today. See ya!
Have a good day!
That girl...she's Keiichi's sister, huh?
I think I can put her to use!
Young lady?
Yes?
My name is Marller.
Today's your lucky day. I'm about to...
Help! It's a ghost!
I'm not a ghost!
I'm a respectable demon!
There's just one thing
I'm after here...your body!
Huh? My body?
Help! It's a pervert!
I am not!
One way or another...
I'm claiming your body for my own.
N-n-n...
No!
What was that?
Oh, I guess I was just hearing things.
Now, Megumi, you know that's bad
manners.
Huh? There's isn't a thing
in this room worth anything.
That's not her! That's not Megumi!
Huh?
Listen, you!
Who the hell are you, anyway?
Such...such power...
You...
This is who the hell I am!
But that mark...it's the
mark of a first-class demon...
Why don't you just lie there
for the rest of your life?
From here on in, I'm Megumi Morisato!
A test drive, did you say?
Yeah, that's what the Seniors
want me to do.
Since our next race is coming up soon.
It's just that they're really into it.
Into it?
There's going to be
a lot of prize money.
Hah! Found you, Keiichi.
Big Brother!
That you, Megumi?
What's with that look on your face?
Big Brother!
What's your problem?
You're creeping me out!
You always call me ''Kei-chan'',
for god's sake.
Don't call me like that.
Oh, well, um...
Oh, come on, Kei-chan!
I was just kidding around, all right?
Megumi, I thought you said
you didn't have class until later?
Oh, um...well...the thing is...
Anyway, see you later!
Yeah.
See you later!
What was that?
Megumi is always so
full of life, isn't she?
Good thing I put up a double shield.
That Belldandy doesn't
have a clue it's me!
That means I can accomplish my goal!
I'm going to give you two a taste of hell!
Using my Ultimate Last-resort Weapon...
feared even by demons!
It is now time to break
the seal of Evil...
Come forth, Demon-god Senbei!
I am most honored to be summoned by
you.
Shakkin!
Senbei, the God of Poverty, has received
your call and is at your service.
Whoa...but you're so puny!
Non, non, non...
I am the No. 1 elite God of Poverty.
You mustn't be fooled
by my diminutive body!
Oh? Well, then, if that's the case,
why don't you show me your powers?
Yes! My greatest joy lies
in making others unhappy.
These special...POWERS!
Take a good look now...if it pleases you!
Target lock!
What was that? I just felt a chill...
Shakkin!
Oh, come on.
As if I were dumb enough to fall
for a 43-year-old trick like this!
Hey, what the hell?
I fell for a 33-year-old trick...
Hey, watch out!
Well, Aoshima...
You pack a pretty good punch, don't
you?
No, it's just an ancient joke...
You pack a pretty good punch, don't
you?
No, it's just an ancient joke...
I hope you're pleased with the results?
Needless to say, I am totally happy!
By making my opponent miserable,
my wealth meter goes up, up, and away!
That's the Law of the
Conservation of Happiness.
If you wish, I can generate
more unhappiness!
Now I can win. With this demon
on my side, I can win at last!
This guy's our real target.
Make him miserable beyond belief!
Oh, yeah! Just leave it to me!
You better brace yourself. Keiichi!
Belldandy! Today's your last day
together!
I've got to tell the Goddess Belldandy
what happened as soon as possible.
Or else Megumi will be...
A walking stuffed animal!
I've got to show this to my mom!
We're going in the opposite direction!
Have some tea.
It's persimmon leaf tea,
from the trees in our yard.
Persimmon leaf tea?
Hey, it's good.
I'm glad to hear that.
Hey, look, there's a
tea stalk floating upright!
Tea stalk?
Yeah. It's good luck when you see
a tea stalk standing up like this.
Oh, is that right?
So why do they say that it's good luck?
Oh, well...um...I wonder why?
Anyway, why don't we head
over to the club house now?
All right.
Who am I?
Let's see...
Why are you acting like a kid?
Now's your chance, Senbei.
While I block Belldandy from seeing
or sensing anything...possess Keiichi!
Roger!
I've got it! It's Megumi.
Bingo!
Perfect!
Belldandy isn't suspicious in the least.
Megumi, you're not acting
like yourself today.
Oh, come on, Kei-chan!
You must be imagining things.
Right, Belldandy?
Yes, you're just like you always are.
Well, if Belldandy says so...
You're crazy, Kei-chan!
Damn you, Keiichi,
you're sharper than I thought.
But what does it matter as long as
Belldandy doesn't get wise to me?
Oh, it's you, Keiichi.
Oh, hi.
Good afternoon, Sayoko.
Oh, so you're here, too?
Yes.
Really, I don't know why I even bother.
Do your thing!
Understood!
No one is more suited for
unhappiness than this young fellow.
Shakkin!
Keiichi?
What's the matter?
What do you think you're doing?
You get off me right now!
Keiichi! I'm really going
to get pissed off!
Huh? What? What the heck...
Keiichi?
What's going on?
Kei-chan, you're such a pervert!
Oh, but you always were the type
to do it anytime, anywhere, and...
...in any kind of weather!
What are you talking about, Megumi?
Hah! This will send Keiichi's
reputation right down the toilet.
If Keiichi's miserable, Belldandy will
have no choice but to return to Heaven!
Victory! Victory is mine at last!
Good for you, Keiichi!
You threw yourself onto Sayoko
to protect her from danger!
I'm not quite sure what happened
just now, but thank you, Keiichi.
Uh, you're welcome.
Um, were you mad at me, by any chance?
What?
But I wonder what that
was all about just now.
I know.
It was supposed to be
sunny out all day today.
Well, it doesn't matter!
Oh yes it does matter!
Senbei, make sure you get
the job done next time.
Just leave it to me,
I'll handle it at full throttle!
The sweet sound of...shakkin!
Hey, not bad!
All right, let me do my part, then...
Hey! Kei-chan, you're such a pervert!
I can't believe you'd molest
your own sister right here!
Huh? What? Not again...
Really!
Just because you can't
get anyone to date you...
...that's no reason to sink to
this subhuman level!
Come to think of it, you've always
looked at me inappropriately!
And with that, Keiichi will
be labeled ''subhuman'', and...
...he won't be able to escape his misery!
That will force Belldandy to
leave if nothing else will!
This time for sure, victory is mine!
Keiichi, you were trying to
remove that insect from inside...
...Megumi's shirt, weren't you?
Tell me...you're not mad at me, are you?
Why should I be mad?
Well, as long as you're not, that's fine.
NO!
Why did it end up like this?
I'd like to ask you that myself.
Little Bear! Where did you go?
Little Bear!
I'm on my way, Goddess Belldandy...
Goddess Belldandy!
All these weird things have
been happening all day.
You think so?
Changing clothes? Maybe it's Hasegawa.
Shall we wait, then?
Hey! Senbei!
Aye, aye, sir!
If things go on like this, my pride will
suffer huge damage. Super-pathetic...
Shakkin!
Not again?
Keiichi!
N-no!
What's going on?
Attaboy, Senbei!
This time for sure...shower those
two with misfortune and despair!
So now we're seeing
Kei-chan's true colors, huh?
Flirting with any girl he can get his hands
on. Girls are objects to him!
He's in a lose-lose situation now.
He can't escape the onslaught of misery!
This time for sure...
victory is really mine!
Oh, I get it, it's this!
I knew it, the pilot light went out!
We've got to open
the windows right away!
Keiichi?
I just spaced out all of a sudden...
If you hadn't come when you did,
I really would've been in trouble.
I'm just glad you're all right.
It's all thanks to
Keiichi's quick thinking.
Is something the matter?
It's actually pretty scary
when you get mad.
I don't understand this!
I know my happiness index
should be going up!
For this to happen...
...he must have a lot of happiness
gushing out of him from somewhere.
That's exactly it.
That's why Keiichi was
able to escape misfortune.
And the source of that
happiness is...Belldandy!
We've got to seal her, no matter what!
I was wondering what kind of
test you had in mind, but...
...entering a vehicle with off-road
specs in a quarter-mile race...
...nobody would do that!
Moron!
Where's the fun in being conventional
in a quarter-mile race?
''Catch your opponents off balance!''
is the motto of the Auto Club.
And the incentive?
We'll walk away with both the
laughs and the prize money!
All right, all right.
Keiichi!
Good luck!
Here goes!
Okay, now's my chance! I'm going
to hold back Belldandy's powers.
Yes, yes, yes.
Super...
Full Throttle...
Gorgeous...Delicious...
Shakkin!
This is bad. Something's not right!
Keiichi!
Damn!
Keiichi
What's going on?
Hey, you guys! Come with me!
Calm yourself, Spirit of Fire!
Retreat, Spirit of Air!
In the name of Goddess
First Class Belldandy...
...heed my command!
It can't be...why?
Can't you hear my voice?
Please, Spirits...
please put out that fire!
It's pointless.
Your powers have been sealed!
This is it...
This is the end.
Stuffed Bear Kick!
Goddess Belldandy...
Marller has taken over Megumi's body.
And she transformed me in this manner.
Who are you?
It is I! The Earth Spirit who
lives in Megumi's apartment!
Belldandy...I'm...
What? You've been possessed?
Your powers have been
sealed by that demon!
Are you going to believe
what that stuffed animal says?
Never mind him...what about Kei-chan?
Who cares if she finds out,
she can't attack me anyway!
This plan is absolutely failsafe!
Goddess Belldandy!
That's right, there's no time to lose!
If you're not Marller, then
you should be able to drink this!
It's tea with a tea stalk floating upright,
it's good luck, like Keiichi said!
Back...back off!
You're sending chills down my spine...
I've got goose bumps!
Now, then...
Stop it!
The fire's going out!
Whoa, it's cold!
The fire's under control, guys!
So that's the full power
of a First Class Goddess...
Keiichi...
Are you okay?
You cast a spell at full power
to save me, didn't you?
Thank you!
Thank goodness...Keiichi...
I was so afraid you'd be killed...
If only I'd realized it was Marller...
Keiichi, you knew that Megumi
was acting strangely today.
But even so, I never...
Belldandy...
I'm a failure as a goddess!
I'm supposed to bring you happiness...
...but I don't think I should
be near you, or else...
Don't worry.
As long as I have a goddess
like you by my side...
...I'll never think of myself as unhappy.
Keiichi...
Keiichi!
Huh?
The school racetrack?
What in the world am I doing here?
Okay, why don't you come home with
me?
You call yourself a God of Poverty,
you worthless loser!
Oh, no! Don't pin the blame on me.
My work was flawless.
Why don't I show you right now?
Shakkin!
Always believe in yourself and your
Dreams. You have a Wing!
I love you so much it hurts...
And it hurts me that
I can't tell you how I feel.
You and I have matching hearts...
So we must share the
same scars deep down inside.
But now that I'm in your arms,
I think I can catch...
...your pounding heartbeat this time.
Nobody else matters...
All we have to do is gaze at each other.
It's all right for your heart to flutter...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
Don't run away from happiness.
I'll always be waiting for you.
So come rest your wings anytime.
It's all right to cry...
anytime you need to.
I just want to see you again...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
I just want you to be happy.
Scars of the heart...a curse from
the past that can't be easily broken.
Yet people learn to overcome all that,
and move on towards the future.
Next episode: Ah! What Do Talent
and Hard Work Have to Do With It?
I know it's boot camp, but
does she have to move in, too?