Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather will come
fluttering down, swaying gently in the air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
Ah...
What's wrong?
Nothing. It's just that I feel
so pathetic, looking like this.
I just want to go back to normal soon.
Do you? But Keiichi,
I think you're quite lovely.
That's not the point, see...
As long as I'm looking like this,
I can't even show myself outside.
I haven't been to class in 3 days now.
Keiichi...
Keiichi?
I'd like you to let me handle this.
Keiichi, sorry to keep you waiting!
This will turn you back to normal!
What are you doing?
What do you think? You won't stand out
in these clothes, no matter where you go!
I told you, that's not the point...
Oh? You mean you'd prefer
a different style of clothes?
No, no...what I mean is...
There!
How sweet!
What is she doing?
Ah! What Wouldn't I Give for
an Angel With White Wings?!
Thanks, I appreciate it. I'm so much
more comfortable as a man.
Well, now you owe me big time, Keiichi.
But you're the one
who made that potion, Urd!
But it was Skuld who made you take it.
Is that Belldandy singing?
Along with Holy Bell...
By the way, what exactly
is an angel to a goddess?
Well, to put it simply,
she's there for support.
There are some high-level magical spells
that can't be cast without an angel.
Yeah?
And also, the angel is like a symbol
for a goddess's soul and condition.
Oh, I see, when Belldandy got sick,
it affected her angel, too.
Well, there you go.
Every full-fledged goddess
has her own angel.
So then you have one, too, Urd.
An angel?
Well, yes.
Big Sister!
Hello, Skuld.
That was so...
that was so beautiful just now!
Your singing, and Holy Bell's too!
Thank you!
Big Sister...um...uh, you see...
What is it?
Well, the thing is...um...I...
I was thinking I'd like an angel, too!
What?
Because you're not a full-fledged
goddess
until you have your own angel, right?
I can't wait to be just
like you, Big Sister, so...
I'm proud of you, Skuld!
Huh?
You've found your sense of
responsibility as a goddess!
Huh? Well, not exactly, but...
We'd better start your training at once!
Huh?
I just want to have an angel like you!
You've decided to take this seriously!
As your older sister, I can't be happier.
I just want to have an angel like you!
What shall we have you practice first?
I am the goddess of the Pillar that
controls
the workings of Heaven and Earth.
I bid you now in my name, release
yourself from the chains of the earth...
...that bind you!
There!
There! There! Come on!
No one has ever mastered this
without some difficulty at first.
Don't worry. If you just keep working
at it, I know you'll be able to do it.
I know!
Behold!
I'll use a Gravity Canceller Magnum!
You mustn't use a device like that!
I did it! That's what you wanted
me to do, right, Big Sister?
Magic is a power that comes from within.
You mustn't depend on outside sources.
But I'm not like you, Big Sister.
I don't have any talent for magic.
But isn't that why we're practicing?
Urd!
Only those who have achieved
their goals can talk about talent.
You haven't accomplished anything yet!
You shut up!
All I want is to have
an angel like Big Sister!
It has nothing to do with
whether or not I can use magic!
Oh yes it does.
Is that true, Big Sister?
Yes. To have an angel, you must first
have enough power to support her.
That's why you must practice magic
spells, to enhance your power.
Oh, is that right...
In other words, it's 100 years
too soon for you to have an angel.
Start practicing more diligently!
Who do you think you are? Butting
in and acting like some hotshot!
Well, I am a hotshot.
See that? It's a piece of cake!
Grr! Then what about yours, Urd?
My what?
Anyone who talks like such a hotshot
must have the most amazing angel ever!
Urd...
You bet I do! You can't even imagine
how magnificent this angel of mine is.
After all, I'm just way out of your
league, you know...out of your league!
I hate you, Urd!
Skuld!
What a little baby she is, huh?
Urd!
It's all right.
Just make sure you get Skuld
to understand something...
...that having an angel isn't
something to be taken lightly.
Urd!
Urd, are you there?
Huh?
Why don't we take a walk together?
All right. I guess I'll join you.
All right!
Well, hello!
Urd...
What is it?
Listen...
Yes?
The angel...
Urd!
How did you feel when
you first got your angel?
Weren't you scared?
I know I was scared.
You're still thinking about that day...
I'm sorry I made you worry.
Urd!
She who is closest to me...
who knows me better than anyone else.
She who is the mirror-image
of my innermost soul.
That's right. Your angel is
the reflection of your soul.
Your other self...
Come forth, angel!
Who am I kidding?
Of course she wouldn't come out.
Aha! This is my chance!
I thought something was fishy...
Urd doesn't have an angel either!
That means if I can manage
to get an angel before Urd does...
Too cool...
That would rock...
that would really, really rock!
All right, then...I'm going to start
practicing my magic spells again!
Ta da!
With the help of my Virtual Simulator
''Mr. Heartthrob'' Model 156, I can...
...become a magician, starting today!
Training should be conducted
in a scientific way, after all.
Why do I have to take part in this too?
Don't worry.
This simulator isn't just for magic...it has
a wide variety of applications.
I'm going to get my helmet
back the way it was, right?
Stop whining. One has to make sacrifices
in the name of scientific progress.
Switch on!
Darn, that's a wicked curve!
Oh man, I missed the corner!
No, no...I'm not done yet!
I have yet to unleash my full power!
I'm the king of Nekomi Ridge!
My experiment was a success!
Just look at the way Keiichi's acting.
At this rate, I'll be
using magic in no time!
Just you wait, Urd.
I'm going to show you what I can do
when I really put my mind to it!
I did it! I finally got it to levitate!
Okay. One more time!
Nothing's levitating...what in the
world does she think she's doing?
Now that I think of it, was there
a time when I was just like her?
I'm pleased to meet you, Big Sister.
I wished I could be just like her.
I'm remembering that day again.
Even though I know it's pointless,
no matter how many times I look back.
What was it that
Belldandy said that day?
Hey, I didn't realize
how quiet it's become.
She's hopeless!
All she has to do is train hard,
and she'll get to meet her angel...
Well, I guess I have no right to talk...
Why didn't I realize it sooner?
What's the point of casting virtual magic
if I can't use it in the real world?
At this rate, I'm never going
to be able to control an angel!
Hey, weren't you going
to show me up big time?
It's just like I said...
it's 100 years too soon for you!
Wait, that's it!
It's the results that matter!
As long as I learn to use some kind
of really amazing magic, anything goes!
This time around, I'm beyond serious!
I'm home.
I can't believe I was such a moron.
Why the heck did I run all the
way up Nekomi Ridge for no reason?
Huh?
Uh-oh. So it finally died on me, huh?
Wait, don't tell me...
Well, you don't have to
tell me who was behind this.
Done!
Now that I have this, I'm sure
to get an angel before she does!
I see. So that's the reason, huh?
Oh, please. I was just
borrowing it for a minute!
What's this gigantic thing?
Just listen and be struck with awe!
Ta da!
Power Amp Alpha 707!
This device will amplify my powers...
...even supporting an angel will
be just a walk in the park for me!
Didn't Belldandy tell you
to stick to training?
You be quiet!
I don't need steady training when I
have the power of science at my
fingertips.
Switch on!
Let's go, Alpha 707!
What's that?
Urd!
What's going on?
This is a high-level water spell...
But...
Keiichi!
Don't worry, she's just unconscious.
I see. It's that device
that's amplifying her power.
Keiichi, I'm going to
open up the wall now!
It's no good. The wind-elemental spell
isn't strong enough.
The only way to break through that wall
of water is with a fire-elemental spell!
Urd...
No, I can't.
Urd!
I know you haven't been using
your angel all this time...
But please, just this once!
It's not that I don't use her.
I can't use her.
What?
Ever since I was a child,
I've always suspected...
...that I might be
half-goddess, half-demon.
That's why I was a little scared
when I swallowed the angel's egg.
But even so, deep down inside
I expected it to happen...
...that an angel with pure
white wings would emerge.
But that's not what came to pass.
And when I was confronted with reality,
I couldn't stop myself from screaming.
You heard me that day, didn't you?
''Don't ever come out again!''
Don't ever come out again!
Urd...
Angels must always
obey their goddesses...
...so let's try to come up
with another way.
Belldandy!
Keiichi?
There's something wrong with Skuld!
This is terrible! That device
can only force power out.
If we don't do something,
Skuld will lose all of her powers!
Urd!
I can't take back what I said. I'm the one
who ordered my angel never to appear
again.
Urd!
There's nothing I can do now.
Believe in yourself, Urd.
I know you'll be able to meet her.
I've seen that smile somewhere before.
Urd!
I'd forgotten, you see...
What?
Why I wanted to have an angel.
That's right, I'd forgotten.
I'm pleased to meet you, Big Sister.
Because I wished I could be...
...just like her.
Like Belldandy!
No matter what you may look like,
you are my other self.
Don't ever come out again!
Thank you, Belldandy...
You have such a lovely angel!
...for accepting me as I am.
Come forth, World of Elegance!
We meet at last...
...my other self.
Consumed by fire!
I'm never going to
let you go again. Never!
Skuld, I hope you get
to meet yours soon, too.
An angel's egg...
I'm sure that day isn't far off...
...when she'll hear
your soul calling to her.
Skuld!
Hey...hey! So you did
have an angel, too, Urd!
Of course! Doesn't that annoy you?
Look at us, look at us!
Urd!
I don't think I can stand this!
Keiichi! Phone's ringing!
Come on, isn't anyone around?
Yes, hello?
What?
We're back. Huh?
What's the matter, Urd?
Urd? What's the matter?
Hello? Oh...yes?
All right.
What's wrong?
Oh, um, that was the
Almighty on the phone...
The Almighty?
He's suspending Urd's license as
punishment
for walking off the job the other day.
Goddesses can get their licenses
suspended?
Yes.
Goddesses can get their licenses
suspended?
During the suspension period, you
can't use your powers as a goddess.
Hey! Please don't go! My little angel!
I finally got to see you again!
So that's the deal, huh?
I hate getting my license suspended!
Always believe in yourself and
your Dreams. You have a wing!
I love you so much it hurts...
And it hurts me that
I can't tell you how I feel.
You and I have matching hearts...
So we must share the
same scars deep down inside.
But now that I'm in your arms,
I think I can catch...
...your pounding heartbeat this time.
Nobody else matters...
All we have to do is gaze at each other.
It's all right for your heart to flutter...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
Don't run away from happiness.
I'll always be waiting for you.
So come rest your wings anytime.
It's all right to cry...
anytime you need to.
I just want to see you again...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
I just want you to be happy.
A pure white soul clashes
with demon-black blood...
When that balance is broken, she is
transformed into the Lord of Terror.
Next episode: Ah! The Devil's Whisper
Coming from an Urn?
Uh-oh, look what's happening to my bike!