Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather will come
fluttering down, swaying gently in the air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
It's good to be by the sea...
At the seaside, man and woman are
freed from the curse of daily life...
...body and soul are bared...
That goes for man and goddess, too.
Keiichi!
Hey there!
Thanks, Megumi. I owe all this to you.
I just told you,
I'm right at the good part now!
You're always hogging the TV,
every single day!
I won't let you get away with it today!
Won't let me?
And how do you intend to stop me?
I don't know, but you're
not getting away with this!
Oh yeah? Then bring it on!
Really, those two!
So, how are you getting along
with Belldandy these days?
If you're so concerned, then maybe
you shouldn't come barging in...
...for breakfast everyday?
Now, now, lighten up, will you?
I really don't mind at all.
The more people at the table,
the better, you know...
I see I have no choice!
Kei-chan, these are for you.
For a hotel?
But where did you get these?
I got them at the shopping arcade.
I want to thank you for breakfast.
Why don't you take
a trip with Belldandy?
Megumi...
But those certificates were given
to you, Megumi... are you really sure?
It doesn't look like I can take the
time off, see...in other words...
You know what I'm talking about!
Right, Kei-chan?
You really should make the most of
this and go...just the two of you!
Just the two of us?
You'll never get anywhere unless
you drop that grammar-school mentality.
This is your chance to go all the way...
get the job done! Got it?
A-a-all the way?
Um...
Go all the way and get what job done?
Huh?
Here, under the blue skies...
...a goddess clad in a
swimsuit waves to me.
At this moment, I'm on cloud 9!
But the thing is, Megumi...
We didn't get to be alone at all.
Yay!
Ah! Confess Your Love Under the Moon?
Keiichi, I hope you understand
what it means to be by the sea.
What are you talking about?
We're here by the sea!
There's no better chance for a man and a
woman to open their minds and souls...
...and affirm their love for one another!
Then you shouldn't have tagged along.
Keiichi!
Keiichi, aren't you going to swim?
Oh, but you know what,
I can't swim, you see...
Hey, really? Then I'm going to
lend you something that'll help.
A Banpei robot equipped
with marine parts...
I call him Blue Six!
How the heck did you
bring this thing here?
So don't worry about
not being able to swim.
You can steer it with
this remote control.
Wait a minute, what about you, Skuld?
I bet the real reason you brought this
here is because you can't swim yourself!
Keiichi!
You should've just kept
your big mouth shut.
Are you all right, Keiichi?
Oh, right, I got thrown
into the ocean, and...
Thank goodness you're safe!
SAHARA
Hey, I'm fine, I'm fine!
You don't have to worry about me!
Darn that spineless fool!
But it's so lovely here,
don't you think?
The sea is so beautiful.
Yeah, if only those two weren't
around, it would be paradise.
Keiichi?
Huh?
You look so tired.
Oh, uh, the thing is...
Isn't there anything I can do for you?
I'll do anything, if it'll help
you to feel better, Keiichi.
No, that's all right.
Just sitting and looking at the scenery
with you is enough to make me happy.
What?
Looking at the sea you love so much...
Keiichi!
Belldandy...
All right, now's your chance!
Just do it!
That's as far as you go!
Just when it was getting really good...
Please free to bathe at any time.
Oh! But that's it, Keiichi!
Whenever one is weary...
...there's no better remedy
than to wash your sweat away!
Take a bath?
Mixed Bath
In a mixed bath?!
Ah, no, no, no!
What's the matter?
I have to get mentally
prepared for this...
You need to be mentally
prepared to take a bath?
I mean, since it's a mixed bath, okay?
Is it wrong, perhaps?
No, no, it's not wrong, but...
All right, then please come in
when you're mentally prepared!
''Please come in,'' did she say?
But are we really at that
level in our relationship?
We're barely even really held
hands yet, never mind kissed.
I mean, before we start
taking baths together...
...there's other steps we have to take,
that's the natural order of things.
No, but this is a mixed bath, after all.
There's nothing wrong with me
taking a bath with Belldandy here...
...I don't think.
And anyway, Belldandy
said it was all right!
If I let this chance slip away,
I might never get another!
Ahhh, what a lovely bath.
Well, hello, Skuld!
Where's Keiichi?
He's over...
Men's Bath
I'm such a loser. Megumi...
Hey...if it were you,
would you have gone?
I can't wait until
I'm just like you, Big Sister!
Oh, you've still got a lot of
growing up to do, so don't worry,
Really? Do you think
I'll be just like you?
Oh, more attractive than I am!
For real? You mean here, too?
Oh, my! What are you doing?
Your skin is so soft and smooth, Big
Sister!
Stop it, Skuld, don't touch me there...
You're tickling me!
So am I really going to look like this?
I just can't wait!
This in itself is intense enough...
Does it bug you that much?
Urd?! Hey, this is the men's bath!
Never mind that, why didn't you
take a bath with Belldandy?
Well, because...
Can't you see that you're only making...
...Belldandy unsure of herself
because you have no spine?
That might be true, but...
At this rate, you'll never get a kiss, and
forget about getting her to be your
girlfriend!
But...
More likely, she'll just get disgusted
with you and go home to Heaven!
But no...she can't!
All right, then, climb over!
The only thing that's standing between
you two is that flimsy wooden wall!
That's going too far!
Are you going to just let it slide?
Unless you climb that wall...
...you'll be branded a loser
for the rest of your life!
But I can't just all of a sudden...
Never mind, just go!
Or else I'm going to punish you!
Hey, wait a minute,
that's way too harsh!
You're driving me mad! It's nothing
but wood! All right, take that!
BATH
I wonder what that sound was just now?
Beats me.
Sorry, Megumi.
Your big brother is a loser.
It's just too big an order for me
to have to go all the way.
Keiichi, if you don't act fast,
nothing will come of this trip.
Urd...
The thing about girls is...even if
they know the guy's in love with them...
...they still want to hear
him say it in so many words.
Here, take a look at this.
Sea cucumbers, right?
That's right, sea cucumbers.
Are they for dinner?
No, certainly not!
They're for fortune-telling!
Echinoderm fortune-telling.
My reading tells me that the moon is
protecting your primary star and...
...a powerful attraction is drawing
you towards your stellar companion...
...the time has come for you
to shine eternally!
Understand?
Not one word...
Man! Listen...
See how 3 sea cucumbers are lined up
nice and cozy, in a vertical row?
They're symbolizing
your destined place...
Destined place?
Yes!
Somewhere on this beach,
there's a place that looks just that.
And tonight, if you confess
your love under the full moon...
...the two of you
will be joined forever!
Forever? You mean, Belldandy and me?
Yes, forever!
It's written in the stars...
it's your fate...
...your destiny!
Destiny?
Of course, whether you want to
believe that or not is up to you.
Well, just let me know
if you ever need my help!
Sure, 3 sea cucumbers
all lined up somewhere...
I don't see anything like that anywhere!
Destiny? No way am I ever going to let
Keiichi confess his love to Big Sister!
Yes, forever!
It's written in the stars...
it's your fate...
...your destiny!
Joined forever, huh?
Okay!
Keiichi.
Don't take this personally, but I just
can't hand over my Big Sister to you!
Bring it on if you're up to it!
But I'll be coming right back at you!
But wait a second...
where the heck is my lookout?
She never knows when to quit, does she?
Oh well, I suppose this must
be part of the challenge...
But once you've overcome this ordeal,
Keiichi, true love will be waiting for you!
If push comes to shove,
I promise I'll be there for you.
It's very quiet, isn't it?
Uh, yeah.
I wonder where those two
have wandered off to?
It's getting so late.
Yeah, you're right.
Keiichi, are you wishing you'd never
come to the sea with me, perhaps?
No, no, I'm not!
I wanted to come here with you.
But you seem to be brooding
over something, so I thought...
That's because...
Sorry!
Listen, I'm going to go out for a while.
Keiichi...
But...but that's...
That looks like 3 sea cucumbers
lined up vertically, nice and cozy!
I see, they're visible now
because the tide's out.
If I confess my feelings up there
on the night of the full moon...
...then Belldandy and I will
be joined together forever!
What...what's the matter?
My chest...my chest started
hurting all of a sudden...
What am I supposed to do, Megumi?
I've got to go back as soon as possible...
...but I can't just ignore
someone in trouble.
If I start back right away,
I know I'll get there in time!
Thank you...
He fell right into my trap, huh?
She weighs a ton!
But that's not possible...
It happens to be a Magnetic Control Unit,
a mannequin made of iron filings.
Looks like it's all you can do to inch
forward, with your puny strength!
I knew it wouldn't take long for
Mr. Nice Guy Keiichi to fall for it!
Could my strategy be more perfect?
Sorry!
Are you all right?
Hey, what's up with that?
No good! I'm busted!
All right, no choice!
Self-destruct!
Only Skuld could be so efficient
and yet so undisciplined...
Is she afraid I'm going to take
Belldandy away from her?
Well, I'm gonna do it!
I'm gonna make it on my own!
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
I never thought he'd fall
for that one so easily.
Now that I think of it, there's no way
that Keiichi can get there anyway.
Oh, well, now I can rest easy.
Okay, I'm heading back!
Belldandy!
Keiichi!
What in the world happened to you?
Just look at you!
Oh...it's nothing really.
Keiichi, what on earth happened?
The moon looks beautiful tonight.
Want to go take a look?
But first we should take
care of your injuries...
Oh, I'm fine.
Anyway, there's something
more important than that.
Oh, man...
Bringing her here was one thing, but how
the heck am I gonna get us over there?
Keiichi, what should I do now?
Isn't there anything
I can do to help you?
Why oh why can't I swim,
now of all times?
Megumi...isn't there a way
I can pull this off?
I'm so close!
Didn't I tell you if you were in trouble,
you only had to call out to...
Me, the great Urd!
Urd!
Hey! My Blue Six is gone!
Well! You only just got here now?
You took my Blue Six, didn't you?
That's right.
Where are those two?
Over there!
Hang on tight, now! We're almost there!
Over my dead body! Crash-dive mode!
What's going on?
Darn, we're so close now!
I'm going to make it there somehow
and tell Belldandy how I...
Keiichi!
Keiichi, are you all right?
Sorry! You had to rescue me again...
I'm so pathetic...
You most certainly are not!
Because, Keiichi...
...even though you're terrified of
the ocean, you tried your best...
...so that you could show me the moon.
That's what I love about you, Keiichi!
Belldandy...
Thank you.
Hey! Now they're like,
getting all romantic!
I've got to do something or
Keiichi will declare his love!
Well, like I said, that's their destiny!
Now that they've gotten this far,
stop fighting it and just leave them alone.
No way!
Big Sister belongs to me and me alone!
Really, Skuld...
You're always changing the
negative to a positive...
That's what always rescues me,
you know...your smiling face...
And that's why I...
...want to tell you, the one who's
always by my side with that smile...
...I love you!
Oh.
Huh?
Oh, my...
F-forever...
...joined together?!
Congratulations! Congratulations!
It didn't work out after all, Megumi...
No! Keiichi!
Both of you, pull yourselves together!
Kei-chan, how was your trip?
Kei-chan?
I'm nothing but a loser, Megumi...
I have no spine, I have no guts, and
I don't seem to have any luck, either!
Why do I have to be with
Keiichi of all people?
I didn't think they'd believe my story!
Why oh why?
Forgive me, I'm a worthless big brother...
What the heck happened?!
''And that's why I love you'', he said...
Always believe in yourself and your
Dreams. You have a Wing!
I love you so much it hurts...
And it hurts me that
I can't tell you how I feel.
You and I have matching hearts...
So we must share the
same scars deep down inside.
But now that I'm in your arms,
I think I can catch...
...your pounding heartbeat this time.
Nobody else matters...
All we have to do is gaze at each other.
It's all right for your heart to flutter...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
Don't run away from happiness.
I'll always be waiting for you.
So come rest your wings anytime.
It's all right to cry...
anytime you need to.
I just want to see you again...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
I just want you to be happy.
The seeds of love... a magic potion
that will make you irresistible to all.
When this is taken by a goddess,
her hidden feelings come flooding out.
Next episode:
Ah! Please Don't Look at Me Like That!?
What's gotten into you, Belldandy?