Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather will come
fluttering down, swaying gently in the
air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
System error?
What did you say?
Yggdrasil's self-defense functions...
...and the goddess support
systems are malfunctioning!
The energy transfer system is down!
Put the sub-system into backup mode!
Rebooting the main system!
It's no good.
The massive gravitational
pulse observed earlier...
...has almost completely
crashed the main system.
Impossible...
how could this be happening?
At this rate, Yggdrasil will
soon be vulnerable to attack.
Due to the effects of a
gravitational pulse on Earth...
...Yggdrasil's defense mechanisms
have been compromised!
Combat Division, prepare for an attack
on the demons in defense of Yggdrasil!
Repeat, Combat Division...
Do you understand the plan of action?
Yes.
Urd has unleashed her demonic
powers, and become the Lord of Terror.
Unless we take action now...
...this could have an adverse effect
on all of Yggdrasil's functions.
So I must defeat Urd
before that happens...
Can you do it?
If defeating her is my duty...
That power surge...it couldn't be...
Ah! The Savior of the World Arrives
with the Sound of the Flute?
Unrestricted, the power of a 1st class
goddess...
...could accidentally destroy Earth.
If I were to remove
the seal on that power...
...I might have a chance against Urd,
who's awakened as the Lord of Terror.
Big Sister, breaking your seal
without permission is a huge offense!
And also a chance of saving Keiichi...
You might not even get away
with just a license revocation!
My sealed power...
Return to me!
In a flash of light!
Big Sister...
Belldandy has dared to
break her power seal.
I'm putting the attack on hold for now.
1st class goddess,
special duty category, Lind...
You are to remain in combat mode.
Stand by until you receive new orders.
Understood.
I just hope that this
can resolve everything.
Even at full power,
I'm still being jammed.
That's what's keeping me from
locating Urd and the others.
But the moment she uses her powers,
there should be a gravitational pulse.
As long as I don't miss that moment,
I should be able to find her.
Both Keiichi and Urd...
I'm going to save them no matter what.
Please have mercy on me!
Oh, shut up.
Just take your medicine and
think about how you messed up!
You demon!
Really...
Thanks to your incompetence as a
servant...
...not only did you fail to seal
Belldandy...
...but you brought back
an unnecessary souvenir.
Listen, Urd!
If you don't cut it out, you'll be in
big trouble! Wake up, for crying out loud!
Wake up, did you say?
That's right...
I've awakened all right...
to who I really am!
Don't tell me you're going to use
the Ultimate Destruction Program...
Ultimate Destruction Program?
I'm saved!
Hey, servant, what's this
Ultimate Destruction Program?
Uh...well...I've never
heard of it before, either.
Darn, so they didn't know about it.
Then why don't I just ask him
directly by scanning his mind?
My power shall connect
your mind with my mind...
Two minds on a date!
I'll die before I tell you anything!
Don't tell me he can
throw up a mind shield?
Come to think of it, I don't
know much about it, either.
If that's the case,
you should've told me!
You made me use unnecessary power.
Code confirmed!
I will now proceed to explain
the Ultimate Destruction Program.
Explanation of the program's operation.
First...
The Ultimate Destruction Program
was...
...written by demons to
create a world for demons.
In other words, it will lead to the
annihilation of all human life on Earth.
...it is a program that
will usher in a demonic age!
I don't believe this! Picking such
an uninspired place to meet me!
If you're going to make me wait, at least
pick a 5-star restaurant or a swanky bar!
You could've been more thoughtful!
''Famous loyal dog'' or not, making me
wait in front of some pooch's statue...
Who in the world do you think you are?
Now what do I do?
How's he going to find me now?
How am I doing so far?
Well done! You must accurately
bring down 52 buildings.
The Ultimate Destruction Program is...
...safeguarded by layers of powerful
protection.
Once you've cracked them all, this
world will become a realm of darkness!
You'd never...would you?
You bet I would!
I'm going to destroy this world and
rebuild it into a Dark Realm for demons.
The urn!
Yes, my Lord.
All right, the first layer of protection
has been removed. What's next?
Don't be impatient.
The Night of Terror is still young!
Our time will come soon enough.
I've found her! Urd!
Big Sister!
Keiichi! Urd!
I'm coming.
Why?
Why am I always the one
who gets left behind?
Lord Urd! You've done it!
The stars have vanished!
This means I've successfully
completed the second process, right?
At this rate, the world will...
Keiichi...
Just stay very still,
right where you are...
Belldandy...
All right, what do I do next?
What the...
Holy Bell!
Belldandy!
Just one shot...
If that urn is the catalyst, things should
go back to normal once it's destroyed...
Wind Arrow!
Very clever!
Shield!
What the...
Curses! You removed your power
limiter!
Yes.
If the urn is broken,
the spell should be lifted.
Belldandy!
Keiichi, everything will be all right now.
Now then, let's go home
together, the 3 of us.
You're the only older sister
I have in the world...
That was brilliant, Belldandy!
You couldn't have done it better.
Everything has happened as planned.
From making you sense Urd's presence,
to having you destroy me.
But, no...
Now that I've been destroyed
at the hands of a goddess...
...the final process for activating
the program has been completed.
Now then, Lord of Terror!
Let us now transform this world
into a Realm of Darkness!
No! Wait!
It can't be...it's all my fault...
...that my sister and this world...
Behind you! Shield!
Belldandy!
She's out of my way at last!
And now it's finally mine to use as I
wish...
...the Ultimate Destruction Program!
Go, Fenrir!
Go forth and feast on
the people's suffering!
Burn it all down! Destroy
everything in your sight, Fenrir!
And once you've trampled
the earth to ruins...
...we shall lay the foundations
of our new Demon Realm!
Don't you think you might
be going a little too far?
Belldandy!
Belldandy! Belldandy! Belldandy!
Man, can't he shut up?
This is the best part,
for crying out loud!
Urd, aren't you even a little
worried about Belldandy?
You may be the Lord of Terror, but you
are still sisters with half the same blood!
True, half of the blood in my veins is
the same blood that runs in Belldandy's.
However...
Now that I've awakened as the Lord of
Terror...
...all that matters is my demon blood!
There is no justice but destruction!
This world has no need for goddesses!
Belldandy...what am I supposed to do?
How am I supposed to find
Big Sister and the others?
Huh?
What's a cell phone doing
in a place like this?
Uh...hello?
It is I.
The Almighty?
I can see there's much
turmoil down there.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you about Urd...
I am willing to overlook both that and
the fact Belldandy unsealed her powers.
Your priority now is to stop
the program from executing.
Do you mean that...
The Lord of Terror unlocked the seal on
the Ultimate Destruction Program.
The program is now running with the
objective of creating a Demon Realm.
But, no...
As things stand, the Lord of Terror's
descent has triggered...
...a series of aberrations in
Yggdrasil's main system.
Even if I were to deploy the Combat
Division, only one could get through now.
Combat Division? Don't tell me...
you'd do that to Urd!?
I'd like to avoid that myself.
But it will be my last resort.
I am now going to send you the vaccine
for the Ultimate Destruction Program.
Ultimate Destruction Program vaccine?
A flute?
Deliver that to Belldandy.
The program will be nullified by
the pure melody of that flute...
...played by a 1st class goddess.
But I don't know where
I'm supposed to go...
Almighty One...thank you!
That spirit I just felt now...
That was the spirit of the Urd I know.
If I use all my powers to create a barrier
field, I still have a chance of saving her.
My sister wasn't the
Lord of Terror after all.
Holy Bell!
So you're going to help me, too?
Thank you.
All right, then, let's go.
Wind Cage!
Lord of Terror, what should
we do with this fellow?
True, now that we've gotten rid of
Belldandy, he's of no use to us.
Why don't we feed him to Fenrir?
You shall be offered as a living sacrifice
for the coming Demon Realm!
Take him, Fenrir!
But this is the Wind Cage spell!
I've sealed the Ultimate
Destruction Program's life-form.
Belldandy!
You may have unsealed your powers...
...but I can see how
that spell's depleted you.
I know I sensed Urd's spirit just now.
If her spirit was driven out by negative
energy, the opposite must be possible.
Please, Urd, free yourself
from that negative energy!
You think you can take me
in that weakened state?
Belldandy!
What was that supposed to prove?
I've had mosquito bites
that were more painful!
It's no good. There's just
too much negative energy.
I don't have enough power right now
to create a reversal effect!
Hey, servant.
Give your powers to Fenrir.
Huh?
You're going to give Fenrir a power-
boost so he can break that barrier field.
But if I do that, I won't survive...
Never fear...
Your accomplishments as
my servant will be celebrated...
...by generations of demons,
long after you're gone!
Oh, so I have to die for that?
If I do as she says,
I'm really going to get killed.
The hell I will!
You're so spineless!
Marller!
Fine, then.
I'll just give him a power-boost
with my own energy!
Fenrir! I am endowing you with my
power!
But why?
He's absorbing my power in unlimited
quantities...I can't control it!
Urd!
What's the matter with you, Urd?
Impossible...
Are you okay?
Hey!
Belldandy!
Are you all right?
Thank goodness, Keiichi...you're safe!
How could you be so reckless?
Because if I lose you...
...then there'll be no reason
for me to exist here.
That's why...
It's the same for me, you know.
If I lose you, I don't know what...
So you have to promise me not
to push your luck anymore.
All right.
Urd!
The emblem on her forehead is
going back to the way it was before.
All the negative energy's
been driven out of Urd's body...
Fenrir!
Not Fenrir...
I am the one who will lead this world
into darkness...I'm the Lord of Terror!
Impossible! You're the life-form of
the Ultimate Destruction Program.
That's right.
I am the Ultimate Destruction Program.
And now that I've absorbed
all of Urd's negative energy...
...I can claim my place
as the new Lord of Terror.
Thanks to you, I have awakened at last.
You still intend to put up a fight?
You actually think you can take me on
with the little power that you have left?
If it means saving the world...
and saving Keiichi...
...then I'll gladly sacrifice myself!
I can see that you're prepared...
very well, sacrifice yourself!
Skuld!
Sorry to keep you waiting,
Big Sister! This is for you!
What is it?
It can't be...
Yes, it is! That flute is the
Ultimate Destruction Program vaccine!
It's Midgard's flute!
And it can only be played by a
1st class goddess like you, Big Sister!
Now then, hurry! Play that flute!
Over my dead body!
Midgard!
The vaccine's more
powerful than I thought...
You did it!
I'm not going to go down so easily...
I won't go down like this...
I'm not going to let it end like this!
Looks like it worked!
Yes.
It's over now, isn't it?
Urd, the nightmare is over now.
Now then, let's all go home together.
Right!
Well, I don't know about that...
Huh?
What's wrong? Banpei?
Skuld!
Midgard...
You're the program vaccine...
Your nightmare has only just begun!
Always believe in yourself and
your Dreams. You have a Wing!
I love you so much it hurts...
And it hurts me that
I can't tell you how I feel.
You and I have matching hearts...
So we must share the
same scars deep down inside.
But now that I'm in your arms,
I think I can catch...
...your pounding heartbeat this time.
Nobody else matters...
All we have to do is gaze at each other.
It's all right for your heart to flutter...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
Don't run away from happiness.
I'll always be waiting for you.
So come rest your wings anytime.
It's all right to cry...
anytime you need to.
I just want to see you again...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
I just want you to be happy.
The program has started
to spin out of control...
And soon, both the goddess and
the human will be faced with...
...the greatest ordeal of their lives.
Next episode: Ah! Always By My Side
Keiichi, I'm so glad I got
the chance to meet you...