Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather will come
fluttering down, swaying gently in the air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
The Debugger program 3.5
has been activated.
Proliferation Level A!
The Earth's stability level
has dropped to 0.833.
How bad is the proliferation?
We can't stop it!
The Debugger program has been
destroyed!
How can there be so many of them?
The bugs are proliferating
at an increased rate...
The Earth's stability level
has now dropped to 0.331 !
At this rate, there will be
an aberration on Earth.
Oh, do something, will you?
I found the cause. Here it is!
My sister Belldandy... is the cause?
Ah! Who Does Big Sister Belong To?
I'm off, see you later!
Have a good day!
All right.
Sleipnir?
What are you doing here?
Keiichi!
What the heck is going on here?
Belldandy!
Please don't move... just stay still!
Keiichi... give me your hand!
There's nothing like a
nice hot bath in the morning...
Keiichi?
When did you get to be so bold?
There must have been some
kind of glitch in Yggdrasil.
What's this ''Yggdrasil''?
It's our control system up in Heaven.
Belldandy!
Could you help me send Sleipnir back?
Oh, yes, all right. I'll be right back.
It sounds like a lot of trouble...
Whoa!
That's hot!
Do you have to drink tea, of all things?
I could've burned myself!
Um...
Where's Big Sister?
Big Sister?
Wait a minute, are you...
Where is my Big Sister?
Big Sister!
Skuld?
I missed you so much! Big Sister!
You look like you're doing well, Skuld.
But why did you come down here?
Oh, that's right...
It's a big mess up there in Heaven!
It's your job to look after Yggdrasil.
How can you just abandon the system?
You're the one who crashed the server!
Who's been living without a care
in the world down here on Earth?
So what's the problem with Yggdrasil?
There's been an unprecedented
outbreak of bugs in the system.
Things are precarious now, so I need you
to come back to Heaven right away!
Go back?
Is the problem that serious?
So you're Keiichi Morisato, huh?
Uh, that's right.
This is all your fault, you know!
My fault?
So, the main computer or
something in Heaven suffered...
...a massive outbreak of bugs and
is on the verge of breaking down?
Yes. But as I explained to you earlier,
Yggdrasil is Heaven's control system...
...so if a malfunction occurs, the
repercussions would be immeasurable.
For instance, my teacup
could suddenly disappear...
Or Sleipnir could appear all of a sudden,
like he did just now...
Or it could cause something
like this all of a sudden, right?
Keiichi!
But how can this be my fault?
It is your fault!
We had a massive outbreak of
bugs today because Yggdrasil was...
...affected by Big Sister's unstable heart!
My heart has become unstable?
Right, the only cause for that can be...
...you wished for Big Sister to
stay with you forever forcing her to lead...
...a life she's never known before!
Is that right?
Terminate the contract right now,
and let Big Sister go back to Heaven!
Skuld, this has nothing
to do with Keiichi.
But...
The first thing to do is to make sure
the bugs don't have an effect on Earth.
I know you're up to the task!
Big Sister...
They're here already!
All right!
Take that!
Over there!
Okay, I'm on it!
Take that!
Belldandy!
Right!
What the heck is this?
For crying out loud, what is this?
There's a whole load of them!
We'd better exterminate them quickly.
Keiichi, please stay there.
Sure.
Ready... set...
GO!
Take that! Take that! Take that!
Hey, don't lose control!
Ugh...
I'm exhausted.
But I'm sure we got rid
of a significant number.
Argh!
No good! No good! No good!
There's no end in sight!
Hey!
Keiichi?
I'm over here!
Keiichi!
My! Keiichi, you cutie you!
You're choking me!
Are you all right?
I got chased by a cat. It was awful!
Is that right? I'm so sorry.
Don't be. It's not your fault, Belldandy.
So what's going on with the bugs?
Whoa! There's that many?
See, you have to come back, Big Sister!
Having a good-for-nothing sister
brings you no end of headaches!
I'll go back to Heaven.
There is no point doing that!
What do you mean?
Didn't you hear me?
Big Sister's the cause!
Please, come back.
But I'm here on a mission from the
Goddess Help Line... to be with Keiichi...
I know you have a strong sense of
responsibility, and I really respect that.
But if we don't do something,
Keiichi will be in danger...
...and all of Earth will go
out of whack, won't it?
Well, that's true, but...
Skuld's a serious kid, isn't she?
No, I can tell she's hiding something.
Skuld?
What?
Didn't you invent a
Bug-zapping Machine a long time ago?
Doh!
You said there'd be nothing left
to worry about with that machine...
Oh, that? Um... well, it broke down, see?
It broke down...
Broke down? My, how unusual for you.
''My inventions are flawless,
so they never break down!''
Isn't that what you told us?
What a letdown! That's the one thing
about you I thought was awesome...
But what's this? You make defective
inventions that break down?
I've never made a defective invention!
I can get it to work anytime if I want...
I knew it!
Skuld...
Well, since Big Sister left Heaven...
...I had to look after Yggdrasil
all by myself... and I was so lonely...
There you go again, you crybaby.
Oh, you shut up!
You're the one who dumped
all the work on me!
I understand now. But you know we
can't leave things the way they are.
Yes, Big Sister.
Are you sure this really works?
That's rude! Don't you dare
make fun of my Bug Paku-paku!
He'll obliterate every last bug
in a mere five minutes!
Combining form with a gorgeous design!
What a masterpiece!
Does she have a mechanical fetish?
Never mind that, has anyone seen Urd?
Let's get started!
What are you doing?
To safeguard against any errors, I always
do this before touching the machine.
Skuld's inventions are renowned
as among the best in all of Heaven.
All right, let's activate him!
Come on! You should be helping me
catch those bugs, too!
Huh? There's one right there!
No, stop!
Take that!
Urd!
It's your fault for leaving it out here!
This is why I don't like you, Urd!
Hey, hold up... what's going to happen
now that the machine's destroyed?
The thing is...
Keiichi!
Urd!
What's going on?
Oh, no! The effects from the bugs
are getting stronger!
AUTO CLUB
Nothing beats spending all afternoon
working on machines like this...
...wouldn't you agree?
Dai-chan, hand me a towel.
Here you go, Den-chan.
Morisato!
Since when did you become
an iron-on patch?
I'm not so sure myself... but the thing is,
your sweat smells pretty bad.
Yeah? Just hold on a sec.
You think this is his new part-time job
or something?
Wh-what the heck is going on here?
I'm picking up a neutrino up ahead!
Let's go, then.
I'm sorry.
I never thought it'd turn out like this.
I was worried about you, Big Sister.
Worried?
Big Sister, your heart is always so
peaceful and kind, but now it's become...
...so unstable that
it's affecting Yggdrasil.
I was sure that you must have been
really suffering for that to happen...
I'm not suffering at all.
It's just that...
Wait! He's down there!
Let's hurry, then!
Huh? How could I have gained weight?
That's because of me.
What?
When did you sneak in here?
You're trespassing, you know!
No, wait, I can explain this...
Keiichi, are you all right?
Somehow...
Hold on a minute.
This will protect you from
the bugs' effects for a while.
That's good to hear!
In that case, if you don't mind...
...I've got to get some rest...
Keiichi!
Are you awake now?
You've had to go through
so much because of us...
That's okay. At least
I could go back to normal.
Never mind that...
are you really okay with all this?
What?
I mean, Skuld did say
your heart was unstable...
Yes, but I don't really
understand why myself.
That's why I'm planning to go back
to Heaven tomorrow morning.
I see. And how long
do you think it will take?
I don't know.
Time flows differently in Heaven
than it does here on Earth...
A single second in Heaven can equal
several hundred years down here.
You mean...
That's right.
But...
But I'm not going to
terminate our contract.
No matter how long it takes,
I promise I'll come back.
I promise.
All right.
I'll be waiting, too... I promise.
Keiichi!
I'm so bored!
Isn't there anything good on TV?
I wish you'd just stay
inside that TV forever!
Big Sister!
I've decided to go back
to Heaven tomorrow morning.
For real?
Are we going back together?
You're going back with me, Big Sister?
That's great!
Big Sister's coming back!
We can be together again!
What did Keiichi say?
...he'd wait for me.
Did he?
So now you can finally go back to
Heaven!
Aren't you excited, Big Sister?
Aren't you, Big Sister?
Well?
Hmm? Oh, um... yes.
Then when we get back,
you'll sing for me again, won't you?
Yes.
And I want to learn how to use magic
soon. I want you to teach me, okay?
Of course.
Oh, and...
Big Sister?
If my heart is unstable,
then it might be because of...
...the way I'm feeling right now.
The way you're feeling now?
Yes.
It's the same way I felt the other day...
That feeling of being
separated from Keiichi...
Big Sister...
Can I talk to you for a second?
I'm really sorry about Belldandy.
I had no idea you were
feeling so lonely, Skuld.
I am not feeling lonely!
Would you mind not treating me like a
kid?
You're right... sorry about that.
But you're going back together, right?
That must make you happy.
No, it doesn't!
I thought Big Sister was staying here
because of her contract...
...or out of a sense of duty...
...but now I'm coming off as the villain!
None of us thinks you're a villain.
Why did you have to make a wish like
that?
Well...
Out of all the other wishes
you could've made, too!
But you had to go and ask her
to stay with you...
That's right... I don't know why myself.
Oh, give me a break!
It's true, those words just
suddenly came out of my mouth...
...but that's how I really
felt when I said them.
That I wanted Belldandy
to stay with me forever...
Rats.
Give me a hand, Keiichi.
Huh?
I want you to gather all the viable parts
you can find around the house.
I'll rebuild Bug Paku-paku!
Can you do that?
Of course I can! Who do you think I am?
Goddess Second Class, First Category,
Limited, Belldandy's younger sister...
...the great Skuld!
All right, then, let's roll!
He's good to go now!
We did it!
Yeah! We're all set!
Thanks.
Uh-huh!
Good morning!
Good morning.
You're up early today, aren't you?
Belldandy, do you have a minute?
Look at this, Big Sister!
It's Bug Paku-paku!
I'm going to activate him now!
And if we get him up and running,
she says you won't have to go back!
Skuld!
Keiichi!
But is that thing really going to work?
Don't be so rude! I'm absolutely sure
he'll work! After all, it was me who...
It was Keiichi and I who made him.
All right, here we go.
Please... just work!
Skuld...
Don't worry!
I'm sure...
All right!
To be expected from Belldandy's sister!
That's right.
And now I can stay by your side, Keiichi!
Okay, okay, step back now, step back!
I've decided to stay here on Earth.
Huh?
After all, I have to keep an eye on
you two to make sure Big Sister...
...doesn't get all unstable again...
Skuld!
No use trying to stop me, either!
I've already applied for
my Earth Training License.
So here's the scoop,
as long as I'm around...
...I won't let you get all
touchy-feely with my sister!
Touchy-feely?
Touchy-feely means touchy-feely!
Now move farther away from her!
Always believe in yourself and your
Dreams. You have a wing!
I love you so much it hurts...
And it hurts me that
I can't tell you how I feel.
You and I have matching hearts...
So we must share the
same scars deep down inside.
But now that I'm in your arms,
I think I can catch...
...your pounding heartbeat this time.
Nobody else matters...
All we have to do is gaze at each other.
It's all right for your heart to flutter...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
Don't run away from happiness.
I'll always be waiting for you.
So come rest your wings anytime.
It's all right to cry...
anytime you need to.
I just want to see you again...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
I just want you to be happy.
Rivals...
Although they acknowledge each other's
power, they are destined for a showdown.
With their pride on the line, the
two kid sisters take hold of the controls.
Next episode: Ah! Teaching a Lesson
Called Competition?
That doesn't mean
you have to use a giant robot!