Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather will come
fluttering down, swaying gently in the air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
We're done!
Is it all right if we eat now?
Nurse's Office
Ah! What Do Talent and
Hard Work Have to Do With It?
Good job!
Here.
Thanks!
You've improved greatly, haven't you?
Yeah. Thanks to everyone's hard work!
We're going to do really well
this year, I bet.
Morisato!
Here are your lap times.
On average, you took a
whole second off this time!
Really? I guess I have
you guys to thank for that!
Please, Morisato. No one else has
improved as much as you have.
Morisato, I'm sure you have a talent
for driving. You might be a genius!
A genius?
I don't think so!
Come on, I'm not trying to flatter you!
Hey! Hasegawa!
Yes!
Excuse me.
Miss Hasegawa is such a
hard worker, isn't she?
Yeah, she isn't really the type to stand
out,
but she always gives it her all.
She's a real behind the scenes type,
I guess you'd say.
You mean she's a backseat driver?
Uh, no...
That's not what I meant...
What? I can't do that!
There's no way I can do that!
It's too late!
We already signed you up.
You didn't!
What's going on?
Morisato, just look at this!
Let's see...a go-kart race,
female drivers only?
It's a new event they're
introducing this year.
We've decided to participate in the race.
There's no way I can do it!
There's no ''no way'' about it!
You're the only female member we have.
We don't have any choice!
Why don't you give it a shot?
I think Keiichi's right.
Not you too!
Don't worry!
It's not going to be a tough race,
since all the drivers will be girls.
It's not going to work out!
There's absolutely no way
that I can race!
But why not?
I just know it! I know I can't do it!
Listen, you do know how to
drive a regular car, don't you?
Well, yes...
Then, don't worry.
It'll seem like you're going really
fast at first, but you'll realize...
...you have nothing to fear.
But still!
A man's gotta have balls! Go on!
But I'm a woman...
Too...too fast!
O Spirit who exists in the Valley of Air...
O Spirit who arrives with the Wind!
Air Bug Spiralee!
Stifle that vehicle's power!
The engine shut down!
Great, she got lucky!
Miss Hasegawa?
Are you afraid of riding this go-kart?
I'm terrified!
There's no way that I'm ever going
to be able to drive that thing!
All right, looks like
it's still intact, Den-chan!
But I don't know if we can
keep it running until the race.
And we can't have
Hasegawa getting hurt.
Yeah, I think you're right about that.
She'll be fine!
I'm certain that she'll
be able to drive that kart!
Huh?
Belldandy?
Please, will you let me
take care of this?
We'll have an extra person living here
a while, so make her feel welcome, okay?
Boot camp, huh?
Well, I guess it's just like Belldandy
to come up with something like that.
Whoops! I forgot to turn off Banpei!
What?
What...what in the world is this thing?
Please forgive us.
Sorry about that.
I'm fine, I'm fine! I'm just a
little out of breath, that's all.
But anyway, that robot you made is
very impressive! It's really amazing!
He is, isn't he?
If you can tell how awesome my Banpei
is, you're amazing yourself!
Now, now, let's not get carried away.
Oh, you shut up!
Listen! You're here to train, aren't you?
Then I'm going to help you out!
Huh? Oh, um...
I didn't know you had something
like this right in your backyard.
Actually, this is the first time
I've ever seen it myself.
Only one person would do this...
I made it!
I call it the Tariki Hongan Temple
Race Circuit!
There's a super-tight curve
at the first corner!
You've got to time your deceleration
and acceleration perfectly!
Once you're through
an S-shaped chicane...
...you'll hit a backstraight running!
You'll exploit the full potential
of your machine!
And once you clear the last hill,
it's just a straightaway to the finish line.
Well? Brilliant, wouldn't you say?
Um, we're just borrowing
this place, you know.
Never mind the little details!
Time to practice!
If you can just master this course
of mine, you'll have nothing to fear!
But I can't do it!
It's beyond me, really!
Don't worry! Look at that!
My Voice-controlled Device,
the ''Aye-Aye-Sir'' No. 1!
Just tell him what to do
and he'll drive for you!
Hmm...
Too fast!
Aye, aye, sir!
No, what I meant was slow down!
Stop, please!
Aye, aye, sir!
You should've just
let me take care of this!
Come on, as if you could
ever get it right, Urd!
Oh, wanna bet?
Ta-da! Industrial-strength
Jekyll & Hyde 500!
Not again!
The thing is, she's way too timid,
and that's what we've got to fix!
This will reverse her personality!
In other words, she'll
become super-aggressive!
Hasegawa?
Why don't you shut up? Get off my case!
Man, what a drag...
That potion reversed her
diligent nature as well...
...and turned her into a total slacker!
I knew you couldn't handle it, Urd!
It was just a little too strong for her.
I'll just neutralize it with this!
Morisato!
I'm gonna go out now, so get all
the shopping done before I come back!
Let's go, Dai-chan!
Was that Tamiya just now?
Well, it is supposed to turn her into
the person who resembles her the least.
Oh, I get it...
What's the problem, Hasegawa?
I can't do it after all.
I'll never be able to
go fast like you, Morisato!
Hasegawa...
I just don't have the
talent for this, you see!
Neither do I...
Yes, you do. Look how fast
you can make that kart go.
No matter how many times I try,
I'm still scared!
Look, I'm just as scared as you.
How can it not be scary?
Let's call it a day, then.
Why don't you go wash your face?
All right.
Ouch!
All right, that should make it better.
Thank you very much.
There's just no way that I can do this.
Here you all are, trying to help me out,
and I'm still not getting better.
I just keep messing up...
I know you can do it!
How in the world can you say that?
I've tried and tried with all my might
and I've never once succeeded!
That can't be true.
Yes, it is true!
Miss Hasegawa...
Let's eat.
Tomorrow I'll see to it that
you do better, I promise you!
Not gonna happen.
Oh, come on!
As if you didn't mess up yourself!
Did I, now?
What's the big idea?
Yuck...
What is this slimy stuff
that's sticking to my tongue?
I'm sorry. I'm the one who made it.
Huh?
I've been a terrible cook
since I was a little girl.
They used to call me
the Homicidal Chef...
My teacher put ''Please have Sora
practice cooking'' on my report card.
All right, then please
let me make dinner tonight.
That way, I can show you once and
for all that no matter what I do...
...I'm bound to fail.
Miss Hasegawa...
I went through intense training.
I had my mom teach me at home,
and I practiced everyday.
But no matter what I do,
I always fail. So please...
One more time...
Let's try it one more time.
One more time.
All right, please get on.
Um, where am I supposed to sit?
Right here.
What?
There?
All right, we're off!
Careful, now.
It's scary...it's scary after all!
Just because we're riding double doesn't
make it any less terrifying!
A skylark.
If you're looking down at the ground,
you'll lose sight of what's around you...
...that's what makes it seem even scarier.
Look straight ahead and feel the wind.
And little by little,
start talking to your machine...
Look straight ahead...
...feel the wind...and...
...start talking to your machine.
Hey, is it all right if ride you?
I wonder if I'm good enough to?
I don't know.
Here she comes.
All right! She completed the course!
Good job, Hasegawa!
Thanks to you, Morisato.
You see? You can do anything if you try.
Don't act like such a hotshot when
everything you did was useless.
What did you say?
You wanna fight?
You little...
Here's to the end of training camp
and Hasegawa's great achievements...
...Cheers!
Cheers!
This is great!
Really?
I made that, you know.
Really, it's delicious!
All your hard training
paid off, didn't it?
Yes!
Now all you have to do is
to come in first tomorrow!
Huh?
Oh, yes, that's right.
Hey, why are you all spaced out?
You know you're gonna win for sure!
Tomorrow...
Miss Hasegawa?
Miss Hasegawa...um...
Oh, I'm all right. I admit
I'm still a little anxious, but...
...since you all did so much to help me
get this far, I'll do my best.
I really appreciate all your support.
Well, then, good night!
It's going to be all right...
this time...
I'll be all right...this time, for sure!
Miss Hasegawa...
Ready, set...
Right, we're set.
Where's Hasegawa?
What's holding her up?
She's going to be late.
Miss Hasegawa, are you ready to go?
Yes.
Miss Hasegawa?
Miss Hasegawa!
I got a stomachache all of a sudden.
Oh, no! We have to get you
to the doctor right away.
No, I think I'll be fine
if I just lie down a while.
But...
What? Does that mean
she's not going to be in the race?
After all that training, too.
It's just a stomachache,
she's got to psyche herself out of it!
I'd like to ask a favor of you...
Would you please wait, just a little?
Miss Hasegawa, I've brought you
some rice gruel.
Belldandy...
Yes?
When I was in grammar school,
I practiced hard to learn how to cook.
I didn't want to make everyone else look
bad at a presentation in home ec class.
I practiced and practiced and
my friends all cheered me on.
And I did get a lot better.
My cooking started to
taste a little better too.
But...
You feigned...your illness?
Yes.
Even though I practiced so hard,
I was so scared that I might fail.
While I was resting in the nurse's office,
tears started rolling down my face.
I was so frustrated, and so embarrassed.
I was so ashamed of myself...
That's why I decided then and there that
I'd never pull a stunt like that again.
But...
But?
But I'm still scared, after all!
Whenever I think that I might fail,
it scares me so much I can't even move!
This is who you are right now.
Please, give her all of your support.
Please believe in her.
You've done so much
to get to this point!
Belldandy...
But, Belldandy...
We all get scared.
But you never want to betray yourself,
so you have to...
...believe in all that you've accomplished,
and try to overcome that fear.
Why do you suppose Keiichi was
able to improve his lap time?
What?
Not because of his talent.
But because he's trained so hard
to overcome his fear and insecurities.
A genius?
I don't think so!
Look, I'm just as scared as you.
How can it not be scary
If you're looking down at the ground,
you'll lose sight of what's around you...
...that's what makes it seem even scarier.
Morisato...
I...
You've got one hour
before the race starts.
Morisato!
All right!
I'm not going to look down
at the ground anymore.
Always believe in yourself and your
Dreams. You have a Wing!
I love you so much it hurts...
And it hurts me that
I can't tell you how I feel.
You and I have matching hearts...
So we must share the
same scars deep down inside.
But now that I'm in your arms,
I think I can catch...
...your pounding heartbeat this time.
Nobody else matters...
All we have to do is gaze at each other.
It's all right for your heart to flutter...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
Don't run away from happiness.
I'll always be waiting for you.
So come rest your wings anytime.
It's all right to cry...
anytime you need to.
I just want to see you again...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
I just want you to be happy.
The sea...it is both the source of life,
and a place to rest your soul.
Embraced by Nature, the goddesses
bare their minds and souls.
Next episode:
Ah! Confess Your Love Under the Moon?
Megumi, just watch
this brave act of mine!