Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather will come
fluttering down, swaying gently in the air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
Something's going on...
I'll try to pinpoint the cause
as soon as possible.
Is it true that the System crashed?
Yes, it seems like it is.
Well, you have to admit it
was an impossible contract.
The System's to blame for
approving a contract like that!
How dare he keep
my big sister all to himself!
Well, I'll go down there
and check it out.
Hey! I'm going with you!
You'll stay right here and
work on fixing the System.
Huh?
But if you go without permission,
you'll get punished by the Almighty...
Now then, I think I'll be on my way.
Ah! Can You Pass the Love Test
With Those Low Scores?
It's gotten a lot warmer,
don't you think?
Yes, it has.
You're still sneezing, huh?
Yes, I've never experienced
anything like this before.
Maybe it's because you're not
used to the environment...
Do you think so?
Are you okay?
I think you'd better go home.
But we're not finished
with our shopping...
Don't worry, I'll take care of it.
You go on home and get
some rest, Belldandy.
I think I will then. I'm sorry.
Wait... what about the System Force?
Do you think it'll kick in?
I don't think so...
And besides, lately the System Force...
Anyway, today's your day to rest up
at home, Belldandy. All right?
All right. I'm so sorry.
Kanazawa Pharmacy
Excuse me?
Welcome!
And what can I do for you?
Uh... um... do you have anything
that will take care of sneezing?
For that ailment, I'd recommend
these two remedies.
Are these safe?
Excuse me? Give her these, and
she'll fall head over heels for you!
How do you know it's for a she?
But, there's more! Buy now, and I'll even
throw in this special video as a bonus.
Video?
Just watch this tape, and all your
anxieties will disappear at once!
Because it's packed with
practical advice, you see!
Right.
Okay, I'll take those, then.
We appreciate your patronage!
I'm home!
Welcome back.
I got you something that should
at least help with your sneezing.
Thank you so much!
I think you should take those
and go rest in your room.
Sorry to trouble you...
It's no trouble.
I just want you to always be
in good health, Belldandy.
Keiichi!
Yeah, so don't push
yourself too hard, all right?
All right.
Oh, yeah... I wonder what
that video's about?
Hey, it's a Betamax.
Love Guidance
Huh?
What the heck?
Hello, everybody!
What I'm going to do in this video is
show you, my bashful little viewers...
...just what techniques you'll need to
master so you can do this and that...
...and the other thing, with a girl.
Okay, you there, the spineless one!
Have you gotten past
the kissing stage yet?
Now, keep in mind that a girl sometimes
prefers to be wooed aggressively!
Is that true?
Jeez, this video is way too realistic!
Don't be depressed about your lack of
height. It's boldness that makes the man!
It's almost like she knows me personally!
Now, then, let me show you how to
give her a kiss she'll never forget.
Don't forget to create
the perfect mood for it...
Ow!
Oh...
...oops.
This is...
Keiichi, um, about this medicine
you brought me...
Keiichi?
Oh!
Augh...legs popped out of the video...
Keiichi!
A woman...
Video?
Excuse me, I'm going to
take a look at your memory...
Call forth this man's short-term memory
streams...play them back now.
I knew it!
Huh? Belldandy, what's going on?
Urd! I know you're here!
Urd?
Urd!
Whoa!
Shoot, I knew I'd get busted.
You're from the pharmacy!
Goddess 2nd Class, Administration,
Limited License...
I'm Belldandy's big sister, Urd.
So nice to meet you.
B-Big sister?
Oh, please! Must you be so
blown away by my good looks?
Urd, what are you doing here?
You've noticed how the System Force
has been malfunctioning, haven't you?
Yes. In the last few days, I've
had problems with my health as well.
Have you figured out why?
No.
It's all your fault!
Thanks to your goddess-monopolization,
you've triggered...
...a host of aberrations and now
there's a glitch in the System!
Hey, I was just kind of going with
the flow when I made that wish...
But the fact is, his wish was
officially approved by the System.
All the same, this is totally
unprecedented, you know.
Is it going to be a problem if
Belldandy and I stay together?
Don't worry about it. That's why
I've come here, to fix things!
But Urd, that's out of
your jurisdiction, isn't it?
Come on, I came to help
my sweet little sister.
And I have permission
from the Almighty One.
Then I guess it should be all right...
But who's running the System?
Oh, the kid's handling all that...
Ohhh... man! I hate you, Urd!
You don't want your wish
to be invalidated, do you?
Of course not. I'll do anything
to stop that from happening.
That's what I like to hear!
I'll need you to cooperate with me.
Okay.
This is pretty serious stuff
we've gotten ourselves into, huh?
Everything will be all right.
She doesn't look it, but my sister is
actually more powerful than I am.
She is, is she?
The only thing is, she has a tendency
to resort to strong-arm tactics at times...
What do you think you're doing?
Oh, I just need to talk to you.
Huh?
About the System Force.
Come in.
The System Force is part of
a goddess' support system.
So unless the damage is repaired, it'll
put more strain on Belldandy's powers.
That's why she hasn't been well lately.
So now what?
She's going to have to return
to Heaven to regain her powers.
But you just said
everything would be fine!
Didn't I also make it clear that
your cooperation would be crucial?
My cooperation?
The aberration I mentioned was
an error in your personal data.
That's what caused the
System to malfunction.
But all that can be resolved by
sending a sample of your DNA to heaven.
How are we going to do that?
You have to make physical
contact with Belldandy.
That is, you have to kiss her.
Say what?
Shhh! Of course, you-know-what
would be more foolproof...
...but in your case, that would
be like asking for the moon!
Anyway, all you have to do is kiss her,
and you two can stay together forever.
Yeah, but...
No worries.
Just do whatever I say, that's all.
Am I really gonna do this?
Stop procrastinating, for god's sake!
Belldandy!
Yes?
Now go!
What is it, Keiichi?
Oh, uh... I was just wondering
if your sneezing fits were gone.
Yes, but Keiichi, your
face looks rather red.
Huh? There's nothing wrong with me!
I just can't do it!
The color of Keiichi's emotions...
yellow, mixed with red.
He seems a bit desperate...
He must be under stress
because of Urd...
There's no need to worry about me.
But thank you for your concern.
Belldandy...
Now's your chance! Go for it!
Hey, Belldandy...
Listen... I'd like you to
close your eyes for a second.
All right.
If I do this... if I do this,
then Belldandy can stay...
But...
No... I've got to take the plunge!
Belldandy...
Oh, no, I forgot I left the kettle on!
You little wuss!
What was I supposed to do just now?
It was bad timing!
Okay, that's it.
Obviously, you need to
change your whole mentality.
For now, go take a bath so you can
get yourself properly psyched up!
Yes...
I know it's all for Belldandy's sake,
but still, what a headache...
Huh?
Hey there! Why don't
I scrub your back for you?
No, thanks!
Oh, don't be so shy.
If you could just learn to be bolder
in these situations, Keiichi...
You don't have much
experience with girls, do you?
Just get out of here, will you?
Excuse me? Is this body of mine
so unattractive to you?
I never said that...
Then what's the big deal?
You come out of there now.
Are you crazy?
Speech Control... start!
Come out now.
You want me to scrub your back,
isn't that right?
Yes, I want you to scrub my back.
Then, come out.
But... I...
Hurry up!
Yes, I'm getting out now.
Attaboy...
Damn!
Are you or aren't you...
make up your freakin' mind!
What was that sound?
Keiichi!
I'm so sorry, Keiichi, I've brought you
so much trouble because of Urd.
But I know Urd's just as
worried about you as I am...
Yes...
But the problem is that she will
stop at nothing to achieve her goals.
And she gets so caught up in her
methods that she forgets her goals.
I think I know what you mean by that.
There was a time when I fell
victim to a demon's poison...
No healing spell could cure me.
Our only hope is to borrow the power
of the Blue Dragon Stone of the East.
But we can't possibly
make it back here in time!
Leave it to me. I'll go get it!
My sister went straight
to the Almighty One...
I'm borrowing him, okay?
See here, you... come back here!
She took Sleipnir, the Almighty One's
eight-legged steed, without permission...
...to bring back the Blue
Dragon Stone for me.
She did something good, then, right?
No... it was only good until that point.
Let's go!
She became so enraptured with riding
Sleipnir that she rode him nonstop...
...for three days and three nights.
By the time she returned,
someone else had...
...already brought back
the Blue Dragon Stone.
I guess she's the complete
opposite of you, Belldandy.
Like how she bares all her emotions.
That's not exactly true...
I live life on my own terms,
just like her.
My staying with you, for example...
Belldandy...
Yes?
Do you want to be together forever?
Yes!
If I don't take action now, Belldandy
will have to go back to Heaven.
But still...
What do I do?
Excuse me!
Damn, another bust!
It's not that I didn't have the chance...
I've got to get it done tomorrow,
somehow!
You can't put the moves on Belldandy...
...because you've never known
the wonder of a real woman!
Let me help you out with that... to make
up for what happened in the bathtub.
I think you're going
about this the wrong way...
You're not bold enough.
Go on, you can have your way!
Whaaat?
Jeez! You're so annoying!
Put your hands on my chest!
Yes, ma'am.
But be gentle, now.
Keiichi.
Belldandy!
What am I doing?
You're resisting again?
Keiichi, you care about Belldandy,
don't you?
Well, I guess...
If you really care that much,
then why can't you kiss her?
I guess I have no choice.
Here, you can have this.
Huh? What is that?
A supplement for what you lack...
it's medicine.
Are you sure it's all right
to use measures like these?
Are you saying you don't care
if she has to go back to Heaven?
What? No, but...
Then take your pill.
There's no other way now.
Keiichi?
That pill is actually a
power-boost for Speech Control.
Huh? What's going on?
You are going now, Keiichi,
to Belldandy's room.
Here I go... I'm going to Belldandy's
room.
Belldandy? Do you have a minute?
Of course, come in.
Let the games begin!
Is something the matter?
Belldandy, can I tell you what I wish for?
Yes.
Good boy, good boy... let's go!
Belldandy...
I want you!
Keiichi, you've been acting...
...how should I put it?
I want you.
Keiichi?
You got it! Come on, now!
Belldandy...
I want Belldandy...I want Belldandy to...
Gray and black...that means...
I ask for the release of
this soul from captivity...
What am I doing here?
What in the world happened to you?
Oh, it must've been that pill...
See, Urd told me...
What?
The only way to fix the System
would be for me to kiss you...
...and send a sample of my DNA
to Heaven. That's what she said.
But if it means you won't have
to go back to Heaven, then I...
Urd, what's the meaning of all this?
Now that you're onto me,
I'd better come clean.
How could you deceive Keiichi?
What an awful thing to do!
Hold on a minute. You told me
that goddesses can't lie.
No, the reason that Urd has a limited
license despite being more powerful...
...is because she's being penalized
for having lied in the past.
This is unforgivable, Urd!
Excuse me? It's Keiichi's fault
for being so damned inept!
Huh? It's my fault?
And I went to all this trouble for you!
Here's your punishment! Lightning bolt!
Wind!
Take that! Take that! Take that!
Thunderbolt!
Keiichi!
I'm all right.
As if you had a prayer of defeating me
with your powers sealed!
I helped you two move to the
next level in your relationship.
But I never dreamed you'd actually
raise your hand against your big sister!
Summoning electricity...
Roll of thunder! O Supreme Ruler
who splits the heavenly skies...
...let your power smite my enemies now!
Look out, Belldandy!
Keiichi!
Sky-splitting Thunder and Lightning
Strike!
Keiichi!
Urd?
Did she self-destruct?
No, I think something else happened.
Here's a message from the Almighty One.
It has been determined that System
Force intervention by Urd, Goddess...
...2nd Class, Administration, Limited
License, has caused the Server to crash.
What does that mean?
My sister used her powers here
on Earth without permission, and...
...apparently that generated
even more glitches in the System.
Therefore, Urd is hereby forbidden
to return until further notice.
Huh?
Kei, I brought you some food!
Coming! Welcome!
Whoa!
There's another one!
Kei, you sneaky thing.
Hold on, Megumi.
That one just barged in...
Oh, are you going to be that way?
Too bad, I was going to show you
pictures of Belldandy as a little girl...
What? Really?
Hey, I want to see them too!
One day when I woke up...
A day like any other...
another one just beginning.
There you are, yawning...
your face is still so sleepy.
Because each peaceful day
we share is a miracle to me.
This is where my heart
will always return...
Forever...
There's only one thing I wish for.
I chase after the same dream,
wherever it may go.
The love I feel for you
gives me strength.
May tomorrow be as joyful as today...
That's my wish...
The smiles of the goddesses
shine down on us like sunlight.
The Queen's rage is
like a tempest unleashed...
...and with those furious eyes
she investigates our private lives.
Next episode: Ah! The Queen and
the Goddess' Secret
Caught in the crossfire of the battle,
mankind faces destruction!