Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather will come
fluttering down, swaying gently in the
air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
Skuld Laboratory
S...s...
Sticking out!
Sculpted!
All right!
I'm an adult now!
What's all this yelling so early
in the morning...whoa!
What are you staring at?
Um...
And who would you be?
Ah! Is My Heart Pounding
Because I'm a Grownup?
Oh, man. Look how carried away she
is...
Is this another one of those
Yggdrasil side-effects?
Most likely.
But why did she turn into an adult?
Oh, that's easy. The three of us
control different time domains.
I govern the past...
Belldandy, the present...
And Skuld, the future.
So if there's a shortfall in our
energy supply from Heaven...
...I regress to an earlier age...
...whereas Skuld is catapulted
into her future, adult self.
I see.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Look at me, look at me!
Well? Am I sexy?
My, don't you look lovely!
You do.
Ha! Who are you trying to kid?
You need to stick out and be tight
where you're supposed to.
That is ''sexy''!
Take a good look! See how big they...
Whose? And what? Are big?
Just give me a little time, and
they'll be bigger than yours for sure!
Little idiot, give you a little more time,
and you'll be middle-aged.
What's that supposed to mean?
Think about it! You're going
to keep growing at this pace.
If we don't do anything about it...
...this time next week,
you might be an old hag!
No way!
And that means that 2 weeks
from now, she'll be...
No way! Tell me you're joking!
When that happens,
I'll call you ''Big Sister''!
I'd rather die than let that happen!
You don't have to worry, Skuld.
Big Sister?
Uh-oh.
I asked Heaven about it
just now, and they told me...
...that Yggdrasil would be
fully restored by tonight.
You'll be able to go back to
the way you were before!
Oh, great.
Thank goodness!
I did tell Urd about that, you know...
Wait, but that means...
I can only be a grownup until tonight?
I suppose so.
Is that right?
Thank goodness, right?
That's right...there's
no time to lose, then.
Keiichi, help me out, will you?
Huh? Uh, sure.
All right, you're set.
Now let me just slip
on this ring, and...
Listen...did you really want
to become a grownup that badly?
What do you think?
No matter what, people have
always treated me like a child.
Really?
Whenever we go shopping, it's always
either Big Sister or Urd...
...who gets hit on by guys.
And even if I'm walking with you, people
only think we're brother and sister.
Everyone at college, too! They all treat
me like a kid, giving me ice cream.
When I'm just as much
a lady as anyone else!
Hey, look! Look at
all the ice cream I got!
That's because you always
lap it up so eagerly.
Anyway! Now that I'm all grown up...
I've got to enjoy what it feels like,
at least just for this one day.
Where are you going?
I'm going out, what did you think?
So I'll see you later, all right? Oh...
What's the matter?
I'm so hungry...
Urd drinks sake...
Belldandy goes to sleep...
Skuld recharges by
eating ice cream, huh?
That's right. Each goddess has
her own alternate source of energy.
Ah! Now I'm revitalized!
Okay, let's go!
You should just go home
and stay out of trouble.
I'll be fine!
Hey, that girl over there...
don't you think she's really hot?
She's with her boyfriend...
that's one lucky dog.
Wait a minute...those guys
think I'm your girlfriend?
Uh, yeah.
For real? Then that means
they see me as a grownup! Right?
Uh, probably.
Grownup...I love the way that sounds!
Now then, shall we be off,
Keiichi dear? Come on...
Hey! Hold on!
Belldandy's...
...cousin?
Uh, that's right.
Well, now that you mention it,
I think I see the resemblance...
To Big Sister?
Big Sister?
Cool! I've always wanted
someone to tell me that!
You're a wonderful person!
But you're linking arms...
You'd better not have been
two-timing Belldandy behind her back!
Of course not!
Oh, don't tell me you suspect
that Keiichi and I might be lovers?
Suspect? You two couldn't
be anything but lovers!
So we do look like we're going out!
This is no time to be
overjoyed, you know.
Oh! Look at this!
Hey! That's my bike!
I've always wanted
to take it for a spin.
Urd's always going, ''Not for children!''
and totally dissing me...
But at this moment, I'm a grownup!
I have to tell you, being
an adult rocks! See ya later!
That was my bike...
Hey! Skuld! Come back here!
Huh? Skuld?
Aha...now there's a fine specimen...
Pardon me...
Me?
Yes, would you care to join me
for some afternoon tea?
Afternoon tea?
Ah! Isn't that what
you call a pickup line?
I just read about that
in a book, so I know it!
Uh, actually...
It's just that I can't stop
myself from approaching...
...such a beautiful woman like yourself.
Oh...
Listen, I have a favor to ask of you.
There's no need to be bashful.
Feel free to partake of all
the ice cream they have on hand!
Do you mean that?
Of course.
Excuse me!
She really did clean them out!
Energy fully recharged!
You're going to reciprocate in full.
Now, then. Come this way.
Hey...
Excuse me...
Wait...
How can this be?
Keiichi's hands were warm,
but this man's hands are cold.
What's the matter?
No.
What?
I don't want to...
even though I'm not sure why...
You've come this far, you wanted to...
Don't touch me!
You've come this far,you wanted to...
What are you talking about?
Surely you didn't think you could
just eat and run, did you?
No!
Stay away from me!
Come back here!
No...
No...no...
No!
Looks like you've hit a dead end.
Stay away from me!
Now then, shall we go?
No...
Help me!
Big Sister!
Keiichi!
Skuld!
Morisato?
Ouch...take it easy, will you?
Never mind, just take off!
Right.
Come back here!
You again?
I guess you really enjoy being
punished!
Just hold on!
It's so strange...
I couldn't stand that
other man touching me...
...but I don't mind at all if it's Keiichi.
Keiichi...
Hey, what's gotten into you
all of a sudden?
I was right...
About what?
I'm fine with Keiichi.
Actually...my heart
seems to be pounding.
Keiichi!
What's up?
You see...
I just want...
I want to go out just a while longer.
With you.
With me?
Please!
Well, you said you wanted to go out,
so here we are downtown...
...but is there anywhere
you want to go?
Anywhere's fine, really...
You decide for us!
But the thing is,
I wouldn't know where to go...
...except for the body shop
or the recycling shops.
That's fine!
But we can go to those places anytime.
We should go wherever your
present self wants to go today.
Let me think...Got it!
Are you sure you shouldn't
have gone with them?
Oh, yes. I have to prepare dinner
as soon as Yggdrasil gets restored.
That's not what I meant...
Aren't you worried that
Skuld might take Keiichi away?
You saw it, didn't you?
The way she looks at Keiichi, it's
so obvious she's head over heels!
Head over heels?
Man, you're so thick.
I mean she loves Keiichi.
Yes! Both Skuld and I love
Keiichi very, very much!
What's wrong?
Oh...never mind. More tea, please.
I guess this just shows
how stable your relationship is.
So I apply some of this...
Um....Miss?
If I may offer an opinion, I think you
should go for a more natural look.
Do you, really?
What do you think, Keiichi?
Come on, let's move on
to the next place!
Are high heels really this tight
and uncomfortable?
Well, I've never worn them,
so I wouldn't know.
Whoops-a-daisy...
Keiichi...
Are you okay?
Sure, I'm fine!
I'm an adult, after all. Shoes like these
don't faze me. Let's go.
Hup, two, three, four.
Sir?
Huh?
That will be 39,800 yen with tax.
Huh?! Wait, come back here, Skuld!
For crying out loud! Why are
grownup clothes so complicated?
This goes on the outside, so
this cord should go through here...
So...I'm an adult...
Skuld?
How's it going?
Do you want me to get
someone to help you?
I can do it myself.
I think...I can do it.
I'm ready!
I don't know...
I feel a little strange...
Well? Do you feel like
you're a lady now?
Yeah...
Excuse me...
Would you happen to have some
spare time after you're through here?
You see...
Sayoko?
You're asking me to fill in
for that girl as a model?
Yes, she was suddenly
stricken by a stomachache.
Is there any way
you could do me this favor?
Modeling, though...
No, no!
I can tell just by looking at you two
that you fit our bridal salon's image of...
...the ideal couple!
It's a wonderful way to commemorate
your love for each other, so please!
Couple?
Love for each other?
Oh...am I mistaken?
Well, actually...
What should we do?
Well, I don't mind...
I'm indebted to you!
Oh, uh...well...
All right, I'm going to start shooting.
This is really getting weird...
Why is my heart pounding so hard?
Over Keiichi, of all people!
I can't take this anymore! Somebody
please stop my heart from pounding!
All right, next I want to
get some shots of you kissing.
Kissing?
You won't do that for me?
Well, could you just pretend, then?
Oh...
A k-k-kiss? With Keiichi?
Oh boy...what am I supposed to do?
Skuld?
Huh? What? What is it?
We're just going to pretend to do it,
so could you look over here?
Uh, sure. Sure!
Yikes...why is it so hard
to breathe all of a sudden?
Skuld...
Huh...
Keiichi...
Close your eyes, will you?
Okay.
I get it. I must have...
No, I definitely have feelings for...
Okay, that's fine.
Hey, good job, Skuld.
Let's go change.
Ah...
Right...
So the entire system's been restored?
I see...got that.
Good job!
So you're awake now!
Yes, I'm fine now.
They just called to let us know
that Yggdrasil's been restored.
If Belldandy's up, then
I guess right about now...
Oh...it's evening already.
How did you like being a grownup?
Well, I enjoyed some things about it...
...but there were other things that
weren't the way I'd imagined. I guess.
Listen...
Do you remember that time when you,
Big Sister, and I all went for a walk?
Huh?
I remember you were so absorbed in
your conversation with Big Sister...
...and that's when I thought,
''If only I weren't just a kid!''
If I were all grown up,
would you listen to me like that?
Skuld...
But I was wrong.
Even though I'm all grown up, you
still just treat me like you always do.
Uh, do I really?
Yes, you do!
You never once talked to me
the way you talk to Big Sister.
Listen, Keiichi...
Huh?
Do you have feelings for Big Sister?
Yes, I do.
Then...my present self...
what about my present self?
My present...
My present self?
Myself...
But...
...that's not me.
Never mind.
Okay.
Hey, it's gotten a lot chillier.
We should get going...
Hey, Keiichi, turn to your left
and close your eyes.
What's this all of a sudden?
Just do it!
Fine.
Just don't play any
weird tricks on me, okay?
Thank you...
Keiichi...
Whoa...
Looks like I've turned back!
Hey, come with me.
Augh!
Look here, Keiichi...
what do you think you're doing?
Hey...the only one who can
ride up here is the present you.
Isn't that a good thing?
That's not the point!
You're so thick, you know that, Keiichi?
And besides, we can't drive
on public roads like this!
You're right.
You just don't get anything, do you?
Hey, sorry!
Hey, Belldandy! Is it all right
for you to be up already?
Oh, yes.
Oh...where's Skuld?
She went to her room
to change her clothes.
Next time, I want to become a real adult.
I knew it...I guess I have no choice.
I hate to do this to Keiichi, but...
Augh!
Whoa!
Big Sister, what's going...
Skuld! Look, this isn't what it...
My, my! You just got home and you
can't hold back your passion, can you?
Really! Keiichi pushed Belldandy down
to the floor against her will, and look...
No, that's not true! It was Urd who...
KEIICHI!
You're a jerk after all, Keiichi!
You get away from my big sister right
now! I hate you after all, Keiichi!
Always believe in yourself and
your Dreams.You have a Wing!
I love you so much it hurts...
And it hurts me that
I can't tell you how I feel.
You and I have matching hearts...
So we must share the
same scars deep down inside.
But now that I'm in your arms,
I think I can catch...
...your pounding heartbeat this time.
Nobody else matters...
All we have to do is gaze at each other.
It's all right for your heart to flutter...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
Don't run away from happiness.
I'll always be waiting for you.
So come rest your wings anytime.
It's all right to cry...
anytime you need to.
I just want to see you again...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
I just want you to be happy.