Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather will come
fluttering down, swaying gently in the air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
Who is that girl?
So beautiful...
And she moves in such
mysterious ways...
The more I find out about her,
the more she enchants me!
I'll do it!
I'm going to steal you away from
that guy if it's the last thing I do!
Or my name isn't Toshiyuki Aoshima!
Oooh! Aaaa! Mr. Aoshima!
Ah! Can the Auto Club Triumph?
RECRUITING NEW MEMBERS
Welcome! Come on!
Please? Just check us out!
Please, anyone!
The Auto Club is currently
seeking new members!
Please, anybody!
Please stop by!
Not a soul has stopped by yet.
No wonder...
Come hither, youths!
Come to the Auto Club!
You'll find the answers to all your
dreams! Come to the Auto Club!
Hey, freshman!
If you join the Club now, I'll personally
honor you with my special dance!
No, thank you!
What did you say?
We stayed up all night practicing
our special welcome dance!
Den-chan, dance for him! Dance for him!
Right!
Come hither, youths!
Come to the Auto Club!
You'll find the answers to
all your dreams and hopes...
Man, it's pretty lonely
over here, isn't it?
Did you sign up any new members?
Nope, not even one!
No wonder, with seniors like those...
Hey! Why don't you join?
Sorry, but I've already
joined the softball team!
Oh, you have?
There's just been too
few people stopping.
Usually we get a few students who are
into cars coming over.
What's that over there?
Oh, that's the Auto Club.
I heard you might as well skip them
and join the Four Wheels Club instead.
They've got a lot of girls!
Huh? Seriously?
Four Wheels Club?
I've never heard of that club.
Come to think of it, I saw some
skanky people making a lot of noise.
I think it was somewhere over there...
The NIT Four Wheels Club is
currently seeking new members!
Join now, and you'll
receive a free invitation to...
...our Welcome Party,
accompanied by all these ladies!
Count me in!
Me, too!
Since when do we have a club like this?
We'll have to give a
little extra effort, then!
Let's go, Den-chan!
I'm with you, Dai-chan!
They're just gonna drive away
even more people...
All right, then! I'll just give them
a boost with my sexual charm!
That's not what we need, either...
But we have an Auto Club.
Why are they doing this?
It's like a personal attack!
In order to get rid of
the Auto Club, that's why!
Aoshima!
A dingy club like yours is an
embarrassment to our institution.
I've established the
Four Wheels Club with...
...the intention of having
the Auto Club shut down.
Who you callin' dingy, hey?
We clean out our club room!
Yes, at least once a year...
I think the Auto Club
is a wonderful club!
Gotcha!
Then I'd like to propose a challenge...
Challenge?
Whichever club loses the next
Intercollegiate Rally agrees to break up.
How does that sound to you?
We accept your challenge.
Belldandy?
Are you quite sure? If you lose,
your club will have to disband.
Um, that's not...
I understand.
All right... may the best team win!
Certainly.
Hey, hold on a second!
Belldandy...
You don't have to worry. We won't lose.
She is absolutely right!
Our Auto Club cannot suffer defeat
at the hands of those newcomers.
Absolutely not!
But how can we race with no machine?
If we don't have one, we'll build one.
We don't have the parts.
We'll buy them!
But we have no money...
We've got the 500-yen savings
fund we started last year!
That disappeared somewhere,
cookie jar and all.
Morisato!
What?
Willpower!
UNDER CONSTRUCTION
We'll show them what
the Auto Club's made of!
I should've seen this coming...
Let's just do our best, Keiichi.
Hey, kiddo, it must be great to be young!
Betcha you don't get much sleep at
night if you're with a girl like that!
Huh?
But why wouldn't he get
much sleep if he's with me?
Uh... well...
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
You'll find it here.
All right, everyone
start looking around!
Right!
Thanks. You were a huge help to us.
If we can find the parts we need,
everything will work out okay.
Oh, really?
Yeah. At the very least,
I think we can enter the race.
But...
Yes?
We had to rely on your help after all.
But that's not true.
You came this far because everyone
in the Auto Club worked so hard!
But...
Eureka!
All right!
You see?
Listen, can I ask you something?
Certainly!
What made you take on the challenge?
No matter how you look at it,
the odds are against us.
That's true. The odds
may indeed be against us...
But you and Mr. Tamiya and
the others have such love for...
...the Auto Club, such reverence
for the old and used, and...
...you've come this far
without giving up.
I don't see how people like you could
ever lose. That's what I'd like to believe.
Belldandy...
Well, now, I can feel romance in the air!
Urd!
Keiichi, this is when you put
your arms around her shoulders!
Urd!
Come now, don't be so bashful!
Like this... see? It's not hard!
This is it, eh?
Oh my God!
Who the hell did this?
Come on, show yourself! I'll trash YOU!
My name is Belldandy.
In the name of the Shards of Glass,
reveal the identity of those...
...who skulk in the shadows!
How obvious is that?
Well, well! Whoever did
this showed no mercy!
Aoshima!
What are you doing here?
I was told that the Auto Club's
machine had been destroyed.
But, leaving it unguarded here
was practically...
...an invitation for someone to trash it!
You bastard!
Was it you who smashed up this car,
built with all our blood, sweat and tears?
Hold on, do you have a shred of
evidence that I committed this act?
Judging by the extent of the damage,
you have no hope of repairing it in time.
I suppose there's no way out of it.
Shall we forget about the challenge?
Do you really mean that?
Yes... but not without
any strings attached.
Morisato, you will apologize
to me right now, in front of everyone.
Do that, and we can just
forget about the challenge.
I know all I need to know
about your personality.
You're a coward who'd never rise to
a challenge if it seemed too foolhardy.
If your true colors are
exposed in front of Belldandy...
...she'll be sure to dump you in disgust!
I can't miss with this scenario.
What's it going to be?
It's a far better option than suffering
public humiliation in the race, is it not?
Morisato...
Forget it!
Keiichi?
We won't be defeated
by the likes of you!
Good for you, Morisato!
Damn right! You got that?
We'll let you off if
you apologize to us now.
Your bravado will prove worthless!
Keiichi...
No matter how hard you try,
there's no way...
W-What?
We will win this
contest, no matter what.
Kindly leave us now.
Please excuse me.
You were actually pretty cool just now.
You think so?
But losing's not an option
anymore, you know.
Because that guy really
made Belldandy angry.
Angry? Belldandy's angry?
She doesn't look mad...
Just watch this.
Belldandy?
Yes?
Oh, that's right!
I made lunch for all of you today, and...
Belldandy, about the race...
We shall win!
But with no car...
And no time...
We shall win!
We shall win no matter what!
You agree with me, don't you, Keiichi?
Uh... sure.
Now you know what the consequences
will be if you lose, don't you?
Y-Yes...
Go get 'em! I'll be cheering you on!
Show them how tough you are!
Keiichi! Win this thing, now!
Come on, Kei!
How's it looking?
Well, what do you want me to say?
It's no good!
Our adjustments are still incomplete.
We shouldn't be racing this thing!
Idiot!
The NIT Auto Club Off-Road Special
is in perfect condition!
We attached a front wheel system,
making this a Three-Wheel-Drive rig!
It has vented disc brakes as well as
an independent rear suspension...
...with gas-charged shocks.
We constructed the body
from lightweight FRP.
Not to mention this high-end
steering column and car stereo!
Plus this trendy vanity mirror
attached to the sun visor!
With all this, what else in
blue blazes could you ask for?
But this course is riddled
with extreme ups and downs.
And there are even sand dunes!
It would be suicidal to try and race
in an incomplete three-wheel rig like this!
No way is it incomplete!
Never mind.
I'll just have to compensate
with my driving...
But, Morisato!
I'll take it as far as I can.
We stayed up all night fixing this
machine. Our love will make it run.
That's the spirit, Morisato!
What are you doing?
Let's send you off with
our cheerleader dance!
So they managed to fix it in time, eh?
What are you going to do?
Not to worry.
I've planned for this contingency.
Blue Island here.
Put Plan A into action!
Roger.
Here we go!
It is now five minutes before the race.
All teams, start your engines!
Oh, no, I'm running late,
I'd better hurry!
It's locked!
Is there anyone there who can help me?
Where the heck is she? If she doesn't
show up before the race begins...
...we'll be disqualified.
Next, No. !
The Nekomi Institute of
Technology Four Wheels Club!
All right!
I've hired a professional
off-road racer for this race.
Of course, you guys will be
disqualified before the race starts!
Next, No. 16!
I don't see Belldandy!
NIT Auto Club!
What's going on?
No way...
He's up to something again!
Where are you, No. 16, NIT Auto Club?
You'll be disqualified!
What am I gonna do?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Belldandy!
No. 16, are you dropping out
of this race?
No, we're on our way now!
Impossible! How could she
have escaped from that trap?
That's what I've been saying all along!
She's a world-class escape artist.
Who does she think she's dealing with?
There are plenty more traps
where that came from!
Decrease average to 40 and go 50R to
the left and go to 70 once you're past it.
I would, but I can't tell
how fast I'm going!
Keiichi!
What the...
the steering wheel's suddenly...
This voice... it's the car's voice!
Your front wheel's about to go?
All right, then.
It's back to normal.
What next, Belldandy?
Right, you need to go right 100R.
Announcing checkpoint times
for Checkpoint No. 2!
Currently leading the pack is No. 4,
the NIT Four Wheels Club.
But of course...
In 2nd place, currently 10 minutes
behind, is the NIT Auto Club.
Despite having the smallest vehicle...
...thanks to their great chemistry,
they've managed to stay in 2nd place.
Damn those pesky bastards!
With that patched-up machine of theirs?
That guy's up to no good again, isn't he?
I'd better keep my eyes open!
They'll be here any second now.
Make sure they don't see you.
Roger!
It's the steering wheel this time!
It's fixed!
I've used too much power.
But we don't have much farther to go...
Belldandy, what's coming up next?
Belldandy?
Huh?
Ouch...
Belldandy? Belldandy!
Wake up, Belldandy!
Urd!
You really are high-maintenance,
you know that?
We're in big trouble!
Belldandy's...
I can see that.
She's fallen into her dormant state,
that's all.
What?
It looks like she used up a lot of power.
She's not waking up any time soon.
Power?
This clunker was on its last legs.
So she's been using her power
to keep it from breaking down.
Is that what was going on?
It's a shame, but at this point, I guess
you have no choice but to give up.
But you and the others have
such love for the Auto Club...
...such respect for the old and used, and
you've come this far without giving up.
I don't see how people like you could
ever lose. That's what I'd like to believe.
So what are you going to do, Keiichi?
No! I won't give up!
Because I know Belldandy
believes in me!
Attaboy!
Here's your reward.
Urd...
Morisato, what's going on?
Morisato here. Is that you, senior?
I'm at Point B8 right now.
Right, gotcha!
Morisato, turn right.
You must bear to your right!
Right?
Now passing the 3rd
and final checkpoint...
The NIT Four Wheels Club
remains in the lead!
The course is now buried
in sand due to strong winds.
The vehicle in 2nd place is trailing over
30 minutes behind. Hold on a minute!
This information just in...
Another machine can be seen
hurtling over the sand dunes!
Well, now! It's the NIT Auto Club!
What the... that's not possible!
All right!
Morisato!
But why would there be
a road like this here?
It's not a road...
it's a protective bulkhead.
Bulkhead?
There are bulkheads buried along
the coastline in this sand dune.
I see!
Only a three-wheeler can navigate
such a narrow path!
The race is yours to win now!
Right!
Oh my God!
Shit!
They've crossed the finish line!
1st Place, NIT Auto Club!
Dai-chan!
Den-chan!
Kei, you were awesome!
How the hell...
Why?
When are you gonna learn?
Keiichi would never lose to you!
Now then, time for me
to punish you again!
Hey, I didn't do anything!
Keiichi, how did the race go?
We won!
We owe it all to you,
Belldandy, for believing in us.
No, you won because
everyone played a part in it.
Yeah, I guess it's thanks to everyone!
Congratulations, Keiichi!
Belldandy...
Ah, such a romantic atmosphere!
All right, this is when you
put your face next to hers and...
Urd!
Come on, don't be so shy.
Stop it!
Urd!
Would it kill you to cling to each other?
One day when I woke up...
A day like any other...
another one just beginning.
There you are, yawning...
your face is still so sleepy.
Because each peaceful day
we share is a miracle to me.
This is where my heart
will always return...
Forever...
There's only one thing I wish for.
I chase after the same dream,
wherever it may go.
The love I feel for
you gives me strength.
May tomorrow be as joyful as today...
That's my wish...
A demon has been summoned
from the Dark Realm.
She's out for revenge on the goddesses,
changing the human into a strange form.
Next episode: Ah! The Demon
Arrives and Wreaks Havoc?
Huh? Don't tell me I'm gonna
be like this forever?