Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather will come
fluttering down, swaying gently in the air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
Well, we're heading into the homestretch
of the annual Miss NIT Pageant!
Our next candidate is Entry No. 16...
Please welcome the Junior Electronics
major, Miss Sayoko Mishima!
Height, 165cm.
Vital measurements, 85/60/86.
Give it up for last year's Miss NIT!
This contest is open to freshmen, too,
so why didn't you enter?
Come on! Belldandy's in
the contest, isn't she?
I have no intention of competing
against your girlfriend!
Hey, what do mean, girlfriend?
By the way, where's
that big sister of hers?
You mean Urd?
Probably watching from somewhere...
Lighten up, will you?
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
Hi there, boys and girls! How are you?
Fine!
Since when is she an NIT student, too?
Excuse me, you're cutting
into my performance time!
Holding a beauty pageant without
telling Lady Urd? Now that's a sin!
I'm the reigning Miss NIT!
I'll thank outsiders like you
to leave at once!
Ha! Queen at your level?
Not much of a contest, is it?
What do you mean?
You'll have to make yourself over for
the next 100,258 years before you can...
...even think of competing with me!
Isn't that right, everyone?
This is intense!
Oh, come on! Bigger isn't
always better, you know!
But it's better than nothing, no?
I happen to have a magnificent
physique, thanks to years of...
...jazz dance lessons and classical ballet!
Oh? Let's have a look...
The intruder has just crossed
the line with a flagrant foul!
Our time-honored Miss NIT Pageant is
in the greatest jeopardy of its history!
Don't you think you should stop her?
Probably.
Urd!
Well! Here's the frontrunner herself!
Mechanical Engineering...
...major, Belldandy!
You mustn't go out of turn...
...or else you'll cause
trouble for everyone else.
Did she have to say that
into the microphone?
She's naive about things like that.
You, too! Getting in my way...
You'll stop at nothing to
take over as queen, will you?
Hey, who are you to talk?
Do what you will...I'll win the title
of queen on the strength of my abilities!
Now then, prepare to be
dazzled by my lovely voice!
Start the music!
That's not my music!
Why are you playing enka?
Hey, why are you sleeping?
Oh, I'm sorry. My sister falls asleep
whenever she hears enka playing.
For heaven's sake!
Listen, you know perfectly well
that my song number is B13268!
How dare you subject me to enka!
I'll make you pay!
Hey, is Belldandy's sister a magician?
Urd, how could you do such a thing?
I had to punish them for making
me listen to that enka music.
Really!
Heed my call, O Spirit of the Wind...
The heavenly blessing that
vibrates through the air...
Let it rain down here where I stand.
Huh?
Rain?
It's a miracle!
We have just witnessed a miracle, folks!
Miss Belldandy has called on the
heavens to bless us with this rainfall!
Behold... she is the
Goddess of the Campus!
This is what they mean by
''dripping with feminine charm,'' no?
What have I done to deserve this?
Listen, who are those two, anyway?
Damn!
Oh, my...
Miss Belldandy is this year's Miss NIT!
Hold on! I don't think this is fair!
Congratulations, Miss Belldandy!
Thank you!
This isn't happening!
I refuse to accept this outcome!
Ah! The Queen and the Goddess' Secret
Hey, Urd, let's go home now, okay?
What do you mean?
The night is still so young!
Who knew they had such awesome
sake down here on Earth?
She seems to be fitting
in for some weird reason.
Yes!
Is Urd going to be all right,
drinking all that sake?
You don't have to
worry about my sister!
If we stick around any longer,
she's gonna make us drink too.
So why don't we go home?
Good idea.
For crying out loud...
That woman...
how can she hold her sake like that?
I'm...
...the Queen!
I'd rather die than
admit defeat to anyone!
Um... oh...
Ms. Mishima, are you all right?
Belldandy, give me a hand!
We should take her home.
What just happened?
All right!
Take care!
I know it wasn't just a dream...
I could've sworn
I was floating in mid-air.
Belldandy...
Who the hell is she, anyway?
Whoa, there goes Belldandy!
You know, this year's Miss NIT!
She sure is a beauty...
no wonder she's our campus queen!
Hi!
Hey, she's with Urd.
That Urd is so unbelievably sexy!
But look, there's Morisato, too.
Hey, which one's your type?
Let me see, of course Belldandy rules,
but there's something about Urd, too!
Yeah? Well, I'll take Belldandy any day!
Last year's campus queen isn't
such a hot item anymore, eh?
Toshiyuki!
Her popularity is tremendous.
And it's not just her, it's her sister, too.
They're totally mocking me!
Who is she, anyway?
She claims to be an exchange student,
but we have no idea where she's from.
True, she's wrapped in
far too many mysteries.
And that power she wields at times
is beyond human understanding.
You're right, it's certainly not normal.
She came with me to a hotel room, but
nothing happened. That's a first for me.
It really doesn't sit well!
Since when are you into
cheap girls like her?
Oh, so you lost your campus
queen crown to a cheap girl?
Forget that, don't you think we should
investigate that power of hers?
If we're going to do that,
we'll have to find out who she is first.
Belldandy's power...
If we can just find out Belldandy's
true identity, then the truth will come out.
Including who the real queen is...
So I guess you and I have
a common interest in this?
Well, things are starting to
get interesting around here.
Something always happens when Keiichi
Morisato faces some kind of danger.
In that case, we'll just
create our own danger for him.
Queen here. Start Operation Alpha!
Huh?
Look out!
All right, she's going
to use her powers!
Huh?
You saved me, Belldandy!
I'm glad that nothing
happened to you, Keiichi.
Start Operation Beta!
They can't get lucky twice...
Keiichi!
This time, for sure!
What the...
Was that rain?
I really couldn't say...
Operation Gamma! Bishop, you're up!
Go on! Use those powers of yours!
There, now. That's a good boy.
No way...
Thank you.
He was just about to attack us.
He looks fierce, but
he's really quite gentle.
Oh! Easy...
Where the heck did this dog
come from, anyway?
Those two have a secret... I just know it!
I think a change of strategy is in order.
But our opponent has such
formidable tactics at her disposal.
If we can't get to Belldandy herself,
we ask someone who knows her well.
I see what you mean!
That was great!
I'm so glad you enjoyed it!
Is there any more tea?
Here...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Looks like we're fresh out.
I'll go to the cafeteria
and ask them for some.
Let's put our plan into motion.
Don't mess it up!
Right!
Ignorance really is bliss, huh?
Don't you even see
what's going on around you?
There are two people trying to probe
Belldandy's identity, even as we speak.
What?
I know she can take care of herself,
but you really need to watch your back.
After all, you're her one vulnerability.
I'm Belldandy's vulnerability?
When it comes to you, she seems
to lose sight of everything else.
In both a good way
and a bad way, that is.
Really?
It's high time you learned
to see things like that, okay?
Okay...
Hey, listen, Urd...
Why are you sleeping on me?
Keiichi! Sorry to keep you waiting!
Keiichi...
Urd! What on earth happened?
What do you mean?
Where did Keiichi go?
Are you perhaps wondering
where Morisato is?
It's you!
What a lame thing to do!
And how lame of you to fall for it...
Do you know where Keiichi is?
We've taken him into our custody.
What are you talking about?
I want to know who you are...
your true identity!
True identity?
But I'm not hiding anything!
So you're going to feign
ignorance until the end...
Not that such devilish
behavior doesn't turn me on.
Why did you kidnap Keiichi?
First, I want you to tell me.
Why did you blow me off when
it was you who came on to me?
What does he have that I don't?
I'm the better man in both looks and
money! I'm superior in every way!
That has nothing to do
with a person's worth.
But if you insist on going out with
that guy, you'll have no future!
Do you think you'd
actually still be happy with him?
It's not my happiness...
But Keiichi's happiness...
that's all I hope for in this world.
I think this conversation's over.
Belldandy, just leave this to me.
You go look for Keiichi.
Thank you, Urd!
All right, it looks like I'll have to
teach you a lesson!
Keiichi's pulse...
No good, I can't even
hear his heartbeat.
Oh, it's you!
What, you say you just saw Keiichi?
Yes, all right!
See you later!
Keiichi, I'll be there soon...
What's going on?
Oh, you're awake.
What do you think you're doing?
I have a lot of questions for you.
If that's all, then you didn't
have to be so drastic!
It's not you I want to ask about.
It's about Belldandy.
Huh?
Yes, that's right. He's not very tall...
I thought she was suspicious back when
I tried to find out if she really was...
...an exchange student.
Using mysterious powers...
falsifying her registration records...
What's her motive? Is this how badly
she craved my campus queen status?
Don't tell me she infiltrated this school
to threaten me, the daughter of a CEO!
I told you! You're thinking too hard!
She's just an exchange student,
nothing more!
Well, I never expected you
to give it up that easily.
What do you mean?
But you're going to tell me
the truth about her today.
What?
He was with a gaudy-looking girl?
Yes... yes...
Did you say that way?
Thank you very much!
Are you ready to receive your
punishment?
You're the one who
should be bracing herself!
I asked you to please stay with me...
What the...
How do you like it? I've dominated
many an enka contest with this voice!
It's a lullaby for you. Just listen to my
skillful tremolo and tremble in your sleep!
Do you mind living in a six-mat room?
It's not enough to take me out!
You're tougher than I thought.
All right, then! How's this?
Roar, O Atmosphere!
Dammit!
You'd better not cross me or
you won't live to regret it!
Yes, so you say they took him to
the lecture hall, is that right?
Augh! Stop it!
It's so gross!
So? Are you enjoying these live
escargot snails imported from France?
Stop it, please!
Then tell me!
That power she used... what is it for?
Why did she come here?
It's a misunderstanding!
Don't you remember how drunk
you were?
Oh, my, you're stubborn.
Then, it's time to play my trump card.
What the hell are you gonna do now?
Something that'll be more painful for you
than if you were being tortured yourself.
Thank you very much.
See you later.
Keiichi, I'm on my way now.
Well, I see you played
right into our hands.
You're going down!
Really? I wonder if it'll be that easy?
Gorge yourself on the
pleasures of slumber!
I asked you to please stay with me...
Huh? Why aren't you falling asleep?
Ear plugs?
Ow!
This is the proper way to use whips!
Stop it!
Please, stop!
It looks like this is more effective on you.
There!
Do you realize how valuable these are?
I told you... tell me her true identity
and I'll stop right now.
It's no good, I've got
to protect Belldandy.
What ''true identity''? I'm telling you,
she's just an exchange student!
I guess I have no choice, then.
Here's our next victim.
But that's... not the Micropet Debonair!
Wow! You really know your cars.
Of course I know this one!
It's mankind's treasure!
It was released in 1964 and the
manufacturer went bankrupt in a year!
Another manufacturer took over
the model and re-launched it under...
...a different brand name, but the
original, boxed models are rare!
Oh, really?
Do you have any idea
how much this is worth?
Of course I do! Who do you think I am?
I'm the daughter of the
Mishima Group's CEO, Sayoko Mishima!
I can't believe you'd hold
out this long against me...
You need to stop stonewalling me!
Hey, wait, don't do it, Sayoko!
Farewell, mankind's treasure.
Stop it!
Belldandy!
How did she find us?
What's Toshiyuki doing?
Still, this room is impenetrable.
There's no way she can get in.
Now then, start talking!
Tell me Belldandy's true identity!
I told you! She's an exchange student!
What the...
Keiichi!
Thank goodness you're safe!
Thank you, Belldandy, but...
Who are you?
Who in the world?
I am a goddess.
You told me that before.
Prove it to me, then.
Miss Sayoko!
I see you took care of your end, too.
How are we going to cover this one up?
No problem!
Just leave it to Urd!
O Bacchus, God of Wine.
Resurrect yourself now...
...and bring them joy and
the blessings of the earth.
Enough to drown them!
What did you just do?
I just thought I'd make sure
their dreams were happy ones, see...
Forgive me for startling you,
Miss Sayoko.
Ouch...
What the hell happened?
Do I have a hangover?
But what am I doing here?
Belldandy, you'll have to do
better than this to fool me.
Take care!
Ow... What a headache!
One day when I woke up...
A day like any other...
another one just beginning.
There you are, yawning...
your face is still so sleepy.
Because each peaceful day
we share is a miracle to me.
This is where my heart
will always return...
Forever...
There's only one thing I wish for.
I chase after the same dream,
wherever it may go.
The love I feel for you
gives me strength.
May tomorrow be as joyful as today...
That's my wish...
One man falls for the goddess, and has
plans to monopolize her.
But the underhanded tactics of this man
only serve to enrage the goddess.
Next episode:
Ah! Can the Auto Club Triumph?
I thought this was a rally...
what's with the three-wheeler?