Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather will come
fluttering down, swaying gently in the
air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as l've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
O Light of Protection,
I summon you now...
Create a protective wall around us.
Immortal Wall!
Ah! Always By Your Side...
We're safe now, since he
won't be able to come inside...
But why is Midgard attacking us?
That was a good nap!
What's all the commotion, anyway?
Urd!
Thank goodness! You're back to
normal!
Belldandy...
Why did you break your power limiter?
The Almighty said he'd
let it go just this once.
And look at all this...
what in the world happened here?
You mean you don't remember?
Remember what?
Here we go again...
What?
The reason the amusement park's
a mess and the sky's so dark...
...and the whole city's in an uproar...
all that, all that, all that is your fault,
Urd!
Maybe, but I don't remember a thing.
I'd say about half of it is my fault.
Midgard!
So is your emotional reunion over yet?
What is that giant snake?
I am not Midgard.
Huh?
I am the Lord of Terror and I am also
the Ultimate Destruction Program.
Could it be...he got infected?
I see, so the program's
self-replicating...
Excuse me...I don't have
any idea what's going on.
Even if the vaccine
deletes the host program...
...it can still survive by self-replicating
and sneaking into another file.
Actually, what I want to know is
what happened before all of that?
Correct!
So long as I continue to self-reproduce,
no one will ever destroy me!
Behold!
The Gate of the Netherworld!
I know it's the gate connecting
this world to the world of the demons.
But I'm sure the Almighty sealed it!
That's right.
But once I've breached that cursed seal,
what do you suppose will happen?
The demons will be coming!
Precisely!
We demons will be able to infiltrate
this world without a catalyst!
It will truly become
a world of darkness!
Can you imagine how easy it will be to
increase our dominance here on Earth?
Urd!
Belldandy...I want you
to take down the barrier.
I don't know who you are,
and what happened here...
...but the one thing I know is that
you tried to harm my precious sisters!
The hell with my license suspension!
I'm going to strike him down myself!
Descend, Exploding Thunder!
Huh?
He drained all of your power
before you woke up.
Oh...
A creature like that...he's not
worthy of being smited by me.
Skuld! Take him out right now!
Who, me?
Oh, man! What choice do I have?
Take that!
Whoa, look at him burn!
Hey, Skuld...got anything else to toss?
I'll make you cry...
I'll make you scream!
She's not that different now than
when she was the Lord of Terror.
Listen, Belldandy...
What?
Something's not right.
If he just wants to break the seal,
he could just do it in secret somewhere.
Come to think of it,
you're right about that.
There's another thing, too.
We're the ones standing in his way...
but he's not attacking us!
Could it be that he needs some kind
of power in order to break the seal?
Uh-oh!
Look, Skuld, isn't there
any way to delete him?
Didn't you read the instruction
manual for the flute?
Of course, you only have to look
at the manual when you get stuck...
You're wrong about that.
This is the problem with techies!
I think this is it!
We're counting on you!
Right.
Here...line 3, right?
Belldandy! You can do it!
Right!
Damn you, you're not going
to play that flute, are you?
Forgive me, Midgard.
But your fate was always deletion.
Wait, let me just explain myself!
Curses! I won't let you
get away with this!
I pray for the salvation
of their souls...
I'm...I'm getting sucked in!
I've got to...I've got
to transfer myself over!
Aha! That's it!
Dammit!
Look out!
Curses!
Keiichi!
Keiichi! Keiichi, are you all right?
More or less.
Keiichi...
Come on, we'd better get out
of here before someone comes.
Yes.
So beautiful...
Take a look at this horrific sight.
Due to an explosion of unknown origin
that occurred just before dawn...
...the area around Yokohama Bay
has been completely destroyed.
Really, they're making
such a big deal out of it.
Can you blame them?
We didn't have time to put
everything back to normal.
Let's go tidy up properly
later on, all right?
Yes, Big Sister!
What?
I haven't yet died, you see.
Keiichi? What are you talking about?
This body now belongs
to the Lord of Terror...
...and Midgard's flute
is now in my clutches!
There is no longer anything
you goddesses can do to stop me!
Keiichi!
What's wrong? I'm right here.
Go on, attack me from any direction!
Stop it!
Please, stop it!
Why?
Why did you have to take Keiichi?
Why didn't you infect me
instead, Lord of Terror?
This means...
Someone's about to descend.
What?
Are you going to kill my hostage
along with me? Almighty One?
Who ever thought one the Battle Wings
would descend?
Lind!
Why are you here?
I was ordered by Yggdrasil to
annihilate the Lord of Terror.
We cannot risk allowing the demons...
...to take over this world, just
to save the life of one human.
I'm here to put an end to this struggle.
What's the matter?
Why won't you go on the offensive?
Do you really believe you
can parry my attack forever?
Belldandy!
Big Sister!
Looks like you're finished.
No matter what it takes...
I will protect Keiichi!
Are you saying that you'll even
defy an order from Yggdrasil?
Even if it means losing my life...
I will protect him!
I take it there'll be
no changing your mind...
Belldandy!
Keiichi!
Damn him...his mind's been
taken over, yet he still resists!
Whoa.
I think I understand now
what makes you stay here.
Lind!
That being the case, I'll just wait
until the time comes.
But the next time I'm summoned,
I'm not going to hold back.
What could be better?
Almighty, send in your
Valkyries or whatever you want!
Because now I've got
the ultimate shield!
Not again.
Maybe I should find a new medium
to transfer over to soon.
Uh-oh! It's the Gate of
the Netherworld again!
Hey! The little squirt there!
What do you want?
You're going to make me
a 10-Dimensional Scythe!
And what are you going to do with that?
The chains that bind the Gate of the
Netherworld are 10-dimensional, so...
Why don't you make it yourself?
Because a seal made by the gods can
only be broken by an instrument...
...made by the gods.
Well, I don't want to do it!
That's what I thought you'd say.
How about this?
Hey, look! One blow and he'll die!
Hey, no fair!
Is there anything I can
use to do my calculations?
I guess this is it!
Well, I guess it is a type
of digital calculator...
So this gets carried over...
And this gets moved over here
and this is the result!
And that means that...
Done!
Wait, I'm not supposed
to be happy about this.
When all's said and done, she's just
wallowing in the joy of creation again.
What do you think of this?
Hmm...well done!
Now then, here's a question for you all.
After opening this gate,
what am I going to do?
You're going to summon all the
demons.
Nice try! But you're only half-correct.
Humans and demons can
never co-exist, after all.
Therefore, I shall turn this world into a
paradise for demons and reign as king!
But, no!
What about the people on Earth?
I have no use for them,
not in my world, at least.
Belldandy! We have no choice now!
I can't!
I understand how you feel...
...but we can't pick Keiichi over
the rest of the world, can we?
I can't!
It'll be all over if he cuts the chains!
Keiichi!
All right, then! I'm gonna
start cutting! Here I go!
Belldandy!
Big Sister!
I can't! I can't bring myself to do it!
Belldandy!
From here on in, I'm
going to rule this world!
What the...
What do you think you're doing?
I'll take Keiichi's place...
So please, let Keiichi go free!
Big Sister!
Belldandy, get out of my way!
If I kill the Lord of Terror, the Gate
of the Netherworld will disappear, too.
I don't care what happens to me...
Just save Keiichi...
Please, you've got to just save Keiichi!
Well, that's what I was after all along.
After all, a human body is no
vessel for the Lord of Terror.
Belldandy!
Lind...
Once he's possessed me, I want you
to annihilate me along with him.
Belldandy...
Keiichi...
I can't keep my promise to you
anymore.
I'm sorry.
Big Sister! Stop it!
Skuld!
Look at that!
Something's repelling
the Lord of Terror.
What the...
I see...since they're based on different
pulses, he can't infect a goddess.
That's it!
You mean I can't transfer
myself to her body?
At this rate,
I'm going to lose the body.
I've got to find another medium!
Lucky!
This is what they mean by
''A sight for the gods!''
I'm so glad that I got to meet you.
I'll never forget you, ever.
Keiichi!
Belldandy!
It's all right now.
The Lord of Terror has severed himself.
Keiichi's going to be all right.
Thank goodness!
I'm so happy...
I'm so happy...Keiichi!
The question now is how am I going to
transfer to the next host.
Hey! What the hell are you doing?
Now you can't ever escape!
No!
Listen, did you know?
If you subject a disk to a powerful
magnetic force, it'll erase all the data.
You...you wouldn't!
Oh yes I would!
No! Please don't erase me! Help!
Huh? Am I home?
Huh? What am I doing wearing this?
I'm responsible for allowing
the seal to be broken.
The seal was broken?
No, regardless of the outcome...
...the fact remains that you
did destroy the Lord of Terror.
The only thing is...since the main
system is still down and...
...the subsystem is running both in safe
mode and as proxy for the seal...
...all of Yggdrasil's functions
have more or less been halted.
That means...
Correct.
To all intents and purposes, all duties
pertaining to goddess contracts...
...and all records of
work-related penalties...
...all of the aforementioned
have been erased.
No kidding! You mean my license
suspension's out the window, too?
This isn't anything to be glad about!
Oh...sorry.
That's all I have to report.
You may either escape under your
own power, or else remain here.
I'm going to leave it up to you to decide.
Escape?
Don't tell me that Belldandy's...
Now then, I'll be on my way.
Lind, I wish you wouldn't be
in such a hurry to go back.
Well, I may be a Combat Specialist,
but I don't want to be insensitive.
Keiichi!
Belldandy...
I wonder what Big Sister's going to do?
Hey, that's a question we probably
don't even need to ask!
Was she one of those Valkyries
you told me about?
Yes.
That was Lind...
We owe her our lives.
So...uh...
What about the contract being voided?
Yes.
Because the contract you and I
signed has been voided...
...that means that I no longer
have a duty to fulfill it.
I thought so...
So what are you going to do now?
Are you going back to Heaven?
No...
It's true that the contract
has been voided.
But you see...that's not the only
reason I've stayed here until now.
Huh?
You showed me, a goddess, how
wonderful it is to live as a human.
And you also taught me about
feelings that I've never felt before!
That's why I've decided to stay on here,
even if the contract no longer exists.
Because...
...I love you.
You taught me a lot, too...
and I'm really grateful for that.
That's why...
...from here on in...
...I want you to always be by my side.
One day when I woke up...
A day like any other...
another one just beginning.
There you are, yawning...
your face is still so sleepy.
Because each peaceful day
we share is a miracle to me.
This is where my heart
will always return...
Forever...
There's only one thing I wish for.
I chase after the same dream,
wherever it may go.
The love I feel for you
gives me strength.
May tomorrow be as joyful as today...
That's my wish...