Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather comes fluttering
down, swaying gently in the air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
Oh, crap...
What's the matter?
I forgot to bring the materials
for my presentation today.
That really blows.
Did you leave them in your room?
Uh-huh, I put it all together
in a pile last night and...
I'll go fetch them for you.
Huh?
Hey! Wait a minute!
Belldandy?
What's he up to?
Will she be all right?
Ah! Living Under One Roof Together
Oh, whatever. If she can't find it,
she'll just come back, right?
Look at you, Morisato. Did
Belldandy dump you or something?
No, she didn't.
Huh? Did you get dumped?
No, for god's sake!
What's up, you had a fight
with Bell-chan?
Can I sit by myself for a second?
Why is everybody reacting this way?
Ahem.
What's the problem, Morisato?
You look depressed.
Hey, where's Belldandy?
So now you're joining in, too.
Belldandy's just...
Lucky you, Morisato. Getting yourself
such a good-looking girlfriend!
such a sweet girlfriend!
But, uh, Belldandy and I are...
What the...
Is it possible?
You've already gone that far?
Dai-chan!
Den-chan!
We'll gladly bear the responsibility of
finding the right name for your child!
You said it!
Wait a second, will you?
This is not to be taken lightly...
We'll get back to you after
giving it some serious thought.
Just leave it to us!
A name...
What kind of name...
I don't believe those two!
Hey, that was pretty quick...
Whoops! Miss Mishima?
Good morning, Mr. Morisato.
Good morning.
How unusual for you not
to be with Belldandy...
Oh, well, I left something at home,
and she went back to get it for me.
At home? You mean, your home?
Yeah, I guess you could say that.
See, I just got kicked out of the dorm.
So you live alone now?
Well, uh, not alone, actually...
Huh?
Don't tell me that...
I didn't tell you?
I had no idea that you and Belldandy
were that involved already!
What?
Come on! Keep your
voice down, will you?
But, is it true?
Well, I guess you could say it is.
She looks so sweet, but she's
as bold as the next person...
But look, we just live together, that's all.
There's really nothing going on.
What? Nothing going on?
You've got to be kidding me!
There's nothing to kid about, and
besides, I think you got the wrong idea.
Belldandy and I are just...
You two are?
Well, see, you know...
How should I put it...
I don't believe you! You're not
in grade school anymore!
I just want to take it slow...
not jump into things.
With an attitude like that...
...you'll never have a relationship with a
girl except in your dreams!
Still, considering you once dared to
make a bid for me, that girl should be...
...child's play for you.
You really think so?
The first thing you have to do is
tell her how you really feel.
For the rest, you can come up
with it on your own, can't you?
True, exactly what kind of
relationship are we in right now?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
That was pretty quick of you, huh?
Yes. I wasn't sure which ones you
needed, so I brought everything.
Oh, thanks.
They're heavy, so please take care.
Sure, I'll be fine.
Hey, listen...
What is it?
Um, the thing is... you and me...
Oh, never mind, it's nothing.
Keiichi?
The engine evolved as the double-valve
system and was gradually improved.
Early engines used direct exhaust
valves with camshafts, valves...
...and dual exhaust ports all
residing within the engine block.
She is pretty cute, huh?
She did say she'd stay
with me forever, but...
...that's just because of her
contract as a goddess, isn't it?
Well, no, not necessarily!
Belldandy hasn't shown any signs
that she doesn't want to be with me.
I really wish I could find out for sure.
...tell her how you really feel.
Keiichi? Keiichi?
That's it. This is something that I
have to take the initiative on, right?
Tell Belldandy that I lo... lo...
You got that, Morisato?
Love her!
Oh, please!
So you love cylinder heads
to that extent, do you?
Y-Yes...
Jeez, what's he thinking?
I had to go and do it, didn't I?
I made a complete fool of myself!
But the thing is, I really
am in love with Belldandy.
If I can just tell her how I feel,
and all goes well...
Belldandy....
Keiichi...
No, wait, come on. We are
living together, after all...
We can do something more mature.
Keiichi.
Huh?
I've warmed up the bed for you!
Oh, uh, thanks.
No, that's not right! I don't
have those depraved thoughts!
All I want...
All I want is for Belldandy
to go out with me.
All right, then!
But how do I do this?
What am I supposed to say?
Should I just be straightforward
and ask her to go out with me?
But that didn't work with Miss
Mishima...
Actually, isn't what I'm doing just
another form of ''night-creeping''?
Oh, man, what should I do?
If it was going to come to this...
...why didn't I just wish for her
to be my girlfriend from the start?
But no...
How could I shackle Belldandy
with a wish like that?
No other way but to go tell her myself...
Aww, I can't do it after all.
Next, this just in...
Late last night there was...
Were you working on another report?
Yeah, that's right.
I got so much done, see...
Hey, this is really good!
I'm glad to hear that.
But, since you have no classes today...
...I wish you'd slept in a
little longer this morning.
Yeah.
I guess I can take a nap later on.
Would you like to go on
a museum tour with me?
I'm sorry.
That would be a breach of contract.
Keiichi?
You have a call from Mr. Tamiya.
Oh, I must've fallen asleep, huh?
Thank God it was just a dream!
He said he had something
important to talk to you about.
Huh?
I can't believe he was really
thinking up names for our kid.
Keiichi! Dinner will be ready soon.
So please wait.
Uh, sure.
She's good-looking, she's sweet,
and she's a great cook...
What else could a guy ask for?
But if I confess my feelings
and it doesn't work out...
Forgive me, Keiichi!
Oh, crap! What should I do?
I'm gonna give it a shot.
Because I never want to lose
sight of that smile of hers!
Easier said than done, though...
what should I do?
I guess it would be better
to take the right steps...
But I got laughed at when I tried
to go out with Miss Mishima.
And it's not like I have all
these techniques at my disposal...
Techniques?
It's got to be around here somewhere!
Uh... lemme see...
Was it this box?
I could've sworn...
Damn, the seniors just
dumped it all in every which way!
Hold it... hold it... found it!
The ''Surefire Techniques for Love''
how-to book I bought ages ago!
Now I'm all set!
Kiss Belldandy?
Kisu? Would you like
kisu fish for your dinner?
Forget it... forget it!
Cleaning up?
Yeah, that's right!
Then I'll help you later on, all right?
Dinner will be ready soon.
It won't be much longer!
Man, I knew it...
I'm nowhere near the kissing stage yet.
Confess your feelings at a restaurant
that has a beautiful night view...
Sir?
I'm afraid our establishment requires
formal wear for all its patrons.
Well, we can just
have dinner right here.
So that's a pass.
You should confess in
a romantic environment...
...with beautiful music
playing in the background.
Keiichi?
I should've known that was
too much to ask of this place!
Not exactly what you'd
call romantic, huh? Wait!
That's it!
Found 'em!
Candles
Well, better than nothing...
And I need some romantic music.
Heavy metal, Western pop singers,
stand-up comedy, rakugo...
...and unidentifiable folk music.
Damn, I guess I'm not
the romantic type of guy!
Keiichi?
B-Belldandy!
Keiichi, are you not feeling well?
Belldandy, come to think of it, you can
read peoples' minds, can't you?
Yes.
Damn! That means my plans to
confess were all for nothing!
Although I can only see your
emotions as different colors.
And I have to really look for it, too.
Is that right?
Yes.
An angry person appears to be red...
blue when he's sad...
I can see it as a
vague whirlpool of colors.
Oh, no, Keiichi seems a bit blue.
Now he's back to yellow.
My powers as a goddess have been...
...significantly limited. I no longer need
to serve as an emotional antenna.
Is that right?
That's all I need to know!
Dinner is ready now,
so please come to the table!
I'll be right there, so
just hold on a second!
Okay... um...
What's this?
I didn't know I had this...
Oh, I know, it must be the seniors'.
It got thrown in by mistake.
Great, this is perfect!
I see orange, he's a bit excited...
...or nervous?
Um, Keiichi,
is something the matter?
Huh? No, nothing's the matter.
What a lovely song.
Yeah.
Keiichi is all yellow
with joy now. I'm so glad!
This is no time to be eating!
Belldandy...
Yes?
Uh... could you come with me
somewhere?
My, how lovely!
I'm all set to go now!
All I have to do now is tell Belldandy
how I feel about her!
What is this? My seniors
setting me up again?
What was I thinking,
going by that how-to book?
What's wrong with just being myself?
Blue...
Did something happen
to make Keiichi sad?
Wait, now he's orange again.
B-Belldandy...
Yes?
Uh, the thing is...
I know it must sound weird to say this
when we're living together...
...but I just want to be
up front about everything.
I have something I want to tell you!
Heart rate 150 bpm, blood pressure 170!
And still on the rise...
His temperature's 101! This is terrible!
Belldandy?
Keiichi, you must rest now!
No, wait, I'm not sick...
Please don't talk now.
Your pulse is racing and you have a
fever. Your blood pressure's surging!
Your face is red and you're sweating.
This is what they call illness, isn't it?
I told you, I'm not sick!
I'm starting to lose consciousness...
Dammit, I can't let this stop me from...
I've got to...
...tell Belldandy!
Belldandy!
Belldandy...
Yes?
This has nothing to do
with the contract, okay?
Just like any guy and girl, I want you
to go out with me, see...
Keiichi!
So that's why you've been acting
so strange since yesterday.
Keiichi...
It's true that I came
to you on a mission from...
...the Heavenly System.
But there is no more deceit in
my feelings than there is in yours.
I want you to be happy, Keiichi!
And that's more than a feeling...
it is my own wish for you.
Sure...
I should've seen it from the start.
Whether we go out, or don't go out,
or how it looks to other people...
It doesn't really matter,
because after all, Belldandy...
Let's go, then, Belldandy!
All right!
...is going to stay with me forever!
One day when I woke up...
A day like any other...
another one just beginning.
There you are, yawning...
your face is still so sleepy.
Because each peaceful day
we share is a miracle to me.
This is where my heart
will always return...
Forever...
There's only one thing I wish for.
I chase after the same dream,
wherever it may go.
The love I feel for you
gives me strength.
May tomorrow be as joyful as today...
That's my wish...
The young girl has left her hometown
to make a new start in a new land.
Not knowing that she might shatter the
peaceful life of a goddess and a human!
Next episode:
Ah! A Blessing in Every Bargain?
What? We have to go
house-hunting again?