Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather comes fluttering
down, swaying gently in the air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
A wish?
Yes.
I have come here from Heaven to grant
you a wish, Mr. Keiichi Morisato, sir.
Let's see, I was trying to
call Aoyama, wasn't I?
I got connected to some weird place
and a girl appeared out of that mirror...
...telling me she'll grant me a wish.
Wait, come to think of it,
who'd she come out of the mirror?
Not only that,
but she's calling herself a goddess...
Is something the matter?
Allow me to introduce myself again.
I'm with the Goddess Help Line...
Goddess 1st Class, 2nd Category,
Unlimited License. My name, Belldandy!
H-Hello, I'm Keiichi Morisato.
Ah! Those Who Believe Shall Find
Salvation!
Have some tea.
I've never had a girl over before,
so this is all I can offer you...
That's wonderfully kind of you... Oh!
Here... this is my card.
What kind of business would a
goddess like you have with me?
We goddesses have a mission,
which is to do what we can to...
...rescue those in distress,
like yourself.
So what brought you here?
I am here at the request
of Mr. Keiichi Morisato, sir.
Request? I don't remember
making any request...
I did receive your phone call.
Oh, that? That was a wrong number!
I was just trying to...
Up in Heaven...
...we watch over all of the lives
being led in this world.
Needless to say, that includes you,
Mr. Keiichi Morisato.
Your fortitude in the
face of misfortune...
Your kindness towards others...
This is truly worthy
of the highest praise!
But it's nothing special, really!
The balance between your fortune
and misfortune has been so lopsided...
...that it has exceeded all limits.
As a result, this triggered
Yggdrasil into action.
You have earned the right
to receive Heaven's Grace.
What do you mean by ''Grace''?
It means that your wish will be granted.
My wish?
However, keep in mind that
you will be limited to just one wish.
Only one?
Yes. I can grant you
anything you desire.
Well, this is so sudden...
And only one wish, for that matter...
Now then, please tell me
what you wish for!
So I get just one wish, huh?
I wonder if I can ask
for something like...
If your wish is to become wealthy,
we will be happy to...
...bestow riches upon you,
more than you could ever use...
...in an entire lifetime.
Huh?
And should you desire the
destruction of the world, we can make...
...that happen as well.
Destruction of the world?
However, we would never appear before
anyone with that sort of wish in mind.
You want me to believe your story?
You're not from some
New Age religious cult...
...out to swindle me into buying
an expensive vase, are you?
I would never utter such
falsehoods to you. Or rather...
...we goddesses do not tell lies
under any circumstances.
Are you saying you can't
even tell the smallest lie?
Yes.
Then, tell me, do you think I'm cool?
Yes!
See, you can lie, after all...
But what I just said wasn't a lie...
Thanks. You're really nice.
I knew it!
The seniors must've
cooked this up to make...
...fun of me because
I've never had a girlfriend.
No.
I do not understand.
You mean you can read my mind?
Yes, but what I don't understand is
why you, Mr. Keiichi Morisato...
...have never had a girlfriend.
Could you stand up for a minute?
All right.
Now you get it, don't you? Five foot
three just doesn't cut it nowadays...
Just because someone's tall
doesn't mean that he's attractive.
Aside from these overly thick
eyebrows, I have a forgettable face...
That is what makes you unique.
I think it becomes you!
That's the sum of my entire fortune...
and it's not long after New Year's Day!
That's pretty lame, huh?
How uncool is that?
One's financial status must never
be equated with one's worth.
I do not believe one is less attractive as
a person because he has no money.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Clearly you have some kind of complex
about your outward appearance, but...
What exactly does that have
to do with a person's worth?
You possess something of great value...
For example, look...
Love that's bursting at the seams...
Old though they may be, and though no
one would give them a second look...
...they're all in perfect working order.
The sound of the monitor turning on...
The sound of the video heads turning...
These are all such happy sounds...
They know that you will use them and
that they are fortunate to be here...
And it is all because you do not
judge them by looks or capacity...
Because you shower them
with such affection!
Uh, then... I guess I'll tell you
what I want you to grant me.
So you've reached
a decision, have you?
I'd like a goddess like you...
Yes?
...to always...
...stay by my side.
I know, I know. I guess that was
a rude thing to say to someone...
...I just met,
even if you are a goddess...
Huh?
Wait, I just said that for the heck of it!
Keiichi, sir!
Thank God! Are you all right?
Yes.
Huh!
Oh, no!
Excuse me, I need to borrow your
phone.
Hello? This is Belldandy speaking...
Yes. The wish that was
just submitted now...
What? You mean that's
a viable request, too?
But, wait... Almighty One!
''Almighty One''?
What's going on with my phone,
anyway?
Your wish has been duly granted.
So my wish is going to come true.
That's good... good to hear...
Huh?
They granted my wish...
for you to always stay with me?
Yes.
That means that I can stay with you
forever, Mr. Keiichi Morisato, sir!
What!
Is that true?
They accepted that wish of mine?
Yes.
Everything has been duly processed.
This will allow me to stay by your side
forever, Mr. Keiichi Morisato.
That means you're going
to be living with me?
Yes.
There are some days I'll be at college.
I don't have any money!
Are you okay with being poor?
Yes.
Plus, I'm gonna have to work part-time.
By my side...
A goddess always by my side?
That wouldn't be what they
call cohabitating, would it?
I'm actually going to live
under the same roof as a girl?
I've made your
favorite dish tonight...
You know what I love more than
anything?
It's you!
Don't tease me like that, Keiichi, sir!
Wait a sec, shouldn't
we go on a date first?
Take a romantic spin along
the beach or something...
I got this bike just so
I could take you for a ride!
Oh, my! How lovely!
Let us go, and gaze upon
the sunset at the beach!
Hold up. She's a goddess,
so it should be more like...
I obtained this broom just for you!
Now let's take it to go
see the sunset at the beach!
Keiichi Morisato, sir?
Did you just read my mind now, too?
Yes.
I guess it's for real, then.
I'm going to live with a goddess!
But how can I make her live in
a dinky 6-mat room like this?
Will I be hit with divine retribution?
Huh?
Well, that should do it, don'tcha think?
All right, let's go.
Oh my gosh!
If the seniors find out about this...
What is the matter?
Women aren't allowed in this dorm!
Oh, that shouldn't be a problem.
After all, I'm a goddess!
But that's not the point!
I need you to get out of this room!
But there will be trouble...
No, no, no...
There will be even more trouble
if the seniors find out about you!
But the System Force takes effect
whenever wishes are granted...
...and there's no defying it.
The System Force?
It is something that
I am powerless to stop.
If you insist on resisting it, then
I'm afraid you'll only come to grief.
What kind of grief?
Is it even more terrible than
going against the seniors' orders?
Morisato!
Did you hold down the fort?
It looks like the Force
has already come into play.
Morisato!
Yes, sir!
Morisato! You little bastard,
how dare you sneak a woman into...
...our male-only sanctuary
and then push her to the floor!
I trust you're prepared
to face the music for this.
But there are all these
circumstances, see...
He who dares break the dorm rules...
Gets thrown out!
It's human mikoshi time!
Carry him out, men!
Wasshoi! Wasshoi! Wasshoi!
Wasshoi! Wasshoi!
Uh, why am I not surprised?
I get it now.
The System Force kicks in when the
two of us are about to get torn apart.
Yes.
Wait, there's a problem.
My bike has been acting up lately...
Huh?
Now where did I leave
the keys to my bike? Uh...
Morisato!
It's your reward for holding down
the fort! We fixed it for you!
This is a new chapter in your life!
So we're sending you off in style!
Right!
We'll send the rest of your stuff as
soon as you find a new place, got that?
Now then, what the heck
should we do now?
Forgive me.
You have been evicted from your dorm
because of me, Keiichi Morisato.
We'll figure something out!
By the way...
Could you call me something other
than Keiichi Morisato or ''sir''?
I cannot grant such a wish, you have
already been granted one just now.
Oh, that's right.
But I think I'll give you an
extra bonus, just this once!
Keiichi!
Let's hit the road!
All right!
Well, he's gone now.
Uh-huh.
A man's not a man until he sets off
on a journey like this, right?
Uh-huh.
Can we crash at your place tonight?
Great timing!
If I can just keep going 'til morning...
Good luck, Keiichi!
He's got a girl with him...
Don't worry, that guy's easy pickings.
You said it! That Morisato's got
a lot of nerve...
Let's rob him for all he's got
in front of his girl!
I win!
I've cleaned up...
She's my Goddess
of Fortune, you see...
Sleep on the street, jerk!
Hey, did you do something in there?
No...
Listen, I need a favor from you.
Hey!
Hasegawa!
At least hear me out, will you?
Could you put her up, just for tonight?
You come to my door at this late hour ,
and it's for a favor like that?
Please, Hasegawa!
I have no choice.
But only your woman friend.
That's fine! I can crash somewhere...
But, that means that you'll be...
Don't worry. I know
how tired you must be.
But knowing that you
have no place to stay...
Please hurry it up.
I have an early morning!
Go inside, Belldandy.
Oh, wait...
Why can't I get it off?
Excuse me, Keiichi?
This must be...
Don't tell me, it's the System Force?
Yes.
Yoo-hoo.
If you're here to flaunt your affection
for each other, go somewhere else!
Hey, wait a minute! Hasegawa!
I can explain all this!
Oh...
We're free!
Oh, really...
But what should we do now?
I guess there's no choice...
Nekomi Institute of Technology
Can't get in here...
What's the matter, Belldandy?
Well, I've never been to a
place like this before, you see...
I'll show you around
sometime during the day.
There'll be lots of people.
It's livelier and fun to hang out.
Wow...
It does sound like a lot of fun!
But I gotta rig up
someplace for us to sleep!
A goddess, huh?
I can't just say that I dialed the phone
and out she came from the mirror.
Who would buy a story like that?
Still, she's so sweet and
upbeat and so beautiful...
If it means I can live
with a girl like her...
Keiichi?
From now on, you and I will
be living together, won't we?
Yeah...
I hope that every day will be wonderful!
Keiichi.
Uh, you had a long day, right?
I'm going to stay up all night
to make sure you're safe!
You get a good night's sleep.
But I've never experienced
anything like this before.
So why don't we talk some more?
O-Okay.
I'd like you to tell me more
about yourself, Keiichi.
I'd sure like to hear
about Heaven and all that...
Very well! Now then,
I'll start with the questions...
Tell me about your family.
My parents and my sister
live in Hokkaido.
Hokkaido? And where is that?
One day when I woke up...
A day like any other...
another one just beginning.
There you are, yawning...
your face is still so sleepy.
Because each peaceful day
we share is a miracle to me.
This is where my heart
will always return...
Forever...
There's only one thing I wish for.
I chase after the same dream,
wherever it may go.
The love I feel for you
gives me strength.
May tomorrow be as joyful as today...
That's my wish...
There are wandering souls,
those who seek the Promised Land.
Go where the goddess directs you. You
will find a place that will ease your soul.
Next episode: Ah! Apprenticeship,
Home, and the Goddess!
What are the rules about a
goddess living in a temple?