Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather will come
fluttering down, swaying gently in the air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
Big Sister! Guess what? Guess what?
Let's see, now I have to...
Hey, Belldandy, we should be
leaving soon.
All right.
I'm sorry, Skuld. I've got to
go to college now.
Okay.
All right, we're off now.
Have a good day.
See you later!
Just you wait! No way am I going
to be defeated by that Keiichi!
I'll make sure Big Sister has
eyes for no one but me!
Ah! A Heart Stolen by a Goddess?
When I'm finished building this, I just
know it will make Big Sister happy!
And if that happens...
Thank you, Skuld!
You're the most important
person in my life after all!
It's not a big deal, being forced to
organize all the professor's data...
...but on this machine,
it's taking way too much time.
Just one more push, huh?
All right!
His steel body is expanding.
Get on your feet!
This gets me pumped up!
Big Z! Let's go!
Expanding with one injection!
Come on, Big Z! You're at Unit 5!
One more shot! One more shot!
An all-purpose robot who will protect
and serve Big Sister with its devotion...
With this on our side, we have
nothing to fear from Marller either!
And that's all she wrote.
Finished!
Okay, I guess I should hit Save...
Alternate power source on!
Voltage is normal...
Start data read!
Let's go, you got him! Finish him off!
Gyro on.
Now releasing the final safety device.
Voltage, okay! Oil pressure, normal!
Here we go!
Activate!
It's all gone...
All 15 hours and 22 minutes
of my hard work...
Just when Big Z was about
to wreak total havoc...
Only one person could've done this...
it's that girl!
What in the world were you thinking?
What are you going to do
about all that data?
Your timing is perfect, you know.
I just activated him.
This is the multi-functional Big Sister
Helper Robot, which I invented.
He handles all household chores
and has a demon-thwarting function.
He's an all-purpose robot
and his name is...
Banpei RX!
What's the matter?
I can't believe you made
another useless piece of junk!
I can't believe my data
was lost because of this...
I missed the part where Big Z
goes on a rampage because of you!
How are you gonna make up for it?
15 hours and 22 minutes worth of work
went down the drain for this?
This robot I built...
he really is useful, he is!
Oh, hey, sorry. I was too harsh.
You watch, he's incredible!
Banpei is absolutely incredible!
Oh, you're such a crybaby.
What's the matter?
PROTECT THE TARGET
SET/COMPLETED
I did it! Activation successful!
Who is that, a new friend?
It's nothing but a piece
of junk that Skuld created.
Forgive me! You're not a
piece of junk, all right?
Huh?
Pleased to meet you, Mr. Banpei!
I'd like to be your friend!
My, are you going to help me?
Hah! They totally underestimated me.
No sign of vigilance whatsoever!
Little do they know what a terrible plan
I have up my sleeve!
I'll force that Keiichi to take this
maximum strength hair-growth potion...
...I bought through the mail. Belldandy
will be disgusted with hairy Keiichi...
...and she'll be sure to leave Earth then!
Wait, should I go with the potion
that will make his skin...
...turn green and keep growing like
crazy?
Or maybe it's better to use this one?
It feels so good to do
the laundry on a sunny day.
When I look at that blue sky
and those white clouds...
...it makes me feel so much
at peace with myself.
I don't know why, but...
...it's so boring.
I've decided! I'll use this potion that
will make his feet itch for 30 years!
Banpei?
ATTACK MODE
DEMON/AUTOMATIC
Marller!
Was Marller here?
Yes.
And we were saved by this little fellow.
You see? He's useful, just like I said!
Right, Big Sister?
Right.
Thank you, Skuld!
Yes, well done indeed. So...
Please turn it off as soon as possible.
''The Galaxy Vagabond Force''
is about to start.
Rats!
Come on, we just got rid of Marller.
Why do I have to get yelled at?
But I guess it doesn't matter,
since I made Big Sister happy.
Okay, now I'm set to
re-organize all that data...
Deromasa Hankachou at two
is an absolute must-see!
Thank you for guarding the door.
STANDBY MODE
Oh, my, is he powered down?
I feel sorry for him for
not being able to move.
Was this the switch?
My data's gone again!
Deromasa's love scene!
Please, stop powering on that thing.
I don't care if it's you,
I won't have it!
The next time it happens, I'll trash it!
Would you mind activating it
while we're at school?
I'm so sorry.
Big Sister...
It's all right, Banpei.
You have a purpose in life, too.
That's why you were
brought into this world.
Everything in this world
is born out of necessity.
So you have nothing to
worry about. All right?
Isn't that right, Skuld?
Yes.
I'm going to try to
insert a booster circuit.
If it works, he'll be able to operate
on half the amount of electricity.
It will work.
And I'm sure that Banpei will
appreciate how much you care.
Is there anything I can do to help?
No...
Since I'm the one who built Banpei, I want
you to let me finish the job on my own.
In that case, let me bring you
the ice cream I made yesterday!
Please have some!
Done!
Please, please work...
This should work.
He moved!
The lights didn't go out, either!
We did it!
Huh? Is the power gonna be okay?
Hey, what's the big idea, Keiichi!
Are you all right?
Get away from her right now!
Sorry!
ATTACK MODE
NORMAL
Hey, what's this?
Stay away from me!
Thank goodness...
he's got a power cord...
He's not programmed to attack people.
That might be true, but he sure
wasn't trying to be friends just now.
I wonder what happened to him...
Hey!
The data's been rewritten to
make him protect Big Sister...
...from anyone who gets near her!
What did you say?
According to the log, he used the booster
circuit to rewrite the data himself.
Why would he do that?
I don't know.
But I'm sure there must
be some kind of reason.
We might be able to pinpoint the
reason if we power him on again.
ATTACK MODE
NORMAL
Not again!
Keiichi, will he be all right?
Oh, I'm sure he'll figure
it out somehow...
Oh, don't tell me...
Oh, my...thank you!
AUDIO: REPLAY
Thank you!
Thank you...thank you!
Stay back, stay back!
Now, now. You know that's wrong.
After all, Skuld is the person
who created you.
Skuld, Keiichi, and Urd
are all important to me.
So please, try to get along with them.
MEMORY
SAVE
Boy, can you believe it?
That's MY Big Sister he stole!
Can't you do something about it?
You made it yourself, right?
Do what about it, though?
So you brought us some ice cream?
After monopolizing
MY Big Sister all day!
You'll have to try harder to fool me!
Maybe he's starting to warm up to us?
No, there's no way!
Anyway, he just won't leave
Belldandy's side, will he?
How did that happen?
Idiot, it's so obvious!
Huh?
Love.
What?
That's the one conclusion
I never wanted to utter myself...
Ah no, there's no mistake.
Didn't you see his eyes?
But I never installed
any emotion circuits.
Belldandy has something inside her
that no one will ever understand.
It's a power that draws everyone to her,
whether human or object.
This is lunch.
You pour your soul into making lunch
for those who are dear to you.
I hope you'll be modified someday
so that you can eat, too.
Oh, it's the phone.
Today's the day for sure!
Hello?
Who is this?
I'll spike your lunch with this potion, and
a beanstalk will grow from your nostrils!
You moron. As if I'd fall for
the same tactic over and over!
What the...
Marller!
Hey, that's my Big Sister's
lunch box! You give it back!
Hah! What chance does a child have?
Hey, you! Don't you dare
treat me like a child!
You old nag demon!
What did you say?
If you're going to go that far,
I think I'll take you on...
Gotcha!
Humph! That the best you can do?
Banpei!
Not that meddlesome thing again!
It's been three minutes and
you still haven't answered me.
Maybe you're taking a little nap now,
since it's so nice out today?
Well, I can understand that!
This is the perfect day to take a nap.
Oh, my, there's some kind of
commotion going on outside.
You...
Take that!
You're not going to get the best of me!
Hey! Listen, you, stay out of my way!
What's going on?
You're going to help me out?
Banpei!
Banpei, just do exactly as I say.
What a little brat!
Take that!
As if I'd fall for the same trick again!
Oh, that was no big deal.
What the...
The lunch box!
Big Sister's precious lunch box!
Banpei...
Thank you.
Banpei?
Hey, it's the cable!
No! His memory's going to get erased!
Banpei! Banpei!
MEMORY
IMPORTANT
LUNCH BOX
SKULD
PURPOSE
Why...
Why did this have to happen? Banpei!
Banpei! Banpei!
Skuld? What happened?
Skuld did her best to
restore Banpei's memory.
But it was too late.
Banpei's memory was gone.
I'll see you later!
See you later, okay?
Even so, both Skuld and
Belldandy seem to believe that...
...somewhere deep down, a fragment of
Banpei's memory lives on.
MEMORY
THANK YOU
Always believe in yourself and your
Dreams. You have a Wing!
I love you so much it hurts...
And it hurts me that
I can't tell you how I feel.
You and I have matching hearts...
So we must share the
same scars deep down inside.
But now that I'm in your arms,
I think I can catch...
...your pounding heartbeat this time.
Nobody else matters...
All we have to do is gaze at each other.
It's all right for your heart to flutter...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
Don't run away from happiness.
I'll always be waiting for you.
So come rest your wings anytime.
It's all right to cry...
anytime you need to.
I just want to see you again...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
I just want you to be happy.
The demon is enraged, and swears
to get revenge on the goddesses.
And so the demon-god is resurrected,
and spreads misfortune everywhere.
Next episode, ''Ah! Misfortune Arrives,
and the Tea-Stalk Stands Upright?''
Is that why the Earth Spirit ran,
and got captured by the little girl?