Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather will come
fluttering down, swaying gently in the air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
Hmm...so people here on Earth
are into this kind of thing, huh?
What the heck are you looking at, Urd?
Never mind, it's not for kids.
There you go.
Thanks.
Hey, what do you mean by that?
Now, now, when you're
a little older, okay?
It was getting so romantic...
If only nothing had come between us...
Hey, I need some soy sauce.
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
Um, nothing!
If you get any closer to her
I'm going to use a Skuld bomb on you!
Cut it out!
You'd think after that day
they'd have made some progress...
All right, then, I'm going to do it!
A mandrake root, a pumpkin ghost
stem...
The tears of a banshee,
and a cockatrice feather...
Mmm...it smells divine.
Now all I have to do is let it simmer
for 2 hours and get the extract.
Hey, what am I doing? Today's
the last episode of Winter Storm!
Humph! That Urd is up to no good again!
Cooking up a concoction like this...
I just know she'll cause another uproar.
I'd better nip
this evil plan in the bud!
Darn, that show really ripped.
Aha...all done, I see...
Neanderthal, Cro-Magnon,
Australopithecus, Java...Peking!
The seeds of magic,
the seeds of romance...
...the seeds of love,
cultivated to become strong...
Transform yourself into love crystals
to forge a bond between those two!
Was the smoke always this
overwhelming?
But hey...
...it's done.
Ah! Please Don't Look at Me Like That!?
FURIN KAZAN
It's no good, at this rate, the shaft's
only going to get thicker than the gear...
Damn, why'd he have to give
an assignment like this?
Keiichi, you should have something
sweet when you're feeling tired.
Oh, thanks...huh? Urd?!
When you're tired, you should have
something sweet...there's nothing better!
Something's fishy...I just
know this isn't normal candy!
Oh, hey, come on! Of course not!
Keiichi? I've brought you some tea.
Oh, hey, thanks.
Oh, my, what can those be?
It's candy...for people here on Earth.
Do you want some, Belldandy?
Huh?
Yes, I'd love a piece!
Urd...so it really is just candy, right?
Belldandy?
It's yummy!
Urd? What's going on?
Oh, um...nothing!
Something's wrong...did I botch it?
Me of all people?
But how can that be...
I know it didn't have to be Keiichi
who took those crystals, but still...
...why isn't it taking effect?
Keiichi!
Seniors...I can't go on anymore...
Huh? Is it morning?
I keep having these
weird dreams lately...
I guess I must be really burned out.
I'm still dreaming...
Maybe I'll sleep some more...
Good morning, Keiichi.
B...B...Belldandy!
Please forgive me.
I woke you up, didn't I?
What the heck is Belldandy doing here?
In my bed, for crying out loud?
Is this really my room, even?
Keiichi?
I don't know why, but you're sweating.
Were you too hot, perhaps?
I'm so sorry! But I wanted
to be right next to you...
I'm dreaming.
This has got to be a dream!
Keiichi? What's the matter, Keiichi?
Keiichi!
This is terrible! Keiichi's...
Big Sister?
Keiichi!
Big Sister!
Those Seeds of Love pack a punch.
Urd, you didn't use those
things on Big Sister, did you?
Well, you seem to know a lot about it!
Huh? What are you talking about?
I have no idea at all...
You come with me!
It's all right now.
Your temperature's normal. But
what on earth's making you sweat so?
I'm fine, I'm fine! See?
All this exercise is making me sweat!
One, two, three, four, five, six...
Thank goodness! There's nothing
wrong with you, is there?
Keiichi?
Oh, holy...
Let me wipe away your sweat,
or you'll catch a cold.
I want you to hold still now, all right?
This is a dream.
It's some kind of mistake.
I've never seen Belldandy
acting like this before!
It's your scent, Keiichi...
I have no idea what's
going on here anymore...
Keiichi?
Yes?
Um, I have a favor to ask of you.
Sure, just hurry up
and get some clothes on!
The bones of a Nauman elephant,
the tears of a giant sea turtle...Hey!
I'm short on eternity dust, too!
How could you do that?
I couldn't let Big Sister...
Mixing in that stuff was bad!
What?
This is going to turn Belldandy
into a shameless little tramp!
Huh?!
It's all your fault for butting in like that.
Hey, I know! The antidote...
you've got to start making an antidote!
It'll take 30 hours to come up with one.
That long?
The spell has a 24-hour effect,
so it should wear off before...
...I can cook up an antidote.
Big Sister!
I want you to take me
shopping downtown today.
Okay, sure! I'm just going to
wash up first, so wait for me, okay?
Yes!
Now what's gotten into her?
Belldandy's seems so aggressive today.
I wonder if it's because I've
always been too timid until now...
Keiichi?
I've come to wash your back for you.
Hold on! I've already washed it,
so you don't have to bother!
But Keiichi...are you saying you
don't want me to wash your back?
No, no, I didn't say that.
In that case...
Sorry! I'm getting out now, so
could we do this another time?
Ugh...
I'm sorry, asking you to take me
shopping on such short notice.
Hey, no problem. If you want to do
something like that, it's no trouble at all!
Huh?!
Keiichi...you're so kind!
You...really think so?
Ow! Ouch!
Oh, my!
I'm going on a date
with Keiichi today. Please?
Chu!
What's the matter, Banpei?
Pull yourself together, now!
I wonder what the rest of
the day's gonna be like?
Here we are walking around
in familiar surroundings...
...but for some reason,
my heart's pounding today.
And just look how her eyes
are glistening...
I wonder if she's trying to
send some kind of message?
Keiichi?
Huh? What is it?
Um...do you think people
can tell we're a couple?
Huh?
You don't want to be with me?
No, no!
I never said that!
Really?
Then it's all right if we
act like a couple, isn't it?
This is all right, isn't it?
Uh-huh!
All right, then. Let's go!
Right!
Oh, no! My Big Sister!
I've never heard Belldandy
say anything like that before.
Now she's got me feeling
really self-conscious!
Look at this, I bet
you'd look good in it.
Do you really think so?
What kind of clothes
do you want to try on?
What would I try on?
If it were up to me...
Whoa...
How lovely! Which do you think
would look most becoming on me?
I'd love to put something like this on,
and climb into bed with you again.
No, no, no, these aren't
clothes, you see!
I wouldn't look good in them?
That's not what I meant...
Then tell me which one you like best!
Uh, then...how about that one?
It's charming!
All right, then.
I'm going to go try it on.
I can't believe my Big Sister would
even look at such a vulgar outfit!
Come on! This is no time
for you to browse!
Sorry, it's so adorable...
Oh, right, you wouldn't
know anything about it.
What does that mean?
Nothing, actually...
Never mind! We've got
to go after Big Sister!
Talk about a heart attack...
If she walked around dressed like that
everyday, I don't think I could take it...
Not that it would be such
a bad thing, of course...
Hey, what's up?
Would you mind giving me
a sip of that, please?
But you have your own drink, Belldandy.
I'd like to try what
you're having, Keiichi.
Yeah?
Here.
Thank you.
Here. I enjoyed it.
If I were to drink from this,
would that make it a secondhand kiss?
What should I do?
There's still some left!
Aren't you going to drink it?
Don't do it, Keiichi!
Bottoms up, Keiichi!
Belldandy went to the trouble
of planting her lips on this.
I might never get this
kind of chance again!
Who am I?
Oh...
We're so sorry.
Keiichi...
Coming to a place like this...
just what are they up to?
Keiichi, this is the first time we've
come to see a movie together, isn't it?
I guess you're right.
I've been wanting to come here,
you know...with you, Keiichi.
Oh, well, same here.
What's really going on here...why are
you acting like this today, Belldandy?
I don't really understand
what goes on in a girl's mind.
Hey, it's the trailer for Winter Storm.
Well, no matter how we got to this
point, I am getting to see a movie...
...with Belldandy...
Movie theaters are like a strange world.
The onscreen images we see
in the darkness are surreal...
Sometimes it feels as if you're forced to
be aware of the opposite sex.
Especially on a day like today...
...how can I not be aware of her?
I've got to calm down!
Calm down!
Do you want one too, Belldandy?
This is good enough for me.
Augh!
Whoa...whoa! This is right
out of a freakin' manga!
No you don't!
Not that!
What's the matter?
There's something in my eye...
Would you take a look at it?
Are you all right?
What the heck...
Bizarre! Belldandy's behavior
is definitely bizarre today!
Or it's some kind of huge mistake!
You have to get closer, or...
...you won't be able to get it out.
Come on...
But what do you want me to do?
How am I supposed to get
something out of her eye?
Please hurry!
Look at that.
What do they think they're doing?
Aren't they embarrassed?
You need to think about where you
are before you throw those things.
Who are you to tell me what to do?
Where's Big Sister?
We didn't have to run away like that.
We shouldn't do that
in front of other people.
Let's go home before
something else freaky happens.
All righty...
Whoa!
I want to sit here.
I'm dreaming. I've got to be dreaming!
What a lovely ride!
Yeah.
Your back feels warm and inviting,
Keiichi.
From where I'm sitting,
I can feel your emotions.
I'd like to go somewhere
far away, just you and me...
...with you, Keiichi.
What a beautiful spot!
Listen, it's getting late...
A little longer...is it all right if I have
you to myself a little longer?
All right.
Keiichi, you're so kind!
Hey!
The potion should be wearing off soon.
Too bad they can't just go
all the way first, though...
Urd!
Come on, don't just leave me behind
like this! Okay, you asked for it...
We haven't spent time alone
like this lately, have we?
No...
Keiichi!
Keiichi, I have to tell you...
B-B-B...Belldandy!
I love you!
I...
Why are you so afraid?
Right...she's a goddess and I'm a human.
Why is it wrong for me
to get closer to you?
Belldandy will have to go
back to Heaven some day.
When that day comes,
will I be able to let her go?
My beloved Keiichi...all I want is
to stay with you a little longer!
Right...I'm just making excuses
because I'm spineless!
Just like everyone says,
I'm being a total wimp here.
I'm in love with Belldandy.
And she even says...
Keiichi!
Belldandy!
Let's go!
That's it, one more push!
Not if I can help it!
Huh, what the...
I won't let him have Big Sister!
You think you can take me?
Then bring it on!
Keiichi!
This is inevitable, after all...
For us to want each other...
it's natural...
There's no one here but us.
I want to stay in this world of
ours forever...just you and me...
But...
You're not getting in their way!
Big Sister!
I don't need anything else in
the world, as long as I have you.
Keiichi!
I can't do this! You're
not yourself right now!
What? Why not?
Is it because you don't love me?
Belldandy...
Yes?
You're an honest person, you don't
have a distrustful bone in your body...
And you're so kind to everyone...
But the truth is, I want you to only
be kind to me...no, wait, I mean...
Keiichi?
I don't know how to say it, but
I'm in love with the normal, genuine you...
I love you more when
you're being yourself.
Keiichi!
I love you so much!
Belldandy!
Keiichi, I love you!
I'm so pissed! That's my Big Sister...
Good for you, Belldandy...
It's mostly thanks to my Seeds of Love...
And by the way, Skuld!
You know what to expect, don't you?
Your punishment for touching
my stuff without my permission...
Stop!
Stop that!
I can't stand it!
There you go!
This device only goes around and
around!
Don't show me those useless things!
Deep down, those two are really close,
huh?
So horribly simplistic!
Always believe in yourself and
your Dreams. You have a wing!
I love you so much it hurts...
And it hurts me that
I can't tell you how I feel.
You and I have matching hearts...
So we must share the
same scars deep down inside.
But now that I'm in your arms,
I think I can catch...
...your pounding heartbeat this time.
Nobody else matters...
All we have to do is gaze at each other.
It's all right for your heart to flutter...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
Don't run away from happiness.
I'll always be waiting for you.
So come rest your wings anytime.
It's all right to cry...
anytime you need to.
I just want to see you again...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
I just want you to be happy.
One night, the couple finds
themselves alone at last.
But it turns out to be
the start of an ordeal...
Next episode: Ah! If You're
a Real Man, Save the Goddess?
Finally it's just Belldandy and me,
and I have to look like this?