Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather will come
fluttering down, swaying gently in the air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
You low-level demons...
you're 1,000 years too early!
What the?
Curses! Where in tarnation can it be?
I didn't think they'd have
a boss like that...
Could it be...
Aha, I've found it at last!
The legendary urn!
Soon I'll be rid of those
obnoxious goddesses!
Ah! The Devil's Whisper
Coming from an Urn?
O Urn of ancient times,
Urn of Hakushon the Demon King!
I beg of you, grant my wish!
I beg of you, open your eyes!
I'm going to unleash all the
misery of the world on them!
Once the Lord of Terror awakens,
we demons shall rule the world!
We'll have nothing to fear
from those goddesses!
Hey, it's a kitty cat!
Huh?
Ugh...
The moment that the
Urn opens its eyes...
...the bronze-skinned Lord of Terror
shall be resurrected!
Let the world know misery and despair!
What was that?
Urd, would you like some tea?
Uh-huh.
Hey Urd, your favorite show is on now.
Oh?
Urd, I tossed out those weird bottles
of yours, they were in my way.
Really....
Oh...
Who knew there was a
licensing system for goddesses?
Oh, come on, stop sulking,
it's just a suspension!
Whoa!
Skuld!
Do you have a license, too?
Yes.
For example, I'm a Goddess 1st Class,
2nd Category, Unlimited License.
Class refers to precision
and power level.
''2nd Category'' is a commercial license.
And ''limited'' indicates
what you're permitted to do.
I'm a Goddess 2nd Class,
1st Category, Limited License.
Urd's a Goddess 2nd Class,
Administration, Limited License.
And since a license brings with it
responsibility as well as privilege...
...there are penalties for
those who neglect their duties.
That's why you can get your license
suspended just like that, if you lie all the
time!
It's all my fault...I'm so sorry...
It's all right. A penalty's a penalty.
That's right, that's right!
Learn your lesson once in a while!
Suspension, huh?
I'd better watch out, too.
Listen, you guys, all this talk
I've been hearing from you...
Watch out! She's going to explode!
This is all just a joke to you, isn't it?
Summoning...
Huh?
That's right.
If she uses her powers during her
suspension, they'll revoke her license.
So she does know that's the deal, huh?
That's it, I'm going to
quit being a goddess!
Urd!
Maybe we were too hard on her.
Knowing Urd, I'm sure having her powers
taken away must be stressing her out.
So how long are they
suspending her license?
For this long.
Huh? Five months?
Five days? Five minutes?
Don't tell me Five years?
Fifty years in Earth terms...
Fifty years?
Isn't there some kind of course she can
take to get her license back sooner?
Well, actually, there is, but...
Good!
It's a seminar in Heaven,
lasting thirty years...
Thirty!
There's no way she can do that.
Really, who knew that
walking was such a drag?
What's the matter?
You don't look too happy...
Oh, well, I have a lot going on.
Hey, would you mind
lending me that bike?
I don't mind, but you've got one, right?
What?
Don't tell me you don't know that you
can't ride a motorcycle without a license.
License, license, license!
Another license?
Urd? Hey, wait! Stop that!
Calm down! Calm down!
Consideration for others,
for other cars and for this town
So they'll give me a license here, right?
Well, it should be a cinch
to get one for a moped.
All righty!
They said it costs money!
What did you expect?
Lend me some!
That's something I can't help you with!
Oh, darn! All right, then! I'll get
a part-time job, I'll do anything!
Open your eyes.
What? Who's that?
Man, that scared me.
I thought she'd found us out!
Inoue Pharmacy
If there ever was a perfect job for me...
...this has to be it!
They said I have to have
a pharmacist's license.
Well, of course you do!
Hair salon
Blowfish Restaurant
Fugukichi
Sorry, I have an errand to run,
so I'll be going now.
Gotta study for my license...
Hey, did you know
you could get suspended if...
License? Suspended?
I sense you people are ready
for a change, so please vote for me!
License...
Car in front! Stop, or
your license will be suspended!
For crying out loud! License, license
suspension, that's all I ever hear!
In that case, embrace my powers...
Who said that?
Oops.
Hey, you smushed my castle!
Look, I'm sorry...
Wow! That's amazing!
Are you a magician, Big Sister?
Well, I used to be.
Just one more push!
Good evening and welcome!
Oh, it's you guys.
Hey, what a coincidence!
Urd!
That was your power just now, right?
I'm sorry.
Just leave me alone.
I don't need a license here, see?
I'm going to live as a
human being from now on!
Oh, man...
Will that be all?
The dessert special and
a pineapple milk float.
And the sweet red bean soup
and a mountain crepe.
Um, let me repeat your order.
One seafood macaroni gratin and
one salmon and scallop spaghetti...
...and a clam soup and...
Lady, when are you gonna take my
order?
I need an ashtray!
I'll be with you in a second!
I wonder if she's gonna be okay...
I just hope she doesn't
push herself too hard.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, girlie. What are you
gonna do about my clothes?
Hey, don't just stand there,
you gotta speak up!
Shut up!
Huh?
Didn't you hear me?
Nope, didn't catch it.
Urd, don't...
Shut up...that's what I said!
The hell with licenses!
The hell with my suspension!
I'm through with being
a goddess or a human!
What difference does it make,
I'm useless and nobody needs me!
Then assume your true form now!
Unleash your demonic powers!
What?
You are the Lord of Terror's
rightful heir...
No, I'm Urd, Goddess 2nd Class,
Administrative Category, Limited
License...
Oh, even if you're unable to
use your powers?
Why don't you shut up!
Accept me now...
...and you'll have unlimited use of a
greater power than you've ever known!
Huh?
It must be tedious to have to submit
to all these restrictions as a goddess.
Nothing suits you more
than the freedom of a demon!
Act now, and I'll throw in a
special servant, just for you!
Demon, did you say?
Don't give me that nonsense!
Why do you have such hatred for
demons?
When the purest demonic blood
runs in your veins!
That's...that's not...
It goes against nature, for a Black-
Winged
being to be on the goddesses' side.
Think it over carefully...
We're not going to force you to do
anything, you shall only do as you wish!
But I'm...
Now then, take a good look at yourself!
Now release the demonic power in you!
Urd!
Urd?
I've forgotten that name...
what I used to be called!
But no! How can that be, Urd?
My name is the Lord of Terror!
What?
All of you people...know my true name!
I shall destroy everything in my path!
Wait!
Urd!
This can't be...
I can't believe Urd really turned
out to be the Lord of Terror...
The Lord of Terror?
Yes...
The day before I received my
commission as a 1st Class Goddess...
Belldandy, there is something
I must tell you.
Yes?
A legend among goddesses and
demons...
you know of the Lord of Terror, do you
not?
Yes.
When this Lord descends, the earth
shall rupture, its axis shall be twisted...
...there will be confusion among
the people, and after 7 days of fire...
...all shall be destroyed.
Yes...
Urd...might very well be
the Lord of Terror's heir.
What?
I have sealed her demonic blood, so
I don't believe it will ever be unleashed.
But should the demons ever make
a serious attempt to lure her...
...to their side,
it might not be failsafe.
If that side of her should ever manifest,
you must notify me immediately.
Yes...
So Urd isn't really your older sister?
Urd and I were born to different mothers,
you see, and Urd's mother is actually...
A demon, huh?
Even so...Urd is still
our precious big sister!
Our beloved big sister,
who shares half of our bloodline.
Of course she is...but...
...wouldn't the Almighty One do
something about it, in that case?
He will send goddesses under his direct
command, from the Combat Division.
Combat Division?
Yes. These goddesses are called
Valkyries, and their duty is...
...to completely annihilate
the source of all evil.
No way! Isn't there something we can
do?
Do you remember when
Marller was here before?
Huh? Yeah.
A catalyst is necessary for a
demon to appear here on Earth.
That means that...
You mean there must
be a CD or something!
Yes.
Either we destroy it, or use its
counterpart to seal the demon...
Right!
However, once I've sealed her...
...Urd will be forced to wander
in solitude until the end of time...
Oh...
That's no good...
what are we supposed to do?
Whoa!
What in blue blazes happened?
So you've come at last.
Urd? What are you doing here?
Hmm, so it's you...the servant
I was promised as a bonus.
You have no right to call me a servant,
with that weird outfit on!
The way you're dressed
isn't much different!
You shut up!
Don't compare me with you!
Impossible!
How can Urd be this powerful?
Behold, I am the
Lord of Terror's rightful heir!
Know how powerful I am!
I shall destroy everything in my path!
Lord of Terror? Ridiculous!
How can a goddess like you...
Humph! I've quit being a goddess,
it was too stupid.
I have discovered my true power!
Preposterous...how could Urd be...
But come to think of it,
the legend did say...
...the Lord of Terror would be
bronze-skinned.
Well, she always did have
a demonic personality!
What are you muttering about?
My lord!
If you doubt me, would you like
to experience my power firsthand?
Certainly not, my lord!
I'll get her to join with me, and
make those wretched goddesses suffer!
With the power I have at my disposal,
mere goddesses will be no match for me!
What...Yes, my lord!
Along with those annoying goddesses,
we're going to destroy this world!
If I may be so bold...
I have a strategy in mind.
Oh?
This is getting interesting!
So you're not going to
notify the Almighty One?
No. If Urd has truly awakened as the
Lord of Terror, the Almighty One will
show...
...no mercy.
Then, what should we do?
I'll get Urd to change her mind.
Belldandy...
Taking the burden on by yourself?
You can't do that!
Skuld...
Even if she's become the Lord of Terror,
nothing can change...
...the fact that Urd is my big sister.
I'll go with you, Big Sister.
Come on, let's strike Urd down together!
What?
What good will striking her down do?
Oops...
Anyway, if Urd hasn't
lost her whole soul...
...I don't see her doing
any major damage.
You have a point.
But the problem is...
according to the legend...
...the Lord of Terror possesses
the Ultimate Destruction Program.
Ultimate Destruction?
Program?
But Big Sister! If it's a program, then
there's got to be a vaccine or
something...
What's going on?
Banpei!
What is that?
That's it! That's it!
Behold my overwhelming power!
First off, I'm going to smash your
goddess headquarters into oblivion!
Urd! Please stop!
Watch out!
Urd!
Is this what you wanted to do
with your powers, Urd?
No, you're the one who always looks
out for us. You'd never want to do that!
Show us how strong your soul is!
Please, Urd!
Belldandy! Skuld!
Don't pay any attention to them.
They're the ones who
took away your powers!
But...
It's their fault that you got
your license suspended!
Suspended...
Urd!
That's right! Demonic power...
Rules!
Is that what you call an attack
against the Lord of Terror?
What the...there's no effect at all?
I can't have you
underestimating my power, now!
Banpei! Deploy the
Magnetic Net Wire Beam!
Fire!
Did you get her?
Skuld!
Banpei!
It's no good! She's too powerful!
Is this supposed to hurt me?
Keiichi!
This is my Powered Exoskeleton,
Hercules 1!
Hey, this sounds kind of familiar...
That's because I used the engine
from your bike as a power source.
Huh? What the heck?
You fools...
Give it all you've got, Beemer!
Oh no, I guess 45 horsepower
wasn't enough after all...
You should have realized that sooner!
Keiichi!
Ooooh...that tickles!
Whoa! The vibrations
are loosening the bolts!
Bolts?
That's it! Belldandy!
I want you to remove all the bolts!
Not just mine, but all of them!
All right!
Turn...fly...
release yourself from your bonds...
I command you all to descend to earth!
What the...
Man, that was close!
Big Sister!
Belldandy!
You used up your powers,
just as I anticipated.
This is the moment
I've been waiting for!
So Urd and the giant robot
were just decoys?
We couldn't have her doing you know
what.
Those were the Lord of Terror's
instructions.
Sorry, but I'm going to seal you up now!
Belldandy!
Impossible!
Keiichi!
Damn...did you have to get in the way?
Big Sister!
Curses! I've got to seal her
before she wakes up!
What the...
Dammit, Belldandy's come to!
I have no choice but to try again later.
I can probably think of some use for him.
Marller, what are you
going to do with Keiichi?
Who knows? You know what they say...
only the devil knows!
Keiichi!
What's wrong? What happened here?
Keiichi's been captured by Marller.
But how?
When Marller was about to seal you
away,
he jumped in to protect you...
That's when she...
So Keiichi was taken in my place?
Yes.
Not only has Urd turned into the Lord of
Terror, but if she's in league with Marller...
...there's going to be trouble.
I'm removing my power limiter.
What?
Removing your power limiter
is a huge offense!
If I'm going to stop Urd...
and if I'm going to save Keiichi...
...I'm going to need my full power.
But...
I have to...I have to if
I'm going to save Keiichi...
Almighty One...just this once,
please forgive my willfulness...
Always believe in yourself and your
Dreams.
You have a wing!
I love you so much it hurts...
And it hurts me that
I can't tell you how I feel.
You and I have matching hearts...
So we must share the
same scars deep down inside.
But now that I'm in your arms,
I think I can catch...
...your pounding heartbeat this time.
Nobody else matters...
All we have to do is gaze at each other.
It's all right for your heart to flutter...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
Don't run away from happiness.
I'll always be waiting for you.
So come rest your wings anytime.
It's all right to cry...
anytime you need to.
I just want to see you again...
All we have to do is love each other.
Open your heart, and
ride that favorable wind.
I just want you to be happy.
The Lord of Terror's fury
is about to be unleashed!
Possessed by demons, the goddess
unleashes the forbidden power.
Next episode: Ah! The Savior of the
World
Arrives with the Sound of the Flute?
First a battle with a robot...
and now monsters?