Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather will come
fluttering down, swaying gently in the air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
Let's see...
slippers, detergent, and...
Oh, I forgot to get clothespins!
We have plenty of extra clothespins
at the temple. You're welcome to them!
Really? That's great.
Living on your own is more
expensive than you'd think.
Then why don't you move in with Keiichi?
No way! I'm finally moving to the city.
I'm going to enjoy
single life to the fullest!
Plus, I don't want to get
in the way of you two... huh?
Hey, that's right, it's White Day.
Did you already get
something from Kei today?
What?
A return gift for the chocolates. I bet he
gave something neutral like cookies...
Chocolates, did you say?
Wait a minute, you didn't know about
Valentine's Day last month?
No.
So in other words...
Ah! Where to Confess One's Love?
What? You practice such
customs here on Earth?
I wouldn't say ''on Earth''...
It's more like ''in Japan.''
But in a relationship like yours, giving
Kei chocolates would be a no-brainer.
Megumi, did you offer a
gift to someone as well?
No, because I don't care
about that kind of stuff.
But Kei might be
taking it a little hard.
Has he been acting
strangely at all recently?
Now that you mention it...
Another sunny day today.
Yes.
It's the 2nd week of February.
Spring is right around the corner.
It certainly is.
I was wondering if you know about any
of the customs we have here on Earth?
Yes, I am familiar with several of them.
Are you?
What day is it today again?
It's Monday.
If it's Monday,
then that means... right...
It must be the 14th. I see...
Oh, I just remembered!
What?
The 14th is the day the Auto Club
presents its monthly expense report.
Right, that's right.
Oh boy, he was so waiting for it,
wasn't he!
I don't really have a good
grasp on the customs here.
But you guys are living together...
you can't blame him for being depressed.
I'm sorry...
Hey, Megumi, I didn't
know you were here.
We should be heading for school soon.
All right. I'll go get ready now.
Hold on!
Huh?
I need to go somewhere with Belldandy
today, so you go on ahead to class.
I'll be going, then.
Um... I think I'll go and
apologize to Keiichi.
Wait!
Don't apologize, it'll make things worse.
But...
I've got a better idea.
Just do what I say!
Let this mouth-watering
chocolate be suffused with...
...my feelings for
Keiichi as his goddess...
...and make up for my not
having given it to him before.
I knew you could do it, Belldandy!
No question about it,
Kei's gonna be thrilled!
Do you really think so?
You really look happy yourself.
Yes, that's my reason for being here...
to make Keiichi happy.
I'm really glad... that you're
the woman in Kei's life.
Now all you have to do is take Kei
to a romantic spot and hand it to him.
And tell him, ''Sorry I was late!''
And that will fix everything?
You can't miss!
All right!
Man... it's March already, huh?
Keiichi?
Hey, weren't you
going out with Megumi today?
Um... actually, I have
something for you, see...
Are you out of your mind?
Trying to give me that ugly bouquet
in an unromantic place like this?
How insensitive are you?
Unromantic?
Take him to a romantic spot
and hand it to him.
Is this what you'd call
an unromantic place?
Huh? Well, I guess most
people would say that.
Is that right?
Excuse me.
Hey, wait! Belldandy!
Really! These days you can throw a
rock and hit 10 clueless guys like him!
Excuse me?
Oh, it's you! What do you want?
I was wondering if you could tell me
where I can find a ''romantic spot.''
Romantic...
You see, I have to give Keiichi
these chocolates in a romantic place.
Being sarcastic?
What?
I get it now!
You're just gushing over Morisato like
that to make me give up on him, right?
Give up on him? What do you mean?
Are you playing dumb again?
Playing dumb?
Listen, you!
Wait a minute... is this girl just naive?
Um...
Um... so can you tell me about the spot?
A romantic spot, you say?
So you're going to tell me
where I can find one?
Sure I'll tell you, but in return,
I want you to meow like a cat!
Meow!
Stick your head outside
and shout ''Yahoo!''
Yahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo!
No question about it now...
Yahoo!
I guess I have no choice. Come with me.
All right!
So he's going to come here?
Yes.
Oh, here he comes! That's him.
If anyone knows about
romantic spots, it's that guy.
Really?
Thank you very much!
Do you have any idea who that guy is?
The No. 1 Casanova on campus...
Toshiyuki Aoshima!
If you approach him...
Excuse me...
Would you please tell me where
I can find a ''romantic spot''?
I've never seen her before.
Both her body and looks make the
grade...
I guess today's my lucky day!
Very well. Let's go, then.
What?
Wait! Come back! That's not fair!
Now that you're in that rogue's clutches
he'll have his way with you, and once...
...the rumors start to fly, you'll
never want to show your face here again!
I wonder if Belldandy went on home?
She sure was acting kind of weird...
Hmm?
Belldandy?
Belldandy!
Huh?
Dammit! Why did it have to die
on me at a time like this?
I'm sorry!
Are you saying that
this is a romantic spot?
That's right.
Would Keiichi really be happy if
I brought him to a place like this?
Keiichi?
Excuse me, can you
think of another place?
Huh?
It's just that I don't think Keiichi
would like it if I brought him here.
Who gives a damn about a guy like that?
I brought you here because
I wanted to make you happy!
But that won't do...
the goal is to make Keiichi happy!
That's my duty.
Duty?
Do you mean that jerk is
actually forcing you to...
No, he's not forcing me at all...
That's precisely why I want
Keiichi to be happy.
I don't know what your motive was, but
the fact is that you came here with me.
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
You know perfectly well!
Why are you running? You're the one
who pretty much said you wanted me.
I never said such a thing!
It's a little late to say no!
I want you to come here!
You've hit a dead end.
I have no choice, then.
Run, O Spirit of Lightning,
release yourself from your shackles...
And subject this man to an ordeal!
I don't know what kind of spell...
W-What the hell is this?
Where did she go?
W-What the hell is going on?
Belldandy!
Belldandy! Belldandy!
All right, I'm gonna change now,
so you stay out!
B-But...
Didn't you hear a word I said?
That guy duped her into
going with him, that's all.
She's from another country. She doesn't
know how things are done in Japan.
If that's the case,
I guess it's all right.
See ya!
You went along with him to find
a romantic spot, is that it?
Yes. I'm so sorry.
What am I gonna do with you?
Um... could you tell me?
Where a romantic spot might be?
Sure, I could do that, but...
I want to make Keiichi
happy, no matter what.
Kei, you're such a lucky dog.
Ugh... Senior, I can't do it anymore...
Good morning!
Whoa! Belldandy!
Um... I wanted to ask you if
you had any plans for today?
Huh? No, I'm not doing anything.
Um, there's someplace I'd like to go.
I was wondering if you'd
accompany me...
Well, sure...
Then please come to the living room
after you've gotten dressed.
Now all you have to do is
take him to places he likes.
All right.
But the thing is, I'm not really sure
what kind of place he'd like.
Don't worry!
As long as you go with him, he'll have
a ball no matter where you take him!
You can have these.
What are they?
I won them in the
prize-drawing at a party.
If you take him there, I guarantee
he'll have himself a blast.
One more thing, you two have
to be alone together, always.
Three's a crowd.
But why is that?
I always thought the more the merrier...
Because then it won't
be fun for him anymore!
Are you sure that's how he'd feel?
Hey, trust me!
That's how any guy would feel!
Okay then, good luck!
Someplace she'd like to go? I wonder
what's up with her, all of a sudden...
We haven't had much time to be alone
lately, so I guess it's good timing.
This is where you wanted to go?
Yes!
I thought you'd have a good time
if we came here.
You did? Well, thanks.
I wanted to go, but I didn't have
the money so I'd given up on the idea.
Um, are you having a good time?
Of course I am!
Thanks so much, Belldandy!
I'm so glad!
I thought I'd shadow them, but it looks
like there's nothing to worry about.
Still, this is the last place
anyone would call romantic.
Wow!
This is awesome!
Hey, it's my turn now!
Oh, sorry!
So this is what Megumi was
talking about... a ''romantic spot''!
All righty, I guess it's time
for the third wheel to back out...
Wanna go look at the stuff over there?
Yeah!
Oh my gosh, what can I do
to distract those two?
I got it!
Oh, man! I just touched it
and the whole thing broke off!
Broke?
This is where you and I come in!
Hey! You can just leave that to us!
It just so happens, we're
from the NIT Auto Club...
Hey, it's the Seniors?
Whoops, I forgot, Kei's
a member of the Auto Club too!
Uh... um...
This is a shrine to those of us in
the Auto Club and you dare bring...
...Belldandy here on a date?
Unforgivable! Now then,
why don't you just come with us...
We must decline!
Belldandy?
I must spend the day alone
with Keiichi today.
Huh?
Now then, shall we go, Keiichi?
Uh, sure...
What was that all about?
You don't think...
she doesn't like us anymore?
Hey, she's tougher than I thought.
I guess there's no need for me
to follow them anymore!
Good luck, now!
I wonder what's going on?
Hey, I really had a great time!
Now why don't we go someplace
where you can enjoy yourself...
Oh, no! That won't do!
I must see to it that you
have a good time today!
Let's see...
...where would Keiichi have fun,
a fun place for Keiichi...
Oh, I know! Come on, let's go there!
Let's go where?
What is this place?
You can fix cars to
your heart's content here!
Well, maybe I can, but...
It's not fun here?
No, of course it's fun!
I'm sorry.
Such a variety of cars and motorcycles!
Uh-huh...
No good either?
Look at all these ancient cars!
I'm so sorry!
No, don't be.
I mean, I hardly ever get the
chance to come to a place like this!
Hey, look at this one, it's awesome.
So they used parts like these
back in the old days, huh?
Listen, I really do appreciate
all your concern for me, but...
...I think you're trying a little too hard.
You seem somewhat blue these days...
That's why I...
Because I want you to always have
a smile on your face, Keiichi.
Gotcha!
In that case, there's a place I want to go.
Will you come with me?
It's just a ferry that's
been around for ages.
But I like doing this...
taking the last boat at sunset.
Is that so?
I'd like to know what made you
act the way you did today.
Um, you see, since I didn't give you
chocolate for Valentine's Day...
Is that the reason?
But you don't know the
customs here on Earth.
You didn't have to feel bad about it.
Please forgive me.
How can I call myself your goddess...
...when I've made you feel so sad?
That's why you were trying so
hard to show me a good time?
Yes...
But...
I am a failure as a goddess.
That's not true!
I had such a good time today!
But...
I'm telling you the truth.
I mean, I had you by my side...
...laughing and looking so happy,
even looking worried once in a while.
That's what makes me happy!
But I have to fulfill
my job as a goddess...
All right, then, I want you to take me
to a place that you like, Belldandy.
What?
I want to know what places
you like, Belldandy.
To learn more about you...
there's nothing I'd enjoy more right now.
Keiichi...
It's right here.
This is my favorite place to be.
Where the wind crossing
the vast ocean meets...
...the wind that has
descended from the mountains.
You can hear so many different voices
right here. It's such a lovely place.
This is it...
this is a ''romantic spot,'' isn't it?
Here.
Huh?
Forgive me for not
giving it to you sooner...
Oh, hold on a minute!
Here!
It's for you, in return.
Keiichi...
Belldandy...
Keiichi!
Why does it always end up like this?
Just one more inch...
So you did give it to him!
Yes!
That's great!
Caught a cold?
Uh, no...
There's something wrong after all.
Come to think of it...
The System Force has vanished, too.
Then does all
this sneezing mean...
One day when I woke up...
A day like any other...
another one just beginning.
There you are, yawning...
your face is still so sleepy.
Because each peaceful day
we share is a miracle to me.
This is where my heart
will always return...
Forever...
There's only one thing I wish for.
I chase after the same dream,
wherever it may go.
The love I feel for you
gives me strength.
May tomorrow be as joyful as today...
That's my wish...
Blood ties... connections made by
destiny.
A connection that's no different
even if you happen to be goddesses.
Next episode: Ah! Can You Pass the
Love Test With Those Low Scores?
Are goddesses allowed
to wear white lab coats?