Open your mind. Open your mind.
Far beyond the deep blue Earth,
you and I shall meet...
...as a gentle breeze goes by.
AH! MY GODDESS
A snow-white feather will come
fluttering down, swaying gently in the air.
Without holding back, I want to
envelope you, my one and only love.
I know I have the power to protect
the one I love, right here in my hands.
Open your mind.
Just as I've always dreamed.
Let the wind carry off
your hopes, faraway.
I have wings nobody can see.
Look, you have them, too.
They'll take us to where we can be free.
Anyone can be free.
The sky is so blue...
Miss... I think you've had enough.
Oh, you be quiet!
If you have time to lecture your customer,
why don't you just hit me again!
Vodka, Sprodka! I'll take it straight!
Ever since that girl showed up, I've been
stripped of my title as campus queen.
Forced to spend my nights
drowning my sorrows alone...
Why, oh why did this have to happen to
me?
Everything that's happened...
...it's all Belldandy's fault!
Excuse me, miss... are you all right?
Ah! Choosing Between
the Goddess and the Queen?
Damn, my head hurts!
I must've had too much
to drink last night...
What did you do to me while I slept?
Just hold on a minute!
You passed out, and I'm the one
who brought you home!
You got me falling-down drunk and
did this and that to me, didn't you?
Don't get the wrong idea! I'm a woman!
Ugh! I'm not into
that kind of thing, either!
Listen, you... Belldandy's a
thorn in your side, isn't she?
Belldandy?
You heard me.
Just sign a contract with me, and
I'll help you banish Belldandy...
...so you can regain your title
as campus queen.
Did you say Belldandy?
So what are we going to do with this
now?
You can bet Marller will be back for it.
You mean that demon's still around?
Yes, because this CD is
a hindrance to Marller...
A hindrance to her?
Yes.
But as long as it's in our hands,
it won't be easy for her to make a move.
Why don't we just seal her?
That's a good idea!
Thanks to that demon,
I got turned into a scooter...
...I was forced to drink a weird potion
and then I ran all over the city.
I'm the one who made you drink the
potion, and rode you all over the city.
Oh, but I didn't mean...
But if I didn't get turned back,
it would've been such a drag.
I don't mind being a motorcycle,
but not a scooter!
I'll never let her do such a thing!
Even if I have to go head-to-head with
Marller, I'm going to protect you, Keiichi.
But if we do seal her, Marller will have
to wander through the Dark Realm again.
I'd rather not go that far,
if it's at all possible.
All right, then
I'll hold onto this for you.
Just worry about Keiichi,
and nothing else.
Urd...
I'm sure Marller doesn't want to be
sent back to a place like that, either.
That's true, but...
Now that we've settled things,
why don't you two go for a walk?
Brooding over things in the house
won't get you anywhere, you know!
Wait a minute! Urd!
Alrighty, have a good time now!
Really! I don't believe Urd!
Well, we might as well go out,
don't you think?
All right!
There they go.
Even so... that Marller...
can I really trust her?
That's right. If you grant my wish,
I'll help you to banish Belldandy.
Help, did you say?
Fine. So what is this wish of yours?
If you have money in mind,
I'll pay you whatever you ask for.
I have no use for money.
Don't tell me you want to sleep with me!
I told you, I'm a woman! Remember?
Then what is it that you want?
It's quite simple, really.
At least, that's what
she said at the time...
But even if this ends in failure,
it won't really affect me...
...whereas if I succeed,
I'll reap all the benefits!
Now's your chance! Finish him off!
Oh, come on!
Just when we got to the juicy part!
Who's there?
What do you want?
I don't know... this is really awkward!
That must be it.
So, what are you doing here?
If you came to see Belldandy,
she went out with Keiichi.
Well, it's not terribly important, but
I think I'll wait until she comes back.
So you came here to try to
sniff out our dark secrets again?
What do you mean, secrets?
Of course not!
You're really a piece of work, going
to all this trouble to be campus queen.
Excuse me, but didn't you enter the
contest to vie for the title yourself?
You two looked so desperate
to own that title...
...so I graciously yielded
my crown to you.
I'm sorry you didn't realize that!
Who are you to talk, when you're
the one who lost to Belldandy?
If I recall, wasn't it you
who lost to Belldandy?
Those kids aren't old enough to
appreciate a mature woman's splendor!
I guess your breast size
was just right for them.
What does that have to do with it?
My breasts aren't small, either!
I thought you dressed yourself in layers
because you were insecure about them.
If you keep wearing those revealing
dresses, you'll only damage your skin!
But that's better than
not turning any heads.
You're just an exhibitionist, aren't you?
Flat-chested!
Flasher!
Listen, why don't we turn on the TV?
Oh, good idea. There's a show
I want to watch now.
Well, let me turn it on for you.
Oh? Well, thanks.
Channel 6! Channel 6!
All right.
KING OF ENKA
2-hour special
Why, you...
Now you know!
I'll be taking this CD with me, all right?
Not that...
Don't tell me you're in league
with that demon...
Good night...
How did it go?
Here. Is this all right?
Looks like you came up big for me, eh?
Of course.
I am most grateful to you
for granting my wish.
All right, it's my turn. You've got
to hold up your end of the bargain now.
I've already started the wheels turning.
What's that?
This is the Balance Sphere
for Keiichi Morisato's heart.
Keiichi's heart?
That's right.
The human heart is a fragile thing.
Once thrown off balance, he won't hear
the goddess's voice anymore.
Oh, come on! Don't tell me
you're a goddess, too...
No... a devil. That's what I am.
Well, it doesn't matter to me
what you are as long as...
...you get rid of Belldandy for me!
Just leave it to me.
Now, we have a contract.
Put your hand on this Balance Sphere.
Now Keiichi's heart is mired in my spell!
Just one more push, and his heart will be
tipped towards you, just as you wish.
Just as I wish?
I have no feeling for Keiichi!
But if the end result is that
Belldandy disappears, what do you care?
That guy is just a means to the end.
But of course he is!
I'm only using Keiichi Morisato to
banish Belldandy once and for all!
Now all you have to do is
meet up with those two.
But that's easier said than done!
Where in the world are they?
Have no fear. The wheels of Fate
have already begun to turn.
It is inevitable now that
you will encounter them.
Boy, it sure feels good to be outside!
I'm so glad that we decided to go out!
Me, too.
Huh? Is there something on my face?
No, it's not that...
I was thinking that
it's been a long time since...
...we spent any quality time
together like this.
Uh... is that right?
Yes, not since Urd came to stay with us...
Right, things were
pretty hectic for a while.
Yes. That's why I'm so
grateful to you, Keiichi.
Grateful?
Thank you so much for
taking a walk with me!
Really! What's up with her, anyway?
Talking about Fate and all that stuff...
No way am I going to be able
to find those two so easily!
And besides, what am I
supposed to do once I find them?
She left out all the important details!
All right, then, since it's still early
in the day, let's go have a good time!
All right!
Huh?
The rest is up to you, Sayoko.
I really did run into them!
Hello! What a coincidence,
running into each other like this here!
Yes, it certainly is a coincidence.
What are you two doing?
I'm going to take a walk
around the city with Keiichi.
Oh, I see.
I don't see how this is
going to be of any help!
It's such a nice day. We haven't gone out
in so long, so as a change of pace...
That's right.
In your heart you only have eyes for
the woman standing right in front of you!
Is something wrong, Keiichi?
Do you have a fever or something?
Huh? No, it's nothing.
But you're not feeling well...
We'd better go home right away.
What's going on?
We can go for a walk some other time.
Everything's just as it always is.
Sorry to bother you. I'm going now.
Listen, if you'd like,
why don't you come with us?
But you two are on a date, aren't you?
I won't do anything lame
like get in your way.
The three of us can hang out
together, right, Belldandy?
Yes.
We were just thinking of where
we could go have a good time.
If you have a place in mind,
would you take us there?
I have no idea what's come over you,
but I'll keep you company.
I wonder what's up with Keiichi?
What do you mean?
Haven't you ever been to a club before?
Well, I don't usually
come to places like these.
Then I'm amazed you even
had the nerve to ask me out!
That's it, that's it, that's it!
What on earth have you
been doing for fun?
Whatever it is, it's not going
to get you a lot of dates.
Oh, well...
Keiichi?
I think I'll dance, too.
So you're going to challenge me on this
dance floor? I won't lose to you!
Could you teach me how to do that?
If I could dance like you,
I bet I'd have a lot more fun here!
As long as you have talent,
I'd be happy to show you some moves.
Is something wrong?
You don't look too good.
Oh, no... I'm fine, really.
Then maybe you're not having a
good time hanging out with me?
I'll hang out with Sayoko a while longer.
Why don't you go on home
and get some rest?
Ha! Mission accomplished!
The goddess's love can
no longer reach that guy.
All right.
If that's what you want, Keiichi,
I'll go home now and get some rest.
Excuse me.
Hey, are you okay with this?
No...
Keiichi...
Can it be that you no longer need me?
Victory is mine now!
The goddesses will soon be gone...
And the demons will reign
with this Earth as our fortress!
KING OF ENKA 2-hour special
THE END
Next, here is the latest news.
This morning in Nekomi Prefecture...
How dare she subject me to enka...
that woman is the devil incarnate!
If she took that CD, that means
Marller must be behind all this.
This is going to be a pain in the... Huh?
Aha!
What's the matter? You don't look happy.
I was thinking what a great time we had.
I had a good time, too.
I wish she wasn't scared off so easily... I
was hoping for more competition.
Not that I ever actually considered
her to be a true rival, anyway...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, hey, don't worry about it.
Are you ready to order?
Let's see, what should I get?
Two Darjeeling teas, please.
But I haven't told you what I wanted!
Sorry. But listen, it's good,
so just give it a try.
All right. Bring us two of those, then.
Very well.
You were thinking about
Belldandy just now, weren't you?
No, of course not!
Really, now?
You're the one I want to
be with right now, Sayoko.
No, that's not true.
It's not you who I want to be with.
Here is your tea...
You know what... this really isn't for me.
Really? Belldandy said she liked it.
It's her favorite kind of tea.
Impossible!
Why are you bringing her up?
You just told me that
you wanted to be with me!
I can't believe how insensitive you are!
Sorry.
I've had enough.
I'm sorry! It's my fault.
Telling me you were having a good time
with me... you're full of sweet talk!
But at the end of the day,
you only have Belldandy on your mind!
That's not true.
I'll take you to dinner
to make it up to you.
Are you taking me to a restaurant
that meets my standards?
Belldandy's such a terrific cook,
so let's go to my place for dinner...
Are you trying to insult me?
Then, let's go look at the ocean!
You said you loved to listen to
the sound of the wind, right?
No way!
A beach with a beautiful view of
the sunset... that's what I like!
I don't remember ever saying that
I liked listening to the wind!
Sayoko...
If you're going to lie to me,
then do me a favor and lie all the way!
I'm not lying to you...
For god's sake! I'll never know
what Belldandy sees in this moron.
Belldandy?
That's right... Belldandy's the one I...
Tell Belldandy for me...
...that she's the only one who can
handle going out with a moron.
Even if I'm rid of Belldandy,
it's not going to make me any happier.
What a fool! Throwing away
such a golden opportunity!
However! I have the CD in my
possession.
As long as I have this,
those goddesses are nothing to fear.
Hi, Marller! Are you watching?
Urd!
I'll find you, so you'd better brace
yourself!
Spirit of Electricity, Spirit of the Radio
Waves, Spirit of Television...
Heed my call and meld all minds into one.
Channel... Rock!
What the hell?
Not that!
That's right, it's Belldandy!
There you are!
No... damn that Urd!
Taking advantage of the fact that I can't
stop dancing when I hear rock music!
You devil!
Excuse me, but aren't you the devil here?
Now that I've recovered this thing...
No good, she's not home.
Is she out somewhere?
Now where would Belldandy go?
What should I do now?
If Keiichi no longer wishes to have me
by his side, then I have no choice...
...but to return to Heaven.
But that's not it...
I thought I was staying here to
fulfill my job as a goddess, but now...
Keiichi...
I want to be by your side.
Belldandy!
Keiichi!
Wait, don't go!
How did you know I'd be here?
''Where the wind crossing the vast
ocean...''
''...meets the wind that has
descended from the mountains.''
You said it was your favorite
place to be, remember?
I'm sorry I was such a jerk
to you before, but I was wrong...
I only want to be with one person...
and that's you.
Keiichi!
So please, don't ever leave me.
I want you to stay by my side forever!
Then you mean it's all right
to stay by your side, Keiichi?
It's all right to fulfill
our contract, then?
The contract has
nothing to do with this.
I'm not talking about
goddesses or contracts...
All I want... is for you to stay with me.
Keiichi!
What do I care about that girl?
Someday I'm going to defeat Belldandy
without help from anybody!
And when I do, I'll win him over, too...
One day when I woke up...
A day like any other...
another one just beginning.
There you are, yawning...
your face is still so sleepy.
Because each peaceful day
we share is a miracle to me.
This is where my heart
will always return...
Forever...
There's only one thing I wish for.
I chase after the same dream,
wherever it may go.
The love I feel for you
gives me strength.
May tomorrow be as joyful as today...
That's my wish...
It was not only joy that the goddess
bestowed upon this earth.
Who has emerged from the distortion
in time along with these system bugs?
Next episode:
Ah! Who Does Big Sister Belong To?
Don't tell me I've got a rival now!