I've been tall ever since I was young.
When we line up for morning assembly, I'm always at the end.
But I happen to be named "Koizumi."
I'm sorry.
It's not "Oizumi."
That's how it is.
And so...
Summer vacation starts tomorrow.
Everyone needs to watch their health.
Especially the third-years, who will need to prepare for exams soon.
Be careful not to catch a cold.
The first-years should be careful, too...
Damn it!
My summon monsters have all been wiped out!
What an idiot.
Freshman year summer!
I'll definitely find a boyfriend!
So you stayed up all night playing games, huh?
Sorry.
That's not very lady-like.
And sleeping while standing?
Are you a giraffe?
I might have been one in a past life.
Quite the joker, aren't you?
Okay, since you think you're so funny,
...as punishment you'll come to school tomorrow.
No way! Summer vacation starts tomorrow!
You don't get a vacation.
You need to take summer classes.
Huuuuh?
Don't give me that "huh." That's it. Now get going.
Being tall has absolutely no advantages.
No matter what I do, I always draw attention to myself.
Here you go.
Are you making fun of me?
Yeah!
I heard you've been trying really hard on the basketball team.
You're great Kotani-kun.
My name.... is Otani, you idiot!
Move, you amazon.
Here you go, Sensei.
Oh, thanks.
I was being kind and helping you!
How can you turn around and call me an amazon?!
I could call you Kyoshinhei instead…
Shut up, midget!
Oh, you wanna fight?
Bring it on!
Okay, All Hanshin-Kyojin...
Who are you calling that?!
Would you please stop calling me that!
All Hanshin-Kyojin...
The first time Nakano-sensei called us that was on the first day of school.
Does no one want to be class representative?
Hey, what about All Hanshin-Kyojin over there?
We'll have Koizumi and Otani do it.
Whaaat?
Hello!
What the hell?!
What are you doing?! I'm trying to get out!
Move, you amazon.
You're the one who should move, midget.
Okay, okay. The lovers spat ends here.
We're not lovers!
These summer classes are such a pain.
Nobu-chan, you failed the midterm test so it can't be helped.
Well, my darling is going to school for basketball practice anyway,
...so it's fine.
Nakao-kun, huh? That's nice.
Ahh, if I only had a boyfriend, too.
No, at the very least, just someone I like.
Then I would be more motivated.
But you sure are weird, Chiharu-chan.
You actually signed up for this.
As expected from the top student of our grade. You sure think differently from the rest of us.
Well, I didn't want to feel left out.
Okay, okay. We get it.
Hey, I heard that during summer classes all the different classes are grouped together.
I wonder if there'll be any nice guys there.
As long as I won't have to see that midget Otani, it'll be heaven.
I don't really like guys that I don't know.
Why are you here?
I was going to ask the same thing!
Oh, right.
I forget that Otani is a dimwit.
You have no right to say that!
I'm only here because I snored during the graduation ceremony!
That's nothing to be proud of!
At least I didn't fail!
Snoring is so uncool.
All Hanshin-Kyojin, will you perform your comedy routine over the summer, too?
I asked you to stop calling me that!
Nobu-chan, switch seats with me!
Nobu-chan.
Darling.
Oh, I see.
Um... sitting next to a guy.
Okay. You can't do it.
I get it. Okay.
This... This is the worst!
This is the worst summer ever.
I wonder if there'll be any nice guys there.
Sorry, I'm late.
Ah, Suzuki.
I haven't taken attendance yet.
You're just in time.
Starting with Class 1...
Abe!
Here.
Ida!
Yeah.
Ueno!
Here.
Endo!
Omaki!
Here.
Hey, can I sit behind you?
Ah, y-yes!
Please take a seat!
If you sit behind Koizumi, you won't be able to see the board.
Shut up, Otani!
Sorry... I'm a little tall.
That's fine. I can see.
It's love!
Maybe this'll be the best summer ever!
He's dreamy.
What's up with her?
Who knows?
Hey, hey, nee-chan.
I got something to say to you.
Why don't you walk home with me?
Are you a delinquent, midget?
Shut up!
Why should I hang out with you after school?
Because I have something important to say that I can't say here.
How weird... what is it?
You....
...like guys like Suzuki, right?
W-What?!
You sure are easy to read!
How did you find out?
It's written all over your face.
Suzuki-kun
Love at first sight
Are you going to blackmail me for cash?
No way.
I'm a super good guy, you know.
It just happens that I intend to become friends with Suzuki.
I might be able to set you up.
Do you mean it?!
Yes I do!
No way!
Yep yep.
Awesome!
You really are a decent guy after all, Otani.
You only just realized now, idiot?
And here I thought you were someone who bore a grudge against giraffes in his past life.
What's this thing about giraffes?
Well, putting that aside...
All right! It's on me, so order whatever you want.
A jumbo burger, a fish burger, or a super value set meal?
A super value set meal.
Leave it to me!
And.
And?
And...
...Tanaka-san.
Huh?
Tanaka Chiharu-san!
Eh?
Eeeeeeeeh?!
So Chiharu-chan is your type, huh?
Are you an idiot? She's super cute!
From a girl's point of view, I suppose she is kind of cute but...
Well, I guess short people like other short people, huh?
What's she to you?
Actually, I have to tell you something unfortunate.
W-What?
Chiharu-chan dislikes guys.
Seriously?
Very much.
That's so cute!
So what if she doesn't like guys?
I'll cure her of that!
Well then, we're counting on you.
Right! I'll give it my best!
Then we're on the same team.
Sir, we don't allow shadow boxing in here!
The pool?
Yea… Nakao-chi and I are going.
It's going to be fun.
Uh... and...
Um... a friend of mine will be coming, too.
That's okay, right?
Suzuki-kun...
Let's be friends.
It's the pool!
It's just the pool.
A pool can make you that happy?
Incredibly happy!
I haven't been to the pool for a whole year!
Me neither! Me neither!
Splash!
Take this, take this!
This feels so good!
Man, this is great!
This is really different from the school pool.
Idiot!
This is no time to be fooling around!
The same goes for you!
Darn it! I was so happy, I lost sight of my goal.
Suzuki-kun!
Hey, let's go for a swim.
Yeah!
Could it be you didn't really want to come?
If I didn't, I wouldn't have.
Really?
You guys seem interesting.
Interesting?
Suzuki-kun, are you attending summer classes because you failed the midterm?
No. I had a cold the day of the test, so I couldn't take it.
Oh, is that so...
What am I doing?!
A topic... I need to find a topic!
But... But I have no idea what to say!
Heeey!
Koizumi-san?
You guys are having fun?
Let's play beach volleyball, the four of us!
Otani…!
What are you doing?
You call standing around in the water and not doing anything fun?
But I don't know what to say!
That's just because you're trying to pretend to be nice a girl.
What was that?
That's it. That's it.
Just do what you normally do.
Just be yourself.
Hey, that hurt!
Right, let's do this!
Sorry for the wait!
Um...
What is it?
Say, where did Nakao-kun and Nobu-chan go?
Oh yeah...
The two of them went over there a while ago.
To the water slide.
Water...
Slide?
Wow!
Suzuki-kun, let's go on that!
Tanaka-san, lets go on that!
I'm scared of things like that.
Me, too.
Oh, is that so.
Is it okay if we go play for a bit?
Sure.
Go ahead.
Water slide!
My favorite!
Me too!
Where's the entrance?
Over there, over there.
Keep it down! And don't run!
Welcome back.
It was fun, huh?
It was super fun!
Ahh! We did it again.
Oh, where's Suzuki-kun?
I don't know. He's been gone for a while now.
Suzuki-kun?
He went somewhere when I met up with everyone.
She left me all alone and ran off to play with someone else.
I've lost interest.
Oh, he's back.
Suzuki-kun!
Where did you go?
I was a bit thirsty, so I went to get some juice.
I bought enough for everyone.
You sure are thoughtful, Suzuki-kun.
Here, is this okay?
Yeah, thanks.
I got a warm drink for you, Tanaka-san.
For me?
I thought you seemed cold.
Thank you.
Cold.
Sorry. Should I have gotten you a warm drink too?
No, this is fine.
You went on that a lot of times, huh?
It's the best!
It was super fun.
Isn't it scary?
It's not scary at all.
Really?
Well then, I'll give it a try.
Yeah! Go! Go!
I can talk with him normally now.
This is nice.
You sure got tanned.
Amazing, right? I tan really quickly.
Chiharu-chan doesn't seem to dislike guys anymore, either.
That guy really is amazing.
Bye bye.
See ya later!
Is this okay?
What?
Chiharu-chan and Suzuki-kun's houses are in the same direction.
What are you worried about?
Suzuki is a nice guy.
And Chiharu doesn't dislike guys anymore.
She and I were pretty lovey-dovey, too.
Yeah, you guys seemed to be getting along well.
You had a pretty good mood going on too, Koizuni.
Thank you.
This is all thanks to you, Otani.
Right! Let's work hard again tomorrow, okay?
Yeah! Let's reach for happiness together!
Even though I said that,
....I was still filled with an indescribable feeling of dread.
Suzuki-kun sure is a nice guy, huh?
Don't tell me you've fallen for him?!
N-No, no. That's not it.
That's not it.
He is a nice guy.
Yeah, that's right.
He walked me home yesterday.
He walked you home?
I always thought that guys were brutish and scary.
But Suzuki-kun is very kind.
He's not scary at all.
Oh, is that so.
But I thought you were getting along well with Otani yesterday, Chiharu-chan.
Well said, Nobu-chan!
So, what about Otani?
Oh, Otani-kun?
He's really easy to talk to.
Isn't he?
It's probably because he's short, so he doesn't seem like a guy at all.
Fire!
Otani... You're sunk.
Man that was harsh. If Otani had heard that, what would he—
Good morning.
O-Otani…
Good morning, Otani-kun.
Good morning to you, Tanaka-san.
Yesterday sure was fun.
So stiff.
You sure are funny, Otani-kun.
Otani?
I am not Otani.
I am small, therefore I am Kotani.
Pull yourself together, Otani!
It's Kotani.
Please tell the teacher that Kotani will be absent today.
Ko...
Kotani!
It's "Otani."
Otani.
I told you to call me Kotani, didn't I?
Ah.. Um...
What?
Are you trying to comfort me?
Huh?!
Hey, I was just worried about you. What's with that sarcastic attitude?
Who's being sarcastic?!
So what if you got called small?
You're a man, aren't you?
I'm small so I don't count as a guy—
You idiot!
Big or small, as long as you have a **** you're a man, right?!
Girls shouldn't say that word.
Shut up!
Haven't you always been called small?
Acting like this just because a girl said it is pathetic!
If you get so depressed over stuff like this, no one will ever like you, dumbass!
Geez..
Ha. That idiot's punch really woke me up.
Sorry.
Suzuki-kun?!
Good morning.
Good morning?
Class has already started.
Yeah, I'm late.
I'm not good at getting up early in summer.
Is that so?
Well, I don't get up early in the winter either.
Thanks for yesterday. I had fun.
Oh yeah. Me, too.
Um...
What is it?
Am I scary?
Huh?
Yesterday, Tanaka-san seemed scared of me.
Suzuki-kun sure is a nice guy.
Uh.... she's just not comfortable around guys. It's not your fault, Suzuki-kun.
I-Is that so.
Yeah.
But...
...for some reason, I find you easy to talk with, Koizumi-san.
Eh?!
It's probably because we're almost the same height,
...so I don't think of you as a girl.
Uuuh?!
Fire!
Ahh, of course.
I see...
So Tanaka-san doesn't hate me then.
Yeah...
Huh?
D-Don't tell me... you like Chiharu-chan?!
N-No, what are you talking about?
But your face...
No, I'm just hot. Very hot.
Well, I should get going.
Seriously, no.
What the hell?!
He definitely likes her.
That look totally gave it away.
Hey, Oizumi.
You were smacking me just a minute ago.
What are you so depressed for?
Sorry, just forget about what I said before.
What do you mean?
It really is depressing.
I normally pretend to not care,
...but it really hurts when it's coming from the person I like.
You idiot!
That hurt!
That's payback for before.
I'm a girl!
I'm not giving up on Chiharu-chan!
Tomorrow's another day.
Otani...?
If you get so depressed over stuff like this, no one will ever like you!
Those were my grandpa's last words.
Liar!
I'm glad you're here, Koizumi.
If I'd been alone, who knows where I'd have to run off too and hide?
Yeah.
I'm going to keep trying, too.
Right!
Let's do our best!
The summer festival.
I invited Suzuki-kun.
Otani invited Chiharu-chan.
So much for my sexy yukata seduction plan.
It just doesn't look right on a tall woman like me.
Otani!
Chiharu-chan and the others aren't here yet?
The train was packed.
Do you think that maybe they got lost?
What?
I didn't recognize you for a moment.
Do I look weird?
It doesn't suit me at all, right?
Not really.
But you really went all out.
Of course.
Sorry, I was late.
Oh, she's here, she's here.
Risa-chan.
Suzuki-kun is with me.
I bumped into him on my way here.
Oh ho...
To prevent her from getting bumped, he switched positions with her, huh?
It's clear... It's clear, but it's clearly upsetting.
They look pretty good together.
They're like a couple who have just started going out.
Koizumi?
It's fine.
I'm fine now.
I give up.
I give up, too.
Really?
This feels like the ending of the comedy show.
Let's just leave them alone.
Otani...?
Huh? Risa-chan? Otani-kun?
Waah! It broke!
Let me give it a try!
Yeah! Nice!
Hey Otani, next we'll—
H-Huh? Otani?
Otani?
I'm right here.
Oh, you scared me.
You're so short. I thought you got lost in the crowd.
You wanna fight?
Uh, sorry.
How could you say that?
That was pretty awful!
Let's go!
Let's get some grilled cuttlefish.
Otani might be small,
...but his hand still feels like a guy's.
We may always be fighting, but our personalities kind of suit each other.
And we both have height complexes, too.
I like you. Please go out with me.
Okay.
Not long after that, Chiharu-chan and Suzuki-kun became a couple.
Ahh! I feel better now!
That's good.
You and Chiharu-chan looked pretty good together.
But you and Suzuki-kun didn't work out at all.
You...
Well, it's fine.
I can find a girlfriend quickly enough if I want to.
Oh is that so? I'd like to see that.
I challenge you!
Let's see who can get someone faster!
What'll I get if I win?
I'll buy you whatever game you want.
But if I win, you'll buy me a new pair of basketball shoes.
Let's do it.
I'm not going to lose!
Huh?! An ex-girlfriend?!
That's Otani's?!
You...!
Lovely Complex ~ Love Com.
Next: The Ex-Girlfriend Love Triangle?!
Be sure to watch!
The Ex-Girlfriend Love Triangle!?