Man, that was the best!
It freaking rocked!
A Guy You Like, or a Guy from the Past?
I was so worked up!
Me too!
But as expected, that song was the best.
It was awesome hearing it live.
Totally awesome!
Totally!
I'm still totally worked up!
It was just awesome!
Risa?
Risa!
Huh?
Huh!?
Who are you?! Who are you?! Who are you?!
It's me, Haruka.
Fukagawa Haruka.
Haruka?
Don't you remember me?
I lived near you when we were in elementary school.
Elementary school?
Risa is recollecting
Recall
He's a boy but his name is Haruka-chan.
He must have boobies.
I don't have boobies!
Hey!
You guys are teasing Haruka again?
Oh crap!
Risa-chan...
Oh... Oh!
You're that Haruka!
Yeah, I'm that Haruka!
Wow! Long time no see!
I hardly recognized you!
I thought you went overseas.
I just got back.
You've grown taller.
I'm 185cm now.
Really?!
I'm taller than you now.
You sure are!
Boy, this brings back memories.
I've got to get going.
Huh?
Wait... Otani?
It sure does bring back memories!
How's your mom doing?
Good. How's your family?
My family? Everyone's doing pretty well.
Is that so?
Which school are you going to now, Risa?
Oh, Maido High.
Oh, so you're going there.
Everyone! Happy New Year!
Happy New Year!
Yo! I haven't seen you for a while.
You're getting even taller.
I am not!
How are things going with your ex-girlfriend these days?
They're not.
How about you, Koizumi?
Who was that guy?
That guy?
The guy that suddenly hugged you in the middle of the street.
Oh, Haruka?
He's a childhood friend of mine.
He moved overseas when we were in the fifth grade.
Do you actually care?
You're the one who's always saying "ex this," and "ex that."
Please bless me with a boyfriend this year.
Hey, something's coming out of you.
Shut up!
This way. Come on, this way.
What are you doing?
Go on, go on, Otani.
What?
Kanzaki...
Atsushi-kun.
Uh... H-How are you?
Good.
Is this the girl you went to the Christmas concert with?
I'm Koizumi Risa.
Sorry to cause all that trouble a few days back.
I'm sorry! I didn't realize that Atsushi-kun was seeing someone already.
Huh?!
No, no, no! No, no, no!
There's absolutely nothing going on between me and Otani!
There's no love between us at all.
So if there's something you want to tell Otani,
...don't hesitate for my sake and say whatever you want to say.
Okay?! Okay?! Okay?!
I'll do everything I can to support you!
I don't know exactly what happened between you two, but I'll support—
What the hell did you say just now?!
What's your problem?!
This is important to you, isn't it?!
Just hear her out, okay.
It's none of your business!
Um...
I didn't choose him because of his height!
Huh?
It's just that the person I liked happened to be tall.
I don't dislike Atsushi-kun because he's short.
Huh?
Later when I thought about it, I realized it looked like I'd done something awful.
But even so, I felt really awkward about explaining it to you.
Um... I'm sorry.
I'm a little confused now, but...
...was that what you wanted to say?
Yes.
It was good to get it off my chest.
I feel much better now!
Bye then.
So... Sorry, Otani!
I'm so sorry! Truly sorry! Extremely sorry!
Huh?
I know.
You can hit me, kick me, do whatever you want to me.
Koizumi...
I'm sorry!
I had no idea that was what she wanted to say.
I though she wanted to get back together with you.
It was really none of my business.
Thanks.
Thanks to you, I heard what she had to say.
Wh-what?
You should be more upset! What I did was—
That's enough, okay!
That's enough.
To tell the truth, I was holding onto a bit of hope,
...but I've completely given up now.
I'm just saying that, though.
What... do you mean?
Oh, there! There they are.
Hey, want to go get some lunch?
Let's go!
In the end, the boyfriend/girlfriend challenge didn't go anywhere.
When I finally realized that, it was already Valentines Day.
Chiharu-chan...
...chocolate cake or chocolate cookies?
Which is better?
Cookies are much easier to make.
That's true.
Say, why don't we make those cookies?
Okay. They look delicious!
You guys seem pretty happy.
I asked you to join us, didn't I?
I have no one to give cookies to, even if I do make them.
You have Otani, don't you?
Huh?
Why should I give cookies to Otani?!
He ended up with his feelings hurt again because of your mistake,
...so you owe him a pretty big apology, don't you?
Th-That's...
Right? It's a good idea, huh?
Morning!
What's up? You look pretty happy today.
Lend me your ear.
My ear?
Listen.
What's this?
New song by Umibouzu?
Not exactly.
It's their album from when they were with an indie label.
U M I B O U Z U
I found it at a second-hand music store.
Are you serious?!
This is a discontinued release, so it's hard to find now.
Are you serious?! Woo-hoo!
They get along well, don't they.
They're both so carried away that they could totally get together right now.
Is Umibouzu responsible for that?
I made this chocolate myself.
Please accept it.
Hey, do you want chocolate cake or cookies for Valentines Day?
What? Are you going to make something yourself?
Yeah. Risa's going to be helping us out, too.
Huh? You're talking about that again?
Huh? How sickening.
Who'd fall victim to such a thing?
What do you mean "fall victim to"?!
If any guy eats chocolate made by this amazon, he'll get sick.
And he'll probably grow huge to boot.
Koizumi?
You're right.
No one would be happy to receive chocolate made by a huge girl like me.
I've never even been on a date.
I don't have any fans who think I'm cute, either.
Huh?
I... I....
H-Hey!
I'll probably never give out any chocolate until the day I die!
Calm down, Koizumi!
What's up with you?!
Why are you always acting so strangely?
It's nothing.
I get it.
You can give me your chocolate.
I don't want you to accept it half-heartedly out of pity.
It's not like that.
I like sweets.
It's okay if you'd rather not give it to me, though.
Oh... I like chocolate cake, okay?
I-I-I never said I'd make anything for you!
I'm just saying.
Otani, you're too slow!
Right!
Um...
Yeah?
We always see you and Otani-kun together.
Are you guys going out?
Huh? No, no. It's nothing like that!
I thought so.
That would be impossible, huh?
Otani-kun wouldn't date a huge girl like that, after all.
You're right.
Those girls will be giving Otani chocolate too, won't they?
Probably.
If he's going to receive so much chocolate, he probably won't need mine.
Risa...
Risa!
Risa! It's so nice to see you again!
Ughh... Haruka, I can't breathe.
Who's that?
Phew. That was close.
You...
Why'd that guy come to our school yesterday?
He came to complete his student-transfer paperwork.
Huh? He's transferring here?
Yeah. He's starting in April.
Oh, That's great!
He's your type, right Koizumi?
Ah, no way! No way!
He used to be a hopeless crybaby.
His grandma's British, so he used to look just like a foreign girl.
Haruka
All his friends were girls,
...and he had a girly personality, too.
What a hopeless guy.
Too true!
He may be good looking now, but...
Huh? Damn it!
I should have said he was my ex-boyfriend!
How stupid am I?! I'm too honest!
What's this?
I thought I was about to lose to you,
...but I guess it's not that easy for a tall girl to get a boyfriend, huh?
Anyway...
Anyway, you don't have any plans today, right?
Let's go to the CD store and look for some more Umibouzu CD's.
Sure.
Risa!
Risa, this chocolate cake looks really easy to make.
Let's make this one.
Oh, it looks delicious!
Chocolate cake?
I'd better have my stomach pills ready.
S-screw you! I'm not making it!
Not for you, anyway!
Okay, okay.
Risa!
He's here again?
Haruka? What's up?
I came to pick you up.
If you're free, let's have tea together.
Uh, sorry. I've already made plans with Otani today.
Otani?
Oh, it's okay. I—
What...!
What on earth is this little creature?!
What are you talking about?!
Now that I think of it, Risa,
...you were taking this little guy out for a walk a few days ago too, right?
Don't talk about me like I'm a pet!
You're not fit to be seen with a beauty like Risa.
Oh my...
How is she a beauty?!
Now, now...
Gee, I'm so embarrassed!
This guy's an idiot.
There must be something wrong with his head.
What's your problem?!
You're so rude!
Who are you calling rude?!
Wanna fight, baldy?
How am I bald? Are you an Idiot?
I can't take this!
This guy keeps getting on my nerves!
Now, now. Take it easy, Otani.
Otani?
Is this the guy you just told me you had plans with?
Yeah.
This can't be!
You're so cool, Risa!
It's totally uncool for you to be seen with a midget like him!
You've been my hero for a long time now.
I hope that you'll always be as cool as you were back then.
Your hero?
I'll kill you!
Even if I kill you, God will forgive me for it!
Calm down, Otani!
Shut up, midget.
Risa is my personal hero.
I won't let you have her!
Huh?!
Let's go, Risa!
Huh? Wait...
Haruka?!
Don't... Don't say something so unreasonable!
Next
Day
Uh... About that...
Haruka isn't really a bad guy.
This is the first time I've ever come across such a mean guy.
Oh, is that so?
Don't get me involved in such an unreasonable situation.
I had no idea!
Haruka said that stuff out of nowhere!
You're the hero. Do something about it.
The hero...
The hero, huh?
A man who needs a woman's protection is just pathetic.
Man...
It's even more pathetic for a man to be that short.
Haruka!
You...!
Good morning, Risa!
I made you a lunch box.
Do you like wieners?
Don't go barging into other people's classrooms!
You're not a student here yet!
Have you no shame?!
You're quite a noisy midget, aren't you?
A midget should act like a midget. Now be quiet and stay out of sight.
Risa,
...could you go over there for a minute?
Idiot Trio
Look, we've captured an alien!
Arghh! I'm gonna kill you!
Th-Thanks for the lunch box. You'd better get going now!
Huh? So soon?
Hey. Otani, who was that guy just now?
Her childhood friend.
Those two look pretty good together.
They're both tall like models.
Come to think of it, Koizumi-san is really pretty, isn't she?
I've always thought so.
Yeah, you're right. She's really beautiful!
But she looks like one half of All Hanshin-Kyoujin when she's with Otani.
You guys are gonna say the same thing he did?!
What the hell?! Is it my fault that Koizumi's so freaking tall?!
Is it?!
It does kinda seem that way.
So tired...
Amazon!
What?!
All Hanshin-Kyojin returns.
Your cake looks really nice, Risa-chan.
No way.
Do I seriously have to give this to Otani?
Yep.
Never mind. I...
Otani is already super mad at me because of Haruka.
I wonder if Haruka-kun likes you, Risa-chan...
"Like"? That guy only sees me as his hero.
His hero?
A hero is normally a man, right?
I don't look very feminine, do I?
But he said you were beautiful.
I think so, too.
If you were more serious about it, you'd probably be really popular.
Give it a rest.
How am I supposed to be more serious?
Take part in girly activities from time to time, like a girl, for example.
Here.
W-Wait...
Something is coming out of your body.
Don't want it.
What did you just say?
How come you say you don't want it now?
You're making me feel stupid!
I don't care.
You don't care?
Valentines Day doesn't mean anything to me, but you said you wanted this!
Who said they wanted it?!
I only said if you had nobody to give your chocolate to, you could give it to me!
That's why I am giving this to you.
You have that annoying Haruka now, don't you?
Haruka's not—
Oh, Koizumi is giving chocolate to Otani!
No way! Are you serious?
Y-You've got it all wrong! I was just...
It's a CD! It's a CD I wanted to borrow, right?
Y-Yeah.
Liar. I can smell chocolate.
It's not for me.
It's for her childhood friend, right?
What? What are you saying?
So that's how it is.
Fine then. I'm giving this to Haruka.
Give it to me.
Risa.
Haruka?
I came to pick you up again today.
That's an excuse, though.
I was actually hoping to receive Valentine's chocolates from you.
This is for you.
Really?! Thank you!
It's nothing. You don't need to thank me.
I'll never eat it!
I'll treasure it my entire life!
Don't keep it! You'd better eat it quickly, otherwise it'll go bad!
But I kept the chocolates you gave me before.
Don't keep them! Just throw them away!
Don't want it.
Want to hang out with me for a bit?
All right!
Heh, I lost.
Ahh, I feel much better now!
You're still so good when it comes to games.
You're cool no matter what you do.
Hearing that doesn't make me happy at all.
Why? That's what I like most about you, Risa.
You're the only one who would say a thing like that.
Everyone's always calling me All Hanshin-Kyojin at school.
That's because you've always got that midget hanging around you.
What's your relationship with that guy, anyway?
Our relationship?
It's not like we have a relationship, as such.
We're just in the same class, and walk home the same way.
You're cool, Risa!
You're wasting your time hanging around with him. He's totally uncool.
You say that, but he actually has a lot of good qualities.
He trains really hard at basketball, even though he's short.
And whenever I'm in trouble, he always come to my rescue.
And on Christmas...
Risa...
A-Anyway, he's not a bad guy.
...you like that guy, don't you?
Huh?
Wh-What are you talking about?
That's ridiculous!
It's okay.
No matter what happens, I won't lose to that midget.
Huh?
I always dreamed that you'd one day be my girlfriend,
...and we'd spend our high school days together, swept up in romance.
One of these days I'll declare my love for you, and ask you to be my girlfriend.
Please think about how you'll answer me.
Sorry.
Never mind. It was only obligatory chocolate, anyway.
Right. Obligatory chocolate.
OBLIGATION
Otani is kissing?
The era of short guys is coming!
What's that?
Lovely Complex ~ Love Com.
Next: Kiss! I've Fallen for You!
Kiss! I've Fallen for You!
Be sure to watch!