I always dreamed that you'd one day be my girlfriend,
...and we'd spend our high school days together, swept up in romance.
One of these days I'll declare my love for you, and ask you to be my girlfriend.
Please think about how you'll answer me.
Sorry.
Nevermind. It was only obligatory chocolate, anyway.
Right. Obligatory chocolate.
Kiss! I've Fallen for You!
You're in your second year of high school, yet you still yawn in the morning?
Leave me alone.
As they say, "When hibernating, one sleeps a sleep that knows no dawn," idiot.
It isn't "hibernation," it's "spring." "In spring, one sleeps a sleep that knows no dawn."
Well, I guess you can put it that way, too.
You're such an idiot.
Shut up, you totem pole!
Yeah, yeah, that's right!
Atsushi-kun needs to grow a widdle bit bigger, doesn't he?
You...!
Someone, please help me!
Yeah, hold still for a sec.
Okay, okay.
There, there, boy. That's enough.
What are you, an animal loving old man?
You're a good boy, aren't you. Don't pick on girls, okay?
You're hopeless when it comes to dealing with females,
...but when it comes to males you're a genius.
Idiot! He's a male dog.
A genius when it comes to dealing with males?
See ya. Bye bye.
Um... thank you very much!
What's your name?
You don't need to worry about my name.
See ya.
I've fallen for him!
New Class Formation Notice
What's everyone gathered around for?
Oh, right. It's the new class list.
Risa! We're in the same class again.
Really? That's great!
I'm by myself in the class next door though.
But Chiharu-chan, you and Suzuki-kun are in the same class.
Eh?
Good morning.
Good to see you.
Yes.
I'm in the same class as you.
Me, too.
How wonderfully heartwarming.
Darling, we're in the same class again!
Really? I'm so glad!
Nobu-chan.
Darling.
Huh?!
I'm in the same class as you again?!
When will I be able to shake being known as one of the half of All Hanshin-Kyojin?!
Just grow a little more, and eveything will be fine.
Shut up! Why don't you try shrinking?!
Don't ask for the impossible!
It feels like we haven't changed at all,
...but things are a little different from last year.
We have the same homeroom teacher again, too.
This is his doing, isn't it?!
Otani is my natural enemy, but...
...for some reason he gives me an odd feeling.
Could it be that I... towards Otani...
No way, no way. That's impossible. Impossible!
Koizumi?
Huh?
There seems to be a familiar name in the class next door.
Fukagawa Haruka
Haruka?!
One of these days I'll declare my love for you, and ask you to be my girlfriend.
Risa...
What a shame. I'll be going now.
You traitor!
Even though the chocolate you gave me on Valentine's Day was only obligatory chocolate,
...I decided not to give up and considered it just another step towards reaching my goal.
But I didn't get placed in the same class as you.
Oh yeah. You said that you were going to transfer to this school in April, huh.
"Oh yeah"? "Oh yeah"?!
Don't tell me... Don't tell me you forgot all about me, Risa?!
How could I do a thing like that?! I'm not that forgetful, you know!
Liar! You did forget! How cruel...
I didn't! It's not like that at all...
Risa, if you don't hurry, you'll miss the opening ceremony.
Nice flow.
So Haruka, I'll see you later, 'kay?
Risa...
You traitor!
Let go of me, you giant!
I just thought I'd be in your way.
Your concern was completely unnecessary!
They never change, do they.
A husband and wife double act.
What was that?!
And in the same breath, too.
Otani and I will be in the same class together for one more year.
So he's a senpai at my school?
Yay!
2nd Year Class 3
Now, we're supposed to decide on the general representatives and what have you...
But it's always a pain, so we'll just vote for class reps first,
...and let them deal with everything else, okay?
Yes sir.
Well then...
Do not make eye contact with that old man, Koizumi.
I know.
Well then, why don't we pick Koizumi and Otani,
...who seem to be magically communicating using only their eyes?
What?!
All in agreement.
Aye!
What?
Wait!
It's decided. Congratulations.
The class supports you 100%
Sorry to bring this up now,
...but we need to organize the opening ceremony for the first-years.
Why don't you two go help out?
What the hell?!
Amazing! Their timing is so precise!
So these two were the famous "All Hanshin-Kyojin" back in the first year?
This...
Whatever. I give up.
Huh?! You're betraying me again?
Just consider this a continuation of last year. It'll be fine.
Let's go, Otani.
Okay.
Huh?
Where do you think you're going?
Basketball club.
Liar.
They're arranging things for the opening ceremony in the gym right now.
Where are you gonna play basketball?
Sheesh! We're gonna practice in the park!
What about helping out for the ceremony?!
You gonna skip out?
I don't have time for stuff like that right now.
Why not?
I'm going to be a regular on the basketball team this year.
Really?
It's true.
It was decided during spring break.
Awesome, huh?
He's the only second-year on the team.
You don't need to say that.
He's the number-one candidate to be the next team captain.
I told you not to say stuff like that, didn't I?
That's right... he's worked so hard...
But you sure look happy.
So anyway...
This and that are two different things.
So aggravating...
You are seriously aggravating, woman!
Shut up!
It's your fault for accepting the job as class rep in the first place.
As a man, I'd be uncool if I didn't accept in that kind of situation.
Even if that is the case, don't drag me into it if you're just showing off!
You're such a pain in the ass!
Shut up, totem pole!
Quiet, midget!
All right everyone, thank you for your hard work.
Risa, are you done yet?
Uh, yeah.
Sorry for making you wait.
It's okay.
Look, look. The first-years are already trickling in.
They're all in crisp new uniforms.
It looks like they're fresh off the shelf.
That reminds me, Nobu-chan.
You came to our opening ceremony in a really cute casual outfit,
...and got told off by the teachers, huh?
Ahh, that was just because I didn't have my uniform at the time.
What do you mean you don't have a uniform yet?
Even if you didn't get your uniform in time for the opening ceremony,
...couldn't you have dressed more formally?
I could have, but...
I got this really cute top yesterday,
...so I really wanted to wear it, and...
Sorry.
Even if you say "sorry"...
But it's cute, right?
Even if it is, today is not the day to wear it!
This is a formal occasion!
Oh dear.
And on the first day of school, too. Poor thing.
Right?
What is it?
That girl's not bad.
Huh?
This is bad.
My pride is...
What did you say?!
I mean, when I get as old as you,
...I won't be able to wear cute clothes anymore.
I have to wear them as often as I can while I'm still young,
...otherwise I'll turn into an old lady before I know it.
Who are you calling an old lady?!
Oh... I didn't mean you, Sensei.
Oh my, oh my.
Sensei! Some boys are fighting over there!
That's awful!
Just kidding.
Senpai, you're the one from this morning.
Oh, it's you.
You know her?
Yeah. Kind of.
Um... That "just kidding" just now...
That teacher is really strict so be careful, okay?
If you let her, she'll lecture you for a whole hour.
You saved me again!
Thank you so much!
It was nothing.
Now, now. Don't worry about it.
She's so cute...
Hey, Koizumi.
I'm gonna get going. Will you be okay?
Uh, yeah. I'll be fine.
Huh?
Why do I have to come shopping with you?
I will not lose to those new girls.
Don't let them bother you.
You don't have to treat them as your rivals.
How can I not?!
But still, it's not like you've got money to spare.
I don't give my rich granny a shoulder rub every night for nothing.
Aww, this would really suit Otani.
Idiot! What does that matter?!
I'm going to be a regular on the basketball team this year.
What are you doing?
The shop assistants are staring.
Ahh! I'm gonna buy that!
Wh-What the hell is this?
How rude. I told you, It's a present.
What is it?!
Is it cursed? Is it a trap? It has to be a trap, right?!
Ah, I see what you're doing.
You want the signed Umibouzu CD that I found in that used CD store.
Like hell I'll give it to you!
That's not it at all!
I was just giving you a present since you're a regular on the basketball team now.
But if you don't want it, give it back!
Huh? Seriously?
I lied. I bought it for myself.
See. Cool, huh?
Wow, it really is cool!
Hey, wait...
Cool, huh?
I-I guess...
Thanks. I accept it.
Ahh, strange things do happen.
I just felt like getting it for you.
Risa, what's the matter?
I'm starting to think it's more than just a height problem. My real problem is within.
Huh?
If only I could make myself cuter.
Cuter?
What's all this? You're talking like a young maiden in love all of a sudden.
I seem like that?
Yeah.
That's a problem.
Senpai!
Hello!
Thanks for the help during opening ceremony.
Hello.
Oh no. This could get bloody.
Oh! That bracelet is so cute! Where'd you get it?
Oh, this? Well, this is...
You're friends now?!
But this girl is just so sweet!
I see.
So, did you want something?
Are you two in any clubs?
Not really.
Are you going to join any?
They're holding an introduction for the various clubs in the gym tomorrow.
I was going to check them out and then decide.
Oh, Darling said he was going to dress in black for that.
In black?
What kind of introduction is the basketball club going to be doing?
Who knows.
I think Otani-kun will be making an appearance, too.
It sounds like fun, huh?!
I'll be sure to check out the basketball club, then!
So cute.
Girls that cute exist in this world...
...so why am I like this?
God is so cruel.
Self Study
Is it really okay for us to skip class to watch this?
It's fine. It's self study anyway.
It's not fair that people in clubs get to miss class.
And I want to see my darling dressed in black, anyway.
So, what's with this dressing in black thing?
That was the swimming club.
Who knows...
Next is the basketball club.
We, the boys basketball club, currently have eleven members.
Boys Basketball
We're a great club, ranked quite highly within the region.
However, we still welcome new members anytime.
Even if you're not that good, I'm sure you'll improve!
Where are Nakao-kun and Otani?
Huh? That's weird...
Okay everyone, please turn around and look behind you!
Even that short boy over there...
It's Otani.
After joining our club, he can now perform a slam dunk.
Huh?
Now, go for it!
Okay. A round of applause, please!
What the heck was that?
How funny.
How pathetic.
No! I didn't want to see my boyfriend doing that!
See, even a shortie can slam dunk.
I'm sure his mama would be overjoyed.
Who's the shortie?!
We, the boys basketball club, welcome you all!
Height isn't a problem, so you can join even if you're short.
Stop that...
Stop...
It's love!
See ya.
What the heck was that just now?
You shouldn't have come to watch.
See that?
Nobu-chan is so shocked,
...she still hasn't recovered.
I thought it was fun.
It wasn't fun at all.
What would you know?!
We were just trying to recruit new members.
Our training really is strict, so a lot of people quit right away.
We just want more poeple to start off.
I wonder if you'll get anyone with such a lame-ass stunt.
Wha-What'd you say?!
It wasn't lame!
Oh, it's that girl from before.
Who?
You know, that girl who was hassled by that dog on her first day.
Ohhh...
Don't you remember me?
Don't worry about it.
This guy's just an idiot.
A real birdbrain.
I'm gonna smack you!
W-Well... it's okay.
Huh?
Senpai, that dunk just now, it was really cool!
You hear that?!
Thanks.
It's love!
I'm Otani Atsushi.
Second year, class three.
Nice to meet you.
Ah, I'm Kotobuki.
First year, class four.
Kotobuki Seiko.
"Seiko-chan"... How cute.
Um...
Huh?
I've fallen for you.
Huh?!
Uh... Umm...
Ahh! I'm so sorry!
My body tends to move before I can think.
You didn't want me to do that, did you?
Uh, it's not really like that.
Um... This might be kind of weird after that...
If you want, we can start out as friends...
...but will you go out with me?
Okay.
What...?!
I'm so happy!
What the hell was that?!
I'm a sinful man.
I've captured Seiko-chan's heart so easily.
No way...
I don't have a comeback...
Lovely Complex ~ Love Com.
Next: Send Forbidden Love Flying!
Send Forbidden Love Flying!
Be sure to watch!