Quiz (review problems)
I don't get it.
This's totally beyond me.
Nibutani
Napping?
Magic?
Why would Nibutani join that stupid circle?
Nibutani
She's the Nibutani who won the first cutie poll,
the girl who's so popular with all the guys in class!
Nibutani
I don't get it.
Is she really into magic?
Or does she have a fondness for napping?
Or maybe... No way! But what if...
Huh? Why did I join?
Sorry! I just couldn't stop thinking about it.
I was wondering if you really liked napping that much...
You want to know?
Y-Yeah...
I guess a certain someone...
is a little slow on the uptake, isn't he?
No way, no way, no way!
Guys tend to misinterpret those situations
I love you!
and end up making fools of themselves!
I bet 80% of the planet's male
population has been there before!
Let's stay calm and think this through one more time.
Ouch!
What's she doing?
Let the Sabbat be joined.
Affix your blood seal within the circle.
I wound up joining Rikka's circle.
What are you doing, Togashi?
Uh, I just...
Needless to say, I'm not interested in the slightest!
Stop fooling around and focus on your work!
I'm sorry...
It's just that her words kept echoing in my head.
I decided to join your circle!
I just handed in my application.
She called it my circle...
shibaraku mitsumeatte kara
We looked into each other's eyes for a while
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no?
What did you think of while it lasted?
ki ni naru
I want to know that
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
Look at me as I now pout my lips
dou shita no tte kiite kuru no?
Will you ask me what's wrong?
matte miru no
I'm waiting
gomakashita ato no hitorigoto wa hazukashii kara
I'm embarrassed by what I mutter after being so evasive
kikanaide kureru?
So please don't pay it any attention
ato ni hikenai hodo hikareau koi
Our love is so strong we can't run away
mou hajimatteta
It's already begun
yume nara takusan mita
I've dreamed of our meeting so often
sameta mama demo mada aitai
Now I'm awake, and still I want to meet you
kimi ga sou saseta
You did this to me
koi ga yokubari da ne
Love is greedy
My heart seems to hop with glee, so I'll let it guide me
tobihanesou na kokoro no yuku mama ni yukou yo
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
My ideals, delusions and reality
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
Are all about you
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
Far Eastern
Magic Nap Society
of Summer
Mabinogion... of regrets
I doubt Nibutani would be here...
What the—
Looks like the Dark Flame Master has answered the summons.
The Arcane Sigil of Saturn works just as I expected.
Its tremendous power calls creature after creature to this world.
You kno—
What the hell is that?
What have you drawn on the floor?!
You don't even know about magic circles? Did your brain suffer an untimely death?
I know it's a magic circle. What I'd like to know is why you drew it on the floor.
I told you during class, didn't I?
We're holding the Sabbat.
Yeah! And we already have a sacrifice for Death.
Pitcher plants, so yummy...
The hell? And don't bring the cat to school!
The purpose of our society is to find the Ethereal Horizon.
The chimera is essential.
Master! Let's summon something else with this sacrifice!
Very well.
In the name of the Wicked Eye, I summon thee.
Thou art the Dark Massacre.
Thine blood, flesh, and form are all unseen.
Deathly awesome, isn't it?
You're seriously going way too far!
Master! Do it now!
Once more!
Wow! Master, you're so cool!
Wanna try?
Yeah! I wanna do it every day until my death!
Darkness beyond twilight.
Crimson beyond blood that flows.
Let the fools who stand in our way be destroyed!
Dragon Slave!
What the...
What do you think you're doing?!
You're great, Master! You understand!
Of course.
Damn! I'm nothing compared to you!
Clean your mess up!
Our own summon's ordering us around. I'm so ashamed I'd welcome death.
He's the Dark Flame Master, after all.
Less chatter, more cleaning.
Kumin, you wake up too!
Sundews are so bitter...
What is she dreaming of?
Hello!
N-Nibutani!
Sorry for taking so long to stop by after I joined.
I've been busy at the cheerleaders'.
Worry not. Our search for the Ethereal Horizon proceeds as we speak.
Ethereal... what?
Don't worry about it.
What's this?
I-It's nothing!
Oh, is that a magic circle?
So you're seriously researching magic?
It's just for decoration!
The goal of our society is to find the Ethereal Horizon.
We unite the powers of the Wicked Eye,
the Mjolnir Maul,
and the Dark Flame Master to that end.
H-Hold on a sec!
I told you not to call me that!
What are you whispering about, Dark Flame Master?
Why are you so deathly silent, Dark Flame Master?
You're doing it on purpose.
What do you mean, Dark Flame Master?
Dark Flame Master!
Open the door! Release me this very instant!
Are you sure?
Don't worry. She'll get used to it.
This barrier might be connected to the Otherworld!
See?
Wh-What?!
Ah, that's Tsuyuri Kumin.
She's a second-year who joined as well.
Her hobby is napping.
Remember how the circle's name has "nap" in it?
Oh, right!
Then you're here to nap too?
Th-That isn't really it either.
Then why did you join?
Well, um...
Hey, what about you? Why did you join?
Why did I join? It's, uh... It's hard to say it to your face, okay!
That sounds so suggestive! Does it mean what I think it does?!
It's gone!
What is it now?
The Mabinogion is nowhere to be seen! It's gone!
I put it in this locker!
Mabinogion?
Ah, that book you had earlier?
If it was taken to the Otherworld by—
Don't worry.
It's at my place.
I accidentally took it home with me when we were cleaning up the other day.
Give it back!
Give it back now, or face your death!
Okay! I'll bring it next time.
Give it back! Give it back!
Give it back already!
What are you doing?
Oh, it's almost time for cheerleader practice, so I gotta go.
Okay.
Togashi, can we talk for a sec?
Sunday?
Yeah. Or any time you're free.
Is that all right?
No problem, but there's nothing to do at my place... Why there?
No reason. Just wanted to have some time with you alone.
Okay?
What should I do now?
This is weird, no matter how I look at it.
Let's go home together!
Let's go home together!!
Let's go home together!!!
Let's go home together!
Let's go home together!!
Let's go home together!!!
It's not like I raised our affinity parameter little by little.
Geez, you're so hopeless...
There weren't any special events either,
Let's go then
.  .  .  .  .  .
By the way...
and yet this event's happening already.
There's this place I'd like you to come with me...
Okay
No way!
That usually means I'm in for a bad end...
But this is the real world!
I understand your plight.
How long have you been there?!
I was searching for intel on the Ethereal Horizon.
Sadly, I only found one such document.
Melon Girl
Has your mind been corrupted by the human world?
I'm sorry...
Wait, I'm not in the wrong here!
You are! The Dark Flame Master must avert his gaze from such things!
What?
Well, whatever.
Got plans for this Sunday?
Sunday?
I cannot divulge any part of my plans due to fears of informati—
Just tell me!
Nothing in particular.
I feared as much. That means...
The view's so pretty!
Really? Not half as pretty... as...
you...
What?
You leave me no choice!
Rikka, let me show you something cool.
Something cool?
Yeah! This is a way to cross over to the
Otherworld that I discovered in junior high.
Listen!
How to cross over to the Otherworld
Firstly, walk to the seventh pylon and chant "Wolensak Tanbur Wetzler!"
Then do the same at the third pylon, followed by the fourth and the ninth.
You must not talk with any humans along the way.
Next, go to the thirteenth pylon and put the mirror under it.
13th pylon
You talk, you fail.
It might take a while, but if you follow this path, you can find the link between the two worlds.
What do you think?
The link...
"At 4pm the second hands of the clocks in both worlds coincide."
"At that time, if you go to the point shown by the the 13th pylon from the station..."
Four hours remain. We should hurry.
I'm so excited!
I wanna see what curry tastes like in the Otherworld!
I didn't think my Darkness Notes would ever be useful.
New e-mail
Nibutani Shinka
Hey there
Body
I'm one station away.
New e-mail
Nibutani Shinka
Hey there
Body
I'm one station away.
New e-mail
Nibutani Shinka
Hey there
Body
I'm one station away.
New e-mail
Nibutani Shinka
Hey there
Body
I'm one station away.
New e-mail
Nibutani Shinka
Hey there
Body
I'm one station away.
New e-mail
Nibutani Shinka
Hey there
Body
I'm one station away.
Togashi!
Hey!
My real youth begins from this moment!
Wow, your room's really tidy!
Is it?
Togashi, do you have any brothers or sisters?
Yeah, two little sisters.
But they both went somewhere with our mom.
So it's just you?
Yeah, we've got the house to ourselves until tonight.
I-I didn't mean it like that!
Like what?
Uh, I... um...
I-I'll make some tea.
It's okay!
My heart can't take much more!
But I can't rush ahead just yet.
Back in junior high, I got way ahead of myself!
When I think of how we met in our previous life, it speaks to me of our future.
I put all my magic into this e-mail.
Love you forever.
Die! Die! Why won't those memories die?!
Huh?
Did that come from my room?
Is everything all right?
What's up, Togashi?
Uh, what...
Um, I'll go get the tea.
It's okay!
What was that all about?
Come on, where is it?!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Where did he put it?
Dimensional Seal
Here?
Could it be in this box?
W-W-Wait—
Don't look in there!
Where is it?
Where is what?
The Mabinogion that stupid girl had!
Why?
Just tell me!
Um...
It was somewhere... Ah, here!
It's quite heavy.
Wh-What?
I may have lost my memories,
but I, a true magician, have walked this sphere of existence for five centuries.
Thus, I inscribe these truths as suggested to me by the spirits.
For my name is Forest Summer.
Stop!
Don't... Don't make me listen to that!
I presume you understand that this world consists of the Black and White Planes.
Make it go away! Make it go away!
That reaction...
Wait a moment.
Ni
bu
ta ni
Shin
ka
Nibutani Shinka...
Shinka...
Ni
bu
ta ni
Shin
ka
Forest Summer...
Shin
ka
Forest
Summer
Shin
ka
Forest Summer!
Shin
ka
What a weird book.
I wonder who wrote this
piece of crap!
Damn it! Screw this stupid garbage!
Nibutani... that's...
Let us open the gateway through spacetime.
Okay, Master!
Are you ready? This could be dangerous.
I was born ready!
Then let us—
Oh no! Schwarz Sechs Prototype Mark II!
Wait for us!
Uh...
It's funny, isn't it?
I deleted it from everywhere I could on the Internet.
But I never would've thought someone would actually print it out.
I never would've thought you'd write something like that in the first place.
I made sure I chose a different high school to everyone else from my junior high,
just so I could leave that dark past behind me.
Got it? If you so much as think of telling anyone, I'll chop you into tiny pieces.
Talk about a change of character!
I-I understand! I won't tell a soul!
Those trolls are always giving me hell...
So, uh, when you said you wanted to talk...
Talk? Gimme a break.
Bingo.
And when you joined our circle...
That was to destroy this book, of course.
Why else would I have joined?
I hate being right.
But now I can be freed from the past...
Wh-What's going on here?
It's over 200,005,000 degrees!
Dekomori, you must withstand until I'm done with my chant!
You're back already?
Sadly, we were unable to find the link point due to cloudy weather.
And while we're here, give back my Mabinogion!
Where is it?! Give it back or meet your death!
There.
There's nothing left but ash.
Too bad.
Now all records of it are erased forever and ever!
Wh-Why would you...
That's so mean...
H-Hey, are you okay?
My dear book...
Smirk...
"Smirk"?
Smirk, smirk, smirk, smirk, smirk!
Dekomori?
Smirkyahahahah!
No worries!
I thought something like this might happen,
so I made copies in case it met an untimely death!
Forest Summer is a most admirable person.
She and Master answered all my questions about the Otherworld.
I want to go to the Otherworld
I want to go to the Otherworld.
My friends all tell me that things like that
only exist in games and won't  come with me.
I want to go to the Otherworld.
My friends all tell me that things like that
only exist in games and won't  come with me.
I want to go to the Otherworld.
My friends all tell me that things like that
only exist in games and won't  come with me.
I want to go to the Otherworld.
My friends all tell me that things like that
only exist in games and won't  come with me.
Mark as best answer
I want to go to the Otherworld.
My friends all tell me that things like that
only exist in games and won't  come with me.
Answer by: Wicked Eye
Mark as best answer
I want to go to the Otherworld.
My friends all tell me that things like that
only exist in games and won't  come with me.
Answer by: Wicked Eye
The Otherworld exists.
Mark as best answer
Answer by: Wicked Eye
The Otherworld exists.
The Overseers are merely concealing
Mark as best answer
Answer by: Wicked Eye
The Otherworld exists.
The Overseers are merely concealing
Mark as best answer
Answer by: Wicked Eye
The Otherworld exists.
The Overseers are merely concealing
all trace of its existence.
Mark as best answer
Answer by: Wicked Eye
The Otherworld exists.
The Overseers are merely concealing
all trace of its existence.
Mark as best answer
Answer by: Wicked Eye
The Otherworld exists.
The Overseers are merely concealing
all trace of its existence.
There must be a way to break through their obstacles.
Mark as best answer
Answer by: Wicked Eye
The Otherworld exists.
The Overseers are merely concealing
all trace of its existence.
There must be a way to break through their obstacles.
Mark as best answer
Answer by: Wicked Eye
The Otherworld exists.
The Overseers are merely concealing
all trace of its existence.
There must be a way to break through their obstacles.
Mark as best answer
Answer by: Wicked Eye
The Otherworld exists.
The Overseers are merely concealing
all trace of its existence.
There must be a way to break through their obstacles.
Mark as best answer
Answer by: Wicked Eye
The Otherworld exists.
The Overseers are merely concealing
all trace of its existence.
There must be a way to break through their obstacles.
Mark as best answer
Answer by: Wicked Eye
The Otherworld exists.
The Overseers are merely concealing
all trace of its existence.
There must be a way to break through their obstacles.
Answer by: Forest Summer
Mark as best answer
The Otherworld exists.
The Overseers are merely concealing
all trace of its existence.
There must be a way to break through their obstacles.
Answer by: Forest Summer
Mark as best answer
The Otherworld exists.
The Overseers are merely concealing
all trace of its existence.
There must be a way to break through their obstacles.
Answer by: Forest Summer
I understand how you feel perfectly.
Mark as best answer
The Overseers are merely concealing
all trace of its existence.
There must be a way to break through their obstacles.
Answer by: Forest Summer
I understand how you feel perfectly.
Most of the common folk have no sense for otherworldly matters,
Mark as best answer
all trace of its existence.
There must be a way to break through their obstacles.
Answer by: Forest Summer
I understand how you feel perfectly.
Most of the common folk have no sense for otherworldly matters,
and they can't even grasp what those with abilities, like you
Mark as best answer
all trace of its existence.
There must be a way to break through their obstacles.
Answer by: Forest Summer
I understand how you feel perfectly.
Most of the common folk have no sense for otherworldly matters,
and they can't even grasp what those with abilities, like you
Mark as best answer
There must be a way to break through their obstacles.
Answer by: Forest Summer
I understand how you feel perfectly.
Most of the common folk have no sense for otherworldly matters,
and they can't even grasp what those with abilities, like you
Mark as best answer
There must be a way to break through their obstacles.
Answer by: Forest Summer
I understand how you feel perfectly.
Most of the common folk have no sense for otherworldly matters,
and they can't even grasp what those with abilities, like you
Mark as best answer
There must be a way to break through their obstacles.
Answer by: Forest Summer
I understand how you feel perfectly.
Most of the common folk have no sense for otherworldly matters,
and they can't even grasp what those with abilities, like you
Mark as best answer
There must be a way to break through their obstacles.
Answer by: Forest Summer
I understand how you feel perfectly.
Most of the common folk have no sense for otherworldly matters,
and they can't even grasp what those with abilities, like you
Mark as best answer
She's a great magician!
Forest Summer
Her wisdom was considered so powerful
that the government tried to erase all evidence of it.
The page you're looking for cannot be found.
But as her prophet, I must—
I erased it myself.
I couldn't deal with it.
Who the death are you?
I'm Forest Summer.
Listen! I wrote that book.
And I was the one who answered your questions a year ago.
I wrote the Mabinogion, so hand it over!
Are you past brain death?
There's no way a rotten commoner like yourself could be Forest Summer.
Who are you calling rotten?!
Hey, Nibutani!
Is her head made of stone?!
That's your punishment for pretending to be Forest Summer.
I really am her!
Do not utter that name again in my presence.
Maybe then I will spare you from death.
Dekomori's not kidding.
Master, I must take my leave.
That troll... She'll pay for this!
O spirits of the earth and skies!
I call upon your power and beseech your blessing.
May misfortune befall Dekomori Sanae...
May misfortune befall Dekomori Sanae!
Um, Nibutani...
I have to repeat this a hundred times or it won't work!
I'm okay with it if you are,
but I think you're reverting to your old self...
I've still got eighth-grader syndrome deep inside!
Yeah, back then...
I can hear the spirits whisper to me.
Die! Die! Why won't those memories die?!
Stop, Nibutani! The ground isn't at fault here!
But I totally understand how you feel.
I was a pretty serious case myself.
I became obsessed with cartoons and video games,
and started to believe I had dark powers.
Dark Flame Master!
That kind of thing.
Really?
Lame.
More to the point, where does that girl live?
I don't know. Rikka might.
Did you summon me?
Wait, you were here all along?
Even if I told you, it'd be no use.
Dekomori swore loyalty to Forest Summer next to me.
She probably has countless copies of the Mabinogion.
No way...
She won't open up to anyone but the real Forest Summer.
But even then...
there's still a way.
Huh? What is it?
Though...
Tell me! My high school life is at stake here!
Well...
What do you want?
Shall I test your powers?
You never learn, do you?
Talk big while you can!
You're not half bad.
It's just like Togashi said.
The point is...
You only have to make her believe that you're a great magician
in her imaginary world born from eighth-grader delusions.
Blast reality!
Burst it into shreds!
Banishment... this world!
Prepare to meet your end, troll!
You don't pull any punches.
Mjolnir Tornado!
Divine Brionac!
Why continue your useless struggle? You're not Forest Summer!
But I am!
She told me...
that love is everything!
That the spirits respond only to the call of a pure heart!
That she, the only magician who
survived from an era long since past,
has to live carrying the weight of all that pain and sadne—
No!
Please, stop!
Your rotten heart cannot withstand the purity of Forest Summer's wisdom!
You impostor!
I don't wanna hear that!
Don't make me remember!
So even harnessing the power of her latent eighth-grader syndrome wasn't enough...
Stop it!
Here. Enjoy.
Thanks.
You decided to stay with us, after all.
Yeah.
At least until I reach my goal, anyway.
I welcome you to the Nap Club,
and present you with the Member No. 5 Pillow!
No thanks.
Oh, it's the troll.
Is that the fake Forest Summer I see?
Don't call me that!
You got a real big mouth for such a tiny girl.
What did you just say?
I'm not tiny!
You're tiny, no matter how I look at you.
I've got a lot of growing ahead of me, okay?
What's that? You're self-conscious?
Hand over the Mabinogion, and I'll show you how to grow.
I'd sooner die, you rotten fake Forest Summer!
Don't call me that!
Shut up!
Can't you do something?
Roger.
What are you doi—
What was that?
What do you think you're doing?!
To be continued
inside identity ibasho wa doko
Inside identity! Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji ka douka
Getting it wrong is a shame?
sunaosa ga itai toka
Being honest hurts?
dare ga nanto iou to tadashisa nante wakannai ze
Whatever people say, they don't know what's right
futsuu ni nagareteku nichijou ni
The boring river of time flows on
muri shite najimase to
When the stars tried to fit in
shizunjimatta kouseitachi wo
They ended up sinking into it
kande nonde haite ware
So chew them, swallow them, and spit them out!
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I wish you understood me"
iitai kedo ienakute
That's what I want to say, but I can't
nande daremo wakatte kunnai no to
"No one ever understands me"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kana
Is it selfish to think that? Is it? Is it?
kanjouteki na taiyou wa
The emotional Sun in the sky
netsu wo agesugite dounika narisou
Overheated, reaching its limit
sakebitakute shou ga nai
Of course I want to shout
gamushara ni mo tometeru identity
My fast and furious identity
inside my identity
Inside my identity
inside my justice
Inside my justice
tamashii wa ite
There's a soul
ibasho wa doko
But where do I belong?
Wait,
what?!
Dirty
Book
Tune in next time!