Thanks.
It's love!
I'm Otani Atsushi. Second year, class three.
Nice to meet you.
Ah, I'm Kotobuki. First year, class four.
Kotobuki Seiko.
Um...
I've fallen for you.
What the hell was that?!
Send Forbidden Love Flying!
How shameless.
What was that?
Do you really want to go out with Seiko-chan?
Shameless.
How could I say no when her eyes were all sparkly like that?!
You always say stuff like that.
You say you're acting cool, but maybe you're just indecisive.
You're just taking it out on me because you're not popular.
What do you mean I'm not popular?!
Haruka confessed to me, remember?
He doesn't see you as a woman.
She likes me so much, she couldn't control herself and suddenly kissed me.
I'm a sinful man.
All it took was a minute.
Gah! Gahara tapachine poke maha buu!
What are you saying?
It's a shame, huh, Koizumi.
As Japan is such a small country, compact things have now become a necessity.
Cellphones. Digital Cameras. Laptops.
And...
MEN!
The era of small men has finally arrived!
Wouldn't you say?
This has all gone straight to his head.
Afternoon
Physical Examinations
In the Gym
Honestly, that idiot has gotten too carried away.
Well, any guy kissed by a girl that cute would get a little cocky.
Is that so?
Plus, while most girls call Otani cute,
...very few call him cool.
That's why he's particularly happy.
She is cute, but she sure is bold.
That's the first time I've ever seen someone kiss right in front of me.
Senpai!
Good afternoon!
Ah, the infamous Seiko-chan.
You've had your physical examination?
Yes.
Um... sorry for surprising you yesterday.
Y-You sure are forward, huh?
After seeing Otani-senpai, I just couldn't help myself.
Ahh... I'm getting all weak just remembering it...
U-Uh... Seiko-chan?
Ahh! Sorry, I lost it again.
L-Lost it?
Whenever I think about someone I like, my mind goes blank.
And then my body starts moving by itself.
This is bad. This girl is weird.
Um, about back then...
...is Otani-senpai angry because I did that all of a sudden?
Not at all. He couldn't be happier.
Thank goodness!
I'm going to try my best from now on!
If you don't mind, please help me, okay, Senpai?
Ah, okay.
Thanks! I'll be counting on you, okay!
Help, huh?
That girl seems to use a strange technique.
Technique?
A technique to grab guy's hearts.
While she's spacing out, she emits a ton of pheromones.
Pheromones, huh?
That's a substance that doesn't exist within my body.
In other words, she's sexy.
GYOOO! Bupe pubupere bupepre pe zo!
Well, she might not even be Otani-kun's type...
...but he was probably caught by all those pheromones.
Risa, you give it your best too.
Why do I have to give it my best?
And just what am I giving my best for?!
Risa-chan, Risa-chan...
WHAT?!
Ahh... s-sorry.
You're helping with the physicals aren't you, Chiharu-chan?
Okay, okay. Risa, have your height measured already.
That Seiko-chan is small and cute...
Otani's probably happier that someone like her likes him, rather than a giant like me.
Not like I'd ever admit that to anyone, though!
Risa-chan, 1...172cm.
Huh? Wait!
172cm?!
Ri-Risa-chan... your eyes are scary.
You're lying, right, Chiharu-chan?!
You're lying, right?!
Something is definitely wrong!
Risa, come back to reality!
No! No!
I was definitely 170cm last year!
You definitely made a mistake!
Measure me again!
1...172?!
Are you kidding me?!
Two centimeters...
I grew another two centimeters...
This is the worst.
And what about you?
Listen and be amazed...
I grew two millimeters!
Wow. I'm amazed.
You seriously piss me off!
You can gain 2 millimeters just by wearing socks.
Say whatever you want.
I'm in a good mood today, so I won't let the little things bother me.
Little pervert.
Who are you calling "little pervert"?!
Seiko-chan is here.
Otani-senpai!
Yo.
Who the heck are you?!
You're as cool as always!
Thank you.
This is no time to be growing taller, Risa!
You think I'm doing it on purpose?!
If you don't do something, Otani-kun and that girl really will get together.
Who cares.
He can do what he likes.
See you.
Bye bye.
What the heck?!
It was your fault for spacing out.
What if I'd hit my chin and ended up with a big split in it like some foreigner?!
It'd be handy. You'd be able to stick memos in it.
MEMO
Idiot!
If you ruin this manly face Seiko-chan will be sad.
You sure are a happy guy.
Huh?
Oh, this?
I really like it.
Oh, is that so.
With this charm from the giant goddess, maybe I'll grow taller too.
The Giant Goddess?
Allow me to explain.
She is known as Koizumi Risa.
Although she appears to be an ordinary human,
...she is actually the giant goddess from the land of the giants.
Who the hell is?!
I really like it.
Oh, is that so?
What's up?
You seem to be in a pretty good mood.
Y-You think so? I'm not really.
Wow! How cool!
Otani-senpai is really cool, isn't he!
Over here, over here.
Do your best, Otani-senpai!
Otani! Ball!
Owww!
Idiot.
Otani-senpai!
Are you okay? I'll take you to the infirmary!
Eh? Se-Se-Seiko-chan?
Otani, who's that cute girl?
Your girlfriend?
Huh? It's not like that!
Maybe in the future, though!
This is dangerous.
Stuck in the infirmary with a devilish woman who doesn't care what others think...
...and has a tendency to kiss suddenly?
The infirmary!
"Senpai, don't you think it's hot in here?"
And then Seiko slowly undoes her buttons, one by one...
What the heck are you saying?!
Na...Nakao-senpai! I remember now.
That girl seems really cute, right?
But everyone gets fooled by that.
She says she doesn't like her real name,
...so she tells everyone her name is "Kotobuki Seiko."
Don't you think it's hot in here?
Otani!
But her real name is Kotobuki Seishiro.
She's actually a guy!
O...Otani?
The sports festival is coming up soon, huh?
I think the cheer squad is recruiting.
I-I think I'll sign up.
If you're signing up, I-I'll sign up too.
What does the cheer squad do?
Ch-Cheer, of course.
What's so funny, you guys?!
Oh? What's wrong? You're so upset.
Stop that snickering!
I can't hold it in anymore!
Hey, Nobu-chan! I've been holding it in this whole time!
I'm gonna hit you!
I'm gonna hit all of you!
Don't worry, Otani. This kind of thing happens all the time.
How can this kind of thing happen all the time?
It's taken years off my life.
You guys! Stop laughing! Seriously!
How unfortunate, Otani.
But for some reason, I feel relieved.
What am I thinking?!
Ah, senpai!
Are you going to go watch basketball practice again today?
So this is a boy?
Oh? So you really do like Otani-senpai...
N-No! It's not like I'm going to watch Otani.
I'm just keeping Nobu-chan company while she waits for her boyfriend.
But you gave him a wristband as a present, didn't you?
A wristband?! This is the first I've heard of it.
You wouldn't give something like that to someone you didn't like right?
B-But, you see...
...if a girl as tall as me liked someone as short as Otani, it'd be weird, right?
You think so?
I don't really think that matters.
Huh?
I mean, if that were the case, isn't it even more weird for me to like Otani-senpai?
Well, that's...
But Seiko-chan, you don't look like a boy at all.
Oh, it's not Seiko-chan. It's Seishiro...
It's Seiko!
Right...
I've never thought of myself as a boy.
I'm sure God just put me in the wrong body.
But... um...
...did Otani-senpai say anything about me?
Since that day in the infirmary, I feel like he's been avoiding me.
Does he think I'm disgusting?
Uh... I think he's just confused.
Really?
Yeah. I'm sure everything will work out.
I'm sorry.
I had no idea you liked him, and asked you to help me.
Uh, that's not...
From now on, we're rivals.
Uh, no... Like I said...
But, I'm not going to lose to you!
I'll use my charm and pheromones to make Otani-senpai fall for me.
S-So dazzling!
Sparkle! Sparkle! Sparkle!
Sparkle
Seiko is so dazzling! Why?
You wouldn't give something like that to someone you didn't like, right?
You're slouching.
Really?
Geez, Risa, you're too concerned about your height.
It's only 2cm, yet you're this depressed about it.
Only 2cm? It's a big problem!
Do you know why it's a big problem?
Could it be because...
...you've fallen for a guy who's shorter than you?
A guy who's shorter than me?
Otani-senpai!
Wh-What's this?!
I came to play with you.
No, what's with that outfit?
I joined the sports festival cheer squad.
We decided on cheer girl uniforms!
Cheer girl...
Cheer girl
Yes.
Cheer GIRL?!
Cheer
Girl
I thought it was super cute, so I had to show you right away!
Cute, isn't it?
It's cute.
A guy falling for another guy...
That would make things really difficult.
But he's trying so hard...
...and he's so cute.
Meanwhile I'm sitting here worrying about our height difference...
...keeping my own feelings hidden.
Hey Risa,
...let's join the cheer squad too!
Cheer girls are totally cute!
Say what?
Thanks for your hard work.
Seiko-chan, you'll be in the same squad as us right?
Otani-senpai will be with us too, so I'll do my best!
Say, why do you like Otani-kun?
Wouldn't you prefer someone stronger and more manly?
I think Otani-senpai is really manly and cool.
The way he helped me on my first day was just amazing!
And also...
Height isn't an issue so you can join even if you're short.
...I figured Otani-senpai would be able to accept me wholeheartedly.
I see.
He is a nice guy, after all.
He is, isn't he?!
Otani-senpai!
Ahh! Hey, stop that!
Hey! Let go, you! Let go of me!
Hey, stop that! Let go!
Nobu-chan, I'll be going on ahead, okay.
Okay!
Are you really a guy?
Yep.
So you're not really going out with Otani-kun, right?
But I do like Otani-senpai.
Ah, I see. Thanks.
Okay.
See, they can't be going out.
Otani wouldn't date a huge girl like that, after all.
Hey!
What do you mean "they can't be going out?!"
Senpai?
How can you say such rude things without knowing how hard other people are trying?!
Senpai! Senpai!
It's fine. It doesn't bother me.
Seiko-chan!
But they were so rude!
Don't you think?!
You think?
I don't really think they were...
But... now that you mention it...
...it's making me sad.
It's weird, isn't it?
It really is weird, huh?
Me saying that I like Otani-senpai...
N-Not at all!
But, even if I confess to Otani-senpai...
...I'll just be laughed at like before.
He thinks I'm disgusting.
That must be it!
You know...
Hey!
What are you talking about?
Otani-senpai...
Otani?
I'll say this, at least. I don't hate you.
And I don't think you're disgusting either.
But if you want me to be your boyfriend, that might be a bit of a problem.
Uh... What to say...
Ch-Cheer girls are kinda cute, huh...
Otani-senpai!
Hey, stop that!
Can I still visit your classroom?
Yes, yes! Just let go of me!
I'll visit every day in my cheer uniform!
Don't!
12th ANNUAL MAIDO HIGH SPORTS FESTIVAL
I don't wanna!
I said no!
Too bad.
The girls in our squad will be wearing boys' uniforms,
...and the boys will be dressed as cheer girls!
Yeah, that's right...
Unlike me, you're a girl Koizumi-senpai.
You really could become his girlfriend.
If you're always so concerned about height, you won't find love.
Do your best, okay?
I think I'm going to try being a bit more honest.
Got you!
Let me go! What are you doing?!
He fits snugly in my arms.
Hey, hey! Wh-Wh-What do you think you're doing?!
It doesn't matter if I can carry him in my arms.
It doesn't matter if he's shorter than me.
I...
...like Otani.
He's being carried!
Like a princess!
Now, let's put him in a cheer girl uniform!
Put me down! Put me down, damm it!
Koizumi, is there someone you like?
Uh... I... Otani... uh...!
You sure are acting weird.
Lovely Complex ~ Love Com.
Next: A Maiden's Determination! Love-Love Confession Plan!!
A Maiden's Determination! Love-Love Confession Plan!!
Be sure to watch!