He's right here.
Huh?
Did you ever even think that the guy might be you?
Think that...
Huh?
ME?!
What should I do?
Still... even if it's just once...
I want him to think of me as a girl.
Comeback Impossible! Major Heartbreak!!
Just once...
...I want him to think about me in that way.
He's thinking hard. He's thinking hard.
He's definitely realized this time.
Good job, Risa. Your hard work has paid off!
I... I shouldn't have done that.
I did something completely unnecessary.
I'm scared!
What are you saying now?
What on earth should I do?!
You don't need to do anything. You did everything you had to.
Now it's all down to Otani-kun's reaction.
His reaction?
I'd better go tell him I was just kidding!
I don't care if he's an idiot! I like that idiot!
Wait, Risa!
Hey, Nobu-chan...
I know I'll be in the way, but let me hang out with you on the class trip.
It's fine by me, but what about Otani-kun?
You haven't spoken to him at all since then.
That's because I don't want to!
I don't know what to do!
And when we finally have our class trip too...
No, no! I don't care about the class trip!
Koizumi?
I just remembered there's something I have to do!
I'm gonna go on ahead!
Risa, wait!
Hey, what do you think I should do?
Go with whatever you think is best, just tell her what you're thinking now.
What I'm thinking now, huh?
I just wanted him to think about me...
...but if I stop being All-Kyojin, then what will I become?
Can I really become a normal girl?
I can't sleep!
Did you ever think that the guy might be you?
After going around in a big circle, I finally told Otani how I feel.
And now...
Just what is going to happen to me now?
I was so preoccupied with telling him how I feel.
I never even thought about what would come after.
Now it's all down to Otani-kun's reaction.
His reaction...
To tell you the truth, Koizumi, I've liked you all this time too.
Let's go out.
No way. That's absolutely impossible.
I'm scared! I bet he's gonna say...
How disgusting.
No way.
He'll definitely say something like that!
For now, I'll just avoid being alone with him.
It'll be fine as long as I don't speak to him.
Huh? How long have I slept in?
Hey. Good morning. Koizumi speaking.
"Good morning"?!
You just woke up?!
You forgot we've got our class trip today, didn't you?!
I've been calling you for ages!
The bus to the airport is about to leave!
L... Late!
S- S- Sorry! I overslept!
Wasn't there anyone to wake you up?
Everyone else at home was asleep as well.
I'm asking the two of you, don't pull a comedy act at a time like this.
"The two of you"?
Sorry!
I'm la—
Right let's go.
I was planning on not being alone with Otani for a while...
Ahh. We're too late.
I'll go take care of the tickets. You guys just wait here.
Pair of idiots.
Sorry.
Th- This is bad!
Wait! Don't go!
Don't leave us alone!
Sit down.
I said sit!
This is bad.
I need to act natural. Just like I was before.
How could you sleep in on such an important day, you idiot?!
You did too!
Uh... oh, yeah...
W- W- W- What?
Well, to be blunt...
NO!
I haven't said anything yet!
No! No! Don't say anything!
You've been calling me an idiot for so long it's really starting to piss me off!
Listen to me!
Please.
Is the guy you like really me?
Asking so directly is bad for my heart!
Is there any other way to ask?
There should be!
There isn't, that I know of.
Listen, and answer me properly.
Even when I tried so hard to confess, you brushed me off.
Why do you have to make me relive that scene now.
That's why... I think...
I'm sorry.
If saying sorry were enough, there'd be no need for cops in this world.
I wanted to say it earlier, but you kept trickling away!
What do you mean "trickling away"?!
You make me sound like a shishiotoshi!
Do you realize that you haven't heard a thing I've said?!
Then...
Couldn't you have said it in a way that's easier to understand?
I... like you, Otani!
I said in very simple terms!
I came right out and told you!
Oh. Right.
Give me some time.
I'll think about it.
Think?
What? You're the one that wanted me to think in the first place!
That's true...
...but hearing you say that so seriously really scares me.
What's going on here, All Hanshin-Kyojin?
I'm surprised. Are you regretting being late?
Y- Yeah...
I guess...
The late couple have arrived!
So they have.
Risa...
What happened to you? I was worried.
How suspicious.
Maybe they were together till morning...
It's not like that.
Risa, I was worr—
I can't take this! I wanna go home!
If you ask the seagull, "Have the herring come?"
"I'm just a migrating bird. Ask the waves."
The plane trip was so long...
...and Otani sat right next to me.
It was hard to breathe!
Don't you think you're being overly self-conscious?
This is bad.
I have to think of a way to dump him five seconds before he dumps me.
Dumps?
But...!
You don't know if he's going to reject you, though.
I do know!
Don't get your hopes up about ever finding a boyfriend, amazon.
Aren't we All Hanshin-Kyojin partners?
Huh? What? I... I don't get you...
To Otani, I'm just an amazon... and a comedy partner.
The thought that I might like him never even crossed his mind.
Even if I did confess, it'll never lead anywhere with someone who thinks like that.
I know it.
Risa...
But now that you've told him, you're not a part of All Hanshin-Kyojin anymore, right?
So at the very least, you've escaped from being his comedy partner.
That's great! You've worked hard and taken another step forward.
Yeah, I guess so.
Hey Nobu-chan, what'll happen to me now?
That depends on Otani-kun's  reaction.
No! I wanna go home!
Now, now. Calm down.
Let go of me!
Calm down.
Koizumi-san sure is agitated.
I'm sleeping.
Even though you slept so much that it made you late?
I haven't been getting enough sleep.
Is that because you've been thinking about Koizumi-san?
Shut up. Don't make me hit you, you idiot.
Someone this scary can't be Otani... sniff, sniff, sniff...
So, what are you thinking?
Ok, you're free to explore this area, but remember to meet back here at the right time.
Yes!
Sensei, the late couple isn't waking up.
Wake those idiots up!
But they didn't even wake up when we stuffed snacks in their mouths.
What's wrong with those two?!
Guess there's not much we can do. Call them by cell phone and meet up with them later.
Okay!
Koizumi, I can't go out with a giant like you.
I'll be going out with this crab from now on.
She's a Hokkaido specialty. She was just caught today, and is still fresh!
Wait, Otani-kun!
A sheep!
Ooh... Mongolian Lamb sounds good, too.
Wait!
What the...
What's going on?
Where is everyone?
Why...?
Why has it turned out like this?
Glass? What?
I told you. We're at the Otaru Canal Craft Hall—
Where? I have no idea what you're saying!
So we just follow the Otaru canal?
Okay, got it.
Yeah, yeah.
What did Nobu-chan say?
She said they'll get here soon, so we should run into them if we just wait around here.
Oh, great.
This is so awkward.
What do you mean I took a step forward? This is definitely a step backwards.
If I knew it was going to be like this,
...I'd rather keep things the way they were, just saying whatever we felt like saying.
But now that awkward topic is all I can think of...
Did... Did I fail?
Maybe I shouldn't have told him.
I really want to go home.
How awesome does that look?!
Wow, seriously!
It's a rickshaw!
How cool! It totally suits the atmosphere here!
I wanna ride it!
Are you an idiot?
It'd be embarrassing and touristy.
I guess so.
Come on. Let's go buy some souvenirs.
I wonder how they're doing...
I hope Risa and Otani are all right.
Ah. Found them.
Chiharu-chan!
Suzuki-kun!
Where should we go?
Haruka!
Here. Please be careful.
Thank you!
What are you two doing?
The rickshaw was awesome!
That felt great!
Yeah! It was super fun!
The driver even gave us nicknames.
He said, "How about I call you guys 'Suke-san' and 'Kaku-san'?"
"You can bring Komon-san along next time."
It was a cold joke, but it was great!
I wanna ride again!
Me too!
But we just did the 10 minute course. Should we go for the 30 minute course?
You idiot. If we do that, we won't have any money for souvenirs.
Then we can just make some cash by doing a comedy act here.
Sounds good!
Could it be that things are finally going well between the two of you?
Uh... Well...
I'd forgotten all about that awkward feeling.
I'm thirsty.
I'm gonna go get some juice.
You guys decide where to go next.
Otani!
Maybe I shouldn't have confessed after all.
It would've probably been better if I'd forgotten this crush and we'd just stayed a comedy duo.
If I knew it would be this awkward...
...I'd rather things had stayed the way they were.
Otani-kun sure is slow. He still hasn't come back.
I wonder if he's deep in thought again...
I'll think about it.
Deep in thought...
Well, do you want to go shopping around here for a bit, then?
What do you want to do, Risa?
I'm gonna go look for him.
Wait, Risa!
If I hurry, I can still make it.
I'll tell him to just pretend that nothing happened.
If we pretend that nothing happened...
...then, just like before...
What are you doing?
Um...
I found the bear curry that a friend asked me to get, so I was going to buy some.
Bear... curry...
Bear Curry
Here you go.
Thank you.
Let's just pretend that nothing happened.
I... like you, Otani!
Did you ever even think that the guy might be you?
If nothing had happened...
You asked me to think about it...
...so I've been thinking about it a lot.
Thinking about...?
If you're asking me whether I like you or not...
...I'd say I like you.
You're the only one I can make a big fuss and get excited about riding a rickshaw with.
But we've been a comedy duo for such a long time...
I don't think I can suddenly see you as my girlfriend.
So...
Ah. Right.
I knew it.
What's with that serious expression?!
It's sickening.
Sickening, you say?
It's fine, it's fine. Forget about it.
Let's just pretend that nothing happened.
I actually came to say that.
We'll just stay All Hanshin-Kyojin from now on, okay?
If you want, maybe we can join a comedy troupe!
Koizumi...
Okay, hurry up and buy your bear curry or seal curry or whatever.
Go on, go on. Everyone is waiting.
I'll go catch up with the others, okay?
Wait... Koizumi...
I knew from the start that it wouldn't go smoothly.
Even my confession was just to get him to see me as a girl for a bit.
That's all.
I'm back!
Where's Otani-kun?
Oh, Otani?
Uh, Otani is... bear curry...
Otani is bear curry?
What do you mean?
No...
Bear...
Bear curry...
Like I said, what's this about bear curry?
What happened?!
Still, having it said to my face... it still hurts.
Bear curry...
What's that supposed to mean?!
Bear...
I know about the bear! What happened with Otani-kun?!
Seriously, what are you? The spokesperson for bear curry?!
For some reason I feel like having bear curry now.
Darling, please don't speak right now.
Koizumi Risa, heartbroken!
Koizumi, what do you want to do during our free time in Hakodate?
I want to get a soft serve!
Look over there! That's...
Umibouzu, in person!
Lovely Complex ~ Love Com.
Next: Back from the dead!! Aim for girlfriend status!!
Back from the dead!! Aim for girlfriend status!!
Be sure to watch!