Blast reality.
Burst it into shreds.
Banishment... this world!
Avalon Smasher!
How long do you plan to continue this farce?
Do you enjoy it?
Do you enjoy babbling this childish nonsense?
Wicked... Twinkle!
Do you hate Mom?
No...
Do you just want to cause trouble for Grandma and Grandpa, then?
No!
Don't you get it? We can't change the past!
There's nothing we can do about it!
When will you be satisfied? We have no choice!
Evil Eye...
No...
No!
There's no house here anymore. Dad's gone too.
The Ethereal Horizon doesn't even—
It exists.
The Ethereal Horizon exists!
You?
Let's look for a
sparkling daydream...
shibaraku mitsumeatte kara
We looked into each other's eyes for a while
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no?
What did you think of while it lasted?
ki ni naru
I want to know that
A
kuchibiru
togaraseta
atashi wo mite
Look at me
as I now
pout my lips
A
dou shita no tte
kiite kuru no?
Will you ask me
what's wrong?
A
matte miru no
I'm waiting
A
gomakashita
ato no
hitorigoto wa
I'm embarrassed
by what I
mutter after
A
hazukashii kara
kikanaide kureru?
being so evasive,
so please don't
pay it any attention
A
ato ni
hikenai hodo
Our love
is so strong
A
hikareau koi
we can't
run away
mou hajimatteta
It's already begun
yume nara takusan mita
I've dreamed of our meeting so often
sameta mama
Now I'm awake
demo mada aitai
And still I want to see you
A
demo mada aitai
And still I want to see you
kimi ga sou saseta
You did this to me
koi ga
yokubari da ne
Love is greedy
koi ga yokubari da ne
A
tobihanesou
na kokoro no
My heart seems
to hop with glee
yuku mama ni yukou yo
So I'll let it guide me
A
risou mo
mousou mo
genjitsu mo
My ideals,
delusions
and reality
subete kimi
wo jiku
ni mawaru
Are all
about you
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
A
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
I think you're right, Tooka.
Yuuta...
I think Rikka's doing this because she knows it too.
You can tell her to accept reality,
but there are many things that none of us are able to accept.
She had no time to prepare for what happened,
and it was all over before she knew it.
Togashi
She isn't running away.
She isn't even trying to look the other way.
She just wonders if it's okay to sum things up with the usual platitudes as if that was all there was to it.
3rd period
Study hall
My Notes
Togashi Yuuta
And yet, everyone tells her, "that's life." "That's reality."
Is that really right?
That's what reality is.
Everyone has to live with it. That's what it means to become an adult.
Maybe so, but for her...
Rikka!
The exile... of two
Ah, welcome back!
Where's Rikka?
She came back in a taxi not too long ago.
I guess she's on the shore.
Everyone else left a while ago to light fireworks.
Thank you very much!
The time has come for the Black Dragon to be unleashed on its deathly rampage!
Wait! Wait!
What's wrong with you?
Here you are.
Come on, boy! Fetch!
Go get it!
Why?!
Isn't this fun?
Yes, it is!
Togashi and Rikka sure are late, though.
Where could they have gone?
Where do you think they'd go after sneaking out to the beach together during summer vacation?
Don't tell me they encountered a warrior from the Otherworld!
Ah, Togashi!
Where's Rikka?!
We haven't seen her!
Damn...
Togashi!
Youth at its finest!
Could this be the battlefield of love?
Battlefield of Love is a powerful barrier spell!
Yuuta!
Geez, I barely made it!
But why?
That's my line!
Where do you think you're going?
The Overseers' power in that location is overwhelming.
Their barrier is just too strong.
I must retreat.
So you're going home?
Who helped me notice
The growing darkness behind the light
Yuuta...
Hm?
Yuuta, how did you first come to realize the power of the Dark Flames?
By shouting so loud in the distance
I never even had it...
You turn your back to hide your smile
Well, I first realized when I was talking with my friends.
They were excited about going somewhere to hang out.
Don't just call honesty weakness
I felt left out, as if I was something different.
Don't say that not crying is strength
It felt odd, a weird loneliness like being left behind by the world.
Your hands holding mine
So your dark self awakened to its memories of another world?
Give me warmth I dare to trust
Even that seems like a better explanation than the truth.
That's why...
Finally I realized, at least I found it
Damn me!
What's wrong? The Overseers' curse?
The truth blurred by my tears
No...
Anyway, do you—
Our eyes met.
It's okay to be myself
You tell me, stroking my head
I look at your face as you sleep
And new feelings are born in my heart
Now we're bound by an even stronger contract, Dark Flame Master.
I told you...
Thank you for being by my side
"Vanish into the embrace of—"
Stop it!
The seeds of a new beginning started to sprout
It's from Togashi.
What's it say?
Takanashi's going back home, so he's going with her.
So they left?
They're so bold!
Bold?
You know, acting cute will only get you so far.
Have you ever dated a boy?
Of course!
Takashi, from kindergarten! We were in the same class together.
But then we had to move overseas for my dad's work,
and I was homeschooled until high school.
It's been a while since I last met a real airhead.
Ouch!
Sorry!
It stings!
My body was seared by the Sun, like the wings of mighty Icarus before he fell to his death!
Wh-What do you want?
Well, I thought since we're all here, I might as well wash your back.
I found a nice, soft sponge too.
I-I'll pass...
Please, it's no trouble at all!
Get away from me!
Incoming mail
Togashi Yuuta
Untitled
We're going home
ahead of you.
Rikka's with me. Don't worry.
We're going home
ahead of you.
Rikka's with me. Don't worry.
Incoming mail
Togashi Yuuta
Untitled
We're going home
ahead of you.
Rikka's with me. Don't worry.
We're going home
ahead of you.
Rikka's with me. Don't worry.
Incoming mail
Togashi Yuuta
Untitled
We're going home
ahead of you.
Rikka's with me. Don't worry.
We're going home
ahead of you.
Rikka's with me. Don't worry.
Darn, it's gotten quite late.
Yuuta! I've been barred from my room!
The passcode was changed!
You just forgot your key, didn't you?
Damn. I guess that leaves one option.
Huh? I'm back!
Huh? No one's here.
Wait a moment.
Could the Overseers have invaded?
Stop! Please, spare his family!
Don't jinx them!
Oh, right.
Kuzuha and Yumeha are at summer school
and Mom's got a night shift.
Watch out! They might hiding in camouflage!
No.
They're all coming home tomorrow.
Which means...
We're alone tonight?
Uh... Which way was the toilet again?
Huh? Kumin?
Ah, you're up too, Isshiki?
What are you doing?
It's so dark outside, the Moon must be really pretty,
so I thought I'd go for a walk.
Want to come with me, Isshiki?
Just... Just a moment!
A walk?
If you wanna go, just go.
I'm hanging up.
That answer's no answer at all!
Just because you got a girlfriend, now you're abandoning your friends?!
When did I get a girlfriend?
Did you forget I was the one who talked to you on the day of the entrance ceremony?
Sorry, gotta go!
Hey, wai—
Quit going through my stuff!
Yuuta, what's this?
Dunno.
Just put it away already.
Could this be some ultimate equipment you couldn't tell even the Wicked Eye about?
No!
Geez, you're so hopeless.
You put it on like this, then this here.
Then you swing your arm...
like this!
Amazing! Yuuta, that's amazing!
You don't have to appreciate it to tears.
With the full power of the Wicked Eye, I look at you with respect!
You don't have to do that.
Feel like anything in particular?
Though there isn't much left, so I can't make anything like Tooka.
I'd rather challenge the final boss than eat something like that.
That's some determination.
Then do you want to go to the store and grab something? It's getting pretty late.
The "store"? Could you possibly be referring to a "convenience store"?
What? Is that a problem?
The Priestess always forbade the use of such
stores, saying we should make our own food.
Well, if anything, you should thank her.
So I wanna try it!
Thank you, come again!
Is this really gonna be enough?
Tuna
Its structure has piqued my interest
since I saw you eating one in school.
You tear it open here, then split the packaging.
Take the two sides and pull them.
That's so cool!
It is?
It's good.
Tooka would be red-hot furious if she saw you now.
Here, have some fried chicken.
Quite a smart taste.
How can something taste smart?
What about your rice ball?
Wanna have a bite?
Here.
Spicy, isn't it?
That's mean!
Sorry, sorry.
Here, have this to make up for it.
Red means danger!
Not taking the bait, huh?
Replenishment complete.
Then let's go home.
Yuuta!
I don't wanna go home!
I'll bathe in the moonlight!
Hey!
What do you think? It's night! And we're alone!
Could the message be "I set the stage, now confess to me!"?
How should I know?
You're so cold!
Did you forget I was the one who talked to you on the day of the entrance ceremony?
Didn't you say that already?
I'm hanging up.
Wait, please!
What?
How are things with Takanashi?
We just had dinner.
She forgot the keys to her place.
What? So you're alone with her?
Yeah.
I thought it all seemed suspicious, but this is beyond my expectations!
What are you even talking about?
Can you really imagine things going that way for us?
Why?
Do you need to ask? It's Rikka! She's
eighth-grader syndrome at its finest!
But you're high schoolers!
So?
Yuuta!
But...
Hello?
Hey!
Geez.
It sounds like
you'll be on the phone
for a while,
so I'm heading back.
Kumin
It sounds like
you'll be on the phone
for a while,
so I'm heading back.
Kumin
With Rikka...
Not a chance!
She's so deep in her syndrome, does she even understand the concept of love?
Yuuta...
Is this the Mjolnir Maul?
Nope, no way.
Stop that. You'll stretch it out.
Just roll up the sleeves, okay?
You're good at making references, huh?
Anyway, it's getting late.
You can sleep in this room, so brush your teeth and—
It smells of Yuuta.
Stop that!
Why?
It smells of you.
Stop! That's really embarrassing!
I'm turning the light off.
The Wicked Eye is even more active at night, so I alread—
Whatever. Get some sleep.
Geez, talking about my smell...
Didn't I say to get some sleep?
I got butterflies in my stomach.
She must be close by. We must be on alert.
Come on, why—
I'm turning it off.
I got butterflies in my stomach.
It'll get better if you sleep.
My heart's racing!
That's the same thing.
I'm excited!
What are you, some theme park commercial?!
I'm explosive!
Why?!
I don't know!
J-Just go to sleep already.
Wait!
Hey, wh—
Don't go.
No way! She's...
Yuuta, close your eyes.
Just for a moment.
Just for a moment, please.
N-No way... Is she... really...
C-Can I... really do this?
No... But...
What's this?
A fragment of a spell that contains the ultimate power.
Proof of the new contract we formed earlier.
Could you draw it somewhere less noticeable?
This is the most effective location.
It will amplify your powers of darkness many times.
As well as the Dark Flames, you can now use the even more powerful Dark Buster.
Get some sleep.
Eighth-grader syndrome will always be eighth-grader syndrome, huh?
Well, this ended quite well... I guess.
Whatever.
My heart's racing!
This aura...
Who's there?!
Yuuta.
To be continued
inside identity ibasho wa doko
Inside identity! Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji ka douka
Getting it wrong is a shame?
sunaosa ga itai toka
Being honest hurts?
dare ga nanto iou to tadashisa nante wakannai ze
Whatever people say, they don't know what's right
futsuu ni nagareteku nichijou ni
The boring river of time drifts on
muri shite najimaseta
We tried to fit in with the flow
shizunjimatta kouseitachi wo
And our uniqueness sunk in the mud
kande nonde haite warau
So chew it, swallow it, spit it out and laugh
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I wish you understood me"
iitai kedo ienakute
That's what I want to say, but I can't
nande daremo wakatte kunnai no to
"No one ever understands me"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kana
Is it selfish to think that? Is it? Is it?
kanjouteki na taiyou wa
The emotional Sun in the sky
netsu wo agesugite dounika narisou
Overheated, reaching its limit
sakebitakute shou ga nai
Of course I want to shout
gamushara ni mo tometeru identity
My fast and furious identity
inside my feeling
Inside my feeling
inside my justice
Inside my justice
jama shinaide
Don't get in my way
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
Woohoo
Tune in next time!