It was the first time I'd ever hugged a girl.
I could feel a slight heat beyond the soft sensation.
She was so fragile, I felt like she'd break if I held her any tighter.
So lost and sad...
Rikka...
Rikka?
Forget it! Forget it! Forget it! Forget it! Forget it! Forget it!
Media lab
Movie screening area
Far Eastern
Magic Nap Society
of Summer
Let's look for a
sparkling daydream...
shibaraku mitsumeatte kara
We looked into each other's eyes for a while
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no?
What did you think of while it lasted?
ki ni naru
I want to know that
A
kuchibiru
togaraseta
atashi wo mite
Look at me
as I now
pout my lips
A
dou shita no tte
kiite kuru no?
Will you ask me
what's wrong?
A
matte miru no
I'm waiting
A
gomakashita
ato no
hitorigoto wa
I'm embarrassed
by what I
mutter after
A
hazukashii kara
kikanaide kureru?
being so evasive,
so please don't
pay it any attention
A
ato ni
hikenai hodo
Our love
is so strong
A
hikareau koi
we can't
run away
mou hajimatteta
It's already begun
yume nara takusan mita
I've dreamed of our meeting so often
sameta mama
Now I'm awake
demo mada aitai
And still I want to see you
A
demo mada aitai
And still I want to see you
kimi ga sou saseta
You did this to me
koi ga
yokubari da ne
Love is greedy
koi ga yokubari da ne
A
tobihanesou
na kokoro no
My heart seems
to hop with glee
yuku mama ni yukou yo
So I'll let it guide me
A
risou mo
mousou mo
genjitsu mo
My ideals,
delusions
and reality
subete kimi
wo jiku
ni mawaru
Are all
about you
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
A
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
Students are to leave the school by 8pm at the latest.
Pandora's Lunchbox...
of the Holy Mother
Master!
Do you dare design to draw forth the deathly night of devils from this darkness?
Master?
You're still as death! Did you freeze yourself in time?!
It doesn't seem that you have.
Master?
What the death are you doing? Master!
Could it be that Master finally accepts me as...
Master, we mustn't!
I'm your servant! We mustn't give in to our emotions like this!
Though of course, it's only natural that strong joy should turn to passion...
Master?
I hugged Yuuta.
I love Yuuta.
Master?
No way... Are you just a fake copy of Master?!
So now we not only have a fake Forest Summer, but Master as well?!
I'm the real one.
But... does that mean...
Master, you f-f-fell in love with the Dark Flame Master?
Master, I am needed for an urgent matter of life and death! I must take my leave.
Dekomori...
Don't try to stop me!
As your servant, it's my duty to cast the one who stole your heart into the darkn—
What should I do?
You said that you were able to protect the Wicked Eye for this long thanks to the Dark Flame Master.
I'm sure he'll be able to realize your heartfelt feelings as well.
I wonder.
I've been serving under you for a little over two years.
It's the duty of the servant to know everything about their master.
Dekomori...
There's no need for you to worry.
The Wicked Eye's power exceeds death itself!
You'll be saying "'Til death do we part" in no time.
Then, you and Takanashi...
Yeah.
What should I do?
About what?
Am I supposed to confess?
You love her, don't you?
I think so...
But it's not because she's cute or hot!
She's way beyond help with her eighth-grader syndrome,
but there's more to her than just that!
She has her problems, and I feel sorry for her, but...
I mean... I'm not just doing it out of pity, of course...
Say no more, dude.
You don't need a reason to fall in love.
What an expert you must be.
Good luck!
Same to you.
That's damn creepy!
How dare you treat me this way after I listened to your troubles?!
No one asked you to!
You mess up everything by spreading half-true rumors in class!
But darn, you're lucky.
Takanashi's got the potential to place 4th on the cutie poll.
With a girl like that...
With a girl like that?
One day, you'll...
We'll what?
Yuuta, I regret to say that I have no prior experience regarding bodily interactions.
Regrettably, neither do I!
Don't even suggest that! Are you nuts?!
Well then... I've got something of my own to sort out, so I'll catch you later.
Kumin!
What?
Would you come with me to the school fair afterparty?
Sure!
Really?
Cut!
Why do I always have to endure your two-bit acting?
We're not acting! And why are you even here at all?!
We need to get ready for tomorrow's performance.
Where are Togashi and Takanashi?
Do not utter those names in my presence.
My mood is deathly foul.
We shall fight.
You think we have time for that?
Put that energy into looking for those two so that—
They already left, for death's sake!
The Dark Flame Master said they had something to discuss of deathly importance—
Um...
Follow my orders as bound by your pledge...
What's that?
An enchanted gem. It fulfills wishes.
I got it from Dekomori.
Wishes?
I can't go into details!
That's okay, I don't need to know.
You dropped it.
It's warm.
Strong wishes cause the gem to emit heat.
Which means—
Don't!
Ouch...
It started raining...
Do you have an umbre— Of course you do.
What did you want?
Oh, right.
I have something too.
Something highly confidential I must discuss with you.
I-I see.
I wanted to talk about... But not here.
This can't go on.
Hey...
Schwarz Sechs Prototype Mk II!
How can you say its full name so fast?!
Hey!
Good thing it didn't fall into the river.
What's up?
The lights...
The lights... are moving.
Rikka...
I love you, Yuuta.
Wait, I was gonna say it first!
No. The Wicked Eye is destined to always be first.
I'm the Dark Flame Master!
The Wicked Eye's the strongest of all.
Geez, whatever.
It took me ages to come up with this, so I'm saying it anyway.
Thou who art surrounded by the flames of darkness,
I, the Dark Flame Master, beseech thee to forge a lover's—
Okay, screw that. The point is—
Continue!
Yuuta!
Thou who art surrounded by the flames of darkness,
I, the Dark Flame Master, beseech thee to forge a lover's contract between us.
Okay.
Shouldn't you be leaning on my chest?
Is it embarrassing?
Then, your hand?
My pinky.
Your pinky, then.
I'm home!
You're late!
Sorry, Kuzuha.
Demandant, do you possess feelings of love for the respondent?
No.
All I feel is that I want to be divorced from the respondent as soon as possible.
What are you doing?
We have to talk.
Huh?
This one's lost its taste too. You can have it.
Can't we discuss this at home?
I can't allow Rikka to hear it.
It's from the head restaurant in Italy. They invited me there for training.
I have no reason to refuse.
You really are that good, huh?
Did you doubt me?
Not at all!
Whatever.
But isn't that nice?
I'm sure Rikka will be—
You get it, don't you?
I can't let her live there by herself.
So Mom's moving in in my stead.
Rikka's mother?
What do you think?
I don't—
Do you think it's gonna work out?
Rikka doesn't hate her mother, right? Then—
Mom...
Mom tried to talk with Rikka a number of times.
She apologized for not telling her about Dad.
But...
What's wrong, Tooka?
Please help me!
I'm sure she'd listen to you!
You just need to tell her to grow up!
She's grown up enough.
I think that eyepatch is the armor by which she protects herself.
I'm sure she understands... all of it.
But she can't deal with the gloom in any other way.
Acting like that is the only way she can protect...
Protect what?
I don't know.
But I'd say she still wants to hold on to it.
If she listened to you or your mother and swallowed the bitter pill, it'd be all over.
She doesn't want that.
What's wrong with it being over?
There's no Horizon or Wicked Eye!
No matter how much she looks for Dad, she'll never find him!
Well...
How is affirming what she says better in any way?
She's never gonna get what she's looking for!
But...
Encouraging her like that...
is irresponsible.
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Gin
kgo
Fair
Here's your cheese potato! Thank you very much!
Wow, it's really popular.
That's just on the outside! Inside, it's a cruel, backstabbing gang!
That's why I don't want anything to do with them anymore.
So it's golden on the outside, gooey on the inside, just like a cheese potato?
Spare me your smart comments!
And where are Takanashi and Togashi?
They said they were going to change.
Hurry up!
Just you watch! Our impromptu performance will take all your customers away!
Oh look, it's Forest Summer!
Don't call m—
Sato! Suzuki!
Hey! Haven't seen you since junior high!
How old are you this year? 716?
Are you still catching lizards?
Don't bring that up!
Didn't you paint your lips purple to feign sickness, Sato?
Oh, you were into stuff like that too?
You too, Suzuki!
I remember you claiming you'd found fairies!
I just...
Fairies?
You never know what'll be unearthed next. Mining for eighth-grade memories is a dangerous job.
Yesterday's business is still far from over!
Today I've increased my powers fourfold!
Ugh, it's heavy!
You're nuts.
Magic
Nap
Society
Magic
Nap
Society
How is affirming what she says better in any way?
Encouraging her like that...
is irresponsible.
Yuuta, you're so cool!
You don't have to look that impressed!
Your move!
"Vanish into the embrace of dark flames!"
Yuuta, do it!
I don't wanna.
But you'll have to do it soon anyway.
Yeah, I guess so.
Vanish into the embrace of dark flames.
There was no power in that.
Can there be any power in it?
Of course. Open your legs, bend your knees, and flap the tail of your coat.
Yeah, yeah.
Vanish into the embrace of dark flames!
No pictures!
Next, together.
It's almost time to begin our mission.
Let's proceed to our positions.
Yeah... I'm not really feeling it, though.
Rikka!
What?
Nothing.
Your pinky.
Excuse me...
Yes?
Would a girl named Takanashi Rikka happen to be here?
She's...
She's not here right now.
I see.
Could you give her this?
Um...
It's okay. I'm leaving right away.
I think she still doesn't want to meet me yet.
Am I really being irresponsible?
Yuuta!
Why are you spacing out there?
It's about time we started!
We've got so many visitors too!
Rikka...
Take off your eyepatch.
It's time for our long-running talent show!
Ad-lib entries are welcome too!
Let's start then! Number one, on stage!
I'm number one, class 1-3, Haruno
Shinya! I'll be doing impersonations!
First, the principal!
Are you done with the performance?
Yeah. The brat and I managed to pull it off.
She came at me with killing intent, you know!
Sorry.
I didn't expect ...
you to say something like that.
That lunchbox, you know...
It was still warm.
It had a good heft to it, too.
It was stuffed.
With love?
With reality.
Number two! Class 1-4, Isshiki Makoto!
I'll shout!
Tsuyuri Kumin!
Please go out with me!
Sorry...
What about Takanashi?
I'll go look for her.
Togashi!
I think you did the right thing.
Okay, let's welcome the next person on stage!
Class 1-4, Takanashi Rikka.
Thanks.
I'll sing.
Take a look
What is she doing?!
at the stars of the night
The tiny lights
Dad...
of the tiny stars
Dad liked this song.
Sing of feeble
happiness
inside identity ibasho wa doko
Inside identity! Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji ka douka
Getting it wrong is a shame?
sunaosa ga itai toka
Being honest hurts?
dare ga nanto iou to tadashisa nante wakannai ze
Whatever people say, they don't know what's right
futsuu ni nagareteku nichijou ni
The boring river of time drifts on
muri shite najimaseta
We tried to fit in with the flow
shizunjimatta kouseitachi wo
And our uniqueness sunk in the mud
kande nonde haite warau
So chew it, swallow it, spit it out and laugh
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I wish you understood me"
iitai kedo ienakute
That's what I want to say, but I can't
nande daremo wakatte kunnai no to
"No one ever understands me"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kana
Is it selfish to think that? Is it? Is it?
kanjouteki na taiyou wa
The emotional Sun in the sky
netsu wo agesugite dounika narisou
Overheated, reaching its limit
sakebitakute shou ga nai
Of course I want to shout
gamushara ni mo tometeru identity
My fast and furious identity
inside my feeling
Inside my feeling
inside my justice
Inside my justice
jama shinaide
Don't get in my way
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
That was Takanashi Rikka from class 1-4!
Rikka...
Thank you very much!
Does this song bring back memories for you, or something like that?
To be continued
Tune in next time!