Oh. So this is where you went.
If you stay in a place like this you'll catch a cold.
Why...?
You idiot.
What's so funny, dammit?!
I don't know.
Maybe someone like you is more suited for me.
Before we go home, let's go to that karaoke place by the train station again.
Every time Otani says or does something,
...I end up going to heaven, or hell.
My whole world has been revolving around Otani, going round and round.
Recapture Love!
Improve as a Girl With Winning Chocolate!!
So, I've been rejected once already...
And I haven't got much confidence left, but...
I was thinking "Maybe Koizumi is crying again," or something along those lines.
Maybe someone like you is more suited for me.
What was that all about?
Since he said a thing like that,
HOPE
...I can't help but hold out a bit of hope.
You're the worst.
Go die, why don't you?!
What?
I told you to line up the edges before stapling them, didn't I?
I did line them up.
Idiot! How are these aligned?!
Just look. This is terrible.
Shut up. Why are you rambling like some old man?
Because you're not doing it properly!
No need to be a stickler.
You're freaking irritating! Just shut up and work!
What are they arguing about now?
I looks like they're organizing the print-outs for the next self study period.
Man. And I lined them all up so neatly too.
I can't see them.
Otani's feelings are like...
...a ramen stall owner standing behind a stove.
Completely shrouded in fog.
Couldn't you come up with a better analogy?
That is the best I could do.
Self Study
But it feels like things are great right now.
Really?
Really, really!
It's going up.
What is?
Koizumi Risa's ranking in the eyes of Otani-kun.
Koizumi Risa's ranking
What the heck is that supposed to mean?
As far as Kanzaki-san is concerned, you've won.
You really think so?
Yeah. From now on, just go for the finish.
It's almost Valentine's Day too.
Give him chocolates or something.
Chocolate, huh?
Oh yeah. In the end I didn't give him any chocolate last year.
Don't want it.
No good!
If he says "Don't want it" again like last year, I'll never recover!
Don't say stuff like that.
Is it fine to just let other girls give him chocolate?
That's no good either!
See?
But I can't do it!
He already knows I like him.
I can't run or hide or anything. I'd actually be giving him honmei chocolate!
Exactly!
What's the point of giving him obligatory chocolate now?
But it'll be like confessing to him all over again. I don't wanna!
What do you mean you don't want to? You have to!
Gah! What should I do?!
She sure is rowdy.
We're in the middle of class.
Hey...
Did you get any Valentine's chocolate last year?
Yeah, I did.
F-F-From who?
You know, those girls that come and watch me play basketball all the time.
Them, huh?
It was just obligatory chocolate, though.
How do you know?
How could I not?
The moment we had new members, they all flocked to them.
But it's fine.
I mean, I'll definitely get chocolate from at least one person this year, right?
You're gonna give me some, right?
Wh-What? Me?
Aren't you?
You want some?
I do. I want to eat it.
Well, since you asked, I guess I could give you something.
What's with that attitude!
Ah, but you've given me a lot of presents lately.
I guess I'll give you something in return next time.
Is this all right?
At this rate, I'll really get my hopes up.
See you, then.
Bye.
Bye bye!
Could it be he's starting to have feelings for me?
If he's asking me for chocolate, does that mean...
Risa.
Koizumi-senpai! Long time no see!
Haruka! Seiko-chan! What are you guys up to? Shopping?
The Home Ec Club going to make chocolate for Valentine's Day.
We're picking up some supplies.
Koizumi-senpai, why don't you make chocolate with us and give it to Otani-senpai?
If we all make something together, it'll save money, no?
Ahh, that's true. Well then....
Huh? You're giving chocolate to that midget?
What about me?
Fine. I'll give you some too.
That attitude... It's like you don't care about me at all!
It's not like that...
It's okay, isn't it?
You'll be getting chocolate from your girlfriends anyway, right, Haruka-senpai?
Huh? You have a girlfriend?
Yeah. Seven of them.
Huh? Seven?!
By dating various different types of women, I'll grow as a man.
It's all for the sake of one day going out with you, Risa.
Go out with them one at a time!
I don't have much life left in me.
I have...
Maybe ninety years left.
That's plenty!
Koizumi-senpai, how are things going with Otani-senpai?
Are you all lovely-dovey now?
Uh... Haven't I told you yet?
You got rejected?!
What the heck?! Why did he reject you?!
Like I said, he can't see me as his girlfriend.
That's...
Let's not talk about it. I don't want to remember.
LIKE HELL!!!
That damn midget... I'll cram him into a vacuum cleaner!
Wait a second. You were rejected, but you're still giving him chocolate?
You don't need to say "You were rejected."
But that's what happened.
You were rejected. Well, whatever. Why are you still giving him chocolate?
You still love him, right?
Seiko-chan, you truly understand this lonely maiden's heart.
I understand! I'm a maiden too!
Shut up, Seishirou!
It's Seiko! I'm a maiden!
We don't need to understand that kind of maiden's heart.
Hey Risa, just forget him.
Forget all about that idiot who rejected you!
Okay?
It's fine. I think he'll fall for me eventually.
Besides, it feels like things are going well at the moment.
Koizumi-senpai!
Risa!
Do your best! I'll be cheering for you!
Thanks. I'll do my best!
Man...
I won't forgive him... That damn midget...
That's right. It doesn't matter if it takes time.
I don't need to rush.
Just slowly, slowly become captivated by me.
Koizumi?
What is it?
Gross. what's got you in such a good mood?
Nothing. What did you want?
Check this out.
A new album will be out in Spring.
For real? We've gotta get it!
He'll be doing another concert too.
Really? Wow! That's awesome!
I'm definitely going.
Me too!
Of course. Who else would I go to an Umibouzu concert with?
Is that so?
We need to book tickets soon.
Haruka?
What the hell was that, you...?!
Fukagawa Haruka. Handsome seventeen year old boy,
...and Risa's childhood frien—
I didn't ask about that!
Hold on! Haruka, what were you...
Hey, hey, what's going on?
I dunno.
Hey, you midget.
What the hell do you want?
You rejected Risa, right?
Seriously?
Risa was...?
The comedy duo is breaking up?
Or is this more material?
For real?
What?! Tell me exactly what you think is wrong with Risa?!
Hey! Haruka!
Well, I mean... that's... how should I put it...?
Wait. Why do I have to explain myself to you?!
Shut up!
Since you had the nerve to do that, stay away from Risa, from now on!
Stop toying with her maiden heart, you playboy!
Don't you think you're being cruel?!
It's not like that, you idiot!
Oh? Then what is it lik-
Haruka!
That hurt...
Come with me.
Oww, oww!
Why?
You really rejected her?
How cruel.
And you seemed to get along so well.
Poor Koizumi-san.
Say something, you guys!
I'm on Risa's side.
I'm on Nobu-chan's side.
What the hell!
Sheesh. Don't do pointless stuff like this.
But that guy is so cruel!
How so?
He rejected you, but he's still going around smiling like nothing happened!
There's a limit to how dense a person can be!
It's fine. I told him to do that.
I told him to not worry about it and just act the way he did before.
But even so...
I said it's fine, so it's fine!
Stop interfering or I'll bite your head off!
I was just worried about you.
I know, and thank you.
But it's fine. I'll work hard on my own.
Risa...
So just leave me alone, okay?
Understand?
I don't!
Why?!
Fine! I don't care anymore!
Koizumi-san...
She's so determined.
What a sweet girl.
You're an idiot, Otani. How could you reject such a nice girl?
So cruel... You're so cruel.
Just a minute, you guys. At least hear me out...
Uh, don't worry about what Haruka did just now.
Koizumi-san!
We're all on your side!
Hurray for Koizumi-san!
Hurray!
H-H-H-Hey, what's going on?
Don't worry, everyone's cheering for you.
Just do your best!
Ah, I see...
I don't know exactly what's going on, but I'll do my best.
Am I really dense?
Am I really a playboy who's toying with a maiden's heart?
Haven't you been?
No I haven't!
So how do you feel about Koizumi-san?
"How"?
Do you like her?
Well, if you're asking me whether I like or dislike her, I'd say I like her, but...
Do you want her to be your girlfriend?
I don't know.
That's the problem, isn't it?
Oh, really?
I mean, suppose she was my girlfriend...
Then we'd have to kiss...
Don't you think that's kind of comical?
Not really.
You're laughing, aren't you?!
Damn it. I'm breaking out in a cold sweat.
And here I thought it'd only be a matter of time before you guys would go out.
Huh? Why?
Because when you talk to her, you seem like you're interested.
When?
Like after that incident with Kanzaki-san.
I heard about it from Nobu-chan.
I was thinking "Maybe Koizumi is crying again," or something along those lines.
Maybe someone like you is more suited for me.
I was just saying what was on my mind without really thinking about it.
And didn't you ask her for Valentine's chocolate?
I just want to eat chocolate. There's no meaning behind it.
You natural flirt.
I am not, you idiot! What are you saying?!
Let me just say this...
A casual comment from you makes Koizumi-san more flustered than you can imagine.
D-Don't make it sound so scary.
It's true.
Gather round!
It's done!
Do you think we made too much?
It's fine, it's fine.
I wonder if darling is finished with his club activities.
It might be a day early, but I'm going to give these to him.
Risa, do you want to bring yours over too?
Of course. I've prepared the wrapping and everything.
Are you really giving that to him?
Shut up, would you? Just leave me alone.
What about mine?
You don't get any. Eat what you made yourself.
But you said you were gonna give me some...
She's really going to give that midget chocolate?
He's so short...
Naturally lacking in nutrition...
This is no good. I'm too nervous.
I'm gonna go to the washroom for a bit.
Thanks to Haruka, I'm even more determined now.
I won't run or hide any more.
This is definitely honmei chocolate.
Accept my feelings, Otani.
What is this? This feeling...?
This... isn't obligatory chocolate, is it?
Um... couldn't you just make it obligatory chocolate?
What does that mean? You won't accept it if it's honmei chocolate?
You're the one who wanted it!
Well, that's true, but...
So in other words, you can't accept my feelings?
Otani, the teacher's calling for you.
Drop by the office, okay?
Sorry, I'll be right there.
Wait—
Sorry. Did I interrupt?
No. It's okay.
Geez! Hurry up!
Owww!
Sorry, Risa. Darling said some pointless things to Otani-kun.
Was it pointless?
"If you aren't interested, don't be so nice to me."
I can't say something cool like that.
Still... even if he's not interested, I'll be happy if he's still nice to me.
And I'll try even harder!
I'm a real idiot.
Accept it!
I told you, I can't.
Why?
I can't accept honmei chocolate when my own feelings are still uncertain.
Don't be so extreme! Are you trying to be a tough guy?
I never thought you were so dense, or a playboy.
You haven't done anything wrong, Otani.
If anyone is in the wrong it's me, for refusing to give up.
So I don't care if you like or hate me.
Just say whatever is on your mind.
Koizumi...
Anyway, just take it for now.
Sorry that it's honmei chocolate.
It's fine if it takes time.
As long as he gradually starts to like me.
But the girl who's fallen for me is a real idiot, huh?
Hey! What's that supposed to mean?!
You're the one who told me to say whatever I think.
That's true, but...
Hey, are you trying to piss me off?
IDIOT MIDGET
Hmph! No matter what...
...I can't let that idiot get Risa's chocolate.
Does St. Valentine just hate me?
Koizumi, what are you doing at my house?
Ooh! All alone with Otani-kun in his room huh?
But I'm not the least bit tempted to do anything.
What was that?!
Lovely Complex ~ Love Com.
Next: Heating up! A First Kiss in His Room?
Heating up! A First Kiss in His Room?
Be sure to watch!