Rikka.
Mom wants you to come say goodbye to Dad.
This is the last chance you'll have to physically touch him.
Please take the time to do so.
You okay?
Yeah. I'll be fine.
It's cold.
Why don't you wash it?
If you just pour it from the top, Dad's gonna get cold.
Takanashi
Dad...
Let's look for a
sparkling daydream...
shibaraku mitsumeatte kara
We looked into each other's eyes for a while
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no?
What did you think of while it lasted?
ki ni naru
I want to know that
A
kuchibiru
togaraseta
atashi wo mite
Look at me
as I now
pout my lips
A
dou shita no tte
kiite kuru no?
Will you ask me
what's wrong?
A
matte miru no
I'm waiting
A
gomakashita
ato no
hitorigoto wa
I'm embarrassed
by what I
mutter after
A
hazukashii kara
kikanaide kureru?
being so evasive,
so please don't
pay it any attention
A
ato ni
hikenai hodo
Our love
is so strong
A
hikareau koi
we can't
run away
mou hajimatteta
It's already begun
yume nara takusan mita
I've dreamed of our meeting so often
sameta mama
Now I'm awake
demo mada aitai
And still I want to see you
A
demo mada aitai
And still I want to see you
kimi ga sou saseta
You did this to me
koi ga
yokubari da ne
Love is greedy
koi ga yokubari da ne
A
tobihanesou
na kokoro no
My heart seems
to hop with glee
yuku mama ni yukou yo
So I'll let it guide me
A
risou mo
mousou mo
genjitsu mo
My ideals,
delusions
and reality
subete kimi
wo jiku
ni mawaru
Are all
about you
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
A
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
Result
Emails Received
Oh, morning.
Eternal Engage
There's a letter for you.
It's on your desk.
Thanks.
I know!
What was I supposed to do?
Takanashi
Rikka!
Are you there, Rikka?
I'm so stupid!
Takanashi?
I haven't really heard from her.
Don't tell me you two got in a fight.
No, it's not like that...
Yeah, right! You totally did!
Far Eastern
Magic Nap Society
of Summer
Excuse me...
Who're you?
Oh, you're so funny.
I'm Dekomori!
Dekomori Sanae.
Bleh!
Are you not well?
Did you eat a dark plant?
Who'd eat something like that?!
You're the one who's creeping me out!
What the hell did you do to your hair?
I thought I was getting a little old for
pigtails. Don't you think, my dear senior?
Stop that! You're killing me here!
Hang in there!
Stop it!
Hearing you talk like that makes my skin crawl.
Please, let go of me!
A woman's hair is vital!
You can't just grab on to it as you please.
This is totally out of left field!
What happened?
Well... I spent a lot of time thinking after what happened...
Like about Master... I mean, Takanashi.
And about what you said.
Yuuta!
Kumin... Kumin's...
Wait, who's this cutie?
See?
Hey, Tsuyuri, is your eye all right?
Yes. I'm fine.
Did you catch a cold?
I wish...
I'll be all right.
If I drink this...
What's that?
You wanna know?
Uh, I...
Kumin...
My goodness, she does look rather strange.
How shameful.
Like you can talk.
Ow!
That deathly hurt!
Huh? "Death"?
You're that middle schooler?
Little slow on the uptake, aren't we?
So you've come...
Dark Flame Master!
Please don't call me that.
Do you want to see my eye?
No, thank you.
What? You can't say that...
But...
Anyway, what's with the Rikka impression?
This is no mere act.
I inherited it...
from the wielder of the Wicked Eye.
Inherited it?
Yes.
On the final eve of the new moon, I was entrusted with the full measure of that dark power.
In other words, I am the Wicked Eye's successor.
Does that thing really need a successor?!
But of course.
The Wicked Eye must live on.
So long as the Dark Flame Master draws breath.
Is that what Rikka said?
Yes.
Wow, that sounds so... deathly cool!
And whose side are you supposed to be on?
Well, that didn't take long to clean up.
Yeah.
Looking back at it, we really weren't doing much.
By the way, how was the Drama Club?
Oh, I went to check it out.
But...
But what?
The President's a bit over-enthusiastic.
They were like, "we'll do things no one has ever done before!"
And "we'll pave the way for a new age!". That kind of thing.
Oh, one of those people...
I mean, I have no problem with enthusiasm.
It's just... this really seemed like a case of eighth-grader syndrome to me.
Was it really eighth-grader syndrome?
Maybe not exactly, but like...
I got the impression they felt like they were different to other people.
Like they were special because they
could see something others couldn't.
It felt like they were a bit full of themselves, you know?
I mean, remember how we both wanted to put our eighth-grader syndrome behind us
and just be normal high schoolers once we got here?
Yeah.
But I think we were just caught up in our own ideas of what a "normal" high schooler should be.
What are you trying to say?
Nothing much.
Just that maybe everyone always has some kind of "syndrome", you know?
That's deep.
No...
You're just shallow.
Oh, don't worry about it. I'll do the dishes.
You sure?
I don't want you to break any more of them.
I don't break them that much, do I?
I understand you're sad because Takanashi's gone, but...
She's not gone.
And I'm not sad.
What?
You mean you don't know?
The movers came in the evening, and...
Rikka!
Goddamn it! Why?
You said you'd come back.
You said you'd be right back!
HishiyamasdlkfsldfjsldfjsjfsldfsdStation
I don't think you can make it at this hour.
The train you need doesn't run this late.
I see...
Inbox
Email
Received
Inbox
Email
Received
New Emails
No Subject
Inbox
Email
Received
New Emails
No Subject
Takanashi Rikka
Inbox
Email
Received
New Emails
No Subject
Takanashi Rikka
Inbox
Email
Received
New Emails
No Subject
Takanashi Rikka
Inbox
Email
Received
New Emails
No Subject
Takanashi Rikka
Inbox
Email
Received
Inbox
Email
Received
New Emails
No Subject
Takanashi Rikka
Inbox
Email
Received
New Emails
Inbox
Email
Received
New Emails
No Subject
Inbox
Email
Received
New Emails
No Subject
Takanashi Rikka
Rikka...
Mom, Grandpa, and Grandma all looked so happy.
They were so relieved when I said that I'd do it.
So I think I made the right choice.
You agree, right, Yuuta?
Right...
This all started with me.
I told her to take off her eyepatch...
and leave her eighth-grader syndrome behind.
It was me.
Message
Okay.
Mr. Togashi Yuuta
My Brave Friend Yuuta
From... Dark Flame—
When you read this letter, you may no longer be the Dark Flame Master.
Because in 2012, as per the Mayan prophecy,
the world will be devastated by wave of
destruction, weakening your mental energy.
You may have attained enlightenment and abandoned your destiny,
reducing yourself to a pathetic
commoner, content simply to enjoy life.
I sense that this is the case.
That is why I have written you this letter.
Do not be fooled, Dark Flame Master.
You have power.
You were chosen by the Dark Lord.
You, and nobody else.
You are special.
I wrote this to myself in two years when I was in eighth grade.
Some letter, huh?
This is so stupid.
It's just a token from one of the local arcades.
It doesn't have any special powers.
But...
Tails, huh...
I guess this is fate.
Not that I mind, but where are you going in the middle of the night?
I'm going to go get Rikka.
You're going—
Wait, are you serious?
This isn't what I wanted.
This isn't what I wanted to say or do for her.
I... I...
Halt.
Dark Flame Master. I, wielder of the Second Wicked Eye, bear a message for you.
Hey, did Dad die?
Rikka...
It didn't feel like it had really happened.
In fact, I couldn't feel anything at all.
Because I thought he'd get better for sure.
I thought that until the morning he passed away.
Rikka...
I... I...!
That's when I met Yuuta.
Me?
Rikka said that?
Yes. Rikka...
I mean, the Wicked Eye found you two years ago.
When she went to the Priestess's place.
We're moving?
Yeah. Grandpa said we can live with them.
Then what'll happen to our place?
I understand.
Nothing we can do, right?
Rikka...
Ow, ow... Ow!
Hey!
The air drips heavy with malice.
They must be close by.
I watched him every day since then.
What? Over there?
And another one here?
Finally, I will...
Who's there?
I sense that I'm being watched.
Rikka thought it was wonderful that you could think like that.
She thought you were so much cooler than she was because you were true to yourself.
Then what...
was... her eighth-grader syndrome?
Rikka is a girl who was saved by her eighth-grader syndrome.
From the moment she laid eyes on you, she came to admire it.
She was bewitched by your power and tried to follow you in your footsteps.
That's why she came to you!
It couldn't have been anyone else!
Rikka was...
always, always, always...
always...!
Rikka!
Yuuta.
Oh, I need to water the plants.
Yuuta!
I am not this "Yuuta"!
Takanashi Rikka!
No, wielder of the Wicked Eye!
I have something I must show you.
Yuuta...
Make...
a contract with me!
Who's that?
A burglar?
What the hell are you doing up there?
Crap...
Dear! Call the police!
Rikka, come!
But...
Are you satisfied with this boring reality?
Or will you choose to rewrite it with me?
Yuuta!
Dear!
Rikka!
Yuuta!
Excuse me!
What are you doing up there?
It's not what it looks like!
Help! A molester! Help!
Come on, do your part already!
What, I'm the molester?
Hehe! I'm gonna feel you all over!
Help!
Hey, stop right there!
Oh, crap! It's not what it looks like!
What are they doing here?
Now, hurry up and go!
You too?
We asked Deko to give us a ride.
Take these too.
Stop!
Come back!
My leg's cramping up!
Want me to pedal?
Don't fret.
With the Dark Flame Master's power... this is... nothing!
The lights are...
Yeah, they're beautiful.
But those are just cruise liners.
They're just ordinary lights.
Get off.
This is the power of darkness.
Blast reality.
Burst it into shreds.
Banishment...
this world!
Yuuta.
This is the Ethereal Horizon.
The lights are watching you.
Tell them.
Tell them your feelings.
The true feelings you've been holding back.
Goodbye...
Goodbye, Dad!
Goodbye!
People always say they feel awkward
about having eighth-grader syndrome.
They say that they don't want to talk about it, that they want to forget about it for good.
But does that really get rid of our crazy old selves and their wild fantasies...
back when we thought we were special, when we thought something greater watched over us?
On Patrol
People sometimes tell lies, imagine a completely different fantasy world, dream about the distant future,
or invent a lover's relationship that only exists inside their heads.
This process repeats from the day we are born until the day we die. Forever and ever.
It is depressing.
It is shameful.
But it is dear to us.
It is an illness known as self-consciousness.
It is something we must all face known as "ourselves."
Indeed, we carry our eighth-grader
syndrome throughout all of our lives.
Man, it's cold.
Do you want to see my eye?
But to be honest, it's an embarrassing thing to have.
inside identity ibasho wa doko
Inside identity! Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji ka douka
Getting it wrong is a shame?
sunaosa ga itai toka
Being honest hurts?
dare ga nanto iou to tadashisa nante wakannai ze
Whatever people say, they don't know what's right
futsuu ni nagareteku nichijou ni
The boring river of time drifts on
muri shite najimaseta
We tried to fit in with the flow
shizunjimatta kouseitachi wo
And our uniqueness sunk in the mud
kande nonde haite warau
So chew it, swallow it, spit it out and laugh
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I wish you understood me"
iitai kedo ienakute
That's what I want to say, but I can't
nande daremo wakatte kunnai no to
"No one ever understands me"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kana
Is it selfish to think that? Is it? Is it?
kanjouteki na taiyou wa
The emotional Sun in the sky
netsu wo agesugite dounika narisou
Overheated, reaching its limit
sakebitakute shou ga nai
Of course I want to shout
gamushara ni mo tometeru identity
My fast and furious identity
inside my feeling
Inside my feeling
inside my justice
Inside my justice
jama shinaide
Don't get in my way
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
She's the cute girl from the mochi store.
Tamako Market!
OPPOSE
REALITY!
See you again!