This... isn't obligatory chocolate, is it?
Um... couldn't you just make it obligatory chocolate?
What does that mean? You won't accept it if it's honmei chocolate?
The teacher's calling for you.
Drop by the office, okay?
Sorry. I'll be right there.
Wait—
I'm a real idiot.
Accept it!
Heating up! A First Kiss in His Room?
According to Nakao-chi's information,
...Otani's stance on seeing me as a girlfriend is still...
I don't know.
Oh? Really?
...like that.
What does he mean by "I don't know"?
It's cold.
What is it?
Look at this spot right here.
It's been a week, and it's still red.
You hit me with the corner of that box.
It was damn careless.
Shut up, would you.
Are you seriously going to go around behaving like this?
You might get arrested for assault.
What's that supposed to mean?
I don't understand.
You idiot. I'm the one who doesn't understand.
Is that any way to give someone honmei chocolate?
Accept it!
That happened because you said those stupid things!
What do you mean, "stupid"?
I gave it a lot of thought before I responded.
But you just ignored me and threw the chocolate at me.
And even then...
...when I opened the box, the chocolate was like that!
IDIOT MIDGET
There was even icing in the shape of a turd on it!
That wasn't my fault!
Haruka switched my chocolate!
I gave you a proper one later, didn't I?
Nakao-chi's information #2.
Suppose she was my girlfriend. Then we'd have to kiss.
Don't you think that's kind of comical?
Or something along those lines, right?
Wh-What?
The next time we see each other, it'll be in the courtroom!
Plaintiff
I'll sue you for slander!
Defendant
Bring it on!
Did Koizumi-san really get rejected?
They're no different from before.
Even rudeness has its limits!
Kiss...
What's so funny?!
I was just thinking that Otani-kun probably couldn't even reach Risa's lips.
Th-That's...
Kiss...
That's funny. It really is funny.
Don't you think?
It's not like that's gonna happen, anyway. We're not even dating.
What are you talking about?
You can't think like that.
If confessing didn't work,
...you should actively pursue him and take him by force!
Ugh. That might work for you, Seiko-chan...
Say, Seiko-chan, you've kissed Otani before, right?
That was a nice scene.
Ah! I'm embarrassed!
Don't be shy, now.
Whatever.
It's not like I wanted to kiss him anyway.
It's like your love-point level is lower than an elementary student's.
Just how old are you?
I'm just a kid, of course.
I've never kissed anyone.
Oh, then why do you want to be his girlfriend?
"Why," you ask...
I mean isn't it so that you can walk hand in hand..
Or kiss...
Or get hot and heavy?
Not really.
It's okay. It's okay.
As long as she and Otani-kun can be like...
"Yay! Umibouzu!"
...she'll be happy enough.
That's so cute!
Don't make fun of me!
Man. Everyone is so damn rude.
No good, no good. It really is comical.
Why the hell are you so damn short?!
It's pissing me off!
Wh-What did you say? I'll smack you!
Hey, wait up.
What?
Here you go. My treat.
What's this?
These... These...
These are...
...tickets to the Umibouzu concert!
In return for Christmas and Valentine's Day.
White Day would be too late, so I thought I'd give them to you now.
Seriously?
Yep. I waited in line for them all morning yesterday.
Oh! What's this? Seat #3?
We'll be in the front row!
We'll even be able to distinguish Umibouzu's pores.
You're awesome, Otani! You're awesome!
One more time, one more time.
Otani, you're so manly! Otani, you're so cool!
Well, yes.
What if he looks right at us?
We could shake his hand.
Maybe he'll remember us from Hokkaido.
Maybe he'll even call out to us!
Yay! Umibouzu!
Thank you very much. I humbly accept.
Who the heck are you?
So, when's the concert?
The day after the graduation ceremony.
Never mind. I am just a kid after all.
I didn't say anything.
It's been a while since you've been on a date with just the two of you.
It's not a date or anything! There's not much romance between...
Then make some romance, you idiot!
Are you just going to let all that effort with the honmei chocolate go to waste?
Your goal is to be a kissable girl! Chu!
Enough with the "chu-chu"!
What are you, a mouse?
Darling!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
It's like we've been apart for so long!
I missed you!
Good work.
You sure have a lot of free time.
I was wondering if you were waiting to throw something at me again.
I wasn't.
I see.
Otani isn't here today?
Yeah. I heard he has a cold.
Really? I hope he's okay.
The concert is tomorrow...
Why don't you pay him a little visit?
If you're nice to him in his weakened state, it'll leave an impression.
He's weakened, weakened.
For the sake of tomorrow's Umibouzu concert, you need to do your best now!
B-But I don't know where he lives...
We'll tell you all you want to know, right?
Here ya go. A map to his place.
Right! I get it. I'm gonna go for it!
You can even do things that might result in you catching his cold.
What are you saying?
Okay. Here are the report cards for you second-year students.
Otani
Yes?
And you are...?
Um... I'm Otani-kun's classmate, Koizumi.
He wasn't at school today, so, uh...
...I came to visit him and brought his report card.
Are you A-chan's girlfriend?
A-A-chan?
What's this? A-chan's girlfriend?
Uh, no. I'm not...
She's a beauty too, isn't she?
Well, come in, come in.
Wh-What?
That boy's been practically dead since this morning,
...but he's a bit better now.
A-chan! A-chan, wake up!
I'll make some tea. It'll just be a minute, okay?
Shut up. What's going on?
So how are you feeling... A-chan?
What are you doing in my house?!
I came to visit.
A-chan, what good timing.
Let's have some cake.
I just picked it up. It's round.
Just a minute while I cut it.
You shouldn't feed a sick person cake!
Why not? That's such a waste.
You sure are tall, aren't you.
How tall are you, exactly?
Um... 172 cm.
172?
You're shorter than her, A-chan. How uncool.
Shut up! Get out!
Mom's not scared by your shouting.
You aren't even tall enough to kiss her.
Totally uncool.
Why would I do that?!
She's your girlfriend, isn't she?
No!
Fine. Just go away!
It's your birthday today, Otani?
Yeah. You should at least know the birthday of the guy you like.
So, what brings you here?
Here. Your report card.
Did you look at it?
I did. It's about as bad as mine.
And, here. Some oranges to help you get better.
Thank you.
I'm not sure if I'll be okay tomorrow.
For Umibouzu?
If I can't go, then just go by yourself. Enjoy it for me, okay.
If you're not going, then I won't go either.
There's no point if I don't get to go with you.
What are you saying? I went to a lot of effort to get those tickets.
Oh, that's right.
Then you have to come, no matter what.
I'll do that.
Hey...
I've been wanting to ask you something.
What is it?
When did you start liking me?
H-How can you ask something like that?!
Didn't you tell me to say whatever is on my mind?
How could I expect this?!
Aren't you always talking about how short I am?
Do you really want a boyfriend this short?
I'm seriously going to hit you, you idiot.
That hurts... What the heck?
I'm fine with it.
It's not like you want a tall girl like me for a girlfriend either, right?
No, height has nothing to do with it.
Well, I guess it does... I guess it does a little bit.
What do you mean?
You're the one who told me not to think about height, and just go for it.
Huh? I did?
When did I say that?
You said it last summer!
You have your own charm, Koizumi.
Don't be indecisive. Just go for it.
So, who do you like?
Never mind.
How can I not mind? Of course I mind, being the only one who doesn't know.
Back when you didn't know it was you, and you were going around asking,
"Who does Koizumi like?"
That's when!
What was that? Me?
Was that supposed to me be?!
Damn straight.
My face doesn't look like that!
It sure does.
Is this how you treat the guy you like?
Yep.
Please don't taunt a sick person.
I'm not really as concerned with height as you think.
So it's because of my twisted personality?
If you know that, then you should do something about it.
But it'd be weird if you changed all of a sudden.
Don't call me weird!
The rest of the problem lies with me.
It's your problem?
Even though the two of us are alone in this room right now, I don't feel a thing.
That's a big problem.
So what should I do?
Am I really that unattractive?
Ko-Koizumi...
Sorry I forgot to give you sugar.
Uh, um, I'll be leaving now!
Oh, already?
A-chan? What happened, A-chan?
Oh my! You're burning up!
Yay! I'm completely cured!
Oh, sorry. My fever came back again last night.
Man, the last thing I remember was eating oranges. It's all a blank after that.
What were we talking about again?
Huh? Koizumi, did you catch a cold?
Wh-What did you just say?
"Koizumi, did you catch a cold?"
Before that!
"It's all a blank after that"?
All?
All.
All!
Yeah!
Wow, the weather sure is nice today!
Perfect for an Umibouzu concert.
You...
Go and die!
L-O-V-E Maity!
Oh no! Koizumi is acting weird.
Go away. All I can see right now is that guy.
Lovely Complex ~ Love Com.
Next: A Killer Crush on Maity!
A Killer Crush on Maity!
Be sure to watch!