It's such a waste to spoil such a cute face with a furrowed brow.
Go on. Smile, okay?
Cain-sama!
That's it!
Wha-Wha-Wha-What did you do that for?!
I guess that really was just an accidental bump, huh?
An accidental...
I've been trying so hard...
Even though you rejected me, I've been trying my best.
But if I go on liking you like this, nothing will change.
Koizumi...
I've had enough.
I've had enough of this.
I'm through with loving you!
Enough...
I give up.
A Dangerous Man
Maity's Sweet Seduction
Rice.
I remember now.
When I was sick and you came to visit me...
That's right. I was staring at your face like this...
And then...
Your hair...
There was a grain of rice stuck to it.
Rice... Rice... Rice...
Rice stuck to it...
Rice...
What's the matter?
We should have bread for breakfast!
"A Japanese breakfast should consist of rice and miso soup."
Weren't you the one who said that?
I've had enough of rice!
So then I was thinking I'd take this rice off while making a joke, when I suddenly got dizzy...
Apparently my first kiss was just an accident.
He didn't try to kiss me.
He was just trying to take off the rice that was stuck to my hair,
...when he accidentally bumped my lips.
Yeah, right!
What? Does that character from that game of yours like bread or something, Ni-chan?
Yes. Cain-sama has croissants and café au lait for breakfast.
I need to be like him, otherwise it'll be a problem when we get married.
Nee-chan seems pretty messed up.
Risa, hurry up and come back to this world!
I'm Koizumi Risa, 17 years old. 172 cm tall.
A girl who's just a little on the tall side.
The truth is, I have a crush on someone right now.
And that person is...
Maity-sensei!
Good morning.
Maity-sensei, who looks like Cain-sama...
He's wonderful again today.
It's great that you're so full of energy today.
I'm always full of energy.
Weren't you crying yesterday?
How did you...
You passed me when you ran down the hallway.
You can talk to me any time if you feel like it.
Maity-sensei...
Yes!
That's right. I love Maity-sensei.
Koizumi, I wan to talk to y—
Huh? I heard a voice, but I don't see anyone.
Was it my imagination?
Or is there a guy about one inch tall hiding somewhere around here?
Well, never mind that.
Maity-sensei, I'm looking forward to your class as always!
Thanks.
After stealing a kiss from my lips, are you just going to ignore me?
Lips? Stolen?
Th-Th-That's not what happened!
What are you saying in front of Maity-sense?!
What? You're ditching me now that the deed's been done?
"Deed"?!
Shut your mouth!
That hurt! What the heck was that?!
Shut up! I barely touched you.
How typical of a comedy duo.
You two sure get along well.
Are you two going out?
We are not!
We don't get along. And we're not a comedy duo, either.
Come on. Classes will be starting soon.
It doesn't matter. I've given up.
I've been acting like a fool.
I don't like this idiot anymore.
When I think about it, it's a total waste of time.
Huh? What do you mean, you've given up?
What's that? Why?
Well, you know... youth is fleeting.
If I keep chasing after an idiot like that,
...I'll be an old granny in no time.
What the hell!
This is bad. She's talking nonsense again.
Risa-chan... Please come back, Risa-chan!
What is it? What happened this time?
Nothing.
I'm just tired of Otani's idiocy.
Are you serious? Just a second!
Yeah, Risa-chan. You've worked so hard up until now...
It's fine. I don't care anymore.
From this day onwards, I'm taking the first step towards my new love!
"New love"?
"The first step"?
Hey, Maity-sensei, how old are you?
How old do I look?
Around 23?
Well, it's somewhere around there.
Aww, that's not right?
Not quite.
It's back! What's with this chilly atmosphere?
Then... 24?
You got it.
When did she...
Don't tell me her new love is Maity-sensei?
Wha—?!
Not good! Not good, not good, this is not good!
Mommy will not forgive you!
"Mommy"?
I mean, I've already given it my best.
No matter how hard I tried, nothing changed.
What's wrong? You seem all broody.
Of course I'm broody.
Did something happen?
Koizumi forced a kiss on me.
Oh? This happens to you a lot, huh, Otani?
Last time it was Seiko-chan who did it, right?
Just a minute! Can't you see how shocked I am?!
And then?
How on earth did that happen, anyway?
W-Well... I'm not really sure.
But I supposedly kissed her before.
"Supposedly"?
What do you mean by that?
It happened while I had a fever, so I don't remember.
So you violated her and you don't even remember?
You beast.
I am not!
And as for who violated who...
Am I really that unattractive?
I was the one who was violated...
Koizumi-san sure has been trying hard.
She must really like Otani.
Shut up! I know, okay!
So you know, huh? That's a surprise.
You said yourself you couldn't remember.
I didn't forget that much!
But she said she's giving up.
I give up. I'm done. Good bye!
Maitake Kunimi Fan Club
Maity Club
Thank you all for coming!
Maity for Life
I'm the president of the Maitake Kunimi Fan Club, aka Maity Club.
My name is Koizumi Risa.
Good day to you all.
To commemorate the formation of our club, we've invited Maity-sensei himself.
So, let's welcome him, everyone. One, two...
MAITY!
Hello.
Come, come, come.
Now, raise your hand if you have a question for Maity-sensei.
Yes!
This is amazing.
Sensei are you going out with anyone right now?
That's a secret.
Sensei, why are you ****?
That's also a secret.
Sensei, could it be you're **** ****?
That's all secret.
What's that sound?
Hey, where'd Koizumi go?
Club.
Club?
Yeah. The Maity Club.
Maity Club? What's that?
It seems to be a club dedicated to Maity-sensei.
Huh?
Don't say "huh," you idiot!
Risa-chan has moved on.
Wh-Why are you so angry?
Darling told me everything.
This is all your fault, Otani-kun.
Do something about this Maity Club!
Why is it my fault?
If you weren't such an idiot, you wouldn't be in this situation wondering whether you'd kissed or not!
If you just apologized, I'm sure Risa would let it go.
What should I apologize for?
Anything!
Just get her to quit that stupid club, idiot!
Nobu-chan...
Maity! Maity! Maity!
What are you doing here?
What about basketball club?
The coach sprained his hip, so it's canceled for a while.
Maity for Life
"Maity for life," huh?
That's going a bit too far...
Why do you care?! Leave me alone.
This is no good. We can't be alone together,
...otherwise I'll remember again.
Even though it was a spur of the moment thing, the fact that I—
About yesterday...
It's fine! Just let it go!
Did I really kiss you while I had a cold?
I just told you to let it go, didn't I?!
I'm sorry.
Sorry... Sorry... Sorry...
"Sorry"?
What are you apologizing for?
For forgetting that you kissed me?
Or for not seeing me as a girl, no matter what I do?
You don't have to put on such a confused expression.
It's fine. I've had enough.
I've had enough already.
I told you. I'm done.
Sorry for bothering you for so long.
You don't need to worry about me.
Koizumi...
For some reason...
Wait! Don't give up on me!
...I was kind of hoping he would say something like that.
But I guess that's impossible.
There's no way that would happen.
Oh, are you going home now?
Uh... yes.
What's the matter? Did something happen?
Koizumi-san sure has been trying hard.
She must really like Otani.
But if I go on liking you like this, nothing will change.
I'm through with loving you!
I've had enough. I've had enough already.
Love Maity!
Go!
M A I T Y Love Maity!
Not loud enough. Again!
I don't think I can be friends with Risa anymore.
Is that another Maity Club activity?
I said, starting today, Maity-sensei is going to be the coach for the basketball club.
What the heck?
The coach has sprained his hip, so just bear with it until he gets better.
Why the heck does that guy have to be his substitute?!
Geez. Otani-kun, you have to do something about this.
At this rate Risa really will fall for that cold guy.
Like I care.
What do you mean, "Like I care"?!
This is all your fault!
How is it my fault?!
She as the one who chose to go after him on the rebound.
Hey, please don't bully my cute Nobu-chan.
You bastard.
I'm the one being bullied!
Koizumi-san.
Maity-sensei!
Are you feeling better now?
Sorry about that sudden outburst yesterday.
I don't know what happened, but don't push yourself too hard, okay?
Yes! It was nothing.
I'm going to watch the basketball club and cheer for you today, Maity-sensei.
Thank you. I'll look forward to it.
Do your best!
He's so cool!
I'm in your care.
Can you actually play basketball?
Well, why don't you decide?
That was cheap! Hold it right there!
Maity! Maity!
Maity! Mai—
Maity! Mai...
Sheesh, what is he doing?
Hey, President! We need to cheer properly for Maity-sensei.
Maity!
I played basketball all through high school.
Shut up! You're damn noisy!
How rude.
Maity! Do your best!
Otani?
Let's go again.
Okay.
Otani, what about practice?
Shut up!
Risa...
Is this really okay?
It's fine.
I plan to devote my youth to Maity-sensei from now on.
Good lord, would you stop this?!
I absolutely refuse to let you be with a guy like him!
Risa-chan...
But it's not like I have any choice.
I tried so hard, and even when I said I was giving up, he didn't even try to stop me.
Ah, you're still here?
Darling, is practice over?
Yeah.
Where's Otani-kun?
He ran off sulking.
He couldn't steal the ball from Maity-sensei, you see.
Maybe he's off being depressed somewhere...
Risa, go find him and talk to him.
Why do I have to?
He might go so far as to quit basketball after this.
That's stupid.
Otani-kun.
Yes?
I'd like to ask you something.
Is that all right with you?
Sure. Go ahead.
Koizumi-san was crying recently.
Were you the reason for that?
You looked pretty mad just now.
Shut up! You're creepy!
What's it to you, anyway?!
Girls are hurt easily. You need to be gentle with them.
It's none of your business! Leave me alone!
Koizumi-san probably likes you a lot.
So? What about it?
I was wondering how you feel about her.
That's none of your business.
Then maybe I'll take her for myself.
Do whatever you want.
Are you really all right with that?
I said, do whatever you want!
I don't like Koizumi or anything!
Did I hear that right, just now?
I've been rejected by the same guy twice?
Chomp!
Ahhh!
Maity-sensei!
"Maity, Maity." Shut up!
Quit that disgusting Maity Club, already.
Otani, are you jealous?
Lovely Complex ~ Love Com.
Next: Maity's Magic! The Transforming Power of Love!?
Maity's Magic! The Transforming Power of Love!?
Be sure to watch!