Koizumi.
Can't you pull a better face than that?
What?
But...
Do you have a fever again?
It's not like that.
Ah... Not like that... Not like that...
Don't laugh.
Then...
Am I still dreaming?
Sudden Downturn!
The First Date is the Beginning of Misfortune
I thought my heart was going to burst.
I couldn't sleep at all last night.
At this rate, I'll die of heart failure, thanks to Otani.
Risa, do you have summer classes again today?
You've really got to get it together, don't you?
Your future will be something to look forward to.
I'm just... no good without you, Koizumi.
So this and that really weren't dreams.
What are you, some old geezer?
Your bangs are completely flat!
Well, I was wearing a hat, so...
Good morning!
Good morning.
Good... morn...
Hey, look.
Wha-What are you doing wearing that, you idiot?!
What? Then just when am I supposed to wear it?
Risa, good morning.
Good morning.
Good morning, Nobu-chan.
Good morning, darling.
That's a cute necklace.
Where'd you get it?
Oh! Ah, this is—
Koizumi!
It was.. uh...
...a gift from God.
What's that supposed to mean?
Right. You, come with me.
You absolutely cannot tell those guys anything unnecessary, okay.
"Unnecessary"?
A-About this...
And that...
"This and that"?
Ahh... That.
So like I said, just keep your mouth shut.
Why should I have to listen to your lecturing?
I am not lecturing.
Don't pull that face.
But... I'm really happy.
I  just want to say so out loud.
I'm sorry, but I don't just want to tell Nobu-chan.
I want the whole world to know how happy I am...
...about this and that.
You're an idiot.
I am.
Fine!
Do whatever you like.
Wait up!
Don't follow me.
But...
What's the matter?
We heard.
I already told you! Nothing happened!
Honestly?
Shut up. I'm going home.
Risa, you got that necklace from Otani-kun, right?
Otani bought it for me
Oh my! How did you know?
Otani
bought it for me
Oh? Is that so? That's wonderful, Risa-chan.
What. When did he give it to you?
Yesterday, while you guys were watching the fireworks.
Oh? I had no idea.
What's up with that?!
Wait. Were you guys sneaking around doing things behind our backs?
How dirty.
Well, he gave me a present,
...and he said, "I'm just no good without you, Koizumi."
And then...
I can't say it!
What the heck is that "kyaah" about?!
Well, I've been trying really hard, but now it's paying off...
...and my dream is finally coming true.
I'm just so happy.
You should be. You worked really hard for this.
So.
All Hanshin-Kyojin are finally a couple.
It's been a long wait.
We're not going out yet.
Wait! What the heck?!
Didn't he ask you out?
So... he just gave you a present?
Well, I got more than just a present...
But let's just leave it at that.
What's that supposed to mean?
Oh? But Risa-chan, you said your dream came true.
You see, not long ago he said...
"I mean, suppose she was my girlfriend."
"Then we'd have to kiss."
And...
"Even though the two of us are alone in this room right now, I don't feel a thing."
...and stuff like that.
But then yesterday, that happened.
It was no illusion!
What's "that"?
Who knows.
All of my hard work has paid off.
Hey, are you an idiot?
Say whatever you like.
Well then, I'll see you tomorrow.
Yeah.
Koizumi.
What is it?
Want to go somewhere before going home?
At this point it would be natural to jump straight into dating, wouldn't it?
By the way, Koizumi...
What is it?
I forgot to give this to you.
Here, take one.
Cool! A ticket to the World Athletics Championships!
And it's the night of the finals!
These tickets are really hard to get.
My dad's been itching to get one.
Amazing, Otani! Well done.
Good job. Big man! Big man!
What are you doing? I don't get you at all.
You're making me uneasy,
...so I'm gonna hold onto this for safekeeping.
Huh? Risa?
It really is you, Risa!
Oh! Ake-chi! Long time no see!
How are you?
I'm great!
Oh, this is a friend of mine from middle school.
Ah. Hello.
Don't tell me this is your boyfriend?
No, no. We're just friends, just friends.
But he might be my boyfriend tomorrow...
Of course.
You always said you'd never go for a guy shorter than you, right Risa?
No! I meant...
Well, I've got to get going. See you around!
Yeah, uh... see ya.
Otani?
A-Are you angry?
Not really.
I said that stuff about not wanting a boyfriend shorter than me a long time ago.
Like I care about that.
Then what is it?
You...! I'm...!
Never mind.
What's the matter? I'm concerned.
Be concerned.
Hey, what's the matter? Otani!
Sorry! I'm really sorry!
You're late.
Well, you are always like this.
What do you mean, I'm always like this?
You make it sound like I'm always late!
You're late one in every three times we go somewhere.
You're just as bad!
You're gonna lecture me when you're the one who was late?
N-No.
Well, I'll treat you to something today.
Sorry. Were you waiting long?
Nope. I just got here.
It should've been like that...
What is it?
I forgot my handbag!
I was in a rush...
I'll go get it.
You idiot! The event is about to start.
But my purse is...
Ah... I have some change in my pocket.
What are you, some old geezer?!
Were you on your way to go play Pachinko?
That's why I wanted to get my bag.
Fine. It'll be my treat today.
Sorry.
Come one. Let's go.
It's a good thing I held on to your ticket.
Honi-san! Iwashi-san! Hurry! Hurry!
It's about to start.
We'll miss Murouchi!
Okay!
You there, get out of the way!
Otani?
What are you doing, you old bags?
Nothing. Never mind.
Let's go! Hurry!
Okay! Okay!
Are you all right?
What is it?
I think my finger got cut by one of those women's handbags.
I see. Just a minute. I have bandages.
I always keep some in my handb—
Ugh, that's right. I forgot my handbag.
That might Murouchi. Let's go!
Murouchi is amazing!
He easily passed the 80 meter mark!
This the worst.
I can't take it.
If Otani's ex-girlfriend, Kanzaki, was in that situation,
...I'm sure she would've pulled out a bandage right away.
She was manager of the basketball team, after all.
Thanks.
Or something like that...
She really was a sweet girl, that Kanzaki-san.
Koizumi, you've been sighing for a while now.
Aren't you having fun?
What? No. I'm having fun, I'm having fun.
Is Murouchi about to start? I'm so excited!
Right. Come here for a sec.
What's up with you? It's just a handbag.
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry for being like this...
Koizumi.
I'll tell you what bothered me last time.
Are we friends?
Couldn't you have paused for a second before saying we were just friends?
Are you talking about what I said when I bumped into Ake-chi back then?
Would friends do that?
"Тhat"?
Do you honestly think I would do that with someone I considered "just a friend"?!
I would never kiss a girl who was just a friend!
Oh, I see...
That's right.
After kissing like that, we're not just friends, are we?
So... What am I to you?
You really are an idiot.
But you never told me clearly. How should I know?!
You should know!
What should I know?!
The kiss alone was enough to make me happy!
Why would I have done something like that for no reason?
It made me happy, too.
What's with you?
I'm going to have you arrested for stealing my heart, old man.
It's an illusion...
Don't cry, you.
Here.
I-I like you...
I like you a lot, Otani!
I love you!
I really, really love you!
I'm seriously in love with you!
I get it!
I love you so much!
I love you.
I know.
And... you love me too, right, Otani?
Good job, buddy!
You idiot!
What were you thinking, saying all that in front of so many people?! Geez!
But... I was just so happy!
What's with that ugly face of yours?
But I can't help it!
You've stolen my heart, Otani.
Oh dear. I've stolen it, have I?
Yeah. It's not fair.
I want to steal yours, too.
You idiot. Mine isn't so easy to steal.
I'm thirsty. Go get me something to drink.
Your choice.
You have change, don't you?
You want to steal my heart, don't you?
Yes, I do!
Off you go.
Roger!
Otani sure is a nice guy.
I'm falling in love with him even more.
I wonder if he's really happy with me...
Well, he did say "yeah."
This road has sure been long.
This is my first time experiencing requited love.
From now on, we're gonna be all lovey-dovey!
Ot—!
It's...
It's the ex-girlfriend!
Huh? Just now, was that...
Ah. I thought so.
That looks like it hurts. Is it a blister?
Yeah... I'm not used to these shoes.
Why don't you sit down over there?
It's a good thing I'm carrying bandages...
I knew it.
She'd always carry bandages, wouldn't she...
Raise your foot a bit, okay?
She's such a sweet girl.
It's not too bad. You should be fine.
Thank goodness.
Oh, what's the matter? Does it hurt?
What's going on?
Atsushi-kun
She got a blister, and...
Oh? Really? You should've said so.
I hate this. I'm so embarrassed.
I'm so embarrassed right now.
You can't like a girl this embarrassing, right?
You'd prefer Kanzaki-san to me, right?
That's right. Kanzaki-san is still broken hearted after breaking up with her giant.
Goodbye, Otani.
Our time was short, but it made me so happy!
Thanks, Kanzaki. I'll take it from here.
Really? Okay then.
Um... sorry, what was your name again?
Koizumi Risa.
She's my girlfriend.
Oh, is that so?
Yeah. The giant's waiting for you, right?
Oh, that's right. Bye.
Apparently she and the giant got back together so they came here today.
Good for her, huh?
"Girlfriend."
Is this okay?
Are you really okay with having a girlfriend like me?
What are you talking about now?
Here, give me your foot.
This happened because you got carried away and wore clothes you're not used to.
But this... this is our first date.
I wanted to look cuter for you. At least just a little.
Oh no. This is bad.
I think my heart was just stolen a little.
What was that?
Just talking to myself.
After that, I cried for ages.
Because of that, I couldn't see the World Championships through my tears.
Murouchi sure worked hard.
What? Are you still crying?
You look pitiful. Here, dry your tears.
My heart's been stolen again!
Just how many hearts do you have?
You're finally back to your usual self.
A-chan!
Mimi!
You came to watch, too?
Yeah. I came with Papa.
Woah! What a beautiful girl!
"A-chan"?
"Mimi"?
Who is this?
Oh, she's my neighbor.
Hello! I'm Yoshioka Mimi. I'm in my second year of middle school.
Middle school?
She looks so mature!
You think?
A-chan, who's this? A friend of yours?
Girlfriend.
Nice to meet you!
No way!
When did this happen?!
This is the first I've heard about it!
Didn't I tell you?
No, you didn't!
Your old man is waiting for you, right?
Let's go, Koizumi.
Okay, okay.
See you later, Mimi-chan.
I will not accept this.
A lame girl like that is A-chan's girlfriend?
There's no way I'll accept it!
Koizumi, want to come study at my place?
Sure! This feels so lovey-dovey.
Ah, Mimi.
Lovely Complex ~ Love Com.
Next: Declaration of War!! The Dangerous Beauty Who Burns With Jealousy!!
Declaration of War!! The Dangerous Beauty Who Burns With Jealousy!!
Be sure to watch!