Otani's Catastrophic Declaration!!
Nobu-chan received her acceptance notice from the undergraduate university in Hokkaido,
...and she's been even more lovey-dovey with Nakao-chi than before.
Otani, who wants to become a teacher,
...has started attending prep classes,
and is studying for the entrance exams.
I don't like studying or taking tests,
...so I've decided to try for a technical college.
Hey, Otani...
What?
What do you want to do about the next Umibouzu concert?
I'm gonna pass this time.
This is Umibouzu we're talking about!
It's the last Umibouzu concert of the year!
I know! But I don't really have a choice.
This is the only time I have to study for exams.
I was choking back tears when I finally decided not to go.
I see...
Idiot! Who was it who said she was going to support me?!
Exam students sure have it hard.
Are you mocking me?
Not really.
If not, stop talking to me while I'm trying to memorize English vocabulary.
Wait, Otani.
Be quiet. Why are you following me, anyway?
No need to put it like that.
I've got a reason for coming this way.
Huh? A reason?
My part-time job.
It's at the restaurant opposite your prep school.
Why are you working all of a sudden?
This way I can at least walk you halfway home.
Your ribbon isn't on straight.
Sorry.
And your nails are too long.
Please cut them before you come tomorrow.
And tie your hair up tighter.
S-Sure!
How strict.
Kohori-kun!
You're five minutes late.
I-I'm sorry.
And this is the second day in a row.
I was held back at school by my teacher.
I already told you to call ahead if that happens.
Another part-timer? What a cute boy.
An Umibouzu wristband!
And it's the limited edition one that you can only get at his concerts!
Don't tell me you're a huge Umibouzu fan too?
A mega fan!
Same here!
It's awesome to have another Umibouzu fan around!
Yay! I'm feeling all excited now!
Koizumi-san! Kohori-kun! Stop that right now!
Sorry...
These dumplings are just delicious!
They really are.
You like them?
Of course. You made them, after all.
So what's this younger co-worker of yours like?
Oh, Kohori-kun?
His face is kind of cute,
...and he's about as tall as Otani.
Is your midget fetish speaking to you?
Who's got a midget fetish?!
Come to think of it, Otani-kun seems to be working really hard.
No way. Otani-kun is?
I heard he stayed behind yesterday,
...and was asking the teacher lots of questions.
Otani really is trying.
That's correct.
N-No way!
Like I said. If I put my mind to it, I can do it.
Seriously?
At this rate, getting into college won't be impossible for him.
In comparison, I...
...I need to decide what I'm going to do with myself.
Maybe I should just start doing this full time...
Koizumi-san!
I'm sorry.
Sorr—
Koizumi-san!
You shouldn't always make such a fuss.
Man... I really can't do anything.
And I was thinking of doing this full time?
I'm sorry.
Good morning!
I think it needs more salt.
It was too sweet, was it?
I don't get this part.
Let's see...
Use this formula...
Wh-What's up with all of you?!
It's like you're all ready to fly off into the future!
Oh, Risa, you're here? Good morning.
Maybe I should add yams to the recipe.
Darling, you're a genius!
You'll definitely become a great artisan.
Wh-What's going on?
Somehow... somehow...
...I feel like I'm being left behind.
My face looks terrible.
I'll get yelled at again.
Smile, smile.
Welcome!
She said "Welcome."
What did you come here for?!
You're saying "What did you come here for" to your customers?
How rude.
Working hard?
What is this? Did you come here just to laugh at me?
Excuse me!
This employee's attitude is terrible.
Please let me know what you would like to order.
How weird!
How funny!
At least me finish.
P-P-Please go ahead...
Hey, that hurt, you idiot!
I'm a customer, you know.
What happened to studying?
I am.
I'm going to prep class in a bit.
They even hold them on Sundays?
There are no weekends for exam students.
Especially not for the ones with bad grades.
Exactly, exact—
Hey. Enough, enough.
Say Risa, where's that cute guy you mentioned last time?
Not working today?
Oh, Kohori-kun? Doesn't look like he's here today.
Who is this guy?
Midget fetishist Risa's next target.
Midget fetishist?
I told you it's not like that!
What? So that guy is short too?
No! That's not important!
He's a huge Umibouzu fan.
No way! Seriously?
I'll get yelled at if I keep talking.
Uh, my order...
Well, well... She seems a lot happier than I expected.
Oh really?
You said you came to laugh at her,
...but you were actually worried about her, weren't you?
Since she was down about always getting chewed out.
What?
Right?
Right, right.
How cute!
It's not like that, you idiots!
An exam student's got no time to worry about others.
That again?
If you're like that, Risa will hook up with that cute short kid behind your back.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Don't be stupid.
I see. So Otani has class on Sundays too?
Thank you for your patronage.
Work hard.
See ya, Risa.
I was planning to go out with him next Sunday since I'll have the day off.
Oh well. He's an exam student. It can't be helped.
GLOOM
What's with this odd, gloomy atmosphere?
What's the matter?
Shut up, idiot. Don't talk to me.
Risa, over here, over here.
What is it?
We heard he did terribly in the practice exams.
The results for his top choice school were all C's.
Is that bad?
It's very bad.
What the hell?!
I even sacrificed sleep for study...
Why...
Well, even if you start studying now, you can't expect your grades to go up right away.
You've still got time, so don't worry.
That's easy for you to say.
I'm worried about you.
You'll wear yourself out at this rate.
Shut up! Just leave me alone!
What the... You're just crazy!
This has nothing to do with anything like that!
Stop blurting out whatever comes into your head!
Fine. Do what you like.
I would've done that without you telling me.
What the heck?!
What was that all about?
Am I getting in his way?
I know he's under a lot of stress, but couldn't he have been a little nice?
Koizumi-san!
Oh, Kohori-kun.
Yay! We're on together again today!
What's with that? What happened?!
Oh. I cut myself just now when I was sharpening the knives.
I was wondering what to do about it...
There.
Thanks so much.
I break glasses and cut my hands all the time,
...so I've had to use the first aid kit a lot.
Old lady Matsumara helped me at first,
...but I kept getting hurt, so she told me I should deal with it myself.
She'll get angry if she hears you calling her an old lady.
Crap! She's not here, is she?
You're pretty funny, Koizumi-san.
You're really funny and kind.
You're a great person.
Ah, no, no...
Seriously.
I've been working here for six months, but this is the first time I've met someone like you.
Even in the kitchen, you're famous.
We can alway hear you shouting from outside.
Like, "Whoops!" or, "I'm so sorry!"
Oh no!
I get yelled at by old lady Matsumara for shouting loudly like that too...
Wait. I called her "old lady" again.
Man! She's definitely not around, right? Right?
You're so funny! My stomach hurts from laughing!
Well, I'm feeling better now, at any rate.
The weather forecast was right.
I was right to bring my umbrella.
You've still got time, so don't worry.
This way I can at least walk you halfway home.
She... probably didn't bring an umbrella.
Matsumara-san, is everything on our menu available to go?
Yes.
And if you don't memorize the entire menu tonight, I'm not letting you go home.
Well, there sure is a lot of text... I'm getting sleepy just looking at it.
You make mistakes because you don't know the menu!
I've memorized all of the noodle dishes perfectly!
Of course you have. We only have two.
Right. So all of these menu items can also be to go...
Maybe I should get something for Otani to have for dinner...
I'm leaving now.
Right. Good work.
Can't be helped. Can't be helped. Can't be helped.
Koizumi-san? Why are you sleeping here?
Koizumi-san?
Hey!
If I bring him dinner, Otani will probably be surprised.
Otani...
What...?
That was, uhh... S-S-Sorry!
I w-wasn't... th-that... uh... th-this...
I wasn't kissing you...
Otani! Wait!
It's not what you think, Otani. Please listen!
So that was who Nobu-chan was talking about?
Midget fetishist!
It's not like that!
Um, Otani...
I'm studying. Please be quiet.
Morning.
What's going on?
She cheated on me with that midget she works with.
I told you, you got it all wrong!
How am I wrong?!
I saw it clearly. He definitely kissed you.
That...
That was...
I had no idea...
So you only wanted me for my body?
So it doesn't matter who it is, as long as he's short?
Pervert!
Like hell!
Who would deliberately look for a boyfriend shorter then herself?
That's so uncool!
Uncool? You're calling me uncool?!
I don't believe it.
No matter how busy Otani was with his exams...
I never thought you would two-time him!
No...
I didn't think you were like, Risa!
I'm so disappointed.
Pervert!
Will you just listen to me?!
You fell asleep?
I'm telling you, there's absolutely nothing going on.
That's what you say, but he went and did something like that...
Who knows what he thinks?
I don't know, even if you ask me.
Did he say anything?
Not really.
So ask!
But we'd already finished work...
And if I'd stayed to chat, I would've been yelled at.
Idiot.
Wait. Honestly, I'm not two-timing you.
Can I believe you?
Of course.
Then tell that shorty.
Tell him what?
Next time he tries to lay a hand on you,
...I'll give him a hook so hard his nose will be crooked.
Maybe you shouldn't punch him in the nose...
I'm serious. I'll really do it.
I should've hit him when I had the chance.
Seeing him this upset over me makes me kind of happy.
This is no laughing matter, idiot.
I'm sorry about yesterday!
It was a moment of weakness, and by the time I realized...
That was your boyfriend, right? I'm so sorry!
Kohori-kun...
It's no big deal. Really.
You're not mad?
Not really. I was asleep anyway, so I don't remember a thing.
Thank goodness.
What is it?
Are you busy this Sunday?
There's an Umibouzu event.
Umibouzu... Umibouzu... Umibouzu...
Really? What kind of event?
It's a radio event. Only fifty people get to go.
Wow! And you won?
Yes! And I'd like to invite you. Is that okay?
Even if it's just this once...
I'd really like to go with you, Koizumi-san.
I won't do anything that will make trouble for you!
You don't want to come?
Wh-What should I do?
Can I go? Taking everything into consideration it's obvious that I shouldn't...
Even if I'm not interested in him, going to a concert with him after what happened is...
There's no excuse this time.
I can't.
No way. No way.
No way! No way! No way!
So... it's a "no," then?
I'll come.
Yay!
Yay, yay, yay!
I'm the world's biggest idiot!
I couldn't say no to him!
But it's not cheating. We're just going to a concert.
I'll hurry there and then hurry on home once it's finished.
Thank you, baby!
See you again at Osaka Castle Hall next year!
Okay. That ends our broadcast of the Umibouzu concert.
She was at work, so she'll definitely be happy when I give this to her.
It was an invite-only concert, after all. A once in a lifetime thing!
That was great!
That was my first time seeing Umibouzu perform before such a small audience.
Me too, me too!
Thank you for inviting me to such a great event.
I'm glad I finally asked you out. I'm so happy!
Why is that?
Koizumi-san!
Actually, I...
Actually, I... towards you...
It appeared!
What are you doing?
Otani...
Don't laugh! I'm asking you what you're doing!
I...
It's not what you think!
I was the one who pressured her into going to the Umibouzu concert with me.
Koizumi-san didn't do anything wrong!
Kohori-kun...
So the two of you went to a concert together?
It's not like that. I was the one who really wanted to go to the concert.
I'm the one who's in the wrong, so if you really want to break someone's nose, break mine.
Otani...
Whatever. I don't care anymore.
How stupid...
I'm breaking up with you.
I can't go out with someone like you anymore!
Otani...
Don't say you're going to break up with me.
Do what you want with that midget, Koizumi.
What do you mean, "midget"? He's taller than you.
Shut your mouth!
Lovely Complex ~ Love Com.
Next: Many Future Paths!! The Circumstances We All Bear.
Many Future Paths!!
The Circumstances We All Bear.
Be sure to watch!