Many Future Paths!!
The Circumstances Everyone Bears
I'm breaking up with you.
I can't go out with someone like you anymore!
Breaking up...
Who is?
I am?
Otani and I are breaking up?
Stuff like that is the very reason Otani is fed up with you!
Honestly, what the heck were thinking leaving your boyfriend behind,
It wasn't like that...
What? Was my account inaccurate?
No...
Nobu-chan!
What should I do?
I don't care. You reap what you sow.
Figure it out yourself.
I guess you're right.
It'll be all right Risa-chan.
If you keep apologizing, I'm sure he'll forgive you.
I didn't mean to cheat on him, but...
That really was the wrong thing to do.
There should be a limit to my stupidity.
Otani!
Otani, I'm sorry.
What for?
I'm sorry for going out with that other guy.
I'm not going to do anything that stupid ever again.
It's fine.
You can go out as much as you want.
It's got nothing to do with me.
Hey! Wait!
Don't say that!
What's your problem?!
I'm really sorry!
Please don't break up with me!
Shut up! A man never goes back on his word.
Don't say that.
There's no need to act all macho now!
This only happened because you did something you shouldn't have, right?
That's why I'm apologizing!
There are things that can be fixed with an apology, and things that can't.
Then what do you want me to do?
Do whatever you want.
You're a stranger to me from now on.
Otani!
Wait, Otani!
No way...
This can't be happening...
This is bad.
The end.
I can't believe it.
This can't be happening...
This is all a dream, right?
This is just a bad dream.
It's been a while since that last happened...
Ouch.
This isn't a dream.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'll help out.
Thank you.
I guess it's really over, huh?
Koizumi, I'm sorry I said such cruel things.
What's that?
The whispering of your heart.
Is that what you asked me to come here for?!
I'm going home! I'm busy.
So what are you planning to do?
About what?
You're really going to break up?
Of course.
For how long?
What do you mean, for how long?
For good!
FOLEVER!
Wrong.
Forever.
The future doesn't look good.
That's why I'm breaking up with her.
I worry about her so much that I can't concentrate on my studies.
Even if you break up, won't you still worry about her?
Not at all! I don't care anymore!
I'm totally relaxed!
Is that so...
I didn't think he was that stubborn.
It can't be helped. It was all my fault.
Besides, this is an important time for him.
I shouldn't bother him anymore.
Don't tell me you're just going to leave it like this?
Sorry for worrying you.
What are you saying?
You're the one who helped me with the Hokkaido problem.
I want to help you too.
Thanks, but it's okay. Thing are already over between us.
Risa!
I forgot to give this to him.
I took the time to make it, so it's still okay to give it to him, right?
Otani, do your best.
Hey, what's the matter?
A-chan, here.
Otani Atsushi
Otani Atsushi-sama, I support you in your test efforts.
Koizumi Risa.
Oh, it's from Risa-chan!
Don't just open it!
How nice! It looks really warm.
Put it on, A-chan.
Do your best
Otani
Wow! How cute!
PASS
OTANI FOR LIFE
Recycled, huh?
Risa-chan sure is a nice girl.
But why didn't she come in?
I wonder if Otani accepted my support package?
Koizumi-san, are you getting off now?
Yeah. You're still working, Kohori-kun?
Yeah.
Oh, the boss asked for your availability for December.
Oh, I forgot!
December...
Christmas...
I'm going to be all alone this year...
Koizumi-san, do you want to come in to work on Christmas Eve?
We're all going to get together and have a party after we close.
Would you like to come too, Koizumi-san?
Everyone is?
Yeah.
Matsubara-san will be there too.
I heard that the old lady got really drunk last year and went completely wild.
No way! Are you serious?!
Don't you want to see that?
Kohori-kun?
What's this about "the old lady"?
Uh... nothing at all!
I'm taking out the trash!
Keep up the good work!
If you're looking for Koizumi-san, she already left.
I was just on my way home from prep school.
Of course you are.
You guys already broke up, after all...
You really are short. How tall are you?
I'm 158 cm.
Huh? No way! I'm 2 cm shorter than you?
Oww! What did you do that for?!
Don't play dumb with me. This is all your fault!
Attacking Koizumi while she was asleep...
It was only because she looked so beautiful while she was sleeping...
Good lord! Don't say something so embarrassing out loud!
It's not embarrassing! It's true!
Shut up! Cram it, you midget!
I'm 2 cm taller than you, aren't I?!
So what?! And besides, just what do you want with Koizumi?!
I like her.
I'm not going to hold back anymore.
I wonder what he did with the coat?
Well, it doesn't matter.
As long as he's doing his best.
A Christmas without Otani...
I'm Koizumi Risa, and I'll be singing an Umibouzu song!
Can't be helped. Can't be helped. Can't be helped.
I'm okay.
I'm going to be fine.
See? I'm having fun.
This is where Otani would usually break in and interject.
He'd always make a silly face and shout "Yeah!" right around here.
I want to see him...
I really want to see him.
A-chan, want some Christmas cake?
You look really tired.
You should take a break once in a while, you know.
It is Christmas, after all. Why don't you spend it with Risa-chan?
You think?
Yeah.
I saw her near the station not long ago.
She was with a boy around your height.
I'm not going to hold back anymore.
Koizumi-san!
A-chan!
I thought I could go on being normal without Otani,
...but I just can't!
I'm just...
That's dangerous!
That looked painful.
Is she all right?
Oww...
I'm just no good without Otani.
Otani... Why?
You sure fall over a lot for someone with such a big body.
That coat...
Yeah...
I'm not too sure about the recycled aspect of it, but thanks.
Once you finish with your exams, I'm going to ask you out again.
I'm persistent, you know.
Even if you dump me, or say you're breaking up with me, I'm not going to give up.
So just focus on the entrance exams for now.
O-Otani...
Sorry.
Forget that I said we'd break up.
I take it back.
But... your exams...
Oh no. This is bad.
What?
I...
I seem to like you more than I thought.
No way...
Don't make weird noises.
If you're going to say something that nice to me,
...I don't mind if we break up a hundred times.
Otani...
What is it?
Everyone is staring at us.
I know that!
Your face might be hidden, but everyone can see mine.
Idiot. I've got "do your best" written on my back, don't I?
You really should do your best...
Let's make a run for it.
1... 2...
Oh... I didn't get you a Christmas present.
But you already gave me something.
Huh? I didn't give you anything.
It was something wonderful.
I seem to like you more than I thought.
That was the best present ever.
I don't need anything else.
And so, we overcame that unprecedented crisis and entered the new year.
This is bad!
It's New Years Day and we're already late!
I only slept in because you called and woke me up at some odd hour!
You'd be sad if I hadn't, though.
Who says?!
You guys are both late, as always.
Okay everyone, the lovey-dovey couple is here.
Congratulations on getting back together.
I thought this was my chance...
I'm going to pray for them to break up again.
Haruka-senpai is being petty as always...
Otani and the others started seriously getting into pre-exam study,
...and Nobu-chan and I prayed for them from the sidelines.
Time to hit the sales!
Nobu-chan, this'll go really well with that skirt you bought last time.
Oh, this is great!
Everyone else is working so hard.
Is it okay for us to be doing stuff like this?
Not "us." You're the only one who still hasn't decided on any future plans.
What course are you going to take at technical college?
Well, there are so many...
Say, if Otani is going to be a teacher,
...how about I become a kindergarten teacher?
You'll need to take an exam to get into a college specializing in early childhood education.
You're kidding!
Say, what about going into fashion design?
You've got a good sense of style.
Well, I do like looking nice... but this and that are...
Ah, darling, I'm on my way now.
Sure. See you.
Chiharu-chan?
Suzuki-kun?
Suzuki-kun failed the Center Exam?
Then you and Chiharu-chan won't be able to go to the same school!
I was sick the day of the exam.
Are you all right?
I'm fine. I... I'm...
He took too much cold medicine, and couldn't remember anything from about halfway through.
So... that means...
We can't go to the same school.
I'm sorry for breaking my promise.
Promise?
Wait! Suzuki-kun!
Leave him alone for now.
What was the promise?
Well, last year we decided to visit a university,
...and went to their festival.
Suzuki-kun, where are you?
Oh, what a cute girl.
Wanna come have some fun with us?
What year are you in?
Umm... I'm still a high school senior.
So are you going to apply here next year?
It'd be great having a cute girl like you come to our school.
Tanaka-san!
Suzuki-kun!
What? She's already got a guy?
Too bad.
College is scary.
Lots and lots of guys came and...
Tanaka-san...
So many... There were so many...
Who... Who am I?
You'll be all right.
I'll always be by your side, Tanaka-san.
Suzuki-kun...
So that's what happened.
What do you think I should do?
Chiharu-chan...
Suzuki-kun...
I'm going to go to whichever school you go to, so do your best, okay?
I know, I know...
What?
Don't you get it?
Get what?
So you're going to give up on your first-choice school?
Yes. I want to be with you, Suzuki-kun.
I'm not confident.
Even if you lower yourself to my level and change your first choice university,
...I don't know if I can get in anywhere.
What are you saying, Suzuki-kun?!
When Chiharu-chan is willing to...
Why? Why would you say such a thing?
I couldn't keep my promise.
I'm sure there are other guys who could protect you at college in my place.
T-Tanaka-san!
Chi-Chiharu-chan that's dangerou—
Be quiet!
Yes!
I don't want to go to the same school just so you can protect me!
I want to be with you!
Tanaka-san...
And yet, you say I can replace you...
Chiharu-chan!
Saying you're not confident...
Suzuki-kun, you're an idiot!
Ch-Chiharu-chan...
She got pretty angry, huh?
She was really upset.
What are you going to do?
What do you mean?
Why does it have to be like this?
Can't you two just go to the same school?
It's for her own good, and for my good too.
Oh, I see it. That book.
Thank you.
There's a literature professor who Tanaka-san really respects...
...teaching at that university.
So to give up her first choice school for my sake...
I think when she works out what she really wants to do in the future,
...she'll regret not going there.
I see.
I don't want that to happen.
So you said those things deliberately, Suzuki-kun?
Why'd you try to act cool like that?
That's completely the wrong way to show her you care about her.
Yeah! Why not just tell her the truth?
She would've been much happier that way.
Hurry up and go.
Up here!
I'm sorry.
You were being considerate of me to that extent...
I never realized.
Tanaka-san...
Yes?
I'm going to keep studying, and get into the same school as you next year,
...so please wait for me until then.
Of course.
Good for you, Chiharu-chan, Suzuki-kun.
What's wrong? You've been sighing for a while now.
What's the meaning of life?
What was that?!
Well I'm the only one who hasn't decided on anything!
Koizumi...
After watching those two today, I realized I really need to decide now,
...so that when I work out what I really want to do in the future, I won't have any regrets.
That's right. Work that brain of yours.
You'll need to get yours into gear too for your exam prep.
So time passed quickly,
...and now the entrance exams are already tomorrow.
No good! What the heck am I thinking?!
I'm home.
Get out!
Wh-What?
This house has been infected by a level five virus.
Level...
What the heck is going on?! Open up!
It's influenza.
It's not just me.
Your father and sister are both feverish and sick, too.
This house is under quarantine.
Quarantine?
But what about me?!
I have an exam tomorrow!
Here.
Hurry. Take that and flee!
Go and stay at a healthy friend's house for the night.
This is crazy!
Otani, I'm praying for you.
Hey, wait... I have an exam tomorrow.
Why is this happening to me?
You've got to be kidding!
Do your best in the exams!
But it's already time for graduation!
Koizumi, this isn't the time to cry.
We're going to be late for graduation!
Lovely Complex ~ Love Com.
Final episode: Together Forever!!
Together Forever!!
Be sure to watch.