And why are you crying?
Because you are.
I-I cleaned it, don't worry.
It's not dirty.
I won't curse you.
I never thought you would.
Quit crying; it's annoying!
Sawako-chan, what happened with Kazehaya earlier?
I just thought that I like him.
Are you going to go out with him?
Did you tell him that you like him?
Did he tell you?
Him? Me?
No way.
Really? You're not going out with him?
Of course not.
Who knows! Who knows what could have happened in that situation.
You might have said “yes” in the heat of the moment.
Kurumi-chan, do you think it's possible for Kazehaya-kun to fall for me?
I didn't even have anyone to talk to until just recently.
Kazehaya doesn't care about that sort of thing.
He's nice, and he's caring,
and he makes his own judgments.
When he smiles, you feel relieved and smile back.
I know.
And he gets angry when he needs to.
Yeah.
He's sort of short-tempered, and he hates anything that's wrong.
He's popular with both the guys and girls.
He's honest...
and cool...
and cute—
Why am I here with you?
I'm happy.
This is the first time I've talked to anyone like this.
Kurumi-chan accepts me for who I am, even after everything she said.
Kurumi-chan is like Kazehaya-kun.
It was my chance.
We're in high school, and everyone's cheering me on.
I could have made him notice me.
It was my chance.
But now it's too late.
Kazehaya-kun thinks I like Arai Pin.
Anything I say, he's only going to think I'm saying it because I'm embarrassed.
How did that happen?
I miscalculated.
Forget it.
I've always known that Kazehaya doesn't think anything special of me.
It doesn't matter anymore, whether he finds out or gets the wrong idea...
Yes it does.
I didn't want Kazehaya-kun to think I like Sanada-kun.
It's a misunderstanding. He'll understand if you tell him.
You think he'll understand if I tell him the truth?
You're an idiot.
I still wouldn't like it.
I know.
We both like Kazehaya-kun.
We both feel the same way about the same person.
Yet we can't be friends, even though we have the same feelings.
Then what will that make us, Kurumi-chan?
Nothing?
Will we be nothing at all?
Or will we be something else?
Kurumi!
Is your stomach okay?
Yeah, I'm okay now.
You scared me, disappearing all of a sudden.
Sorry.
I'll be at the game tomorrow.
That's good.
Right?
See you tomorrow.
Bye bye.
It's sort of late.
Want to go somewhere?
I'm hungry, aren't you?
Kurumi-chan, let's be in the same group.
Kurumi-chan...
Kurumi...
What, really?
There's no one you like?
But you're so cute.
What a waste.
I'm glad I'm friends with Kurumi.
I know.
We're in the same group, yay.
What? No way.
Miyagawa said he likes Kurumi?
What the hell?
But Miki has always liked him.
Kurumi lent Miyagawa her notes and stuff.
She doesn't like it when a guy likes any girl besides herself.
That's why she acts as if she likes them.
What a bitch.
Kurumi my ass, her name's Ume.
We let her in our group so we could talk to guys.
Let's get in her way if she ever starts to like someone.
She got in our way already, right?
Have you been a little bummed lately?
Not really.
Yeah?
See you tomorrow.
Bye bye.
I don't want to do club work in the rain.
You want to skip?
We can't.
Lame...
Hey, you're still here.
Are you okay?
It's nothing.
Really?
Do you have club work?
Yeah, I just came to pick something up.
I see.
Here it is, I knew it.
Good luck.
Yeah.
Seriously, you okay?
What's wrong?
This person is different.
He's always with the guys.
We're in the same class.
He sees me for who I am.
I'll never tell him.
I'll never tell anyone.
Anyone.
Until Kazehaya likes me...
Kurumizawa.
I didn't know.
So you don't care if Kazehaya finds out?
Kurumizawa.
That you liked Pin.
No!
Sorry, that was uncalled for.
My bad, sorry.
You didn't hear?
What?
What a bitch, acting all nice.
Kazehaya...
What's Sawako-chan like?
Kuronuma's easily misunderstood.
But she always speaks the truth, even when it's risky.
So when Kuronuma says something, I believe her.
Risky?
I don't think she agrees,
but if she always played it safe, Yoshida and Yano might not have trusted her either.
As much as you want to help her, she always does it by herself.
I think she really worked hard.
It's a misunderstanding. He'll understand if you tell him.
What the hell am I saying?
I sound so stuck up.
Later.
Kaze—
Oh,
Cheer up.
If Kazehaya got the wrong idea...
I don't want him to.
No.
No!
Wait.
Wait, Kazehaya.
I don't like Pin.
I like you.
I've always been watching you.
It's you.
Please don't think I like someone else.
Sorry, Kurumizawa.
Sorry.
It's my fault.
There's someone I like.
I can't make myself think of anyone else more than her.
Sorry.
I know.
It's obvious.
Are you at least a little happy that I confessed to you?
Yeah.
Thanks.
Call me by my first name, just once.
Ume.
I guess this old-ass name isn't so bad.
Geez, I wasn't going to tell you.
I totally screwed up my calculations.
Calculations?
It was you that made me screw up the most.
You're never going to meet anyone as cute as I am.
And why would I like that dumbass Pin?
Seriously.
Dammit, I feel better.
Were you always like this?
You don't have a good eye for women, do you?
Bye bye.
I told him.
I wonder if we might have understood each other better if Kurumi-chan and I had liked two different people.
I don't know.
What? Kazehaya?
I knew it.
I see!
Why are you acting like you didn't know?
No reason.
Man.
Hey, what made you realize you like him?
What?
I think...
I think it was Kurumi-chan.
But if she had liked someone else, I might not have known.
Kurumi, huh?
I can't believe how aggressive she is when it comes to guys. I admire her in a sense.
I couldn't do it.
I wonder if I could.
I might become a monster.
Monster?
Who?
Anyway, that's good news, Sawako.
Things are going to get a lot more fun.
I'm glad I said it.
I'm glad I could tell Kurumi-chan too.
And I was glad when she told me.
Morning.
Kurumi-chan?
What's up with those shades?
Why do you care?
Hey, you, what's up with those sunglasses?
Sunglasses are for outside.
You're that kid that likes me.
What, did you cry yourself out of it?
Alright, fine.
Yeah, yeah.
Like someone your own age next time.
With high school kids, you tell them that you like them, and they'll be thinking about you all day.
Because they're dumbasses.
Later.
I wonder...
I'm going to win the rest of the soccer games.
You sure are having fun.
I'm going to win and party like hell.
We lost, huh?
Oh well, right?
Kurumi-chan...
She looks awesome.
Are you talking to them?
We'll wait over there.
I was happy when I fell for him too.
I never said anything when people said nice things about him.
I never told anyone how much I liked him.
I always kept it to myself.
If by any crazy fluke things work out between you two,
I'm never going to congratulate you.
I hate any woman that Kazehaya likes.
We can't be friends, can we?
Friends?
We're rivals.
Rivals.
Rivals!
Dammit, I'm pissed!
How could we lose?
Dammit!
I know, I was pissed too.
What's up with her?
Who knows.
I might have liked her if she'd always been like that.
R-Really?
Since then...
Why?!
We lost every game.
My steak...
Arai-sensei lost his spirit,
and sports day ended.
Okay, let's head home and party at six.
Sixth place!
Not bad.
Party? My first!
I went home and looked it up in the dictionary.
My first rival.
So, since when have you liked him?
What about since his public confession?
Public confession?
Nah, I doubt it, not yet.
I think I had feelings for him by then.
I wonder when I started feeling like this.
Kazehaya, what are you singing next?
I'm taking a break.
I'll sing then.
Where's Kuronuma?
Sawako-chan?
She said she went outside because her face got red.
Okay.
Gee, who made her get red?
Kuronuma?
Hey.
Is she asleep?
Sawako.
Yes?
S-Sleep-talking?
I over thought it.
Sawako.
Kuronuma Sawako, right?
My world had changed that moment.
I'd fallen in love the moment he called my name.
Talking at midnight.
A little chat.
Next episode: Night Talk