I entered middle school when I was twelve.
In ninth grade I applied for Kitahoro High School, since it was nearby.
And then in the spring of my fifteenth year, I met you.
“If only I could be like Kazehaya-kun...
Maybe then something will change for me too.”
Thanks.
You've always been the first step for me.
This year was too different for me.
It'll take too long to describe.
Sorry, I guess that was boring.
I'll try to have a different vibe next year.
You already do, for the better.
You're easier to talk to.
You're fine.
Don't say that...
You're going to ruin the makeup Ayane-chan did for me.
Kuronuma!
Three seconds, wait three seconds.
Three?
You've always had a good vibe.
You were smiling, even before the entrance ceremony.
When you gave me directions.
Then we were in the same class,
but I haven't seen you smile like that since.
I've been wondering what kind of person you were.
I didn't think you'd remember when we first met.
I thought you'd be a good person,
but more than that...
More?
I guess I can assume he thinks I'm a good person.
You changed a lot today too; you scared me.
I-I'm sorry. I didn't mean to scare you.
See, that's not what I meant.
No.
Which is it?
Forget it.
Let's line up to visit the shrine.
It's almost new year.
You already do, for the better.
Maybe I've changed.
You wished you were cute when you met Kurumi, didn't you?
Think about why you want to be cute.
Ayane-chan, there's only one answer to that.
It's too hard to say.
You were cuter than I thought.
I used to want to be more like Kazehaya-kun.
Now I want him to think I'm cute, if only just a little.
Arms...
How long are we doing this for?
Until Joe gets bored of Yano-chin?
I'm going home.
Later, Joe.
Later.
Sweet sake...
Hey, Ryu.
Joe, your down jacket.
Like it? I just bought it.
It's probably full of holes from the sparks.
Later.
Hey, what about the shrine?
He came all the way here.
Go, Chizu.
You didn't really explain why you dragged him around, did you?
Go already.
Sorry, Yano-chin. I'll hook you up with ramen next time.
No, I'll get fat.
It was so expensive.
But now we're alone.
Ryu!
Why'd you ditch us like that?
Sorry, it got lame.
I couldn't put up with it.
No hesitation.
Why don't you be a bit more friendly?
Oh yeah.
Try saying Chi.
Never.
Why?
It'll make you smile.
Whatever happens,
however Kuronuma acts,
even if they bump into someone they know,
Shouta will figure it out.
Well, I guess...
Just let them be.
You're having too much fun.
But I wanted to see them.
Besides, I don't think you need to worry about them.
It looks like they're doing well.
See?
So I'm going to have sweet sake and go home.
No you're not.
You're visiting the shrine with me.
Sweet sake...
Five, four, three, two, one
Happy new year!
Happy new year.
Best regards for the new year.
Y-You too, best regards for the new year.
It's already...
Did you receive a text?
Oh yeah, I did.
Two even.
They're from Chizu-chan and Ayane-chan.
Aren't you going to respond?
Can I?
Of course.
Happy-new-year.
They beat me to texting her.
Oh well.
I'm having fun. Thanks.
Sawako responded.
Happy new year.
Best regards for the new year.
So much of what happened last year were firsts for me.
It's our turn, Kuronuma.
All the things I thought about,
all the things I experienced...
It's all because I met all of you.
It became an unforgettable year.
Thanks.
It's slippery here.
You're right.
Here.
My brother's coming over on New Year's Day.
With his girlfriend.
You don't remember her name yet, do you?
Busted.
Haruka-chan, right?
Seriously.
She's going to be your sister-in-law soon, isn't she?
I'll come over.
Ryu, if something ever happens to you, I'll comfort you.
Yeah, when that happens.
Let's see what our fortunes will be like.
“Very Good.”
Wow.
“All will be as you wish.”
“Beware of your temper; be composed and approach everything with calmness.
Take heed of the advice of others.”
Can I do that, though?
I wonder what I got.
Maybe Fair.
Probably not Very G—
I expected too much.
I think I'm too greedy these days.
Kuronuma, what did you get?
I uh, well...
Ah, bad luck.
The best...
So true.
I heard “Bad” is actually pretty good.
Because it's not too common.
Really?
You're supposed to hang these up on trees, aren't you?
Kuronuma,
have this one.
The "Very Good" you got?
That's, well...
I think I'd absorb your good fortune.
Go ahead.
I've always had good luck.
Besides, well...
I want to give it to you.
It's sort of a shabby birthday present, but...
T-Thanks.
Hesitation?
Do I have any?
Now that I think of it, I don't know why I wasn't sure I liked him.
How did I see him only with admiration all that time?
Wow, I spent New Year's Eve with Ayane.
Finally found you.
You said you'd be at the bonfire.
I'm sorry.
Sorry about my idiot of a son.
No, no.
We're going home, now.
Ayane!
All these holes in your jacket.
You're not getting any new year's allowance.
Oh come on, Mom.
Thank god!
Dear God, please erase the fact that I spent New Year's Eve with Joe.
That's all I ask for.
They're getting along well.
I guess I won't need to get my fortune then.
But man, they really look like a normal couple when they're like that.
Come on.
Enough, already.
I said no.
Why? Come on. Let's go drink a little.
So many idiots.
If only Tohru were here.
He'd score with some totally random pick-up.
That bastard says he's going to his girlfriend's for the new year.
Marriage my ass!
Don't look him in the face.
Hey, are you here alone?
We finally meet!
Don't people tell you you're cute?
You shall not...
Give me your e-mail address.
Anything to say about guys with glasses?
...see success!
See you!
Let's be together in our next lives!
Tha—
What, you think you're good enough to get picked up?
Are you that idiot from earlier?
Why are you following me?
I'm not interested in brats.
Dammit, stop getting led on.
Why would I?
I'm going home.
I'm going home too.
You're embarrassing me, go away.
Past this hill...
...is the usual way to school.
And...
This is where I first met you.
What will this year be like?
I just want to know if it's for eternity or not
I wish I could live like this forever, but...
I want to be like those paper airplanes filling the sky
That's good.
Yeah, it's good.
Look, you see that empty house?
and I will find only one
They're there too?
What is?
I'm not telling you.
Thank you, love grows with being needed
What? What's there?
Hey, don't leave me here!
Hey, Kurumi, did you make a wish?
If only I could smile and enjoy the distance between us
What did you write?
I'm not telling you.
Come on, tell me.
Just a little bit.
Okay, just a little.
I want to tell you the thoughts he accumulated
This?
Chips?
Sounds good.
Okay.
What can I do in a world like that where nobody notices me?
Happy New Year.
What are you up to?
Spending the new year together.
Us too.
Hey, why don't we hang out together?
You look like a pervert.
I just want to know if it's for eternity or not
I wish I could live like this forever, but...
Isn't Sawako coming home yet?
I want to be like those paper airplanes filling the sky
Come on, Dad.
Here, it's sweet.
I'm about to cry
It's sweet.
One more.
If the two of us accepted each other more
Let's go.
Look at me just a little bit
Flower of love blowing in the wind
See you.
Thanks.
I had fun. Really.
Me too.
See you.
Be safe.
I wonder if I can change my temper.
I don't think I can.
“Relationships — Offer your love. Happiness awaits.”
“Classmate,”
“Guy next to me in class”—but not my friend.
He's more distant than a friend, and I want him to be more than a friend.
“Someone I like.”