Sawako, your bath's ready.
Okay.
Hey, Sawako, how's school been lately?
I-It's fun.
She always says it's fun, but she really looks like she's gleeful this time.
Gleeful...
Maybe she's in love.
Sawako... my Sawako!
Geez, Dad, what are you doing?!
I'm so happy.
I'm about to forget what I used to be like.
...to myself.
I don't know what he meant, but I'm happy.
I wonder if I'm using up my lifetime's supply of happiness right now.
But I'm happy anyway.
What? No way.
Yoshida? The thin-eyed girl?
Yeah.
She used to be a real problem in middle school.
She made her teacher cry and beat up all the guys in her class.
I was a lot worse than that.
And my eyes aren't that  thin.
Yano-san, right?
She does look like it.
A hundred guys in middle school... that's just crazy.
Are you saying there are a hundred guys that could satisfy me?
Hook me up.
I'll let you know what they're like.
Dammit, my legend was way grander than that.
It's just a rumor.
And my eyes aren't that thin.
They are  thinner than you think, though.
Geez.
Lies. All lies.
Even the rumors about Sadako.
What do you think?
I'm asking you who told you that.
Who told you?
Sadako.
Everyone's saying so,
that she's using Kazehaya and you two to up her status.
Bullshit.
You wanna ask just to be sure?
So that ramen...
Morning, Yano-san, Yoshida-san.
Morning, Sadako.
So I beat up all the guys in my class huh?
And I'm a slut, and I did a hundred guys in middle school.
Really?
You're both so amazing.
Pure!
Yoshida-san, if it's okay with you...
What's this?
It's a summary for the midterm.
I made it last night.
I was hoping you would have a use for it.
Pure white!
I'll be happy to use it.
Yano-san?
I was going to rent some horror story videos.
Could you please give me some recommendations?
Pure white!
Hey, Yoshida,
Can I copy that?
Me too. I'll give you some scrubs.
Me too.
Can they?
Of course.
I really like being helpful.
Triple pure white!
Ryu.
Morning, Sanada-kun.
Morning.
Kazehaya-kun's late.
You don't believe me, do you?
I seriously saw him last night.
Little old man.
Pin, I really want to go to class.
I was drinking last night…
Lots of them. Running around my glass.
Round and round, round and round.
And then one by one they went into my glass!
Pin!
I told you I'm late!
Those are some tough bastards.
I'm leaving.
So how's that Kuronuma girl?
What about her?
All sorts of weird stuff has been happening since I looked into her eyes.
You sit next to her, you must know about her.
Is she cursed or—
I'll believe what I see.
The Kuronuma I see is pure-hearted and good.
You... are you going out with her?
W-What are you getting all red about?
Y-You're not really—
Shut up!
I've heard enough from you!
I'm leaving.
S-Seriously?
He really has a type, doesn't he?
Morning.
M-Morning.
You're late.
Pin was talking to me about little old men.
What the hell?
No idea.
His bangs are standing.
She's normal, I think?
After I talked about having her to myself.
His bangs... I want to see his bangs again.
Are you going out with her?
Shit, I can't look at her anymore.
His bangs... too bad.
In my happiness, my heart's racing faster day by day.
I wonder what everyone else is thinking.
Do they like being with me?
I hope they do.
I always thought it was normal not to have anyone around me.
I never even thought about it.
Ever since that day, I've been filled with feelings that I'd never known before.
I want to have them close to me.
They're like presents that I've received for the first time.
Yano-san, Yoshida-san.
Hey...
There's a rumor going around lately.
Sounds like it.
It keeps getting worse.
They're saying you beat an elderly man to a pulp.
I did help up an old guy after he fell.
And that Yano-san is involved in paid dating.
Bullshit!
We don't believe it, of course.
But apparently that rumor's coming from Kuronuma-san.
No way!
Impossible!
We're sort of worried... why would there be such a rumor?
Isn't it too much?
Such a horrible rumor.
Can you believe it?
I think people are even more afraid of me lately.
Sadako,
Shino-chan.
Over here.
There are some serious rumors going around these days.
Shino-chan heard the rumors about the psychic aura and curses and all that too.
I don't think misunderstandings go away that easily.
Misunderstandings?
I see.
Obviously, Sadako would never spread rumors about her friends.
But it doesn't bother me as much as it used to.
Everyone around me is so kind.
Seems like you've loosened up, Sadako.
Why is everyone talking about Sadako?
I guess the three of us are notorious.
I can understand the rumors about us,
but the rumors about Sadako are different from the usual.
But I'm glad you made some friends.
Yano-san and Yoshida-san, was it?
They aren't friends.
Oh, really?
Wait, go on...
Perfect.
Come here.
They're not friends?
No.
Friendship is like what's between Yano-san and Yoshida-san, right?
I really get the sense that they care for each other.
So I don't think I deserve to be called a friend yet.
But I care for the two of them.
So I really hope I'll be able to call them friends someday.
Top secret practice menu?
Give it to Ryu.
Dammit!
Ow.
Everyone's pissing me off!
Calm down, Chizu.
They're not friends.
We haven't asked her what she meant by that.
To be honest, we might not be friends with her per se.
That's true.
Huh?
What's wrong with them?
They're not laughing like usual.
Sadako, can you come sit here?
They're sort of bummed.
I want to talk about something important.
Don't lie, okay?
I—we both like you.
What do you think?
Do you like us?
L-Like you?
More like—
I got it.
Sadako,
sorry to trouble you.
Did they understand? With so little?
Is that how it works?
We like you.
I should be happy.
But Yano-san and Yoshida-san don't look happy.
I don't feel happy either.
I wonder if there's something I can do to cheer them up.
So she got all cocky and got Yano and Yoshida to back her up.
To back her up?
She's even using Kazehaya.
Even Kazehaya-kun?
That's amazing.
Seriously?
That  Sadako?
First I was Sadako, now I'm a gang leader!
Those black rumors about Yano and Yoshida are really something though.
Black rumors?
Backing me up?
That's why they were down.
They were hurt.
It's Sadako's fault.
Yup.
It's because she's wandering around.
Kazehaya's going to become seriously worthless too, if he keeps getting followed around by Sadako.
My fault?
Yano-san and Yoshida-san are just kind.
They're approaching me in kindness.
Yet...
It's because she's wandering around.
Am I hurting people by being around?
Am I going to hurt Kazehaya-kun the way I hurt Yano-san and Yoshida-san?
Did you hear the story about the little old men?
I've seen them before.
Yeah, I've seen them too.
No way.
Yeah.
They looked just like Zen.
You're shitting me.
I am.
Should I not be around?
Can I not be around?
What the hell, you look like you cried yourself to sleep.
You look like you stayed up all night.
Yano-chin,
do you think Sadako spread those rumors?
Honestly, I don't know anymore.
Especially after what she said yesterday.
Either way, she doesn't like us.
You asked if she liked us, after all.
She wouldn't have been the one to spread rumors about us if she said she did like us.
That's what you hoped, right?
I totally believed she wouldn't spread rumors about us.
But now I'm worried; what if she did?
I want to believe that she wouldn't spread rumors.
I hate myself for thinking that.
Morning.
Their eyes are red.
I'm sorry.
I upset you, didn't I?
What's that about?
I'll be going.
Sadako!
She was apologizing.
What does she mean, she upset us?
No way, did she really spread those rumors?
Stop it, please!
I don't like it either.
Maybe it's about yesterday.
Maybe she's sorry that she doesn't like us.
Either way, this sucks.
It does.
Maybe I was being stuck up.
I thought I was a pretty big part of her life.
I totally thought she liked me too.
They're more hurt than I thought they were.
I want to find the people spreading the rumors and set the record straight.
Yano-san and Yoshida-san aren't backing me up.
I want to tell them that they're just really kind.
I know how to fix misunderstandings.
But I can't find them.
I want them to be happy and laughing again.
Shoot.
It's the other two that want to cry.
Kuronuma.
Wait.
Did I do something?
I have to go somewhere.
Were you crying earlier?
It looks like you're avoiding me.
Did I do something to hurt you? To make you hate me?
Tell me.
Nothing, you didn't do anything.
But...
No matter what happens, I would never hate you.
No matter what happens. Never.
Kuronuma.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Kazehaya-kun.
He never avoided me, no matter what happened.
But I cause him trouble.
I cause him trouble.
But I don't want to avoid him.
I need to stay away from him.
But I want to stay by him.
Is it right to avoid him? Is it wrong?
I don't know.
What should I do?
The people I care for.
What I can do right now...
Next episode: Decisions