Sawako!
Good morning!
It's mid-December.
Ow.
I'm glad.
Finals are over, and all that's left is the closing ceremony.
I'm glad for Chizu.
She looks better, now that she had a chance to meet Tohru.
I guess it's thanks to Ryu for calling him.
I later learned that Chizu-chan reluctantly had Ryu comfort her.
Good, exams are over too.
Good, good.
Not good!
This'll mean review sessions!
Oh well, you have an excuse this time.
Sawako even made me personalized study notes.
S-Sorry I wasn't helpful.
Why me?
Why you?
Don't know.
Don't the review sessions end before Christmas?
Christmas?
Oh, that festivity where couples incessantly show off their love for each other?
The party girl's being pissy.
There's no school on Christmas Eve.
How about all of us single people get
together to do something for Christmas?
We were going to meet up with Ryu and Joe.
Right?
Yeah.
Let's trade gifts and eat something good.
Eat?
It'll be a good way to chill out after reviews too.
Thank you, Kazehaya!
You're going to bring some chicks too, right?
Truth or dare, yay!
Denied.
C-Christmas!
With everyone...
Who's eligible to participate?
Like I said, everyone.
Is Sadako praying?
Everyone.
You're bored this Christmas as well, aren't you?
Really bored.
Everyone means everyone, Kuronuma.
Everyone.
This might be the first and last time I'll be able to spend Christmas with you and Chizu.
I probably can't next year.
Who knows, I might not either.
I'm part of everyone too.
I'll put this up like always.
Write your name down if you're coming.
I can.
Thanks.
No problem.
I can go.
I can write my name down here.
I've always wanted to.
I think I'm doing something for Christmas at home too.
I should ask my parents.
You haven't signed up yet?
No.
Aren't you coming?
I have to ask my parents.
Let's go.
I want to.
Christmas with someone other than family.
Christmas with my friends.
My first Christmas with Kazehaya-kun.
An apron for Chizu-chan,
and coasters for Ayane-chan.
I made them as Christmas gifts.
A belly warmer for Dad, slippers for Mom.
First I have to ask if I can go, though.
For Kazehaya-kun...
No, no.
That'd be way too scary.
A hand-made scarf.
Besides, even if I knit one,
I don't think I could give it to him.
I definitely couldn't.
Maybe I can just make one.
Just make one.
Sawako, Dad's home.
Okay.
Let's try asking if I can go to the Christmas party.
Dad, welcome home.
Hey, about Christmas...
Oh, right, right, Sawako.
You haven't told Santa what you want for Christmas this year, have you?
Better hurry, or you'll miss his deadline!
Umm, a notebook and pencil leads.
I could buy that myself.
Santa said he's going to spend a lot this year.
A-An ergonomic mechanical pencil, then. Please.
Why are you telling me?
You gotta write it down and hang it up.
What should I do?
Sawako's chicken last year was delicious.
Not that I'm complaining about your cooking, Mom.
Dad's totally revved up.
I'll help all day, from early in the morning on.
Um...
What, Sawako?
Cake, huh?
I'll leave that to you. Surprise me!
Santa shows up every year, you're such a good girl.
I can't.
Let's go.
Hey, Dad, Mom...
You know, you were supposed to be born on the 24th.
We were worried because your mother didn't go into labor.
Look at her now, all big and healthy.
Those were the days.
You ended up being born on New Year's Eve,
but to us, you're a Christmas present.
Stop it Dad, you're crying.
Dad.
What is it?
You were about to say something.
No, nothing.
I can't ask them.
You're not going?
My dad's really looking forward to it.
Come on.
Can't you come just for a little bit?
We start early in the morning and go on all day.
That's pretty crazy.
So it's a bit early, but...
An apron!
I'm going to wear it when I help at Ryu's.
And coasters for you.
They're so cute.
Did you make them yourself?
Yes.
Maybe I shouldn't have.
Impressive.
Thanks.
Thanks, I'm going to use it.
They liked it.
What's that?
Oh, this?
I got it from Sawako.
Like it?
Christmas gifts.
Really?
Nice.
I wonder if he'll take it.
Nah, no way.
That's way too much.
Are you sure you shouldn't have given them on Christmas though?
Ah, Sawako can't make it.
Sawako's dad is really hyped up about Christmas.
Really?
Let's go.
I want to.
Yeah.
Oh.
Kazehaya.
Yo.
We got a reservation for the Christmas party.
Come here.
Thanks.
Sawako.
Let's do it on a different day next year.
Yeah.
We could do it on the 25th.
Have fun.
Too bad, they invited me too.
Next year.
And on December 24th, Christmas Eve...
Done.
I can't give it to him, but I'm sort of proud.
I'll hide Mom and Dad's gifts so that I can surprise them.
Sawako, Dad, are you awake yet?
Yes.
So cold.
The water's ready.
It looks good on you.
It does, right?
It's perfect.
Thanks for the Christmas present, Sawako.
You remembered I said my head's cold.
You have a wide forehead.
It's so warm.
I've always wanted something like this.
Thanks, Sawako. Merry Christmas.
I'm glad you like it.
I was going to give it to you later.
Here, Mom.
I couldn't have given it to him anyway.
It's better that someone makes use of it.
He's so happy too.
I wonder if they're all having fun about now.
What's up, Sawako?
Having fun?
Yeah.
Is the phone ringing?
I'll get it.
Hello?
I can't hear anything.
Chizu-chan.
Sawako?
Dude, shut up.
I was wondering how you're doing.
It's sort of boring without you.
Talk to Yano-chin.
Here, Yano-chin.
Hello? Sawako?
Ayane-chan.
You're not lonely, are you?
I was sort of worried.
Too bad you couldn't come, not even for a little bit.
Here's your Christmas present, though.
Huh, what?
Kuronuma?
Is it you?
It's you, right?
I want to go.
Oh no.
I can't speak.
Sawako, I'll say hi. Pass me the phone.
Hello?
Sawako's mother speaking.
Nice to speak to you again.
Good evening.
Sounds fun over there.
Sawako, come here.
It's fun here.
But...
It'd be even more fun with Kuronuma-san here.
Dad, can I go for a little bit?
It'll be a lot more fun with Kuronuma here.
Open it.
It's from Santa—well, from me.
Go ahead.
Y-You could have said so earlier.
I-I'll call if it gets late. Take it.
I charged it.
Thanks, Dad.
Did Sawako leave?
Finally, the day's come!
This is just the first jab of round one, Dad.
I hope I can make it.
Let's get going then.
Bet there'll be less people next year.
Cheers!
I might not make it.
Sawako.
But I still want to go.
Let's go for karaoke next.
Who's in?
Let's go, Kazehaya.
I want to go!
I thought just maybe...
You're here.
The Christmas party and the presents stuff is over already,
but here, for you.
Might not be useful, though.
Hey...
I don't even know how to use it yet.
Give me.
Sent.
The first name on my first phone is Kazehaya-kun.
Being sad, not making it on time...
Oh yeah, my present for you...
What, really?
A neck warmer?
The small miracles, the little mistakes...
It's a b-belly wa—
It's all a merry Christmas.
The echoes of my ringtone
and a small taste of regret.
Next episode: The Two of Us