R-Rumors?
The bad ones about you two?
Yeah, those.
And the one about me being the one who spread those rumors?
That too.
And the one about me being a secret school gang leader?
School gang leader...?
Sadako: Legend of the Secret School Gang Leader
A-Apparently I had you two backing me up,
and I even had Kazehaya under my control.
Huh?
Seriously?
Seriously, that's awesome.
And to think you used to be “cursed.”
Rebel! Rebel Sawako!
I seriously hate all of them.
But it must be some kind of mistake.
Even if she did spread those rumors...
Wait. In rumorland, these two are backing me up,
but I'm spreading slander about them...
What exactly am I trying to do?
It was probably bullshit.
Basically...
Kurumi's just stupid.
No, Kurumi's not stupid—
She loses track because she's always messing around,
that dumbass.
That's so stupid.
So what were we talking about again?
Shut up already!
What do you expect?!
I'm not the only one spreading rumors.
The Kazehaya fans made up the gang leader rumor. It just stuck.
This wouldn't have been so hard if it all had worked as I'd planned.
K-Kurumi-chan, that's not true, is it?
You might give people the wrong idea, saying that.
But we'll understand if we talk.
You wouldn't do such a—
Wrong idea?
It's not the wrong idea.
The rumors about these two,
and that you started them...
I started all of it.
Not the wrong idea?
Did she just admit it?
Yeah, just a little before you noticed.
W-Why?
You were in the way.
You're in the way, Sawako-chan.
I wished you'd get away from Chizu-chan and everyone else.
Kurumi-chan...
You...
...hated me?
Yeah.
You just noticed?
We're friends now, right, Sawako-chan?
Friends...
I've never thought of you as a friend.
What a bitch!
See, that's what she's like.
Tell her, Sawako!
Come on!
S-Sawako?
S-Say something to her.
I can't take it anymore.
That's it, I'm going crazy.
I'm going to tell her.
Okay, Yano-chin?
Y-Yeah.
Kurumi!
You piss me off with what you did, but whatever.
I don't even want you to apologize.
Say what you want about me,
but don't talk about Yano-chin or Sawako like you know anything about them!
And don't ever make Sawako cry ever again!
I've had it with this rumor stuff.
I feel better now.
I love you man, seriously.
I want to live like you.
Yoshida-san...
And don't take advantage of people either.
What a waste of breath.
There, I said it.
She's not awesome anymore.
It's still not fair, Sawako-chan.
What's wrong with using people?
Everyone takes advantage of me too,
and then they toss me out when they're done.
Why is it wrong for me to use people?
Oh, now she's being defensive.
So you don't intend to change your ways?
Why should I have to?
Yeah? Fine.
You should know that I'm not as simple-minded as Chizu.
You don't care if Kazehaya finds out about this?
I think I'll go tell him right now.
Seriously?
Y-Yano-san—
Go ahead.
Go ahead, tell him.
Okay, I'll do it.
Hey, Chizu, volley-ball's next.
Oh, right.
Come on, Sawako, forget about her.
What?
Go.
You have to tell Kazehaya about me, don't you?
Get him to feel sorry for you again.
C-Chizu-chan! Ayane-chan!
C-Chizu-chan, huh?
She sort of said it earlier too.
Don't tell him.
Go ahead.
I don't know why she'd say such a thing,
but that wasn't really her talking.
Go ahead, tell him.
It couldn't have been.
I don't want you to tell him.
Well I'm not really interested in that stuff, but...
Fine with me, if that's what you want;
but really?
Yeah.
She wouldn't want someone she likes to think bad of her.
Hey, Sawako,
I screwed up. Sorry.
I didn't think you'd be so hurt by this.
Well, I did,
but I had my own motives.
Seriously, what “motives”?
I didn't know she felt that way for my sake.
I-I'm so sorry too.
I'm sorry I got you into this.
We seriously don't think anything of the rumors.
But what about the rumors about you?
Oh, that's, whatever.
I'm used to it, I guess.
Oh.
Besides,
those rumors weren't all bad.
I have friends.
I have Chizu-chan and Ayane-chan with me.
I can tell them what I'm really thinking.
What about things between me and Kurumi-chan?
Dammit!
Get over it, they're on the volleyball team.
Chizu-chan.
All right, soccer's next.
I wonder where Kurumi went.
I know.
She didn't show up for practice either.
I wonder if she's okay.
Then again, maybe we won because Kurumi wasn't here.
That girl Mariko that took her place was pretty athletic.
Kurumi's not really the enthusiastic type.
She needs to fix her hair better.
Totally.
I wonder if Kurumi-chan hasn't come back yet.
She never tires.
Kuronuma Sawako-chan, right?
I'm Sadako.
You're Sawako.
It's perfectly fine.
Go, Chizu.
Good luck.
Go.
Kurumi-chan called me by my name.
She called me a friend.
I've never thought of you as a friend.
But she called me a friend. She came to talk to me.
Truth or not, it made me happy.
You're the only person I've ever told.
Was it a lie? Was it the truth?
Thank you.
Yay, Sadako.
There was something I wanted to tell her.
Kurumi?
I'll be right back.
Sawako didn't say anything to Kurumi earlier.
I guess we were doing all the talking, come to think of it.
I just met her,
and I don't know her too well...
But she told me her precious feelings.
I want to tell her mine too.
My precious feelings.
Huh, is girls' soccer over already?
Kazehaya.
Only now you show up?
Dammit, Pin wouldn't let me go.
Oh yeah, you're on the sports day committee.
Hot guys have it rough.
What are you looking at?
Should we interject?
Where would we start?
Really, you too?
Forget it.
Where's Kuronuma?
Sawako went to find Kurumi.
Kurumizawa?
Oh, that girl.
What do you mean, “that” girl?
By “that” I mean “that.”
I'm a tragic man.
That girl's probably sulking somewhere.
Thinking of me.
I did it again, yet another miserable woman.
You two better never fall for me.
I'm not interested in kids.
Don't tell people. That's mean.
What are you talking about?
You're talking to tactful kindness incarnate.
Did you hear that?
Kurumi-chan's got bad taste.
Pin? Of all people?
That's a little weird.
I just felt sorry for Kurumi for the first time.
Even I do.
So you were still here.
What, are you here to laugh?
Still have more complaints?
Just say it.
You better not be pitying me.
I like Kazehaya-kun.
Actually. Romantically.
I love him.
That's what I came here to tell you earlier.
I wanted to tell you.
That was the first time I told anyone.
I never knew it would be so embarrassing to tell your friends.
My heart's racing.
It makes me realize how much I love him.
This is how you felt when you told me.
I said I'm not your friend.
Don't treat me like we're the same.
Didn't you get nervous?
Weren't you a little embarrassed?
Weren't you a little happy?
When you put it into words
and when you realized that you liked him...
Happy?
Why would I be happy telling you?
I said you're in my way.
You're always with Kazehaya,
and you don't even have to try.
I hate you.
I thought I could win against you.
Because I'm a lot more...
more...
I know, she's a lot more in league with him.
in love with him.
I swear.
She does.
Kurumi-chan really likes him.
I think you're cuter now than when I first met you.
I know I am.
But that doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter if Kazehaya doesn't like me.
I know he doesn't like me.
I know.
I've always been watching him.
Why did you come back?
I don't want to cry like this in front of you.
Because you know everything good about Kazehaya-kun.
I can talk to you about him.
I hate you.
I don't think I envied her just because she's pretty or because she's cool
or because she's on the same level as him.
I think it's because I thought she's cute, the way she thinks of Kazehaya-kun.
See me for who I am.
Now and forever.
Next episode: Rival