It's true that I was attracted by his kindness,
his coolness, his honesty, his outgoingness.
That's...
no mistake.
I can expect to see you over the summer, right?
My name is Kuronuma Sawako.
I hope someone nice will adopt you.
My nickname is Sadako.
Like Sadako from Ringu.
My favorite phrase is, “Do one good deed a day.”
Did you hear?
Sadako from Class B...
That girl who has a psychic aura or whatever?
Yeah.
Before the summer break, she made a public announcement that she got rejected.
Seriously?
By who?
Ka-ze-ha-ya.
Kazehaya?!
She wouldn't have a chance with him.
Morning.
Oh yeah, it's because I approached them out of nowhere.
Sorry to scare you.
She's praying.
Is there something there?
I wonder if that puppy is okay.
Why is she staring into the void?
And why is she soaked?
It's hard to approach people,
and I have a hard time talking to them.
But I still hope I can break down that wall.
Morning.
You're soaked, Kazehaya.
I got caught in the rain.
Wow, all those people are crowding around him.
That's Kazehaya-kun for you.
He's cool even when he's drenched.
Morning.
M-Morning.
He still talks to me like normal,
after all the trouble I've caused him.
He's so nice!
Did you get caught in the rain too?
You're soaked.
Do you have any spare clothes?
Kazehaya's sure being nice to her.
Spare clothes?
Oh yeah, I could have worn a jersey if I had one.
You don't have any?
And that ramen–
Yoshida, don't you have a spare jersey?
Yeah, I do.
What the hell?
You don't have any spare clothes, Sadako?
Fine, whatever.
There it is.
Tada!
It smells moldy. Seriously.
Oh yeah, could you wash it for me while you're at it?
Thanks.
You're going to need more than a hanky, aren't you?
I used it too, so it's a bit wet.
Tha– Thanks.
It's hard interacting with people,
but these days I think there are a lot of really nice people.
I'm so happy.
My classmates lent me stuff!
I want to thank them if I can...
Was that a Buddha statue?
Come to think of it, it was Kazehaya-kun that gave me a chance to befriend Yano-san and Yoshida-san.
Kazehaya-kun is still my idol.
I admire him.
You're worrying too much about her, Kazehaya.
Sadako this, Sadako that.
I know you feel bad about rejecting her, but...
I didn't reject her.
You didn't accept, did you?
That's not how it is.
I can expect to see you over the summer, right?
I can see you during the summer sessions?
So you're not going to avoid me during the sessions?
Kuronuma?
I've always wanted to be like you.
I've always admired you.
I really think highly of you right now.
I don't think I'll ever stop feeling this way.
“Attracted”... she meant that she admires me?
I got so cocky.
Thanks, Kazehaya-kun.
Kazehaya?
It wasn't about rejecting her...
or anything like that.
What? I don't get it.
It's me. I was the one who didn't get it.
No, I really don't get it.
All I ever thought was that I was being a bother.
But Kazehaya-kun gently let me know otherwise, without faking it.
What's this?
There's one on my desk as well.
Sadako left those there.
Why me?
She's repaying me.
You're too materialistic.
I never knew happiness could bring tears.
Kuronuma!
Did you give this to me?
F-For the towel.
Well, you could have just told me
or I would've never found out.
S-Sorry.
Thank god it was you.
I wouldn't know what to do if it wasn't.
I tend to be pretty mindless sometimes.
I thought maybe the towel was too much.
Honestly I'm still a bit nervous.
Just a bit.
Hey, didn't Sadako get rejected?
Are you having milk?
Oh, this is for a dog.
You like dogs?
I saw a dog today, an abandoned one.
Abandoned dog?
I got my clothes wet playing with it.
B-By the riverbed?
Over here!
So this was your umbrella.
That's why you were drenched.
I'm so embarrassed.
Oh yeah. It has your name on it.
I've been using it since grade school.
Can I keep him?
Really?
Hey.
It's fine, I've built up immunity.
Immunity?
Animals have always been afraid of me.
Kids too.
But I like dogs the most.
Oh yeah, don't they say dogs get attached to their owner when they're friendly with each other?
See, we're friendly.
Friendly?
See.
It's fine.
It's strange, whenever he says it, I feel like it's really true.
This is what he's like all the time.
He has no prejudice against anyone.
That's why everyone likes him.
I wonder if dogs are the same.
I want to break down this thick wall that I have between me and everyone else.
Even if just a little at a time.
I...
I want to be friends with everyone.
I have to do it.
Yeah, go for it.
It'll be fine.
See you.
H-Hey, if you don't mind...
Can I see it again?
What, just the dog?
What about me?
You too, of course.
Of course.
Sure, then.
It's weird, Kazehaya-kun.
Why is it?
I don't feel a wall between us.
This is a first for me.
Maybe I should wait until after school to give this to him.
When there's no one around.
But I wonder if he'll eat them.
They're hand-made too.
Maybe I overdid it.
I'm breaking out in a cold sweat.
I thought I was used to having this sort of thing rejected.
Morning.
You have math in the first hour, huh?
We're in separate classes, right?
Y-Yeah...
That dog...
He's doing well.
I still haven't chosen a name though.
It'll be fine.
Kazehaya.
See you.
I hope he likes the cookies.
Hey, that seat's open.
In the front?
Seriously?
Why not? The seat next to it is empty too.
Who's usually here, again?
Sadako.
Sadako?
Yuka sat in Sadako's seat and stayed home sick for a week.
Go for it.
Um...
It's fine.
It's not dirty.
Nothing will happen if you sit there.
I don't have the ability to make you sick.
Besides, I don't have any psychic aura or anything either.
I said it.
I said it!
Next time...
There's always next time.
It won't happen right away.
We'll rearrange seating during homeroom. Figure it out amongst yourselves.
Don't make a racket.
Seating change!
Sensei looked pale.
I think he's been sick since summer break.
Summer brea–
Is it because he made Sadako run more errands?
Didn't Ueda's grades drop? He was beside Sadako.
Nakanishi broke a leg.
Remember he said some nasty things to Sadako at the test of courage?
Let's just do the seating change.
Yeah...
Seating change huh?
I hope I can become good friends with whoever's next to me.
Is it just me or is everyone watching me?
Please don't let me be beside, behind, in front or diagonal to Sadako.
Kazehaya, what number?
32.
You're next to me.
Seriously?
Trade, please?
Please? Pretty please?
He's in there.
It sort of sucks that I have no one to share my joy and sadness with at times like this.
Come on, I'm at the front.
Poor you.
Um...
I'm at the back.
Do you want this?
It's fine, I'm sorry.
Sorry!
Sadako's number 3!
Who's next to her?
12, 19, 25.
Thank god, I'm not next to her.
Number 19 better watch out.
That's right next to her.
That hurts! I heard all of it!
But oh well.
I wish I could tell someone that I'm glad I'm here.
Number 19, switch with me, please?
Yay, I'm next to you.
You can have this back.
Yoshida, your draw–
No thanks, don't need one.
Got a problem?
Ryuu, move!
Make me.
You don't need to be here.
This is my seat.
By the window, at the back.
Hey,
I made cookies to thank you for yesterday.
Want some?
For me too?
Yeah...
And the jersey you lent me.
It's really good.
Thanks.
You baked those?
Yeah.
Thank you, that's so thoughtful!
You're right, they're good.
I'm hungry.
You just had lunch.
I'm hun–
I'm...
so glad...
I got this seat.
I'm so happy,
from the bottom of my heart!
Kuronuma.
You're not crying.
H-How embarrassing.
Embarrassing, huh?
I see.
I work so hard to bring down the wall,
but he breaks it down with nothing but a smile.
Isn't that Kazehaya and Sadako?
Aren't they together a lot lately?
I wonder if Sadako really did get rejected.
See you tomorrow.
I still respect him and admire him.
That hasn't changed.
But...
Since when did it become a lot more than that...
that I started really liking him?
New seating arrangements.
My dreams are becoming a reality.
Next episode: After School