Sawako!
G-Got it!
Sawako-chan!
Good luck!
O-Okay.
So then when the pass comes this way,
you head straight that way.
Oh, I see.
See, this is important.
The enemy's going to try to block you.
Don't panic, just kick it back a bit.
You have to, like, picture how the game's going to unfold in your head.
You know what I mean?
They're pumped up.
Sports day's coming up.
Sawako-chan.
Keep your knees bent.
And then sort of grind the ball out with the inside of your foot.
And push! Push! Push! Push! Push!
I see.
Grind the ball out?
Sawako-chan.
Bye bye.
What?
We're friends.
Really?
Dammit, seriously?
You really don't like her, do you?
How can you tell, Yano-chin?
Because you're simple-minded.
Not that it's a bad thing that Sadako has new friends.
Friends, huh?
Bye bye.
But seriously, I'd be so pissed if she became closer to her than to us.
You're cute, Chizu.
I made a new friend again.
Honestly, it's not like I put in any effort, so I don't know what to think.
We're friends now, right?
I guess this is what it's like to make friends.
It hasn't really hit me, but I still feel happy.
Kuronuma.
Wh-Why did I just see Kazehaya-kun's face?
It has nothing to do with anything.
I can't sleep!
Kurumi-chan's my friend now too.
I'm so blessed, yet I feel the opposite...
Here.
T-Thanks.
What's up with them?
Don't you get it?
Tension, you know, tension.
Oh no.
I can't really talk to Kazehaya-kun too well.
Kazehaya.
What's up?
I have to give you the committee form.
Here.
Thanks.
Oh yeah, the CD.
Hold on.
You brought it? Thanks.
Here.
Yay, thanks.
So natural.
She's so cute, nice and friendly.
She's something else.
Thank you.
Kurumi-chan doesn't get nervous like that.
She's so smooth.
So nice...
Sawako-chan.
What's up?
Thanks.
Sorry I surprised you.
You didn't notice me calling you.
No, I'm sorry for everything.
Here you go.
Thanks.
I, uh...
Ku—
K-Kurumi-chan.
I called her by name.
Was that uncalled for?
You finally called me Kurumi-chan.
I'm so happy.
It went alright!
Isn't that heavy?
Want me to carry half?
It's fine.
This is my job.
Job? You're funny.
I wish I could be like Kurumi-chan.
Here's the form, yo. Pass me the CD.
Okay.
Woohoo! Thanks dude!
Woo!
American?
Sawako-chan?
Is something bothering you?
You can talk to me about it if you want.
I'll hear you out.
No, not really.
Talk to me about anything.
My role model wants to hear me out.
Bring it on pitcher!
Pitcher, pitch to contact!
You have a hard time talking to Kazehaya?
Maybe boys and girls are too different.
You get too self-conscious.
I knew it.
I've known him since middle school, and my guess is...
Kazehaya's always been really nice to kids that don't fit in.
He talks to anyone and everyone really casually.
So I think he talks to you normally too.
That's so true.
So it's not anything special that he talks to you.
I don't think you need to get so tense.
I see.
But then again, you're so different from Kazehaya.
Yeah.
So maybe you'll have a better time talking to someone not as outgoing,
someone like you.
You know, people get along with some people better than others.
Oh, I see.
I guess that's why you talk to him so casually.
I wonder.
We're sort of alike in a way.
Wow.
Kazehaya-kun was calling her by name.
You're close to him, aren't you?
Close to him? No, that's just normal.
Normal? Really?
Really? The standards are so high!
I see; if that's normal for Kurumi-chan, then no wonder I feel nervous.
Maybe we should head back now.
O-Okay.
Morning, Kuronuma.
I could hardly even say “hi” to him at first.
And that used to be normal.
Of course.
Hey, Kurumi-chan,
I think I'm more confident after I talked to you.
Thanks.
One step at a time. That's what I'll do.
I'm a little nervous, but I'll do my best.
Wait—
See you.
Sawako-chan,
I wonder if I could ever become like you someday.
I know I can't.
Sorry. Forget I said that!
Kurumi's, like...
Well, back in middle school...
Chizu-chan,
Yumi-chan likes Kazehaya.
You're good friends with Kazehaya.
Do you think you can help out?
I don't mind being relied on.
So you just want me to make an opportunity for the two of you to be alone?
Done and done.
You're so helpful, Chizu-chan.
So then she confessed to him and got rejected.
Well, that was all fine and stuff, but...
Chizu-chan, can you help with her too?
Chizu-chan, it's her this time.
Chizu, me too.
Me too.
Hey, there's another girl who wants to talk to you.
What's up with you lately?
Dammit! I'm done!
Why?
You're going to help Yumi but not me?
You were on Yumi's side, Chizu?
Pain in the ass!
Hey, Chizu-chan,
why, why?
Wait,
it's not Chizu-chan's fault.
It's not good for the girls in our class to get split up like this.
Maybe no one should confess to him.
That's so stupid.
Of course.
Kazehaya belongs to all of us.
Oh my god, that's so stupid.
Everyone who was afraid of having him taken by someone else joined up.
So anyway, she's not exactly a bad person.
I help her out; she helps me out.
She's a pain.
I don't like her type.
Honestly, I don't want to hang out with her.
You're so being used.
I sort of know what she's really like now.
Let's see if things really go as she wants.
Got it.
Let's take a break.
Alright!
I'm going to get something to drink.
Hey, buy me some tea too.
Okay.
I wonder if I could ever become like you someday.
I think I went a little too far.
I'm embarrassed.
Kuronuma.
Ka—
Kazehaya-kun.
Shit, I called her name but now I'm nervous.
Nervous?
Kazehaya-kun?
I haven't talked to you in a while.
What am I saying?
I was just going to buy a drink and I saw you here.
That's all.
I see, Kazehaya-kun was nervous too.
Later.
Kazehaya-kun was thinking the same thing I was.
Ever since we went to Ryu's place.
Kazehaya-kun—
He smiled.
You smiled.
I haven't seen you smile in a while.
Thank god.
Oh yeah, Maru's pretty big now.
Like, this big.
He's so active.
He makes a mess inside the house.
I need to make him a doghouse soon.
Maru-chan...!
You want to come visit him sometime?
He gets so lonely though.
I wonder if he'll stay put inside the doghouse.
Sawako-chan.
Kurumizawa.
Zawa?
Kurumizawa?
Kurumi-chan?
You didn't know?
Her name's Kurumizawa Ume.
Kurumizawa Ume?
Right, Kurumizawa?
Yeah.
Kurumizawa Ume-chan.
Yeah, Kurumizawa.
Oh, he wasn't calling her by name.
Kurumizawa Ume-chan.
Ume-chan.
Huh? I'm burning up.
Ka—
Kazehaya, can I borrow Sawako-chan for a second?
Sure, I think.
I want to talk to her, girl to girl.
Girl to girl.
Why does someone always get in the way?
I wonder what she wants to talk to me about.
How far are we going?
Hey, Kuru—
Ume-chan,
Don't call me Ume.
Kurumi-chan,
please.
Kurumi-chan.
I see, a nickname.
I thought I had crossed the line and made her angry.
You know, there's someone I like.
I want to go out with him, but I don't think I can.
I wonder what I should do.
What should I do?
Wh—
What?
What should you do?
She needs my help, but I can't think of anything.
Actually, I want you to help me.
Me? Be of use to her?
A-Am I good enough?
Are you good enough?
You're the only one who is.
I think this is the first time I've ever been so depended on.
I-I'll do my best.
Really?
Thank god.
But what exactly do you want me to do?
Don't worry, I'll tell you exactly.
But wouldn't I ruin the mood?
It'll be fine.
It's someone you know well.
Kazehaya.
Kazehaya is the one I like.
Kazehaya-kun?
Uncertain feelings.
Incomparable emotions.
Next episode: Special?