I begin my weekends by feeding the birds.
After that, I go jogging.
Burnable trash.
Recyclable trash.
And then I go home to shower.
After all that, I normally clean and have breakfast, and then I'm done.
But today,
Chizu-chan and Ayane-chan are coming over.
Your friends are coming over today, aren't they?
They're here.
Oh no!
Dad will get it.
Sawako's old man?
Punk!
He looks just like her!
Where are your manners?
Greet him.
's-sup.
Y-You're Sawako's friends?
The other one seems to be pretty normal, though she's got a lot of makeup on.
Hello,
I'm her classmate, Yano.
How many piercings does she have?!
Her friends?
Chizu-chan, Ayane-chan.
Come in, I was baking a cake.
Homemade?
Seriously?
Shoot, I brought some too.
Cake!
I should have made something savory.
I'm so inconsiderate.
I like homemade cake more.
I'll eat as much as you want me to.
Don't, you'll get fat.
Well well, don't just stand at the door, do come in.
This is my mom.
This is my dad.
Hi.
Would you two please have this?
My, my, thank you.
Yano Ayane-chan and Yoshida Chizuru-chan.
Nice to finally meet you.
It really is.
Nice to finally meet you too.
She saved her from bombing a class.
You're embarrassing me, Yano-chin.
Your room's actually pretty colorful.
I figured no one would be bothered if my room suits me or not.
You're seriously over-thinking it.
Hey look, pictures.
I was looking through pictures of the trip, and you were in these ones.
You sure there are no ghosts in these photos?
That's perfect then. Here, a gift.
From the party.
They're pretty good, right?
Wow, they don't look creepy.
We're so close together.
Wow.
Look through them more.
When did I do something so rude?!
Yano-chin sneaked that picture of you.
Not bad, right? You look like a couple.
I-I must have been heavy.
Come on, as much of a loser as he is, it'd be sad if he couldn't hold up one girl.
That's so mean.
Kazehaya caught on in that one.
All of a sudden, I have so many treasures.
Thanks.
Don't be so content with just pictures.
Go confess already.
To who? About what?
To Kazehaya, your love.
Love?
I love you, sir.
Is that so?
What for?
To go out with him, obviously!
I couldn't.
You totally could.
I couldn't, and besides, I'm already overwhelmed as it is.
I can't imagine going any further.
Keep saying that. What if someone takes Kazehaya away?
I don't think I could be happy for them.
I don't think I could congratulate them.
Sorry, sorry.
I guess you wouldn't want to go out with someone right away just because you like them.
Poor Kazehaya.
What's this?
I rented these yesterday.
Want to watch?
Nice.
Dear god no!
Ryu.
Pedro.
Maru's so happy.
You really like animals, Ryu.
Cute.
Huh who is it?
Aren't you answering?
It's Pin.
He hung up.
What?! Fourteen calls, all from Pin.
You're not answering?
Nope.
It's been ringing for a while.
It's a pain in the ass, so I figured, whatever.
Hello?
Where the hell were you?
I have things to do too, man.
Bring Kuronuma here, now.
Huh?
Now.
Please.
Please, I can't stop shaking.
I ran into Kuronuma last night.
Good evening.
Are you doing research too?
Yeah, research.
Research?
Ghost photos?
Adult videos, huh?
She got me.
Society.
Documentaries.
He sure is an adult.
You...
What do you see behind me?
He sounds a bit nasal.
Why is she staring at me?
Sensei, be sure to wash your hands and gargle with salt water when you get home.
Prevention's the best cure.
Why does she want me to cleanse?
But I got home and forgot all about her warnings.
That's all.
Uh...
All I could figure out is that he rented porn.
Please, help me.
What's he want?
I don't know, but he sounded weak.
He wants me to bring Kuronuma.
Oh yeah, Chizuru said she's going to Kuronuma's place today.
I wonder if she'd want to see Maru.
Is Sawako okay?
She won't become a bad girl?
Hey, look, five cakes!
She bought enough for us too.
She's so kind.
Thank you.
Oh, don't bother.
They're telling ghost stories in there, so I ran away.
Just leave those there.
Let me wash them.
Can I use this?
I'm so awesome at washing dishes.
See, so fast, so clean!
Oh my.
See!
Thanks, you didn't have to.
Nah, I'm trying to show off here.
Sawako's got her dad's brows, eyes and nose.
And her mom's profile and mouth.
That's awesome.
Oh...
Wow.
Later.
What's up, Kazehaya?
They're both nice girls.
See?
Huh?
Yeah sure, I'll go.
Yeah.
Ew, gross.
I'm a bit worried.
Maru's here too.
Maru-chan?
Kazehaya-kun?
Yeah.
Kuronuma?
Pin's sick or something.
He wants to talk to you.
Let's all go to his place.
I knew it.
I guess it's too late for gargling if you're already in the nasal stage.
I'll be right there.
Please do.
I bet Maru wants to see you too.
That's it?
What?
Shouldn't you have said you wanted to see her too?
I mean, I thought you would.
Hell no.
Today's a good day.
And I even get to meet Kazehaya-kun.
Yo, get in.
I'm screwed.
Such a mess.
How's it looking for me?
Terrible.
Just stay in your blanket.
A cold.
Just a cold.
I brought some stuff.
To banish the spirits?
I'll do it.
Cold!
And this.
I'll do it.
Here.
Next...
Why am I acting like his boyfriend?
He's so dependable!
Hey,
do you think I'm okay?
Is this room okay?
What are you growling at, Pedro?
There was this scratching sound yesterday night too.
He's hearing things because of the fever.
You're fine, please just get some rest and sleep.
Your room might take some time.
I'll clean it.
I'm pretty good at that.
A purification, huh?
I like cleaning.
You want me to tell you a story until you fall asleep?
What?
Do it.
I just heard this.
This actually happened in this neighborhood.
A man lived alone in an apartment.
He heard knocking every night.
He opens the door, but there's no one there.
Indeed, in that apartment, in that very room...
He sleeps pretty well for someone who just freaked out.
It's Kazehaya-kun when he was little.
S-S-Sorry.
I've infringed on your privacy.
No, I mean, it's embarrassing.
I'm crying because I lost in a game.
Pin laughed at me so much.
Can I see it again?
No.
Oh yeah, aren't you going to play with Maru?
I didn't want to get in Sanada-kun's way.
Y-You should go play with him.
Seriously, just go out already.
So cute...
He sleeps so peacefully...
He really does.
I feel lighter.
The medication kicked in.
The room smells different.
It's been changed.
You're awesome!
I'm going to ask you next time I'm haunted.
What, you're still here?
Go home, pesky brats.
We're never coming back.
T-Take care.
Let me know if there's anything you want to talk about.
I know everything about Shouta and Ryu.
Come talk to me and I'll tell you their soft spots.
They better not be talking smack.
Really?
No doubt.
Try it out when you want to thank him.
He'll love it.
He'll love it?
This is awesome, I feel so much better.
Huh, forget something?
Sawako's cake was so good.
It ended sort of weird, but I'll come over again.
Yes, please do!
I sort of don't want to part, since we were together all day.
The longer we're together, the harder it is to say bye.
I'm going this way.
Take care.
Walk her home, Kazehaya.
Yeah, it's really dark, it's dangerous.
It's fine, I'll be careful not to scare anyone.
Okay.
I'll walk you home.
But...
Tell me if you don't want me to.
That's not it.
I'll go too, then.
You idiot.
You're coming this way.
Pedro!
See you.
Good night.
Say hi to your folks for me.
Let's go.
Why wouldn't I want him to?
The days are getting shorter.
I'm so happy.
I'm too happy.
I want to thank him, but I can't speak.
I can't look at him.
Y-You scared me!
What was that?
Arai-sensei told me to hold on to you and close my eyes for five seconds when I want to thank you.
That bastard!
I don't know.
Seriously, if you do that again, I don't know.
I seriously don't know.
If I hear his voice so much,
and if I'm with him so much,
and if I see him so much...
See, I can't stand parting with him.
Don't look at me for a while.
I wonder if I'll feel like telling him how I feel someday.
The arrival of winter,
the footsteps of hope.
Next episode: Chizuru's Love