It's Ryu's brother that I like.
I'm going to spend some money on him this year.
I wonder if she gave it to him.
Thanks for everything.
No, thank you. It's been fun.
We'll be back again for New Year's.
Chi never showed up again.
I bet she's busy. She's growing up.
Ryu,
tell Chi to say hi properly next time.
Okay, I will.
It's cold.
I don't have a face to show.
You're late.
My brother said to say hi properly next time.
He went home around noon.
I-I know that.
Are you trying to be nice to me?
Are you starting a fight?
Which is it?
Nice?
Y-You thought it'd be bad to tell me about Tohru, didn't you?
I wasn't being nice.
I'm glad it's finally come to this.
Why?
Now you can finally give up on my brother.
You idiot. Idiot!
You baseball nut!
What's baseball got to do with anything?
Idiot.
I can't do anything, can I?
Chizu-chan does so much for me.
Maybe if I were like Kazehaya-kun,
I might have been able to cheer her up.
Morning.
I wonder if Chizu went to see Ryu's brother after what happened.
I wonder if she congratulated him.
In that mood?
Without a speck of disappointment?
Congratulations, good going!
Thanks.
In jeans.
I know. I know, Sawako.
She should just snap for once.
I feel sorry for her.
And I sort of said something to make it worse.
Are you sure?
There's more fish in the sea.
Yeah, I did. I totally did!
Chizu froze up for a second.
Ayane-chan, what did you...
I can't tell you!
I want to disappear.
No, don't disappear!
It's not like it bothers me when I'm hurting her deliberately, though.
What are you doing?
I wonder; what were we doing?
We were savoring our powerlessness.
Powerless.
Is it something about Yoshida?
Ah.
I never knew that was bothering you.
Did you know who she liked too?
We used to hang out at Ryu's a lot when Tohru was back.
Chizu's easy to read.
Ayane-chan was just like me.
She was worried about Chizu-chan, but she couldn't do anything.
Honestly, I can't even tell whether she's playing tough or if she's so shocked that she's in denial.
And she's supposed to be easy to read.
Chizu-chan looked happy, as always.
I don't know what she's feeling.
But I know she's not okay.
I know, but...
Miniskirt...
No! No! We're so bad!
You okay?
Yoshida'll be fine.
What?! She's your friend.
This is why I hate guys.
Ayane-chan!
No, because she has you two.
Were you listening to me?!
There's nothing we can say to her.
Yeah, but I don't think that's a problem.
I'd be glad to have friends who worry for me.
Do you need to force yourself to say something to her?
I'm sure you're doing the right thing.
She might not be able to say anything right now either.
What about you? What would you do?
Me?
Didn't Joe just get rejected?
I'm totally useless.
We should head to class.
I was wondering how Kazehaya-kun would help her.
I see.
I can't really say anything to her,
Kazehaya!
but even so I hope there's something I can do.
Thanks, Kazehaya-kun.
I just got comforted by a loser.
Loser?
Now I can't really tease him as much.
She'll be fine.
She has Kuronuma, Yano and Ryu.
Oh, Sawako and Yano-chin aren't here yet.
I'm glad it's finally come to this.
Yano-chin, Sawako, you're late.
Morning.
Morning, Chizu.
We didn't meet up the other day.
Sorry, I even kicked you guys out.
It's fine, we see each other every day anyway.
Let's get to our seats.
Pin will be here any minute.
I was about to cry.
I shouldn't cry; Chizu-chan's not crying.
Morning, Kazehaya.
Morning, Yoshida.
Let's hear her out if she talks to us.
And let her vent as much as she wants.
Ayane-chan.
And I'm going to act normal around Chizu-chan until then.
Maybe that's the best I can do for her.
Lunch!
Go, lunch!
Kazehaya, what are you having?
Cafeteria food.
You?
Rice balls.
Yeah?
Come on, Kazehaya.
Later, then.
I'll go buy bread.
Should I come with you?
Nah, I'll be back right away.
See you.
Has Ryu talked to Chizu at all today?
Did something happen?
What's going on?
Did Ryu go after Chizu?
I don't know.
What's going on?
Half and half, an Elizabeth with cheese and mayo,
a bagel, a melon bun, nuts and a dried fruit bun, please!
A-All right.
Huge catch.
Chizuru,
My bread!
Sorry, you wouldn't even look at me.
Yesterday—
What? All that stuff yesterday, and now my bread.
Do you want to apologize?
I don't care to apologize for what happened yesterday.
Huh?
Were you always thinking that?
That I was hopelessly in love with Tohru?
That I should hurry up and give up?
Yeah.
I didn't fall in love with Tohru just for the sake of getting rejected.
I didn't really go to see Tohru yesterday.
What?
Are they fighting?
And what the hell?
“You're late?”
I would have wanted to see him properly if I could.
But I couldn't go.
I couldn't go.
So I went to give you the present after he'd already have left.
You dumb shit.
Chizuru, your bread.
No. Take it.
Don't talk to me for a while.
How could I eat all this?
I didn't fall in love with Tohru just for the sake of getting rejected.
At least let me say thanks.
Chizu...
Why are you here?
I was sort of worried.
Were you watching?
Yeah.
That's embarrassing.
I had a bit of a fight with Ryu yesterday night...
I can't take it.
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry.
What a scary face.
Here.
Chizu?! A-Are you okay?
I hate him.
I hate Ryu.
I-I gave him the present.
I didn't even want to see him.
“I'm glad it came to this.”
“Now you can give up.”
What the hell?
What do you mean it's hopeless?
You're too blunt, you idiot.
Chizu.
Did you even feel sorry for me?
I hate him.
But I hate myself the most for blaming him.
I wanted to be happier when I gave it to him.
I was so eager to.
I threw it at him.
I can't take it.
I don't even understand marriage, and here I am taking it out on people.
She snapped.
Chizu snapped.
Thank god!
What?
Yeah, come on, let it out.
When else are you going to vent?
You have every right to take it out on him.
Ryu's totally being an asshole.
He is, right? He's a douchebag right?
Yeah he is.
I wouldn't even have given him the present if I were you.
Really?
You did well.
Yano-chin, Sawako!
There, there.
Let it all out.
He's so stupid.
I went to his house, and he goes, “forget about him.”
Why did I give him that bread?
I'm hungry.
I couldn't find any words to help Chizu-chan.
But on the way home, she said...
Hey...
What?
I felt a bit better after you made me cry.
All right, let's go eat cake.
Hurry up, Yano-chin.
Yeah, yeah.
Seriously, I get fat when I hang out with you.
Hello?
Hey,
I have a ton of bread. Want some?
Chizuru gave it to me.
The shimmering night sky.
Smile like you used to.
Next episode: First Snow