I wasn't really disliked in elementary school,
though I didn't have any close friends either.
I was never really part of a clique.
May I join?
I didn't notice you, Sawako-chan.
Sure, let's play.
One day, a classmate named Shino-chan said...
Sadako!
She didn't mean to say that, but...
Sadako?
Sadako.
And I became the “Sadako girl.”
Some people in my middle school thought it was funny.
Sadako really does seem like she has a psychic aura.
I wouldn't be surprised if she does.
She really does.
Before I knew it, I was the “psychic aura girl.”
And then, when I came to high school...
I heard that Sadako has a psychic aura.
And if you lock eyes with her for 3 seconds, a week later...
One rumor led to another, I guess.
Come to think of it, maybe I was fortunate.
I got a bit depressed at times, but I don't think I was ever really upset.
Oh yeah, remember that rumor about Sadako?
About Yano and Yoshida backing her up?
T-That's a mistake.
Yano-san and Yoshida-san aren't backing me up.
Shut up, dammit.
I know, right?
The criminal and the slut.
Morning, Kazehaya.
Morning.
Morning, Ryu.
What's going on?
The girls' washroom.
Did something happen?
Hey, Kazehaya.
There's a fight in the washroom.
A fight?
Guess who?
Sadako and the girls from Class A.
Kuronuma? Why?
We were inside earlier.
I think Sadako started it.
Something about the rumors about Chizu and Yano-chin.
Rumors?
That stuff about Chizu-san being covered in blood and doing a hundred guys, right?
They say Sadako's spreading the rumors.
No, I'm going to try my best to be their friend.
Kuronuma wouldn't do such a thing.
What's with the yelling?
What's going on?
Kuronuma's trying to do something
about those rumors about you two.
Let me through.
Move!
Are you holding something in?
Of course I am.
But I can't do anything about it.
They have to do it.
Go for it, Kuronuma.
Go for it.
Go for it!
What you said earlier...
take it back.
What's with your hand?
Let go.
It's a misunderstanding.
You're making a mistake!
Did you just hear that?
Yano-san and Yoshida-san aren't like that.
You're going to hurt them.
Look who's talking!
They're nice? They're going to get hurt?
Bullshit.
You're the one who said all that stuff,
about Yoshida being a delinquent and Yano being a slut.
Me? What?
You're the one spreading rumors about Yoshida and Yano, Sadako.
Me?
I think she got shoved down.
Maybe we should go stop them.
Leave it to us.
Why would I say that about them?
That's a mistake.
In fact, they're really kind to me.
I don't give a shit.
There's something we want to talk to you about.
They were probably just hanging out with you for the hell of it, anyway.
They're probably sick of you by now.
Aren't you the same?
You just started hanging out with them to get close to Kazehaya.
And now they're in the way, right?
You're a pest.
Get lost. Be by yourself.
Then we'll get off your—
No.
You don't need to get off my back.
Just take it back.
Huh? What the hell—
All of it.
It's all wrong.
You people don't get it.
You don't know anything.
You're in luck.
Everyone was avoiding me.
Snack time. Drink up.
They weren't afraid of me.
They didn't avoid me.
It's soaked.
Here, my jersey.
You don't know how kind they were to me.
You don't know anything.
How I more than just like them... I love them.
Do you like us?
W-Well—
More like...
I...
I love you.
So...
Y-Yoshida.
You're still sticking up for her,
after all those rumors she spread?
It wasn't Sadako.
She wouldn't do that.
What are you—
It's our problem, so piss off.
Get lost already.
W-What? This isn't your problem.
I was talking to Sadako.
You think you can beat me up?
You were in my middle school, so you must know me.
About my 99 consecutive victories dueling against guys.
The hell are you talking about?
Mess with Sadako again and I'll mess you up.
What the hell?
Let's go.
Wait.
All that stuff... it really is a mistake.
Just shut up.
Fine.
I'll take it back.
Happy now?
They understood.
Yano-san, Yoshida-san,
they understood.
They understood me.
That the rumor was a mistake.
It's okay, Sadako.
It's fine.
It wasn't Sadako.
She wouldn't do that.
Yano-san,
Yoshida-san.
Thanks.
Thanks for believing in me.
K-Kazehaya?
Did we do something to piss you off?
I'm not pissed off.
He's pissed off!
I just...
hate stupid rumors.
You knew those rumors about Yano and Yoshida were bullshit, didn't you?
You seriously thought Kuronuma would do it?
Well, I...
I don't know much about Kuronuma.
I thought maybe she did, since it was a rumor.
Sadako was defending them.
Defending them?
Even after she got pushed down,
she was defending Yano-san and Yoshida-san.
We couldn't do anything...
But Yano-san and Yoshida-san came to help her.
Really? Yano and Yoshida helped Sadako?
So it really was bullshit then.
Oh, it was a rumor.
I thought it was weird.
Oh yeah, Sadako's notes were good, no?
Yeah, I aced the exam yesterday thanks to those notes.
Me too.
Sadako's awesome.
Oh yeah, I totally thought it was just a rumor.
Kuronuma's going to be so happy,
when she finds out that it was thanks to Hirano and Endou.
Good job, Hirano, Endou.
Make the most of it, Kuronuma.
I thought I could stop the rumors by myself.
Sadako—
I never thought I could do anything about it.
“It didn't work out.”
“Oh well.”
I kept wanting to fit in with everyone,
but somewhere inside I'd already given up.
Yet I couldn't give up on you two.
Even if it meant that there'd be bad rumors about you,
and you might get hurt...
I couldn't give you up.
I don't know how to make you feel better when you get hurt,
but I want to be with you.
Like right now.
No, I want to be closer to you.
Even if there are more rumors.
I'll stop all of them.
I'm being so selfish.
But they're listening to me, without even looking away.
I want to be friends with you two.
Sadako,
you thought we were hurt because of that?
That we would get hurt by you being around us?
And you still wanted to be with us?
Is that why you were hurt?
Yano-san, I'm dirty right now, I just fell.
You idiot.
You're an idiot.
You just said everything I was about to ask.
I'm embarrassed for having doubted you.
I'm sorry, Sadako.
Don't get used to being alone.
Don't you know? We adore you so much.
Don't you know?
Becoming friends happens before you know it.
We were already friends, Sadako.
Friends?
We were?
Dammit, I'm going to hug you all.
Stop it! Shut up!
You're going to start a rumor again.
Seriously, you cry too much.
Friends?
You're teary-eyed too.
I can tell one of those horror stories now.
My first friends.
She's crying and laughing at the same time.
They seem pretty happy together though.
What's going on?
That's so creepy.
It's solved!
They switched roles, and now it's solved!
You hear that?
Guess I won't have to cheer her up, then.
A fight!
Where's the fight?!
Who's fighting?!
What?
Got a problem?
We're busy right now.
What's this rotten teen drama?
That's so lame!
Start fighting!
You call yourself a teacher?
Dammit!
Move!
Get lost, all of you!
Like the bugs that you are!
That bastard ruined it.
Kazehaya-kun.
I'm glad.
I always heard what you told me.
“Go for it, go for it...”
I heard it all along.
Thanks, Kazehaya-kun.
Wasn't she...
...smiling just now?
I saw that, I totally saw that.
Exams ended, and my grades were horrible.
Seriously? Sadako 30th?
That's still pretty good.
The first day was bad.
But the class average was up dramatically for some reason.
Yay for Sadako's notes!
Praise be!
Zashiki warashi.
Sadako warashi?
Maybe it's just me,
but I think everyone looks at me just a little differently these days.
Maybe I made a difference.
Let's go eat ramen, Sadako.
Me too? Really?
Oh yeah, we haven't heard your horror story yet.
You want to hear it?
Please no.
Do you have money, Sadako?
A little.
That's good then.
I don't have a chance to be alone with her anymore!
Let's go hang out, Kazehaya.
I haven't had ramen in ages.
I feel like I was just reborn.
Ever since I met you.
It's not fair.
You okay, Kazehaya?
Did you know? Friends eat ramen together.
I have people to care for now.
Really?
Don't be fooled, Sadako.
I did something that I couldn't do on my own.
How am I supposed to take her from them when she looks so happy?
Come on...
What's wrong Kazehaya, are you okay?
You want to go to the nurse's office?
Hey, Sadako.
Oh, from earlier.
So you became friends, just like you wanted. That's good.
Friends.
Nice to meet you, Sadako.
Later.
I just acknowledged it.
Sadako,
What did you say about us again?
You more than like us, you what?
I love you.
Yeah? You love us, huh?
A lot of things have changed since I met Kazehaya-kun.
I've learned a lot of new feelings.
Oh yeah, tell that horror story.
I'll listen.
There once was a Biwa player named Houichi.
Isn't that Miminashi Houichi?!
Kazehaya-san was seriously pissed.
He said he hates stupid rumors.
It was about us, wasn't it?
I'm sort of worried.
Yuka's really liked Kazehaya since middle school.
Wait, Yuka.
Silly girls.
Of course he's going to hate you for that.
My beloved friends.
My precious time.
Next episode: Saturday Night