Hey—
Look out!
See,
you got helped.
Why don't you try talking to him more?
Yeah, just the two of you, alone.
You might find something in him if you talk to him.
He helped you out, you know.
So he's the same as Kazehaya.
The same?
What do you think of Sanada?
I think he's a good person.
See, he's the same.
He doesn't avoid you or anything either, does he?
The game!
The game's starting, Kurumi-chan.
Were you listening to me?
I was, but...
Didn't you want to see Kazehaya-kun play?
I heard that he used to play baseball in middle school, and I really wanted to see him play.
I wanted to know more about Kazehaya.
See, you don't know anything about Kazehaya.
Don't think you feel the same way about him as I do.
I've been watching him since middle school.
On rainy days...
On rainy days?
Windy days too...
Windy days too?
Even in snowstorms...
Even in snowstorms?
And I talked to him whenever I had the chance.
And I made sure he wouldn't get a girlfriend.
You—
You tried so hard.
Yeah, I did all sorts of things.
That was close.
Anyway, that's how well I know Kazehaya-kun.
It's not like I started to feel this way just yesterday.
It's always been like this.
I've always been watching him.
Out.
Let's keep it up.
Yeah!
You can't keep your eyes off of him.
Don't talk as if you know what you're talking about.
He'd always be in your sight.
You can't stop watching him.
You'd always be thinking about him.
You always see his face before you fall asleep.
Everything was so new to me.
I thought it was special, what I was feeling.
I think I really don't know anything.
About Kazehaya-kun.
Or if I'd feel this way even if it wasn't Kazehaya-kun.
Or if there's anything more.
I want to know.
I want to know more about Kazehaya-kun and about my own feelings.
Strike! Batter out!
I'll try talking to Sanada-kun properly.
Thanks, Kurumi-chan.
She actually took the bait.
I'm going to do things my way.
K-Kurumi-chan, what about the game?
Huh?
I-I wonder if she didn't want to watch it with me.
Kazehaya-kun must be really special to her.
She's been watching him all along.
I want to go out with him, but...
Go out with him...
I see, so Kurumi-chan has a crush.
A crush?
A crush?!
I never thought of that word until now.
Thank you very much.
We're through round one.
I'm so glad.
Congratulations, Kazehaya-kun.
Congratulations, everyone.
Kurumi-chan never came back.
There you are.
I couldn't tell with your hair done differently.
Endou-san.
It's Tomo.
We won softball.
I'm going to go cheer for our volleyball team.
Come on, let's go.
I can come too?
What are you talking about?
Weren't you going to go cheer for Ayane-chan and Chizu-chan?
Ekko's playing too.
Let's go.
Did I say something bad?
N-No,
I'm just happy.
Thanks.
I'm so happy.
I used to be alone all the time.
Everyone around me is so nice.
It wouldn't have been this way if even one of us was missing.
If it wasn't for Kazehaya-kun,
I probably wouldn't have known how nice everyone is.
My world changed.
Admiration, respect, romance...
I don't know how I feel either.
I want to know my own feelings.
Sanada's the same as Kazehaya-kun.
Maybe I'll find out if I talk to Sanada-kun.
Maybe I'll find some answers.
Let's go back.
What's next?
I think girls' volleyball and boys' soccer.
Ryu...
Hey, about earlier.
Earlier?
Are you interested in Kuronuma?
Oh, Sakako—I mean, Sawako...
Was it?
Kuronuma.
Kuranuma?
Kuro.
Oh yeah, like “black.”
Kuroyama's cool,
but it's not what you're thinking.
It's Kuronuma.
Didn't I just say that?
You said yama.
Really?
The magic ball from earlier?
No, forget it.
That was just because I was right there.
I know.
I know, but...
I still feel like I wish I'd caught it.
Girls' soccer and boys' softball, all good for round one.
Free steak!
Sensei,
I want to check the sports day committee schedule.
What year, what class?
Name?
Um, never mind, I'll find it myself.
Huh?
Just say it.
I'll tell you.
I don't want to give you trouble.
What's up with her?
Here.
Thank you.
Kazehaya.
There.
The first afternoon block is clearing the field, and taking the equipment into the storage room.
If you're done, get out of here.
Okay.
Thank you.
See you.
S-Sure...
What's with that crazy smile?
I've always,
always been watching him.
And for Chizu...
Hey, it's Kurumi-chan.
You're Yano Ayane-chan, right?
You're Sawako-chan and Chizu-chan's friend.
You were in the same middle school as Chizu, weren't you?
What are you using for foundation and stuff?
Nothing, really.
Tonight it'll be a pack.
Using my sister's really expensive one.
You knew my name.
There were rumors about you.
Rumors?
Oh, that's nothing.
People shouldn't believe that stuff.
I guess.
You'd have to be an idiot to buy it.
Hey, you heard the rumor too, right?
Did you tell it to anyone?
Of course not.
I never believed it in the first place.
I just overheard a bunch of girls talking about it.
Yeah, I bet.
I can't imagine you spreading rumors.
Oh, come on.
I bet it was someone who liked him, who spread that rumor.
I bet Sawako was in her way.
Even worse with me and Chizu backing her up.
So setting aside the rumor about me...
A lot of the rumors about Chizu were actually true but greatly exaggerated.
So I figure it was someone from the same school he was in.
I wonder what she'd do if Kazehaya found out.
I wonder.
Well, you can't really doubt someone without any evidence.
I suppose.
We've been talking for a while.
Really.
Maybe we should go; the game's starting.
Well, good luck.
Yeah, you too.
Thanks.
Oh yeah,
Sawako's not easy, is she?
She's seriously upfront.
Kazehaya's playing next too?
He's got more than one.
He's in the committee too.
What are you doing afterwards, Ryu?
Eat lunch then nap.
Lunch now?
And a siesta?
Garbage?
My nap...
What's up, Ryu?
Oh well, I'll nap outside.
Outside? Where?
Around the gym storage room?
W-Why there?
Who cares?
Not easy?
I just miscalculated a little.
Good work!
Here, towels.
Thanks, Sadako.
How was I?
You were awesome.
And really red.
I'm flattered.
Is “red” a compliment to you?
So what now? Lunch?
Yeah.
Sure.
I'm hungry.
Me too.
I have to go somewhere.
Where?
Sanada-kun helped me when I was about to get hit by a ball.
I want to thank him.
Ryu did?
He's not all bad after all.
And there's something I want to find out.
I don't really understand it myself either,
and I don't know how to explain it,
but...
Can you hear me out once I know?
I'm confused, but—
Sure, of course.
Thanks.
See you.
Sawako,
don't get thrown off.
Just do what you feel is right for you.
What?
What was that about?
I bet Sawako has a lot to think about.
Like?
And we have some work to do too.
Yano-chin looks evil.
Sawako-chan.
Kurumi-chan.
Did you see Sanada?
I saw him just now.
What's with that face?
You talked to me!
I thought I said something bad to you.
Geez, you're annoying.
Sanada-kun was awesome.
S-Sanada-kun went to the gym storage room.
Thanks, Kurumi-chan.
It's not like she's a strong rival, but she's a real pain.
S-Sanada-kun...
Hey, you're here.
Eh? I'm here?
Kuro—
Kuronuma, Sawako.
You got it. Wow.
No, I just read this.
Huh?
Wow, why does this letter say exactly what I had in mind?
Hey, thanks for saving my life earlier.
Now I can continue living.
I doubt that ball had that much force.
Have this.
You're giving it to me?
Is that it?
Oh yeah, I wanted to talk to you.
About?
About...
Do you know anything about romance?
Romance?
So, like, when you like someone not just as friends but as someone special—
Yeah, you don't need to explain.
Yeah, I do.
I'm all about Chizuru.
Don't tell anyone.
I think you'd make a perfect couple.
You're flattering me.
Kazehaya...
Kurumizawa.
Looks tough.
You want some help?
This is—
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I was just thinking, Kuronuma would be like, “This is my work.”
Hey, Kazehaya...
Is it true that you rejected Sawako-chan before summer break?
Huh?
People are still saying that?
I never did.
Really?
She never confessed to me to begin with.
It's not like she likes me anyway.
You're right.
She said “no way” when I asked her if she wanted to go out with you.
It didn't look like she cared about you earlier anyway.
Earlier?
During softball.
She was staring at Sanada.
You couldn't help but fall in love with someone, if they saved you like that.
Let's cheer her on if she likes him, okay?
Since when have you liked Yoshida-san?
When was it again?
Was there a reason?
Why was it?
How did you know she was special?
Do I have to answer logically?
She was always special to me by the time I knew it.
I can't compare her to anyone else.
D-Does it make her special if you can't compare her?
Dunno.
Should it?
See, let's cheer her on.
I felt strongly, very strongly.
Next episode: Love