Oh yeah, did you hear about class D?
About the test?
The Sadako Notes right?
Yeah, the Sadako Notes.
Crap, I sort of want them too.
Me too.
Kurumi.
Sorry, did I keep you waiting?
No, not at all.
That's good.
You're so nice.
There've been lots of rumors about Sadako lately.
Especially since what happened last time.
What's she really like anyway?
It's so weird.
I remember seeing her with Kazehaya.
Oh yeah.
I wonder if they're going out? Just kidding!
No way!
I wonder.
I can imagine him liking her.
No way, no way!
You know what he's like, he can't help but be nice.
If anything it would be you.
Yeah right.
Why not? You two are so close.
That's just because we were in the same middle school.
You should just go out with him.
No.
You might not like him, but he might start liking you.
Lately,
some strange things have been happening around me.
It's Sadako.
Hey, come on, make a funny face.
Funny face?
Like this?
What do you think?
U-Uh...
No good.
Darn.
I'm so surprised and I can't explain it,
but I'm happy that I'm not being avoided.
Oh, that.
They're saying good things happen when you laugh.
Good things?
No one's ever said that about me.
Good for you.
I'm going to laugh!
Hey, come on.
Say something funny to her.
Pops yelled at me for drinking pop!
That was a failure.
In more ways than one.
Why do you look like that when you smile?
Morning.
Morning!
Good morning, Yano-san, Yoshida-san.
You're totally friends with Hirano-chan and Endou-chan now, Sadako.
F-Frie—
Yup.
We are.
By the time we noticed...
I'm so happy.
This is the best time of my life.
Hey, can I call you by your first name?
Your last names are long.
Sure.
Call me Ekko.
I'm Tomo.
You can call us Chizu or Yano-chin or Ayane or whatever.
Okay.
Chizu-chan and Ayane-chan.
Thanks for filling in for me.
That was smooth.
Huh?
What was?
That's how you start calling each other by your first names.
I learned something new.
This isn't smooth.
Usually it just sort of happens.
Do you even know?
Ekko.
Tomo.
Chizu.
Ayane.
We're talking to you too.
Me too?
Come on.
Try it.
Ayane-chan.
There you go.
C-C-C-C-Chizu-chan.
That's a lot of "Ahs" and "Chis."
E-E-Ekko-chan.
T-T-Tomo-chan.
That's fresh!
I'm sort of happy.
They're happy for me.
You're stiff enough as it is.
Why don't you start calling the girls by their first name?
By their first names?
Isn't that rude?
I think it's okay.
You're really awkward, aren't you?
I guess it'll take a while.
Start with your close friends, maybe.
Here comes a good practice target.
Practice target?
Morning.
Try calling him by his first name.
Y-Y-Y-Yano-san.
Yano-san?
A-A-A-Ayane-chan.
That's too much.
You think you can fit in with everyone like that?
Yano-chin's so sadistic.
Weren't you going to try harder?
Morning.
Hey, Kazehaya.
Sadako's...
Kazehaya.
That's his last name.
Hey, what's up?
-kun.
Kun?
See, I told you, it's too hard on guys.
That's why I said to start with the girls.
Yeah right...
I'm so nervous.
Right, start with the girls.
Okay.
I'll do it.
I'll talk to the guys like normal for now.
Oh, you made her do it.
Guys.
He talks nicely to everyone, regardless of gender,
like Yano-san and Yoshida-san do for me.
Kuronuma going "Kazehaya," huh?
Kazehaya-kun's a guy.
I was wondering what you were going to say.
He's different from Yano-san and Yoshida-san.
He's really...
a guy.
We're choosing the sports day committee today.
It's too much work. The P.E. committee can do it.
All right, done.
That's me!
Kazehaya, you're screwed.
He didn't even let anyone volunteer.
By the way, I'm also the committee representative.
You better show up, or I'll tell everyone about your embarrassing—
I'll go.
I get it, I'll go.
Listen up.
You kids better win.
We're kind of short on people, so if you end up competing in more than one sport you need to be athletic.
If you've been in an event before, you need to be in it again.
If you're slow, you better not come.
You're excused from school.
Asshole.
And so...
I can barely control myself,
I'm bursting with excitement!
It's the twice-a-year festival in my name.
That's the spirit!
For victory!
Beat them all!
Whatever.
I better not drag them down.
Kuronuma, can you play soccer?
Not at all.
Seriously?
You look pretty slow.
I'll do my best.
Don't bother.
You can take the day off.
Why don't we practice during lunch then?
Sounds good.
Roger.
That'd help.
We'll do our best.
We will.
Practice for sports day, huh?
I don't feel like it, but it'll probably be fun with Kazehaya.
Kazehaya didn't even have a chance to say no before he got chosen.
I know.
We have homeroom next, right?
Yeah.
I wonder if we're going to choose sports day events.
Oh yeah, Kazehaya's going to be the committee member representing class D.
Really?
You should join.
Me?
Yeah, it'll be good.
Do it.
You might even end up going out.
No way.
I told you, that wouldn't happen.
I don't mind joining the committee though.
Do it, then.
But I can't volunteer.
I'm too shy.
We'll nominate you.
She's getting embarrassed.
Here it comes!
Sadako.
Okay.
Huh?
I thought so.
I guess we can't throw you in at the deep end.
We should start you off with kicking first.
I'm sorry.
We all sort of expected it.
She should just laugh it off.
She might even scare the opponents that way.
Maybe she'll bring us good luck and we'll win.
Chizu-chan.
We better head back, we're going to be late for fifth period.
Seriously?
Lunch break is too short.
But the clubs use the fields after school.
It's only practice and I'm already dragging them down.
I can't use up their precious time.
I need to practice alone.
I need a ball.
What are you mumbling about? You're creepy.
She's chanting something.
Let's go.
The guys are still playing.
Over there.
It's Kazehaya-kun.
What the hell?
It's like he's chilling as usual.
Looks fun.
I've never seen him exercising.
I wonder what he looks like playing softball.
We better go back.
We're going to be late for fifth period.
Okay.
We're heading back.
Pigtails.
Let's go, Kazehaya.
Yeah.
Sadako?
Kuronuma Sawako.
What's up with you?
We're going back.
Your face is so red.
Really?
Did you run that much?
Not really.
Huh?
Was there anything special?
I wasn't even close to him.
He just walked back.
I just couldn't stop watching him.
All rise.
Bow.
Done!
Let's go eat, Yano-chin.
You too, Sadako.
How about ramen?
No.
I'm going to get fat hanging out with you.
Anyway, didn't you need to go shopping?
Yeah, I need a red t-shirt,
so that I stand out on sports day.
You're coming too, right, Sadako?
I have to water the plants and stuff.
Some other time, maybe.
Really?
We can go shopping after that.
It'll be faster if we help.
It's fine, not today.
But I might...
ask some other time.
Sure, we'll do it.
Shopping too, then.
Okay.
Knowing them, they'd probably help me with practice too.
I'll ask you when you're not busy.
Thanks.
What are you doing later, Kazehaya?
It's Kazehaya-kun.
Seriously, what am I doing?
What?
You want to borrow the soccer ball?
Yes.
Please.
Can't do that.
It's not for personal use.
Can't you make an exception?
I'll bring it back, I swear.
I said no.
So much for that plan.
I guess I'll have to buy my own ball.
I'll use my New Year's gift money.
Is this good?
I think so.
This is where I first talked to Kazehaya-kun.
Huh, you're a committee member too?
Oh, you too?
Let's make the best of it.
Tough luck, huh?
This seat's empty.
Thanks.
Oh yeah, thanks for the CD.
You're welcome.
There's one I want to borrow off of you too.
Sure, I'll bring it here.
Yay!
That album I lent you before the last one—
Are you listening, Kazehaya?
My bad, what were you saying?
That CD before the one I lent you.
Okay, I'll bring it next time.
Where the heck are you going?
Huh, what time is it?
This way.
I don't get it.
I can't really smile.
Something's different about the wind.
So reach him,
in place of my smile.
I don't get it.
Why does my heart ache?
Next episode: New Friends