Time flies.
It's already late November.
There's only one month left of this busy, dizzy second semester.
Morning, Sawako.
Chizu-chan.
Did I scare you?
Yeah.
That was the friendliest morning greeting I've ever had.
I'll do it every day if you want.
Really?
Really.
Chizu-chan, you seem happy today.
Yeah?
You know, it's cold today.
It's almost New Year's, huh?
Almost?
Yeah, almost.
It's still November.
Morning, Kazehaya.
Good Morning.
It's cold today.
He's wearing a blazer.
So why are you so happy?
So fresh. Ever since spring.
Did you notice my bedhead?
Oh yeah.
You didn't notice?
Oh. I should have just pretended that's how I wanted it then.
Kazehaya.
Come here, you gotta see this.
See what?
Later.
Bedhead?
It was cute.
What is it?
They're selling Ogura flavor.
It's a juice box sampling.
I like it when he's with people.
Eww.
He looks like he's having so much fun.
Oh yeah, I used to think,
“Wow, everyone's gathering around him.”
“I wish I could be like Kazehaya-kun.”
You're all red.
Time flies.
I think my feelings are moving forward as well, step by step.
Bah.
Dammit, he's getting annoying.
Boyfriend?
Yeah.
That college student?
Day in, day out, all day, every day...
“What are you doing?”
“Who are you with?”
“Let's meet up.”
“Why don't you answer right away?”
“Why can't you come out?”
“Are you with a guy?”
I wake up, come to school and attend class with my classmates, dammit!
And at night, I sleep.
You do.
Why are you going out with a guy like that?
He picked me up.
Why do I always get picked up by the kind of guy who acts like a big grown-up only at first?
I used to think hanging out with girls was a pain in the ass.
Now I think guys are.
Is that how it normally is?
No, I think there's a serious mess.
He must be crazy about her.
I guess everyone's relationship is different.
Ryu.
I'm coming over tonight, be home.
Let me play the rest of that game from last time.
Sure, I guess.
Or do you want to play against me?
Hell no.
Chizu-chan and Sanada-kun sort of have the same air about them.
I'm all about Chizuru.
Perfect!
There aren't too many couples this perfect.
I wonder what Chizu-chan thinks.
Does she like Sanada-kun?
Hey old man, busy day?
Yo, Chizu-chan.
It's so cold.
Oh yeah, I'll help with the store during the winter.
Awesome.
You're our poster girl after all.
Yeah, I guess.
I'm heading upstairs.
But damn man,
I wish you were my daughter.
I would be if I could.
You getting ready to sleep?
You're late.
I said I'm coming.
Shoot, I died!
Damn lion!
You mean chimera.
I just remembered you talking in your sleep.
I don't talk in my sleep.
That lion... that lion... chimera...
Oh yeah,
Isn't there anything you want?
Under 500 yen.
New mitts.
Under 500 yen!
Anything other than a shoulder massage coupon.
Anything's fine. Thanks.
I never said I'm giving you anything.
Yeah, thanks.
I'm going home.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, on New Year's...
Never mind, forget it.
Good night.
What the...
So that's what she wanted.
Hello?
Yeah, Dad's taking a bath.
Next week?
I'll have to tell her.
Sawako, Yano-chin, come shopping with me.
Shopping?
I can't.
Why not?
I'm seeing my boyfriend.
I want to see him as soon as possible.
See you.
I have time.
Really? Yay.
What are you buying?
Ryu's birthday present.
It's coming up soon.
That's good.
You know how I'm kinda loyal.
Let me go!
Calm down, Joe.
She's always giving me the look!
You mean you are.
You don't even know her name, do you?
Do you believe in destiny?
Do you hear our destiny stepping towards us?
I love you too.
Who are you?
Stand!
Stand up!
Stand up, Joe!
What did you give him last year?
I didn't have money, so I gave him a shoulder massage coupon.
Shoulder massage coupon?
He used it all up right there.
Three hours of shoulder massage.
She cares for him so much.
My budget's 500 yen this year.
Perfect!
I can't get him new mitts, but a glove pouch...
Hold on to this.
I have enough.
I'm shocked too.
All right, I'm gonna spend some money on him this year.
Love!
That was an impulsive buy.
I'm so glad for you, Chizu-chan.
Miniskirts?
I thought maybe for a change.
Ramen, ramen...
I want to hear...
Should I ask?
Should I not?
But I feel like I could ask.
Hey Chizu-chan,
is there someone you like?
I did it!
That was random.
Yeah.
It's always been a crush, though.
A-Always?
I've had a crush for ages.
Could it be...
I've known him since we were little.
I knew it!
He only thinks of me like a little sister, though.
That's not true.
Why?
...I think.
It's all right, don't worry.
I'm just a kid.
He's not even going to look at me yet.
So I'm going to become an awesome woman.
Who knows once I'm grown up, right?
I'm so glad I asked.
I've never seen her like this.
But it sort of sucks that I don't get to meet him often.
He lives in Sapporo. Too bad.
He didn't come back for the Obon festival last year, so I haven't seen him in like a year.
But I just know he'll be back for New Year's.
Just watch, I'm a high schooler now!
I'm getting confused.
Is it okay if I just ask straight out?
What?
It's Sanada-kun that you like, right?
Sawako, are you talking about Ryu?
No way.
Ryu's important to me, like a brother.
I seriously wouldn't mind being his sister.
Sister? Brother?
It's Ryu's brother that I like.
I'm embarrassed.
Hey,
does Sanada-kun know?
Of course he knows.
Oh, he does.
Why?
Nothing.
It's nothing.
Shout, Sanada.
Yes!
You too.
Go!
You were still there?
I was cheering up Joe and Tanaka and the lot.
That guy's so wild.
So we're getting together to cheer Joe up.
Are you free next weekend?
Next week?
I can't, not next week.
Is something happening?
Well...
My brother's coming home.
How's this?
Looks so cold.
You must have guts to wear that.
Bring it on!
Chizu-chan's shining.
She's a girl.
She must be happy to meet someone she likes.
Morning, Ryu.
Morning.
M-Morning.
Hey Kazehaya, what do you think of this?
What, winter clothes?
Yeah, the miniskirt.
How much is it?
15,000—Oh shit.
I don't have money.
I wanted it for New Year's.
You're getting some for your New Year's allowance.
What if Tohru's here only on New Year's Eve or New Year's Day?
Huh?
So that's his name.
I never said anything.
Did I?
I think so?
What's the fuss?
Hey, Yano-chin.
We broke up.
You got dumped?
I dumped him.
It wasn't easy, you know.
I can tell.
I told him straight up.
Sorry, I'm sorry.
You're all I have.
Let's live together.
Okay, Ayane?
This guy didn't hear a thing I said.
I didn't like him after all.
He's too annoying.
I thought you were meeting him for some quality time together.
After what I told you? How?
I can't think of any words of consolation.
Not that this is what I wanted.
Yano-chin.
Why are you acting like I just got dumped?
I just got rejected too!
We're both heartbroken!
I'm not like you.
Breaking up is part of dating, but it still sucks.
I said I dumped him.
You don't have to act tough.
Ryu.
You haven't told her yet.
I couldn't.
Would you tell her?
Huh? Me?
I might.
It's not for me to decide what to do after that.
I thought that's what you'd say.
Yeah, I guess.
It'd end up like a really bad drama if she saw my brother without knowing the truth.
But I can't.
A miniskirt? For New Year's?
Sounds good.
Yeah?
How about a frilly one...
How about one that'll look good on you?
It wouldn't look good on me?
Girl talk!
I wonder what your crush is like.
Can we come too?
That's embarrassing.
Chizu-chan looks so happy.
I'm getting all hyped up while Yano-chin's upset.
It's fine.
Sorry, Yano-chin.
Cheer up!
Let's meet at my place to cheer you up.
Fine, fine.
You can sleep over.
You should come too, Sawako.
Sleep over? Me too?
Let's all play against each other!
G-Game?
Chizuru, it's me.
I'm coming in.
At least wait 'til I say so.
What if I was changing?
Right back at you.
What's up?
You don't come too often.
Here.
Aren't you having any?
Hey...
That was close.
What?
Nothing.
Hey, Chizuru...
Go.
Huh?
Just go.
But I have to—
Go!
Well, damn.
I was always busy just trying to talk to people.
I'd never had time to think about relationships.
Relationships must be just as hard as friendships.
It must be because I like Kazehaya-kun, that I can tell.
Crumbling smiles, never tarnished.
Next episode: Dream