It's Sanada and Sawako-chan.
See? Look.
Let's cheer her on.
It was the first time.
Whether it wasn't...
Or whether it was... I don't know.
But if I were to be allowed to have a wish come true,
I'd wish it was love.
I'd hope it was love.
I really, really would.
Why?
Oh well.
Why?!
What?
Kurumi? That rumor?
Probably.
That bitch!
Well, wait up.
No fair, Yano-chin.
Why didn't you tell me?
You see...
Wait, why Kurumi?
Yeah, about that,
Kurumi should be thankful of me.
Why is she trying to screw me over?
Yeah, you see...
Oh, do you think...
What? Tell me, I guess.
This is just my guess, but...
You know how I'm pretty sharp, right?
I've always had a feeling...
I think she likes Ryu.
I bet she's got the wrong idea.
You know, I'm like Ryu's sister.
Kurumi huh? Kurumi...
Sort of lame, her getting jealous of me.
You idiot!
What?
Come on, it's obvious she's liked Kazehaya the whole time.
Why?
So you never noticed.
Sorry.
I couldn't take it anymore.
I got worried.
I couldn't help it.
My body...
I'm shaking.
Kuronuma...
Do you like Ryu?
Like?
Like...
Like!
I don't know what to do.
I just like Kazehaya-kun that much.
I love Kazehaya-kun.
I-I don't have romantic feelings for Sanada-kun.
He's nice, and he helped me,
but, but...
It's not romance.
No, it's not.
It's not?
No.
I'm going to believe you.
Seriously?
Don't look at me right now,
I'm really embarrassed.
Did I say something horribly rude about Sanada-kun?
Wait, but, as a person,
I admire him,
I mean, he's a good person.
So I—
It's fine.
Sorry.
It's okay now.
But...
Isn't this what it means to like someone?
This feeling I have towards Kazehaya-kun.
It's all love, right?
Geez.
And I wanted to be the one helping you.
I'm a hypocrite, huh?
I might not be able to cheer for you all the time from now on.
Sorry if that happens.
I'm really not who you think I am.
I'm really self-centered.
Really selfish.
It's okay.
Selfish or self-centered, do anything for me or don't,
it's okay.
Hey, by the way,
what do you think about going out?
Going out where?
No, I mean, as boyfriend and girlfriend.
That's so grown-up, really.
You're so grown-up.
I can't even begin to imagine it; it's totally alien to me.
I don't have a clue.
She's probably never even imagined going out with someone.
Well, whatever.
Not right now.
I still don't get it!
So wait, if she likes Kazehaya, then why would she help out someone who likes him?
Like I said, she doesn't want him to have a girlfriend.
The whole point was to make that stupid pact.
That's why she set up all those decoys.
I'm totally confused.
I guess you don't have to get it.
Hey, Ryu.
Ryu, Sadako was looking for you.
Yeah, I met her already.
She called me out.
Called you out?
I don't think this is from her, though.
What's that?
T-This obviously isn't Sadako's writing.
Did you find that in your shoebox?
Yeah, I did.
Did someone come when you were with Sawako?
Shouta and um... that long-haired girl with the summer-ish sounding name.
Kurumi.
Oh yeah?
What's with that evil grin, Yano-chin?
I was right all along.
I don't know what's going on, but let's go to Kurumi!
Wait.
What? Why are you stopping me?
No fair, Yano-chin.
Why do you know things that I don't?
I was keeping quiet until I was confident because I knew you'd run off like that.
Let's go then, you have confidence now right?
Not yet.
We need more evidence.
Evidence?
Yeah.
Evidence that Kurumi could never dismiss.
And then I'll pound her into a pulp!
Scary.
Why aren't you coming back, Kazehaya?
I should have gone after him and interrupted.
But that would have annoyed him.
He wouldn't go out with her, would he?
Kazehaya, come back, please.
Ka—
Ka?
Go!
It's that creepy...
What are you doing here?
I was just cleaning this up.
Hurry up and do it then.
I made a mistake.
Another member has the keys.
I'm waiting for them.
Keys?
I have the keys, hurry up and put it away.
Why aren't you leaving?
I, uh...
Why don't you go already? Kazehaya's going to come back.
Why is she squirming?
Why is she everywhere I am?
Why is she leading me on?
It must be...!
Sorry, I'm not into kids.
I know how you feel.
I would have fallen for me if I was a woman too.
Well, to put it this way, you're 10 years early.
You get it, right?
What are you—
Why do I have to get rejected here?
By him of all people?
Settle for some brat from your own class or something.
Sorry, I didn't mean to eavesdrop.
No!
I know.
I won't tell anyone, trust me.
That's not—
Shouta, you damn brat!
You're slacking, aren't you?
Oh, shit!
Perfect. I'll find you some really hard work.
Give me a break.
Kazehaya, no!
Oh, yeah.
Forget about me.
Don't go telling people, Pin.
Who asked for your opinion?
No!
That rumor?
It was like, by the time we knew, everyone was talking about it.
We wouldn't know if it was her that started it.
Okay.
Sorry I can't help.
No one really remembers, huh?
Maybe we should hit up division A.
I guess.
It's Tomo and Ekkou.
Okay, let's try asking them.
Seriously?!
Yeah, I saw her making rumors.
Kurumi? For sure?
She's with Kazehaya sometimes.
It's her for sure.
Right?
Yeah.
That was the first time I heard rumors about Sadako.
I remember being surprised at how bad the rumor's gotten.
Thanks, Tomo, Ekkou.
Awesome, Yano-chin, now—
I got you, Kurumi, you bitch.
There it is! Yano-chin's evil-stepmother-face!
Get back, Tomo, Ekkou!
Just wait, I'll even make you fess up what brand of toner you use.
Isn't that sort of personal? Yano-chin?
Yano-san and Yoshida-san aren't here.
Oh, maybe they're at volleyball practice.
“There's someone I like.”
I wonder what they'd say if I told them that.
I can't even imagine.
What the?
Victory dance?
Shadowboxing?
The twist?
But I'm happy.
It's even better than I thought, being in a world not all by myself.
To like Kazehaya-kun,
and to be able to tell people about it,
is such a happy thing.
There's someone I like.
It's Kazehaya.
I'll tell Kurumi-chan.
Kurumi-chan told me her feelings.
I want to tell her mine too.
I just realized, we can talk about love together.
So tell me, what's this about, Kurumi-chan?
You said you never spread any rumors, didn't you?
What are you talking about?
Don't try to play dumb.
I have the girls from division A backing me up.
Damn, it's like a samurai drama!
You keep quiet, please.
Even if I did spread that rumor, that's not proof that I started it.
Is this succulent, spotless face of yours still going to talk smack?
You think I can't tell the difference between maintained skin and unmaintained skin?
Yano-chin, you're getting personal.
We asked everyone in the school.
That's such a bluff.
Kurumi's being different too.
Go, Chizu!
Listen up, Kurumizawa Ume, we checked your handwriting
and here's the proof.
So?
What? So, so...
B-But this is your writing!
Liars go to hell, you know that?
Good job, Chizu, you did well.
You seem pretty different from before.
So, about that, did it work out?
Huh?
Ayane-chan, Chizu-chan, Kurumi-chan.
Sawako...
I haven't seen you three together much.
Have you become friends?
No, we were hanging her.
Hanging?
That rumor from inside the washroom,
it was Kurumi.
Sawako, it was Kurumi that made you suffer so much.
The answer that I found and want to share.
Next episode: Kurumi