Well, I'll be going now.
Have fun.
Sawako's first sleepover...
What's your dad supposed to do?!
You don't have to do anything.
Oh yeah, I'll call you.
I'll say hi to her parents.
Be sure to give them those youkan.
Okay.
Today's my first sleepover.
I'm staying at Chizu-chan's place, together with Ayane-chan.
Chizuru...
Hey.
About tomorrow...
Morning Chizu.
Morning.
What's that, your sleepover kit?
Yeah.
What were you saying?
Never mind.
But don't come to my house tomorrow or the day after.
Don't.
What, why?
What's up with him?
What? Did you piss him off?
Dammit, Ryu!
I was so going to play games to cheer Yano-chin up.
So go ahead and do it.
But it's Ryu's game.
I was going to go to Ryu's place.
Don't you remember how you might have pissed him off?
Huh? No.
I kicked him out last time he came over, but...
Why?
He almost saw this.
That must be it.
That's it?! He's such a baby.
And now you're pissed?
Don't come to my house tomorrow or the day after.
Why? It's Ryu's birthday the day after tomorrow.
Screw this!
I can't do it!
Chizu, let's go gaming.
He didn't say not to come today, did he?
Go make up with him.
Bring him your birthday present too.
Why would he get upset over that?
Yano-chin, I love you.
There, there.
Friendship!
All-in huh? Who would have thought.
Cross-counter for the win.
I'm the boss right?
I'm the boss tonight!
And that's why you haven't told her yet, huh?
I can't find a good time.
You sure that's okay?
She can just meet my brother during New Year's.
It's not like I especially wanted him to meet Chizuru anyway.
Why's there so many of you?
What's going on?
And you?
We're here to cheer Joe up.
Yano, my break-up buddy!
I know, let's do a double cheer-up party.
Sorry, Yano-chin.
It's fine.
You know how it goes.
Two people get dumped and comfort each other, then fall in love...
Yano...
You're awesome, Joe.
Yeah.
I can be here tonight, can't I?
Yeah, I guess.
Why don't you guys shuffle over then?
Sorry.
I'm coming in.
Doesn't anyone have any good news to share?
Nope.
No way.
I guess there wouldn't be any.
Yano, why did you split up?
Stuff happens.
It's so strange.
I'm thirsty.
Sleeping at a friend's place, being with so many people, talking about love...
Yeah... oh yeah, ...
Bumping into the person I like...
All this stuff is really happening to me.
Ryu, could you get me a cup?
Their ramen's so awesome...
Hold on.
I'll go help.
And give him this.
I hope he likes it.
Yano, what's your type of guy?
A laid back, easy going, mature guy.
Ryu.
Are you mad?
Nope.
Really?
No, but...
I was a bit hurt when you kicked me out.
Sorry.
It wasn't really about you.
I just wanted to hide something.
Oh, wasn't there something you wanted to tell me?
I'm listening.
What?
Say it.
Hey,
So tired.
I'm home.
Chi!
Tohru?
Tohru!
You're so strong.
You've gotten so big.
I never knew.
My bad.
Of course it is.
Weren't you coming home tomorrow?
Yeah, I got off work early.
Could that be...
What?
Tohru, brother!
Shouta.
Your hair's gotten long.
Come on, Kazehaya.
I'm talking to him right now.
This is the person Chizu-chan likes?
Hey, girls.
Good going, Ryu.
Yeah, they're Chizuru's friends.
High school friends.
Sawako and Yano-chin.
Come here.
Hey, not bad.
Hide Yano!
Put her in the closet!
I'm kidding.
You haven't changed, Chi.
I'm in pajamas and jeans!
I should have worn my old miniskirt!
Hey Ryu, why haven't you told me?
Huh?
What's up? Come in.
Really? Can I?
Well, duh.
Is there any more luggage?
I got everything else.
Evening.
G-Good evening.
Girlfriend?
Yeah.
We're getting married.
Nice to meet you.
Married?!
Chizu, get a grip.
Hey, Chizu.
This kid's my brother, Ryu.
I'm his brother.
Katayama Haruka.
I'll introduce her too.
Yoshida Chizuru-chan.
I call her Chi.
I've loved her like a little sister since she was young.
Katayama. Nice to meet you.
I, uh...
I'm from the neighborhood, my name's Yoshida.
I'm not really family or a relative or anything, but yeah.
Hi.
Likewise, hi.
Don't be so cold, Chi.
Married?
Come in.
Ryu,
let's call it a day.
Tohru's back home, after all.
Yoshida, you too.
Let's all go.
Oh, right.
We sort of came here at an important time.
Hey you, outsiders, let's get out of here.
Already? I'm not boss anymore?
You're an outsider too.
That's why we're all going.
Thanks for the company.
Later.
See you.
Chi,
take care.
You haven't changed.
I live right there.
I'm strong anyway.
Let's go.
I wonder what she's thinking right now.
Later.
Shouta, what do you think?
What if I'd said something?
She'd be uncomfortable if she thought I told her because I was being nice to her.
I wouldn't mind her getting angry, but I think she'd be sad.
You've been worried about Yoshida the whole time.
It's not your fault, cheer up.
I'm not upset or anything.
I don't know.
Was I really worried?
I think you were.
I guess he must like Yoshida.
Oh man, I win again.
We've been playing for four hours straight now.
What's next?
Chizu,
are you okay?
Oh.
About Tohru.
Actually I haven't even said congratulations to him yet.
I guess I'll go see him tomorrow.
My beloved brother-like friend's getting married.
That's it.
There's more fish in the sea.
Oh, whoops.
Yeah.
Sorry I ended up getting us all kicked out
We were supposed to cheer you up.
Don't worry about that.
Look at the time.
Maybe we should sleep.
I've had a crush for ages.
He's not even going to look at me yet.
So I'm going to become an awesome woman.
Who knows once I'm grown up, right?
It's Ryu's brother that I like.
Chizu-chan.
She's already up.
Did I wake you up?
I'm wearing a miniskirt!
Maybe she didn't wake up.
Maybe she didn't sleep to begin with.
Nice sweater, right?
It's a hand-me-down from my brother.
There's a hole here, but whatever.
See you at school.
I thought she'd bitch and moan like always.
I couldn't tell if she was sad or not at first.
Dammit.
Is there anything we can do?
In this situation?
We can't even hear her out.
I don't think there's anything we can do.
She was so happy to wear a miniskirt.
We couldn't cheer her up or anything.
I had no words for her.
Nothing.
Me neither.
Of all times, this time I had nothing to say.
What are friends supposed to do when this happens?
The old man's having a blast.
Like a daughter? Except not.
Like a younger sister? Except not.
Not a relative or anything.
What's some kid from the block doing here on such an important occasion?
Kid from the block.
Let's fight, Ryu!
I'll kill you if you don't hit me with all you've got!
Ow.
Don't make girls cry, Ryu.
Bye bye boo boo!
Tohru, look, I have a bug!
Tohru, bugs!
Tohru!
Bugs!
Why bugs?
Why did I express my love with bugs?
But...
Nice, Chi.
Tohru'd always laugh about it.
Tohru often had a girlfriend with him,
but it never really lasted.
I always thought he was just dating.
So my dream was always to marry him.
I guess I'm not the one to realize that dream.
Feelings unconveyed, tears overflowing.
Next Episode: Present