It happened!
It actually happened!
Dad,
thanks.
Sawako...
Weren't you shocked?
And upset?
You're still happy even if it's from me?
Sawako went to get the newspaper.
Today is December 25th.
The day of the closing ceremony.
Man, that was crazy yesterday.
Yeah, that Sadako.
She showed up for the second half of the party yesterday...
Yoshida handed her the mic, she sang one song and left.
And is it just me, or did she come with Kazehaya?
No, I think so too.
But... no way.
You're all stupid.
I invited her.
Kazehaya lost to me in a game yesterday, so he had to wait for her.
Sawako didn't know where the second half of the party was.
Oh, no wonder.
Not done yet.
There's still tasty stuff like Valentine's Day coming up.
I can't let you ruin it with your antics.
What's this bad feeling I'm getting?
Besides, Sawako isn't even there yet.
She might go on about
“Kazehaya's reputation” and stuff again.
Morning.
M-Morning.
They responded!
Kazehaya...
You're here early.
I'm always early.
Yeah right.
It's a belly warmer.
I made it stitch by stitch, thinking of my dad.
Oh, it's not for me.
I accidentally swapped it with what I was going to give you.
If you don't mind, could you give it to your dad or mom or grandpa—
But I can have it too, right?
Thanks.
He's so nice.
He probably won't even wear it.
But he took it anyway.
I guess he won't wear the cap either, though.
Morning.
M-Morning.
It wasn't the same to me.
I made it with different feelings, but...
It's snowing pretty hard today.
A necktie?
It's the closing ceremony today.
Even snappier than usual.
Morning!
Morning, Chizu-chan.
Morning, Sawa.
Morning.
Morning, Yano-chin, Kazehaya.
The cold hasn't gotten to you at all, has it?
Oh yeah, the closing ceremony.
I guess winter break starts tomorrow.
It'll get a bit lonely.
Long time no see, everyone.
Who are you?
What are you waiting for? Hurry up.
Zen! It's Zen!
Our homeroom teacher.
Long time no see!
So here's the news.
I'm going to be running my wife's family's brewery.
So today's my last day teaching here.
What the hell?
Weren't you sick?
Sick?
I thought something bad happened.
No no, the brewery's doing great, and things are going well with my in-laws.
He's a gold-digger?
Arai-sensei...
What about your farewell party? Let's have one.
Thanks, but I have to go home right away.
I won't forget the time we had together.
Zen!
Why don't we have a “worship your new teacher, Pin” party then?
Anyway, let's line up in the hallway for the closing ceremony.
Single file!
So much has happened—
She's so cute even when she's making faces.
—this second semester.
Winter break is starting.
Don't get too excited.
Be safe,
and we'll see you in good health next year.
There was really so much that happened.
Some painful things,
but so many more happy things.
This is from all of us.
K-Kuronuma, huh?
It's alright, she's an exorcist.
All rise.
I don't look any different,
Bow.
but so much of what I thought about and experienced was new to me.
Yay, winter break tomorrow!
Hey, let's go eat somewhere.
Sure.
Where should we go?
Kazehaya, let's go karaoke.
We just went yesterday.
I won't see him after this, until the third semester.
Thanks for everything this year.
I had a lot of fun.
Kazehaya, come on.
He's going.
Something short, umm...
Bye bye.
H-Happy new year.
See you next year.
Nice, your dad's awesome.
Did you set up e-mail?
I haven't read the whole manual yet.
You're going to read the whole thing?
Don't bother.
I'll do it, here.
Thank you.
What address do you want?
Make it long so that you don't get spammed.
Name, birthday, stuff like that.
Wow, that'll help fix the misunderstandings too.
Wait, your birthday's on New Year's Eve?
Chizu-chan, Ayane-chan, um...
Do you think we could meet over the winter holiday too?
When you're bored.
When you're really bored.
Only if you don't mind.
You idiot, of course we can.
You scared me, why would you bring that up now?
We can get in contact easier now too.
I don't have to wait until the third semester!
I always go to the shrine with Ryu on New Year's.
You guys want to join us this year?
Sure.
I can see everyone on New Year's.
I want to go!
Wait, I'll check.
So fast.
With Chizu-chan and Ayane-chan? Sounds good.
Ask Dad when he gets home.
He feels bad about yesterday. He won't say no.
Yes!
Was it that bad yesterday?
I get to see them,
on New Year's Eve.
On my 16th birthday.
I get to be with everyone.
Do you have Kazehaya's phone number?
I got it when I met him yesterday.
Have you called him yet?
I don't have a reason to.
You do now.
At this rate, it'll be just Chizu, Ryu, you and me.
I don't mind, but if you want to see Kazehaya, you better invite him yourself.
Invite him?
You better call him now, or he'll have different plans.
I'm not forcing you.
Just if you want to see him.
If I don't call him now, I won't see him until the third semester.
I-I don't know his email address.
So I'll call.
Hello? It's Kuronuma.
New Year's Eve Festival.
Breathe.
Now I'm getting nervous too.
It'll be nice if I can see him.
I'll be so happy.
Go me.
Hello?
I-It's me, Kuronuma.
Do you want to come to the New Year's Festival at the shrine?
It'll be Chizu-chan, Ayane-chan, Sanada-kun and me.
I'm bored.
I mean, if you're bored.
I'll come.
Yoshida, Yano, Ryu and you, right?
I won't get in your way.
I'll come.
I'm looking forward to it.
He says he's looking forward to it.
That's good.
Of course he is.
I'll get to see him.
On my birthday, too.
I get to see him.
Now then...
...what's the plan?
It's like a dream.
Time flies, and it's December 31st.
Don't worry about cleaning up.
Aren't Chizu-chan and Ayane-chan coming soon?
Right, it's not good to make your friends wait.
Okay, thanks.
I'll wear the poncho you got me.
New Year's Eve Festival with your friends, huh?
Huh? Chizu-chan and Ayane-chan are friends, but Sanada-kun and Kazehaya-kun... are they my friends?
Especially Kazehaya-kun.
We're here.
Good evening.
You're here early.
Come in.
Thanks.
I'll go get my coat.
Actually, can we come up to your room?
Sure.
Huh?
W-What's happening?
Don't move.
Sorry.
Don't worry.
You can hardly tell you're wearing anything.
Okay, eyelids.
Like this?
Don't close your eyes.
You wished you were cute when you met Kurumi, didn't you?
Think about why you want to be cute.
Done.
Almost done here too.
This is from Yano-chin and me.
Happy birthday, Sawako.
Cute.
We're awesome.
Nice.
That hairpin looks good on you too.
Stop!
Don't cry! Don't!
I'm not going to ruin their efforts.
She's even scarier with make-up.
Thanks.
I'm so, so happy.
So many good things happened since I met you two this year.
Okay...
We're pretty close to where we're supposed to meet.
Let's go, Chizu.
Good thinking, Yano-chin.
We'll get going now.
Have fun with Kazehaya.
Wait, where are you going?
Don't worry about us.
Ryu's not coming either, by the way.
Give us a status report later.
Why so serious? You're the one that invited him.
This is why Chizu-chan and Ayane-chan wanted to make me as cute as they could.
Ryu's not here yet.
Where's Yoshida and Yano?
They're not coming.
Neither is Sanada-kun.
I wonder if I disappointed him.
Is he upset?
He might leave.
Let's go.
December 31st.
Thirty minutes until the new year.
Words woven
on a night lit by snow.
Next episode: Birthday