You wished you were cute when you met Kurumi, didn't you?
Think about why you want to be cute.
Happy birthday, Sawako.
Ryu's not here yet.
Where's Yoshida and Yano?
They're not coming.
Neither is Sanada-kun.
Let's go.
He's not looking my way.
But I don't think I dare look either.
Look out!
T-They're stone steps.
I-I know; I didn't even s-see them.
What the hell are they doing?
Dammit, they're slow.
Chizu, call.
I'm on it.
Why did we change our meeting spot? Why are we here?
Shh, be quiet.
Hello?
Hey, Kazehaya, it's me.
Yoshida?
Where are you?
Chizu-chan?
You're too loud.
Sorry!
We couldn't make it.
Sorry.
Ryu says he's busy too.
He told me to say hi to you.
Go make our wishes for us too.
Sure.
Am I hearing things?
I bailed on Sawako too.
I bet she's not sure what to do.
I'll let you deal with it.
That's all.
Okay.
It was Yoshida.
She says she's sorry she can't make it.
Oh yeah, I still haven't explained.
I see; they're backing me up.
Aren't you cold?
There's still a lot of time until midnight.
They're giving out sweet sake over there.
Okay.
He's next to me.
They're finally walking next to each other.
They're headed for the sweet sake next. Sweet sake!
Let's catch up!
So that's why.
Bad taste.
I had plans with Shouta.
This is getting fun.
It's just getting started.
I don't mind, but I want some sweet sake.
Look at it burn!
Idiots everywhere.
Isn't that Joe?
Oh yeah.
He's embarrassing the whole class.
Creepy.
His parents look just like him.
Sweet sake...
Wait, Sawako and Kazehaya are...
Shit, they're headed straight for Joe.
Seriously?
He loves Kazehaya; he's totally going to spot him.
Shit, hurry.
Sweet sake...
Hurry, Ryu.
So warm.
Huh?
Hey, Joe.
What a coincidence, Joe.
Wait, did you all come here?
You could have invited me, Ryu.
Hey Joe, who are you with?
My parents.
Where's the usual crowd?
They're at home watching comedy and stuff.
Good, no one left to get in our way.
So where's Kazehaya?
Like, I thought I just saw Kazehaya for a second.
Kazehaya?
Kazehaya said he couldn't make it.
You're seeing things.
Really?
Shut up!
Yeah, really.
He'd be here if he came.
She's holding my arm.
I guess.
He was with some hot chick too.
Good thing he's stupid.
Yano might like me.
I want sweet sake.
He's gone.
Oh shit, I might feel her boobs.
No way in hell.
The sparks...
I'm pretty warm now.
You want to go have some sweet sake and chat?
I hate sweet sake.
No sweet sake.
Really?
Sweet sake...
It'll warm you up!
Would you like some?
Sweet sake, anyone?
Sweet sake here...
Would you like some?
It's good.
Yes please.
Two for the couple.
Couple?
Here.
Thanks.
Oh no, I'm actually happy.
That's uncalled for.
She misunderstood.
I wonder if he might be annoyed.
He probably is.
It's warm.
Maybe I'm just thinking too much of it.
I'm so embarrassed.
It's good.
Really?
This is the first time I've ever
thought sweet sake tasted good.
You didn't like sweet sake before?
Not really.
Oh really?
I'm so happy.
I've wanted to learn new things about him.
I got to see your “first ever.”
I've always wanted to.
To see something about him no one else has.
You always have.
This is my first time coming to the New Year's Festival with someone.
It's also the first time I ever bought a girl's phone strap.
Oh yeah, one more thing.
It's my first time wearing a belly warmer.
I put a hand warmer in the pocket.
My belly's all warm.
But that's my d-dad's—
Don't say it.
It's mine now.
I should have given him the cap.
No, it doesn't matter.
I wanted him to have something I chose.
Something I made.
Maybe he accepted it.
Maybe he's using it.
Kuronuma, have you chosen an e-mail address?
Y-Yes.
Can I send it to you?
I-It's my first time texting; i-it might take me a while.
Take your time.
What I want to tell him,
what I want to convey to him...
Oops!
When it comes down to it, I have too much to convey.
I don't know where or how to start.
I wish there was a way to tell him in a single word.
Sent.
I sort of wish I'd asked you for your number back then.
Not even “sort of.”
I wish I'd forced it out of you if I had to.
Got it.
sawako.not.sadako.1231
Up to three and back to one.
When's your birthday?
Today.
It's over in 15 minutes.
Oh, it is.
Barely made it.
Happy birthday.
I could have given you something if I knew sooner.
You already did.
I got to learn new things about you.
I got to see some of your “first ever” experiences.
Besides,
this is about the time that I was born.
You were with me at the moment I turned sixteen.
11:45 PM. Sixteen years old.
Fifteen minutes until the new year.
What kind of kid were you?
Nothing special,
well, I don't know.
Start from the top, then.
So you were born about this time, sixteen years ago.
It's boring.
That's fine. It's just me asking. Tell me.
It's really boring.
Sixteen years ago, I was born weighing 6.6 pounds.
I entered preschool at four,
in the Sumire and Suzuran groups.
This is when my older cousin used to call me a Zashiki Warashi.
I want coke, Zashiki Warashi.
Right away!
I wonder if I'm bragging.
I was in Ume's group in grades one and two.
How about three and four?
Matsu.
Five and six?
Take...
A good combination.
What were you in to?
In to?
In to...
Solo rope jumping, maybe.
Solo rope jumping?
I tied an elastic rope to some chairs, and jumped.
That was a big hit.
In my mind.
And solo volleyball.
And solo string figures.
Suspension bridge!
Solo speed.
Fast, so fast!
Solo...
Is that gloomy?
I think I'm going to ruin the mood again.
I'm ruining New Year's.
Not really.
I guess, if I'd heard all that when we entered school,
I might have thought you liked being alone.
But since we met,
I think you're having fun no matter what you're doing.
I just thought you're good at finding fun things to do.
It's fun imagining.
He thought that of me.
Then what?
I entered middle school when I was twelve.
Elementary's over already?
Nothing special happened.
In ninth grade I applied for Kitahoro High School, since it was nearby.
And then in the spring of my fifteenth year, I met you.
“If only I could be like Kazehaya-kun...
Maybe then something will change for me too.”
Thanks.
You've always been the first step for me.
This year was too different for me.
It'll take too long to describe.
That was the end of my year with Kazehaya-kun,
and my birthday I spent with him.
A new year was about to begin.
Next episode: New Year