Morning.
Hey.
Morning, Sadako.
Sadako, morning.
Morning, Yano-san, Yoshida-san.
Right now I'm experiencing the very thing I've always longed for!
I'm in bliss!
What's with that look?
I'll start crying if I stop contracting my eyebrow muscles.
I thought you were pissed.
Smile, if you're happy.
Never mind, you don't have to smile.
It's sort of creepy.
You definitely look gloomy.
You might as well take advantage of that appearance.
Take advantage of my appearance?
Safe.
You're safe.
Kazehaya-kun.
He's so nice.
Morning.
Ryu, you too.
M-Morning...
He's so nice.
Wait, who were you again?
Come on Ryu, she's a classmate, you should know.
I don't really leave much of an impression.
You do, in a bad way.
Kuronuma Sawako. Nice to meet you.
Sanada Ryu.
I'm bad with names.
Sorry.
So much has changed since Kazehaya-kun chose to sit next to me.
Hey,
I still can't decide on a name for the dog.
Could you pick one?
Pick one.
U-Um...
Pedro Martinez.
Pedro Martinez. Done.
Pin.
You're our sub teacher; why are you here?
Where's  Zen?
He's supposed to be our homeroom teacher.
He's got problems at home, apparently.
I'm filling in indefinitely.
Grand slam!
Problems at home? Is this because of Sadako?
Because he made her do stuff over the summer?
Pedro Martinez.
Maru-chan.
Perfect.
Oh yeah, Zen mentioned...
Kuronuma.
Yes?
See that?
I'm awesome!
Being tough again.
But it would be a good rumor if Pin survives.
That's true.
I see.
What was that supposed to be?
Kuronuma.
It's hot today.
Yeah.
What's that?
Standup comedy?
About innocence.
Why?
Why is my pulse different from when Sensei was staring at me?
I've known Ryu forever.
We were in middle school together along with Kazehaya.
I met Chizu in high school.
We sat close to each other, so we became friends.
That's great.
Speaking of Kazehaya, has he always been so cool?
Yeah, always.
He's always been nice to people who don't fit in.
And he's always the leader amongst the guys.
And popular with the girls.
He was a good person in middle school too.
There was this huge fight over him amongst the girls,
but those who realized he probably doesn't like that sort of thing
established the “Kazehaya Belongs to Everyone Accord.”
“The People's Kazehaya.”
Are you serious? That's so retarded.
Wow!
He moves people, captures their hearts and brings them to action.
Kazehaya-kun is amazing.
Because of that there's a lot of girls from our middle school here.
Like them?
Yeah, like them.
They came to see him from another class.
He's so popular.
All right,
someone stay behind after school and write up the attendance form.
Isn't that your job?
Don't push it on us.
Zen always does his.
Fine then, I'll choose.
No one wants to do it.
I'll do it.
Well that's no fun.
I'll do it too, then.
It shouldn't take long with two people.
I wouldn't mind helping if Kazehaya is doing it.
Me too, then.
Now everyone wants to do it.
I–If everyone else wants to do it...
Kuronuma.
You said you'd do it, didn't you?
Yeah.
Did I say that out loud?
What the hell? What's with this mushy stuff?
Kazehaya!
Come to the office!
We're done!
Stand.
Bow.
I'll do it too, then.
I was so happy.
One sec, I have to go to the bathroom.
Kazehaya-kun.
I slipped out while Pin went to the bathroom.
I'll help.
T-Thanks.
Thanks for everything.
You've given me all sorts of opportunities.
I had so much fun today.
I didn't really do anything.
Maybe everyone's waiting for a chance to talk to you.
Could you lend me your pen?
Can I do the rest?
Tha–
Kazehaya Shouta of 1-D, come to the office immediately!
If you don't get here within one minute,
everyone's going to know everything about your embarrassing past.
I'm out.
Sorry, Kuronuma.
I better go.
T-Thanks.
Sorry, I–
Kazehaya-kun was here, so...
Hirano-san and Endou-san.
Maybe everyone's waiting for a chance to talk to you.
Hey,
would it be okay if we talked for a bit?
I'll get set up.
It's fine.
No luck...
No luck again.
It's fine.
We'll do it.
You're not angry, are you?
Thought so.
You always look so angry, so...
I thought you liked being alone.
But you said you were happy being able to talk to Yoshida-san or something.
You always said hello to us.
So we got sort of curious and came by.
And Kazehaya said...
Why don't you come inside? Don't just stand out here.
We'll help.
You're always doing our chores anyway.
Why are you crying?
I'm so happy.
S-Seriously?
You're the sensitive type?
T-Thanks.
So what did people call you before “Sadako”?
I liked it when people called me “Zashiki Warashi.”
Zashiki Warashi is a mythical creature that brings good fortune.
You liked that? Really?
I was so freaked out when you were that ghost in the test of courage.
I honestly thought you were a real ghost.
Kazehaya-kun gave me opportunities,
and things are slowly changing around me.
Y-You're done?
Y-Yeah.
Hirano-san and Endou-san helped me out.
Seriously? Nice.
Thanks.
Thanks to Kazehaya-kun, I'm changing myself.
I think it's you giving me the strength to act.
Haven't you noticed?
Yano, Yoshida, Hirano, Endou–they're all being moved by your diligence.
You're the one moving me as well.
Me?
Moving someone like Kazehaya-kun?
I would never have thought it possible.
But I'd be so happy if it were true.
Awesome, Sadako.
I heard Hirano-chan and Endou-chan helped you out.
It's thanks to you two.
Because you both talked to me.
That's why they talked to me too.
Thanks.
You idiot!
I think she's trying to say that it's because you worked so hard.
But it's true, though, Sadako.
I'm glad things are working out for you.
I'm so lucky to have such nice people to talk to.
Anyway, what's that?
This? Horror stories.
Horror stories?
I thought that, maybe, I could live up to your expectations with this.
Sadako? Horror stories?
Actually, I kind of want to hear.
You're such a pragmatist.
Pragmatic or weird? I don't know.
Everything up until now will be on the midterm.
What are you doing, Kazehaya?
A bug—there's a bug.
It's the first time I've gotten a note. I didn't know it was for Yano-san.
Kuronuma.
My hand was shaking.
Once I'm done taking this to the office,
I'll go home, get changed…
I'm too excited.
I have to focus.
Here.
Thanks.
She looks like a French doll.
This must be the high point of my life.
Wait, Maru.
Maru-chan!
Come here.
Maru-chan.
Oh, that?
My baiting plan is a success!
Maru-chan.
He responded.
What would you usually be doing?
Studying and stuff.
I mean, not before exams.
Studying and stuff?
Wow.
I just go out.
I usually have fun fantasizing—
Wait, fantasizing?
I like imagining things.
Like, say the person next to me is having trouble.
I think, “maybe she's having trouble with this,”
or “how can I explain it so that she would understand?”
Eventually I would get a lot of studying done.
Speaking of which, have you told anyone about Maru?
No.
I see.
So then, we're the only ones who know about how we found him.
I'm not telling anyone then.
I can't be the only one who's seen him smile,
or has been smiled at by him,
but for now, I get it all to myself.
I hope tomorrow will be a good day too.
Kuronuma,
can you help me with this?
I'm the person next to you, after all.
Why isn't this “なに”, even though it's “what”?
This “what” is called a relative pronoun.
What's up with you, are you actually studying?
And these two phrases are together.
This one and this one.
Oh, I see.
Huh?
Sadako's helping them study.
Oh yeah.
So if you translate these two together...
I got it!
I actually did it.
She actually got Yoshida to answer a problem.
You're good at teaching.
Um...
Could you help us too?
I hope you don't mind.
So this works the same way...
Oh wow.
I tried so many times.
See, like this.
I get it.
You make it so easy.
She should just use the blackboard.
Thanks, Sadako.
Can you help us again sometime?
Thanks.
I've made myself useful!
You're definitely weird.
She—She's smi—
Did you see that?
K-Kazehaya-kun.
Today—
About yesterday, that was great.
All those people who helped. You got your wish.
I was happy, of course.
It came true when you asked me to help you.
You must have gotten sick of hearing it by now,
but I want to say it again.
Thanks.
Hey, Kazehaya.
Huh, he's talking to someone.
Let's go.
Sorry, I'm so selfish.
I thought I was the only one that knew.
I was a bit bummed.
So let me have this one....
...to myself.
Man, that was the first time I've ever seen her smile like that.
She looks pretty normal when she's like that.
What, really?
Yoshida's that thin-eyed girl right?
Yeah, the ex-delinquent who used to be in a detention center.
And that other Yano girl's a real slut, huh?
She did a hundred guys in middle school.
No way, that's insane.
Oh yeah?
And who told you that?
Well...
Who...
told you that.
Everyone.
Bullshit.
I'm asking you, who told you that?
Who started that rumor?
Sa-Sadako.
Words misplaced;
feelings miscommunicated.
Next episode: Rumors