watashi ga umareta asa no machi yuki no naka ni umoreta
My hometown lay buried in snow the morning I was born.
sore wa sore wa chiisai te de aozora wo aoida
I looked up at the blue sky with my tiny hands.
sanagara mukashi kara yoku shiru tonari no ano ko no you ni
The face of the girl next door that I've known so well...
katahou no mimitabu de kiku sotsugyou no canon
It's as familiar as the graduation canon.
hitori demo daijoubu yo tte mekureteru watashi no story
Thriving in solitude has been mistaken as my life story.
dareka no sei ni shitai yo
I want to blame it on someone.
tsurai naa iya iya
It's so difficult. No, I hate it.
kanashikutte naite bakkari itara me ga tokete nakunatta
Tears and sorrow caused me to miss my chance.
aki ni nari mata fuyu ni nari hitotsu toshi wo totta
Autumn passed, winter came again, and I became a year older.
tooku made nigete iru tsumori demo owaranai kimi no story
You think you've run far away, but your story never ends.
niya niya waratte iru
And yet, you're smirking.
fugainaiya iya
It's so cowardly. I hate it.
sugari nagara oikakete mitemo ashige ni saretemo
Even if I have to cling to you, chase after you, and get kicked down...
aita ana wo fusagou
...I'll close the hole that's opened...
chigai nai ya iya
...without a doubt. No...
fugainai ya iya
It's so cowardly. No...
tsurai naa iya iya
It's so difficult. I hate it. I hate it.
Turquoise for H.
Bronze for A-2.
Brownish green for three.
All right, this should be okay.
Please go with these.
Yes, thank you.
You seem busy.
What else are you working on right now?
Well, they're adding another room at the Kosouan, so I'll be making pottery for that.
Huh... the Kosouan?
Do you mean the one in Kamakura?
Yeah, it's a wonderful venue that was converted from an old private home.
You work for some amazing places.
It's all thanks to Rika-san.
She really got me a lot of connections.
Rika-san really must like your work.
Things seem like they're going well. Now is when you need to work hard, Yamada-san.
Yeah.
Rika-san is working in Spain right now...
Isn't it amazing that she gets to work at the Valencia Museum of Art?
You're right... That is amazing...
Rika-san left for Spain last week...
...but Mayama didn't go with her.
I don't know what happened between the two of them before she left.
But I can tell something has changed.
Sometimes, when she calls, a new voice, calmer and deeper than before, will flow through.
That's right.
She has opened her heart to him.
All right.
Well then, Yamada-san, shall we go somewhere nice?
I'm sorry, you're staying home, Leader.
Somewhere nice?
Yep.
Health Land
Um...
M-Miwako-san... t-this place is...?
All right, we're gonna enjoy this to the fullest!
Huh? Um...
C'mon!
But... I... Miwako-san... Um...
The rose and fruit bath really is wonderful.
A p-pineapple...
Okay... After we warm up, we're getting a body scrub!
Hi!
Welcome!
Note: They are smiling...
Is this your first time here?
We're gonna make your skin so smooth...
...so go ahead and relax!
Aren't you glad, Yamada-san?
Scrubbing in progress
Scrubbing complete
Ah, so smooth!
It feels like I have new skin.
Now then, we're off to our next stop!
Yamada-san! Isn't this one piece nice?
Or maybe I should call this a muumuu?
Y-Yeah...
Everyone here is barefoot, has no makeup on, and is wearing the same muumuu.
Isn't it nice?
Viva Health Land!
Don't you agree?
It's strange. Wearing these clothes makes me laugh.
That's right. It's basically impossible to think of sad things when you're wearing a flowery muumuu.
Miwako-san...
Well then, we're gonna experience everything this place has to offer!
[ Edamame is boiled and lightly salted green soybeans ]
How about we start off with some draft beer and edamame?
Then, let's go!
Y-Yeah!
Miwako-san...
Could it be that you're trying to cheer me up?
Hey, Yamada-san, take a look.
I thought something smelled nice. Look!
ureshii nukumori ni tsutsumareru tame
Longing for the happiness in my warm embrace...
Fragrant olives...
ikutsu mo no machigai kasaneteru
You repeat the same mistake...
Every year, when the city is filled with the scent of this flower, preparations for the school festival begin.
je t'aime...
baka da yo na
You're such a fool.
Bathed in the orange glow of the school's lights, and surrounded by the scent of the fragrant olives...
betsu ni kamawanai to kimi wa iu kedo
You say that you don't mind...
...I'd keep wandering the places I thought I might see the person I like so much...
tekitou na kotoba ga mitsukaranai
And I can't find the words to play it off.
I wanted to catch just a glimpse of him.
je t'aime...
I wanted to hear his voice.
sonna toko da
That's how it is.
My long...
Long...
kimi ga iru no wa ikenai koto da
But you shouldn't be with me.
My...
It smells so nice.
It's my favorite flower.
nayami tsukareta kyou mo mata
I'm tired from all the worrying today.
Do you like the fragrant olives, Yamada-san?
Yeah, I love them!
Let's drink, Yamada-san!
Yeah...
Now drink and eat!
Once we've eaten, we're going to the pool, the massage room, and the germanium bath!
We're doing the full course tonight!
kimi ga iru no wa suteki na koto da
It's nice that you're here with me.
Yeah...
yasashiku naru nani mo kamo
It makes everything more kind.
Hey, it's
Yamada-san! Welcome~
All right, that did the job.
kimi ga iru no wa ikenai koto da
But you shouldn't be with me.
Oh, Nomiya, good timing.
nayami tsukareta kyou mo mata
I'm tired from all the worrying today.
Yamada-san is right there?
Why?
She's asleep?
Yeah, I basically wore her out with a full course at the Health Land.
Sis... you wore her out?
Did something happen?
Well, something did between Mayama and Rika-san.
Was she crying again?
A little.
But she's all right now.
She's sleeping with her beautiful legs all exposed...
...in her underwear.
I wanna see that...
Oh my, Nomiya-san.
You're too honest.
I'm sorry, Sis.
Please take care of her for me.
I'd welcome a girl this pretty any day.
But you know, Mayama's pretty weird.
He was around a girl with her figure day in and day out and didn't budge.
She must've really been precious to him.
Damn!
Why doesn't that damn adolescent give me a call?!
I hadn't heard from her so I figured she was doing well, and now this!
Gimme a break!
Did something happen to Yamada-san?
Was that an S.O.S.?
Are you gonna go to her, Nomiya?
I am not.
I don't give a damn.
She can cry by herself!
N-Nomiya...!
I'll be able to come back in a little bit... just a little longer...
So until then...
Please don't cry all by yourself...
Don't cry in front of some other guy...
Why...
Why is it?
The sand from those dunes, his expression, and his words...
They...
...won't go away.
M-M-M-M-M-Morita-san!
Why are you eating someone else's food?!
I'm broke this month because I put all my money into getting a license!
My plan to make it through to next month with just 100 yen bread crusts...
Takemoto-kun, you can have my steamed bun!
It's okay, isn't that your lunch, Hagu-chan?
It's all right, Takemoto-kun.
Please eat it...
No-!
Morita-san?!
That's dirty!
That is so dirty!
Hey, Takemoto, am I that dirty?
It's dirty!
Am I so dirty that she has to rush to wash her hands with soap?
Oh no, oh no!
You're filthy.
Like the part where you put on little acts like that.
Oh no!
And the part where you eat other people's food.
In fact, you're pitch black.
You've been a smartass lately, Takemoto!
You're yelling back at me?!
Don't make a fuss here.
If you get in the way of Hagu's work...
I'll kill you.
Or you know what, become one with the wind!
2nd Floor
Like, heave ho!
Oh no, my money!
W-What am I gonna do?
William, Bill, Billie! I'm gonna save you all right now!
If have that much money, why are you eating my food?!
Hey!
I got them all.
They all came back to me...
Morita-san...
What do you do for your job?
You work so much.
But you don't seem to be spending any...
What in the world are you gonna do with that much money?
Well, you know...
Sorry, Takemoto...
I've got to go.
Yo, I've been waiting for you, Shinobu.
I wanted to show this to you as soon as possible.
It's finally complete.
It's a perfect system to swindle 50 yen a month from every kid in the world forever.
What do you think, Shinobu?
Look, Shiroyama is so touched that he's crying.
No, I think Shiroyama is crying for a different reason...
Well, whatever. We'll stop kidding around.
Shinobu, can you do another job before next month?
One more?
On what scale?
Hundred of millions.
Impossible.
Shiroyama, reduce the timetable from forever to one year.
And switch "every kid" to "every single person under thirty" and see what numbers come up.
I'll take that job.
Kaoru...
Have you been sleeping properly?
I have.
For how long?
Four hours.
You should sleep more, or you'll dull your senses.
And don't make any flashy moves. They'll catch onto us.
I don't want to hear that from you, of all people.
How much longer do we have to go?
Just a little more.
Just one last push to make.
You take things too far, Takemoto.
I understand that you wanted to get your license right away, but you didn't need to invest all of your daily living money...
This tastes great, Mayama-san!
I can feel the grains of rice spreading through my body!
Yeah, dig in.
Fill yourself up.
But Takemoto...
What was the big hurry to get your license?
That's...
Oh, and Takemoto-kun.
Yes?
If you want to work for us, you should get your driver's license while you're still a student.
Yes, sir!
Oh, during your trip, huh?
Yeah.
I see.
All right, I'll be paying for you tonight.
So let's go to the bath house!
And I'll even buy you an ice cream at the convenience store on the way back!
I'll seriously never forget this gratitude, senpai!
Um... Mayama-san...
Huh?
Why do you still live in that apartment?
Since you have a job, shouldn't you be able to rent a better room?
Well... it's because there's something I want...
Or rather, I'm saving up for when that time comes.
For when that time comes?
That's...
Well, I don't even know if that time will come.
When I was a kid, I read in some book...
...that every human has at least three opportunities in life.
And I thought this as I grew up...
I get the feeling it's a matter of having the money to take advantage of that opportunity when it comes.
Mayama-san, could it be that you have a significant savings?
Yeah.
So I'm the only one that is actually poor?
You're fine since you're still a student.
So you're preparing yourself for that opportunity?
Something like that.
If something were to happen to the woman I love...
...I want to have enough to be able to tell her, "Go ahead and take some time off."
Mayama-san...
M-Mayama-san?
I'm sorry, Takemoto.
That was hammy of me.
I admit it.
I'll say it myself!
That's not true.
That was awesome, Mayama-san!
Let's hurry to the bath.
I need to wash off this hammy stench.
Better yet, please forget it, Takemoto!
Please forget I said anything!
No, you're brilliant, Mayama-san!
If something were to happen to the woman I love...
...I want to have enough to be able to tell her, "Go ahead and take some time off."
I really agreed with Mayama-san's words back then.
But... all I could do was agree.
I still...
...don't understand a thing.
I'm sorry, Yamada-san.
We had you come all the way out here and...
I really wonder where Miwako-san went.
Ah, it's Yamada-san!
Don't worry about it, Takaido-san.
I'll just wait.
Leader, Leader, you're such a cutie.
Wow!
That's a new song,
Yamada-san.
The backs of your legs are so fluffy.
Don't you wonder where Miwako-san went, Leader?
Health Land was so much fun.
We drank beer together under the fragrant olives.
The fragrant olives...
Yamada-san, when you feel helpless, please call me.
When you feel helpless...
Eek!
Ah, welcome back, Miwako-san...
N-Nomiya-san.
Nomiya-san,
Nomiya-san!
Hey, Leader. How've ya been?
Yeah, yeah. You're doing fine.
I wanted to see you, too.
And Yamada-san...
I'm home...
A r-roundhouse?!
I ran out because it felt like he saw right through me.
I honestly wanted to call him.
I wanted to listen to a lot of things.
And I wanted to ask him so many things...
...but I hated myself for thinking that.
I mean, if I thought that, all of my feelings for Mayama would turn into lies...
I don't care how pathetic or embarrassing I look in front of everyone.
My feelings for him... only that...
...was my bittersweet treasure...
Leader...
God...
I didn't want to be saved.
I wanted to keep crying over Mayama...
And yet...
I'm so happy that he came back...
Though...
...it hurts so much.
arifurete iru kimochi nante sa
It would be so much easier...
nanimo iwazu ni isso kieteshimaeba
...if these stale emotions...
raku ni nareru no ni
...could just disappear without a word.
sorezore no michi wo yuku sono wakaremichi
At the crossroads where we split ways...
mou nidoto au koto no nai deai wa kanashisugiru
...it saddens me to think we may never meet again.
tarinai kimochi wo mochiyotte
Despite adding the emotions that are lacking...
atatameta saki kara hieteitte
...things cool off just as soon as I warm them...
sonna hazu naitte shinjiteru
...but I still don't want to believe.
ittai itsumade onaji kotoba wo kakaekondenda
Just how long am I going to brood over the same word?
kakekondenda
How long...?
Next episode: We were never to go to the beach.