ANIME-KOI
PRESENTS
onnanoko hajimemashita
A tired girl starts her day
tameiki wa bioron no shirabe ni nite
With a sigh like the moan of a violin
akai mi hajikechatta
A cherry bursts in her mouth
mada anata wo shiranai
This was before we had met
konna koto hajimetette
This is the first time I've ever felt like this
manazashi wa aku no hana sakimidarete mo
I could see that your pretty eyes were filled with contempt
ie e to tsuzuku
But I had to go home
basu sutoppu demo anata wa tsurenai
Even at the bus stop, you gave me the cold shoulder
karameta hanabi myaku utsu
The fireworks in the sky pulse
koi no shiruetto
In a silhouette of love
karui mahou
With a little magic,
usotsuki na kuchibiru
Two sets of lying lips
sou kasaneteru
Lock together
ano ne
You see
nee kamisama
God...
warui ko ni naritai yo
I'd like to be a naughty girl
ii ko ni shiteru kara
I'm tired of being good
onegai dayo
So, please
zurui koto sasetoite
It's for a good reason
ii koto shitai nara
So let me be bad for once
sukaato hirogaesu shite
By flipping my skirt
sugu kaeru yo
I'll be back soon
doyoubi wa haresou da
It looks like Saturday is going to be sunny
kamisama hajimemashita
God, it has already started
The hat-wearing sparrow that flew toward the
Earth Deity was obviously no regular sparrow.
It is wearing a hat, after all.
Will this sparrow bring good or bad luck?
Does it herald simply a visit from royalty
or could it be a miracle of love?
The Deity
Ties Fate
Blossoming Flowers
Earth Deity.
Huh?
I am the familiar of the Imperial Priestess.
I have a message for you.
The Priestess of the Lake will be here today
to pay her respects to the new Earth Deity.
Priestess of the Lake?
Her name is Isara. She's the master of the lake.
The bird talked like it was totally normal!
She's the reincarnation of a catfish.
The bird... talked!
Catfish?
Lake Isara was one of Mikage's guardian bodies.
It only makes sense that they would
pay their respects to the new deity.
So it's a catfish demon this time, huh?
I'm almost nervous about her coming to greet me.
Why are you tidying up?
Well I need to look proper when greeting guests, don't I?
You don't need to show yourself at all.
Huh?
An incompetent brat like you would only screw up.
Don't leave the room until everybody leaves.
We humbly welcome you to our abode,
Imperial Priestess of the Lake
I am the shrine familiar, Tomoe. We are honored that you would grace us with your presence.
Unfortunately, our deity has fallen ill
and will not be able to greet you properly.
What?!
The Imperial Priestess of the Lake...
A being that knows Mikage out of friendship.
I shan't allow Nanami's blunders to spoil that relationship.
I have prepared seats for you.
Nanami-sama, the reason why Tomoe said that...
...was in your best interests!
They're right. Even if I were to attend, I wouldn't know what to do.
Though, I wonder if Tomoe-dono can handle it himself.
The Priestess is basically the chief of all the demons in the lake.
She might be out of even Tomoe-dono's league.
We decide to pay her a visit, yet the new deity cannot be bothered receive us herself?
Is this not a bit rude to the Priestess?
We're terribly sorry. Once she gets
better, we'll be sure to reciprocate.
I hear that the new deity is just a human girl.
Could the reason that she isn't here be
the fact that she's cowering in fear somewhere?
Oh, stop that. Remember, Mikage chose her himself.
Although she's a human, she's still special.
And yet I heard something strange.
The new deity was chased by a specter,
and she ran away panicking.
Your Earth Deity is not only human, she is a helpless little girl.
They are arguing over me, after all!
This temple has lost its former glory, don't you think?
I beg to differ.
Nanami may appear weak, but her soul is strong.
One day, she will surely be able
to make even flowers bloom.
Blossoming Flowers
I get it now.
Basically, you're just that incompetent little girl's slave!
My, oh my. Your accusations are truly harsh.
Dare I say that your master, who came to visit our
deity knowing her nature, is stooping to her level?
I've had enough of your impertinent tongue.
Hurry up and bring the girl here.
Else your head will roll, fox.
What a perfect opportunity to liven the party up.
My, someone's blood-thirsty.
I suppose I have no say in this matter.
I'm so sorry I'm late! I am the Earth Deity, Momozono Nanami.
I apologize for my rudeness.
Sir, may I request that you sheathe your sword?
Oh crap. He told me not to come out, and I did anyway!
But I couldn't just stand around while he pointed his sword at Tomoe.
Even so... right now, Tomoe scares me more.
Tomoe
scares me more.
You idiot. Why did you come out?
Now that you're out here,
I have to protect you.
Unlike his words, Tomoe's hands had an aura of
gentleness while they were wrapped around mine.
So you're the rumored Earth Deity.
You look as incompetent as your reputation says.
Would you allow the Priestess's followers
the liberty of fixing that?
I hate to spoil your fun, but I won't allow anyone
to lay a finger on my master as long as I serve her.
Don't blame me if you die!
I'll make you eat your words!
W-What am I supposed to do?!
Now, how shall I prepare you for dinner?
Hey, everyone! Let's stop arguing and talk this
through! I'm sure we can reach an understanding!
Out of the way.
D-Die, you bastard!
I've got it. I'll grill you.
What?
Grill delicately over medium heat for five minutes.
Perfect for a grand breakfast.
How does it feel to be a fish who's about to be grilled alive by a fox's fire?
Tomoe...
Let go of that fish!
Let go of that fish!!
You always take things too far!
Now, sit down and make up with the fish!
Good, will you two drop it and stop fighting now?
You're surprisingly obedient.
Yes, this is the curse that haunts shrine familiars.
The ability to force action through the power of words.
It seems that you are indeed the Earth Deity.
She can talk?
The power of words?
The words that a deity speaks become
a powerful spell cast upon shrine familiars.
The more conviction you have in your words, the more powerful the spell.
And thus shrine familiars are bound by such words.
Those two idiots! I told them not to tell Nanami about that!
I had this power all along?
Look at how she's beaming now!
Shrine familiar.
I'll shoulder the blame for the fish's rudeness.
I had no intention of offending you.
I had come to ask you to tie my fate to another.
Hmm?
Wait, you mean like a love story?
Response
Let us hear your story first.
We have only met once.
It was ten years ago at Lake Isara.
I fell in love with a human boy.
Urashima Kotarou from the Sara estate.
I'm scared. I'm scared...
The face he made when he cried was adorable.
That boy was eight years old.
It's been ten years since that day came to pass.
I'm sure he's grown into a fine young man.
Our fates were torn apart, and I wish to have them reunited.
However, I cannot meet Kotarou because of who I am.
Nanami-dono, would you please grant my wish?
Forget it.
Love between demons and humans is forbidden.
You should know this already, Priestess.
I know.
I know, but...
I understand.
I'll do what I can!
What?!
Thank you.
Their love probably won't work out,
but that's all the more reason to ask for a deity's help.
Love can exist even between demons and humans.
Good morning.
Good morning, Nanami-sama!
Huh? Where's Tomoe?
It seems that he's feeling ill today.
He's down there.
He's been holed up since the Priestess left yesterday.
Tomoe-dono?
Nanami-sama is here.
Silence
I guess no one's home. We'll get started with the chores, then.
We'll see you later.
Are you upset over yesterday?
I ignored what you said and
showed myself to the Priestess.
I even ended up promising her something,
but still you protected me. It made me happy.
I'll try my best.
I want you to accept me one day.
What are you mumbling to yourself about?
Huh? You were behind me?!
D-Did you hear what I said?
If it's about the priestess, I'd rather not.
I'll just apologize to her and decline. Don't try to stop me.
Humans and demons aren't meant to be together.
Besides, what can you do?
Well we won't know until I try, now will we?
I already know how it's going to turn out.
Demons and humans can at least love each other!
"At least"? I don't think they'd normally fall in love.
Whatever. I'll go by myself.
Where are you going?
I'm going to town to look for Kotarou.
I'm going to town for a bit. Make sure you look over the shrine until I get back.
Wait.
I'll come with you.
Huh? W-Well okay.
Just put on something normal before you come!
The very fact that I would fear Nanami never returning, like Mikage...
We'll be back soon!
We're back!
We're here!
Look at all the people!
The smell of the exhaust fumes!
It's like I'm back on Earth!
Has it been a long time since you've visited, too?
Well, I guess.
Mama, his ears are weird.
Don't look!
I let my guard down just because he changed his clothes!
My standards for "humans" are dropping!
Is this better, Nanami?
I'd better be careful.
SIGHTSEEING
MAP
Now, let's look for Kotarou-kun!
Crap, that's my school's uniform.
This is bad. Today's a weekday!
What's wrong?
Let's have ice cream, Tomoe!
Don't stop me!
I used to come and eat ice cream here
whenever I got my paycheck.
Isn't it delicious?
Remember that we're here to look for Kotarou, Nanami.
I know, I know.
Huh? Momozono-chan, what are you doing here?
Isobe?!
Why this guy of all people?
What the heck are you doing ditching school?
Hanging out with guys? Wow.
You're getting the wrong idea. Now, go away.
By the way, what was that thing at school?
It was way too cheesy.
Did your dad run away leaving you his debt?
Did you get evicted and have to stay in a park?
There are a bunch of rumors, but what's really going on?
N-None of that's true! My dad's just away on a job!
I thought he couldn't hold down a job!
I bet he just never found his way home! Tell me the truth!
We're leaving.
What's up with you? Hey!
Don't take me lightly,
you brat.
Wha—
S-Stop it!
Stop it!!
Are you okay, Isobe?
S-Sir?
Wha—
What the heck do you think you're doing?
He's a human for crying out loud. Be careful!
Stop yelling into my ears!
You've got guts ordering me around
without doing any work yourself!
I'm here to work!
U-Um... Could you not quarrel here...
That's the reason why we're in town!
I didn't come to town to eat ice cream with you!
I'm here to look for Urashima Kotarou!
Well, what a surprise, same here!
U-Um, what do you need me for?
Huh.
I-I'm Urashima Kotarou.
On the third day of her job as Earth Deity, she found her target.
This can only mean...
So this is what deities who tie people's fates do!
Sorry for the wait, Kotarou-kun.
And sorry for calling you out here so suddenly.
Uh...
Also, sorry for the ruckus at the restaurant earlier.
Y-You don't need to bow!
I'm just...
A-Anyway, you said you needed to talk to me?
Do you remember who you met ten years ago at Lake Isana?
Ten years ago...
S-S-S-S-Sorry, I can't remember anything.
You went to the trouble of calling me...
I-It's not a big deal!
Don't worry!
Oh, is that a Rubik's Cube?
Y-Yeah.
I don't have too many redeeming qualities,
but I've always been good at this.
Whenever I have one in my hands, it calms me down.
Oh, so it's like a lucky charm?
I just killed the conversation!
There's this friend I have that's always liked you.
She's the Imperial Priestess of the Lake.
Won't you meet her just once?
Amazing, Nanami-sama!
You managed to get Kotarou-dono to promise!
Onikiri-kun, Kotetsu-kun, you were here?
Yes! Tomoe-dono asked us to escort you, so here we are!
Where's Tomoe?
He went to fetch the car.
Car?
It looks like you're finished talking to Kotarou.
Let's go back to the shrine.
Whoa! What is this?
It's Mikage's beloved vehicle, the Night Fog Cart
It runs on darkness, so it only works at night, though.
Now, if you'll excuse us.
U-U-Um...
Huh?
Hurry up.
U-Um!
If you don't want to go back, you can stay. I'm leaving.
W-Wait up! Hold it!
Don't you want to remain...
...as a human?
Stop spacing out and give me a hand!
It's too high for me to climb in.
Jeez... You're helpless.
By the way, I have a request regarding the Priestess.
What is it?
Where in the world is the Priestess?!
You're causing a ruckus.
The Earth Deity asked her to meet up
last night she still hasn't returned!
What did you do to the Imperial Priestess, you damn fox?!
Quiet, Aotake.
Wha—
We're done!
Priestess!
I let her wear my school uniform.
Don't you think she looks great in it?
Please, be honest with me.
It's great. No one will realize your true identity with that on.
I'll be able to meet my Kotarou now, right?
But, be careful. It's difficult for me
to maintain your disguise as a human.
You are not to use any magic. In the event that
you do, you'll return to your normal form.
Crunch
Response
Also, stop that.
Now, let's go, Priestess. Kotarou-kun's waiting.
Nanami-dono,
thank you.
Kotarou-kun will be waiting by
the Nishiguchi Park entrance at 5 PM.
She's late.
Was this all a prank?
Why would there be a girl who actually likes me, anyway?
Kotarou-kun?
It is you, Kotarou!
Do not cry, boy.
Smile.
Smile!
How sweet! They haven't seen each other in ten years!
A rendezvous between a human and a demon
is still living on borrowed time, though.
Don't say that!
At least for today, the string of fate that was once cut is reunited.
Kotarou.
Kotarou!
S-She's way too close!
I wanted to see you.
C-Could you g-give me some space, please?
Why?
T-T-This is the first time we've met, after all.
But I love you!
I-I'm not sure how to react to being
confessed to by someone I don't know.
I see.
I don't know why a girl like you
would love someone like me.
What is that box?
O-Oh, this is a Rubik's Cube. You've never seen one?
Yeah.
It's a six-sided cube-shaped puzzle.
You rotate it and try to align all the colors.
What a complicated little box.
It's not that difficult.
You just have to look at the back-side of the face and turn accordingly.
See? One side is done.
Wow, already! You're amazing, Kotarou!
Oh.
D-Do you want to try?
May I?
Y-Yeah! I'm going to go get us some drinks real quick.
Just wait here.
Okay.
What is this?
My heart's won't stop racing.
Amazing, Nanami-sama!
Your first job is complete!
Well done!
I'll keep doing my best!
First-Year
Stop being ridiculous. It's too early to celebrate.
The Priestess is in trouble.
First-Year
Huh?
Yo, yo, yo, Shawty, you be lookin' fine.
You look bored. You free or somethin'?
'Wanna come eat with us? I'll pay for 'ya.
Quit screwin' with this junk.
Give it back.
What, is this crap important to you?
C-Crap! We've got to help!
Hold it, Nanami.
That isn't your job.
From here on out, the human will have to do his part.
If he has the slightest will to make
this work, it will turn out for the better.
Your job is to give him the nudge
that will make him change.
W-What should I do?
I want to help her...
But...
I'm so scared my legs won't move.
Kotarou-kun...
Move... Move!
Move, dammit!
ah ah ah ah
Here, go on.
I wonder if my nudge reached him.
Kotarou
ah ah ah ah
Hey, Tomoe...
You didn't have to literally push his back, you know.
ah ah ah ah
That was pretty straightforward.
But it seems the two have managed to take a step forward.
ah ah ah ah
I can only hope that their bond will only strengthen with time.
kamisama onegai da
Please, God
boku no
I...
ano hito ni aitai no sa
I want to meet her
ah ah ah
ah ah ah ah
kamisama tsurain da
God, I'm in pain
kyou mo mata nou ni
Because, she...
konakatta
didn't come today either.
onegai ga aru no kamisama
I have a request, God
boku wo tasukete
Please, save me
ah ah ah ah
kamisama mou osoi
God, it's too late for me
ano ko wa...
Because she's...
Next Episode Preview
Nanami saves a white snake, only
for it to fall in love with her!
In an attempt to save Nanami,
Tomoe disguises himself as a high school student and goes to class!
Wow, what a hot guy!
Next time: "The Deity is Kidnapped"!
｢The Deity is Kidnapped｣
Oh no!