Translation: MoeJo & w0lf\\\Translation check: Winterreise\\\Editing: Minami_\\\Typsetting: Layton\\\Encoding: Layton\\\
Anime-Koi Fansubs
------------------------------------------------------------------------------
The Deity is Kidnapped
sign:We'll be right back!
sign:And we're back!
Next Episode Preview
｢The Deity Loses her Home｣
sign:The Deity Loses her Home
I've borrowed this hammer of lightning from
Daikokuten-sama for precisely these situations.
That's Tomoe-dono's pocket mirror.
ah ah ah ah
Kamisama
Onegai da
Boku no ano hito ni
Aitai no sa
Kamisama
Tsurainda
Kyou mo matta noni
Konakatta
Onegai ga aru no
Kamisama
Boku wo tasukete
Mou osoi
Ano ko wa
Touku sora ni
Kieta no sa
Yeah Yeah Yeah
Sayonara Baby goodbye
ah ah ah
ah ah ah ah
Momozono Nanami
left:17
17 Years Old
A High School Girl
Kid
m 0 0 l 245 0 245 180 0 180 c
Popular
ah ah ah ah
m 54 42 b 54 42 54 42 54 42 b 54 45 56 49 56 52 b 55 53 52 56 51 57 b -9 49 -70 41 -130 33 b -131 32 -133 29 -134 28 b -134 26 -135 22 -135 20 b -134 19 -133 16 -132 15 b -136 14 -140 13 -144 12 b -144 8 -145 4 -145 0 b -146 0 -149 -2 -150 -2 b -150 -6 -150 -11 -150 -15 b -109 -14 -68 -12 -27 -11 b -26 -8 -24 -3 -23 0 b -22 2 -20 5 -19 7 b -19 10 -20 15 -20 18 b 2 20 25 24 47 26 b 49 31 52 36 54 41
ANIME-KOI
PRESENTS
The Deity
\h\h Loses
\h\h\h her Home
The Deity
\h\h Loses
\h\h\h her Home
We'll be back soon!
We're back!
Momozono Nanami... a high school girl?
How did a normal girl come to be Mikage's successor?
Where is Mikage now?
He's been missing for 20 years.
He ran away?
Then, can I have Tomoe?
No.
...and then he ran off for twenty years!
I feel sorry for Tomoe-kun,
having to play shrine familiar to a human and such.
First Mikage and now this girl, they all keep stealing Tomoe from me!
I'll make her pay for this!
Momozono Nanami.
I, thunder deity Narukami, shall decide
whether you are worthy of the title "deity."
That was the seventh thunderbolt from the east.
Narukami must be in a bad mood again.
It's getting closer and closer.
She's coming to visit, from the looks of it.
I overslept!
Tomoe, why didn't you wake me up?
Finally, you're awake.
Today's breakfast is my special sesame tofu with reed starch and morning dew—
I don't have time to eat breakfast!
Stop!
You almost forgot your lunch box and your headband.
No thanks!
Just shut up and put it on!
It's not like I'm going onto a battlefield or anything!
I'm just going to sit around in school all day!
We're going to have a guest at the shrine today.
I'll be stuck here.
I'm just worried about you.
Because... you look as weak as a bug.
I'm leaving.
Nanami!
Geez, he worries too much.
Oh my,
it looks like it's about to rain.
Nanami-chan, your training as a novice deity and studies are both progressing...
Or they should be.
Storms lie ahead for you.
Severe ones.
I heard that Kurama-sama is absent today because he's sick.
What?!
Wha—
Nanami-sama!
Onikiri-kun, Kotetsu-kun!
Why were you two hiding inside my bag?
Tomoe-dono asked us to escort and serve you today.
We, the fire demon children, will protect you!
Hey, Momozono-san.
T-This isn't what it looks like!
These guys are...
Is Tomoe-kun not coming today?
Huh? U-Um...
Y-Yeah.
H-He'll be absent today.
Don't worry, Nanami-sama.
Normal people can't see us.
Huh?
This is odd.
Narukami should've been here by now.
But the rainclouds just passed by.
Did I read too much into it?
The clouds were headed toward Nanami's school.
Don't tell me she's...
Thanks so much for bringing my lunch box!
It's delicious.
Seriously, Tomoe's a great cook.
Was Mikage-san a foodie or something?
No. Normally, deities and spiritual beings such as ourselves do not require food.
Tomoe-dono has been practicing his cooking every day because you have a body to nourish.
I see.
Tomoe-dono always puts you first.
I'm just worried about you.
Stop it! There's no way he'd do that!
No, no, Tomoe-dono is actually—
Hey, you shouldn't tease a girl!
Are you Momozono Nanami?
A demon?!
I've created a barrier so we won't be interrupted.
We're alone in here.
I am the deity of a shrine in the sky.
Narukami the thunder deity.
I've heard your story and how you became an earth deity.
You became one against your will.
It must be hard for you.
But, your suffering ends today.
I'll take Mikage's shrine in your stead.
Suffering?
I'll free you from your suffering.
No, Narukami-sama.
I'm not suffering.
I have the children of the fire demon and Tomoe with me.
Everyone is so kind.
The shrine is like a home to me.
So I don't want to leave.
That's no good.
Huh?
Nanami!
Tomoe.
Are you okay?
You're here at last, Tomoe.
Tomoe-dono,
Nanami-sama's been...
Narukami, what do you think you're doing?
Set Nanami free now.
She's my master.
You must have grown weak if you're
willing to accept her as your master.
Wh-What do I do, Tomoe?
It pains me to see you being subservient to a human.
Mind your own business!
I've borrowed this hammer from
Daikokuten-sama for precisely these situations.
Huh?
Wh—
Here I go!
Shrink!
Wh—
Tomoe!
You're next.
Mikage's symbol is now mine.
You're no longer an earth deity.
You can now live peacefully as an ordinary human being, Nanami.
Tomoe!
Tomoe, it would behoove you to visit
the shrine if you want to return to normal.
I'll restore you if you promise to be my familiar.
Stay strong, Tomoe!
Come, children of fire demon. Lead the way.
Yes, ma'am!
Huh?
We're sorry, Nanami-sama.
We're spirits of the shrine.
We have to obey the commands of its master.
Well then, have a nice day.
We lost our home, Tomoe.
I don't have money.
And now you've turned into a little kid.
What do we do now?
Just do whatever you want.
This is the human world,
and you're a human, so you'll definitely find a place to live.
I can't take care of you anymore.
Tomoe, what's wrong?
Tomoe!
You have a fever!
What should I do?
Tomoe, tell me what to do!
I'm so stupid.
Tomoe's not even human
and I took him to a hospital.
He's so hot.
At the very least, I have to find a place to sleep for the night.
Nanami? What are you doing out here?
Huh? What...
What happened to your deity mark?
He's cuter than before.
Sorry for making you do this.
I know you had to skip school because you were sick too.
Sick?
That was just an excuse so I could go to work.
It's difficult to get permission because the school just...
...doesn't understand the life of a celebrity.
It's okay, though, since I'm the first mega-celebrity to enroll there.
But, aren't you a Crow Goblin?
Quit calling me a Crow Goblin!
I'm a dark angel, you know.
Hey, do you know a doctor who can help spiritual beings?
Calling a doctor wouldn't help.
Huh?
His body is rejecting the change.
This body cannot contain his demonic power.
So it's spilling out.
That's why he has a fever.
So...
He won't get better unless he returns to his normal form.
I'll restore you if you promise to be my familiar.
It'll only work temporarily, but you can use this.
It's a medicine that's been passed down from generation to generation in my clan.
You should be thankful that I'm even giving you this.
It's really bitter, though.
Tomoe...
Thank goodness.
Looks like you're getting better now.
Get well soon.
Here, you can have this sticky rice cake.
Yukiji,
I...
Tomoe, thank goodness! You're awake!
I was so worried!
Do you want a drink?
If there's anything you want, tell me.
I want a sticky rice cake wrapped in bamboo leaf.
Kurama! Let me borrow your kitchen and some money!
Money?!
Oh, so you know how to make sticky rice cakes?
My mom used to make them for me.
Tomoe finally asked me for something.
It kind of makes me happy.
Is it good, Tomoe?
It's my special sticky rice cake.
It tastes normal.
He's still the same Tomoe on the inside.
Nanami.
Huh?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'll have to take leave today.
I'm having trouble sleeping from being overworked.
It's raining.
The roof is leaking!
What's with this rundown shrine?
We're sorry.
The shrine is returning to to its original state due
to the absence of Tomoe-dono's spiritual powers.
I thought he'd give up quickly and come to me.
Koume, Kotake!
Bring Tomoe to me!
Yes, ma'am!
What is this?
It's feathery and ticklish.
Kurama?!
Who is it?
I can't sleep like this.
Why are we in the same bed?!
What makes you think you can sleep on my bed?
Sleep on the floor.
Does that mean you'll sleep on the bed with Tomoe?
As if!
Just let the fox sleep somewhere on the floor!
I'd much rather sleep with a woman—
Damn you, little fox!
Stop that!
I fell asleep just like that?!
Korusaki-san, why are you calling me at this hour?
I've made the biggest mistake of my life.
I didn't ask you to do that.
He's a demon.
Tomoe, how do you feel?
Be a little more cautious.
I'm what?
Hey brat, are you sure you should be up and around?
It doesn't look like your fever has gone down yet.
Don't be so rough with him.
Are you happy that you have to
depend on a woman to protect you?
Don't forget that she's here because of you.
He's right.
The fever isn't what's making me grumpy.
This is irritating.
I have to find a way to get Tomoe back to normal.
If the hammer made him shrink,
then it can return him to normal too.
That's all you need.
So you'll get it from Narukami for me?
Oh no, look at the time.
Where are you going?
I have a rehearsal for my concert at 10.
I see.
You look lonely.
N-No I don't.
Here's a spare key, and I left my number and some money.
You can use them.
Call me if anything happens.
T-Thank you.
Tomoe, I'm going to do the
supermarket to do some shopping.
Is there anything you want?
Wh—
Tomoe.
I'll come with you.
I'm okay now.
This body is irritating me.
Don't you have school?
Huh? Today's Saturday, so there's no class.
More importantly, we should find a way to return—
You should think about yourself first.
I can handle myself.
Handle yourself?
And how are you going to do that in this bod—
You're now a normal girl,
so you should live a normal life.
And I'll live the way I want.
Tomoe.
Don't tell me you're going to her.
Wait, are you okay?
Your fever's worse.
Tomoe-dono, we've been searching for you.
We've come to retrieve him.
Narukami-sama is praying for his safety
and is awaiting his return at the shrine.
How dare you say things like "praying for his safety"
after all the awful things you've done to him!
We're a family thrown out of our own house.
I don't care that he's a demon and I'm a human.
I'll save him somehow.
You can't do anything.
There's no way you can save me, Nanami.
Tomoe.
It's irritating to think about living on your pity.
Hey, dog servants, I'll come with you to the shrine.
Take me there.
Right away.
Are you leaving?
It's only painful because you have to see me like this... probably.
Goodbye, Nanami.
To—
Tomoe, you idiot!
Oh my, it didn't take much to break them up.
What should we do?
Tomoe.
I've been waiting for you.
I knew you couldn't leave this shrine.
You can live here if you don't have anywhere to go.
Now, swear your loyalty!
You shall be mine, forever and ever!
Form a contract with—
What?!
Tomoe, where have you gone?
Nanami.
Oh my, what a warm welcome.
"Welcome"?
Never mind.
So, why are you sitting out here?
I was waiting for you.
Thanks for everything.
Tomoe went back to his shrine.
It looks like he's decided to
become Narukami's familiar.
I couldn't stop him.
You can't do anything.
I can't do any—
Don't cry over spilled milk!
I-I'm not crying.
And how could you call it "spilled milk"?
I guess I have no choice.
This is a parting gift for you, since you're human now.
Holding part of a demon's body allows you to see the supernatural.
A feather?
Nanami-sama!
Onikiri-kun! Kotetsu-kun!
How long have you been there?!
They've been bawling and clinging to you from the start.
It's terrible!
Tomoe-dono is avoiding Narukami-sama and hiding inside the shrine.
Narukami is on a war path!
She might level the shrine at this rate!
Nanami-sama, please save the shrine and Tomoe-dono.
There's no way you can save me, Nanami.
Okay, let's go there right now.
We've brought you the flying wagon.
Come, get on.
Kurama, I'll be borrowing your feather.
You can keep it.
And be careful.
Thank you.
We can't find him!
We've looked everywhere, including the back of the roof and below the floor!
Damn you, Tomoe!
You're making this hard on me!
If you don't show up...
I don't need this rundown shrine!
So, I'll burn it to ashes!
Hey!
Why would a deity destroy her own shrine?
Why are you here?
If you're looking for Tomoe, he's nowhere to be found.
I know I could find where he's hiding easily.
There's no way a mere human like you can find him.
If you're that confident,
then promise me that you'll return Tomoe to normal if you find him.
I give you my word.
I will definitely find him.
I can't find him.
Tomoe...
Maybe he fell unconscious because of his fever.
Huh?
Nanami-sama.
This...
That's Mikage-sama's pocket mirror.
I can feel his presence from inside the mirror.
I can feel his warmth.
It's hot.
I found you, Tomoe.
Tomoe.
Let's go home.
I didn't expect him to hide inside the mirror of his former master.
He must've despised me.
If you refuse to be mine, then I don't need you.
She also said that she doesn't need this rundown shrine.
We've come to deliver the deity mark and the hammer.
S-She has some gall?
Tell her to come here!
Now, I'm returning the mark to you.
My body's glowing!
Now, the deity mark is yours again.
Next, please swing this hammer at
Tomoe-dono while saying, "Get big!"
Only you can do it.
Yeah.
Get big!
I'm back to normal.
Your hair is much longer, though.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Why am I so dazzled by him?
Oh, it looks like the rain stopped!
It stopped!
The rain really stopped falling!
It's wonderful.
I'm in your debt now.
Huh?
Yea!.
You should be grateful!
This is the most gratitude you'll get.
A new contract with your shrine familiar.
That was the proof of our eternal pledge.
Nanami has a cold, and Tomoe transforms into
her double to take her place at school.
Suddenly, Kurama makes a move.
Meanwhile, Mizuki comes to visit Nanami.
Next time: "The Deity Catches a Cold."
Achoo!
onnanoko hajimemashita
A tired girl starts her day
tameiki wa bioron no shirabe ni nite
With a sigh like the moan of a violin
akai mi hajikechatta
A cherry bursts in her mouth
mada anata wo shiranai
This was before we had met
konna koto hajimetette
This is the first time I've ever felt like this
manazashi wa aku no hana sakimidarete mo
I could see that your pretty eyes were filled with contempt
ie e to tsuzuku
But I had to go home
basu sutoppu demo anata wa tsurenai
Even at the bus stop, you gave me the cold shoulder
karameta hanabi myaku utsu
The fireworks in the sky pulse
koi no shiruetto
In a silhouette of love
karui mahou
With a little magic,
usotsuki na kuchibiru
Two sets of lying lips
sou kasaneteru
Lock together
ano ne
You see
nee kamisama
God...
warui ko ni naritai yo
I'd like to be a naughty girl
ii ko ni shiteru kara
I'm tired of being good
onegai dayo
So, please
zurui koto sasetoite
It's for a good reason
ii koto shitai nara
So let me be bad for once
sukaato hirogaesu shite
By flipping my skirt
sugu kaeru yo
I'll be back soon
doyoubi wa haresou da
It looks like Saturday is going to be sunny
kamisama hajimemashita
God, it has already started
Please, God
I...
I want to meet her
God, I'm in pain
Because, she...
didn't come today either.
I have a request, God
Please, save me
God, it's too late for me
Because she's...
has disappeared
Into the distant sky
farewell, Baby, goodbye
Next Episode Preview
｢The Deity Catches a Cold｣
Momozono Nanami
17 Years Old
A High School Girl
Dispel
Poor
Little
Kid
Plop
m 0 0 l 195 0 195 550 0 550 c
Today's
operational
time is
over.
m 0 0 l 245 0 245 180 0 180 c
Hospital
Popular
Super
The ostrich
strikes back
Crunch
Mercy! Mercy!
Squeeze
Feathery
LAST
NIGHT
Squkk
Slash
Poof
Agh
Passed out
Rub
Wow, you are useless
Slap
Slump
Rub
Bow
One hour later
m 0 0 l 245 0 245 180 0 180 c
Return to
Daikokuten-sama
Kamisama
Onegai da
Boku no ano hito ni
Aitai no sa
Kamisama
Tsurainda
Kyou mo matta noni
Konakatta
Onegai ga aru no
Kamisama
Boku wo tasukete
Mou osoi
Ano ko wa
Touku sora ni
Kieta no sa
Yeah Yeah Yeah
Sayonara Baby goodbye
ah ah ah
ah ah ah ah