True Calendar, year 71.
JIOR, a proponent of peace through neutrality, had enjoyed economic prosperity,
but came under sudden, overwhelming attack by the Dorssia Military Pact Federation.
The JIOR government quickly conceded to their demand of unconditional surrender,
but Haruto Tokishima, a student in the developing colony of Module 77,
climbed aboard the Valvrave, a mysterious weapon, and drove off the Dorssian forces.
Dorssia and ARUS are now in a contest to determine who will control the Valvrave.
As a result of the declaration by Shoko Sashinami, the daughter of JIOR's president,
their school has become an independent country.
Why did—
I...
...want to be famous.
Miss Rukino!
Don't go in there!
These things are cursed!
Will she make the perfect guinea pig?
ARUS' pilots all died.
People all around the world will hear my songs.
"Saki Rukino? Sure, I know her! 'La-la-lalalala,' right?"
That's fine by me.
I hate humanity.
And if it'll make me special, I'll do anything!
This is...
Miss Rukino, she... Is she okay?
Saki-chan...
She's so hot!
Let's all be free...
This is amazing!
I feel like a bird!
No, I'm a vampire! That makes me a bat!
Miss Rukino! Come back!
No way!
You had no idea what would happen!
How could you give up your humanity?
Think about all the people you care about whose hearts you're going to break!
Be careful!
I'll be fine!
We're indestructible, right?
Besides...
I don't have anyone that I care about.
Poverty, abuse, alcoholism, crime...
I swear, my parents were like poison.
The only way I had to escape from them, from that lousy world, was to become famous.
Miss Rukino...
I don't care what happens to me.
I don't have any family or friends.
I have nobody.
Miss Rukino, I...
Is there anything I can do?
Why?
Well, a friend is crying.
I want to help.
You're a genuinely nice guy, aren't you, Haruto?
Sorry about this...
Miss Rukino?
Because...
...that was all a lie!
I look forward to working with you, Miss Nanami.
After all, you're the representative of the newborn JIOR.
Oh, come on... I can't be a representative!
Its a teacher's job to lead her pupils, isn't it?
I'll see you on the moon, then.
A teacher? I'm just a trainee...
Right...
Right... the one that's one level further down...
Oh, is this it?
We're connected.
Next, we—
Got it. I check these numerical values to tweak the output of the transmitter system, right?
You have a gift for this.
You'll make a fine technician.
I'm saying that you have talent.
Tokishima!
Have you seen Miss Rukino?
No.
She skipped her turn on the cleaning chores rota again.
Just because she's a celebrity, she thinks she—
Don't be so wound up all the time.
I'll keep you girls safe.
Also, and your mouth...
There's too many words coming out of it.
Tokishima?
I plugged it up for you.
I'll expect to see you cheering me on in the next battle, okay?
Wow, it's fun to be a boy!
That girl was compatible with the system?
Hidden weapons, the school curriculum...
The conclusion I'm led to...
...is that this school itself is a sham.
Why?! Why am I being taken off the mission?!
Lord Cain's orders are absolute.
"Lord" Cain, huh?
Hey, which rank is higher, a captain or a prince?
I'm relaying Captain Cain's exact words.
If you say you can't obey, then—
I'm a man of Karlstein, the chosen elite.
I'm well aware of the rules.
Good morning...
Yo, Haruto. I gotta say, I never took you for a bad boy.
I hope we see more, you love guru you.
Watari was crying.
Haruto!
What the hell is this?!
Are you going out?
Are you going out?!
It's against the rules to make a move on an idol!
It's a gentlemen's agreement!
Miss Rukino!
Good morning, Haruto.
What's the big idea, taking my body?!
Today, I'd like to introduce you to my little sister.
Well, I call her that, but she's not my real little sister.
She's someone who means as much to me as a real little sister, though.
Don't you think it's a great idea?
I'm marketing myself as the surrogate little sister of a celebrity!
You can't do that!
I thought you said that you wanted to help me.
You said you were lying.
A promise is a promise.
Besides, I paid you in advance, remember?
That was—
You, um...
Tell me, Haruto, what was it like to be a lonely vampire?
Miss Rukino?
For me, I had always—
Haruto!
Shoko?
This is bad! Really bad!
Someone who isn't you is posting under your name!
I don't think it's all that easy to fool the wired's retinal authentication system.
No, this isn't Haruto!
"Her songs are amazing.
And out of all of us, she worked the hardest on the music video the other day."
Haruto would never say that one person worked harder than someone else!
Shoko!
Don't worry. A girl I made friends with recently knows all about this kind of stuff.
I'll have her look into it!
Are you jealous?
You don't like it when Haruto is friendly with other girls?
You two are friendly?!
It's no big deal! It's not like we kissed or anything!
Kissed?!
No, no! I didn't say kissed!
I said, um... Dissed!
Pervert!
How?!
I don't know, but it sounded perverted!
What the hell?!
And you had a perverted look on your face!
I did not!
This is stupid.
Look, I don't care about Haruto at all.
All I want is to become famous.
But you're already a star.
Aren't you already plenty famous?
She's right. Why would you do something like that?
Because if you don't leave your mark on the world, you'll just disappear.
That was a—
Talk about a rough intro...
What was that?
That sound's an emergency broadcast.
We decided on it earlier, remember?
Everyone, please listen!
We're under Dorssian attack!
I repeat, we're under Dorssian attack!
Attack?
You mean they followed us?
Shall we go to the control room?
We're under Dorssian attack!
Let's hurry.
Please take shelter immediately!
But why? What about Shoko's threat?
I really mean it! Dorssian forces are here!
That we'd hand over the robot to ARUS?
The declaration should have reached Dorssia, too.
What about the ARUS ship?
I'm trying to contact them!
There's nothing we can do.
We're completely surrounded.
But how? When did they—?
Our Lagrange 4 forces have secured the area ahead.
We have them surrounded.
I bet they just couldn't catch up to us.
I was hoping for a chance to catch them in a pincer movement!
They kept us waiting too long for that.
Let's go! C'mon! C'mon!
If we gave ARUS the robot, wouldn't Dorssia surround them and give us time to escape?
But they'd be—
What's ARUS doing?
I can't get through!
Call Tokishima!
Y-Yes!
Huh? What's "VVV IV"?
There's one more...
What's going on?
Huh?
Miss Rukino?!
I asked you to call Tokishima!
Miss Rukino's piloting it!
Huh?
I've been found out.
Miss Rukino, where did you get that robot?
Her name's Carmilla.
Calling it "robot" or "Valvrave" doesn't fit my image.
From now on, call my Valvrave "Carmilla," okay?
Hey! What are you doing in there?!
I'm launching. See ya.
Hey! Rukino!
There's lots of those robots...
I gave up on expecting anything from others a long time ago.
I'll do this myself.
What weapons do I have?
Spindle Knuckles... These, right?
Nobody said there was more than one of those things!
Carmilla, you're the greatest!
Miss Rukino, you're going out too far ahead!
So what? We're indestructible superhumans!
There are two Valvraves?!
Its loadout seems somewhat different, but we'll proceed according to plan.
These guys seem pretty tough.
According to my analysis, the Valvrave is a close-quarters combat weapon.
No way!
In short, if it can't get close, its combat effectiveness is cut in half.
Whittle it down bit by bit, and victory is assured!
Haruto! What are you doing?
They're up against Ideals.
It's no easy matter to—
Right, then! That's the battleship sorted out!
No... Senator Figaro...
Just like that...
ARUS was...
I have to get away! Right now!
What?
Haruto?!
Miss Rukino, stay back!
Valvrave... There's a pair.
Pair?
Haruto! I have to help him!
Why am I shaking like this?
I'm scared...
Even though I'm immortal?
The green one is just sitting there!
What's it doing?
Fight!
Trade places with me, you chicken!
Miss Rukino...
I'm sorry, are you oka...?
Senpai?
Are you all right?
Hey, watch where you're going!
Takahi-senpai, why are you dressed like that?
This? Um, I... was asked to cheer them on, so I...
I can't get anywhere near them!
At this rate...
I won't let you do your harakiri thing this time!
The instant you stop, I'm gonna grab you!
Why?
Why...?
Pull yourself together, Saki Rukino!
You're the only one who can save Haruto and us!
Sashinami, you can't just—
The eyes of the entire school are on you.
Are you going to act that pathetic when everyone's watching?
You're putting on a show!
Saki Rukino is a star, isn't she?!
A star...
It's not enough.
This audience is way too small.
After all, I'm gonna be the biggest star in the world!
Miss Rukino...
Stream this battle to the wired.
The feed from my cockpit, too!
Look, it's that robot!
It's fighting again?
It's a girl this time!
Hey, she's cute!
Don't I know her?
She's that former idol. From JIOR.
That girl who retired?
Miss Rukino, stay back!
Leave this to me! I just had an idea!
It will be the same.
No matter how many they send out.
Let's try this!
Not yet!
Becoming famous is the only way!
Miss Rukino!
She's no match for them!
We have to get someone else!
But she's doing—
Look, they have her on the defensive!
We don't know that yet!
They took out that ARUS ship in the blink of an eye!
Who are you saying should pilot it, then?
You can do it, Saki Rukino!
You can do it! You can do it!
You can do it!
Shoko?
Don't give up, Saki Rukino!
Sashinami, what are you doing?
Cheering her on.
You said it yourself earlier, remember, senpai?
I meant—
Miss Rukino, fight!
You, too, Ma'am?
It's the same thing in sports!
Having a cheering section gives players a huge boost!
This is hardly the time!
What a bunch of nonsense!
If that's all it took to win, we'd—
Keep it together, Saki Rukino!
You join in, too!
No way...
Don't let em beat ya, Saki Rukino!
Hey, what are—
Um, go for it... go for it...
You can do it, Saki-chan!
- Don't lose!
- Fighting women are so cool!
- It's like a dance!
- You're great!
Don't get shown up by that boy!
The world... is watching.
You hurt me.
Mocked me.
How can it be so manoeuvrable?!
That's impossible!
The world that tried to kill me is now...
NOTICE OF CONTRACT TERMINATION
It's beautiful...
I won't be killed...
...by the world!
It's closed the gap!
X-eins!
What is that thing?!
Damn it!
Wait! Retreat!
Why?!
All forces, retreat to L2!
I repeat, all forces, retreat!
Is this an order, too?!
We're running away?
You heard her!
Bring X-eins' escape pod into hangar #2.
Yes, ma'am.
You have the bridge.
You're all right with this, sir?
I have another plan in motion.
L-elf...
For the sake of our friendship...
Perish.
Next time, episode 7.
"Haruto Under the Rubble".
Valvrave the Liberator...
The system that will expose the truth of the world.