Memorial Corner
Aina Sakurai
Wow, this girl ﻿died.
A cute thing ﻿like her?
Hey, she was ﻿the same age as us.
Poor thing!
That's so lame, ﻿I hate those Dorssians...
Rest in peace, ﻿Aina-chan.
Rest in peace.
Just you ﻿watch, Nobu.
Next time, I'm gonna avenge you ﻿in that robot for sure.
I'll avenge you, ﻿you hear?
REST IN PEACE
Tokishima Haruto
L-elf Karlstein
I've worked out ﻿everyone's assignments.
Six systems are integrated at Command:
Navigation, ﻿Gunnery, Communications, Radar, Engineering, Shields.
Are you sure you want to let me ﻿work up the battle station assignments?
I'm asking you to do it because I think ﻿that's the best way to minimize loss of life.
Aina Sakurai, ﻿huh?
I've decided to believe.
That you also have something precious to you.
It looks like the intervals between ﻿attacks are growing shorter...
I'm hungry.
Training Journal. ﻿Rion Nanami.
Module 77 is en route to the Moon ﻿which is neutral territory.
The students have begun military drills ﻿in order to prepare for battle.
The person who drew up the drill regimen was ﻿none other than L-elf, our country's first refugee.
I think the reason that the students have been ﻿so surprisingly quick to accept his instructions
is that they don't want to see ﻿anyone else die.
I myself am teaching ﻿first-aid procedures.
Though I hate the thought of ﻿any of my students being hurt...
I take some comfort in the fact that lessons are ﻿still being conducted in the classrooms.
Inuzuka, quit looking at those ﻿stock prices or whatever!
Intruder detected in the Pit!
I repeat, intruder detected in the Pit!
An enemy?
Our "intruder" was ﻿Yamada, huh?
This is the fifth time. ﻿When is he gonna learn?
I get it. ﻿He wants to use this to—
He wants to use it to get revenge ﻿with his own two hands.
Pathetic.
Hang on.
Wanting to avenge ﻿a friend's death is pathetic?
These machines have ﻿a registration system.
Once one pilot uses it, it can't be ﻿changed over to another.
What about it?
If I gave in to emotion and let someone pilot it, ﻿and it turned out that he had no talent for it, what then?
Nothing is a bigger nuisance than ﻿the hopes of people who have no talent.
Will avenging someone's death ﻿bring them back to life?
Instead of that, you should think about ﻿how to prevent future losses.
War is something that should be conducted ﻿calmly and efficiently, like a machine.
Like a ﻿machine...
47 seconds.
46 seconds.
48 seconds.
44 seconds.
Is he okay?
Haru—
What're you ﻿doing here?
I was worried about him. ﻿What about you?
I'm worried, too.
I wonder if ﻿they were going out...
Him and ﻿Aina-chan?
They were joined ﻿at the hip.
He was always heading out ﻿to visit some girl from another school.
Oh.
Haruto. ﻿Say something to him.
This is too big ﻿to carry alone.
Why not you?
This has to be done ﻿guy to guy!
Yamada's ﻿at it again?
No. Yamada's supposed to be ﻿in solitary confinement.
A Dorssian fleet is ﻿closing in on us from behind!
The barrier ﻿system?
Already ﻿on it!
We won't let them ﻿hit us!
I'm widening ﻿mine!
What are ﻿those?
The barrier system ﻿seems to be working.
Way to go! You guys are ﻿great at this!
I can't believe he retrofitted the EM debris shield ﻿into a barrier system...
How long had he been ﻿planning it?
Calmly. ﻿Like a machine.
A systematic ﻿defense strategy...
L-elf is ﻿in command?
It's the ﻿Valvraves.
Fall back slowly.
Draw them both away from Module 77.
They're ﻿running?
My show's just ﻿getting started!
DORSSIA MILITARY
#6 FLEET
Exactly ﻿as planned, sir.
The Valvraves are moving away ﻿to aft in pursuit of Captain Cain's fleet.
They're only students, after all.
I can't believe ﻿they fell for such an obvious diversion.
Wow, the Valvraves ﻿are so powerful...
They're our ﻿guardian angels.
Still, aren't they too powerful?
JIOR didn't have ﻿any weapon manufacturers, so how—
Ration time!
Those look ﻿tasty!
Thanks.
I'm starved!
What's that?
Emergency rations.
You told me ﻿to make some, remember?
What did you do ﻿with the recipe I gave you?
It's better if they ﻿taste good, right?
These are a JIOR specialty, ﻿jellied bean paste called "Youkan."
What counts is nutrition. ﻿Flavor doesn't—
Here!
See? Nice and ﻿sweet, huh?
We've been ﻿making these forever!
E-Enemy vessels detected!
But Haruto and ﻿Saki chased—
No, these are coming ﻿from up ahead!
It's not the same ﻿fleet as before!
They had another ﻿force out here?!
Where were they hiding?
Then we'll just have to ﻿defend against these, too!
But there's way more ﻿of them this time!
Quit your ﻿whining!
We don't need Haruto ﻿to defend ourselves!
The Module's ﻿being attacked?!
A different fleet moved in ﻿when you left!
You're saying ﻿we were lured away?
Miss Rukino ﻿let's head back!
If you want to go back, ﻿you'll have to go through us!
#3 bulkhead ﻿destroyed!
Enemy fleet now has us ﻿completely surrounded!
The Valvraves are ﻿pinned down!
You're some kind of war pro, ﻿aren't you?!
Do something!
What the—? ﻿What happened?
A power outage?! ﻿Why now?!
Damn it!
Hey, what the hell is going on?!
Open the door! Open the door, damn it!
Now's ﻿my chance!
What is it? ﻿What caused it?
The barriers must have put too big a strain ﻿on the generator system.
You could have mentioned ﻿that might happen!
Did Haruto and Saki ﻿get taken out?
That could ﻿never happen!
Then why has ﻿the power gone out?
Calm down, ﻿people!
Inuzuka-senpai!
Otamaya! Are you in here?
We need you ﻿to get the generators back—
Don't do it, Thunder! ﻿
That thing isn't what you think it is!
Get lost.
You're nothing but a lapdog ﻿tor that stinking detector!
You can't! This is—
You said you wanted to ﻿get revenge, too!
I know exactly how you feel!
But that's just your ego talking!
For everyone to survive, it should be piloted ﻿by someone with the knack for it!
You guys can wallow in your pity party on the net ﻿if you want...
But I don't want any of it.
I have to do something! Personally!
I'll never be able to ﻿live with myself if I don't get revenge!
It's to keep more people from dying!
It's so we can all be happy!
"We"? ﻿Who's "we"?
Does this "we" ﻿include you?!
Cause a "we" that don't include ﻿yourself don't mean jack!
When she laughed, ﻿it made me happy, too.
She didn't believe in herself, she was kind, and she could be happy for others.
She didn't like ﻿shiitake mushrooms.
She didn't like tragedies ﻿but she loved horror movies.
She looked so tiny when she cried ﻿that it made you want to hold her.
Made you want to kiss her.
Made you want to be with her forever!
What the hell are you ﻿talking about—
I don't want to ﻿do this for us.
I want to ﻿fight for myself!
There are 17 students ﻿with a pilot aptitude of rank A.
Of those, the ones with the mindset to get in ﻿voluntarily are the most suitable to be pilots.
This is...
This is what ﻿happened to him?
I've made up ﻿my mind!
Cain was having trouble ﻿against opponents like this?
In the end, ﻿he's only a spymaster.
They aren't spies.
The Karlstein Agency is ﻿a training school for agents that—
I know!
Main guns, fire at will! ﻿Blow their whole ceiling away!
Blitzendegen!
No!
We're done for!
What the—?
Our main ﻿guns!
Who is that?
God's touched ﻿me, too.
Isn't that ﻿right, Aina?
Form up! ﻿Waffen, position 7!
How do you ﻿like that?
Stupid amateur! ﻿Your back is wide open!
Oh, crap!
Take that, ﻿you Dorssian dick!
Yamada?!
It's "Thunder"'!
You... ﻿You hit "Yes"?
Oh, you mean that thing about ﻿resigning humanity or whatever?
Oh, you did it, ﻿too...
I'll explain later! ﻿For now...
Yeah! I'm gonna ﻿avenge Nobu!
It has ﻿eight arms?!
Ten, counting ﻿its original two!
I can ﻿see that!
Superconducting fluid accelerator ﻿cannon, prepare to fire!
But sir! At this angle, ﻿we'll hit our own forces!
That's ﻿an order!
Kyuma Inuzuka. ﻿068 is the enemy's flagship.
Crush the head ﻿of the snake, huh?
That's a siege cannon meant for ﻿assaulting fortified positions.
It's not the most ﻿accurate weapon...
But they're between us ﻿and the target!
Tell me, Aina...
If I had told you how I felt, ﻿would you have given me the go-ahead?
Would it have put you on the spot?
Or would it have made you happy?
Fire!
Aina!
Impossible!
The accelerator cannon ﻿was deflected?
Sure... ﻿
I understand, Aina!
Evasive!
There's ﻿no time!
No response from ﻿Commodore Manninger.
This makes ﻿four people.
Did they manage to ﻿reproduce them?
I knew it, ﻿I didn't mishear him!
Order all forces to withdraw.
This operation is over.
Thank you, ﻿Inuzuka-senpai!
Let me ride with you ﻿next time!
Hey, I saw you ﻿out there, Inuzuka!
Weren't you scared?
We can count on you, Senpai!
Way to go, ﻿Thunder!
I was wrong ﻿about you!
That's our Thunder!
You were awesome!
Got anything to say ﻿to me? I piloted it.
Escaping from solitary counts as a jailbreak.
You're in for another week.
You— ﻿Not even a freaking "Thank you"?!
I'm surprised.
I never expected to ﻿see you in one of these.
What, it's ﻿out of character?
Nope! It's exactly ﻿like you.
L-elf!
Haruto?
L-elf! What about ﻿our promise?!
These two decided on their own to get in.
What could I have done?
That's a load of bull!
You should have been able to tell ﻿that those first enemies were decoys!
You give me ﻿too much credit.
Cut it out.
Senpai!
This is ﻿for the best.
Haruto, from now on, ﻿let us fight alongside you.
But...!
I got dumped. Clearly.
Aina told me ﻿not to come join her.
It isn't working?
Even though ﻿it has an official number designation?
Takumi Kibukawa. ﻿ID number JS27-9154277.
Master Fellow attached to ﻿the JIOR Army #4 Research Institute.
Aside from Rion Nanami, ﻿all the teachers were in the JIOR military.
Why was that?
Not just the teachers.
The city residents, ﻿the dock workers, we were all military personnel.
Come again?
Dude, these are ﻿awesome!
Okay, let's make these ﻿our local specialty!
When we get to the Moon, we'll get a ton of tourists!
These things will sell like crazy
We'd better register ﻿a trademark, too!
I'm saying that Module 77, ﻿even the students...
all of it was created ﻿for the Valvraves.
Next time, episode 10, ﻿"Campaign Promise of Love".
Valvrave the Liberator...
The system that will expose the truth of the world.