True Calendar year 71.
Humanity, 70% of whom had been sent out into space, was largely divided into two powers.
The Dorssia Military Pact Federation, which developed out of military alliances,
and ARUS, the transatlantic treaty organization which expanded trade alliances.
Lying between these two superpowers, there was a third state that had gained economic prosperity:
JIOR.
A proponent of peace through neutrality.
Although they had been enjoying the blessings of peace and tranquility,
the course of history took a sharp turn towards chaos as a result of a sneak attack by the Dorssian military.
So what you're saying is that he isn't a Sakimori Academy student,
but is actually a Dorssian soldier?
Yes, sir.
Do you know anything else about him?
His name. It's "L-elf".
Hey, what's—
Stand up!
I give my word that your interrogation will be conducted in accordance with the New Guinea Treaty.
A hand mic.
An earthquake. A riot 3:14 PM.
The answer lies behind you.
It's ARUS!
This is the ARUS Lunar Orbital Forces.
Line up and wait your turn!
Are there any injured?
You're safe now!
Thank you, Senator Figaro!
The only adults left here are myself and Mr. Kibukawa, the physics teacher.
I'm so relieved!
Not at all, it's the least we could do.
We of ARUS and JIOR are friends, after all.
The school...
It seems like forever since last time I saw it.
Yeah, even though we had classes just yesterday.
At the shrine, I...
What about the shrine?
Well, uh...
Um, I...
It's Haruto!
Did he say Haruto?
He's alive!
What a relief!
Haruto!
Thanks, Tokishima!
When did you get a robot?
You were so cool, Haruto!
The herd's triumphant return, huh?
No, I'm not a—
You're welcome.
Haruto, here's my address!
Thank you, Haruto. Thank you...
Don't cry!
Yeah, we're safe now!
Come on, I can't help it...
She's right...
We've been saved.
During the New Guinea Conflict two years ago,
you kept our brigade of 5,000 men pinned down all by yourself.
Ever since, we've called you the One-man Brigade.
I never imagined that you would be so young.
That's the worlds GDP leader for you!
The world's policeman! The land of freedom!
You can always count on ARUS!
Oh, the sensation of being held tight by polymerized carbon cermet armor... What a rush!
I'm almost myself again!
Now that I'm out of those tattered rags, I feel like a woman!
You'd tell him how you felt if we survived, who did you mean?
Aw, but...
Better to regret something said than unsaid. If you're just not sure, just come out and tell him.
See, our life coach says so, too.
But it's not like Nanami has a boyfriend.
How did you know?
It sounds like Haruto doesn't really know, either.
He says he found the robot, and when he got in, he knew how to fight in it.
Oh.
It's hard to believe that Haruto of all people would have a knack for that.
Oh...
Did something happen between you and Haruto?
No.
Nothing... happened at all. That's why...
Temperature and pulse, both normal.
See? You're fine.
But...
...you can't call that normal.
We should have a doctor look at you.
The military should have doctors with them.
I wouldn't do that if i were you.
They'd just use him as a lab rat.
No way...
Adults are sleazeballs.
Rukino, did something happen to you?
What's wrong, Haruto?
Hey, Haruto! Haruto!
Haruto?
Cut it out, Haruto!
Haruto!
What's your problem?!
Haruto...
What did I do?
You attacked him, right out of the blue!
Like you were a vampire.
Just like that other time...
I knew it, I'm not human!
There's no telling what I'll to do you guys!
Calm down, Haruto!
But—
You used that power to save us all, remember?
But that doesn't mean... I...
Is Tokishima in here?
Do you have a minute?
Sure. What is it?
Senator Figaro says he'd like to speak with you.
Senator Figaro?
With me?
Welcome, Haruto Tokishima.
Um... It's good to meet you,
...Figaro.
Senator.
Senator...
You've never talked to a politician before?
I'd like to think that I'm not as scary as those Dorssian forces you defeated.
That's...
It was through these posts that we learned you were still putting up a fight here.
The user who uploaded the video was...
"Rainbow"?
If wonder if it's one of our students?
Beats me.
Why not post something?
People around the world are worried about your safety.
But I...
If you post, the people of JIOR might see it, too.
This is Haruto Tokishima.
We're fine. We were saved by the ARUS military.
Look, look! That high school boy says he's alive!
He's gotta be around the same age as us!
That's awesome!
Wonderful news has just come in!
We're told that that high school boy has posted a message!
Haruto! Let us invite you to our match!
Oh, no way! Was that the Goal King?
It was. Best-selling authors, gold medalists, and even our president have friended you.
Wow! This says your friend count is over 700 million!
The high schooler who took on the mighty Dorssian military all by himself.
They've given you the tagline,
"The Boy Who Took on the World.''
Do you like it?
I never wanted—
You're now the last hope of JIOR.
The symbol of the fight against Dorssia's schemes.
So are you telling me that I have to fight?
No. To run away.
What we drove off was just a single frontline unit.
If the main force that occupied your Sphere comes at you, you won't stand a chance.
You're running?
I'm not a soldier. I'm a coward.
And besides, running isn't losing.
Really losing is when you die.
In other words, surviving is a sort of victory.
Will you help us, Haruto Tokishima?
To help everyone survive?
Sure.
It's just a nutrient solution.
Failing to feed a prisoner is a treaty violation.
What happened?
Lights! Turn on the lights!
Freedom acquired.
Will now commence Plan D7.
Many thanks, Captain.
Your retrieving us was a big help.
Please allow us to participate in the recapture of Module 77.
You appear to be a man short.
He must have a good reason.
For L-elf of all people to have—
The fact is that he inflicted casualties on our forces.
I'm not averse to the word "friendship", you know.
The Valvrave has the absolute highest priority of all special missions.
I will overlook any irregularities resulting from it.
Recover the Valvrave without fail.
Blitzendegen.
Blitzendegen!
Form up by classes, please!
Make sure that the students before and after your student number are there!
It's all right! Just follow the military's instructions!
Haruto, can we really get away?
Don't worry. I'll protect you in the robot.
I guess that's okay, then.
We're all counting on you, Haruto!
Why's he cooperating?
The choice that avoids fighting is the best choice. That's so Haruto.
You really get him, don't you?
They grew up together. Shoko and Haruto.
You two.
Join the evacuation at once.
R-Right.
They're at cable car #1.
Where's Satomi?
Student Council President Renkoboji went to make a phone call.
A phone call? At a time like this?
He has a lot on his plate.
Ah... Anyway, join the evacuation right away, you two.
What's with the command form?
She's snooty to the core, I guess.
The enemy's coming! How long are you going to stay cooped up in your room?
Are you listening to me?! Hey!
If you don't hurry, you're gonna end up left behind!
Quit bugging me, big brother...
This is war! If you stay—
Wha—? Hey! Hello? Hello!
There's no need to rush! You can all fit in!
ARUS will help us, so please don't push!
A hand mic.
A hand mic...
Given the difference in relative troop strengths, their only choice is to retreat.
If they intend to conduct a smooth retreat, using a student is the best choice.
Influence, ideology, docility...
The conclusion this leads me to is...
Haruto Tokishima.
The Dorssian prisoner has escaped!
Height, 177cm! Hair, silver! Male! Age, 17!
Capture upon discovery!
I repeat, the Dorssian prisoner has...
I can't believe it took them 15 minutes to discover I had escaped.
Proficiency assessment, E.
We're fighting just one enemy!
Hem him in and hunt him down!
It's a student!
It's L-elf!
Shoot! Open fire!
He breached our perimeter?
All hands, arm yourselves! Commit our reserves, too!
Impossible... Our garrison is company-sized! 200 men!
Have you forgotten his nom de guerre, Captain?
The One-man Brigade...
Physical abilities and mental faculties, both normal.
Same as always.
Which leaves him as the only irregularity.
Is there anyone still here? We're about to leave!
Rukino?
Um... Thank you.
For what?
Earlier...
I was too scared to move, and you grabbed my hand and dragged me away, remember?
I owed you.
You're the only one who's never treated me differently from anyone else.
This might be our last look at it.
Don't be so maudlin.
Can you blame me?
Someone's still in the school!
It must be Haruto.
He said he was going to make sure no one was still there.
No, that wasn't him!
Shoko!
This vessel will now forcibly dock at Module 77!
But sir, the prisoner is still at large!
Further delays in the escape schedule cannot be tolerated.
Next up is an earthquake?
Come on, we're in space.
Haruto Tokishima, I presume?
You're— Yamada, right?
The name's Thunder!
Hand over that robot to me.
I have to get even for Nobu.
You cowards can run away if you want.
I can't do that! It's—
You wanna be the hero and hog all the glory?
We're all running! We're all going to live!
Spare me the excuses!
I'm pretty sure this is where I saw him...
I'm in!
No lifesigns! No thermal signatures detected!
Gate has been secured!
Change alert level. All hands, conduct check.
Course is clear!
Course is clear, sir!
Was I worried over nothing?
Smoke? An enemy attack?!
Fall back! Emergency reverse'
An earthquake? I don't believe it!
You've run aground?
Yes, sir. In our current condition, carrying out a large ship would be difficult.
I don't believe it... We're trapped here?
Is it true, what they're saying? We can't escape?
Answer us, soldier man!
You're gonna save us, right?
Is there any information?
What's going on?
A riot...
I'm telling you, that Dorssian prisoner is behind this!
Calm down! A single prisoner couldn't do all this!
That guy is no ordinary prisoner!
Please don't abandon us!
I don't want to be stuck here!
Everyone, calm down! Don't run!
A hand mic... An earthquake... A riot.
You!
Is that true? ARUS is your source?
N-No, I heard it from a student!
A student? Who?
3:14PM... The answer lies behind me.
Him! He said it!
Plan D7 complete.
You? You're the answer?
Make a pact with me, Haruto Tokishima.
What?
We're going to liberate Dorssia.
Next time, episode 4, The Hostage is Valvrave".
Valvrave... The system that will expose the truth of the world.