I always wanted to try that!
No manners at all...
Don't you want to try it, too, Haruto?
You do, right? I know you wanna!
No it's only you!
A week has passed since Shoko's declaration of independence.
Dorssia and ARUS' militaries are waiting to see who will blink first,
and as a result, Module 77 has found itself in an almost anticiimactic peace.
We're establishing a set of rules, and are getting by.
Admittedly...
...in this Neverland that's free of adults...
...we're enjoying ourselves quite a bit.
Things with Shoko are exactly the way they used to be.
Disappointingly enough...
It's so hot...
It's hot, all right...
But that's not the reason...
Hey! Let's use this to load up the supplies!
You don't have a license.
What's the problem?
You guys make the laws, and you're also the police.
I always wanted to try driving one of these!
Otamaya!
What's the big idea?
You're paying for that!
Shoko?
That feels great!
Me, too!
It's so cold!
Yay!
State of progress is 63%.
The evacuation team is slightly behind schedule.
Ma'am, what do we do about that?
Well, what if they went "Oo!" and then "Vroom vroom vroom!"?
The retrieval team is ahead of schedule.
What if we assigned some of them to the evacuation team?
That's the Student Council President for you!
It was nothing.
Still, it's so hot...
Is it because we're farther away from the artificial sun?
The system is working hard to make sure we don't get too cold.
Keep the temperature at 28°C at all times!!"
ARUS, Office of the President
You're officially recognizing them, sir?
You can't give in to their childish threats!
Perhaps, but support for them among ARUS citizens is growing.
Thinking ahead to the next election, it would be a good idea to side with them.
These are children we're dealing with.
We just need to humor them.
Keep your priorities straight.
The real threat to our country is—
Dorssia Military Pact Federation Capital
Gentlemen!
What is the state?
What one thing above all else does every citizen require and desire?
The answer is - life!
There can be no freedom or equality without life!
No matter how just the cause or sound the reasoning, without power, they fall on deaf ears!
The state is power!
We must not forget the tragedy of Red Thursday!
We will change the future, and on the blood of our lost comrades,
we will win absolute, undisputed victory for Dorssia!
Blitzendegen!
This is beyond JIOR... no, far beyond the technological level of humanity.
Professor Tokishima... what demon did you make a deal with?
Professor! Professor Kibukawa!
You're still recuperating, and yet what are you doing here?
Starting today, I'm going to stay in here.
I'm going to figure out what this thing is.
It gets my physics teacher blood boiling.
You can't! You're the oldest person here, not to mention a proper teacher!
So you have to keep everyone in line!
I'm just not cut out for that stuff.
I'll leave that to you, Nanami.
That's so irresponsible!
Hey!
Sheesh!
This is—
I created a page for people to make donations.
Money again, huh?
Money is important, right?
It lets you buy food and medicine, and even hire mercenaries.
How much have we collected?
You were expecting to make more, weren't you?
If each one of your friends had donated just 1 yen, we'd have 700 million yen!
And yet... And yet...
What the—?
Don't panic! Call an electrician!
We don't have them.
Snow...?
It's probably a malfunction in the environmental regulation system.
The pulse coils' charged current could be causing a magnetic field resonance with other systems,
which would throw the central air temperature system out of whack.
I think it's trying to set the entire Module into winter mode.
Uh...
In other words, it's interfering with the magnetic field distribution, and—
Oh, you're talking about triangular wave interference?
You know what that is?
I love machines.
Wow, otaku are amazing!
All professionals are otaku at heart.
Then come with me!
Wait, I wasn't volunteering!
You're gonna fix it!
We're all counting on you!
You can do it!
Otamaya!
Good luck!
It's all up to you!
We're all watching!
Keep climbing, damn it!
B-but we're so high up!
You are the only person who knows this stuff!
Show some backbone! Aren't you a man?!
Stop it, stop it!
I wonder if the boys will be okay?
Is it me, or has it gotten colder?
It's gonna get worse.
Yeah, it's absolute zero outside.
Really?
Are you okay?
We can't have you getting sick on us, not now.
We have just the thing!
We made it ourselves!
Ultra Lifeform Gyaora!
Well? This look like the place?
It's probably... around here somewhere...
That's the control panel, so it should be...
Thanks...
Geez, you are one clumsy nerd...
Sorry...
Hold still, damn it!
I found it!
Found it.
I can't believe it was down here...
Are we gonna die here?
Don't talk like that!
But...
Mom...
It'll be okay.
It'll be nice and warm soon, and your mom is—
Don't talk irresponsibly.
When you get right down to it, you got us into this mess, didn't you?
Yeah! It's all because you said we should declare independence, Shoko!
It was insane to think we could found a country by ourselves.
That is...
Are you idiots?
You just went with the flow.
It's your fault too.
What was that?!
"Sewing Room.Writing on the desks and food and drink are strictly prohibited."
You're almost all the way in!
And... got it!
You're in!
It smells...
But at least it's warm.
Stop it! Miss Rukino didn't mean anything by it!
She should watch her tone when addressing an upperclassman!
Does her being a former entertainer make her a bigshot?
What's going on out here?
Haruto!
Calm down, please.
This is no time to be fighting amongst—
You be quiet, Satomi!
Yes, ma'am!
Don't address the student council president in such a familiar manner!
Then you call him that, too. Call him Satomi.
As I thought, it's useless.
What are you doing?!
How much longer, damn it?
Sorry. Almost done.
Hey, I think your gunshot wound might still be—
Just do your job!
Everybody out there is gonna freeze to death, right?
I don't want any more of my classmates to die on me!
This is against school rules!
Shut up!
Senpai!
You're the cause of all this!
Yeah!
Please stop this!
Okay? Okay?
Stop it!
What good is fighting going to do?
Tokishima, let's—
Now, when the whole world is our enemy!
Let's step outside.
I'll teach you some manners!
Mob rule and violence, interesting "manners" you have here.
You're talking back to Takahi-senpai?
Don't be so uppity, first-year!
You're schoolmates!
Hey, Tokishima!
Let go of me!
Violence doesn't scare me.
Please, call it discipline.
What nerve!
I said stop it!
1... 2... 3... Go!
Jingle bells, jingle bells jingle all the way... Yay!
There you go again, spouting crazy talk...
I thought that singing would warm our bodies and our souls!
Are you stupid?
I'm done with you people.
I'll be the one to decide!
That'll show her!
Stop it!
Come on, reach!
Pervert.
It's not what you think! It's not!
Nooo!
I-I'm sorry!
Hey!
It wasn't on purpose!
What are you doing?!
Thank goodness...
We're saved!
The lights are on!
It's so warm!
The boys did it!
I'm not in the mood anymore.
Please wait!
Takahi-sama!
Miss Rukino, are you okay?
I'm used to it.
Wait!
Shoko, that thing you did—
That thing?
Oh, right!
A song!
Sis, we're connected!
We're connected to the external net via encrypted channel!
Is the mic feed already hooked up to this?
Yeah, we're ready over here.
People of JIOR, can you hear me?
We're all safe. We're doing fine.
We wanted to tell you that, so we all, um...
We all decided to broadcast this video!
So, enjoy!
"SAKIMORI ACADEMY"
Forgetting your cell phone at home,
fghting with the person you like...
Some days, nothing seems to go your way.
But just eat a tasty dinner
and hang out with your goofy friends...
It's because of stuff like that that we'll be able to give our best again tomorrow.
YOUTH!!
Never give in,
no matter what.
Youth now!
Good luck for you, for you.
For happiness.
Big kiss for you, for you.
For our life.
Just all-out like that all the time.
I know you are hero in your life.
I know I am hero in my life.
Welcome to our life.
Let's go have fun!
Look at all these viewers!
We're being accessed from ARUS, too.
There's really no such thing as a lost lamb.
"Fighting spirit", "Sprint flat out", "Sakimori Sports Club"
Everyone has nights that wreck their self-confidence.
Haggard faces on the weekend from night after night of no sleep.
"JIOR Spirit!"
You're here with me and will take me to the sun!
Good luck for you, for you.
For happiness.
Big kiss for you, for you.
For our life.
I can't keep on smiling,
but that's okay.
I know you are hero in your life.
I know I am hero in my life.
In this life that's full of thrills, let's go have fun!
People of JIOR! We're all fine!
If this song reaches you, I know we'll meet again one day!
Let's believe in that!
Fight!
Let's do it!
Mom, are you watching?
The plan was for that song to reach our families, but it looks like it reached the people of ARUS, too!
I'm sure it's reached the people of JIOR, too!
Yeah!
Right! Let's get Haruto to write a thank-you post!
Where is he?
With the exploration party.
He said we should know this Module inside and out.
We'll leave that part to you!
Good luck!
Thanks for all the help.
Coming along as record-keeper, you mean?
No, I meant the song.
I thought you hated doing that kind of thing.
I do.
But at the same time, I'm grateful.
I hadn't done any singing since I got into this school.
What is it?!
This is...
There are more curses...
It's like a rainbow!
Wait!
Would you mind keeping this a secret just between us?
I don't want there to be any more people like me.
Fine.
But in return, let's be lonely together.
"Is this sex?"
Next time, episode 6,
"Saki, Come Back!"
Valvrave the Liberator...
The system that will expose the truth of the world.