The Master Plan just came in from Army Command.
In the six months following the opening of hostilities, ARUS will focus on defense,
leveraging our national strength and vast territory.
During that time, we will devote all of ARUS' energies into mass-producing this weapon.
That JIOR weapon?
They say it defeated an entire Dorssian fleet all by itself.
We can hold out easily enough for six months.
To win, we need to fight.
Enter your votes now.
Once we have confirmation that the JIOR secret weapon has been taken back,
ARUS will enter into an all-out war against Dorssia.
We will liberate Dorssia. Only through changing its foundation will the world change.
You... But aren't you a Dorssian soldier?!
Factoring in your abilities and the Valvrave, my revolution will come three years earlier.
Possess Senator Figaro. Talk with their President, and—
Are you kidding me?! You're our enemy!
You killed me!
Be that as it may, your only option is to choose me.
I'll add an incentive, of course.
I'll save this entire school.
As well as your girl.
It's no use! It's completely impassable!
You mean we're sealed in here?!
Send in some engineers! Hurry!
Hey! Cut it out!
Hang on! Hang on, okay?
Darn it, cut that out!
That transmission just now, what—
That hurt...
Are you a Sakimori student?
What was that transmission just now?
Hey, who—
Don't tell!
Don't tell anyone about me.
This isn't a situation where you can stand on principle.
If there's something you want to protect, get your hands dirty, Haruto Tokishima.
The Valvrave!
Hey, right! I can use that to free the stranded ship—
It's useless.
Your only hope for a future is to make a pact with me.
How can I know that unless I try?
My predictions are effectively prophecies.
Have any of them been wrong?
I... I promised myself that I would protect them.
Even if I have to use that curse to do it!
You will make a pact with me.
When you're ready, give me this sign.
I'll save you.
Are you kidding? Give you the peace sign?
Peace sign?
We're not on the same wavelength at all.
Senator Figaro!
Ah, Haruto!
He's an ace who shot down seven fighters in the Andaman Campaign.
Don't do this! It's dangerous!
Danger is a soldier's business.
Don't do it! Don't get into it!
A guide program?
That so JIOR-like, eh?
It's displaying a seriously cute picture.
Can you see this?
This is bad... Don't touch anything!
That robot is cursed!
What kind of program is this?
Impossible!
That's not what happened when I used it...
Get back! It's not safe!
Why?
Enemy defensive forces are a single battalion deployed in a flat plane.
We outnumber them 14 to 1.
Our victory is not in doubt.
It's not a matter of victory or defeat.
It is how we win.
What's going on?! I thought we still had time before the Dorssian fleet got here!
Those tremors were from cannon fire!
I have it. We'll leave the students behind.
Have a high-speed ship standing by at the auxiliary gate.
We will escape, taking only this robot with us.
Right, right. Forget about the students.
Work quickly.
No way!
You said that we would all escape together!
We did come here to rescue you, that's the truth.
But in order of priority, that came second.
Kindness and volunteer work are just pastimes to spend extra time and money on.
Games meant to garner appreciation.
Senator Figaro... What are you saying?
That we're the ones who get to decide whether or not we'll help you.
Are you kidding me?!
Calm down!
You're saying that now?!
Huh? It doesn't work? I have to touch the skin?
You...!
Go easy on him.
We're taking him with us as research material.
You liar!
You're an adult! Aren't you ashamed of yourself?!
Not in the least. I'm an adult.
Don't worry, everyone!
We've been told that those tremors earlier were from a malfunction in the gravity generator!
I'd like to get our escape preparations back underway as soon as repairs are complete.
For now, please wait patiently.
That's a lie... That man is lying...
What do we do? What should we do?
Right... We were fighting...
Shoko!
I've been looking everywhere for you!
Everyone's in the school building.
Senpai.
We're in a lot of trouble.
The 40th Student Council Petitions Committee is now in session.
ARUS is lying!
Why would they need to lie?
Do you have any proof?
I heard a military transmission!
The ARUS military encrypts their messages
and then transmits across a wide frequency spectrum using the latest scramble codes.
You couldn't have heard it.
I had help from—
Don't tell anyone!
From, um...
Should we adjourn, then?
I suppose so.
In that case, I declare this committee meeting closed.
Wait, you have to believe me!
If I'm going to put my trust in someone, it's going to be in ARUS.
They're gonna run! And leave us behind!
And yet they had the nerve to take that robot!
As soon as the Module's gravity generator is repaired, we'll set out immediately.
Bring us evidence, and we'll hear you out.
Miss Sashinami, what are you—
I'm not lying.
Shoko, don't!
Let go! I have to prove myself!
What does taking off your clothes have to do with that?!
I don't get that girl...
I want them to believe me!
I'm not lying!
All right! All right, already!
I said, all right!
You mean it? You said "All right," didn't you?
You did, right?!
Yes, so please put your clothes on!
Awesome!
Is she some kind of idiot?
But it worked.
Thank you for all your hard work, ARUS soldiers!
We all wanted to express our gratitude.
Gratitude?
Yes, our gratitude!
This way! While Takahi has them distracted!
Let's go find proof that those guys are liars.
And now... We will sing the school song of JIOR National Sakimori Academy!
Here in the city great and fair
of the rising sun
we shine far brighter
than the stars.
A new world
and new dreams,
our ideal is to make them come true one day.
Watch over our path, о brightly shining Sakimori.
What the—?
"Sakimori"
echoes throughout the world, "Sakimori Academy."
I love how students are so docile.
Everything is ready, sir.
Good, bring out Haruto Tokishima.
We'll leave as soon as this song is over.
East and West, past and present,
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Understood, sir.
it calls out to us to return...
You're being moved, Haruto Tokishima.
I'm amazed you knew about these tunnels, Otamaya.
The Miss Sakimori Pageant uses the gym's locker room as their dressing room every year.
W-Wait, you've been—
What was that?
You damn kids!
It's the real thing!
Haruto?
Haruto!
Shoko, thanks!
They've been holding you prisoner this whole time?
You aren't here to rescue me?
Then your phone...
It's nothing! Forget it!
I feel so stupid...
Everyone, thank you for the wonderful song.
Not at all, we're ashamed that this is the best we could do to thank the people we owe our lives to.
Next, we'd like—
I appreciate it, but we're pressed for time.
No way, we insist that you see it!
I'm terribly sorry. Please hold that thought for some other time.
Get us out of here.
Hey, wait!
Get us moving, I said!
Don't let them fool you!
Everybody, ARUS plans to abandon us and escape by themselves!
They're here to rescue us, aren't they?
No way, we even fed them.
That isn't true, is it, Senator Figaro?
Okay, old man!
Is what he said true?
You're going to rescue us, right?
ARUS always does the right thing, right?
Senator...
Call me Moses.
I'm about to part this sea of students.
Wha—
It can't be...
Get inside the school building, everyone! Hurry!
Yamada-san! Yamada-san!
Crap...
Clear the road! If you don't move, I'll gun you down!
So he's shown his true colors, huh?
The Valvrave!
Haruto!
Bastard!
This belongs to me!
You're just a student!
Hey, are you okay?
Hey!
Get down from the transport!
Hey, wait a minute! This is a joke, right?
Do it!
Just as I thought. It only works if I make direct contact with the skin.
I understand. Bit by bit, I'm learning.
But...
Get up, Satomi.
It's all over... We can't take on a whole army.
You said you were going to stay on top until graduation, remember?
It's not like he's your friend...
But...
Forget about these students!
Hurry up and get us out of here!
Please put down your weapons! Now!
All right!
Others too!
Thank you, Haruto!
Not so funny now, is it?!
Let's hear it for Haruto!
We ended up getting saved by Haruto again, huh?
Don't worry.
Unlike you, he won't tell you to pay him for it.
I'd never take money from friends.
This means we're safe now, right?
No, you're not.
The situation is no different from before.
He's...!
This Module is already surrounded by Dorssia.
I don't believe it!
How would a second-year know that?
If the gravity generator malfunction was a lie, what were those tremors afterwards?
Come to think of it...
If it was a ship running aground, there should have only been one tremor.
You're saying it was an enemy attack?
Except for this Module, all of JIOR has been occupied by Dorssia. Meaning...
...they've essentially taken your family members hostage.
Hostage?
No...
But Dorssia might do it.
What do you expect us to do about it?!
Let's surrender! It's not too late!
Mom...
His sign...
You're telling me to make that pact with you?
Haruto Tokishima you will choose me.
I'm going to end up doing exactly as he says again...
Haruto!
Shoko?
We're surrounded by Dorssia...
And we can't trust ARUS.
What should we do?
L-Let's surrender. We did all we could.
I don't want to die!
Is surrendering all we can do?
We can't fight against Dorssia!
It'll be okay!
We won't let Dorssia lay one finger on our families!
How do you suggest we do that?!
They have hostages! If they threaten us with them—
Exactly! We threaten them back!
What?
We tell them that if they hurt our families, we'll hand this robot over to ARUS!
They won't fall for blackmail like—
That robot is the key that will change the outcome of the war...
Um...
Use a robot as a hostage?
That will work!
It'll work!
Great idea!
I never would have thought of that!
Mr. ARUS Senator!
We can't give you the robot.
Nevertheless, keep fighting alongside us, just like before!
Are you kidding me?! As if we would let you manipulate us like that!
In that case, we'll just hand this robot over to Dorssia!
What?!
I look forward to our two countries continuing as before in their amicable relationship!
Um... That means...
It means that neither Dorssia nor ARUS can lay a hand on us.
Our families are safe, too!
And ARUS will stay our ally!
That was awesome, Shoko!
Nice idea!
We're saved!
Shoko, you're...
The path ahead is clear! Waffe squadron, charge!
Valvrave, why aren't you showing yourself?
Don't be in such a rush, Highness.
Lieutenant! It's Lieutenant now.
You saw it on the net, right? It wasn't L-elf piloting it.
We haven't seen that weapon before!
Be careful!
After him!
What the...?
They're damaging their own Module?
Captain!
Everybody! Let's stop depending on others!
Instead of using anything else as a crutch, let's stand on our own two feet!
We're declaring independence!
Make no mistake! Your enemies are back here!
As of right now, we're independent!
Our school is an independent country, an equal of both Dorssia and ARUS!
Preposterous! You can't have a country with nothing but children!
Can we form a country?
Seriously?
Sounds like fun!
Very well, let's now take a vote.
Those in favor of independence, please raise your hands.
For it!
Me too!
Count me in on your crazy idea!
No, we ought to carefully consider this.
Do we have another option?
The Module's separating?
Yeah, independence!
Our own country!
Independence! Independence!
I'm for Shoko's idea!
Who in the world is that woman?
Shoko Sashinami!
The daughter of JIOR's prime minister!
Independence! Independence!
What's this strange sensation?
I haven't laughed in a long, long time.
Next time, episode 5, Singing Sakimori Academy".
Valvrave... The system that will expose the truth of the world.