Third Galactic Empire, Year 214
The limit, huh?
That's nothing but an archaic weapon.
To have fought the Royal Guard to a standstill for 40 stunde,
you Golden Seven live up to your reputation.
Nevertheless...!
The Condemnation Mirage?!
This this—
Even after two hundred years, a promise is a promise.
Right?
I can't believe there were more of them...
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize, Haruto.
Yeah, you should show some more backbone!
In any event, these will prove to be invaluable firepower.
The Student Council will take charge of them.
You can't!
Why not?
Because...
You have no right to tell us what to do with them.
Vice-President, go fetch the Student Council Property stamp.
Please don't do this!
I won't let you touch the Valvraves!
I was chosen by vote to represent the entire student body.
He might hate competition and stuff, but this is the one area where he's bullheaded...
When Haruto gets like this, he won't listen to anybody.
You know him really well, don't you?
One time, we ran away from home together, and he—
Hey, don't tell them about that!
But I think it's a cute story!
Only you would think that!
You two...
Oh! Sorry...
Mr. President, no one knows these robots better than Haruto.
Perhaps we should let him decide?
He can't get his way all the time!
I cast my vote with her proposal.
Same here.
Me, too.
Sorry, Satomi.
That's a majority.
Democracy in action.
You can't be serious!
If you want to vote, put it before the entire—
Hold on, now!
I'm going to check these over.
No one will get into them until after that.
No way!
After all, teachers are responsible for the safety of their students.
President!
Thank you.
I did it because when you get like that, you always have a good reason.
Shoko...
That completes my mission from captain Cain.
And now...
Next!
Uh, I don't—
He says it's combat training.
Next! Who's next?!
It's to take his mind off things.
Thunder was dying to pilot a Valvrave.
Yamada doesn't know...
When you pilot one, you stop being human.
That's why you didn't tell anyone that you found those Valvraves?
There's a lot of things that I was able to protect, thanks to it, but I'm scared of it.
Every time I get the feeling that I turned into an animal, and I'm always afraid...
...that this indestructible body is someone else's.
And that maybe I'm...
...really dead.
It's okay.
You're a human being, Haruto.
You're our friend.
Now... and forever.
Thanks, Aina.
I'm sorry!
Shit...
Why do they do what Sashinami says?
I think you were right, Mr. President.
I know, right?
That's how it'd normally be, right?
Yes!
Satomi? For a second.
What are... What are you doing?
Takahi?
Takahi...
No good.
No. This's totally different.
W-What just— Why did—
Big brother is bugging out.
What's that?
Hey, where's the salt?
Here.
Thank you!
That looks like it could turn you into a frog...
Doesn't it look delicious?
It's got tons of veggies, too!
Oh, that rich aroma...
Anyway, give it a taste.
Um, thanks, but I think I'll pass.
Miss Rukino, are you okay?
Here, have some water!
Not to worry!
I boiled the heck out of those veggies, so you don't have to worry about chok—
That was great...
Figures, since it was cooked by a girl whose appearance is deceiving.
Are you complimenting me?
The biggest I can give.
That's delicious!
That's awesome, Shoko!
Give me the recipe!
I'm surprised you could cook!
It's not that surprising!
Thanks, Miss Rukino. For helping out.
I'm sorry for being so useless.
But I hate being in someone's debt.
Cheering me on. Earlier.
Oh, hey, that was fun! Let's do it again!
I'm not sure if I'd call it "fun"...
That's quite good, actually.
Um, your name was...
Ham-elf!
It's L-elf.
Be careful.
This guy is a Dorssian soldier.
No way!
Sashinami Shoko.
Me?
Take this.
I've written out the future of your country.
This is...
"A Plan Regarding the Military Development and Territorial Expansion of New JIOR"...
"Pilot Selection Tests"...
"Establishment of Alliance With ARUS"...
"Implementation of Total Military Conscription"...
You want to turn us into a military state?
That is this country's only means of survival.
No, thanks.
Negotiations have broken down, huh? In that case...
Hey!
What's going on?
The alarm isn't going off!
Citizens of New JIOR.
This voice...
This country is now under the control of L-elf Karlstein.
All citizens are hereby subject to mandatory conscription.
He can't be serious!
You will give your lives to pave the way for the growth of the state.
He's launched a coup d'etat, huh?
Kyuma Inuzuka, it isn't safe to stand there.
What?!
I have set traps throughout the school building.
If you do not wish to die, I suggest that you remain where you are.
Gimme a break!
I'm Thunder, the gang leader of Sakimori Academy!
No way, this is the third floor!
It's all about guts!
Never underestimate a man's fighting spirit!
If you're here, I take it that means there aren't any traps in here.
True enough.
I didn't anticipate this situation.
I owe you some payback from earlier.
But can you?
Quit trying to act so tough!
Miss Rukino!
I had no need to anticipate it.
End of story.
I don't understand girls at all.
Miss Rukino, you mean?
I can't believe she was suddenly so eager to help Shoko with the cooking...
I think it was to thank her.
Thank her?
She's kind of a stickler for that.
I remember one other time...
Scissors!
I'm taking another picture!
Hey, they say that guy is single now!
Get in there and make your move!
Here.
For your knee.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
Someone who can thank people is a good person at heart.
Just like when you became a Kamitsuki.
Kamitsuki?
Oh, from the biting...
No, not like that. I meant...
I think you've been touched by God.
By God?
Yes.
You're indestructible, can possess people, and can pilot that amazing robot...
I think only God could be behind that.
Kamitsuki...
Kamitsuki, huh?
I like it. It's way better than "monster."
Citizens of New JIOR.
This country is now under the control of L-elf Karistein.
Tokishima Haruto, report to classroom 2-B immediately.
What did he say?!
I will have you operate your Valvrave as the core of our national defense force.
That bastard!
I should've known better.
I didn't expect him to go up against the entire school by himself.
That's far enough.
If I blow your brains out, I suspect that even you will die.
How...?!
That was me from 15 minutes ago.
A recording, huh?
If you're this gullible, you'll never be able to protect those precious to you.
Precious to me?
I recall telling you it was a phantasy.
A world without conflict.
A-drei!
Even with one eye, I'd recognize you anywhere!
So that's how it'll be?
I anticipated combat in here, as well.
Where is he?
Damn—
Don't move.
It's impossible for me to believe that you would turn traitor.
If you don't believe, what are you going to do?
Forgive me? For shooting out your eye?
I forgive you.
You are going to be my right hand man one day.
One eye is a small price to pay for the ultimate hand.
I have no intention of becoming anyone's right hand.
What?
I've found a right hand of my own.
Who?
Set the school free...
Why are you alive?
Stop this.
That's my line!
We're never going to be your soldiers!
Put down your gun!
That is my right hand.
Set the school free...
This country needs me.
Come to your senses, L-elf!
Hey! Are you alive in here?!
Prof. Kibukawa, how did you—
I am a physics teacher, you know.
I'll keep them safe...
You, a fool who can't even calculate properly?
L-elf! Come back to us!
How did that get in?!
Q-vier! I've left the gate open!
Capture him!
That's too much trouble!
I thought I told you to capture him, Q-vier!
You're such a sentimental softy, Highness!
I'm gonna blow him to hell in my Carmilla!
Oh, so that's where you are, huh?
He's running, he's running!
The great L-elf is running!
Stop it, Q-vier!
Why? Traitors deserve to die!
If I don't, we're gonna get a nasty scolding.
He's not a traitor!
Your upbringing was noble to a fault.
What the—
Skewers?!
Come back some other time.
Kicked out the door, huh?
Talk about pathetic!
Switch to Plan B.
All units, take up siege formation and commence attack.
They had a force waiting outside, huh?
Where's Tokishima Haruto?
Today, I'm gonna show you some new steps I worked up just for you.
So, it's come out... H-neun.
I know, I know, stick to the plan!
They're running?
He wants a one-on-one fight, huh?
I'd love to, but...
What are these?
These things are—
Adhesive electromagnetic boomerangs created as a peacekeeping measure.
These will keep you from moving.
Miss Rukino!
What's keeping Tokishima Haruto?
Should I amputate the leg?
No, that would impede his ability to pilot the Valvrave.
There's no time to remove this beam.
The conclusion I'm led to is...
The temperature is climbing!
You're awake?
L-elf...
Your leg has been skewed by a steel beam, you can't move.
So what now?
If I can't pilot my Valvrave,
you have no use for me?
Use my body.
Ordering me around again, huh?
There's no guarantee that my body will activate the Valvrave.
Nevertheless, there is no other way.
Do you seriously expect me to trust you?
It's the choice with the best chance of success.
Unit IV's radiant heat is at 80% capacity!
At this rate...!
If I die, you'll die with me!
I've factored in that risk.
Move!
All wrapped up and ready to take home!
Haruto!
Didn't you kill him?!
I thought I had!
Haruto, watch out for these boomerang things!
"Adhesive electromagnetic boomerangs"...
Exactly as he predicted?
"Only target the unit that launches the boomerangs," huh?
H-neun! Crossfire!
Roger!
It's fast!
Pinpoint accuracy like that...
This is—
Hand-to-hand combat, huh? With pleasure!
Fall back, H-neun! Gain distance!
Let's do it!
"H-neun tends to choose hahd-to-hand combat against opponents who get close."
What is that guy, a prophet?
What?!
"Objective is not to defeat the target, but rather to destroy the launcher."
There!
H-neun, are you all right?
Sorry, I got careless.
That wasn't the result of carelessness.
They have L-elf on their side.
I knew, he really was a traitor.
Our first plan has hit a roadblock.
We'll fall back and come up with a new one!
He's body-jacked someone?
Guess I'd better take you somewhere before somebody sees you like this.
Oh, you were here—
We pulled through somehow...
What's this mean, I'm invincible if I work with you?
Licht... "Light"?
A girl?
Why...?
Next time, episode 8.
"Princess of Light".
Valvrave the Liberator...
The system that will expose the truth of the world.