ANIME-KOI
PRESENTS
onnanoko hajimemashita
A tired girl starts her day
tameiki wa bioron no shirabe ni nite
With a sigh like the moan of a violin
akai mi hajikechatta
A cherry bursts in her mouth
mada anata wo shiranai
This was before we had met
konna koto hajimetette
This is the first time I've ever felt like this
manazashi wa aku no hana sakimidarete mo
I could see that your pretty eyes were filled with contempt
ie e to tsuzuku
But I had to go home
basu sutoppu demo anata wa tsurenai
Even at the bus stop, you gave me the cold shoulder
karameta hanabi myaku utsu
The fireworks in the sky pulse
koi no shiruetto
In a silhouette of love
karui mahou
With a little magic,
usotsuki na kuchibiru
Two sets of lying lips
sou kasaneteru
Lock together
ano ne
You see
nee kamisama
God...
warui ko ni naritai yo
I'd like to be a naughty girl
ii ko ni shiteru kara
I'm tired of being good
onegai dayo
So, please
zurui koto sasetoite
It's for a good reason
ii koto shitai nara
So let me be bad for once
sukaato hirogaesu shite
By flipping my skirt
sugu kaeru yo
I'll be back soon
doyoubi wa haresou da
It looks like Saturday is going to be sunny
kamisama hajimemashita
God, it has already started
Nanami has just traveled back in time with the assistance of Mizuki's Route of Time.
In her quest to recover the Dragon King's right eye, she encountered the former Tomoe.
However, the Tomoe she has come to know and the one standing in front of her are two different beasts.
The Deity
Goes to The
Palace of The
Dragon King!
The Deity
Goes to The
Palace of The
Dragon King!
Is that... the Dragon King's eye?
Wait!
Tomoe!
He's leaving!
Do you really think you can catch up on foot?
Are you sure you're a deity?
Sorry.
I should've known this Tomoe wouldn't recognize me.
Where do you think he's going?
Well, he has fish and one of the Dragon King's eyes. A banquet, perhaps?
We need to get the eye back!
Maybe if we just explained the situation...
Dummy. That's not going to work.
We have to wait for an opportunity and then snatch it.
I mean, you have to.
Snatch?
He's going there?
Probably.
It smells like the sea.
You went all the way out there to get medicine for me?
Yeah...
But what I get in return is well worth it.
Take this, and you'll surely get better.
Yukiji, never leave me.
He looks the same and sounds the same, but I barely recognize him.
Everything he's doing is for that woman.
She's beautiful...
Nanami-chan has probably never felt jealous, as I used to be.
The medicine is probably too hard to ingest like this. I'll go fetch some water from the spring.
I'll be right back.
Nanami-chan, aren't you going to take the eye?
Do it, Nanami-chan.
If I were you, I wouldn't hesitate.
After all, that woman's an eyesore.
Hang in there!
Just swallow this, and you'll get better!
Come on...
What are you doing, Nanami-chan?
Mizuki!
Didn't you come here to get the eye back?
Why are you giving it to her?
But...
Do you really want to give it to her? You won't regret it?
I want to save Tomoe.
But I can't just sit by and watch a person suffer either!
So I have to...
Thank you, Mizuki.
Why?!
Here, Yukiji-san.
Thank goodness.
She seems to have gotten better.
Let's go, Nanami-chan.
I can't keep us here forever.
Time's up.
I can't make him pay his dues from the past.
I have to pay it back with something from the present.
Tomoe...
Welcome back.
Mizuki!
Crack
You would be wise not to make any sudden movements.
Your body is probably in pain.
It's not exactly happy with the stress of time travel.
Anyway, what's your plan now?
Do you think I could still find Isohime today?
Isohime?
What do you plan on doing?
She said something to me.
If you give me the Dragon King's eye inside you, I'll give you this in return.
She said I had the eye in me.
She offered to trade her clothes for it.
That might be the key to saving Tomoe.
You have a shop here of all places, Miss?
Only at night, though.
You can make any lady fall for you with just one bite of this!
Hm, I wouldn't mind trading it for that gold ring you have there.
Huh?
Wh-What the hell just happened? Was that the tide?!
Crap, let's get out of here!
Yeah.
Wait a minute!
You haven't changed in five-hundred years, have you?
I have to say, it did make finding you a cakewalk.
Wh-What do you want?
I want to trade!
What?
Bla bla  bla bla
Bla bla bla bla
Yeah, yeah...
Bla bla  bla bla
Bla bla bla bla
Yeah, yeah...
Bla bla  bla bla
Bla bla bla bla
Yeah, yeah...
Bla bla  bla bla
What's that?!
You'll give me the Dragon King's eye?
Where? Where is it?
This person's just a bit different from five-hundred years ago!
And that's not what I meant!
If the Dragon King's eye is really inside me, I want you to get it out for me.
Let's see here...
Hm, yes... Yes. You have one, though it's small.
It's definitely an eye.
Really?!
Regardless of what you might think, my eye doesn't lie.
I'll do it. However, I'd like to hear what I'm getting in return.
Anything!
As long as it's within my ability...
Well, then...
Can I have thirty years of your life?
It's a bargain!
Thirty years? You're shrewd.
Huh?
You don't need to trust her, Nanami-chan.
What? Can you grab the eye yourself, then? You don't even know where it is!
My eyes have a certain quality of clairvoyance to them!
There's nothing I can't see!
Snake boy should butt out. This is a job for an adult.
Fine, you can have thirty years.
Wha—
What a bright girl! You understand!
Nanami-chan!
Don't do it...
It's fine. I'm still young.
Thirty years won't kill me.
But Tomoe only has a day left.
She's an idiot.
She's not supposed to be able to do anything, so why is she choosing this path?
She keeps biting off more than she can chew.
I can't deal with this.
Okay, lie on your side.
I'll let you pay later.
Relax, this won't take long.
My eyes see everything. I knew you had something much better to offer than your life.
Miss Deity!
Talk about luck! You have the Dragon King's eye and the mark of the Earth Deity!
Don't mind if I help myself to both!
See? Told you.
You should've listened to me, Nanami-chan.
Tomoe-kun's only reaping what he sowed.
There was no need for you to sacrifice yourself.
Nanami-chan, I don't understand you.
If you're so bent on helping people without even a familiar to protect you...
I'll help you once more.
This is the best...
I can do to show you my loyalty.
The weight in my heart is lifting.
How did you...
As long as I'm with her,
I can be myself.
We'll be back soon!
We're back!
I see that you've awoken, my new master..
Huh?
I decided to be your new familiar!
Forget Tomoe-kun! You'll be blown away by how much better I am!
Hold on, rewind. What's going on?
That's why... you see...
Isohime, don't think that you can get away with harming my master.
Mizuki, don't kill her!
The absolute power of her words...
This testament to my everlasting loyalty...
A sweet numbness is overcoming me...
The feeling of being ordered by a deity is splendid!
I can't get enough! Bind me tighter with your invisible chains!
You're sick, Mizuki!
You basically just told me that you kissed me while I was asleep!
Molester! Sexual harassment!
That's not exactly what happened, but at least you understand the situation.
So this is the Dragon King's eye?
It's like a pinball.
The size and shape don't matter. It's still the Dragon King's eye!
Let's hurry up and get it back to him!
Though, Isohime...
Beach
Dragon Palace
Go
Return
Turtle Taxi Ticket
I didn't actually take anything! Just take these and get out of here!
She gave us tickets to the Dragon Palace.
Letting her off like that was too nice of you.
I'm glad that you didn't actually do anything.
I wouldn't kill someone in front of my master.
Tomoe-kun's probably feels the same way.
I don't want to soil my hands in front of you.
Dragon King!
We're in trouble!
Will you shut up? I'm busy balancing my books!
The giant oyster we set up...
Tomoe?
Man, I was so comfortable in there I fell asleep.
It's been a while hasn't it, Dragon King?
You've got some nerve showing your face in front of my master.
Wha—
I can't allow her to see anything gory.
Now that I've relocated...
Wow! Amazing!
So you really do ride a tortoise to the palace!
Nanami-chan, those windows only keep out the water. Be careful, will you?
I can help Tomoe now... Finally, I get to see my Tomoe again!
Huh? What's wrong with me?
Mizuki...
Hmm?
What is it?
I wonder if Tomoe is still in love with Yukiji-san.
I...
I'm a bit scared to meet him.
I'll probably just start comparing myself to her.
He was definitely nicer to her than he is to me.
He was so desperate to help her.
He's never been that way with me.
He won't even touch me.
No, I can't worry about that right now! I'm losing what little motivation I have left!
Wanna turn around?
Turtle Taxi Guide Book
Why is that your first suggestion?
Because you look like you don't want to go.
Turtle Taxi Guide Book
What's happening?! Turtle!
Passenger boarding.
Pardon me.
A member of the Dragon tribe?
Good afternoon.
H-Hello! Nice to meet you!
Oh no, now every woman I see looks better than me!
What business does an Earth Deity have down here?
It's sort of complicated.
Someone important to me was taken away, so I'm here to retrieve him.
Oh dear, I'm sure he can't wait to see you.
I'm actually heading down there myself to drop off something for my dear husband.
May we both meet our dear ones soon.
The embroidery on that is beautiful!
What is it?
This is a haori I made for him.
I spent seven days on it.
When we can't see each other,
I spend my time thinking about him.
What a beautiful kimono. I don't think I could make this if I spent ten years.
T-The haori!
You can't!
Mizuki, that woman's haori just got blown out!
We have to get it back!
Don't worry about it.
Huh?
The water has probably washed it far away by now.
That aside, the turbulence must be caused by the palace.
I can make another haori. We need to get to the palace, though.
But you spent seven days on it!
Yes, and I enjoyed every minute of it.
That's more than enough for me.
I'm embarrassed.
Until just a moment ago, I was preoccupied with how my feelings weren't being reciprocated.
He won't look me in the eye or lay a finger on me.
When did I get this passive?
Wow! Th-This is the palace?
Wait—
Though Mizuki's disappeared already...
Wh-What?! Are they doing construction?!
It appears that something is amiss.
Your highness!
You guys explain to me what's going on here!
The fox we captured is going rampant!
The King is fighting him right now!
T-Tomoe!
I see.
You're much more monstrous than you were before.
If that girl saw you now, she'd be scared for the rest of her life.
You know Nanami?
She was begging me to let you go.
She was out of her mind. She said she'd get my eye back to save you.
What are you, crazy? She might be an Earth Deity but she's weak and helpless.
Wait, that girl was an Earth Deity?!
I thought she was your mis—
Despite her looks, she is one.
One mustn't touch her so readily with bloodied hands like mine.
Tomoe!
I'm glad you—
Slam
!!
Hold—
Why are you hiding in there again?!
I already know what's happening!
I went back to the past and met the old you.
I don't care if you don't share my feelings.
I don't care if you don't want to touch me.
I don't care if you love someone else.
I won't wait for things to go my way.
T-Touching—
You don't have to look at me.
I'll make you look at me.
Even if you don't look my way...
My feelings won't change for you.
That's enough to make me happy.
Let's go home.
I don't get it.
That girl is an Earth Deity?
She's just a kid no matter how you slice it.
Um, Dragon King?
Hmm?
Darling.
Do you mind explaining to me what is going on here?
T-Turtle Queen! Weren't you visiting your parents?!
Wait, he's your husband?
You went after the demon fox again? Have you not learned your lesson?
Have you forgotten the promise you made when you lost your right eye, perhaps?
W-Wait! There's an explanation for this!
Th-That Earth Deity came to give me my eye back!
Right? Right?!
Huh? Oh that's right.
Here's your eye!
You can have it back.
Don't make fun of me!
About that...
I'm not taking this!
Would you like this instead?
Mizuki!
What the hell is that rag?
Do you think I'd even consider that crap?
Oh by the way, this was made with love by the person standing behind you.
What?
Don't you think this is a fair trade for the fox?
I love it! I'll take it!
Mizuki! You went back for it!
Why are you here?
I was just worried about my senior, that's all.
What?
Well, I look forward to working with you, Tomoe-kun!
What?!
Let's all go home together!
Please, God
Kamisama
Onegai da
I...
Boku no ano hito ni
I want to meet her
Aitai no sa
ah ah ah
ah ah ah ah
God, I'm in pain
Kamisama
Tsurainda
Because, she...
Kyou mo matta noni
didn't come today either.
Konakatta
I have a request, God
Onegai ga aru no
Kamisama
Please, save me
Boku wo tasukete
ah ah ah ah
God, it's too late for me
Kamisama
Mou osoi
Because she's...
Ano ko wa
Going back several centuries,
Next Episode Preview
has disappeared
Touku sora ni
we explore the story of how Tomoe became Mikage's familiar.
Into the distant sky
Kieta no sa
I wonder what their life together was like.
Yeah Yeah Yeah
Next time, "Tomoe becomes a familiar!"
｢Tomoe becomes a familiar!｣
What? Another one?
farewell, Baby
Sayonara Baby
Also next time, "The Deity Goes to a Mixer!"
｢The Deity Goes to a Mixer!｣
Goodbye
We have two stories next time!