True Calendar year 61.
Hurry up and catch him!
He's just a kid!
Wait, waaait!
Who are you?
There he is!
Shoot him!
Don't! You'll hit Her Highness'
Freeze!
Drop your guns! Do it, or I'll kill her!
There's nowhere left to run! Let Her Highness go!
You awake?
Hey, can you hear me?
Don't ignore me!
This guy pisses me off...
You have six hours.
Until what?
That's how long you have until this country of yours falls.
The hell?!
Let it go, Yamada.
Don't!
It's "Thunder"!
Another enemy attack is coming?
Tokishima Haruto.
You haven't given me an answer regarding our pact yet.
Make a pact with me, and I will save you.
Both you and this country.
I wasn't strong enough, that's why...
You're lying... It can't be...
Why? Why...?!
Couldn't you have protected her?
You were there, weren't you?!
Why couldn't you keep her safe?!
Senpai, please stop!
But—
Aina-chan wouldn't like to see you this way, Senpai.
God damn it!
Sakurai, that first-year? Seriously?
That's what I hear.
What's gonna happen to the rest of us?
Hey, stop it.
But, you know...
It can't be helped. I mean, she did die.
Eri...
You people piss me off, every last one of you.
Miss Sakurai...
Look, you should ask someone else to do that.
No. I can't make the students do this.
I'll help.
It was just as you indicated, Captain.
I located five completed Valvraves in the lowest level of the Module.
I also found several dismantled units that were either incomplete or had been abandoned.
A-drei. These are excellent pictures. Fine, indeed.
Incidentally, about L-elf...
I've given him just about as much leeway as I can.
I can only hold back the pre-Reformation old guard for so long.
That's why...
this will be your final chance.
Yes, sir! If I can strike a blow at the students who are holding him prisoner, L-elf will return.
I'll leave this next operation to you.
Someone familiar with Module 77 is the best choice.
Sir! Thank you, sir!
Blitzendegen.
Blitzendegen!
Have that finished in 40 minutes. I know you can do it.
You're as lovely as ever, Kriemhild my dear!
She's our superior officer.
I'm a man, she's a woman.
No, I'm an adult, and you're a horny child.
In that case, please make a man out of me!
By all means!
Drop it.
Why hasn't Captain Cain reported L-elf's actions?
Because it's a hassle?
I expect it's because there isn't enough accurate information to make a proper report.
Yes... That must be it.
I'm so sorry.
I should have realized it sooner.
Too much happened.
Like cooking...
and a coup d'état...
and the enemy attack...
T-Tha... Thank...
I'm sorry, I told myself I wouldn't cry...
I told, but...
Akira!
Sorry I'm late. It's been hectic for me, too.
Sashinami?
Don't look! Get out!
Why?!
Akira's talking to someone besides me?
"Kamitsuki"?
That's the name Aina-chan gave us.
She said we weren't monsters, we've been touched by God.
That's a really sweet name...
That's so like her.
Professor Kibukawa! Please, let me pilot a Valvrave!
After I've made certain they're safe.
Please! I can't leave things like this!
I want to avenge her!
In that case, stay alive.
Live for her, too.
Sashinami again, huh?
Just hand it over, damn it!
We can't! Not without the Presidents permission!
You're whining about permission?
We've got bigger problems!
Please, calm down!
You expect me to be calm at a time like this?!
Taking out equipment without permission is prohibited!
What's going on here?
President, he's trying to—
The ARUS fleet got taken out!
So we have no choice but to fight, right?
Do you want even more of our buddies to die?!
We're students. We can't fight a war.
Besides, JIOR law prohibits its citizens from carrying guns.
Are you some kind of moron?
We're under enemy attack!
Our buddies are dying!
If we fight, even more will die.
Everyone, it's the Dorssians!
Return to the school building and take up the stations we decided on earlier.
I repeat, return to the school and take up the positions we decided on earlier!
We're all counting on you, Haruto!
Tokishima Haruto. Valvrave, box out!
Aina-chan, I'm sorry.
But I can't let..
Haruto, that was amazing!
But I'm can too...!
How's that?
I've been practicing!
Him again!
But before he can use those silver things, I...
I'm your true target!
There's another one?!
Miss Rukino!
I left this hatch unlocked the last time.
L-elf...
I'm going to take away all of your options.
Situation?
Not good.
I just can't...
Miss Rukino!
What...?!
Battleships? But how?
Those are JIOR navy ships...
They must have towed them here from the harbor.
They really are nothing but students.
They can't even manage their own weapons.
Citizens and comrades of JIOR.
Again?!
Who is a "comrade"?!
Lay down your weapons and surrender.
The shells' point of impact is moving closer to you by 100 meters each minute.
They're both inside and outside...
Crap!
President!
Give an answer before our attack reaches your school.
A surrender ultimatum, huh?
You never did like to get your hands dirty in a mop-up operation, A-drei.
Don't get any funny ideas just because your buddies are here, you bastard!
Former buddies.
Haruto!
All I'm doing is slowing him down!
According to my analysis, those weapons will shut down after a set period of time has elapsed.
There's no need to destroy them.
We simply need to prevent them from resting.
The school field!
The volleys are getting closer and closer.
Haruto, you've got to do something!
Aina. Rest easy, I'm going to avenge you.
Here too?
If I don't do something, I'm gonna overheat!
Aina-chan...
Is the spy in here?!
Satomi?
Beg your Dorssian friends to spare your life!
We'll use you as a bargaining chip to negotiate with them.
And if I refuse...?
Satomi?
Hey!
I'm the Student Council President Renbokoji Satomi!
I'm going to resolve the crisis the school is facing!
President! Don't do this!
Stop!
Haruto?
Shoko. Patch this call through to him.
"Him,"...?
Eight people.
Give me the chance, and I'll defeat the Dorssians at the cost of only eight lives.
No good. Save everyone.
Tokishima! Are you seriously letting this guy come up with our plan?
Screw that!
We can't trust any plan that this guy comes up with!
I trust him!
I know you have a reason for not being able to let things end here. So do I.
Don't do it, Tokishima!
You're making a deal with the Devil!
It's all right. After all, I'm already cursed.
I will save everyone.
I'll save everyone in the school!
And you! And the girl in the picture, too!
I see that even being caught up in a war won't cure that sweet sentimentality of yours.
Add some sugar, and coffee tastes delicious.
Add it to you, who's too bitter, and it tastes just right.
You have a deal, L-elf.
For victory!
For peace!
To make both our dreams come true!
Dreams...
I take back what I said.
Oh, no way!
We'll go for zero losses, as you said.
You're not getting away!
Move to point L-3074 and bring the green Valvrave with you.
It's time, sir.
They're more stubborn than expected...
No matter. Aim at the school.
We're here! Now what?
Position the green Valvrave 30 degrees behind you and to your left.
Destroy block 208 with your rifle. At maximum output.
But if I do that...
No, I'll believe you.
Your target is bulkhead B41!
He's firing on the Module?
Maybe he's gone nuts!
The silver things are peeling off!
They froze the Sabas with sea water?!
They're peeling off!
The seawater is venting into space!
This plan... It's L-elf?!
It's no use, we can't hold position!
We did it!
They're sinking!
They dealt with our forces inside and outside at the same time!
The operation's a failure...
Which means we can do whatever we want, right?
Why you...!
Commercial's over! The show's back on!
Keep climbing! Hurry!
Now, while it can't move!
Crap!
What?!
I'm going to buy him time to charge up.
Miss Sakurai, are you watching?
I never got the chance to tell you.
I'm there!
Your target is the fleet behind you.
Coordinates are 032-316.
I'm gonna destroy you, that sword and all!
You have a nasty habit of moving in straight lines, X-eins.
L-elf!
Retreat! Hurry!
Just as I thought, this is the Light of Rune!
We did it!
I couldn't do anything...
Let go of Her Highness! We'll shoot!
Let's go halvsies then.
Halvsies?
Everyone, I'm giving this boy half my life.
So would you be so kind as to give him one?
You can't give half your life to someone!
My mother told me that a woman's hair is her life.
Wha—?
You and your halvsies... That sentimentality...
Do you have any idea how long I've been looking for you?
We said zero losses, remember?
Trying to break our pact on the first day?
No, it's all according to plan.
I knew that you would come looking for me.
I've factored your saccharine nature into my calculations.
You're one bitter guy.
With this, our clan can sustain itself...
I can hear the bells ringing out to bless our union...
Our...
bride!
Next time, episode 9.
"Dogs and Thunder".
Valvrave the Liberator...
The system that will expose the truth of the world.