Military Tribunal 54 ﻿is hereby convened.
The charge.
That you lied to other countries about peace through neutrality
and developed grave threats, the Valvraves, in secret.
Do you have anything to say in your defense,
Prime Minister of Old JIOR, Sashinami Ryuji?
It's the truth! It's delicious, you've got to try it!
Search results: zero. ﻿For that way of eating them.
I'll treat you when we get ﻿to the Moon, then.
Moon?
On the Moon, I can get ﻿all the ingredients I mentioned.
Plus, the Moon is ﻿neutral territory.
The Dorssians won't be able to ﻿attack us anymore.
The war will be ﻿over, too!
We'll go back to being ordinary students ﻿and focus on club activities.
We'll have proper ﻿classes, too!
On Saturdays, we'll all go ﻿hang out together,
and everything that was called off, ﻿we'll start up again.
Don't you worry! Once we get to the Moon, ﻿I know everything will be okay!
You're late!
You're the one ﻿who asked me to meet you!
We were supposed to meet at 10, right?
Me getting here first is the same ﻿as you keeping me waiting.
Sorry...
Fine, whatever.
Miss Rukino. The reason ﻿I asked to meet you is—
Miss Rukino?
You're planning to talk ﻿on the sidewalk?
I'm at 90! ﻿Nobu Lightning, coming in!
Nobu-what?
It's this thing's name! "Unit 3" ﻿or whatever is lame, you know?
I know! I know ﻿what you mean!
Okay, it looks like this will let you ﻿fight for extended periods.
Otamaya, ﻿how does Unit 1's—
Otamaya ﻿isn't here.
He left for the photo shoot. For the new cabinet.
A minister... Minister... ﻿
Minister of Culture & Science.
Yusuke Otamaya
Me, a minister, can you believe it?
Minister of Land, Infrastructure,
Transport and Tourism:
Juto Bansho
Your tie's crooked.
Minister of Finance.
Kyuma Inuzuka
So sorry, my good ﻿Minister of Land & Transport.
Chief
Cabinet Secretary:
Satomi Renbokoji﻿
Minister for
Foreign Affairs:
Takahi Ninomiya
Isn't that dress ﻿a bit daring?
I have to dress the part ﻿in order to associate with foreign countries.
Minister of
Health and Welfare:
Rion Nanami
Is everyone here?
Minister of Justice:
Iori Kitagawa
No, Tokishima and Miss Rukino ﻿aren't here yet, and neither is—
Sorry I'm late!
See? The "egg" for "sunny-side-up" ﻿is a manga eye!
Minister for Internal Affairs
and Communications:
Marie Nobi
Pretty sweet, huh?
If you want, we can all ﻿wear this shirt so we mat—
Vetoed!
Prime Minister
Shoko Sashinami
Um, Miss Rukino?
No! We said we'd talk ﻿after we got there.
There it is! The one ﻿with the blue sign!
There? But that's a place ﻿that serves alcohol!
What's the big deal?
We're cabinet ministers now! ﻿
We can just change the stupid law!
Flip this switch to the left... No, this can't be it.
But these are ﻿the only switches...
Oh, this is ﻿the one!
Ow! That's hot!
I refuse to let you apologize to me.
That's weird, ﻿he's not picking up.
Miss Rukino isn't ﻿here, either.
Wait, you don't think ﻿they're together, do you?
Is that Haruto?
No, it's from ﻿another address.
"Congratulations,
Madam Prime Minister."
"Akira-chan,
thanks for the text!"
Akira-chan, ﻿thanks for the text!
"You’re welc—"
You're... welcome.
I heard you!
Who's that?
A friend! ﻿Akira Renbokoji!
Renbokoji?
Hey! Why is my little sister calling you?
I'll take care of anything she needs done ﻿outside, so I'll thank you to butt out.
Oh, you have ﻿a little sister?
Takahi, this is ﻿a personal matter!
Have any pictures?
Give it back, ﻿you girls!
No way it's Shoko's phone.
Hi, here!
This is Rion Nanami ﻿the Health and Phys-Ed teacher.
I-It's nice to meet you!
I-I'm on ﻿the student council with your brother!
I'm so sorry! ﻿I bet they spooked you!
We were all here taking the cabinet photo.
Oh, hey! Why don't you come join us?
The outside world is a lot of fun!
You'll make lots of new friends, too!
You can eat cake with them ﻿go swimming with them!
It's for your own good, ﻿Akira-chan.
You need to experience ﻿the outside world more.
Akira-chan, ﻿please be our friend!
No!
No! No! No!
Wha— ﻿
Akira-chan? ﻿Akira-chan!
Um...
I'll go.
But...
Akira is my sister.
I've been alone ﻿my whole life.
Because no one ever chose me.
Not my family, not my friends.
But they have!
You were a huge pop star, ﻿and were even in movies!
I wanted to be picked. ﻿If only by one person.
I'm all alone, so if I could be alone ﻿with someone else, that would be enough.
Miss Rukino... ﻿Are you talking about...
I've been alone ﻿my whole life.
Because no one ever chose me. ﻿
Not my family not my friends.
Isn't that amazing? I did this movie ﻿two years ago, and I still remember my lines!
Turns out that I had a knack ﻿for acting, too!
You're wrong!
You aren't alone, ﻿not anymore.
Enemy forces detected!
All personnel, ﻿please go to level 1 battle alert!
Time's up, ﻿I guess.
They're between Module 77 ﻿and the Moon!
There's so many!
But we were ﻿almost there!
We'll never reach the Moon ﻿without punching our way through them!
We'll have to do ﻿just that.
But how?
Watch team, report ﻿to the radar room!
Air defense gun turrets will be set to debris ﻿shredding mode for this operation only.
"From: Satomi Renbokoji"
It's unlike you to commit ﻿such a blunder, Capt. Cain.
My apologies, sir.
According to your report, those Valvraves have a limit ﻿to how long they can remain operational.
Yes, sir. If we ﻿press them en masse—
Exactly.
All we have to do is engage them ﻿in a protracted battle and exhaust them.
Module 77 is changing course ﻿to a heading of 741!
What?!
They're running?
It's the pragmatic ﻿choice. Nevertheless...
Understood, sir. ﻿We won't let them get away.
All ships to maximum combat speed!
Commence pursuit battle!
Dorssian fleet ﻿is pursuing!
Maintain ﻿heading of 741.
Concentrate barrier system ﻿on our side facing the Moon.
Here they come!
Take up formation! ﻿
Yamada, follow my lead!
It's "Thunder"!
Eat this! ﻿And this!
Dome block damaged ﻿through frame 277!
Barrier system ﻿output down to 87%!
L-elf! There's just ﻿too many of them!
We can't take ﻿much more of this!
I've factored everything ﻿into my calculations.
The enemy fleet has utterly broken their ﻿formation in order to pursue Module 77.
Hey, you're right! ﻿They're in a line now!
In this formation, you can wipe them all out ﻿at once with your Harakiri Blade.
So that's why you ordered ﻿the course change!
It wasn't ﻿to run away!
Your Harakiri Blade is the key ﻿to turning the tables.
If you miss your chance, this ﻿operation will end in failure.
Understood.
Satomi Renbokoji.
What?
I've written out what will happen at each stage ﻿of the remainder of the operation.
Give the orders ﻿as written here.
Why me?
When it comes to talent for carrying out instructions ﻿written in a manual, you are the best there is.
What about you?
You sound like ﻿you're going somewhere.
Secure transmission from Dorssian fleet!
They want to speak with the Prime Minister!
Me?
Shall I put it ﻿through?
Yes. But in the Prime Minister's ﻿official residence.
You said "official residence"?
You're the prime minister of a country. I insist ﻿that you make the minimum effort to look the part.
Yeah. It's my turn ﻿this time.
"This time"?
Until we got swept up ﻿in this war, I had no idea.
I never knew how incredibly lucky ﻿we were to live in peace.
So I got to thinking that our peace didn't come free, ﻿and it's something that someone protected for us.
So now it's my turn ﻿to protect it.
A state's ultimate duty ﻿is the safety of its citizens.
That's what ﻿Dorssia thought, too.
As a result, they keep ﻿a massive military.
That's not—
You're patched through.
Dorssian Rear Admiral ﻿Delius Wartenberg.
Shoko Sashinami, ﻿Prime Minister of JIOR.
This is a time of war.
I'll dispense with the empty formalities.
Dad!
The verdict of former JIOR Prime Minister ﻿Ryuji Sashinami's military tribunal was death.
You can't!
I thought we told you that if you laid a hand on our families, ﻿we would hand over the Valvraves to ARUS!
Prepare to carry out ﻿the execution.
You cowards!
To adults, that's ﻿a compliment.
Worrying about methods and ﻿aesthetics is a childish affectation.
Using any means, however dirty, to achieve ﻿one's objective is what an adult does.
Are you ﻿watching, Nobu?
You and me, we're gonna ﻿blow these guys to hell!
This is war. Victory glosses over ﻿any cowardice, any injustice.
I've pinpointed ﻿the enemy's location.
The heart of the enemy fleet.
It's within the Harakiri Blade's firing range.
No way!
I'm there!
Now charging ﻿Harakiri Blade!
Understood!
Haruto, my father ﻿is over there.
If we let this chance pass us by, ﻿we'll be defeated.
I knew that you'd be ﻿coming at me from the left!
Carmilla is destroying ﻿enemy Waffen!
Enemy fleet speed ﻿increasing to 20!
Amazing... The battle is playing out ﻿exactly as L-elf wrote.
What do I do? ﻿What should I do?
The operation... ﻿The Valvraves...
The war... ﻿The school...
Dad...
Think! ﻿Think, Shoko!
Another 26%. ﻿until he can fire.
Let's make a deal, ﻿my young Prime Minister.
In exchange for the transfer ﻿of the Valvraves...
I will allow all of you students and ﻿your families to take asylum in a third-party country.
But that's—
What about ﻿the other citizens of JIOR?
Abandon them.
They're only the same race as you. ﻿
The vast majority are total strangers.
We refuse!
We'll never make ﻿a deal to save only ourselves!
21% to go...
It's a sad thing, ﻿being alone...
Safety and family.
That's ﻿more than enough to be happy.
Maybe so, but...
You should leave the fighting to adults.
You don't want your friends to die, do you?
What's so funny?
Dad!
So it's you, Shoko.
You're ﻿the new prime minister huh?
The condemned isn't permitted ﻿to make an statements!
What harm can it do ﻿for us to talk a little?
After all, this is a father's last ﻿conversation with his daughter.
It's not the last! Don't give up so easily!
I'll save you, ﻿you hear me?!
Shut him up!
Stop that! ﻿Don't hurt my dad!
Their line is ﻿starting to scatter...
How much longer ﻿for the Harakiri Blade?
Don't worry ﻿about me...
It's an adult's job to return to the earth ﻿to make new flowers grow...
Shut your mouth, ﻿you damn JIORan!
Dad!
Keep facing ﻿forward, Shoko.
Your future doesn't ﻿lie behind you!
Don't make me ﻿laugh, weakling!
Dad!﻿
Another 3%...
Dad...
I... I...
I'm there!
He did it! ﻿Tokishima is so great!
We can reach ﻿the Moon now!
Did ya see that, ﻿you Dorssian bastards?!
Enemy fleet destruction ﻿confirmed at 74%!
Now! Charge through the hole we've opened ﻿in their middle and make for the Moon!
I couldn't... ﻿
do anything...
Nothing...
Everything went ﻿according to your plan, L-elf.
How far ahead ﻿can you see?
He can't see ﻿anything.
Object closing in ﻿at high speed from below!
From below?!
What happened?!
A-An Ideal-class has—
The pit's wrecked! ﻿The Valvraves can't get back in!
We can't cool them off now, ﻿either!
What are we gonna do?!
Bastards!
Don't!
Professor!
H-neun. ﻿The drill is yours.
Blitzendegen!
We're being boarded ﻿by the enemy!
Mr. President, ﻿we need orders!
G-Give me ﻿a second!
It's not in here!
There's nothing ﻿about this written in here, damn it!
We'll just pull ﻿the damn thing out, then!
Valvraves.
We're going to ﻿settle things once and for all.
Miss Rukino, take me back ﻿to Module 77!
Unit 1 can't move!
I know! I'll fight ﻿them hand to hand!
Now sealing all bulkheads ﻿below level B4!
I repeat, now sealing ﻿all bulkheads below level B4!
Annihilate the enemy after ﻿luring them into position.
I'm happy to see you following ﻿my training so scrupulously.
However, that makes you ﻿easy to predict.
I'll come back when ﻿my Valvrave has cooled off!
Do your best ﻿to rescue Shoko.
Wait! Ow!
Idiot, what do you think ﻿you're doing?!
I've been thinking about ﻿what will happen after this battle is over.
Saki Rukino...
Will you...
marry me?
Next time, episode 12, ﻿"The Heretic Activates”.
Valvrave the Liberator...
The system that will ﻿expose the truth of the world.