ANIME-KOI
PRESENTS
onnanoko hajimemashita
A tired girl starts her day
tameiki wa bioron no shirabe ni nite
With a sigh like the moan of a violin
akai mi hajikechatta
A cherry bursts in her mouth
mada anata wo shiranai
This was before we had met
konna koto hajimetette
This is the first time I've ever felt like this
manazashi wa aku no hana sakimidarete mo
I could see that your pretty eyes were filled with contempt
ie e to tsuzuku
But I had to go home
basu sutoppu demo anata wa tsurenai
Even at the bus stop, you gave me the cold shoulder
karameta hanabi myaku utsu
The fireworks in the sky pulse
koi no shiruetto
In a silhouette of love
karui mahou
With a little magic,
usotsuki na kuchibiru
Two sets of lying lips
sou kasaneteru
Lock together
ano ne
You see
nee kamisama
God...
warui ko ni naritai yo
I'd like to be a naughty girl
ii ko ni shiteru kara
I'm tired of being good
onegai dayo
So, please
zurui koto sasetoite
It's for a good reason
ii koto shitai nara
So let me be bad for once
sukaato hirogaesu shite
By flipping my skirt
sugu kaeru yo
I'll be back soon
doyoubi wa haresou da
It looks like Saturday is going to be sunny
kamisama hajimemashita
God, it has already started
Momozono Nanami, a high school girl, has just become a deity.
Though some things are better left unexplained,
to put it simply, being a deity isn't for everyone.
And now we present, the second episode!
Man, what a dream!
My father ran away, I got evicted from my house...
Then I got lost, and some guy gave me his house.
When I went, it turned out to be a rundown temple.
And then they kept saying I was the Earth Deity.
I was like, "What?"
Then a really rude demon named
Tomoe said that he wouldn't accept it,
except I ended up kissing that
thing and now he's my familiar.
What a dream!
Huh?
You already did that last episode.
Where am I?
The inner sanctuary of the shrine.
This is your room, Nanami-sama.
But it's completely different from yesterday.
I remember it looking like
it was going to fall apart.
Tomoe-dono gathered all of this for you
so that you could live more comfortably!
Tomoe did?
Why?
Last night, you finally took Tomoe-dono as your familiar!
It's a familiar's duty to serve his deity!
I remember now!
That wasn't a dream!
I forced a kiss on Tomoe last night!
W-Where's Tomoe?
Tomoe-dono has been
at your side for quite some time.
I forced him into being my familiar...
Good morning, Nanami.
Your bedroom was quite a mess,
so I cleaned up while you slept.
I did what I could think of.
While it was against my will, from here on out, I'm your familiar.
I, Tomoe, am mandated to carry out your orders without qualm should our eyes meet.
Should you be troubled by anything,
don't hesitate to come to me.
This is rather unexpected.
I thought you'd be more upset
about becoming my familiar.
Is that so?
I'm so relieved. You don't seem upset at all!
It would be half-assed of me to be simply upset.
Huh?
I'm so pissed off, you couldn't
possibly begin to understand!
Why on earth do I have to
serve some wretch like you?!
It's so damn pathetic that I couldn't get a wink of sleep last night!
But what's done is done.
I'll simply have to make you
into a deity worthy of my service.
Worthy?
Deities have an innate power within them.
Mysterious Power
You measure the standing of a deity...
by how much of this power they can use.
Mysterious Power
For you to raise yours,
you first have to listen to people's prayers.
Mysterious Power
Simply granting their wishes will be a quick and easy way to do this.
Hearing? Prayers?
For example, Mikage was a deity of marriage.
Having listened to many prayers for marriage, his power to grant such wishes is very strong.
I see. So this temple is for good fortune in marriage?
He's taking the time to explain everything clearly even though he doesn't like me...
Now, let's see how powerful you are.
Turn this water into sake. You may use a talisman if you like.
Oh, this thing I used before, huh?
All right, time to show him what I can do!
Sake
How's that?!
Allow me to test it.
T-This is delicious...
...water.
Tomoe-dono, where are you going?!
Don't follow me.
Please stay!
We can't take care of this place alone!
Don't abandon us!
Let go!
I don't care!
This is unfair!
Please!
Tomoe-dono!
The Targeted
Goddess
Good morning! I'm Tanaka from JapanNet!
Nanami-sama, breakfast is ready.
Eh.
I hadn't noticed until now,
but Tomoe's doing everything, like the bedroom,
the meals, the cleaning, pretty much everything.
Is this what familiars do?
What have I done?
Our beloved idol Kurama-san has, of all places, transferred to Uchigami High!
Uchigami? That's my school.
Who is Kurama?
What is a "beloved idol"?
Kurama's at my school?!
Slow down, Nanami-sama!
Where are you going to in such a rush?
Let go!
I just remembered that I have to train my powers!
I have to get to school! Yeah!
Yes! Going to school and hanging out with my girlfriends while squealing over celebrities...
I belong in school! That's where the real me lives!
Where are you going?
Kurama's coming to school... This is my chance to meet Kurama Shinjirou.
Who is he?
Kurama's a...
Nanami-chan, allow me to tell him.
Kurama is a mega-celebrity who's taking the nation and its girls by storm.
Sporting black wings, his persona is that of a fallen angel.
That said, his profile says that he's
a character shrouded in mystery.
Yeah! And he's at my school right now!
Can't I go? Even if I hang around, it's not like we'll get any prayers.
Not like we'll get any
No.
Why?
You should know that there will be demons out to get you.
This mark tells them that you're an Earth Deity.
Keep in mind that you're just a powerless girl.
You going out is like begging to be eaten.
Then, come with me.
I'm up to my ears in chores here!
You should do your fair share!
Spoilsport.
If you want to go that badly, I guess you can.
What?
However, I have a condition.
The Condition
What the heck is that?
Oh my...
The Condition
Ew!
I finally come back to
school and this is what I get!
What's on your head, Momozono? I heard that you'd
finally come back to school and you walk in with that!
Why do I have to be in the same class as you again, Isobe?
Wear this hood to hide your forehead.
Tomoe, you idiot! I stick out like a sore thumb!
I gotta get this on photo.
kurayami ni hikaru
Black wings that shine even in
wizu yami no wingo
the blackest depths of the night.
The jet-black fallen angel...
Kurama!
He just looked at me!
No, he looked at me!
He's...
He's coming...
...straight to me!
'Ey, hoodie girl.
You're in my seat.
Get out.
Who's she?
That girl who lost her home.
Oh, I remember.
Momozono... Momozono Nanami!
Oh, Momozono Nanami!
Girls' Restroom
Nanami,
did a human just bully you?
Wh-Why are you here, Tomoe?
I was worried, so I came to check up on you.
Kurama said something horrible to me.
It's all because you made me wear this hood!
Now that you've met that Kurama guy, you don't
have a reason to come to school anymore, right?
Don't force yourself. Let's go back to the shrine.
I'm standing here crying, and you have the nerve to smile?
You don't care about me, do you?
Forget you!
Were you crying in the bathroom?
How adorable.
Sorry about before, Nanami-chan.
I-I was not crying.
I'm apologizing. I was just a bit irritated.
Every day, the kids at school look at me like I'm some kind of exotic animal.
Sorry I took it out on you.
Don't let it get to you. I don't actually hate you.
If that's the case, then I deserved it. I gawked
at you just like everyone else.
I won't ever look at you again, so goodbye.
Hold on!
I didn't know Kurama was that kind of person!
I feel like an idiot for going out of my
way to meet him with this hood on.
I feel so bad for Nanami-sama.
She doesn't deserve to be bullied by Tomoe-dono and end up like that!
Hold on, I wasn't bullying her.
Though...
...I suppose I am the one who made her cry.
Hey, hoodie-head!
What kinda cheap-ass food did you bring for lunch today?
That's not your business! At least for lunch—
What? It's not like you forgot it at home or anything, right?
That's hilarious!
I-I'm going to get bread today!
Do you even have enough money to buy bread?
Of course I do! What do you take me for?
D-Did I even bring money?
Oh, got it.
Right here.
What the hell?! Why do you have 30,000 yen?!
Wait, is this mine? I can't possibly have this much!
Huh? Looks like I'm missing 30,000.
Well, I guess 30,000 is pocket change.
Has anyone seen Kuruma-sama's money?
Momozono-san, where did you get that money?
Huh?!
That's exactly 30,000 yen, too...
Strange...
You don't think she stole it, do you?
No...!
Isn't Momozono-san's family—
Wait, I just remembered. I gave that money to her.
I remember her saying that she didn't have enough money to buy bread.
What's he going on about?
Isn't that right, Nanami-chan?
No... No, he's lying!
Nanami-sama, I humbly apologize for my tardiness.
Today is your first day on the job, a cause for celebration.
I, Tomoe, have attempted to craft an exquisite lunch for you.
Please, feast yourself.
Also, I have a few words for everyone.
Nanami-sama is an important master to us.
I, Tomoe, will not tolerate any words of slander or actions against her.
Kurama-dono. That money you couldn't find, as you can see, is right on the floor.
Wha—
Impossible! I remember specifically putting that cash in her pocket!
As for everyone else, I humbly ask for your generosity toward Nanami-sama.
Tomoe...
The only person in the whole world...
Hurry up and eat.
...that puts me first, might be Tomoe.
We'll be back soon!
We're back!
Nanami-chan just experienced one heck of a start to her school days.
Let's fast-forward to her second day!
See you later!
Nanami, you're forgetting something.
You're forgetting this masterfully crafted triple lunch box and this cat hood to which I've attached a seasonal flower.
Sorry, I think I'll go without the hood today!
I'll be fine! I'm only going to school.
What are you saying? Walking out without the hood is much like walking onto a battlefield naked.
You shouldn't talk like that until you can protect yourself.
Besides, why are you even—
I'll just have one section of the lunch box. See ya!
Tomoe-dono!
Get a hold of yourself!
Phew, it's a relief to get that thing off my head!
Momozono-san!
Huh?
Good morning!
Oh, girls from my class! Do I already have friends?
Is Tomoe-kun coming again today?
If he is, could you introduce him to us?
Oh, I brought lunch today, so I don't think he's coming.
What? Lame.
Women...
No hood today, Nanami-chan?
Get in. I'll drive you.
Kurama.
Let us in!
I don't need it.
Oh how come? Are you shy?
Or maybe because I'm so popular—
No, because I don't like you.
What did she say?!
Who does she think she is?!
Celebrities are a pain in the ass.
Nanami, that idiot... All she had to do was wear the hood.
Now I have to watch over her all day.
I haven't even cooked dinner.
I suppose salt-roasted sweet fish will suffice for tonight.
I have to cook dinner and babysit this girl.
Is this part of what familiars do too?
How boring.
I almost miss my past life.
The kind of life that'd make anyone's skin crawl.
Tomoe-dono.
Tomoe-dono, Nanami-sama's going somewhere.
Why did you call me out here, Kurama?
Let me ask you this first.
Any other girl would avert their eyes
and blush the instant our eyes meet,
so why do you say you don't like me?
Is he for real...
I covered for you yesterday, and I even apologized.
I don't get what there isn't to like about me.
This guy's an air-head!
If you want, I'll even consider becoming your—
Are you an idiot?
Yes. I am a—
What did you just call me?!
If you keep talking down to people like that, forget
about getting a girl, you won't even make friends.
Wh—
If you have no other business, I'm leaving. See you.
I don't care for any of them. All I want is you, Earth Deity.
If I can have you, then I'll...
What's this chill down my spine?
Found you, demon.
You!
You must be pretty sharp to set
your sights on Nanami this soon.
You're the familiar from yesterday!
Kurama? I see, you're the...
I am the Crow Goblin of Mt. Kura.
It's been sixteen years since
I descended from those mountains.
Now that you've seen my true identity...
I have to kill you!
Is that his...
How do you like that, fox?
I heard your services are fantastic.
If I become the Earth Deity, I wouldn't
mind making you my familiar!
You'd rather have me over that girl, right?
You think you can become a deity?
I can! All I need is a bite of that girl's heart.
You're funny, Crow Goblin.
Wh—
When I think of how people like you want to become a deity...
it makes me giddy to know that Nanami is my current deity.
What?
Ostrich meat is low in calories
and rich in nutrients and minerals.
Aren't you happy? You wanted to become an Earth Deity, right?
Hold—
If Nanami eats you, you can become one with meat on her butt.
Allow me to try my hand at
making you into an Earth Deity.
Hold it! wait—
How exciting!
We're having whole-roasted ostrich for dinner tonight.
Why is there an ostrich running around?
What are you—
Familiar? How the hell is he a familiar?!
Someone stop that damn fox!
Earth Deity!
"I can't hold back these feelings."
Oh, I'm so happy for you, Lisa! You can live happily ever after with Mike!
I wish my high school years could be like this too!
I heard there's an ostrich being chased by a fireball!
What's that supposed to mean?
Huh?!
That's Tomoe's fox flame!
A girl!
Watch out!
Damn it.
A-Are you okay?
That pendant...
Tomoe!
Nurse's Office
Not seriously injuring anybody does not make it okay!
You've got some nerve going on a rampage around my school!
I was only protecting you.
And why is Kurama a bird now?
That man is not a human.
He's a demon, a crow goblin to be exact.
Huh?
You're not a fallen angel from hell?!
W-Well, turn him back into a human for now.
But... tonight's dinner!
Turn him back.
Listen up, Kurama.
I'll let you off the hook this time, so don't cause me trouble, and don't be mean to me.
Promise?
I-I-I-I thought I was going to die!
Kurama, look over here.
What do you want? Still got something to say?
Your face!
You're injured. Let's clean it up first.
Forget it.
Will you be quiet? An idol can't walk around with cut on his face.
I don't particularly like you, but
there are tons of others that do.
You have to at least take care of your looks.
Otherwise, you're just insulting them.
Mm-hm.
Wait, why did I get the lecture while he gets his wounds tended to?!
ah ah ah ah
That's because you aren't injured, Tomoe!
That's only because I can take care of myself!
ah ah ah ah
Why are you even at school in the first place?
Nanami-san, I see you're becoming a good deity.
It's your damn fault!
How so?
ah ah ah ah
Listen very well, Nanami.
What?
You're not walking out without your hood tomorrow!
ah ah ah ah
You can't make me!
kamisama onegai da
Please, God
boku no
I...
ano hito ni aitai no sa
I want to meet her
ah ah ah
ah ah ah ah
kamisama tsurain da
God, I'm in pain
kyou mo mata nou ni
Because, she...
konakatta
didn't come today either.
onegai ga aru no kamisama
I have a request, God
boku wo tasukete
Please, save me
ah ah ah ah
kamisama mou osoi
God, it's too late for me
ano ko wa...
Because she's...
Next Episode Preview
Next Episode, a priestess appears at the residence of the Earth Deity!
Wh-What's that? She's fallen in love with a human?
Can love really blossom between ghouls and humans?
｢The Deity Ties Fate｣
Next time, "The Deity Ties Fate"!
Love is real.