The VVV Project?
Given their stated position of peace through neutrality, ﻿JIOR can't possess a big military.
And so, they developed weapons that could ﻿take on an entire fleet singlehandedly.
So that's what ﻿the Valvraves are...
Still, I'm amazed that you managed to develop ﻿weapons that fit the bill so perfectly.
It was because of ﻿the runes.
At the risk of oversimplifying, I suppose ﻿you could think of them as information particles.
All physical matter is ﻿composed of atoms.
In a similar vein, information is composed of ﻿indivisible units called runes.
Or so ﻿they tell me.
"So they tell you"?
Aren't you ﻿a member of the development team?
Uh, right after I was assigned here, ﻿I butted heads with the top brass.
I was demoted to ﻿test subject caretaker.
Test subject... ﻿You mean the students?
Every last student at this school ﻿is being uniquely modified.
That's why all the teachers were military.
We're their caretakers.
Why is that woman ﻿the only exception?
Nanami-chan is ﻿a special case.
We were set up to look like an ordinary school,
so I guess ﻿they felt they had to stick in a PE student teacher.
Stick in. Receive. Insert?
It's a pretty weird ﻿program wizard, huh?
Only VVVI ﻿has one.
Only VVVI can use ﻿that Harakiri Blade, too.
This unit ﻿seems to be special.
Hey, nobody told me about ﻿this "Kamitsuki" stuff!
No, we didn't.
Well, I knew.
Look, I know this might come as a shock, ﻿but try to stay calm, okay?
Stay calm? This is ﻿totally bad-ass!
This is your usual "immortal anti-hero" deal!
Do we have a special pose or something?
Thank goodness ﻿he's so stupid...
Say what?!
Now, now...
Let's all try to get along. ﻿
We're gonna be a team from now on, right?
A team...
In other words, ﻿none of us is alone.
Yeah!
So much for ﻿being alone together...
Not at all, it would appear that ﻿my staff treated you quite rudely.
I'll apologize again ﻿once the ceremony is over.
Ceremony?
You and your students are heroes. ﻿
Of course there will be a ceremony.
Between the international congress and media interviews, ﻿things are about to become quite hectic.
I must be going. Let's meet on the Moon, ﻿Representative Rion Nanami.
I can't... I can't ﻿keep doing this.
I'm sorry I'm all dirty! Miyamoto said ﻿his favorite model had been buried.
Found it!
I can relate... I couldn't bear it ﻿if my favorite shirt got buried!
Here!
Go on, try it!
I know, aren't they great?!
I totally recommend these! ﻿
Potato chips dipped in red chile oil!
Hey, once we get to the Moon, ﻿come shopping with me at the supermarket!
I know these!
You like ﻿these wafers?
The fukujinzuke relish coating ﻿on these is so good!
And if you fry them, it takes them ﻿to a whole new level!
The trick is ﻿to use olive oil!
What do you say, ﻿Akira-chan?
Experiment?
Yeah. It's in our best interest to learn more about ﻿what our bodies can do, right?
You have a point.
Let's start with jumping jacks.
Duration and number. And then...
Hey...
Is that true?
I'm saying that ﻿we should test it out.
What are you ﻿talking about?
What? Hey! ﻿Say something!
C'mon, man up! ﻿
You're ignoring me?!
We all know ﻿you like her!
Right? Right?
Well, I guess...
Let me show you ﻿my special stash!
It's enormous...
You can use ﻿a ruler for that?
I know, right? ﻿This'll do the trick for sure.
Everyone, this is student ﻿teacher Rion Nanami.
We will be arriving at the Moon soon.
Oops, I didn't mean to rhyme!
When we arrive, we will need a representative
for various ﻿international negotiations and interviews and things.
Up until now, I've done what I can ﻿to fill that role, but I don't think it's right.
It shouldn't be because someone is ﻿older or a teacher or whatever.
And so, I think we should hold an election!
An election for the Prime Minister of JIOR!
An election?
We're gonna be ﻿the country’s leaders?
That's a great idea!
I want to ﻿try it!
We have the 7th off, ﻿let's do it then!
We're technically "﻿off" now!
That sounds like fun!
It sure does!
Prime Minister...
As you can see, our food self-sufficiency ﻿has been improved to 17%.
And this isn't the only benefit to come from the Seven R's.
Senpai, who will you ﻿vote for?
Isn't it obvious? ﻿For the winning candidate.
Our public relations activities via the wired ﻿are also going all-out now.
To give an example—
I'm running for election, too! ﻿Thank you for your support!
So you were ﻿serious, Yamada...
How many times do I have to ﻿tell you it's "Thunder"?
To keep our secret, it would be best ﻿if one of us was in a leadership position.
You run, Haruto.
I can't! I just don't ﻿have it in me.
Yeah, somebody crazy like Shoko ﻿would be a better fit.
If it's "crazy" that matters, ﻿he might actually be a good choice.
Say what?!
It's a compliment! She's saying ﻿that you're more of a leader than I am.
Oh, she is? ﻿I suppose I am...
You're a real ﻿sweetheart, ain'tcha?
Thanks.
I'm surprised. I didn't expect you ﻿to volunteer to act as election supervisor.
I'm a refugee, ﻿so I don't have voting rights.
I assume you aren't trying to ﻿pull a fast one on us again?
The election of a representative ﻿aligns with my own objectives.
It will be ﻿a fair election.
I thought you wanted to quit ﻿being our representative.
I don't want to run away from it.
If I'm going to ﻿represent everyone,
I want to be properly chosen to do it.
I see.
You would've made ﻿one hell of a teacher.
Don't treat me ﻿like a child!
Sorry, my bad!
He wasn't elected student council president ﻿three years in a row for nothing.
Trapped in ﻿a room together...
I'll keep you ﻿girls safe.
Also, your mouth... There's too many ﻿words coming out of it.
Takahi-senpai, I—
Get over ﻿yourself!
I don't care how famous you are or ﻿that you're a pilot!
You're just an underclassman to me!
Before this war broke out, ﻿I didn't even know your name!
I'm not as—
What's wrong, ﻿Tokishma?
Takahi-senpai, ﻿stand back...
Miss Rukino?!
You go after everything, ﻿don't you?
Haru-tard, you can't jump her ﻿just because she's got a sexy body.
Oh. Um, I...
She's right! You're so sexy—
I mean lovely, that I couldn't help myself.
Dressed like that, you're asking for ﻿all kinds of unwanted attention from the boys.
I'm really sorry!
Wait a minute! ﻿Come back!
The interval between ﻿attacks is shortening?
I'm scared. What if it keeps getting ﻿shorter and eventually reaches zero?
I'm worried that I'll run around ﻿attacking people like some kind of animal.
Haruto.
If that ever happens, ﻿I'll put you down.
If I'm going to be killed by someone, ﻿I'd like it to be you.
Shoko!
Miss Rukino... Um, ﻿are you guys training?
No, we just bumped into ﻿each other, and—
You're not ﻿running?
The election.
No, no! I'm not ﻿cut out for that stuff.
It should be ﻿a third-year who—
Hey!
The members of the Youth Culture Club ﻿decided to vote for you, Shoko!
You saved my ﻿Shadow X, remember?
And I hear you went to the student council president ﻿and renegotiated the Light Music Club's budget!
I only did that ﻿because I'm a fan of theirs.
What's this? Are you gonna ﻿run in the election, Shoko?
No, no way!
You'd do a great job! ﻿I know it! You've got to run!
But I'm just not—
You've always been there ﻿at our matches, cheering us on!
And you've always brought us food, too! ﻿I honestly think you can do it, Shoko!
Cut it out, ﻿I'm not like that at all.
You're giving me ﻿too much credit, really!
Oh, come on!
Do it!
I can't, I can't!
If they can reach the neutral territory of the Moon, ﻿we'll no longer be able to move against them.
This next battle ﻿will likely be the last.
We won't let them ﻿escape, sir.
We swear on the honor ﻿of the Karlstein Agency.
I'll be joining you ﻿this time.
If the Valvraves slip through my grasp, ﻿it might cost me my head.
Never!
Impossible, you are the Chancellor's close friend.
That wasn't the case 20 years ago.
And he wasn't the Chancellor then, either.
Are you concerned about ﻿the royalists staging a comeback, sir?
That is part of it...
Where is ﻿H-neun?
Playing hooky, sir!
My dear!
You and me, we're like ﻿peas in a pod!
Us running into each other here, ﻿don't you feel the hand of fate at work?
What are you ﻿doing here?
That's a long ﻿story...
For now, ﻿how about some tea?
Where's Shoko? ﻿Isn't she with you?
She said she would ﻿catch up with us later.
Why do you ask?
She just seemed like ﻿she wasn't her usual self.
You think?
She didn't look ﻿all that different to me.
Well, ﻿she was just—
Haruto.
Can I trust you ﻿to look out for Shoko?
I'll come right out ﻿and ask her what's wrong.
I'll leave her ﻿to you, then.
I'll go ﻿look for her!
Don't be late!
Got it!
Shoko!
So does this mean that Prime Minister ﻿Sashinami has been killed?
Take a look at the signature on ﻿the declaration of unconditional surrender.
It says "Acting Prime Minister ﻿"Yamamoto," see?
It's possible that he fled, ﻿but in all likelihood...
Shoko... What was ﻿that just now?
He's alive. ﻿He's alive, I know it.
Why do we have to pick ﻿a new prime minister?
Don't bury my dad in the past... ﻿Don't assume he's dead.
Shoko... How long ﻿have you known?
No way... ﻿Since way back then?
But that would mean ﻿this whole time,
she's been carrying ﻿this all alone.
"May my dad be safe."
I'm such an idiot!
Why didn't I ﻿see it?
All this time, Shoko's been fighting ﻿by herself! Fighting all alone!
Just you wait, Shoko.
I'll bring ﻿your father back with me.
Don't worry.
Even if I'm not around, ﻿Miss Rukino is here. L-elf, too.
Haruto, wait!
It's crazy! ﻿You can't do it alone!
I know it's crazy, ﻿but I'm going anyway.
You don't know what you're saying!
If you did, you wouldn't go!
No, I'm going.
He's not your father, Haruto, ﻿he's mine!
It's none of your concern!
Of course it is! ﻿Because you're crying!
Someone who's precious to me is crying!
If this isn't a time to do something crazy, what is?
Someone precious... ﻿to you?
Oh, um, ﻿I just meant...
Basically, I'm ready to go that far for you.
I mean, we've known each other forever...
Um...
Thank you, ﻿Haruto.
I'll run ﻿in the election.
I want to fight ﻿alongside you, too, Haruto.
I want to stand shoulder to shoulder with you, ﻿not just be protected all the time.
Shoko...
Besides, if we're going to save anyone, ﻿it should be all our families.
Yeah.
It's time.
Wait!
I'm running ﻿in the election, too!
I figured ﻿you'd come.
What's this?
Your application. I already filled in ﻿all the required fields.
Thanks, Marie!
Haruto.
I want to straighten this up ﻿before heading back.
It won't work out, not between ﻿a Kamitsuki and a human.
Maybe you're right.
Are you an idiot? A "like" without ﻿getting something back isn't a "like" that'll last.
Even so, ﻿I'm going to—
Haruto?
Are you okay?
In closing, I pledge to you a better food situation, a steady ﻿supply of power,
and a stable lifestyle with these Seven R's.
He's as persuasive ﻿as ever.
He is the student council ﻿president, after all.
He makes you ﻿want to vote for him!
Next is our final candidate. ﻿Shoko Sashinami of Year 2 Class B.
Nobody likes it when somebody ﻿wins without a fight.
Oh, she decided to run after all!
Shoko, you can do it!
Guys! When we get to the Moon,
let's hold the school festival!
The school festival?
W-What's ﻿she saying?
Hold the school festival?!
I'd go for it.
Come on, ﻿take this seriously!
It was called off ﻿because of the war, remember?
I'm so psyched about it!
I mean, ﻿last year's was awesome!
Right, Otamaya?
Me?
You showed me the monster suit ﻿for that movie you were making, remember?
I've been looking forward to ﻿seeing it at the school festival!
Yeah, that movie's ﻿our pride and joy!
I thought ﻿as much!
Takano-senpai!
We all swooned over ﻿your Romeo last year!
This year, we're doing The Cherry Orchard!
But with all the genders reversed!
That I've got to see!
Shoko!
Come hear our ﻿performance, too, okay?
We were able to get our ﻿instruments fixed, thanks to you!
Will do! ﻿I'll see it for sure!
Come eat at ﻿our booth, too!
I'm looking forward to ﻿your Machida Special!
Our exhibit's gonna be ﻿awesome, too!
I want to make ours ﻿a coffee shop!
It'll be revenge ﻿for last year!
The zero-G ballet ﻿was amazing!
Sashinami, we're fighting a war!
We don't have ﻿the luxury of throwing a school festival!
That's why ﻿we have to.
He's right, we're in ﻿the middle of a war.
There's no telling ﻿when we might die.
That's exactly why I want to ﻿hold the school festival!
This might be the only chance ﻿we'll ever get to be students!
Club activities, field trips, field days, ﻿there's a ton of things that I want to do!
I don't want to give up ﻿a single one of them!
What do you say, everyone? ﻿Let's be more selfish!
I know that it'll give us a reason ﻿to go on fighting! It'll get us amped up!
I have a reason ﻿to go on fighting, too!
When we get to the Moon...
Um, this is just me, mind you...
Um, how can I ﻿put it?
I... I'm gonna tell the person ﻿I like exactly how I feel!
I have a reason ﻿to keep going, too!
Do you think ﻿she means me?
No way! ﻿She means me!
Hey, are you ﻿okay?
Are you having trouble breathing?
Go ahead and body-jack me. I feel fine.
I have one, too! To be ﻿the richest man in the world!
To compete in ﻿the inter-high tournament!
To make my ﻿pro debut!
To become ﻿even stronger!
To buy as many ﻿GX3000's as I can!
I-I'll profess ﻿my feelings, too!
To become a novelist!
To make 100 friends!
Guys, let's do everything that we've always dreamed of! ﻿Let's become the kings of selfishness!
Hey! W-What are ﻿you thinking—
We only go around ﻿once in life!
The things we want to do!
The dreams ﻿we want to fulfill!
Let's try to do them all!
Let's do it!
Yeah, you only get one life!
Let's be selfish!
This can't be ﻿happening...
Is this—
When we get to the Moon, ﻿let's all do whatever we want!
Let's find something different! ﻿Something new!
Now I get it...
This really is ﻿a curse, isn't it?
I know we're gonna be okay! ﻿I know we can do it!
Tell me ﻿Haruto...
Do you think ﻿I did okay?
This says ﻿that Shoko won.
Next time, episode 11, ﻿Military Tribunal #54".
Valvrave the Liberator...
The system that will ﻿expose the truth of the world.