ANIME-KOI
PRESENTS
onnanoko hajimemashita
A tired girl starts her day
tameiki wa bioron no shirabe ni nite
With a sigh like the moan of a violin
akai mi hajikechatta
A cherry bursts in her mouth
mada anata wo shiranai
This was before we had met
konna koto hajimetette
This is the first time I've ever felt like this
manazashi wa aku no hana sakimidarete mo
I could see that your pretty eyes were filled with contempt
ie e to tsuzuku
But I had to go home
basu sutoppu demo anata wa tsurenai
Even at the bus stop, you gave me the cold shoulder
karameta hanabi myaku utsu
The fireworks in the sky pulse
koi no shiruetto
In a silhouette of love
karui mahou
With a little magic,
usotsuki na kuchibiru
Two sets of lying lips
sou kasaneteru
Lock together
ano ne
You see
nee kamisama
God...
warui ko ni naritai yo
I'd like to be a naughty girl
ii ko ni shiteru kara
I'm tired of being good
onegai dayo
So, please
zurui koto sasetoite
It's for a good reason
ii koto shitai nara
So let me be bad for once
sukaato hirogaesu shite
By flipping my skirt
sugu kaeru yo
I'll be back soon
doyoubi wa haresou da
It looks like Saturday is going to be sunny
kamisama hajimemashita
God, it has already started
It's almost the most exciting time of year again, summer!
Our heroine, Nanami-chan, seems to be in a delightful mood!
She's completely absorbed in planning her summer vacation with her friends!
Hey, Narrator! What you're saying and what's happening are completely different!
Oh, you're right.
Get your act together!
Sorry 'bout that.
Oh, that's right. Now I remember
In the last episode, love bloomed.
Unfortunately, it also wilted as fast as it bloomed.
How will she recover from this heartbreak?
Hey, do you want to go to the beach, Momozono-san?
Sounds great. I'd be thrilled to go. Yahoo... Not really.
Momozono-san, don't go toward the light! Get a hold of yourself!
You can't expect much after having your
confession rejected so spectacularly, though.
You still don't have your appetite back? You haven't even touched your lunch!
Not hungry.
You have to eat! You'll collapse if you don't!
Good grief. You barely had any breakfast, and now you won't touch your lunch.
What is wrong with you?
Are you trying to fast?
I keep trying to pick up the pieces of my heart, but then Tomoe just keeps popping up.
I-I'm just not hungry.
Then get hungry.
Stop it, Tomoe-kun! She still hasn't gotten over the rejection!
Re
jection
I can't control these feelings.
Out of the way, Strawberries.
If you're not going to eat, then I'll force-feed you!
Huh?
Wha—
Sh-Shiitake?!
I'm the only one here who can't control their feelings.
Meanwhile, Tomoe still has his composure.
There's just one difference now.
He won't even lay a finger on me.
Momozono-san, cheer up! You've got me right here!
Go to the beach with me!
You'll feel much better once you run around for a bit.
Yeah, let's go!
How does Saturday sound?
That's nice and all, but do you two even have swimsuits?
U-Um...
The beach?
The Deity
Goes to
the Beach
The Deity
Goes to
the Beach
Hey, is Nanami-chan—
What do you mean I can't go?!
You just can't.
Nekota-san asked me to go! I can't turn her down!
Please calm down, Nanami-sama!
The beach and the ocean are breeding grounds for evil.
Humans might be fine, but I can't
possibly let a deity like you go alone!
Furthermore, I can't enter the water, which is all the more reason for you to not go.
I won't be alone! I'll have my friends with me!
Friends?
What good will those friends do you?
How about I take her for you, then?
To the beach...
Mizuki?
Damn.
Look at the ocean!
Yeah!
Enough about the ocean. Why did they have to tag along?!
Hello!
No one's going to hit on us with you guys around!
Can't you take a hint?
Hitting
You want to be hit?
No, they're not going to hit us!
Apparently Kei-chan broke up last night.
Are you trying to act retarded?
In the end Tomoe came with us...
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Ready!
You look like a little kid with that.
I can't swim without one, though.
Momozono-san, how's the swimsuit on you?
Mm-hm.
It's so cute! Thanks for letting me borrow it, Kei-chan!
This is the first time I've gotten to wear something like this!
Don't sweat it.
I just didn't want someone in a T-shirt swimming with me.
Why don't you go show it off to the guys?
Wha—
Speaking of which, are they even going to swim today?
Plop
How to be Attractive
L-Let's get in the water!
You sure you don't want to show them?
I'm sure! They weren't even supposed to be here today!
Why do I suddenly feel embarrassed?
Momozono-san, over here!
I wonder if this is okay.
Does this look weird on me?
Do I... look good in it?
So why are you here, Tomoe-kun?
I could ask you the same. Please die.
Seriously, aren't girls these days much too bold?
I can't believe they'd walk around with so much skin exposed.
I wouldn't be surprised if some human males tried to "eat" them up.
I bet you're actually glad that you came along.
Though honestly, I didn't think you'd actually come along.
I know why you can't get in the ocean.
Eh?
How to be Attractive
I might hate your guts, but I have enough courtesy to not tell Nanami-chan.
Nanami-chan, mind if I come along?!
Sure!
Look, I found this really pretty shell!
Here.
I see...
Let's go, Nanami-chan! Tomoe hates the water, apparently.
Sure.
I wonder what cool things we'll find!
He has some nerve putting his hands all over her while I can't.
That damn snake.
So the snake boy's going to swim?
Maybe I'll join in.
Glance.
Have fun.
You should come along too, Mikage-kun.
The problem is that if I get too close, Tomoe might notice me.
Rather, might I ask why you're
wearing that oven of a coat here?
It's part of who I am.
True.
If he learned that these past twenty years after abandoning him
that you were actually watching from afar...
Well, I wouldn't be surprised if he straight-out killed you.
Tomoe wouldn't do something like that.
He'd dropkick me at best.
Tomoe-kun might look all cool, but I guess he does have his weaknesses.
I wonder if that human girl is one of them.
Now...
I'm going for a swim.
As good of a friend as he is,
I still can't believe he's a deity.
Though, summer sure is nice.
I guess I'll swim by myself since I'm here anyway.
Wow, this is so pretty!
You can have it.
Are you sure? Thanks!
Are you having fun?
Yeah, this is great!
I'm glad...
I'm glad that you're feeling better.
Sorry.
Nekota-san?
Man, the water feels great!
I'm beat.
Oh, what's wrong? You're looking extra scary today.
Tomoe! Ami and Momozono-san are...
Are you okay, Nanami?
Tomoe! Nekota-san...
Nekota-san is gone! I tried finding her but I couldn't!
She can't swim, Tomoe! Please, save her!
Leave it to me.
Will you be okay, Tomoe?
If my master makes a request, can I really say no?
Ami.
Ami!
It's time to go back.
Nekota-san!
Ami!
Nekota-san, are you okay?!
I-I'm fine. I just got a mouthful of water.
You idiot! You had us worried sick!
Thank goodness.
Sorry...
Tomoe...
Thank you!
Well, my job's done.
Thank you, Tomoe.
What?
Thank you for coming into the ocean.
You couldn't have made it any easier for me to find you.
We'll be back soon!
We're back!
I've been waiting for a long time for you to play in the big puddle, Tomoe.
Who are you?!
I hope you haven't forgotten the face of the King of the Dragons!
Tomoe?!
Kei-chan! Nekota-san!
Sorry, but I can't have bystanders getting in our way.
I've got some debts to collect.
And what might those be?
Tomoe!
Allow me to remind your stupid fox brain!
Exactly 526 years and 208 days ago, at 5:28:41 AM,
you came down to my lair at the bottom of the sea and slew the seven-headed dragon
and three—no, five great beasts of the ocean and a sea slug at the Noth Gate of the palace.
Then you destroyed the entire North Gate itself,
came to me, the King of Dragons, and gouged out my right eye.
You've got quite the debt, and I'll make sure you pay back every last cent!
I hope you're ready!
You'll make fine pearls!
You'll be worth more that way, anyway.
That was amazing, King!
We were greatly impressed by your show of magnificence, King!
Of course you were!
I've been planning this out for the past 526 years!
Let's go back to the Dragon Palace and celebrate!
Right away!
Hold it! What did you do to Tomoe!
Who's that girl? Why is she still conscious?!
Give Tomoe back!
Not so fast!
Sorry, but that's as far as you go.
See you around, missy!
I won't let you go!
Tomoe!
I cannot enter the ocean.
You even told me!
You told me, yet...
I let you go!
If I let go now, I might never see you again!
My breath is running out... Tomoe!
You're one persistent brat, you know?
Will you quit already?
Where's Tomoe?!
I had my minions take him. He's long gone.
Besides, I was nice enough to drag you back here.
Here's your bill. You can pay it off over time.
Please! Give Tomoe back to me!
That fox owes me one hell of a debt. Unless it's paid back,
you'd better give up.
What do you want me to do?
What can I do so you'll let Tomoe out?
Let's see...
If you can give me the eye he took from me, I might spare his life.
My eyes are like seeds of power.
Those who manage to get their hands on one and eat it gain incredible power.
That fox took one of them 526 years ago.
In other words I, the Dragon King, had defeat permanently carved into my face.
If I can get the eye to you,
you'll give Tomoe back to me?
It's not as easy as you think.
It's been 526 years. I doubt you can get it now.
You should just give up.
Wait!
Huh?
Promise me that if I get it, you'll let Tomoe go!
I don't know what you're planning, but I promise.
I'll hold onto the fox for two days.
There's one way I can save Tomoe.
Bean Sprouts Lodging
I love how ice cream is so cold and sweet!
I've never had anything like this.
What the hell are you screwing around for?
Momozono and Tomoe are missing, and you decide to take your sweet time in the bath?!
Maybe we should call the police.
I think they'll be fine.
Nanami-chan should be back by tomorrow.
I'll sleep in the middle, okay? I tend to get lonely.
I reserved this room for three women.
You and Tomoe can go sleep in a love hotel for all I care.
Momozono!
Nanami-chan!
Where have you been?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry I made you worry.
I got lost.
See? I told you she'd be fine.
Mizuki!
Hmm?
I need you to let me use your Route of Time.
Huh?
Bean Sprouts Lodging
I need to use it to go back into the past and get the eye from Tomoe.
If I can get the eye back, I can save Tomoe.
So...
Nanami-chan, one of the girls told me that you like Tomoe.
Wha—
T-T-T-That has nothing to do with the situation at—
I'm a bit jealous of him.
Huh?
It's almost painful to watch him have a master that cares so deeply for him.
I don't like Tomoe-kun.
I always imagine how wonderful my life would be if Tomoe just disappeared.
I think this is what people call "envy" or "jealously."
Nanami-chan, have you never
thought that way about someone?
Tell me, how do I deal with these feelings?
I'm sorry. I'm asking so much of you...
But you're the only one I can count on!
When you put it that way, how can I say no?
It is a taboo to interfere with the past.
Then again, you are a deity so...
there's no one to stop you.
You actually brought that with you?
Yeah, ever since my home flooded,
I've been carrying my valuables with me.
Last time I only brought your spirit back, but this time your whole body's going.
I can help a bit, but only as a guide.
The rest is up to you.
Tomoe...
Tomoe.
You're all I see in this light.
I can't help myself. I love you.
I won't fall in love with a human girl.
It's freezing!
I-I suppose the fact that it's snowing means I've successfully returned to the past, but...
M-Mizuki?
Mizuki where are you?
Aren't you freezing in those clothes?
Don't you want this wind breaker?
Huh?
I wouldn't mind trading this for that Dragon King's Eye you have in you.
What?
Nanami-chan!
Nanami-chan?
Don't go wandering off. It's dangerous.
Mizuki, there was a woman just now.
That was a mermaid demon called Isohime.
It regularly ambushes humans around here.
Don't you have to look for Tomoe?
That's right! I have to look for him!
Huh?
Tomoe!
How dare you lay hands on my brethren!
Return the right eye of the Dragon King this instant!
You will pay for this!
I don't have time to deal with you.
ah ah ah ah
The same face...
The same voice...
ah ah ah ah
Tomoe...
He's...
The one I love is still stuck in the darkness.
ah ah ah ah
Nanami-san...
I beg you. Please save Tomoe.
ah ah ah ah
Please, God
Kamisama
Onegai da
I...
Boku no ano hito ni
I want to meet her
Aitai no sa
ah ah ah
ah ah ah ah
God, I'm in pain
Kamisama
Tsurainda
Because, she...
Kyou mo matta noni
didn't come today either.
Konakatta
I have a request, God
Onegai ga aru no
Kamisama
Please, save me
Boku wo tasukete
ah ah ah ah
God, it's too late for me
Kamisama
Mou osoi
Because she's...
Ano ko wa
Next Episode Preview
Nanami and Mizuki have traveled into the past to retrieve the Dragon King's right eye!
has disappeared
Touku sora ni
But little did they expect to find Tomoe with a beautiful woman!
Into the distant sky
Kieta no sa
Oh my, who's she! I wonder if Nanami and Tomoe can get back on good terms!
Yeah Yeah Yeah
｢The Deity Goes to the Palace of the Dragon King!｣
Next time, "The Deity Goes to the Palace of the Dragon King!"
farewell, Baby
Sayonara Baby
Find the beauty within!
Goodbye