True Calendar year 71.
In this year, which would later come be known as the first year of the Third Galactic Empire,
humanity was in the midst of expanding its sphere of activity beyond Earth.
The development of Dyson Spheres accelerated humanity's progress into space,
and 70% of the total population now resides in space.
This is JIOR Sphere No. 1, Module 77. Please transmit your country of registration
This is GS2776 flight 21. Requesting docking clearance.
Registry confirmed.
You are cleared to dock.
You are carrying two transfer students for Sakimori Academy, is that correct?
Yes, that is correct.
Wash it down with water!
Prove your manliness, Haruto!
Don't lose, Shoko!
This is still neck and neck!
You can do it, Tokishima!
Keep up the pace!
We're on the home stretch!
Finish 'em off!
This is quite a ruckus.
It's apparently an eating contest to decide who gets to use the school field.
I can't believe high schoolers would still be fighting over who gets to use the track...
I think it's fine. At least it's peaceful.
Haruto!
We were counting on you, man...
Way to blow it, Haruto...
I told you I didn't want to do it...
Didn't matter. We rock-paper-scissored for it, and you lost.
The odds of the loser winning the next time are—
Zero. Totally zero. Haruto has absolutely no head for competitions.
Someone in a weird shirt like that has no room to talk.
Weird?
Marie?
You, Shoko!
Welcome to JIOR Module 77.
The weather in the module is fair today, and— Hm?
Your manifest said that there were two transfer students.
Peace has made this JIOR country soft.
In short, this was settled by the balance of power between the countries of Dorssia and ARUS.
The defining characteristic of both countries is that they developed
and expanded by means of multinational treaties.
Tell us what will be on the test, already!
What do you expect, this school has only been open for three years.
And it would be a total hassle to go back to Earth.
Hey this school is really pretty.
How do I register someone as a Wired friend?
Hey have you heard the story about the legendary shrine?
Yeah! They say it'll make sure your love is reciprocated.
So anyway have you heard?
They say the Dorssia Mil-Fed is violating our territorial space again.
They'll probably settle with us by paying a fine.
Geez, again?
Man that's so lame.
I'm fine with it. It's more economical than having a military right?
You saying that sums up everything that's wrong with this country.
Hey Haruto. Aren't you ever going to tell Shoko how you feel?
What's up?
It's nothing. Just forget it.
Really?
Yeah.
She's gonna get snatchet up
by somebody else.
Don't come crying to me
when she does.
Hey.
You've been staring at me like a freak.
You have something on there.
Show me!
There's nothing! Nothing!
If it's nothing, then you shouldn't mind me seeing it.
Come on, there's nothing on it!
There is!
Hey!
Pass!
Nice!
G-Give it back! If you don't give it back you and I are through as friends!
Then answer me. Why were you looking at me?
Well...
I was only thinking, "She'd be beautiful, if she kept quiet...."
W-Wha—?!
I just mean, maybe you could keep your mouth shut!
A restriction or something.
So I'm not?! When I talk?!
No, not exactly...
Then, I'm a... beauty?
No, that's not right, either.
So which am I?!
Ah, to be young...
Inuzuka-senpai, you're always talking about money.
Because I plan to become the richest person in the world someday.
If you're going to dream dream big, huh?
Miss?
Do you have a moment?
If you don't mind, could we trouble you for directions?
Huh? Um...
Your skirt is cute!
Butt out. I'm talking to her.
You're so uptight. Are you asking her to the dance or something?
I prefer to mind my manners at all times.
We should keep contact with the locals to a minimum.
Hey, wait! Do you know the way?
The sprinklers.
What did you say?
The sprinklers are spaced one every 13 meters,
but they change to one every 12.5 meters in front of just that structure.
There are 40 desks in each classroom visible through the windows.
Student body, 480.
However, the structure was built using common layered construction.
From a load-bearing standpoint, there is no room for extra facility personnel.
I must therefore conclude that it is beneath the building.
That's our boy...
What year are those guys?
I've never seen them around before.
Transfer students, maybe?
You don't have enough passion in you.
About what?
Our throwdown earlier.
You didn't go into it intending to win, did you?
No, it's not like that.
I just... I wish we lived in a world where there wasn't stuff like winning and losing.
We each could have used half the field just fine.
Halfsies.
Would you use a knife to cut the yolk of your ham & eggs
and the girl you love in half, too?
Uh...
Happiness can't be split into "halfsies".
Hey, what year are you?
Hey, wait! What are you—
Don't!
Stay back, Shoko!
What will you do if someone hits you even when you don't want to fight?
Laugh foolishly and concede defeat?
If you can't concede, your only choice is to fight.
Miss Nanami, what are you doing?
I'm here to give Rukino extra lessons, but she isn't here yet.
Oh, the celebrity...
That's odd... I wonder if I told her the wrong time?
List of students
signed up for
extra lessons.
Sheesh, what was that guy's deal?
Sorry, pal, but I'm the kind of girl who eats the egg white first.
And anyway, the star of ham & eggs is the ham!
Right, the ham is key.
And Haruto was the one who was knocked down, right?
I think that's what happened...
What Haruto said was totally noble!
He wasn't wrong, so what the hell?
Calm down!
But I'm mad!
Thanks, Shoko.
You're getting angry so I don't have to.
It's okay.
That makes me feel a lot better.
Well, that's what friends are for.
I mean, you never get mad at anything.
Yeah, yeah...
We were supposed to keep contact to a minimum.
I'm in.
It's opening.
"May my love come true."
Are you making a wish, too, Haruto?
No!
They say if you profess your feelings here, your feelings are sure to be returned.
This is a legendary shrine.
Schools that were built three years ago don't have old legends, right?
Shoko...
Message from L-elf:
"Bats fly across the cloudy sky."
That's the Colonel's star pupil for you...
Message to fatherland:
Commencing Operation Virgin Road.
Blitzendegen!
Wait, wait!
What? What?
G-Give me a second!
Huh?
I mean, t-this is—
Waffe unit #1, box out!
G-Go ahead.
O-Okay.
Shoko, I'm in—
What are those?
Kind of low, aren't they?
What a racket...
Probably a drill or something.
Where are they from?
Aren't those Waffe?
Dorssians?
They're gonna hit!
What military is that?!
What are those?!
Dorssian model number NW507Be, manned Waffe units!
What are all those?!
Everyone, get inside the school building! Hurry!
What's going on?!
A war?
What the hell, man...?
What the hell?!
Hostiles confirmed as Dorssia Mil-Fed fleet!
Send word to the homeland!
It's no use! I can't get through!
Why would the Dorssian military attack us?
Can't anyone get through to the homeland?
They say they're being blown out of the sky.
Why?
JIOR is a neutral country!
Let's use the Valvrave!
Are you gonna take responsibility for it?
Okay, I'm impressed...
Aw, he hogged all the fun again!
This one was still alive!
Hold it!
What's that?
A robot?
Shoko!
There's someone inside that car!
Shoko! Come back!
I'll be fine! Go on ahead!
Shoko!
Shoko...
Haruto...
Hey, Shoko...
This is no time to be playing hide-and-seek!
Come on out! Okay, Shoko?
Shoko...
Let's go, Haruto!
Shoko!
Haruto, she's—
I can't leave! She might—
Stop it!
You just have to accept it! She's dead!
I'll make them pay...
Haruto! It's not safe!
Let's just sit tight until some adults arrive!
Haruto!
I'll make them pay...
I'll make them pay!
It's not safe here, run!
It's humanoid?
Commander! It's the primary strategic objective!
So, you failed, you punks... I told them so!
I'll drag out just the pilot.
I'll just need a second.
Work! Work! You're a robot, aren't you?!
I have to avenge Shoko! Please!
Work! Come on, work! Work, damn it!
Crap!
This will spread the word...
Reports on the, sneak attack against JIOR by the Dorssian army are still spotty.
The government is struggling to respond.
It's getting pounded!
What? Hey, this is-
Is that a JIOR machine?
Don't you have any weapons?
Come on, you're a weapon, aren't you?
Am I beaten...?
Is this the end?
Dying without getting revenge?
I don't believe it...
I'm sorry, Shoko...
I blew it again.
You didn't go into it intending to win, did you?
I'm...
If you can't concede, you have to fight.
I'm not giving in...
So I'm fighting!
It transformed?!
Its color and power are different, too!
We won't lose to a military that's never known war!
What the hell is that light?!
It's too fast?! Impossible!
What is it? What kind of light is that?
We did it!
Thermal limits exceeded.
Systems shut down.
It stopped...
It's Haruto!
Seriously?!
Who's that?
He's in the class next door.
Thanks, Haruto!
That's the boy from this morning!
I've seen him before somewhere...
It wasn't a movie?
Haruto!
Him and me, we're friends!
Thank goodness...
No way!
That's a kid in there!
It's not a soldier?
Who is that?
He's JIOR's secret weapon!
They say he's a high-schooler!
Why does he have a robot?
That's the guy who lost this morning!
Way to go, Mr. Tokishima!
Shoko...
Go ahead and laugh.
Just like you said, a world without winners and losers is a fantasy.
Who are you?
Captain L-elf, Dorssian Special Forces.
I won again...
...Lieselotte.
Next time, episode 2, "Beyond 666".
Valvrave the Liberator; it's the system to reveal the truth of the world.