I won again...
...Lieselotte.
Haruto!
Haruto! Hey, Haruto!
He can't be...
It's okay, he has a pulse.
But he's covered in blood!
There aren't any wounds.
Maybe it was splattered on him.
Let's carry him to the school.
We should at least have the infirmary doctor look at him.
Step away from the Valvrave.
Valv-what?
It's the name of that ridiculous robot.
You JIOR people named it.
You aren't Sakimori Academy students?
Nope, Dorssians!
L-elf!
There's a ventilation duct over there.
Ignore them.
Hurry!
What's the meaning of this, L-elf?!
Why turn your gun on us?!
A-drei!
Crap!
Q-vier! Watch the perimeter!
H-neun, let's call headquarters.
What's your game?
Why did you save us? Who the hell are you?
I'm... I'm Haruto!
What are you talking about?
I don't know how I got into this body, but I'm Haruto!
L-elf...
L-elf!
Get real!
Why the hell should I hand over my cell to you people?!
Let go of me, you bastards!
I run this school, you Dorssian dicks!
Am I not gonna let you act like you own—
There's no point in resisting!
The JIOR homeland has already surrendered unconditionally!
Surrendered?
I'll say it again so it'll sink through those peace-softened skulls!
It wasn't just here that was attacked?
The country of JIOR no longer exists!
This is now an incorporated territory of Greater Dorssia!
Rock-paper-scissors! Rock! Rock!
Rock! Rock! Rock! Rock!
Is that really you in there, Haruto?
I have mixed feelings that it took a game to prove it's me, but yeah.
Then it's really you?!
It's pretty hazy, but I remember climbing down from that robot, and then...
Have you even fired a gun before?
Its just like amnesia.
Even if you lose your memory, you can still talk or use a phone or whatever, right?
So that means that the owner of this body fought on a daily basis?
What's this guy's story?
What do we do now?
Let's retrieve Haruto's body.
Good point. This is freaking me out.
Right, Haruto?
We have to do more than that.
I'm going to take back that robot and smash those Dorssian bastards!
Haruto?
Otherwise, it doesn't even come close to balancing out what I lost.
Those people killed Shoko!
The JIOR government has agreed to an unconditional surrender.
The annexation of JIOR seems to have been successful.
Correct?
Yes, sir. We have finished neutralizing the enemy's combat potential in Module 77.
Displacement of the JIOR populace is currently underway.
We were able to secure the primary strategic objective with relatively little damage.
Its pilot is still unconscious.
He is a student at that school that was shown on the net.
And what of L-elf?
A-About that...
L-elf turned traitor, sir!
L-elf injured A-drei and remains at large.
Cause, unknown.
I can't believe someone from the Karlstein Agency would turn traitor...
I guess this is the first blemish on the reputation of the Perfection Army.
Who goes there?!
You're—
You killed them?
What's wrong with that? This is war, remember?
But you—
They don't get to kill Shoko and then plead for their own lives.
Inzukua-senpai, you and the girls stay here.
This next part is going to involve killing.
Haruto, what's gotten into you?
If I don't at least avenge her, I could never forgive myself.
This is its engine?
Its way too small. You saw how much power it put out.
What's a neutral country like JIOR doing with tech like this?
This design is based on a totally new line of thinking...
These are radiator fins.
Right, they were giving off smoke in the battle yesterday.
Why did they make it humanoid?
The real mystery is why the frame changed color like it did.
What now?
L-elf?!
The wounds... They're healed?
Crap!I guess this thing doesn't handle like a bike!
I'm coming, too!
No! It's not—
It's not safe in here!
Why not?
Why did you come?!
Hold out your hands. I'll tie you up.
L-elf turned up?!
Yes, sir! The primary strategic objective has been stolen!
L-elf?!
We'll just recreate what you did the first time.
And this will turn me back to normal?
That's how it usually works in the movies.
It's something I can do, so I guess I have to try.
I...
I'm back! I'm in my own body!
What the hell?
I knew it. We're both back to normal, right?
Why are you alive?
Let's get out of here!
Dorssians go home!
Captain! Point-blank fire would be unwise!
Attitude control! Right roll 15!
What the—?
Haruto!
I-I'm sinking?!
This guy is an amateur?
Let's use this chance to leave the Module.
We can rendezvous with our forces outside.
This is— We're in space...
It's the Earth!
Enemies!
There's no surface, how do I—
Of course there isn't! We're in space!
Just surrender!
A single unit can't possibly win!
Be quiet.
Don't block my view!
That's the light that was in the reports?
Don't push yourself too hard, A-drei. Your injuries aren't healed yet.
That's why I'm going.
A-drei! Ideal, box out!
Blitzendegen!
Blitzendegen.
Q-vier, box out!
It's huge!
What is that thing?
The pride of the Dorssian army, the heavy strategic weapon Ideal...
This is how we could fight ARUS as more than equals though Dorssia was weaker as a country.
Let us show you!
What's that?!
Let's go, L-elf!
That attack... It's A-drei?
What's that number mean?
If it reaches 100, it stops moving!
No way!
If you keep it running too long, it overheats.
What should we do?
I don't know!
It's stopped moving?
Surrender.
Signal them that you're standing down.
Let go of Rukino!
There's no wounds...
L-elf! Why did you shoot me?!
What?!
You traitor!
I'll kill you myself!
What's he talking about?
L-elf!
I turned traitor? Me?
He's running away?!
Hey, what's he talking about?
Exactly what he said.
You shot one of your own people. So...
I didn't shoot anyone!
Thanks so much for turning traitor!
I always wanted to see what it was like to fight you, L-elf!
What's the big idea?!
Back off, Q-vier.
I'll be the one to settle things with L-elf.
No fair!
What did you people do to me?!
Me, shoot A-drei? Impossible!
This ringtone, it's—
Shoko?!
Haruto? Haruto, is that you?!
That voice... Shoko? Is it really you?
Shoko, where are you?
In the dirt. It looks like the whole car got buried.
Really...? So that's what happened...
I made certain that he was dead.
What a relief... I'm so glad you're alive...
But compared to his clothes, the damage to his body is nonexistent.
What's going on?
Haruto? Can you hear me?
Sorry, my battery's about to die.
It'll be okay.
I'm heading straight back. We can just talk face to face.
I have no memory of shooting A-drei.
But I have injuries I don't remember getting...
What happened to my body while I was blacked out?
Was I controlled? By who?
Shoko, when I get back, let's pick up our talk where we left off.
The one in front of the shrine.
I promise! Because I'm heading back!
L-elf!
It started!
It's stopped again?
Why now?! Shoko is alive! I promised her!
I said I'd come back for her! Why now?!
It can't end here!
Hey! Work, damn it!
41 Hertz, 30 micropascals.
The engine sound is still running.
The medical box on the seat back shows signs of being rewritten
so all the text would be in the same sans serif style.
It's clear that this cockpit's designer had a pathological attention to detail.
But look at the scale of the heat capacity gauge.
The next unit after 100 is 666.
I find it hard to believe that such a designer would use a number that has no significance.
Why would it do this while there are so many alerts going off?
What comes after 666?
Possibility.
I'll start by ripping off your arms and legs!
I can't die. I don't want to die.
I mean, Shoko is alive!
Surrender, L-elf!
I...
...you.
I made a promise to Shoko!
That's I'd come back to her alive, no matter what!
So I'm gonna—
What the—?
I don't like the looks of that! Get clear, A-drei!
I'm gonna live!
It committed harakiri?
Impossible!
L-elf!
What is that?
Gather remaining forces! Regroup, and—
What's that?!
The ARUS fleet!
They're showing up now?
Fall back! It's time to retreat!
Q-vier!
Yes, sir...
Are we... saved?
That's right, were saved!
Answer me.
I'm sure that I killed you.
So why are you alive?
Why did I shoot A-drei?
Why don't I remember doing it?!
You did all of it, didn't you?
Monster!
We're out!
Sweet!
Haruto!
They were telling the truth! You're piloting a robot!
Wow, it's big!
Thanks. You sent them to look for me, didn't you?
Nah, it was no big deal...
So, about picking up where we left off?
You know, the shrine? We were interrupted.
Shoko.
The thing is, I think you're...
Yeah?
Your T-shirt is lame!
I'd always thought so. "Who makes a T-shirt like that?"
It's a limited edition! And it's signed by the creator's mom!
Are you kidding me?! I can't believe you!
You were looking all serious, and that's what you say to me?!
Well, your lack of fashion sense is that serious.
Hey, where are you going?!
The bathroom! I've been holding it in for hours!
Gross! You're a louse!
What the hell, man?!
Come on... What else could I do?
Why?
I've been turned into a monster!
I don't have the right to tell her how I really feel...
Haruto...
Next time, episode 3. "L-elf's Prophesy."
Valvrave the Liberator; it's the system to reveal the truth of the world.