Galactic Calendar, Year 211
Year 0 of the Third Galactic Empire.
At the time, though, it was called Year 71 of the True Calendar.
It's way out in the backwaters of the galaxy!
I suppose it is.
Is this the planet called "Earth"?
The Empire began from such a tiny world?
Not even from a world.
It all began from a single Module.
"Module"?
I suppose "Module" is an obsolete word now.
Our originator, the Founder, lost many classmates in the battle for Module 77, and then...
he happened across the Magius.
Rukino Saki...
Will you...
marry me?
I want you to make me spend the rest of my life to pay for what I did.
Are you some kind of idiot?
I'm an idol, you know.
It's impossible for me to belong to one person.
But what I did to you was—
You're such a child.
I'm an entertainer.
I've done that tons of times.
I was part of an adult, filthy world that you know nothing about.
You're lying.
You're not that kind of—
You know perfectly well what that was.
It was a Kamitsuki attack.
Now go rescue our prime minister, Haruto.
After all, I don't hate her.
Oh, hey! Why don't you come join us?
No! No!
Rejected...
I rejected her...
Sashinami Shoko. We're moving.
If you sit here, your father will have died for nothing.
L-elf! Where are you?!
The school. Sashinami is with me.
My Valvrave will be offline for a while.
In the meantime, use me!
Drive the Dorssian soldiers out of the Module!
That's an effective decision, coming from you.
Wait for me in front of the #2 track. I'll pick you up.
Understood. And tell Shoko something for me.
We're going to win, no matter what.
Did you hear that?
Don't tell Haruto...
Would Tokishima Haruto suffer if he knew he killed Prime Minister Sashinami?
You two are so much alike.
Bulkhead G-17 has been breached!
Power feed to spaceport block is falling!
Confirmation of drill launch by enemy forces that infiltrated the Pit!
It will arrive at the school in 60 minutes!
Oh, no... My sister is in—
That's a drill, isn’t it?
That doesn't look good...
It's climbing this way! Get clear, hurry!
What's that?
Smoke?
Something stings...
Hirata?
Run! It's gas!
Hurry, it's headed right for us!
It's gas!
Hurry! Move to higher ground!
Bansho, run! It's not safe here!
Poison gas?!
Is that true?
Yes! If that drill reaches the surface, poison gas will spread through the whole Module!
We'll all die!
He's ignoring the New Guinea Treaty, is he?
That's so like you, Cain, a man who puts results ahead of methods.
You know him?
He's the hero who was awarded three Dorssian medals of valor.
He was the central figure of the reformation 12 years ago, the Chancellor's right-hand man.
As well as the man who tamed me.
You're a soldier, I take it?
Professor?
The wound in your left shoulder is from a gunshot. A .45 caliber frangible.
The rough scar left from the suturing tells me that it was a battlefield patch job.
Judging from the cleanliness of your hands, you're either a military surgeon or a scientist.
We'll interrogate him separately.
Add him to the list.
Captain? Where are you going?
The graduation ceremony.
Professor?
Professor!
Poison gas?! These bastards are fighting dirty!
If we don't do something, they'll be wiped out!
We have to stop that drill no matter what it takes!
Let's head to the Pit's entrance!
I'll be our shield! Yamada, you're support!
Rukino, you're our lead-off man!
Roger!
It's "Thunder"!
Ha... Haru—
Hello? Sashinami? It's me, Renbokoji!
Please, save my sister! Save Akira!
The drill is headed right for the school.
If we don't do something Akira will— Please!
Big brother...
She had a rough time at school a long time ago.
That's why she's scared of going outside.
She hasn't answered any of my texts or calls.
Please, Sashinami!
You're the only person—
I don't want your help!
Akira?
Akira-chan?
I'm not scared. I'm here because I love this place.
There aren't any people that I hate here.
Idiots are automatically weeded out.
It is clean and just and a world that's only mine!
Let them take Unit 1?
A Trojan horse. We'll be hidden in the engine, and they'll take us right to the heart of their operation.
It's too dangerous!
This isn't a situation where we can worry about risk.
This is Cain that we're up against!
I can't believe it...
They were supposed to be keeping an eye on Unit 1...
Cain!
Welcome, my greatest masterpiece.
Now, shall we begin the graduation ceremony?
Listen up, you bastards!
Thunder's gonna yank out that poison gas of yours!
Piedra del Sol unit, the Valvraves are headed your way!
But A-drei has gone to join the Captain.
The Captain informed me. It's no problem.
Nope, nope!
After all, I'm here!
I thought I told you that these chumps won't work on me!
Have a taste of my Machine Gun Punch!
How'd ya like that thumping?
Lame tricks like that aren't gonna work against—
Huh? My temperature's spiking!
All I did was punch the thing!
Hey, now!
Dude, seriously?!
You gotta be kidding me!
Yamada! Can't you move?!
No, I'm over 100%!
Irons? Is that their plan?!
The principle is simplicity itself. But Lord Cain is a great man indeed to have been able to notice it.
It's a hot idea, right?!
A Trojan horse, eh?
It's a classic, but not bad.
I'll be taking this machine.
For the future of the clan.
You killed them!
Immortal.
As I thought, he's third generation.
No hesitation to kill your former teacher.
I'll give you a proficiency rating of S. However...
...surely I must have ingrained it in you by now.
You can't win against me.
Drill has reached sublevel 5!
It's even raising the temperature of my shield?!
We're out of time! All right, then...
No matter how formidable the defensive capabilities that unit boasts...
It's no use! No use! No use!
The Piedra del Sol is even more powerful!
Inuzuka-senpai!
You're still weak on defense, I see.
Proficiency rating, E.
Impossible... How can he be beating me?
Run, L-elf!
Wha—?
You're the only one who can turn the tide!
Run and win! In this!
That's a sensible decision, coming from you!
Oh, he's made a friend, has he?
In a long life, friends are a precious thing.
Isn't that right, A-drei?
The Captain called on me to act as interrogator.
But don't worry.
Once it's all over, I'll take your eyes.
You will become my left eye, and together, we shall see my revolution.
Enemy forces are coming!
If you stay there, you'll die!
So what?
If the other choice is going outside, I'd rather die.
It's like telling me to devolve into a water flea or something.
I don't want to live by lowering myself to that.
You're the water flea, big brother, you can go ahead and live surrounded by paramecia.
I'll live by myself and die by myself!
Give me a break...
Give me a break!
You'd rather die? Not a chance!
The key is to not let them touch you, right?
I gotcha!
You little brat!
Die. I'll boil your blood in your veins.
Valvrave units have all shut down...
Isn't this bad...?
Lady Takahi?
Iori! Where's Tokishima?
I think he's with L-elf...
Don't just "think"! Get him on the line right now!
Yes, ma'am!
Drill has reached sub-level 2!
I-I'm fine by myself, I'm telling you!
I don't need your help! Don't come!
Your voice, your smile, the heat of your body, it'll all be gone!
You'll never meet anyone again!
You won't be able to talk!
You won't be able to hate!
Or be touched by anyone!
Y-You're just like everyone else.
You laugh at me! Pity me!
You get mad at me and tell me to go outside!
I'm mad, all right!
See?! I told you!
Because I'm your friend!
I don't remember us ever becoming friends...
We are starting now!
Don't decide that by yourself!
Too late, I already have!
That's so self-centered...
Never underestimate a friend!
You and I, we're friends, right?
Sho—
Drill has reached sub-level 1!
We're done for!
It's not working...
What am I gonna do?
What am I gonna do...?
Let's get you nice and dean, young lady!
You filthy thing!
My, what lovely hair you have!
I think you'd look good in a short cut!
Your scalp doesn't itch anywhere, does it?
I can't...
I promised her...
That we'd—
Come shopping with me at the supermarket!
SUPERMARKET!
I'm out! I made it out!
Shoko! Shoko-chan!
Shoko...
Shoko-chan...
Shoko-chan!
Already did...
Shoko... Shoko-chan...
She's alive!
It's not stopping!
"HACKING CODE..."
My weapon...
What the—?
I'm being hacked?
What in the world?!
Unit 6!
Who's piloting it?
H-neun! Launch your Waffe squadron!
Bad guys get out!
H-neun! What are you playing at?!
It wasn't me! The machines did it on their own!
This is bad!
Shoot, Haruto!
Him? But he's not in a mecha!
Shoot him! He's too dangerous!
I'll... I'll protect our country!
We all promised that we'd never give up, not to the bitter end!
Cain, not even you could have survived that.
He dodged it?!
Impossible!
Didn't I make it clear?
You can't beat me.
That's—
What are you...?
I've won, Cain. That unit doesn't work.
I'm sure this brings back nothing but bad memories for you, but I need you, Ploo.
Curse those humans...
What?
B...ro—
It talked?!
Bro... Bro—
Big brother!
It's taken human form!
Unit 2 was broken...
Only modified students can operate the Valvraves.
He can use the Valvrave's light without a Valvrave.
All these phenomena suggest that he is not human!
Cain, what in the world are you?
We are the Magius.
Those who dwell in the shadows of the world.
I'll die? Me?
Select the next pilot.
You worry about me.
Haruto! Save me!
L-elf, damn you!
It was Tokishima Haruto who proposed human experimentation.
I'll end this curse with us!