The intertwined fates of men give the Mononoke its Form.
Enter the woman, protecting her child.
Enter the mistress who gives the woman shelter for the night.
Enter the man who seeks the woman.
They all reside beneath the same roof.
A splendid cast, set against the nightly
bustle, the splash of drink and the clatter of cups,
and the innocent sound of children’s voices.
Though the voices were clear, the children were
absent, except for the one in the woman’s womb.
The Mononoke is most certainly a Zashikiwarashi,
but where are the Truth and Regret?
The blue moon illuminated
your wandering shadow.
I could never tell you all I wanted to say.
It was so very frustrating.
I think about your faked smile,
and forget all the hot tears we shed.
What do these empty husks,
those empty eyes of yours, reflect, my dear?
The transient quarter moon
hides in a rift in the clouds,
as darkness seeps up from the ground.
Tell me the truth, please.
Are you so despondent
that you still sit alone, sighing?
Part the Second
There is something within this lodge.
The pregnant girl and this inn…
I’m sorry.
I’ll protect you.
Does this perhaps bring
I’m sorry!
anything to mind?
There, there.
What of the man the Mononoke killed?
Do you know him?
The man’s name was Naosuke.
He was an assassin.
Why was he here?
To kill me and my unborn child.
Sh—She was serious about that?
Who sent him?
My master and mistress.
Why?
Because its father is their heir.
It was an unallowable—
Relationship.
But they did allow it!
Good lord.
They just suddenly said it couldn’t be, that it was forbidden!
Idiot.
Stupid girl.
I didn’t want their property!
So naive.
I promised the young master!
I just wanted to give birth!
That’s all!
God, you’re so annoying!
I don’t care if it’s a Mononoke or a ghost, or what, I…
If there’s something in this house,
then why don’t we just leave?
How the…
What…
Huh?
My goodness.
What on Earth is going on?
Mother.
It stinks.
People?
I’m sorry!
What is
this?
Just where is this?
This will be difficult.
How can you be so relaxed?
Do something about this!
It’s gone?
This way.
It’s coming.
It’s gone again.
You’re the one who refuses to talk, ma’am.
Now…
This room was made as an offering to the dead.
What do you mean, an offering?
It was all I could do for them.
All you could do?
This house was once a brothel.
Where is this, ma’am?
This is the abortion room.
It’s a grave for all the children produced.
We were doing them a favor.
What’s wrong with that?
What?
Huh?
Shino?
Shino, I love you.
The young master,
and myself?
Shino, I love you.
I love you.
I am your servant.
The master and mistress will not allow it.
I love you.
Let us marry!
Marry?
Are you sure?
I don’t care what happens.
Really?
Really. You’re all I need.
Oh, really?
Then I can tell you.
What is it?
What can you tell me?
I…
I am carrying your child.
Huh?
Is that so?
You’ll sleep with anyone who has money, right?
What a stupid girl.
Right, Tokuji?
Yup.
Mother.
How nice!
I’ve decided.
I’ll use these people.
Congratulations!
Thank you.
I’ve finally got a mother.
Goodness, what a nuisance!
She seems so nice.
If you can’t work, you’ll never pay off your debt.
It’s no good hiding.
You’re useless.
If you can’t work, you don’t eat.
You’re whores, sold to pay a debt!
You can’t do your job with a child in the works.
Stop it.
In order to survive…
Stop it!
I had no choice.
You’re with child, are you?
That’s
no good.
We’ll help you out.
If it’s gone…
The Zashikiwarashi won’t come after you!
Stop it!
The Zashikiwarashi wanted to be born!
That’s why they came after you.
Stop it!
Don’t kill him!
No.
Medicine Seller?
Those tied to this room were killed when this was a brothel.
A child’s emotions.
Now for the Regret. Just one more.
If I find the Regret, the sword can be drawn.
What is it you want?
Stop it!
Don’t kill them!
What did those poor children do to you?
This is a Mononoke. It wishes to burst forth from your belly.
It just wants to live in this world!
But it cannot.
Come here.
I’ll give birth to you, as well.
You wish to give birth to the Mononoke?
All those within my womb are my children.
Stop it.
You’ll be sucked in.
I will give birth to my child.
That’s all I want.
Why?
Congratulations!
I like this one!
She always strokes me.
So kind.
I’m glad it was her.
I’m sorry I had to hurt you so.
Thank you for always trying your best.
Thank you for talking to me so much.
I love you.
I love
you.
You’re welcome.
Thank you for choosing me, for coming to me.
I’m sorry. I could not be your mother.
We can’t be together.
I…
Without you, I just can’t smile.
I walk this banal town,
feeling such intense emotions.
I know that if I could treasure them and live on,
I would need nothing else.
The summer flowers that bloomed in the sky
Come falling down, dancing in the wind.
I can barely recall the night sky
where they all came tumbling down,
so what I can still recall is all the more precious.
There, there. There, there.
Well, I never did eat, did I?
Are you sure I should be your mother?
I hope to see you soon.
The End