Feelings and memories…
They exist only within my heart.
Though we may pass the same time, or see the same sights,
what we hold within our hearts can never be the same.
Your face, your voice,
the image of you, which exists only within me…
Who are you?
Faceless One
The blue moon illuminated
your wandering shadow.
I could never tell you all I wanted to say.
It was so very frustrating.
I think about your faked smile,
and forget all the hot tears we shed.
What do these empty husks,
those empty eyes of yours, reflect, my dear?
The transient quarter moon
hides in a rift in the clouds,
as darkness seeps up from the ground.
Tell me the truth, please.
Are you so despondent
that you still sit alone, sighing?
Part the Second
I’m afraid I won’t bend to your will.
If you will not show me your true Form, then at least
be quiet
for a while.
What?
Please.
What are you doing?
Stop it!
My, my.
Such a contrary thing.
Well then, shall we restart our little play?
Play?
The intertwined fates of men give the Mononoke its Form.
When an Ayakashi clings onto
a person’s thoughts and feelings,
it becomes a Mononoke.
I see. You came here to kill the Mononoke.
If I could kill it now, my work would be easy.
I must discover the Mononoke’s Truth and Regret,
and without its Form,
I cannot draw the Sword of Exorcism.
This is a troublesome Mononoke, indeed.
Truth is a physical state,
and Regret is a state of mind.
If the Mononoke will not show me its Form,
I will have to make it tell me
its Truth and Regret.
Ochou’s life,
Part the First.
My life?
Sake! Sake!
I need more sake!
I told you to bring me more sake! What are you doing?
What a worthless wife you have.
I’m sorry!
The Mononoke is showing me what you feel.
The perfect feelings for a Mononoke to leech.
This is not a laughing matter!
Yes it is. Quite funny, indeed.
With such a laughable situation as an excuse,
how many did you kill?
This is the result of relying on the Mononoke’s strength.
Relying on…
Do you remember that?
The sky?
That’s right.
The sky.
Your very own sky,
which you watched every day.
My own sky?
I told you to bring me more sake! What are you doing?
I—I’m sorry!
You simply looked.
I was only looking, but it made me happy.
Why did you not leave this place?
Stop it.
Who is it that you really killed?
Who did I really kill?
Stop it!
Ochou-san,
who did you kill?
Stop it!
Step no further into Ochou-san’s heart!
Ochou-san,
if you believe this place binds you, it will be your prison.
If you do not wish to leave, it will become a fortress.
It’s the same as that place.
You thought of it as a prison.
I…
I told you to bring me more sake! What are you doing?
I—I’m sorry!
Why did I not simply leave?
Mother.
You look just like I did when I was young.
With your beauty, you will certainly
be able to marry into a wealthy family.
Mother,
I’ll do my best.
This is most difficult.
I loved my mother.
Stop it, Ochou-san!
You don’t have to tell him anything!
He is deceiving you!
Be quiet.
The play is not over.
Ochou’s life,
Part the Second.
You were born beautiful.
What is this?
Mind your appearance carefully,
Mother?
and you will be able to marry into a wealthy
family, in spite of your humble upbringing.
Yes, Mother!
Good girl. Good girl.
I loved my mother.
I wanted her praise.
So you bore it,
to the point of losing your own soul.
My soul?
How many times must I say it?
I’m sorry!
I’ve warned you about that so many times!
I’m sorry! I’m sorry! I’m sorry! I’m sorry! I’m sorry!
Watch.
Start over from the beginning.
I’m sorry! I’m sorry! I’m sorry! I’m sorry! I’m sorry!
You’ll never be a proper lady at this rate!
One more time!
I’m sorry! I’m sorry! I’m sorry! I’m sorry! I’m sorry!
Yes.
No.
One and two and three!
Four and five and six!
No.
Seven and eight and nine!
Stop this.
I hid myself, so as not to interrupt your taking of vows.
Mother.
Ochou’s life,
Part the Third.
I merely wish to express my
gratitude and extend my best wishes.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Please, sit up now.
We derive no pleasure from watching you prostrate yourself.
My goodness, such a gorgeous lady she is.
Are you as good in bed as you look?
Oh my, stop it!
That’s for our brother to find out!
I can buy as many women as I want with money.
Please! Please!
Please, keep her for all her life!
Is this your mother’s wish?
Yes.
My father died young, and his pension was confiscated.
All my mother wished was for me to marry into wealth.
That was the only thing she wished for.
Now I can finally hold my head high as I visit
the graves of my ancestors, the Umezawake clan.
I see.
So, you became your mother’s tool, to further her ends.
No!
Then, what is that?
Again?
You lost your soul for your mother’s wish.
You became a tool for your mother’s selfish ends.
Then, you fell in love.
You…
But the object of your affections…
Who was he?
What?
Ochou’s life,
Part the Fourth.
I told you to bring me more sake! What are you doing?
I—I’m sorry!
Ochou-san, just get us some more sake!
What a worthless wife you have.
A lazy girl, indeed.
Brother, whyever did you take her in?
Her mother begged me to.
If your first wife hadn’t hung herself, would
you ever have accepted her into your home?
Well, she’s a pretty good cook,
and good in bed, too!
Oh stop, you’re just terrible!
Ochou-san,
who did you kill?
Stop it.
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
Stop it. Stop it.
Ochou-san,
that mask is not
a Mononoke.
A Mononoke controls the masked man.
It deceived you,
and imprisoned you.
That is its Truth.
Lies.
And in trying to accept your mother’s twisted love,
No! No! No! No! No! No!
your heart wavered, and a Mononoke latched onto it.
That is the Regret.
No! No! No! No! No! No!
I loved my mother.
Mother, look!
You’re so beautiful.
You can fulfill my dream and marry into wealth.
I did my best.
I did my best, but…
No! No! No!
No! No more.
Mother, listen! Listen to me!
Mother, listen to me!
I can’t wait!
Why won’t you listen to what I have to say?
Mother, listen to me!
All four of these men are wealthy and prosperous.
Mother, why won’t you listen to me?
Listen…
I can’t wait. I can’t wait…
Listen to me.
I…
I can’t wait. I can’t wait…
I’m so stupid.
Ochou.
Who was it that you killed?
Who did I
kill?
All of them
were me?
I…
You lost yourself in others’ greed.
Why?
I…
You are a Mononoke.
Show me
your Form.
It’s me!
I am
the Mononoke!
May I ask you one thing?
Why did the Faceless One…
Why did it save me?
Do you believe you were saved?
If you wish to know,
perhaps it fell in love
with you.
His love could never be.
The Mononoke despaired.
The Mononoke despaired?
Thank you.
I’ll be fine.
I told you to bring me more sake! What are you doing?
I—I’m sorry!
Ochou-san, just get us some more sake!
What a worthless wife you have.
A lazy girl, indeed.
Brother, whyever did you take her in?
Her mother begged me to.
If your first wife hadn’t hung herself, would
you ever have accepted her into your home?
Well, she’s a pretty good cook,
and good in bed, too!
Oh stop, you’re just terrible!
Hey, what are you doing?
Lazy bitch.
You’re totally useless.
Indeed, she is.
She’s so damned lazy.
Hey!
Useless indeed.
Ochou!
Can’t you hear?
Still not here?
She lazes around so, whatever she does.
I just can’t stand her!
What’s taking her so long, I wonder?
Ochou!
Sake! Sake!
Bring us sake!
Where’s the sake?
But there’s no-one here.
The End
Without you, I just can’t smile.
I walk this banal town,
feeling such intense emotions.
I know that if I could treasure them and live on,
I would need nothing else.
The summer flowers that bloomed in the sky
Come falling down, dancing in the wind.
I can barely recall the night sky
where they all came tumbling down,
so what I can still recall is all the more precious.