I’ll never forgive you.
I’ll never…
I’ll ne…
I’ll never forgive you.
Ghost Cat
The blue moon illuminated
your wandering shadow.
I could never tell you all I wanted to say.
It was so very frustrating.
I think about your faked smile,
and forget all the hot tears we shed.
What do these empty husks,
those empty eyes of yours, reflect, my dear?
The transient quarter moon
hides in a rift in the clouds,
as darkness seeps up from the ground.
Tell me the truth, please.
Are you so despondent
that you still sit alone, sighing?
Prelude
Fukuju Station
Fukuju Subway Station Grand Opening
It is with great pride that I open
this subway station for business.
Fukuju Station
Fukuju Subway Station Grand Opening
Thank you. Thank you.
Yes, thank you!
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Sir, we should get going.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you! Thank you!
Everyone on the platform, please stand back!
We’ll need to see your tickets before boarding!
Nomoto Chiyo-sama
Congratulations!
You won!
Don’t push! No pushing, please.
Um, is this where car number four will be boarding?
Um, no, it’s not.
This is the first car.
Only VIPs can get in there.
Over there.
Aw, all that way?
What’s with him?
Oh my, that huge pack must be heavy!
He looks kind of handsome, though.
He must be one of those sandwich board advertisers.
Yeah, looks like it. Thank you so much, sir!
Excuse me! Sorry!
Excuse me!
Sorry!
Stand back! Stand back!
Excuse me, everyone. Let me through.
Hey, wait!
Police
Thank you for providing security, Detective.
Aw man. It’s not fair!
I want to ride up there, with the mayor!
Excuse me.
Will the train be back by this afternoon?
It loops back after four stops, so it should be less than an hour.
Well, this is a banner day!
Four more minutes!
I’d like to embark on the second stage as soon as possible.
Of course! I trust you implicitly, sir.
You have our full support.
I’m Moria, from the Morning News.
Allow me to congratulate you on the new station.
How do you feel right now?
I’m extremely pleased to meet the expectations of my citizens.
I suppose that’s most of what I’m feeling.
Well said, sir! Well said, indeed!
What suck-ups.
Hey, ink-slinger, let’s leave it at that, shall we?
Banzai! Banzai! Banzai! Banzai! Banzai!
One
Two
Three
Four
This train’s atmosphere is so pleasant, isn’t it?
Yes, it is indeed.
The riff-raff on my last ride were so unpleasant.
Yes, well they are all rather rank.
I could barely breathe!
And the very first train, to boot!
I could hardly believe I won the drawing.
I’ve so been looking forward to this.
Yes, so have I!
One
Was there an accident?
All right. Everyone remain calm.
Two
Oh wow!
Geez.
Three
Four
What?
What? What? Wha—
Four
Three
Two
One
Was it my imagination?
Mr. Mayor?
Where’s everyone else?
Where’d they go?
How did…
They’re all gone.
Oh, thank you so much for earlier!
Oh, not at all.
We apologize for the inconvenience.
We have discovered a foreign object blocking the tracks,
Where is this?
The first car.
and are taking the necessary precautions.
The first car?
Hey, you!
What are you doing here?
Hey, it’s nothing to shout about.
Don’t be rude to the passengers.
But—
Surely none of them have any
insight into these strange occurrences.
I’ll
return to my seat, then.
I’ll be going, too!
It’s too heavy!
I can’t budge it.
Uh. Let me try it!
Useless women.
This is Kinoshita, the driver.
Station One, come in.
That’s strange.
Allow me.
Thank you!
Old man just can’t contain himself, can he?
What’s the matter?
Why aren’t we moving?
Hey, you!
What’s going on?
Thank you so much!
I’ll have to have it modified so that anyone can open it.
Where are the other cars?
Mr. Mayor?
Who’s driving this thing?
I’ll never forgive you.
Did you just say you wouldn’t forgive me?
Did anyone say that?
No.
It was just my imagination.
Oh no, how scary!
My imagination…
What’s the matter with this train?
Aren’t you in control?
I’ve used every tool at my disposal!
We can’t even contact the surface.
I’ll never get promoted now.
I thought that today would go so well.
We’re in the tunnel the whole way, so it really is pretty scary.
10:05 a.m., sudden stop.
Passengers vanish. Cause unknown.
Hey Newsman, don’t you get sick if you write on the train?
I’ve been doing my job for twenty years. I’m quite used to it.
What’s wrong, boy?
Goodness! Don’t scare me like that!
Um…
There was just a…
Here it is.
Who are you?
It’s the Sandwich Board Man.
Newsman!
How?
There’re no other cars back there.
How’d you get in here?
As you saw,
I came from the next car along.
I am a medicine seller.
Huh?
I have to dress like this these days, for my wares to sell.
Still, it’s awfully pretty.
You saw that, didn’t you?
I don’t know why, but we can’t get out of the door from here.
Just a minute ago, the mayor…
Fell out.
Don’t finish his sentences! That’s creepy!
The train’s moving of its own accord.
It’s as though a fox spirit has a hold of it.
This is not a fox spirit’s doing.
I know that.
It’s just a figure of speech.
The mayor
was killed by a Mononoke.
A Mononoke?
Stop that! Don’t be creepy!
Get your craziness out of here!
It was an accident, that’s all!
But the train’s moving on its own.
Of course it was an accident!
He’s yelling again.
You didn’t see anything!
I can tell
even without having seen.
It moved by itself!
What are those?
They’re scales.
Their alignment
tells me the Mononoke’s position.
You are all connected.
The Mononoke has placed all those involved in this car.
Connected? We’re all meeting for the first time.
That’s right!
I just won my ticket in a raffle!
How would you say we’re connected?
You should all know that.
I think I do know one of you!
What?
Me too. I remember one person.
I remember one of you, as well.
Me too.
Who, then?
You too?
I don’t know anyone.
Yeah, I’ve no idea what this is about, either.
My.
To think that four of the six here recognize the same person.
Would you all be able to tell me more?
I don’t remember any of them.
Oh, right!
Let’s have all your names, ages and
professions, along with where you say you met me.
Yes, right. That’s a good idea.
I’m Nomoto Chiyo, aged twenty-one.
I’m a waitress at a café across from the station!
A shining example of a career woman.
Well, yeah.
Don’t be ridiculous!
I never went to that café!
Yes you did!
You came in on an investigation, didn’t you, Detective?
When was this?
Three or four months ago, right?
Yeah, exactly!
Hey, how did…
Oh, Detective!
You were outside smoking while your
partner questioned me, so I didn’t recognize you.
Ah. I’m Yamaguchi Haru, a widow.
Age?
Don’t be rude.
Thirty-five.
You didn’t have to tell him.
And what happened to your husband?
He died five years ago of an illness of the lungs.
I currently live with my mother-in-law.
Just the facts, ma’am!
You really don’t remember?
Unlike you, I’m a busy man!
I can’t remember everyone I meet. Now, say when you met me!
Let’s see, what cures amnesia?
You have to give your name and age first, Detective.
You’re a willful young woman.
Kadowaki Shakei, forty years old.
I’m a police officer.
Then I’ll give you a hint.
It was about a regular customer at our shop.
One of those… Modern Girls, they call them.
Modern Girl
That’s not all. She was totally gorgeous, too!
I was so jealous!
Unfortunately, though, she got hit by a train and died.
I didn’t mean to!
I didn’t mean to.
Morning News. Train accident.
Oh, that!
That’s right. I remember. You
were driving at the time, weren’t you?
Your name was…
Kinoshita Bunpei, twenty-eight.
It was just an accident!
She jumped off the bridge, killing herself, and
my train just happened to be passing through.
Jumped off…
I told you then, I didn’t mean to do it!
We get it! Calm down. It wasn’t your fault.
We determined it was a clear suicide.
I see.
So, that’s it.
You look a bit pale.
Shall I make you a tonic?
No, I’m fine.
And who are you?
Moria Kioshi.
Normally I have a desk job at a newspaper, but they
were shorthanded today and sent me out in the field.
He was the victim’s boss.
She was a writer, then? How nice.
She was pretty famous, if I remember.
What was her name?
I remember her now!
Ichikawa Setsuko!
I was so jealous that she had her name in the paper!
This is some mistake!
I don’t know any of you!
Why do I have to stay locked in here?
Let me off, please!
What does he mean?
I wonder.
Hey, what’s your name?
Kobayashi Masao.
Where do you go to school?
I just graduated from elementary
school, and I work delivering milk.
It must be hard, so early in the morning.
Morning?
If I remember correctly, it was about 5
a.m. when my train passed under the bridge.
Kirigahara Bridge, eh?
A delivery boy, you say.
That’s right.
The dots are finally connected.
Oh.
My word.
There was a woman holding a cat, there.
It’s a Ghost Cat.
To be continued
Without you, I just can’t smile.
I walk this banal town,
feeling such intense emotions.
I know that if I could treasure them and live on,
I would need nothing else.
The summer flowers that bloomed in the sky
Come falling down, dancing in the wind.
I can barely recall the night sky
where they all came tumbling down,
so what I can still recall is all the more precious.