Hey, where did all the other passengers go?
They got off.
Got…
Now, it’s your turn.
They’re all waiting for you.
Ghost Cat
The blue moon illuminated
your wandering shadow.
I could never tell you all I wanted to say.
It was so very frustrating.
I think about your faked smile,
and forget all the hot tears we shed.
What do these empty husks,
those empty eyes of yours, reflect, my dear?
The transient quarter moon
hides in a rift in the clouds,
as darkness seeps up from the ground.
Tell me the truth, please.
Are you so despondent
that you still sit alone, sighing?
Finale
This train will never stop.
I don’t care!
Then, you’ll stay here—
No! I won’t!
Do something about this.
Surely you can help!
How did it come to this?
I just wanted to help her.
Help Setsuko-san?
That’s right!
I felt so sorry that she’d been killed!
Ichikawa.
Moria-san.
You’re terrible.
Show him. Show him.
Show him.
This is…
Are the cats doing this?
Show him.
Stop!
Memories are tied to a single place.
Memory brings about Regret,
and it is through Regret that fates intertwine.
All is turned upside-down.
It’s all your fault!
With Form, Truth and Regret, all can be revealed.
Will you show me
the reason for
your Regret?
Huh? What was that?
Mayor Fukuda is corrupt!
Morning News
I have proof.
Let’s hear what you have to say.
Moria-san?
Is this information reliable?
Of course!
I have it on good authority that
the mayor is meeting with executives
from the railroad company on a regular basis.
Well, there’s nothing illegal about that.
But don’t you think it unlikely
I’m sorry, Ichikawa, but we’re not a tabloid.
that they’re just making small talk?
That’s not enough information for a proper article.
I think you’re just jealous!
Jealous of who?
You’re jealous of me, Moria-san.
Ridiculous!
You’re jealous that I got such a huge story.
It’s not a story at all!
There’s nothing to be jealous about.
We can’t publish it.
Looks like it was a mistake to send you into the field.
You bit off more than you could chew.
I’m putting you back on the advice column.
You can’t!
I’m not giving up on this!
I’ll get to the bottom of this. Mark my words!
Don’t get me wrong, Ichikawa.
I think you’re a great—
Kisshou Hotel
Whoo, yeah! Here it comes!
What’s this?
A woman peeping at me?
I won’t…
I won’t let them beat me.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Yes, indeed, I look forward to it.
I see.
Is this still not enough?
Just as I thought.
I knew you could do it.
I’m sorry for being so hard on you.
Forgive me, Ichikawa.
That’s right! I knew she had it in her!
That’s why I was so hard on her!
When did it happen?
Last night.
And you developed the shots yourself?
Yes.
Where is the film?
In here.
Hey,
let’s go out.
But—
This is a huge scoop.
We can’t let afford to let anyone know about this.
Not even one of our co-workers.
CanCan Café
Here’s the mayor with Touto Railways’ Board of Directors.
Here he is with Nohinbashi Construction.
They met at Kisshou Hotel in Kajima.
The mayor recently passed a city
ordinance at the rail company’s request.
I believe he received a considerable bribe in return.
Where does he bank?
The Ichi’i Bank.
The mayor’s uncle is its president.
I see.
This is more than enough information to move on.
This is front page material.
Have it on my desk tomorrow
night. We’ll run it the next morning.
It’s not much time, but can you make it?
You want me to write the whole article?
Of course!
You did all the work, so you should reap the benefits.
Thank you so much!
I misjudged you, Moria-san.
I was sure you thought of me as a weak, worthless woman,
and that only a man could become a real reporter.
I just thought that…
You couldn’t be more wrong!
Thank goodness!
I’m finally a real newswoman.
Do you know where Hichiriki Zaka’s Konata Inn is?
Write it there.
To prevent any leaks?
That’s right.
We can’t let anyone know about this article.
I’ll put it on the page myself.
Understand?
Yes!
Yes, the very same.
Yes. Actually, I have a proposition for you.
No, it’s not very pleasant at all.
No reason to meet anywhere else, is there?
I’ll come to you.
Her Regret is close.
You promise to help me?
Please, I’m begging you. I want to be famous!
I couldn’t stand to rot away here the rest of my life!
City Hall
Are you the man I spoke to?
I actually had fun last night, for once.
Konata Inn
Hello, Konata Inn.
You’ve got to be kidding me.
I cannot believe that old hag.
I cannot just watch over an invalid
for the rest of my life…
Thanks to her…
I cannot do what I want to.
You have a telephone call.
All right.
Ah.
Setsuko. Aah! No! No!
Working here,
I will never be able to get ahead.
Pitiful, isn’t it?
I was so glad.
I’m different from that loser.
I’m a newswoman.
This is Ichikawa.
Huh?
Why is that?
Yes, I understand.
CanCan Café
It’s true!
People have asked me if I wanted to be a singer.
Aw, I remember that.
I wonder what happened.
Moria-san!
You’re sure you weren’t followed?
Yes.
What’s wrong, Moria-san?
Why do you look so afraid?
We’re in danger.
Oh, poppycock.
It’s not as though we’ll be killed or anything.
I just went to see if she was all right!
There’s no hurry.
Where’s the article?
I have it with me.
Are you going to read it here?
Yes.
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
Moria never looks at the article.
What are you doing?
I can’t let this out.
Just lights a match…
Why not?
Just following orders.
Whose orders?
Sanson Milk Delivery
Masao!
Masao, are you up?
Moria-san, you can’t do this!
You have no right to do this!
I’ll tell our superiors!
No use. I’ve already spoken to them.
You’re lying!
No, I’m not.
You planned this from the beginning!
You were always going to steal my—
I’m sorry. I had to do it.
You coward! You snake!
You planned it from the beginning?
I’ll talk her out of it.
How?
I’ll tell the Chief Editor! I’ll get you fired!
This could be quite a problem.
Well, it’s not really my concern.
At any rate, I’ll leave it to you.
You think I’m jealous of you?
Damn you!
Damn you! Damn you! Damn you!
Don’t make me laugh.
I wouldn’t do this over such petty concerns.
You’re a woman to the end, never
able to catch on when it really counts.
Damn you! Damn you! Damn you!
I was watching her from a much higher position.
What do you mean?
You must not hesitate in executing this order.
You understand?
We can’t have this turning into a scandal.
You’re working for Mayor Fukuda?
How dare you? How dare you?
Yes, you women are so blind.
How dare you?
You have no ability to read a situation.
I’ll kill you!
You never wanted to print the article.
You’ll take orders from me now.
I’ll have it printed somewhere else!
I still have the proof!
I’ve fooled you!
Where is it?
Give it to me!
I’ll never give it up!
This is the only time I really feel alive.
The people won’t allow this!
Stop it! Stop it!
That old hag…
I wish she would just die!
You really are a stupid woman.
I gave you fair warning.
You made me—
Made me kill you?
So sorry.
It’s nothing.
A woman reporter bit off more than she could chew,
and committed suicide after having her dreams shattered.
It hurts. It hurts.
I can’t move.
No! No, it can’t be!
No!
Please, notice me!
Don’t hit me! You have to notice me!
I’ll never forgive you.
No!
She’s not even good enough for the back page.
I want to be an actress.
Here’s your payment.
Yeah, this is a suicide. A suicide, I’m sure.
Shut up!
I’ll never forgive you.
Ayakashi reside in a host,
and humans reside in the physical plane.
A Mononoke is formed with an Ayakashi as its host,
and fed by the fates of men.
However, when a Mononoke comes into the human plane,
it must be killed.
This is
a Ghost Cat.
I will cleanse this world.
The Mononoke must be killed.
Release.
A dream?
I’d like to embark on the second stage as soon as possible.
We’re safe?
Are we safe?
It was just a nightmare.
That’s unlike me.
I’m sorry, Ichikawa.
I had no choice.
I’ll never forgive you.
Without you, I just can’t smile.
I walk this banal town,
feeling such intense emotions.
I know that if I could treasure them and live on,
I would need nothing else.
Afterword
The summer flowers that bloomed in the sky
Lady Reporter’s Death Still Suspicious
Morning News employee involved
Mayor missing along with Morning News reporter.
Come falling down, dancing in the wind.
Lady Reporter’s Death Still Suspicious
Morning News employee involved
Mayor missing along with Morning News reporter.
I can barely recall the night sky
where they all came tumbling down,
so what I can still recall is all the more precious.
Men are born into this world,
Ayakashi simply come into being.
If birth and being are accompanied by Truth and Regret,
they gain a Form.
If they gain a Form, they become a
Mononoke, which should not exist.
We cannot eradicate the Mononoke.
However, we can purify them, and put them to rest.
And so, there must be a sword,
and hands in which it might rest.
My friends, let me ask you of your Truth and Regret.
So long as Mononoke roam this world…
Miss?
I’m coming!
Thank you,
everyone.