ESCAPE
Escape!
ES
CAPE
kono kaze ni
Out into the wind,
namida wo nose
Let it take your tears,
kareru made supiido agete
And just accelerate until they're all dry!
tobikoete yukeru
to
Fly on through it,
kitto kotae wa
The answer is surely there,
harukana ano sora no mukou
Just beyond the sky in the distance!
[AraAraUfufu~] Subs
kotae ga mitsukaranai koko de wa
You won't find the answer here,
tameiki wo tsuite sora wo miru
So breathe a sigh and look up to the sky,
aoku somerareta hitomi no oku de kagayaiteru nowa
In amongst that blue reflected in your eyes, shining his piercing light,
dokodemo yukeru, yume wo miteru
Going where he wants, realizing his dreams,
jibun nano sa
That's another you!
ESCAPE
Escape!
ES
CAPE
kono kaze ni
Out into the wind,
negai wo nosete
Let it take your dreams,
nobashita te wa asu wo egaku
Your extended hand will paint your tomorrow,
mou kowaku nado nai
There's nothing left to fear,
namida no ato
Your tears are all gone,
niji iro ni somatte tondeyuku
Dyed in rainbow colors and flown away,
ano sora no mukou
Just beyond the sky!
Spring,
this is the season when flowers color the Jungfrau.
Today's Universal Naturing TV is brought to you from Switzerland's Jungfrau mountain region.
Two symbols denote the approaching springtime for the Swiss.
One of them is the annual Sechseläuten festival
that takes place in the city of Zurich.
The other one is these blue flowers which bloom
all at once here in the Jungfrau mountain region.
Incidentally, "Jungfrau" means "young lady" or "virgin" in German.
I suspect there are many of you who already knew that,
but are you familiar with the Kriegsjungfrauen,
the fighting young ladies who live here?
That's great!
That's it, smile just like that.
Mm, you're the best!
Lean over just a little more.
Okay, one more.
Now look this way.
That's it, just like that.
Ah, hold still.
Great! Thank you!
Next, if you two could hold each other... ah, that's it!
What are they doing?
It's a photo shoot for a PR pamphlet.
Am I going to do a photo shoot too?
I don't think so.
Shooting photos of you would be all kinds of problematic.
Great! That's perfect!
I wonder if it's because I'm a guy...
Okay, okay!
Come on everyone, gather 'round!
TV?
It's a documentary for Universal Naturing TV.
"The Flawless Flowers of the Jungfraujoch"?
They're referring to you.
But President, we shouldn't be burdening the pilots
with anything besides the missions.
Well, we have sponsors over there, you see...
That again?
They say they want to document how we
at Generation Blue contribute to society.
Well, since that's how it is...
Some material won't exactly be cut out for PR,
but I'm counting on you as my flowery maidens!
This is gonna be a handful.
They want me too?
No way!
O—okay.
It would lead to problems all over the place if you were in it.
That's right.
Generation Bleu's IFO pilots have:
Heart, technique and physique.
They're perfect in all aspects, with beautiful features,
unparalleled leadership skills, and gifted with natural good luck,
and even amongst them, Team Pied Piper monopolize the top spots
of GenBleu's idol polls as the poster girls of the company!
In other words, we're super idols!
I won't stop you if you say you wanna be an idol, though.
Eh? No way, no way, no way!
Well, maybe you should try your best at being a girl, Ao.
And that's why you're an idiot!
Sorry...
Don't gimme "Sorry...", idiot!
That hurt!
Hey!
Ah, I'm sorry, this guy's just... huh?
Could it be... you're that newscaster, Friday?
Why are you here?
Are you filming a piece? You're filming a piece,
aren't you? Man, what a surprise!
I'm a big fan! Please shake my hand!
H—hey...
I'm really, really sorry!
As a symbol of my apology...
Sure... thanks...
Idiot! Don't get so chummy with her!
Come on, let's go!
Good luck with your piece!
I told you not to say it at the same time...
Hurry, hurry!
Why do I have to dress like this?
Come on, hurry, hurry!
Team Pied Piper?
I think the president's room is this way.
Ah, okay.
A mini trip?
Let's call it a small outing.
I know what it is.
In any event, there's no need to worry.
We can always contact them.
But still, for Team Pied Piper, the poster girls
of our company, to be out on a trip...
I doubt this newscaster Friday will keep quiet about it.
Why did you accept their proposal to film the piece then?
Well, the media just want a little something
back in return for their sponsorship.
I was asking what you think.
Have our cute girls go on a journey.
Trips have to be exciting, right?
A mini trip, eh?
Still, to think we could tap them this easily...
That president... he's quite the raccoon...
The president's a raccoon.
Yeah...
It sounds like those three are having fun...
Quite the little field trip.
Does that make us their supervising teachers?
All that's left is to wait for that newscaster Friday to make her move...
Take care of our daughters and our son,
my dear little troupe of spies!
Have you got Gazelle's lot up to no good again?
Alright! This is the guidebook for our field trip.
A guidebook for a field trip?
Sure! You always make one when you go on a trip, right?
I'm asking why we need a guidebook for a field trip...
Don't worry about it.
Our positively moving tour will take us across
the Swiss Alps with all their flowers in full bloom!
To enjoy springtime to its fullest, we'll be taking the Jungfraubahn
and a gondola cruise all across Switzerland in two days!
For dinner, I've put together a menu of cheese fondue, meat fondue, and chocolate fondue!
So, what's this dumpling-looking thing?
That's a snowman.
It's part of the Swiss Sechseläuten festival!
Sechseläuten?
Right!
And cosplayers from all over Europe gather
for the opening parade of the Sechseläuten!
That's a lie
It's an amazing festival that rivals Tokyo's famous Comic Market!
Cos...
...play?
Why?!
It suits you, Ao.
I'm not wearing a wig!
Ao! You ruined it!
Ao can stand!
This isn't right...!!!
Here.
Why did I get stuck doing this...
I'm really getting used to it.
Ao looks like a girl no matter how you look at him now, right?
I didn't even get to go sightseeing properly!
Why, what is this nonsense you're spouting?
I... look like I'm having fun.
Here's Ao in the bear garden,
Ao in the rose garden, Ao at the clock tower.
And this is Ao having fun at the prison tower!
Think I could have a copy of those?
It's an honor to meet you, Kriegsjungfrauen,
especially the much-talked about new flower in your bouquet.
The turquoise-haired mademoiselle, Ao Fukai.
I'm no—
You've got the wrong person!
Oh, there you are!
Sorry to barge in on your conversation like this!
The boss told us to take these guys back to the hotel.
They are our precious, precious princesses after all.
Thanks for rescuing us.
Make sure you contact HQ when you get to the hotel.
Still though, Ao,
you really look like a girl with your hair like that.
Don't!
If you don't want to attract attention,
you're best off pretending to be a girl for the time being.
You... really think so?
Absolutely!
I can't do it after all!
I—I might fall for you!
It suits you so well!
I'll lend you those clothes for now.
It looks even better on you than I expected.
You might be best off dressing like that for the time being.
It is surprisingly passable.
But why did it come to this?
There is a good reason.
But why girl's clo—
Quit your whining!
You're a boy, aren't you?
That's what I've been saying... which is it? Jeez...
Come on...
Alright, we're going back to our rooms.
Let us know if anything happens.
Don't forget to report in, either.
I'm doing it right now.
This is Pied Piper.
Sorry we're so late contacting you.
Yes, there were no problems.
Now that we've contacted HQ...
Elena
Should we go hit the pool?
Why would my swimsuit be a Chinese dress?! This makes no sense!
Splash hot water on him and he becomes a boy,
splash cold water on him and he becomes a girl!
Wait, what?!
Be good and become girl!
Elena
Elena, it's dangerous to throw around kettles.
Sorry, sorry.
Elena
I'll be careful next time!
Now then, moving on...
Splash cold water on him and he becomes a girl,
splash hot water on him and he becomes a boy~!
Splash cold water on him and he becomes a girl,—
I'm a boy!
You should eat more if you're a boy!
No way, no way, no way, no way!
I'm full already.
You two sure can eat, huh?
Desert goes into a separate stomach.
Elena, what are we going to do tomorrow?
Shopping in the morning, then a lunch cruise on Lake Zurich in the afternoon,
and then, in the evening, we'll go see
the Sechseläuten opening parade.
Um, do I have to dress like this tomorrow too?
Of course!
Tomorrow, as part of the Sechseläuten opening parade,
Fleur and I will both be cosplaying as well~
Wait! I didn't hear anything about that!
Now, now, cosplay is the uniform for the Sechseläuten.
Hol—
Let's go to the aroma spa to prepare for tomorrow~!
I'm going to bed...
Hol—
Hold on!
Anyone looking at you now would take you for a girl, Ao.
Doesn't mean I have to let them hit on me!
So cute~
Hey girl, where are you from?
Is that cosplay, girl?
So cute!
Don't call me a girl!
So cuuute!
Here.
Do you know what this is? This flower's called a camellia.
La parfait charme.
It embodies the perfect charm.
Camellia... have the perfect charm.
We call these flowers tsubaki back on the island.
Tsubaki?
So they call them camellias here, huh?
Yeah.
The way camellias fall is beautiful.
The petals don't fall one by one,
but the whole blossom comes off at once.
N— um—
Well camellias... tsubaki, was it?
You had these flowers on your island too, huh?
That makes me a little happy.
Elena, here.
Your soul is mine!
...just kidding.
Elena, who are you?
Guten Morgen, Jungfrauen.
It's an honor to meet you again, Kriegsjungfrauen...
Fräuleins of Team Pied Piper.
Err...
Pardon madame, maybe you have the wrong person...
Is Pied Piper some kind of detergent or something?
Hey, Fleur, Elena, Ao.
Team Pied Piper, do you read?
You forgot to report in.
Excuse us!
After them!
Take the next right!
Next one, too!
Looks like they managed to shake her off just fine.
They're headed towards Sechseläuten park.
Let's go then!
Yes. Yes.
I'm sorry, roger that.
Making us call in every two hours...
Ah, Ao, they said you should stay
disguised as a girl until we get back to the base.
Hey, does it look clear?
It's probably...
o... kay... now?
Hi~
Leave us alone already!
They're so tenacious!
Why did it... why did it come to this?"
Ao, dash!
Yes, this is Pied Piper.
I'm sorry, yes, we're all fine.
Yes, no problems at the moment.
So close... Pied Piper... you won't get away!
Yes. Roger that.
Ao, you seem to have taken the lead.
This week's Miss GenBleu...
What's going on... dammit...
Where did those three run off to?
We might just get away with this.
What part of it?
Add some thigh-highs to that skirt and see how people peep at that...
I just knew you could pull it off even though you're a guy, ne~
I'm taking this off.
You've gotta pretend to be a girl till we get back to base.
But still, I don't think I need to wear a sailor uniform.
It totally suit you though...
That's not the issue here.
What's the current situation?
A Scub Coral has materialized at the border of Switzerland and Italy.
We've received a scramble request for Team Pied Piper.
That said...
The IFO maintenance isn't finished yet, is it?
They have temporary cockpits in place, but they can fight.
Roger.
So, how are you going to pick us up?
You've brought your cosplay up to another level...
A lot has happened...
This is bad, I seriously might fall for you~
So, what kind of Secret is it this time?
It seems HQ is still confirming the particulars, but...
What the hell is that?!
A snowman?
A black snowman?!
Ladies and gentlemen of Team Pied Piper,
we've been waiting for you.
It may seem sudden, but please take off at once.
Negotiations are complete.
That took a while.
Well, the Scub did materialize on the borderline of Switzerland and Italy.
They kept arguing about how to divide the costs.
How ridiculous.
Take care of our precious girls on their field trip.
Fleur, Elena, Ao,
get to the hangers then stand by immediately.
The Scub Coral has materialized near an inlet of the southern basin of Lake Lugano.
The airspace is above the national border
between Italy and Switzerland.
I'm sending you the data now.
Is this a new model?
We're in the middle of maintenance. You'll have to deal
with various irregularities this time, so take care.
Like this?
Of course.
I kinda feel on edge here...
It suits you well.
Georg, what's the Secret's form?
I'm currently running a comparison of this Secret's form.
At present, I have found no references to instances of similar forms.
The Secret will reach the Scub Coral in approximately 7 minutes.
The target is currently above Locarno.
What's our ETA?
Three and half minutes to target airspace.
Judging by this Secret's form, it most likely posses characteristics of the Samarkand Secret, the Australian Secrets, and perhaps some other airborne types.
Target sighted. Putting it on screen.
Alleluia, Kyrie, Nirvash. All units, launch!
Roger!
Taking off!
ZOA mapping complete.
Ao, Elena, I'm sending it over now.
Let's split up for the time being.
Roger!
Rendezvous at the Lugano point.
Roger.
Yes, I suppose so.
As you say, the affected airspace is above Switzerland,
but the combat airspace is on the Italian side of the border.
Of course we've been negotiating the price
with the Italian government as well.
Yes, of course we ca—
He looks just like her...
He's her spitting image...
You mean his mother?
Elena Musou Distance Attack!
Elena, Ao,
the target point is at the base of the Secret,
which means only attacks from below will be effective.
Fleur, I'm sending you the details now.
Ao, Elena, we don't have any time.
You'll only get one shot at this.
Ao, Elena, I'm sending the data to you.
Ao, we're counting on you.
Roger!
Ah... it was our day off as well...
What is this?
For unknown reasons, the Quartz inside this
Scub Coral was already in a damaged state.
Classification: Damaged Quartz,
in other words scrap Quartz.
Because of that, the Scub has collapsed
rather than stabilizing upon bursting.
Europe's dreams of a new Plant Coral have been shattered completely.
Moreover, even if the Secret was left to its own devices, it may not
have caused a large-scale explosion upon making contact with the Scub.
When springtime arrives at the Jungfrau, we can witness the
mysterious phenomenon of all its blue flowers blooming at once.
The fighting maidens who live here at the Jungfrau
operate their IFOs to do battle with Secrets,
otherwise known as G-Monsters.
They are the young women of Generation Bleu.
With their unique abilities, they really are a rare species of the Alps.
You could call them, too, the mysterious and unique
blue flowers that color the Jungfrau in springtime.
But the girls I saw here were more than just the IFO pilots you've come to know,
they all have the innocent, shining smiles of any normal young girl.
These flowers of the Jungfrau, and the hearts
of the young ladies of Generation Bleu,
inspire both me and many women from all around
the world to hold hope for a bright future.
Well then everyone, have a beautiful weekend.
By the way...
How long are you gonna keep dressing like a girl?
Eh—Ahhh!!
takanaru shinzou no koe wa
ta
ka
na
The sound of my heart beating fast against my chest,
ru
shin
Before I knew it it was a sound I'd gotten used to.
itsushika kokochi yoku najindeite
kaze ga tsuyoku fuiteitemo
Even when the wind is blowing strong,
me wo tsumuranaide itsudatte mae wo mukuyo
Don't avert your eyes, always face ahead.
nakitakunattara omoidashite
If you ever feel like crying, just remember,
damatte chikaiatta yukusoku wo
damatte chikaiatta yakusoku wo
da
That silent promise we once swore.
tabidatsu hinadori no uta
The song a young bird sings as it heads out on its journey,
ima mo mada umaku tobenai keredo
Even though it can't fly properly yet,
meguri meguru toki wo koe
Crossing over intertwining time,
hitasurani
The only thing we need,
tsunaida te wo tadotte
Is to follow our hands that are linked together.
Those words; "So I never let you go",
'SO I NEVER LET YOU GO' kotoba wa
Even if they should disappear into thin air,
sora ni kieteku bakari datoshitemo
Within this glimmering light,
chirabaru hikari no naka de
mayowazuni
Without any hesitation,
I know I will be able to find you.
kimi wo sagashidaseru kara