Welome home, Master.
How about another serving?
Become tasty!
Kyun pa!
I cast the magic spell to make it tasty.
Dere...
please take your time.
Hey, what are you doing, you slacker?
Hey, Idiot-Chicken!
Humph...
I will go out on a journey for a while
I will go out on a journey for a while.
Come on, wash it already.
Since this is work.
Don't tell me...
Who would've guessed that your part time job would be at a place like this?
What do you mean? It's not like I'm working here because I like it.
I see.
The pay here is nice, and I get to wear cute clothes.
Even though you're a terrible bunny, you sure have pretty girly reasons, don't you.
What is your problem? You should be thanking me!
Yes, you should appreciate me more. Not only did I let you copy my summer vacation homework, I also helped you get a part time job!
Yes, I'm very grateful for that.
However, when you called...
Yes, Ushami...
So, I know you were panicking, but were you also crying?
Uwaa...
Because...
the phone rang all of a sudden, so I was really surprised...
Surprised?
I've never received phone calls or anything like that from a friend before.
I see.
I heard my cell ring and noticed that you were calling me.
Heh, I have my own ringtone?
What is it?
That is...
I also put your image on it.
It's not something scary or anything that doesn't make sense, right?
Why would you care about trivial stuff like that?
What is that?
She's in the prime of her youth.
Hm?
It's good to be young.
Shop chief!
Well, I was a bit surprised!
The whole staff had summer fever.
They were leaving one by one, so I was stuck searching for replacements.
Then Usagi-chan said that she'd bring in a friend.
I see.
But you're her boyfriend, right?
Um, I'm not her boyfriend!
What? Really?
I was going to tease her about that...
I'm her friend.
Anyway, continue being her friend.
She's cute, so she's really popular. However, she gives off this cold feeling, so I was a little worried whether she had any friends or not.
Ah, you're free to take a break.
Boyfriend, huh?
I don't want to remain as just friends.
What did you say?
Nothing.
Konoe?
It's all right.
Pretend you didn't hear anything.
Even though she said that...
Oh, there you are. You're in charge of the floor from now on.
Go on and back up Usagi-chan. Let's go.
Geh!
Jirou-kun, you shouldn't be saying "geh" right now.
You should say, "Welcome back, Milady!"
I think that it would only be appropriate of you to do so.
Suzutsuki!
You should sit.
I reserved your presence so...
You bought it?
Yes!
Sit down.
That is why you are...
I spotted you as I was passing by the shop,
and I thought to myself, "I must go inside!"
What do you mean by, "must go inside"?
By the way, where is Konoe?
Ah, Subaru. Yeah, I just parted with her earlier.
What?!
I wanted to see Subaru like a hamster after its meal...
You really do have some guts.
Please, you're flattering me.
I can't even retaliate to that.
I texted her and said that I would be out on a journey for a while.
You really need to stop doing these horrible things to her.
You really go easy on Subaru...
Maid-san, what kind of service is provided in this shop?
Please have a look at this menu.
Hey, why do I need to be formal with you?
That is obviously because I am a customer here.
Who would become a maid for someone like you?
So cruel...
I haven't been told, "Welcome back, Milady!" yet.
Please leave, Mistress.
Don't get so upset.
You're tsundere just like the ones in text books, Usagi-chan.
This is something the shop chief put on without my permission.
I see, Usagi-chan!
Don't call me that.
Heh, then... Unagi-chan?
Not that, either!
I wonder if Konoe is alright.
Ojou-sama, where are you?
Hey, what are you doing?
You're late, let's go back.
Come on!
H-Hey wait!
This is...
Welcome back, Milady!
Welcome back, Milady?
Sorry to have made you wait, Milady.
Oh my, didn't this "Drawing Ome-Rice," come with a message?
Write "Love" on it and please draw some hearts as well.
Here.
You're not going to feed me?
You're ordering me around too much!
Here, ahh...
Oh yeah, I think I also want to add the optional, "chance to get a double picture."
Jirou-kun, will you please take the picture?
I don't mind, but I don't know if it'll turn into some scary ordeal.
Here.
I suggest you go find an exorcist.
Mind your own business.
Well now...
Are you going home?
If you make such a happy expression, it makes me want to stay more.
It is almost 3pm.
It's almost peak hours. Go home!
Well, it seems that I don't have a choice now, do I?!
Have a nice tri...
I'm late!
Oh, my glasses, this is bad!
This voice is...
Here.
Hurry up and put your glasses back on.
As I thought, it's you two!
Oh my, Nii-san!
Why are you all here?
Sakamachi Nakuru!
Ah, temporary part-timers.
Yes, we will be in your care.
Part-timers?
Hi, I'm Choco. I'm Milk. We are Yui and Kaori!
Hi, I'm Usami! I'm Masamune! I'm Usami, Masamune!
Is there a problem?
I can't believe both of you guys are going to work here as well.
We didn't think you and Onee-sama were going to be here!
There's also a butler cafe on the same street as this shop.
We're both members there!
Anyway, we heard that one of the part-timers here had taken off and that they were troubled by that.
A Butler's Cafe?
Thank you for waiting, Milady.
Take this to table three.
Then refill the lady's glass of water at the first table.
Also, the floor near the wall is dirty and needs to be cleaned.
Yes.
You're a real pro, aren't you?
Umm, may I leave now?
Not yet.
When I say it's wrong, it's wrong!
You need to at least work off the repair cost.
I understand.
Or you can pay them off with your body.
Jirou...
What? I was kidding.
Are you really a BL?
If you have the time to be joking around, hurry up and go take this!
"Fight"
Super Media Lolita Sexy Beam!
That's too naive.
Ultra Hyper Burning Kick!
First! Start again from the beginning!
It's my absolute victory!
I wouldn't be defeated if it were a real fight.
You're very strong, aren't you, Milady?
Yes, all of us maids will give air kisses for celebrating our customer's victory!
What is that?
Nakuru?
Master, please wear glasses.
Hurry up!
Yes!
Here, line up.
Ready, set,
Congratulations, master.
She's a devil!
I wonder if there are even more interesting services.
More like, how long you plan to stay here?
Because, we have Kureha and Nakuru-chan working here as well.
I have no choice but to make them my maids.
I can't put up with you any longer.
I'll go wash the plates.
This warm and soft feeling...
This is...
Are you all right?
Yes.
We already closed the shop, so rest up.
Sorry.
I wonder what happened to make you suddenly lose your consciousness.
Nothing at all.
You don't seem to have a fever...
Um, really, I'm fine so...
But you look very ill.
It's not that he's ill.
He just got excited.
What do you mean?
He has an extreme maid fetish.
Hey!
To be honest, when I visited his house last time,
I had to wear a maid outfit.
You wore it on your own!
Why did you dress up in it?
It's obvious.
It's so I can give him good service.
He wouldn't let me in, unless I was a maid.
Nii-san! So there was a deep meaning as to why Onee-sama was dressed up as a maid.
I didn't know Nii-san had a maid fetish~!
Kureha!
Nii-san is a treasure trove full of perverseness!
Nakuru will go after her.
Kureha-chan, wait!
Don't worry! Having a fetish is the first step to happiness!
So Sakamachi witnessed it too, huh?
That you made Suzutsuki Kanade dress up as a maid.
Usami...
And not only did you chain her to a bed, but you also tickled her with a feather all day!
Do I look like a guy who loves eccentric play?
What's with that awkward silence?
Be careful Usami-san.
His obsession with maids, especially their garter belts, is very extreme!
Jirou-kun, do you think the skirt has its way to suppress the true power of a garter belt?
I didn't know a garter belt held such a power!
So much power that it needs a skirt to hide its power?!
There aren't any such powers!
Now that I think about it. When I invited you to work part-time,
you agreed immediately!
I didn't know this was a maid cafe until I got here!
Even today, you were giving the maids strange looks while you were washing dishes.
Oh, I did it again.
Enjoy.
Enjoy your meal.
Oh no, glasses, glasses...
You...
I wasn't watching!
What should I do?!
I just touched this maid fetishist!
I greeted him!
I encouraged him, "Do your best."
Didn't I say that isn't true!!!
We'll have to see for ourselves.
I agree.
How much of a maid fetish do you people think I have?
So how are we going to see?
No worries, there's a way.
You just have to show him your garter belt!
What are you telling me to do all of a sudden?!
Don't you get it, Usami-san?
Right now, you are nothing but a maid. Therefore it's not embarrassing for you to act like a maid anywhere else!
If Jirou-kun can endure your temptation, then it will prove that he doesn't have a maid fetish.
I get what you're saying, but...
Temptation... which means...
All you have to do is drag your skirt up a little bit to show him your garter belt.
Huh?!
Of course, you'll have to say, "Oh, please forgive me, Master," with tears.
No matter how I think about it, it seems like such a lewd play.
You can't do it?
Aren't you Jirou's friend?
If you're his friend, you should be able to do that much for him.
Oh, could it be?
You actually like him.
You can't do something embarrassing in front of someone you like.
T-That's not true!
Oh, so you don't like him, you love him?
N-No! There's no way I'd like Idiot-Chicken!
Is that so? Then hurry up and drag your skirt up.
You don't have to show him your undies. You just have to show him the garter belt.
You just have to hold it right at that line.
Idiot-Chicken.
What?
You don't really have a maid fetish, right?
Of course I don't!
Okay fine, after all, I am your friend.
As you please, Milady.
Please forgive me, Master!
How was that, Jirou-kun?
Can you still say that you don't have a maid fetish?
Can you tell me that you hate garter belts?
This is bad. I can't take this anymore!
I love.... maid's..... garter belts....
Ojou-sama, I have been looking for you!
That took you a long time.
A lot has happened.
But I am glad you're safe, Ojou-sama.
Oh Jirou, you were here too.
Yeah...
Yeah, by coincidence.
Let's head back to the mansion.
Yes, Ojou-sama.
Konoe!
What is it?
Well, um, are you doing all right?
Same to you.
I guess I'm doing fine.
It's about what I said before.
When I said, "I don't want to be just friends."
Don't get me wrong! That wasn't a confession!
That was... Um...
Best friends.
Yes! Best friends!
It meant let's be best friends together!
Best friends...
Do you not want to?
Oh, no, it's just that I was a little surprised because it was so sudden.
Best friends sounds a bit embarrassing, but it's not bad.
Let's keep this up, best friend.
You're right, we're... best friends.
Bye!
Is something the matter?
Nothing.
Okay.
Ojou-sama, who were you on the phone with?
Kureha-chan.
I thought that I should fix the misunderstandings.
That Jirou-kun doesn't have a maid fetish.
Maid fetish?
Let's go.
Ojou-sama! What's going on?
Ojou-sama!
Aren't you glad?
After all, it was proven that you're not an extreme pervert.
Although, that was pretty embarrassing.
Thanks.
I think it was because of Masamune.
Hey, isn't this a nice song?
I think the title was, "To Forever Believe in Your Friends"
Oh really.
I guess I should change.
Phew, I guess I won't be coming to a maid cafe again after this.
Huh? What, really?
Wasn't that what we agreed on?
That it was only a one day part-time job.
That's true, but...
Come over here...
Huh?
I said come!
Come work here every once in a while.
That manager even said she doesn't have enough people to work in the kitchen.
And besides, if you do come, I'll let you keep copying my homework...
You won't mind, right? It's not a bad deal.
Oh fine, I'll come once in a while.
Yeah...
Um... Idiot-Chicken.
Hmm?
Um... well... Thank you!
I knew it was here when I heard the ringtone.
Oh, there's a ringtone for me.
You heard it, didn't you!?
Oh no, it was an accident!
Hey, don't run!
Hey! Idiot-Chicken!
Sorry!
Wait~!
Bastard, don't be wearing panties while keeping it a secret from me.
Aren't you wearing some too?
Ah!
Why of all the places am I only wearing my underwear in a convenience store?!
I t-totally don't like your underwear at all, do you understand?
There's no way my sister's panties can be this cute!
Panty flare... punch, punch, punch, punch, punch...
I worked up a good sweat, so for the time being, let's eat a delicious meal!
Next time on Mayo Chiki...
The tenth story,
Let's Eat!
Let's Eat