Hey, darling.
The girl that ran away from home, how long is she going to stay here?
Let's wait and see for the time being.
She said she's Obaa-chan's friend.
How are you feeling? Are you able to go home?
Shall I help you make a call?
Your family must be worried about you.
I'm ashamed...
I can't believe...
I've been walking a tightrope all this while.
I've always taken for granted that he'll take care of me...
I can't say that...
You can think about it after you've calmed down.
Let's go to the living room.
We have cake. Shall I pour some tea for you?
She left?
Why?
Hey... Have you gone to look for her?
I couldn't find her.
Eh? You couldn't?
Have you gone to the police?
Just forget about it.
What do you mean, forget about it?
Jin!
It's none of your business.
Hey, whatever happened to Nagi-sama?
You mean...?
Looks like she's absent again today.
Yesterday, Mikuriya was acting strange too.
Do you know what happened?
I think it's better if you ask Jin directly...
Even I  know how to read the atmosphere. That's why I'm asking you.
You're Mikuriya's guardian, right?
Guardian? That's not...
I don't really know...
I don't think you need to worry so much, do you?
Look, Nagi-san might be throwing a tantrum, just like last time.
Last time?
Oh, you mean the closet incident?
I'm sure something like that must have happened again.
She'll be back in no time.
You think so?
Well, it's concerning the two of them, so I don't think we need to butt in.
I see, they're siblings after all.
This is where we shouldn't be stepping in, eh?
"Is love a calamity?", I asked out of the blue.
"A calamity, indeed.", replied the teacher in the same serious tone.
"Why? I will know why in time to come."
"No, you already knew."
"Hasn't your heart been in motion because of love, ever since ages ago?"
I tried searching my heart.
But it was emptier than I expected.
Okay, that'll be enough.
At this point, Nou-sensei unexpectedly showed strong emotions in response to my questions.
This can be forgiven in view of Sensei's past, which will be described later.
This has nothing to do with you, right?
Mikuriya!
What's wrong?
Are you hungry or something?
I'm fine!
Don't push yourself too hard, Mikuriya.
This isn't the time to be spacing out. You have to look for Nagi-san.
I did.
Hey, what did you do to Nagi-san?
A little squabble.
That's all?
She left on her own volition.
I have no right to stop her at this point in time.
She doesn't have any reason to stay in my house too.
If she can't stand being around any longer, she'll just need to go somewhere else.
Huh? What nonsense are you saying?
Isn't it obvious that she can't come back because she doesn't want to give in to you?
She has nowhere else to go besides your house!
She said you're her family.
Normally, nobody would say such a thing!
What she meant was that you're important to her! She wants you to go after her!
She must be wanting to go home now!
Anyway, I've thought too highly of you.
So this is how little she meant to you.
Don't you think you're too unfeeling?
You actually want her to come back, don't you?
But you don't dare to face her, right?
That's why you're only running away, aren't you?!
Nagi-san said this before.
"When in doubt, act according to your intuition and emotion."
Gosh, why's this child so oblivious to his own feelings?
Jin.
What's the matter?
Jin? Everyone has posted that they've seen her.
It seems that she's walking around town now.
Really? Why does everyone...
Nagi-san's famous around here, you know.
Information will come flying in whenever she goes out.
You can't check because you don't have a computer at home, right?
Be grateful!
Thank you, Tsugumi!
Listen up. The newest info we have now is...
She claims to be a god, yet nothing is known about her...
It's a wonder how you could've lived with something like that for so long.
That's because...
That's because it's been fun!
Everyday was fun!
Nagi!
Nagi...
What do you mean, you were lying to me?
You didn't mean to lie, am I right?
You don't even understand yourself, right?
You don't know about the impurities, or why you have memory lapses!
You don't know anything, and you tried to keep it from me.
Because you don't know anything and you're afraid.
But who cares about all those?
I believe that you're a god!
Even if you can't remember, I've met you before when I was a child!
I've come so far because I hold those memories close to my heart.
I... I think I'm a god.
I think I am...
But I can't substantiate it!
My sense of self that's supporting me is lacking!
Ambiguous? Inadequate?
I don't know!
What is this... fragile sense of self?
Yet I had the cheek to maintain my pride for so long...
That's why we should look for it.
I'll be seeing you even if you go into memory lapses.
Together, we can find the answer.
Let's look for it together, Nagi!
Let's find the true cause of your uneasiness!
Here.
Wipe your nose.
I'm ashamed...
Thank goodness.
I see that you found your family.
Shige.
Oh my!
You're...
What strange fate!
I can tell you more if you wish. How about it?
That road was where the portable Shinto shrine passed through.
It's around the place where the apartments were built.
Can you remember, Kannagi-sama?
On both sides were our field.
During spring, the field of rape blossoms was a sight to behold.
I... remember...
Next to it was a field of Chinese milk vetches.
Those were hard times.
My husband went to war; my children and I were left behind.
Oh, that's right. It was I who hung myself.
I heard that my husband died in battle in the southern countries.
That made me lose myself.
I already had children, and yet...
Back then, there were many people like that.
But the land deity here could not allow anyone to throw their lives away.
I tied a rope to that tree, but the branch broke.
Even though its thickness was such that it shouldn't have.
I've always believed that you were watching over me.
I was really happy that you came for me.
I was relieved.
That has to be the second time I saw you.
The first time was when I was born.
You are the chime that signals life, and death.
I've always had the feeling that I can meet you at the entrance and exit of the stage of life.
TL-Note:
In Buddhism, 49 days is the time it takes for a soul to reborn again into a new life.
I plan to take things at my own pace for these 49 days.
See you again on the day of departure, Kannagi-sama.
Nagi, that woman...
The first family of my followers.
The god-protector, the family of Kamimori.
That was hard to understand...
You didn't understand, huh?
Jin.
Is it all right for me to call myself a god?
Shige said those things to me.
My memories are murky.
Most likely, I appeared before her when I lost my consciousness...
Such an ambiguous sense of self... I...
Everything will be fine, Nagi!
Didn't you say just now that you remembered what happened in the past?
Even I don't know much about myself yet.
But I think we just have to search and ponder.
I'm sure we'll find some hints.
Let's rack our brains together.
Okay?
I'm back.
Replaying messages.
Mikuriya! I saw the message board!
So what on earth happened between you and Nagi-sama?
You'd better tell me tomorrow!
Shino, say something too!
Don't go too far with your fights and make-ups.
Bye, Nagi-sama! See you tomorrow!
Hello, it's me.
I'll bring the videos tomorrow. Tell Nagi-san for me, okay?
I'll call again.
Why's my timing...
Well, I can just tell you in person tomorrow.
Anyway, tell Nagi-san-
Everyone was worried about you.
I'll apologize tomorrow at school.
Yup. At school.
Jin, I'm going to take a bath.
Okay...
Umm... Jin.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
What was that?
In commemoration of my CD release,
I'll hold a handshake meeting and a confession meeting.
Well then!
In commemoration of the release, I'll sing a bit of the new song!
♪ My feelings for you are crescendo ♪
Board:
Zange-chan Original CD Debut!!
♪ ride upon the dolphins ♪
♪ and reach you ♪
♪ Yes we can~ ♪
♪ Sometimes I lost my way ♪
♪ And might look at other people- ♪
I forgot to bring a second set of clothes!
I have to get my acts together!
Can I just run and take my clothes?
♪ Even if you become a beast ♪
♪ God will definitely forgive you- ♪
Cool down, cool down!
If this goes on, I can't look at Nagi in the face.
I'm sorry!
Watch out!
Ji... Jin.
Na... Nagi.
I...
I...!
Jin? I heard that Nagi-san's back!
You should've called me...
I see...
Hey! Wait, Tsugumi!
I can explain this!
Get off of me now!
What explanation? Perverted Jin!
Perverted human!
Huh? Why?
Why am I crying?
What are you doing, getting a free glimpse of me?!
I didn't see anything.
Not the crucial parts.
Say, he'll surely make fun of me if he saw these.