Nii-san, it's morning-!
Here now,
Ass!
Good morning, Nii-san!
Ankle Lock!
And up next, the Sharpshooter!
And a chain combo to a Sol Naciente!
And to finish it off, the Triangle Lancer!
Let's start over. Mornin' Nii-san!
How was I today?
As sharp as ever.
Thanks to that, I almost went right back to sleep, permanently.
I nearly got to meet Father in the gardens of paradise.
So, my skills were enough to send you to Heaven?
Anyway, breakfast is ready, so hurry up and come down!
On a fateful day, much like today, I, Sakamachi Kinjirou, discovered a very important secret.
It was just like any ordinary morning...
Tomato-infested...
With Nii-san's help, morning practice ended without a hitch!
Morning practice?!
Aren't you in the textile arts club!?
Well, our textile arts club is well-known for taking things too seriously.
Our captain can crush a concrete block with a single finger!
You've joined quite the abnormal group, and it's only the beginning of the semester.
We're also going on a trip to the mountains for Golden Week to train.
It's a three-day, two-night survival camp.
Your club's going to be the end of you.
It's still a good opportunity, because I've always wanted to fight a bear with my bare hands.
Don't even try.
Even you would die.
Oh, come on. It'll be fine.
Look at Mother; I received a letter the other day saying that she fought a tiger in India.
Don't put yourself in the same league as your mother.
She quit being human ages ago.
She became so strong that there aren't any opponents left to fight her,
which led her to embark on an overseas journey to train.
And I want to welcome her home properly; that's why I need to train so hard.
I'll be going ahead.
Hey, it's Konoe.
If you will, Ojou-sama.
Konoe Subaru.
I'm afraid that there is no one in the academy who does not recognise that name.
He is popular with the girls for no reason.
On top of that...
Thank you.
He also happens to be Suzutsuki Kanade's butler.
I'm so jealous...
I'm so jealous of him!
I want to be Suzutsuki Kanade's butler, too!
However, it's a wonder that there are still butlers in this day and age.
Huh?
And why does a high school girl need a butler?
Nope... She's no ordinary high school girl.
She's the cutest girl in school,
a lady of high-class from the Suzutsuki family,
and also the daughter of the school's director.
Having said that, why would she bring her butler to school?
Here.
Milady, would you please wait on the ground floor?
I must finish my business as well.
Sure.
Th-That's just unbelievable.
Hey, you know...
Don't tell me...
Oh, Sakamachi-kun, you got a piece of string-
As I thought...
Kurose, get it off me!
You like guys!
Not!
Because, you see...
You don't talk to the girls in our class.
You don't even try to approach them.
That's how a rumour starts.
The rumour that Sakamachi Kinjirou is a homosexual who has no interest in women.
Don't call me by my full name.
You were just watching Subaru-sama with glittering eyes, right?
I just can't keep up with him, he's shining too brightly!
We used to be so close that we'd even share our porno mags... When did you change...
I have to go to the bathroom!
Sorry-
Oh, I have an idea!
A story of love that blossoms because the glasses were blown away!
Write that down...
Boys
Safe...
My stomach hurts...
Was it the tomatoes...?
Meow!
ima mune ni umareta
今胸に生まれた
Embrace this unchanging emotion
yuruginai kono kimochi
揺ぎ無いこの気持ち
Born right now in my heart
dakishimete tobe haruka tooku
抱きしめて飛べ遥か遠く
And fly far away.
Ayako-Fansubs
presents!
game and set nante nai hibi
Game & Set なんて無い日々
In these days without an end,
imeeji shite kanaetai mirai
イメージして叶えたい未来
Imagine a future you dream of.
kazoete uchiaketattara yakusoku akiramenai
数えて打ち明けあったら　約束あきらめない
Count down, then reveal it to each other. Promise not to give up,
yume wo katachi ni suru made
夢をカタチにするまで
Until that dream materializes.
suki na koto zenryoku de oikakeyou yo
好きなこと全力で追いかけようよ
Chase after what you want with full throttle.
issho ni ne tanoshiku ne
一緒にね　楽しくね
Together, have fun,
kibou no hane hirogete
希望の羽広げて
And spread wings of hope.
ima mune ni umareta
今胸に生まれた
Let's begin,
yuruginai kono kimochi
揺ぎ無いこの気持ち
So that we can call this emotion
yuuki to yobu tame hajimeyou
勇気と呼ぶため始めよう
The one born in my heart now, courage.
Be starters
Be Starters!
Be starters!
michisuu no doa tate
未知数のドア立て
Erect countless doors,
kowagarazu akete ne
怖がらず開けてね
And open them without fear.
fly far away
Fly Far Away!
Fly far away!
maiagare kanata e to
舞い上がれ彼方へと
Soar high to infinity.
End of Earth
Konoe... Subaru?
I'm sorry...
I didn't mean to...
The lock must have been broken.
Why is Konoe wearing girls' underwear?
Does his family carry a curse that forces even the men to wear female undergarments?
No way, that's stupid.
Oh, then, I got it; you're just a pervert!
Oh no, I shouldn't really talk about someone else's fetishes.
I should be mindful of their privacy.
Everyone has their secrets.
But...
Amazing grades...
Excels in studies and sports...
Magnificent posture...
The famed Subaru-sama is a pervert...
Did you see it?
Jirou...
Sakamachi Kinjirou...
Is that your name?
If you intend to stay silent, then I will ask you again.
You saw my underwear, didn't you?
What do you mean?
I saw nothing!
You insist that you did not, yet you were looking at it so keenly!
Don't worry. I won't bite.
You saw it, didn't you?
You have engraved it deep within your mind, do you not?
You opened that door because you wanted to see my underwear.
Who the fuck would want to look at your underwear?!
I'm a grown-up; I wouldn't get excited by kiddy underwear!
I apologize that it had character prints.
That aside, how do you know what is printed on my underwear?
C-Calm down-
Shut up, pervert!
You no longer have any human rights!
How surprising.
That blow should have at least knocked you unconscious.
I am amazed that you endured that.
Due to circumstances at home, I've been taking blows like that since I was five.
I do not care about your circumstances. You leave me with no other choice.
I will have to reveal my true strength.
Huh?
You know my secret now.
Because you know it, you must be eliminated.
Do not fret.
I will only eliminate your memory, not your life.
My family has passed down a memory-erasing technique from generation to generation.
Don't tell me that's...
I am going to hit you.
I am going to keep hitting you until your memories are blown away.
That is the Butlers' Memory Erasing Technique.
I'll die!
Your method has nothing to do with butlers!
Rest assured, it will be swift.
When you regain consciousness, you will be on a hospital bed.
You will be muttering,
"Where am I?"
"Who am I?"
Understand? Everything will be resolved cleanly.
Damn it! I have no choice then!
Oh, what?
You are going to resist?
Unfortunately, I hate the feeling of pain.
So...
So...?
I'm escaping!
Wha-?!
I will not let you!
Fight me like a man!
Then I will finish you in one strike as a merciful butler!
Damn it!
Don't underestimate me!
What great determination.
I will finish you this time.
With my Butler Knuckle!
It isn't really relevant, but...
You're absolutely horrid at naming things.
Wh-What are you saying!?
Damn it, I have never been so embarrassed like this!
I will finish you off with my final, sure-kill move!
I call it, End of Earth!
That sounds humongous!
But still... Your sense of names is just...
Shut up!
I'm sorry.
My bad.
You must've put a lot of effort in to thinking that up.
Wh-What?
Do not look at me like I am pitiful.
Damn it...
I thought it was cool.
Oh shit...
He's so cute.
Don't tell me I had interests like this...
Watch out!
Huh?
Soft...?
No way...
You're a girl?!
Cat panties...
Big boys in front of the TV, let's shake hands!
I will kill you!
How dare you touch my breasts and get a nosebleed from being aroused!
You're misunderstanding!
It's just a reflex!
No excuses!
I just had an unbelievable dream.
Huh?
What is this?!
Wait, I'm not chained on this side...
W-W-W-W-
Oh, are you awake now, Sakamachi-kun?
Are the cuffs hurting you?
Do not worry, Sakamachi-kun.
Your operation went well.
You are now a cyborg.
What?!
By operation, you mean modification surgery?
You are different from normal humans now.
Try shouting, "Transform!"
Wh-at?!
I got it!
Trans-
form!
You just became a high school student and you're still shouting out crap like "transform"?!
Amazing!
Um... Suzutsuki-san, may I ask you something?
What is it, Sakamachi-kun?
Or may I call you Jirou like the other classmates do?
I don't mind either.
Thank you, Jirou-kun.
Be my guest.
So was it you who shackled me with these handcuffs?
That is correct.
Be careful.
When those come off, the magic seal on your right hand will wear off.
Why so cliché?
Putting that aside...
Next...
Why are you sleeping together with me?
Oh my, was I not supposed to?
Do not worry.
I have no intention of being raped by someone who only has his left hand free.
What kind of person do you think I am?
By the way, where did the school nurse go?
She left.
After I slapped her cheeks repeatedly with a bundle of cash.
You bribed her?!
In short, you and I are the only ones in here.
It is up to me whether you live or die.
So, what should I do?
Should I start with your ear?
Or...
Sterilisation?
Wait!
What do you want?!
Do not misunderstand me.
I am imprisoning you because you have discovered my butler's secret.
No wonder...
Do you understand?
Why is Konoe coming to school dressed as a boy?
If there's a way of putting it, it would be family reasons.
Left side: Konoe Famaily    Right side: Suzutsuki Family
Subaru's family men have served as butlers for my family for generations.
However, Subaru is a single child and has no other siblings to inherit the job.
Left: Subaru    Right: Kanade
Since she is a girl, naturally, she cannot be a butler.
But she begged my father that she wanted to be one.
However, since my father is the director of this academy, he gave her some conditions.
That is to complete three years of academy life without being discovered by anyone that she is a woman.
If she cannot fulfill something as simple as that, then a woman cannot manage as a butler of the Suzutsuki family.
That means...
Right.
Today, Subaru was discovered to be a woman by you.
That's why she tried to seal your mouth by any means necessary.
I'm sorry.
My butler had troubled you.
Konoe will...
Are you worried about her?
Well, if you wish to see her...
You can see her immediately.
H-Hey, this is-
Oh, I did it all for you.
Who ever asked for it?
I thought you'd definitely be happy.
Unfortunately I have no such strange fetishes!
Then should I remove them for you?
Of course.
Don't regret that choice.
Like hell I would!
You're being mean, Ojou-sama!
Why must you do such cruel things?!
Please take these chains off me quickly!
Otherwise, I cannot kill this pervert!
Don't be in such a rush, Subaru!
I'll be taking them off in a moment.
H-Hey!
Hang on a second!
Let me tell you this, Jirou-kun.
It was I who saved you in the science lab when you were being hit repeatedly.
It was I who also stopped Subaru's rampage.
So, do you understand your predicament a little more now?
Yes.
I understand, Suzutsuki-san.
Oh?
What did you just say?
I didn't hear it clearly.
Can you say it again?
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much for saving me, Suzutsuki-sama!
This woman is definitely an "S".
Is this is the true character of the cutest girl in the academy?
No way...
Please remove the chains, Ojou-sama!
I have to stop this guy's vital signs right now!
It's your fault for wearing a girl's underwear when you are dressed as a boy!
How can I wear male underwear! It's so disgusting!
At least cover your breasts with a chest binder.
I forgot to do so after PE class!
No thanks to you, I'm going to be fired as a butler!
What will you do now?!
I have to be Ojou-sama's butler no matter what!
It's all right, Subaru.
Why do you think I imprisoned Jirou-kun?
Of course, it's so that you won't have to quit being a butler.
Ummm...
Does that mean...
I heard from Subaru.
When your nose bled, you said something about your body reacting.
Jirou-kun, you have some special bodily reaction?
Are you going to keep silent?
I'm fine with that.
I'll hear directly from your body instead.
H-Hey!
Please be quiet.
I might accidentally injure your intestines.
Don't tell me something scary as if it's nothing!
You absolute pervert!
How dare you even get aroused by Ojou-sama and begin to get a nosebleed!
I see.
Interesting.
You have a body that nosebleeds when a girl touches you?
Huh?
Is that a form of allergic reaction?
Even if so, I've never heard of symptoms like yours.
Whatever it is, you are a chicken bastard who's too scared of having girls touch you, right?
Right?
Sakamachi Kinjirou-kun?
Sakama.. chi... Ki... n... jirou-kun?
Sakama Chicken Jirou-kun?
Chicken-kun?
Nooo!
Quit that!
Don't call me by that name!
I'm cursed!
Having such an annoying word like Chicken imprinted in my own name!
Sakama... Chicken... Jirou...
Like I told you, don't call me by my full name!
By the way, Jirou-kun...
Don't you want to cure your phobia?
That's...
If you want to, I will help you.
Huh?
In exchange, I wish you not to tell anyone that Subaru is a girl.
On pain of death.
If you keep this a secret, Father won't realise that his conditions have been broken.
That's totally fraud.
It'll be fine as long as we aren't found out.
What do you think?
Would you like to form a treaty with us?
A treaty?
More like being accomplices!
How wonderful.
I love the sound of that...
Having an interesting accomplice relationship would prevent me from getting bored.
By the way, what if I break the treaty?
I'll have to resort to taking extreme measures just like Subaru did.
In about one month, an unidentifiable corpse will be found at the root of Mt. Fuji.
I-I got it!
I'll go with your offer!
But is Konoe all right with this?
I am Kanade-ojousama's butler!
I will follow her orders.
And...
No, nothing.
So it's decided.
By the way, Jirou-kun...
What happens if you keep getting touched after you nose starts to bleed?
Huh?
I think I'll faint from being unable to resist.
Oh, really?
This is an experiment.
For future reference, I have to know your body's limits.
Quit it!
I only touched a little, but you let out such a cute voice.
H-Help me, Konoe!
I am a butler, not a magician.
I can't slip out of these chains.
Hey, don't give some response like it's funny!
Not there!
Nooo!
Nii-san, it's morning!
Get your ass out!
Breakfast is ready so hurry up and come down.
A morning just as always...
But my nightmare school days begin today.
I'll be going on ahead.
Yeah...
Then this home will be my only sanctuary.
Wha?!
Good morning.
Konoe!
Why are you using the shower?!
Your little sister suggested that I should,
since I was getting drenched by the rain in front of your house.
Rather, why are you in my house?
By Ojou-sama's orders!
I have to keep watch over you.
So that you don't reveal the secret...!
Suzutsuki...
Besides that, you've seen me naked.
Did you know? My family has passed down a memory erasing technique for generations.
Take this, pervert!
So from today, will days like this be ordinary?
koe ni dashite tanoshii tte icchattara
If you say aloud that it's fun,
声に出して楽しいって言っちゃったら
kumo hitotsu nai aozora
A cloudless blue sky,
雲ひとつ無い青空
kono mune ni hirogatteku yo
Opens wide in my heart.
この胸に広がってくよ
haato shigunaru kyuntte tatete
With heart signal on high sensitivity,
ハートシグナルきゅんって立てて
tobikonda sekai
I jumped into this world.
飛び込んだ世界
hamidashichae
Go beyond the bounds.
はみ出しちゃえ
watashi to iu kyapashitii kakuchou
Enhance the capacity that I call "myself".
私というキャパシティー拡張
tanoshii jan
It's fun.
楽しいじゃん
tomaranai supiido ni natte koishitai
I want to gain unstoppable speed and fall in love.
止まらないスピードになって恋したい
isogou futari dake no jikuu
Let's hurry into a realm only the two of us exist.
急ごう二人だけの時空
wan tuu surii tobikoete
One two three jump past.
1-2-3　飛び越えて
kimi ni aitai yo
I want to see you.
君に会いたいよ
tsukinukeru kaze ni natte todoketai
I want to become piercing wind and deliver to you.
突き抜ける風になって届けたい
mouchotto kawaiku apuroochi
Approaching you a little cuter,
もうちょっと可愛くアプローチ
haato gata no mirai ni natte
Becoming a heart-shaped future,
ハート型の未来になって
kimi ni gohoushi
I will serve you.
君にご奉仕
soba ni itai kara
Since I want to be beside you.
傍にいたいから
Hey Jirou-kun, you are free to do as you wish.
You can lick her clean after rubbing honey on her body.
You can also enjoy rope play, or even grope her.
You can even order her to scream erotically.
My brother had such fetishes?!
I'm not a pervert!
Oh, what abnormal play do you prefer?
Next episode on Mayo Chiki...
Episode Two: I fell in love!
I fell in love!