Gotcha!
Wow, it's big!
Creepy.
Let's surprise Tsugumi with this.
Done!
I pulled an all-nighter and it's finally...
Complete.
I name it... the Tree Spirit Statue!
Alright!
Oh crap, I'm running out of time!
It's so heavy!
Can't bring it along on foot, huh?
What did Daitetsu say?
I think I'm beginning to understand.
To craft out what you saw in a tree is like this...
What?
What is this... What a refined human figure.
I materialized.
What's going on here?
A vessel that's able to accept me...
I don't understand.
Oh, you must be shocked.
Poor boy. Just remain like that until you've calmed down.
Don't be afraid, don't be afraid!
Nice.
Even though it's cheap stuff.
Um...
I have a million questions to ask you...
That's my line.
Oh well, you can ask first.
I'm magnanimous. Speak.
I have a strong sense for spiritual stuff.
But this is the first time I can see one so clearly...
Are you a ghost... Um...
Are you a tree spirit?
I cannot believe it's come down to this...
You're likening me to mountain demons? Explain yourself!
I can't believe my child's notion of god has been reduced to such a state.
Fine.
Time to educate you.
In the first place, what did you take a guardian tree for?
A sacred tree?
A sacred tree is as its name goes, a tree of a god.
A vessel for the god.
A land deity had descended upon that big nagi tree.
A land deity is the guardian deity of this land.
All living things were born from that land deity.
That land deity is none other than me. A god that you can call a mother of this land.
Does a god just pop out of nowhere like that?
Now it's my turn to ask questions.
What is this vessel?
Vessel?
What I materialized from.
Look, there was a human shape like this, right?
Like this.
Oh, that was a woodcraft that I made.
It feels very comfortable.
I don't know...
Oh, isn't it because it's made out of the sacred tree?
You're telling the truth, right?!
You'll get struck by lightning if you lie!
Hey, why do you not know anything about it?
It was cut down some time ago.
This shrine is undergoing land readjustment.
I heard the deity is to be enshrined together in a nearby shrine.
A friend gave me that sacred tree,
so I made a woodcraft out of it for a district exhibition.
This place was my childhood playground. I was shocked too...
Say, haven't we met there before? In the past-
You deserve to be struck by lightning!
How... How horrendous!
I can't believe you cut down a sacred tree and made it into a woodcraft!
A dismemberment murder case!
How... how horrendous!
Now is not the time to be singing that!
I can't believe things turn out like this while I was asleep!
How horrendous local administration work is!
Asleep?
Do you still remember? In the past, you and I...
I have no memories of such things!
What do you think will happen if the guardian tree has fallen?
The land for appeasing the god will lose its guardian.
What will become of my lovely children, my followers?
This land will become insecure, and calamities will spread.
Somebody has to bring peace to this land...
How miserable!
What am I supposed to do with this puny split-spirit of a god...
Erm... a bug.
At your feet.
You saw it, you non-believer?
This is an impurity!
The things that were suppressed by the sacred tree are all coming alive!
No point making that expression.
Don't think you're able to touch this thing.
A human can't hold it in the first place, and you'll just get tainted, though not as much as me.
Ewww, dirty.
What in the name of god?!
Umm...
Do you want something to eat?
I don't have any offerings though.
I'll go buy some.
As a god...
I have no countermeasures against the impurities infesting this land...
And I even lost my dignity for being saved by a non-believer...
Even if you call yourself a god...
Didn't I kill that bug?
With a flick.
That only returned to the land. It'll reappear as a new impurity, given time.
With the exception of those who have undergone training,
normal people can't touch the impurities.
Who exactly are you?
I have a strong sense for the supernatural, maybe that's why?
I don't get it.
There are so many things that I don't understand.
Let me think for a while. Don't talk to me.
I don't like silence; can I turn on the TV?
Oh! TV, huh?
Yeah...
I want to watch!
No, wait-
This one, right?
Hey, wait a minute!
Just pass it to me!
Hmm, which one should I press?
Press~
Magical Girl Lolikko Cutie!
I won't forgive evil!
Wow, that's the TV I've heard about?
The pictures are moving.
What kind of trick is this?
You may just continue to watch.
In the name of love and justice!
Eat this! Magical Funny Stone!
It's interesting?
What an eye-opener. I'm starting to feel that this is it.
Do you have writing papers?
Writing? You mean calligraphy?
Time for revenge.
Got it!
Spare me that, really.
Sword or fire has no effect on impurities.
That being said, I'll get tainted if I touch them with my bare hands.
Woah, an outbreak of spiders. Creepy.
Spiders are creepy? Nice pun.
Exorcism is needed to cleanse the impurities.
Which means the purifying power of a god is effective against them.
But I can't summon that much power with this body.
In that case, I just have to compensate with an external option.
In short, an exorcist item!
Hey, wait-
A beautiful young girl, a land deity and a guardian deity!
I won't forgive the impurities!
The streamers on my exorcist item, gather the purifying power of the gods!
A powerful weapon that crushes the enemy!
Erm, what are you doing?
Hurry up and catch them.
Okay.
Don't move.
They disappeared.
This! This is it!
I just need to eliminate the impurities in the name of love and justice, just like that!
My name is Nagi.
I didn't tell you my name yet.
The same name as the tree. Easy to remember, right?
I'm...
Jin. Mikuriya Jin.
Jin, huh?
Jin!
What are you doing?
I'm hungry. Let's go home.
Go home... where?
I asked for a tai fish.
That's also a tai. A real tai is too expensive.
You'll get struck by lightning if you scrimp on the offerings.
Considering that in the past they would have offered fresh tai in various occasions.
Fresh offerings?
Nice pun!
What's with her?
Well, I'll make do with this for now.
I want a real tai for dinner.
This is... What is this?
This is also delicious!
Do you really have nowhere to return to?
The sacred tree has become like that.
You should understand.
Well, that doesn't fit your image...
Isn't it your fault to begin with that you made such a vessel?
It's my fault?
Are you trying to weasel out now?
Wipe away the bean paste please.
Anyhow, I need your power to cleanse the impurities, just like earlier.
Obviously it's better to stay with you.
I see...
Calamities will spread if the number of impurities increase.
In short, it's all for the sake of this land.
Just accept that fact and let me stay here.
It's time for the news.
Firstly...
Even if she appears suddenly before me and says she's a god...
Besides, living with a girl under one roof is a bit...
What am I thinking? I can't possibly be with her!
Jin.
I'm safe as long as I stay with you.
I'll be counting on you.
In any case, you can stay in this house for the time being.
I live alone anyway, but I'll need to give an explanation when my father comes home.
Okay...
Since we're living together, there are many things that we need to decide upon.
For example, the meals.
I eat anything, whether it's seafood or mountain vegetables.
I'm not talking about your food preference.
I'm talking about who should make the meals.
It can't be helped; I'll prepare the meals for now.
Oh yeah, please throw out the rubbish in exchange.
Separate the flammable, inflammable, recyclable trash, and the PET bottles...
I'll explain later.
I don't quite understand, but are you making a fool out of me?
I'm not!
Was I tricked?
And also, the laundry...
Hey, before you sleep...
A bath!
Please take a bath!
A bath feels great! I feel like I've come back to life!
Err!
Hmm? What?
What about your clothes?
Should I wash yours?
Oh, thanks!
Speaking of which, do you have another set of clothes?
Of course I don't have them.
Uh... These.
I'm back.
Oh, where did you go?
I borrowed this from your drawers.
You should take a bath too-
No! Change out of that!
Refreshing!
I'm going to take a bath, so keep still and watch TV, okay?
Don't answer the phone.
It'd be hard for me to explain the situation.
Okay, I understand.
I knew it's impossible to live together.
Hello?
Jin, it's me.
Hello!
Oh, Jin. What's wrong?
Tsugumi! What do you mean, what's wrong?
You were absent from school today, weren't you?
Today's the deadline for the district exhibition.
You caught a cold?
No, that's not it.
I'll explain it to you next time. Okay?
Something seems wrong. Are you feeling unwell?
I'm all right!
Face the other way!
Is someone else there?
No, I'm alone! Don't worry about me. Anyway, later!
I'm worried.
I told you not to answer the phone, didn't I?
Aha, so that's the phone!
I thought this is the phone.
No, that's also a phone. Anyway, you can't use this!
Jin. You'll catch a cold.
Please sleep here. I'll sleep in the living room.
But this is your room.
This room has a lock, so it's safe.
Also, don't touch the things in this room, okay?
Okay.
Well then.
Good night.
Good night, Jin.
I'm worn out.
So even gods...
...use the toilet.
Watch the next episode of Kannagi too!