I'm Aono Tsukune, 15 years old.
From this summer on,
I'll be a sparkling high school student...supposedly...
Damn it, it's an all boys school for the next three years.
I really envy mixed schools.
What are you saying?
It only takes an hour to get to school.
Isn't that alright?
There's lots of cute girls over there.
Right, Tsukune?
Oh, is that so?
Hey!
Well... you don't need to get so depressed over not being able to make the grade.
You will be able to make it by next year!
Well, see you later!
Let's go to an arcade before we head home.
Alright then.
It's about that new game, right?
Tsukune! Tsukune!
What is it, mom?
Isn't this great, Tsukune?
I happened to meet a priest today.
What a good person he is.
My...! Papa is the best!
With this, Tsukune will become a high school student this summer!
But wasn't this dropped by someone?
That's such a relief.
You won't have to repeat this year again then.
Mister.
Are you a freshman at Youkai Academy?
Yeah...
Then you should be mentally prepared.
It's a terrifying school.
Huh? You mean...
Hello, Kyou-chan?
Oh, Tsukki?
I heard from Auntie,
but are you going to Youkai Academy?
Yeah...
Since my favourite cousin is attending that school,
I did some research on it.
That school is...
Hello? Kyou-chan?
Hello?
This is like a totally different world after we entered the tunnel.
Could it be over there?
Be careful, young man.
Oh yeah, I need to call Kyou-chan back.
I still had reception before we entered the tunnel though...
This is the right way, right...?
What was that sound?
It's coming closer!
I'm a bat.
What the hell, just a bat after-
Sorry, my eyes went blurry because I'm anemic.
Cute...!
Sorry, I didn't mean to do it, sorry!
Oh no, blood is...
No... this scent...
My body is...
Scent?
The scent coming from the hair is nice...
Sorry, because I'm a...
Vampire.
Sorry, I...
My blood...
Huh? There's nothing?
Are you also from the Youkai Academy?
Y-Yeah, though I am a freshman...
That's great, I'm a freshman too!
I see...
Erm... do you hate vampires?
She's joking...right?
What's wrong with that?
Aren't vampires indivdiualistic?
So it's interesting since you bumped into me.
I'm so happy!
Then will you be my friend?
Y-Yeah...
I'm really glad...
I don't know anyone here and I was feeling worried.
Oh, I'm Akashiya Moka.
I'm Aono Tsukune.
I'm going to spend my high school days with this beautiful girl,
I think I'm extremely lucky!
Hello, everyone!
Welcome to Youkai Academy.
I'm your form room teacher, Nekonome Shizuka.
The teacher seems to be very friendly, what a good feeling.
I am sure everyone already knows this,
But this is a school for monsters!
I see, for monsters!
As of now, the world is under control of the humans.
For us, demons to survive,
we have to coexist with the humans!
Wait a minute, teacher.
For that reason, school rule number 1:
All students must be in their human form unless special situations arise.
School rule number 2:
No other students should know your true form.
Understood?
Everyone should follow it well!
Boring rules...
You are...
Komiya Saizou-kun, right?
Why don't we just eat those humans?
That's what I'd do, teacher.
Are you serious?
But you shouldn't do that.
Because the school's staffs and students from head to toe, are all monsters.
We're inside a secret barrier.
Any unsuspecting humans who enter,
will be killed on the spot.
Now that you mention it, I smelt a human scent just now...
Sorry for being a bit late!
Oh, and you are?
I'm Akashiya Moka.
This girl is so hot, don't you think she's cute?
I agree!
It's Tsukune!
We're in the same class? I'm so happy!
Hey.
What is this? A dream?
Yeah, it must be a dream after all.
There's no way that a school for monsters exists.
Sorry...!
Huh?
Geez, Tsukune.
Such great strength...
It's delicious isn't it?
Yeah...
But, if she's really a vampire...
You are Akashiya Moka, right?
Tsukune!
Can you tell me why a beautiful lady like you is hanging out with such a guy like this?
Moka-san.
Tsukune!
Wait a minute.
Don't bother with that trash, come play with me.
I'm with Tsukune now.
Tsukune!
Are you alright, Tsukune?
Yeah, somewhat.
That was scary... are you really alright, Tsukune?
Yeah, but that was quite a throw.
Is that the power of a monster?
Tsukune is weird.
It's like you're seeing a monster for the first time.
I...
That's right Tsukune, what kind of monster are you?
Oh yeah, giving out your identity is against the school rules, sorry about that.
I take back my question.
But you already revealed to me that you're a vampire.
I wasn't aware of the rule back then.
But you don't seem like one.
Only right now,
But look at this.
What... do you want me to see?
Y-You mean your breasts?!
Yes...the rosary on my chest.
Once this rosary is taken off, I'll turn into a terrifying, true vampire.
True...?
That's why this is a protective seal...
I can't even take this off myself.
It's ok,
Even if you're a little scary...
Moka-san is still Moka-san.
Thank goodness!
You're my first friend, Tsukune!
Also, one more thing... You're my first love.
First?
Until today, I've only imbibed tomato juice and blood transfusion packets, so...
Sucking real blood like that... Tsukune is...
That sweetness, fragrance... That feeling...
I cannot forget them!
I-I'm sorry!
Oh yeah! I've got to do something.
Tsukune?
That can't be real...
Even though Moka-san's so cute!
She really is different from me.
That person... She too.
Everyone is...!
This school really is...
Tsukune!
I felt that you were... acting strange, so...
I was thinking of going to a school for humans.
Humans?
Even though you're a good person Moka-san, it's impossible for me to go to this school!
You can't!
You can't go to a school for humans!
Moka-san!
I hate humans.
I went to a school for humans during junior high.
I was lonely because humans don't believe in monsters.
I was different from everyone...
It'd be better if I didn't exist!
I kept thinking about such things.
But you told me it's alright even if I am a vampire!
That's why for the first time, I didn't feel alone...
What if...
What if I am one of those humans that you hate,
Would you still accept me?
Eh?
I'm a human.
I'm a human!
I only got into this school because of some mistake!
No way...
Humans shouldn't be able to enter this school...
You really showed that expression...
Is this true, Tsukune?
Don't come near me!
You hate humans, don't you?
I... I...
I don't want to befriend monsters either!
Tsukune!!!
The bus station... Over there?
Tsukune...
Where're you off to, Moka-san?
I'm very busy.
I can't stand it anymore!
This is my real form, an orc!
No!!!
Don't tell me it's that Saizou guy?
Even if a human like me went back...
What's wrong?
Won't you transform, Moka-san?
Or are you too frightened?
It's against school rules to transform!
We're outside the school, so it's fine!
Stop it!!!
W-Wait!
Get away from Moka-san!
Tsukune!
What'd you say? You fool!
Even though I don't know what monster you are,
You're too weak!
Tsukune!!!
Hey, wait up!
I actually ended up here...
Tsukune!
I'm sorry... I'm sorry, Tsukune.
The differences between humans and monsters are just too much.
Moka-san...
I'm a vampire,
Sucking blood and harming humans.
Back in my previous school, what I had really wanted was a friend...
Being human or monster doesn't matter,
But I guess it really is impossible.
What the hell are you doing?
Move aside, Moka-san.
Tsukune?
Indeed, I am weak and worthless, but,
Human or monster, I want to be Moka-san's friend!
Quit your blabbering!
Tsukune!
Even if you're a vampire...
I still like you.
The rosary got removed...
What's with her?
She's like a totally different person!
She's not Akayashi Moka!
Moka-san...
Once this rosary gets taken off, I'll turn into a terrifying, true vampire.
Could this be a true vampire...?
It's just like the rumours say...
Those red eyes,
The silver hair,
A huge demonic aura!
So she's an S-Class Monster, a vampire?!
You are the one who awakened me from my slumber, huh?
What's wrong with my body...
It couldn't be... I'm trembling just from looking at her!
No way!
Go for it!
Who cares if it's a vampire!
You should realise your own place.
I'll be aware of it from now on.
She's completely different from the Moka-san a moment ago...
Overwhelmingly strong,
And also...
Which is the real Moka-san?
This scent...
is the same.
From Moka-san back then...
Thank goodness you're awake, Tsukune!
Are you alright?
Does it hurt anywhere?
Was that a dream just now?
This bus station,
isn't based on time, but day...
Does this bus only come once a month!?
Yep. You didn't know?
Oh no, you're bleeding!
I have to administer first aid immediately!
Dear Mom, Dad and also Kyou-chan...
Even though this can't be mailed,
I'm writing this as a memento.
This Youkai Academy that I'm attending is a little strange,
So much so that I wanted to come back immediately.
However, I've decided to continue attending for a while,
as I found a new friend.
Her name is called...
I really can't resist this scent...
Moka-san?
Forgive me, Tsukune!
Could I have entered a really dangerous academy?
You'll be fine, Tsukune!
Before that, let's kiss!
I'll be stronger next episode
Not to mention there's a succubus!
Eh, what's a succubus?
Next, A Succubus and A Vampire
and a kappuchu for you!!