So hot...
Jirou?
Konoe?
Want a drink?
I sure do!
Thank you!
But what are you doing here?
Well, you see, there's something I have to tell you.
Tell me?
Yeah...
Let's elope!
What?!
Elope?
I'm sure you're confused since this is out of the blue,
But...
I need Jirou!
Huh?
It'll be all right.
You'll just feel a little sleepy.
You...
I'm sorry, Jirou.
A butler must follow their master's orders.
So... That's what's happening...
Is it just me...
Or do you smell like meat and potatoes?
There's the faint smell of a girl too...
Let's elope!
Where am I?
Good morning, Jirou-kun.
How do you feel?
Terrible!
Thanks to a certain someone's schemes, I was forced to drink something weird!
I'm sorry.
I really didn't want to resort to such brutish methods.
Suzutsuki...
Well, I didn't mean to be so hard on you...
I was worried that you'd never wake up.
Huh?
It's the 7AM news.
7AM in the morning?!
It should have been just after lunch when I met Konoe...
Well, actually, it seems the drug worked a little bit too well...
Hahaha...
Damn you!
So, Suzutsuki-san, where am I?
I'm glad that you shift moods so easily.
This is a certain hot spring inn located at a beach.
A hot spring inn?
Yes, it's a luxurious inn with ties to my family.
And to make things more luxurious, the place has been booked all to ourselves.
So, are you surprised now?
No, not surprised, but...
Why are we here?
Well, there happens to be certain circumstances that led to this.
Huh?
I'm running away from home.
My parents told me that we should go on a trip abroad for summer vacation.
They completely ignore my will.
Oh, really.
Don't you find it evil that they chose all by themselves?
It's the once-in-a-lifetime 11th grade summer vacation.
Y-You're deciding my schedule without my consent too!
Right.
Since I thought this might be a good occasion,
I will now begin a summer camp to remedy Jirou-kun's fear of women.
What?!
Preparations are going well.
I asked Kureha-chan to get a change of clothes and other necessities.
I told her it was a trip together.
That's some nice work.
Actually, I'd like to change so could you go back to your own room?
What are you saying?
This is our room.
Huh?
Hey, Jirou-kun, wouldn't you like to know?
A-About what?
The reason why we're in the same room.
It has something to do with the pretext of this trip too.
Pretext?
Eloping.
Didn't you hear it from Subaru?
We came here to elope.
Ojou-sama, breakfast is ready.
Thank you, Subaru.
We're going to go to the beach today.
We should eat well before doing so, right?
Y-Yeah...
Jirou?
W-Weren't you just trying to kiss Ojou-sama?!
Calm down, there's no way that would happen!
But you had your faces so close...
That was just Suzutsuki fooling around!
And there's no way I'd kiss her so easily!
Th-That's right.
Hey, we should have breakfast too...
Yeah...
Oh my, Sakamachi-sama.
Thank you so much for visiting our inn.
Oh no, I just-
But it sure must be tough for you.
Kanade-sama and Sakamachi-sama...
After vowing to marry each other, people were against the marriage and now you're eloping...
What?!
But don't worry.
We are on your side.
Hey Konoe, why is this trip an elopement?
Huh?
You haven't heard from Ojou-sama?
No.
I heard she had a fight with her parents and is running away from home.
Huh?
Jeez.
You and Suzutsuki always toy around with me like this and never explain anything to me.
Look who's talking?
You're hiding something from me too!
What are you talking about?
Hey...
How else could I have done it?
If I told them it was me just running away from home, they would contact the family.
And I might be taken back again.
That doesn't mean you can...
O-Ojou-sama...
I was wondering why you were so late.
Now don't be so shy.
J-Jirou, how is it?
Ojou-sama chose this swimsuit for me.
I-I don't think it's bad.
Th-Thank you!
J-Jirou?
W-Well then, shall we swim?
Before we do that, we'll be starting the long-awaited recovery program!
Can I ask you to apply sunblock on me?
Oh no, so quick and rough...
It's just your fingers-
I'm sure you're doing that on purpose.
You finished already?
The "Guess what letter was written on your back" game?
Y-Yeah, I'm finished!
More like my life would be finished if my nose bleeds here.
Jirou-kun, you really did write some erotic words on my back, though.
No, Jirou-kun, no more!
Like that.
I never wrote that!
Between smashing watermelons and playing in the sand,
which would Jirou want to experience?
Smashing watermelons and playing in the sand.
No, I don't want to do either...
I'll go buy some drinks!
Oh-
Ojou-sama, you didn't tell him about it?
Nope, it's a secret between us.
It sure seems to be popular.
Are you seriously saying that all the attendants are wearing swimsuits?
Yeah, they seem to be pretty attractive, too.
That's a cheap way of earning money.
Sorry!
Oh no, I have to wash this.
Welcome.
Huh?
You have a nice body that glasses would suit!
Glasses prevent all diseases!
Your body weight decreases and height increases!
Muscular body, you are coming here!
Don't tell me you're from the Watch Over Group-
Now you should wear glasses too!
What the hell are you doing, Nakuru?!
Idiot Chicken?
What are you doing here?
Oh my, Nii-san?
What?!
I'm leaving you, fool!
Nagare here.
What does 'tehe-pero' mean?
Thank you for the meal, Sakamachi-senpai.
The three of you are working here part-time?
What choice do we have?
We had nothing to eat since morning.
Weren't you all supposed to be at summer camp?
Well, you see...
We were supposed to swim to the camp location at an uninhabited island.
Sempais
We were separated from the others on the way.
Pink: 'Sempais' - Green: 'Those three'
And that's how we ended up here.
Since the club president is taking care of our luggage,
we have nothing with us.
It's a good thing that you were here.
So this was where the trip with Onee-sama was.
Did you have an older sister of any sort?
Oh, no, it's-
That's not it.
By Onee-sama, I meant my brother's classmate, Suzutsuki-senpai.
What?
How is that?
Why are you travelling with that Suzutsuki Kanade?
Well, you see, that's...
Sorry, hold on for a second...
It seems to be Subaru-sama.
What's the matter, Konoe?
'What's the matter', you ask?
Isn't it taking a bit too long for just buying drinks?
No, well, things happened and...
Well, it's fine.
I'll be going over there soon.
Don't come!
What do you mean by that?
It doesn't matter, you can't come!
You tell me that, but...
Why?
I've already arrived.
I'm going to go pick them up!
Konoe, put these on, right now!
These?
You mean these glasses?
I beg you, it's for your own sake!
Hurry!
It's fine, but...
Could it be that you like these?
Oh, come on!
Nii-san, what are you doing?
Jeez, you shouldn't go running inside the place suddenly-
Oh?
K-Konoe-senpai?!
W-Why are you dressed like that?
What are you saying, Kureha-chan?
This is a girl no matter how you look at her!
What?!
But...
This is Subaru's cousin.
Subaru's mother's house happens to be close by.
Subaru should be coming here soon too.
Konoe-senpai is coming?
Let me introduce you now.
This is Subaru's cousin, Takanashi Punyuru.
Huh?
Huh?!
How is it?
Isn't it a cute, modern name?
Hey, that's really unconvincing; no matter how you put it.
Oh, so you're Punyuru-san.
It's a really cute name.
She believed it...
Kureha-chan, Punyuru is a 10th grader just like you.
You don't need to be so formal.
Huh?
By the way, she would call me Kana-oneechan out of friendliness.
What's wrong, Punyuru?
Call me Kana-oneechan like you always would. Now, can you say it?
K-K-Kana-oneechan...
I may have created a terrible monster!
Oh my, those glasses are...
Oh, she said she lost hers at sea so I let her borrow yours.
Excellent!
Huh?
That one is very stylish, and I was trying to find someone suited to become its owner.
This must be how you caught Narunaru's eyes.
Oh Kureha-chan.
So funny.
Bakachiki, why would you make such a stupid lie?
Oh well that's...
I'm a little shocked.
What about?
I'm not one to judge other people's hobbies but...
I never imagined Subaru-sama's cross-dressing hobby went that far...
Lucky!
She misunderstood things in a convenient way.
But he's amazing.
Honestly, he undoubtedly looks like a girl.
And he's very cute.
Do you still think of Konoe as...
No.
I've finished thinking about that.
But it makes me nervous to be with him.
By the way, eavesdropping is a nice hobby of yours isn't it!
Good evening, Usami-san.
It must be great coincidence for us to meet at such a place.
Why are you travelling with Bakachiki?
Suzutsuki Kanade!
We are friends, Jirou-kun and I.
It's natural to travel.
It's not natural at all!
H-Hey!
That's too bad.
I'll tell you the truth.
What?
He is my fiancé!
N-No way!
What are you saying, all of a sudden?
It's not a lie.
We are right in the middle of an elopement now.
Elopement?!
By the way, we sleep in the same room at the inn.
In the same room?!
D-Don't tell me...
Of course we slept together last night.
N-No, that was...
A lie.
A lie?
Are you saying I'm lying?
Suzutsuki Kanade, I trust nothing about you!
And I've always been feeling...
That your words seem filled with lies!
Your nonsense will not work against me!
It seems like you might be a little trouble to deal with.
So you were fibbing the entire time as I thought!
So you had no confidence?
Of course I did!
It's normal to trust Bakachiki, my friend!
Masamune...?
That's right.
We are quite close friends!
I treated Bakachiki to meat and potatoes too!
And that was at my house!
Oh?
That's something new.
That's...
That's not it!
It was Bakachiki who I first showed this swimsuit to!
After that, we put ourselves together and...
Hey don't say things that would cause misunderstanding-
I'm sorry.
I'll reword it.
Err... We rubbed our bodies together...
It got even worst!
The scent of Nikujaga and girls...
H-Hey!
Bakachiki?
Usami-san?
W-What?!
Where are you going to stay tonight?
I'm telling you to wait!
So you were dating Usami all along.
Huh?
I'm not mad or anything.
Hey-
I should be congratulating you as a friend instead.
You don't have to mind me, so just go to her side.
What misunderstanding do you have?
But you were at Usami's house...
I didn't really want to tell you about this...
Sure, I went to her place.
Since it was a promise that she was going to treat me to her cooking.
It's delicious!
Oh really?
Then praise me more!
Yes, it's really delicious!
The flavoring is marvelous, and the meat and onion are so soft they seem to melt on my tongue.
And even more, the firmness of the Shirataki is a good contrast.
That must have been delicious.
That was definitely unexpected.
But you see, it only was well up to that point.
Huh?
It was delicious.
So then should we now...
Begin...
Begin what?
W-What are you doing?!
Don't put your eyes off me!
You fell for it, Bakachiki!
Unfortunately, I'm wearing swimsuits underneath.
Well then, let's begin treatment.
Huh?
Try hard to bear with it.
Hey, stop it!
It's so tough.
Keep still, will you?
I can't take it anymore!
Hey Bakachiki!
It's coming out!
I'm having a nosebleed!
And as I was coming home from that, you spiked my drink-
Jirou, that's too sexual!
That's why I didn't want to tell you.
So Usami's not...
Nothing at all.
I see.
Huh?
I-I'm begging you, Kanade-sama, pyon.
Please let me stay at the inn, pyon.
What are you doing...?
Bakachiki?!
I thought I should let Usami-san sleep at the inn too.
Then she insisted on doing this cute begging pose herself.
Y-You were the one who ordered me!
You two should sleep over too.
The more the merrier.
Yay!
Why aren't you making them do anything?!
It's going to be a joyful night tonight.
Listen to what people are saying!
Unfortunately, the fun run away is over now.
I've come to pick you up.
Kanade-ojousama.
Hey, do you know who he is?
No, he's a complete stranger.
You might not know him since you haven't seen him much.
This is Konoe Nagare, Subaru's father.
Oh, really?
What are you saying, Subaru?
Hey, Daddy's here.
He's scary, Kana-oneechan!
A stranger is trying to rape me!
Nagare, would you calm down?
Punyuru is afraid!
Punyuru?!
Who the hell is that?
Kana-oneechan, this person is disgusting!
Subaru, I'm begging you to help me persuade Ojou-sama to return home.
I'm not Subaru!
Hey, how long are you going to go with-
Leave me alone!
Or else, I'm going to call the police.
Will I be able to do it properly?
No doubt.
It'll hurt, right?
Maybe a bit.
But this is how it usually is, right?
Of course.
But I'm scared.
I am very sensitive and-
Don't worry.
Relax-
Jirou, it hurts!
Blood, lots of blood...
It's a blood donation, so that's natural!
Next episode on Mayo Chiki,
Episode 8,
It's my first time
It's my first time.