Did you wait long?
No, I just came too.
Moka-san...
You're really early, there's still thirty minutes till the arranged meeting time.
C-Cute.
Moka-san looks cute in casual clothes too!
Is it weird...?
It really fits you!
Really?
I'm glad.
It's finally summer vacation, right, Tsukune?
I'm really looking forward to the trip.
Looking forward...
To be honest, I was really surprised.
I didn't expect things to turn out like this.
A retreat?!
Yup! This year, the newspaper club will have its summer retreat in the human world!
Are you sure?! With the amount of people we have...
It's fine, if I'm with you guys...
...Maybe.
Maybe?!
Going with Moka-san and the others to the human world...
This is so sudden, is it all right to be happy about this? I don't really know.
I'm very nervous.
I said it before, right?
That I was living in the human world until junior high, and I've always hated humans.
Don't tell me... Going back to the human world makes you feel...
To tell you the truth, I'm still a bit anxious after recalling some memories.
But I'll be fine!
If I'm with you, my anticipation will overcome the anxiety!
Moka-san...
I'll be counting on you, Tsukune.
Moka-san.
Tsukune.
Gosh... hurry up!
Wait for me!
What were you guys doing just now?
They're only early in such situations.
Unprepared rivals indeed.
Everyone!
This is the first time that the newspaper club is going to the human world for a retreat!
Let's get excited and have fun!
Yes!
Where's Gin-senpai?
His remedial lessons aren't over yet.
I wonder how many red marks he got.
Damn it, wait for me everyone! I'll be there in a jiffy!
But I don't think Kurumu-san should be talking about others.
Don't worry about me, I finished all my lessons on time!
Or rather you skipped class on time, right?
Uh oh...
Yahoohoo.
The human world... once we pass this...
I... I...
I'm back!
You look happy, Tsukune.
Even saying "I'm Back!", like you were a human.
It's because Tsukune stayed in the human world for a while...
Right, right, Tsukune?
I guess it was nostalgia...
Is that what it is?
Hey Tsukune-san,
Aren't you afraid of the human world?
Not at all.
Youkai Academy is much more frightening.
Tsukune-san is so amazing!
R-Really?
Yeah!
Are you all right?
A lot of sand got into my swimsuit...
Sorry.
Oh, so that's what it was.
For a moment there, I thought Tsukune might be a human.
What are you saying, Kurumu-san?
That's impossible, right?
Geez.
Hey,
Let's drop this topic and have fun since it's summer vacation now.
Here, Yukari-chan!
Just as Moka-san said!
Yeah!
Kurumu-san!
Sorry, you're so small that I didn't notice.
Let's have a showdown then!
A lady accepts all challenges.
That's just what I wanted!
Nice toss, Tsukune!
Everyone... Get along!
Yukari-chan!
Yes!
Take this!
Yukari-chan...!
Don't do that...
You can't use magic in the human world.
I overdid it.
Miss...?
Those are raw.
I like them raw.
The sea... is really beautiful.
Tsukune!
Tsukune-san!
What are you doing over there? Come over!
Moka-san, let's go.
Sorry, I...
I should be apologizing instead, Moka-san.
Even though I knew that vampires can't go into water.
For more details, refer to Episode 5.
Go and swim, Tsukune.
But...
Go on, hurry! Kurumu-chan and the others are waiting for you.
No! If you're staying here, then I will too!
Don't mind me.
Since we're at the beach, you should have a lot of fun.
If you're not around, I can't enjoy myself!
Tsukune...
Are you really all right with that?
Wait a minute!
Moka!
You were about to suck Tsukune's blood just now, weren't you?!
You were, right?
Mo-Moka-san...
But it's because Tsukune smells so good. Teehee!
Don't "teehee" me!
What'll happen if Tsukune faints in the human world?
If that's the case, then I'll take care of him!
No, I will.
Of course, me too!
W-Wait a minute there, everyone.
Umm... me too...
You're the main cause of the problem!
What is that?
What a nice sunflower field!
Are these for sightseeing?
There's no one here.
You're right...
It's such a beautiful place... I wonder why.
Huh?
Oh no, we came all the way here, let's go back now.
There's no need to hurry, right?
Don't tell me you haven't heard of the rumors?
There's been a lot of disappearances occurring on this hill.
Disappearing incidents in a place like this?
Which is why it sends shivers down my spine!
The townspeople think that it's the work of witches.
Rumors say that due to the development plans for this hill,
the witches were angered and caused the disappearances.
Are you serious?
Let's hurry up and leave!
They call this place the "Witches' Hill".
Legend has it that witches live here!
Is that so? You really know quite a bit.
Which site wrote that?
This legend is pretty famous in this area!
Your race is the kind that abducts humans?
Blindly believing those rumors...
I guess Kurumu-san really is a fool!
I really hate witches that aren't cute at all.
Me too! I hate perverted and shameless succubi like you!
What the hell? You're just an immature brat.
Hey you! What are you doing all of a sudden?!
Just dropping a basin on you.
I didn't ask about that!
Now now... you guys...
That type of attitude!
Seriously...
Come on, let's go back to the beach.
Sensei is waiting for us there...
That child...
There's no mistaking it.
I must report this back to Master.
Guys, I'll leave the rest to you, all right?
I'll go get some food.
Food? We have a lot here...
Uh uh uh!
When we come to the beach, we definitely need to have some fresh fish!
Fish from the human world are really delicious!
Sensei, could it be that you decided to have a retreat in the human world because of this?
A-Anyway, see you later!
S-Sensei! Your tail, your tail!
Yes, Master. I understand.
I'll definitely make that small witch become one of us.
No, not like that!
It seems strange, somehow...
Oh well, we can't help it...
All right!
Let me lend you a hand too!
Thanks!
But it's a bit too heavy for you...
I'll be fine carrying it.
Let me hold one side for you.
Oh, thanks.
Moka-san, let me help you!
Thanks, but I'll be fine.
It'd be bad if you cut yourself accidently with the knife.
You can watch us from over there.
Excuse me...
A kid will only be in the way.
Everyone treats me like a child.
But I can already do things by myself!
Witches' Hill.
Are there really witches...
...that are like me?
Don't show such a scary expression, little witch.
I'm Ruby, a witch that lives on this hilltop.
Witch?
That's right, I'm your fellow witch, Yukari-chan.
Why do you know my name?
Haven't you been here during the day?
Ever since then, I've been observing you.
Because I never thought that I'd meet another witch right here,
I was very glad.
Yukari-chan, I want to be your friend.
Can't I?
Not that you can't...
Then it's okay, right?
I'm so happy!
Ruby-san...
Since we're both witches, let's get along well!
Now we have more people!
The fish in the human world really do smell great!
Sensei, your tail!
N-No... I only wanted to count them, really!
Where's Yukari-chan?
Pretty, isn't it?
The humans wish to destroy such a beautiful hill.
I heard that there were plans to develop this area.
Yes, that's why I will destroy the humans!
You'll help me, right, Yukari-chan?
B-But... All of a sudden...
It's alright. I've already finished the preparations.
What's left is to execute the Master's plan.
Master...
Come along, let me introduce you to the Master!
Let us live together at Witches' Hill forever from now.
T-Thats...
Hey!
Yukari-chan! Thank goodness...
I was worried when you suddenly disappeared.
I'm sorry.
Oh, who's that?
Her?
Do you still plan on desecrating our hill? Human!
Ruby-san!
What's that!?
These guys are a swarm of magical plant monsters that will ambush or devour humans.
Ruby-san, you're mistaken!
Tsukune-san isn't a human that's here to desecrate this hill!
Stand down, Yukari-chan!
Tsukune-san is my friend!
Devour him!
Yukari-chan, don't get in my way!
I won't let you do this!
Why not?
Tsukune-san is my friend!
He's not even a witch!
But... He's my precious friend!
That's why I definitely won't let you do such things to him!
Yukari-chan...
Friends?
I don't understand.
I don't accept this! Nothing in this world can compare to the strength of bonds between witches.
If there is something, then let me eliminate it!
Tsukune-san!
Could it be...
that the people who disappeared were all...
I can't... My powers are drained!
You're just an immature brat.
I can do it too.
I'm not just a child anymore!
This week's winner has been decided!
Hey, Moka-san didn't transform this time...
What is this?!
Monsters?
Yukari-chan defeated them all by herself?
Yukari-chan!
Hey, get a grip!
I'm all right... just a little exhaused, that's all...
You idiot! Why are you so reckless?
Kurumu-san...?
The scolding can wait.
Let's bring her back to the tent first.
Climb on...
Ruby-san.
I can't be together with you.
That's because I have friends that are important to me...
I'm sorry.
Wait up! Didn't I say not to exert yourself and let me carry you?
I'm fine!
A witch's self-regeneration is very powerful.
Geez!
You're not honest with yourself at all!
Who's the one not being honest?
Yukari-chan looks like she's fine now.
It's great that you're both okay.
After you left to find her, you didn't come back either...
I was worried that something happened to you two...
I...
Moka-san.
Tsukune.
Ever since summer vacation started, we're finally alone...
T-Tsukune...
I must bring Yukari-chan back no matter what.
That's because it's my...
and also my Master's wish!
Tsukune...
No...
No!!!
Moka-san! Tsukune-san!
You dare... You dare do that to Tsukune!
I made shaved ice for you guys.
It's cold and my head is freezing!
Brain freeze!
This isn't the time for that!
Next week's situation will be more serious!
Next week, Sunflower and A Vampire,
and a kapucchu for you!