School... huh?
Where are you going?
To school.
A place for studying?
That's right. Other than Saturdays, I go almost every day.
Don't follow me, okay?
Tsk.
What's with that tongue clicking?
I'm bored.
Watch TV then.
I'll be going then.
An era where only studying is required of children?
This has become a fine country.
Tsugumi!
Oh, Jin!
Good morning!
How is Nagi-san? Is she all right?
Well, so-so.
She's at home now?
What about school?
I'll think about it after I get in touch with my old man.
Thanks for the side dishes.
I'll return the tupperware at school.
Okay.
How was it?
Which ones were delicious?
All of them were delicious... Especially...
The fried vegetables were delicious.
Yeah.
Oh, I see...
That color is no good.
The harmony is all messed up.
You've lost your sense of direction.
What exactly are you trying to portray?
When your design is slipshod, using eccentric colors isn't going to help.
I've already said you're not up to oil painting yet.
Mikuriya, this is still beyond your ability.
What a waste of time, taking out so many painting equipments.
Your palette is full of paint too.
I know!
I know I suck, okay?
But I...
I understand.
You just want to imitate him, don't you?
It's completed!
The rookie of the Arts Club, Daitetsu-kun has finished his oil painting!
Amazing! To finish a painting with only a palette knife, that's so cool!
A person with a large-build sure has a bold style!
But there's a calculated beauty even beneath the boldness!
That pink highlight is effective.
Sense is needed to use pink effectively.
Jin...
How's the sculpture?
I'm sorry. It was somewhat completed, but I broke it by accident.
I'm sorry you had to carry the tree for me...
I see.
I want to lend you this.
It's... very cute...
Whenever I think about it,
I... I...
Shut up!
I'm trying to work here, so shut up!
Now the focus line I've drawn is off!
Oh my, Akiba-kun. You're here?
I am. I've been here all along.
You were so quiet, I didn't notice you.
So... How's your comic coming along?
Don't change the topic.
Well... it's moving steadily.
Your work's still as good.
Thank you for your compliment.
Which magazine are you submitting to this time?
Monthly Issue Dejavu.
Oh, you mean that magazine full of comics that I thought I've seen before.
But this comic sure gives the feeling of "What exactly is going on?"
The motive of the war is unclear, isn't it?
The world-view is influenced by existing works. There's no originality.
Are you some examiner from a comic school?!
Why did you come to the Arts Club anyway?
If you want to draw comics, you should've gone to the Comics Club.
Comics Club?
Don't group me with the likes of them!
They talk about anime wherever they go, and they even don't care about their attire!
In any case, from what I've seen from their doujinshi, they're hardly active at all!
So you have no interest in anime and such, right?
Like Lolikko Cutie.
No, That's actually a magical girl show that's entirely different from other anime.
Especially in that episode with the collaboration of Director Yajima and Hashida-san,
the quality is comparable to a movie's, and the direction is targeted at adults.
Only that episode is sold well on DVD, the related merchandise is also highly appraised.
I'm sorry.
What do you think, Shino?
I think it's great.
Considering the Arts Club tends to have few male members...
our first-year students this year can be called a good harvest.
A hulk of an artist.
Too-pure-pure-boy.
A self-conscious Akiba-freak.
Don't you think it's a terrific balance?
If this is an RPG, they can form a party and fight a boss!
Takako, which boy do you prefer?
Let's see... it's hard to rule out any of them.
But if I have to choose...
Too-pure-pure boy.
Both Akiba and Daitetsu are amazing.
I can't create a piece of art on my own.
Jin, you're also trying your best.
I entered the Arts Club because I look up to you.
I may be hopeless now...
But someday I will surpass you!
This... This is it!
Friendship and rivalry! Too-pure-pure-boy!
Takako, your nosebleed.
Well then, a boss fight?
Yeah, as they say, youngsters need a trial.
Tidy the storehouse?
Right. In the northwest of the school compounds, there's an old building for hobby groups.
The basement there is used as a storehouse for the Arts Club.
It's been deserted for years, so I'd like to tidy it up before I step down.
Fortunately, we have male helpers this year.
Old building for hobby groups... you don't mean that one, do you?
Oh sheesh, you know already.
What do you mean, that?
This...
I'll pass! Definitely a pass!
Oh? Mikuriya, you're afraid of ghosts?
No, it's actually the opposite.
He's really good with ghosts.
I don't want to go!
It's not like I can do anything even if I can see them!
We keep going to temples and such during field trips, right?
It's not fun at all! It's not fun at all!
Something amazing will happen if you tell him ghost stories.
It's no joke.
Oh my.
I never thought we'd have this kind of talent.
I've always wanted to ask you something, Jin.
What will happen if a ghost meets a netted door?
Netted door?
Can it pass through?
Wow...
Wonderful.
This is the first time I'm seeing it up close.
I usually won't come here.
I can't look straight and walk. Somebody, guide me.
Why are you bringing me along?
Anyway, let's go inside first.
Today we'll just look around.
If we don't see what's inside, we won't know how many helpers we'll need.
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry.
I was born like this.
Jin... It's hard to walk.
I'm really sorry.
Akiba-kun, you look relaxed.
I don't believe in ghosts.
This place's got the atmosphere. A single naked light bulb?
Alright, let's move those obstructions so that we can carry stuff easily.
Daitetsu, your back is so big.
What did you come here for?
Look, this is just a musty storehouse.
The ghost thing is just a rumor.
Is it okay?
There's even a storage under the floor.
This will take more work than expected.
You know...
I heard this from Senpai just now...
It's true that there was an accident here.
It's real. A student fell down from a ladder and died.
There happened to be a sharp pole right below.
He was impaled, but he remained conscious for a short while.
He cried for help, but nobody came.
Around him, a sea of blood.
In the meantime, he bled until he lost all his strength...
But that student has not realized that he's dead...
Even now, you can still hear him calling for help...
Liar! You see, there's no ladder around here!
But...
Isn't the ladder here?
So, have you tidied up the place?
But I'm telling the truth!
I really heard something!
You're so useless. You should find the cause of that.
Are you a beast?!
Let's look at this shop's specialty: the crab ice-cream!
Its sale is limited to fifty per day, so it'll be sold out in a jiffy!
Could that be an impurity?
Should I tell Nagi?
What do I do? Because if I tell her...
I want to go to the school too!
She'll definitely say that!
What's the matter, Jin?
You look down.
What?
Nothing!
Are you troubled over something?
No, it's really nothing.
This worry has nothing to do with you at all.
Is that so?
I tried doing it one more time, but it still stinks.
Can I hold an impurity in my hand and bring it home?
How about putting it in a bottle... That won't work.
But I still can't be sure it was caused by an impurity...
Mikuriya!
Sorry. My emotions got the better of me.
What kind of monster are you?
You're not satisfied with a pretty childhood friend?
Huh?
I'm convinced now.
If this world is a comic, you are the main character.
Shall I carry your bag for you?
Thanks, but it's all right.
That side is the courtyard, and if you go this way, there's a stadium.
This is such a lively place.
She's such a beauty!
Her head is so small! Her legs are long! Her hair is so silky!
Do we have such a beauty in our school?
Isn't she a transfer student?
At this time of semester?
Jin-kun!
He dodged!
He dodged the hug!
Isn't he the guy that Nagi-san was looking for?
You're so mean, Jin-kun!
Why?
Don't "why" me. In any case, your character is gross, so stop it.
Did he just say gross?
This guy is impossible.
He has two ahoge, so he's an idiot.
In English, Aho-Aho-Man, huh?
He may be a homo.
Excuse me, but I'm her relative.
It's not like what you're thinking. Sorry, I'm really sorry!
What are you doing, Nagi-san?
Tell me, what do you mean I'm gross?
Why the hell did you come to school?!
Why? Hah, you have the cheek to ask.
I know you're hiding something from me.
How did you know...
Huh? So it's true?
Huh? You tricked me?
I heard from Tsugumi that there's a commotion concerning ghosts.
I hope I guessed wrong...
But...
you saw an impurity, didn't you?
Yes, I saw it.
As I thought.
My eyes never err.
I sense the presence of an impurity here.
They appear easily at a place with many people.
So you're here.
Tsugumi!
Nagi-san, I told you not to wander around on your own!
I'm sorry, I'm a curious person.
It'd be troublesome if people find out you're an outsider.
You already stand out without doing anything.
Tsugumi, are you the one who brought her along?
Because when I was going home...
I found Nagi-san clinging onto the school gates.
Nagi-san told me she always had a private tutor,
so she has never gone to school bofore.
I won't stand out if I enter the school in school uniform, right?
That's what she said...
So we went home and I lent her a set of uniform.
You did something daring.
But you have spares?
Our school is a private school, so the uniforms are expensive.
Oh, yeah! That's because girls are concerned about uniforms.
I can't tell him that I got fatter during the spring break and the size doesn't fit anymore, so I bought another set!
On top of that, that size fits Nagi-san perfectly!
I can't bring myself to say it!
That's how it is.
Tsugumi-san is such a gentle and kind person!
We're now really close!
Right, Tsugumi-san?
Yes, we became good friends.
I was wrong about you. You're more easygoing than I thought.
I don't think you should call her easygoing.
She's just selfish.
Hey, Mikuriya.
Are you done with the talking?
Can we join in?
So who is that person?
This girl is my half-sibling, born from a different mother.
She ran away from home and now she's staying at my house.
Say...
Nagi-san.
There's something I'd like to ask you.
Yes?
Even though Jin and you are siblings, you hadn't met each other until recently, right?
You've both reached that age, anyway.
Living under the same roof would mean...
Nagi-san, you...
How do you feel about that?
What's going on?!
No, I just think you're so cute.
Jin-kun is just a child to me.
We live together, that's all.
We are family.
That's why there's nothing for you to be worried about.
That's not what I meant...
There's no way we can be in a relationship.
You're an important person to Jin-kun.
Besides,
I have somebody that I like.
Who would have thought you have such a complex situation in your family.
But don't worry about it, Mikuriya.
This kind of situation turns up often in comics!
Comic, huh?
That one, right?
But you're not a student, and you're a girl, right?
You don't have to go to a place with ghosts...
I like supernatural phenomenon.
Fanatic?
I do have some exorcism skills myself.
I knew it, living in an enclosed environment makes one twisted.
Don't worry, Mikuriya.
There are precedents of wealthy girls with a fetish for the supernatural.
In a girl game.
You're talking about a girl game?!
I see.
She put her purification staff in there.
You! You took that from my drawer without asking!
Yes? You mean this bag?
I told you not to open my drawers without my permission!
Why?
No real reason...
As long as you think nothing of it...
Yeah, I thought nothing of it.
Although I did think that you like big boobs.
So you saw everything!
Don't say that! Tsugumi is here!
But I heard this is natural for a healthy male,
so you don't need to feel bothered-
Enough!
Well then,
let's charge in!
Let's go!
Jin, that's...
I'm sorry, even I can't give you a proper answer.
Ah... Isn't that stick from the anime series that got scrapped in the planning stage,
and only its goods are sold by the sponsor's toy company?
There's a craze over it and they're sold over the net at high prices.
What's wrong, Akiba? Your eyes changed color.
Hey...
The air is certainly stagnant.
If there's an impurity here, then...
Nagi.
The place with the ghost...
It's here, right?
Let's open it now.
Let's stop!
No, let's go back instead!
You may get cursed! I feel bad for the ghosts!
As a matter of fact... I've reached the limit of my endurance.
Daitetsu-kun has gone mad from fear and he's crushing Jin!
You're so loud. Stop that ruckus!
You people are humans, aren't you? You're the living.
You have a future, you are the best,
there's no reason for you to lose to creatures that move because they're bound to their past!
Her way of speaking...
She has taken on that personality.
The living is stronger than the dead!
Remember that!
Huh? No way! What's that? Why?
I can't open it! I can't open it!
It's coming. It seems we've agitated it.
It's angry!
It's certainly calling for help.
Poor thing... It was always alone.
He was in such a dark place, hurting and afraid.
And yet nobody could find him.
He can't open that door for sure.
Because he was caught in the maze of dying without being able to open the door.
I shall destroy that maze.
Oh sheesh...
This door is poorly built, really.
This is dangerous. I should tell the school janitor to fix it.
Who's this old man?!
Old man? You're so rude.
Who's that person?
Homeless?
Yay, yay! Gotcha!
If we don't do this, I don't feel like we're welcoming the new members at all.
This sort of thing happens often in sport clubs, right?
This is what they call a baptism.
Let me introduce him.
This is our Arts Club's advisor, Dokusasori-sensei.
He's using the place under the floor as his studio.
You guys don't learn your lesson, doing this every year.
Well, I don't mind since I enjoy it.
You guys were so scared!
Perhaps I should have taped it on video.
Impossible!
Anyway, who is this beauty?
Where's the impurity?
Where's the bug?
Bug? There are lots of them here, big ones.
Big spiders...
There's more over here.
Nagi-
Nagi-san, where are you going?
That can't be!
That can't be, That can't be!
I'm sure I sensed an impurity!
My senses are failing.
A place of worship...
A place for propagating religion?
I didn't notice.
Goal!
You fail the test if it comes with a time limit though.
You were searching in such a wrong place.
You're...
Without that toy, you can't clean up on your own?
Has your divinity diminished?
Why?
Why are you here?!
It's been a while.
Big Sis.
Please watch the next episode of Kannagi too!