It's finally the second semester...
I'm not too sure if I feel happy or empty... it's a complicated feeling.
Hey, Tsukune.
When you went to the human world, you didn't stop by your home; was that all right?
Hello? This is the Aono Residence.
Ah, Mom?
Oh, if it isn't Tsukune! I heard you're on summer vacation, but when are you coming back?
About that...
I was nearby, but I decided not to come visit.
Oh my! Well, if you're doing fine that's good...
Of course I'm doing fine.
I've made lots of friends, entered the Newspaper Club, and cheerfully make newspapers with everybody...
It's very fun!
Why were you spacing out?
Ah, it's nothing!
That's fine then...
When I see your face...
You're not going to-
Sorry, Tsukune!
Right from the start of the semester?!
Someday, Moka and I will graduate from this academy.
It's also possible that the human and monster worlds will become separated.
That's why I decided to make as many happy memories as I can while I'm still here!
The summer vacation's first Youkai newspaper issue looks really good!
Yup, yup!
I think the girls will love the news article about the latest fashions of the human world!
Isn't it? I wrote it, after all.
Let's see here...
Ganguro and loose socks...
What a nice article...
Yahoohoohoo!~
Isn't that article a little outdated?
But, this is worth all the effort we put in. There's more content than usual too.
Yeah, I think-
...so too, Tsukune.
Shi-Shirayuki-san!
"Shirayuki-san" makes it sound like we're still strangers.
From now on, please call me "Mizore-chan".
Ah... okay...
Hey! We still haven't compiled as many issues as we were planning, so hurry up and get to work!
You're pretty into it, huh.
Of course! It's the newspaper that Tsukune and I made, right?
You're wrong, Kurumu-chan! It's all-of-us!
Yup, yup!
Before, when I first met you guys, I thought, "what a weird bunch," but...
Anyways, wasn't the Human World great?
Yeah, it was!
After seeing ganguros, I was thinking about trying it myself.
But?
Eh, really?!
But now I think, "This kind of thing isn't so bad."
That's why...
I think it's better if you don't use too much...
All right! Then, let's pass out those newspapers before class!
Yeah!
Would you like a copy of "Square"?
Would you like a copy of "Youkai Square"?
All of the articles are very interesting and informative!
For our first issue, it's a special edition about the Human World!
Whoa, it was printed in color?
There're even pictures of models in swimsuits!
The latest fashion trends in the human world?
Tulip hats and trousers are in style now, huh?
Hey, what the heck is that?
"Youkai Square"?
Hey, you guys! Who gave you guys permission to hand out newspapers?
Eh? Permission?
And also, "Youkai Square"?
And unlike our newspaper club, this isn't a legitimate club...
That's too bad.
Who are you?!
I'm Keito, a second-year student.
The president of the Super Newspaper Club.
Super... Newspaper Club?
When was this created?
As an official club, I've already gotten approval from the school.
No way!
Since you guys were so boring, we were thinking of bringing in new journalism.
What was that?!
Now now, Kurumu-chan...
If you're frustrated, then compete with your content.
Of course we will! We definitely won't lose!
You're right.
The distribution of the latest issue of Youkai Newspaper commences!
This is the latest issue of Youkai Newspaper!
Look! It's a special edition about the Human World!
Please read it!
If you don't read it... I'll freeze you.
There's a special on the human world in this newspaper too?
Doesn't this seem kinda rehashed?
There aren't any swimsuit models in this one!
With so many stiff news articles, it's so boring!
Somehow, our reputation...
I didn't think that a rival would appear...
Does the Super Newspaper Club really exist?
Sorry. This was something that I only heard of yesterday.
But, I'm surprised they got permission, since there's already a similar club.
About that...
In this situation, there is a belief that the less popular group should be abolished...
B-But...!
This is too much!
If that's the case, fine.
Kurumu-chan?
In other words, we just need to prove that we're more popular than the Super Newspaper Club, right?!
Hey wait, Kurumu-chan!
That's right! We have to talk to Gin-senpai first! He's our president, after all.
Just leave him be!
Besides, he's probably taking pictures of girls changing again!
Nice, nice!
Which is exactly what he was doing.
Ah, man! That's harsh!
That's...
Youkai Academy's...
Newspaper Club! Yahoohoohoo!
Please read our latest, content-filled issue, master!
Ku-Kurumu-san, this outfit is too embarrassing!
Just bear with it. We need to increase our Masters, I mean our readers.
I know, but...
Now, for all the Masters of the Youkai Newspaper here,
You'll get homemade cookies from me, Kuruno Kurumu!
Yeah!
Maid Clothes are the best!
Alright~ Who's the best newspaper in the school?
Youkai Newspaper!
I win.
This is Youkai Square!
If you subscribe now, we'll give you our secret unprocessed pictures as a present!
Please don't use them for strange reasons, okay?
Ah, swimsuits!
Wearing swimsuits in school isn't something you normally see, but that's fine with me!
Let me at 'em too!
Hey... is that legitimate?
Forget 'legitimate', they're actually doing it!
You guys are cute enough!
No, nevermind.
Everyone, who's the most interesting newspaper?
Youkai Square!
We can't lose here, Yukari-chan! Let's go with a more embarrassing outfit...
You're pretty cute! I think your flat chest is so much better than the swimsuits...
NO!!!
Wait, Yukari-chan!
Just a little bit more...
That was scary...
Yukari-chan, don't be discouraged... we're distributing in front of the school next!
Eh? We're still going to distribute them?
Of course! I can't back down now!
This time, we'll wear swimsuits too, and fairly revealing ones at that!
You guys, that's enough.
In the end, things were looking bad, so we talked to Gin-senpai...
And then...
Give up this time. Nothing will happen if you compete with them.
No way! But our opponents are just idiots running around in swimsuits!
And you were planning to do the same thing yourself...
Ouch!
Those guys... are backed by the Public Safety Commission.
Public Safety...
Commission?
What is that?
In a word, they're a more violent version of a morality police.
In order to protect the peace of the school, a militant group was made to control evil activities.
That's the school's police force: the Public Safety Commission.
School police? But that's...
We haven't done anything wrong...
It's a common occurrence, but because of their power, they've started becoming corrupt.
The commission now is just a bunch of violent thugs that collect money and tributes from others.
To think that something that crazy is happening within the school...
This incident is also probably because we've slowly become popular and become an eyesore to them.
Wait a minute! If these people are doing bad things, then isn't it the duty for our Newspaper Club to reveal it?
Tsukune-san, well said!
That's right! We just need to write a bunch of articles against them!
Gin-senpai?
There's no use in just chatting away! Burn all the newspapers here.
Got it?
No way!
Our newspapers...
I'll leave the rest to you.
That's something I can't accept!
This is an official decision of the Newspaper Club.
Is this all of it?
There's some left, I'll go get them.
Are you fine by yourself?
I'll go help too.
Even though we did our best making these...
Shirayuki-san sulked off... I wonder what's going to happen to our Newspaper Club?
Hey, Tsukune...
These newspapers... let's go distribute them now.
But, we can't disobey Gin-senpai's decision-
No.
Kurumu-chan?
Because these newspapers are like treasures to me.
It's the first thing that you and I made together.
To... to burn these... I...
Can't do it!
Kurumu-chan...
Onee-sama!
They're still planning on distributing their shitty newspapers!
Punish them please!
You guys!
Onee-sama?!
For a shitty contentless newspapers, it's pretty lightweight.
You guys, thanks for observing.
Ah, onee-sama!
Hey, why are you guys doing-
Tell us; why are you guys harassing our Newspaper Club?
Oh my... I guess you guys didn't hear anything from Morioka Ginei.
From Gin-senpai?
Anyway, your little Newspaper Club is finished.
That isn't funny! Give us our newspapers back!
"Give back"?
Who do you think you're talking to?
Your paper-thin content burns well!
Our newspapers...!
You can't!
I won't let you!
It's our onee-sama's order!
Hey, let go of me!
Kurumu-chan!
What is this?!
Today's Monster Memo: Jorougumo
Well known in Japan since ancient times, it is a giant spider monster that takes the form of a woman.
So you finally showed your true form!
I know it! Your uniform!
Oh? It seems that the only thing you're good at is finding dull material, Newspaper Club member-san.
That's...
To uphold our school's moral code as a guardian of justice.
This is our Public Safety Commission's badge of pride!
What "Guardian of Justice"? You guys are nothing but a bunch of thugs!
Aren't you talking about yourselves there?
Kurumu-chan!
This is nothing!
It's no use!
You can no longer escape!
You're now just a pitiful prey for our Onee-sama!
These girls used to be members of clubs that opposed us!
I'm from the "Boring Literature" club!
I'm from the Tea Ceremony Club!
And I'm from the Yaoi Manga Club!
But, I injected my spider poison into them, and they've become my loyal servants!
Servant, servant!
I love you, Onee-sama!
I'm her cute servant!
I'll inject my wonderful spider poison into you too!
Don't come here! That's disgusting, spider woman! Go away!
What a nice voice! The voice of a trapped prey in despair!
An ugly spider woman laughing with her mouth wide open.
What an unsightly thing.
Those shards...
Shirayuki-san!
Gosh.
I told you to call me Mizore-chan, remember?
You fool! Calling me, a Jorougumo, a mere spider woman!
Your opponent isn't me.
What?!
Are you guys alright?
Moka-san, please use this!
Tsukune!
Moka-san!
T-This is...!
Once the rosary on her chest is removed,
the Vampire blood within Moka will awaken.
What is this tremendous monster energy?!
Hurry and do something about this!
Don't act so spoiled.
If you really want to protect the Newspaper Club, then do something about it yourself.
I got it already! If I was actually serious here...
I won't let you go!
Chew her apart!
We won't let you escape!
Shut up!
Was that good enough for you?
Don't get cocky, you brats!
That low ability of yours is no match for our Public Safety Commission's President, Kuyou-sama!
And?
You guys will be trapped by my spider web!
This is perfect.
Wrapping a thread...
Pull, and pull, and tap tap tap.
Hey, hey, wait...
Wrapping a thread...
Wait!
S-Stop it!
Small fry.
Revenge Kick!
Together with Onee-sama!
Together!
Together till death!
If you like spider thread so much, you should stay buried in there the rest of your life.
Yes, buried...
This match, including the singing, was decided in 117 seconds!
I've decided!
This might be against Gin-senpai's wishes, but...
As part of the Newspaper Club, I want to reveal every evil action of the Public Safety Commission in an article!
Tsukune...
Even if everyone is against it...
We won't protest, Tsukune.
Let's do it!
I also approve.
Let's show them how the Newspaper Club fights!
Keito was defeated?
Yes. In a mere 117 seconds.
As expected of the powers from a vampire, huh?
How foolish, Newspaper Club. Don't tell me that they don't remember what happened last year...
And also...
About Aono Tsukune?
It looks like I'll be able to enjoy a good show for a change.
Everyone! It's time to show our powers as the Newspaper Club!
Yeah!
Wait, this is bad, Tsukune is...!
What's wrong?
He got all dried out from having his blood sucked.
Phew, *burp*.
Next time, Public Safety Commission and A Vampire
And a kappuchu for you!
Let me suck on you next week too desu~