Uwaaa...
You just don't learn, do you Kosame.
Call me Onee-chan, please!
Aside from that, hurry up and make breakfast for Ojou-sama.
Your breakfast this morning is a mushroom and cheese omelette.
Thank you.
Ojou-sama!
I demand to know why Subaru has been leaving the mansion ahead of you recently!
Calm down, Kosame-san.
Whenever it concerns Subaru, you become much too excited.
Little sisters with small breasts are the finest gourmet meals of all!
Starting today, breakfast is going to be much more interesting.
I find it very fascinating how Kanade-ojousama's favorite dish is never cooked the way she prefers.
I Fell in Love!
Hey Jirou, why were you walking to school with Subaru-sama?
We just met on the way to school.
Actually, I found out that Subaru-sama is a girl, and now she's following me everywhere I go.
She's using the fact that my nose bleeds every time I touch a girl against me so that I won't spill her secret.
Like I'd walk to school with Subaru-sama out of my own free will!
So, you two are going out after all.
No!
Be careful. There's rumor that S4 is on the move.
S4?
Shooting Star Subaru-Sama.
They're Subaru's underground fanclub, and they boast unmatched power in Roran Academy.
If they find out that you two are getting along nicely, they just might send you to burn in the fires of Hell due to jealousy.
No way.
Please be at ease.
We are the ones who make sure that Subaru-sama is well-protected.
Who are you?
We are a group of people that decided to defect from S4.
We had a difference of opinion.
And well, I'd like to ask you a question.
Who's the seme and who's the uke?
So they're fujoshi...
You've got it tough, don't you.
And whose fault is that?
Then I will give this to you as compensation.
What's this?
It's a sheep ticket.
Huh?
If you show Subaru that, she will do anything you ask of her.
Anything?
For example...
Telling her to strip completely naked and pouring honey on her chest.
Lick me.
If you have other fetishes, you can also do things like this or things like that.
Lick.
I'm not that kind of a person!
Well, we will meet again after school.
I've lost my appetite.
So why are we going to an arcade?
It is your first date, so,
I thought that it would be fitting.
What did you say? A date?
I thought that it would be better for you to take a normal girl out on a date to cure your fear of girls.
And where are you exactly?
I am reading manga at a manga café.
You sure act high-class...
Get ready.
It is about time.
Okay, Subaru, undress.
Understood, Ojou-sama.
Wait!
Not there.
I will go and change.
Stop staring at me so much.
Y-Yeah.
It seems like your chest has gotten bigger.
I normally use a breast binder.
However, today, the mistress prepared a padded brassiere for me.
Of course...
They weren't that big to begin with.
What are you thinking about!?
Sorry!
Geez.
Let's go!
Yes.
What is this?
Don't you know?
You put some money in and try to grab a toy.
They sure are cute.
Shall I grab one for you?
Yeah!
It's so cute!
First Date!
Subaru    Kinjirou
Here.
Thank you.
Sorry.
Huh?
I was supposed to help you overcome your gynophobia today, but I got carried away and had too much fun.
I don't really mind.
Can you tell me why you are scared of girls?
Have you heard of Sakamachi Akemi?
Wasn't she a female pro-wrestler?
She was the previous Queen of Wrestlers.
She's my mother.
Like my mother, my little sister is also very good at wrestling.
I've been their sandbag for the last ten years.
And this is the result.
But what causes your nose to bleed?
Maybe it's just a reflex.
If my nose bleeds, they'll leave me alone.
Your family worries about you a lot.
Nope. You're wrong.
It's because the room would get dirty otherwise.
I'm sure things will work out for you.
Maybe so.
I want to cure my phobia as fast as possible.
Since I want to be able to touch girls again!
Are you finished with your warm-up?
Yes.
Then execute the second stage of the mission.
This is an order from Ojou-sama.
Here I go.
Program One.
Program Two.
Three.
Subaru.
Yes?
Give the cell phone to Jirou-kun.
How is it?
Your nose did not bleed yet?
Somehow.
Well then, as a present, you're allowed use the sheep ticket.
'Kay?
Why do you have that?!
Suzutsuki gave it to me.
What are your orders, master?
NO WAY!!!
My master!!
My master.
I really do not wish to utter those words to anyone other than Ojou-sama.
However, a sheep ticket is the same as an order from Ojou-sama, so...
The sheep ticket is absolute, isn't it?
Now, please order me around as you please!
"As I please" sounds kind of...
No way, I'm not a perv!
W-Well then, try saying "mehh."
M-M-M-Mehh...
It was just supposed to be a simple order, but I feel like I've crossed the line.
Not at all. Nevertheless, I am my master's butler.
Well, you can stop now.
Master, you have some dust on your head.
Stop, Konoe!
Why are you are shivering so much?
Is it really that cold?
Well then, shall I warm you up?
A small chest is for the best!
Kanade-ojousama, love.
Kureha!
What're you doing at a place like this?
That's my line!
I heard that you were going out with a guy.
I was worried, so I've been tailing you all day.
You followed me?
Then the unthinkable happened.
I found you with him!
Why?
Why does he have a fetish as perverted as crossdressing?
Huh?
Waitー
I saw all of it.
How you gave a plushie as a present to Crossdressing-senpai.
How you also let him touch your body in lewd ways.
And how you almost kissed even though you're both boys.
I knew something was odd when he came to pick you up.
You tricked my brother didn't you?
Kureha...
You thieving cat!
Give me my brother back!
What!!!
Kureha!
What is this?
This is...
I was defeated so easily?
Wouldn't you say that was a rather unforeseen ending?
Suzutsuki!
You were watching us?
Would I miss the chance to see something this interesting?
Sorry, I did not mean to kick her that hard.
Don't worry.
She wouldn't have stopped if you didn't do that.
But...
Well, see you at school tomorrow, okay?
I'm home.
Hey, Kureha!
Are you back yet?
T-This stuffed bear is...
You were used as Kureha's sandbag while I wasn't around.
I'm so sorry.
Well, it was a huge shock to Kureha after all.
I am sincerely sorry about what happened yesterday...
That still hasn't been resolved, has it?
It feels like it's only going to get tougher from now on.
1.2 Physical Examination Period
Well then, the boys should get changed into their gym uniforms and head to the nurse's office.
What are you going to do?
I don't really have a choice.
It's a physical examination, you know!
You'll be measured here and there while you're naked, you know!
But Ojou-sama said,
"You were able to avoid the physical examination last year because you had a sudden illness,
but this year you will just have to rely on him."
Got it, Subaru?
You've always changed here haven't you?
Yes.
No matter how you think about it, it's impossible.
You don't have to go through with this.
It will be fine.
I will overcome it no matter what.
Height, weight, sitting height.
So far, so good...
You're screwed if they try to measure your chest.
Don't worry, I have bound it tighter than usual.
You don't usually wrap it up like that!
I will fool them somehow.
Next is, Konoe Subaru-kun.
Coming.
What's this?!
Take it off!
I need to take the proper measurement, right?
A girl?!
Konoe is a girl?!
Wait a second!
Konoe is, well, very shy in front of crowds!
I'll measure his chest!
Wha...?
Fine...
Sakamachi!
78 centimeters.
Sakamachi, are you okay?
Okay. Next is, Sakamachi Kinjirou.
This is really bad!
We're already teenagers, yet they still give us female nurses!
It's supposed to be a male doctor!
I will measure his chest.
Please allow me to measure his chest!
You should be fine if it's just me touching you for this short amount of time, right?
I will make this quick, so...
Sorry, Konoe.
I'm sorry too.
We made it through the vision and hearing tests.
Next is...
Here, let me see your chest!
Why are you binding your chest?!
Next is, Konoe Subaru!
Here, let me see your chest...
I'll be Konoe's stethoscope!
You don't have to go that far...
T-Then...
How am I going to get us out of this situation...
I can't take this much longer!
Konoe?
Are you okay?
What happened to the physical?
Thanks to what you did back there, I was able to get away safely.
I see.
I'm beginning to regret not being able to handle it on my own.
Ojou-sama was overjoyed when she found out that we took the physical together.
There'll definitely be rumors about us now!
Is it lunch right now?
If it's alright with you, how about we eat together?
It's not like I want to eat with you or anything!
I will treat you.
I don't want to owe anyone any favors.
A chocolate cornet, a fried-noodle-bread sandwich,
And then some korokke bread.
Curry bread, fried pork and leeks...
He laid his hands on Subaru!
That four-eyed bastard!
I'll kill him!
That bastard!
It seems as though you were grasping and hugging her during the physical.
Why does he get to play doctor with Subaru-sama?
We'll kill you!
Oi, hurry up and buy them!
What are you doing?
You should sit down.
Okay...
Come to think of it, where's Suzutsuki?
Oi, don't ignore me.
Do you usually eat with someone like this?
Yes, with Kurose, I guess.
We've been friends ever since middle school.
Since middle school, you say?
I did not go to one, so I would not really know what it is like.
Ojou-sama and I both started attending school in high school.
Previously, we had private tutors and were home-schooled.
I have never had the chance to eat together with someone.
With a friend, like you.
If we're going to be friends, let's start by calling each other by each other's first names, okay?
You still haven't called me by my name yet, have you?
So, call me Jirou.
Would that really be alright?
What do you mean?
Addressing each other as friends.
It's okay, alright?
But...
It is way easier than saying "mehh..."
Okay.
Well, here I go.
J-Jirou!
Oh!
Well done.
Jirou!
Jirou, huh?
Your nose did not bleed this time!
Maybe the mission did have an effect after all.
Suzutsuki!
She is already asleep.
She probably feels that she doesn't have to be nervous around you if she is able to sleep on your shoulder like that.
Nervous?
She always has to be on guard because of her secret, so she doesn't let anyone get close to her.
But she finally found a friend.
A friend?
Since you already know her secret, she can be friends with you.
She did her best today, didn't she?
I am just Subaru's master, so she does not see me as a friend.
We used to be close, and I called her Kana-chan.
However, that's all in the past.
I'm home!
Welcome back.
I'm home...
Nii-san, can I ask you something?
What is it?
Are you going out with Konoe-Senpai?
No!
He's just a friend.
Well, nii-san.
I just fell in love with someone.
I've never experienced these emotions before.
And I'm not sure about what to do about them.
Don't tell me, you're talking aboutー
Your friend.
Whaaa!
Konoe-senpai is a little strange, but he's really strong and cool!
I really love him!
This is bad!
Dear Father in Heaven,
your daughter has fallen in love with another girl!
Kureha-chan,
do you know where a girl is happiest?
On top of the ring, YEAH!
No, you're wrong.
Let me show you.
Please.
It is a place where you scream with pleasure.
A place where you feel most pleasant.
So it is on top of the ring after all!
Next time on Mayo Chiki,
the third story.
It is without a doubt, in bed.
It is Without a Doubt, in Bed