The keeper of the Kannagi Shrine?
I think you can ask the shrine's prefecture office,
but why do you want to research this?
Well... I'm just curious to know more about the shrine nearby.
Oh, I'm impressed.
I never knew you were such a passionate student.
Give me a moment, I'll ask for you.
Sorry for the trouble.
Hello?
Thank you very much.
Jin.
Daitetsu.
Come with me for a minute.
I'm sorry.
I know we shouldn't be seeing each other...
No, it's all right.
What is it?
This is Nagi's...
Yes, I picked it up just now.
I was on the rooftop, since I would cause another ruckus if I went to the club room...
Then, I found it...
She... I can't find any signs of her anywhere.
I see... There's no helping her.
Thanks. I'll return it to her.
Did something happen between you and Nagi-san?
Nope, it's nothing.
We had a little fight, but that happens all the time.
Ah... You're from the school... for homework...
Cute boy!
Come, come! Come in, Come in!
Want some rice cakes with bean paste?
Oh, it's all right.
Which school are you from?
Umm...
We have boiled chestnuts, want some?
These are ferns that I picked from the mountains!
Want any dried potatoes?
How old are you?
Want some sweets?
I'm fine, thank you.
Sorry about this.
My husband longs for company ever since our sons left home.
Please play along with him.
Okay. Umm...
Our second son went to that high school,
but he failed the university entrance exam and became a private candidate for two years.
He went to a vocational school after that.
But all of a sudden, he said he wanted to study overseas.
Umm, what was it? Hey, dear...
He went to some country in the south.
Later, he met a girl in a bar and is going to marry her, or something like that.
Want some rice crackers?
I want to ask about the shrine...
Kannagi Shrine?
Oh, that place has always been managed by the five families living around here.
The Satous over there, and the Suzukis, and also the Tanakas!
Doesn't it have a Shinto priest?
No, no!
We get one from another place to make a trip here.
Apparently, there were ancient documents stored here,
but they got destroyed in a fire long ago.
That's why nobody knows the name of the god enshrined here.
Our Obaa-sama is the only one who might know something.
Obaa-chan? Obaa-chan!
This child wants to hear about Kannagi-sama.
Umm...
I'm sorry, she actually can hear us.
I'm grateful to Kannagi-sama.
She also saved the people who tried to hang themselves.
What? Hang themselves?
Yes. It was events during the war.
Life was hard, so there were people who did that, or so I heard.
It used to be a deserted place.
But that's all in the past.
Obaa-chan always talks about such things.
Miss!
Lately, I've seen you a lot on TV.
Do you still cost 100 yen?
That's quite some spirit of service you have there.
We're willing to pay a hundred thousand for you.
If you want money, you'll get more out of playing with us.
You've got it wrong, I'm not like that!
Didn't I tell you I'm not like that?
W-What's with this bitch?
Damn, don't get all cocky just because we went easy on you!
Why you!
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
You bitch, don't fuck wit—
You guys, go from that side!
Hey, wait a sec—
I can get more out of playing with you?
I can't even get any fun out of you guys.
Run!
Hey. Take this man with you.
Eww, they're dirty. My shoes are soiled.
Are you all right, Zange-chan?
I'm sorry that I wasn't of any help...
Look, I bought you a canned coffee.
Kyaa! Mister, thanks as always!
Mister will do anything for you, Zange-chan!
But you're so mean to hide in a corner and watch.
I was so afraid!
Mister is weak against violence...
You're strong...
Don't say that, it was all by chance.
I was imitating the kung-fu movies and I hit them by chance.
With her skills, I didn't even need to save her back there...
I'm so happy that you came to find me today.
It was always me looking for you.
What's that?
Ferns...
I came to ask you something concerning Nagi.
I have many doubts...
You're asking whether we're really gods?
Oh, I see. Is that so?
If it's concerning Nee-sama...
That's...
...a woman's secret.
A se-cr-et!
Huh?!
For the impurities that I hunt, I seal them up like this.
Even though it's a watering can, it's used for sprinkling holy water.
If I put them in such a thing, they can't get away.
Since the impurities will taint the land, they have to be eliminated.
And a god has the duty to do so.
That is what I recognize.
I don't know anything beyond that.
She gave the same response as Nagi.
But are you not bothered by that?
It's not important.
As I've told you before, my goal is to become an individualist.
I have little interest in anything else.
As long as I remain a god, all is well.
That's what I feel.
But do you have any proof that you're truly a god?
You're unusually concerned about that.
Whatever gave you the idea that we're not?
The truth is... Suzushiro-sensei said...
What? Lowly spirits?
It's just like him to think like that.
In the first place, it's wrong to speak of Japan's gods from the perspective of western theology.
Sensei said that there were cases of such spirits that believed themselves to be gods.
That got me a little confused...
It's fine like that!
In this world, there are many things that have ambiguity as their charm.
D-Don't tell me... Jin-kun, you're not suspecting me, are you?!
Oh, no...
I'm really a god, okay?
Yeah...
If you don't believe me, I...
But I can't say the same about that dumb sister.
In Nee-sama's case, her method of taking form is special.
A sacred tree is something that possesses great spiritual power.
As a vessel that houses a god, it's a plant with excellent potential.
But that also means it'll attract random spirits.
Some unknown spirit from God knows where might be pretending to be Nee-sama.
Such a thing is possible too.
That's what I think.
No way.
Life was hard, so there were people who did that, or so I heard.
It'll attract random spirits.
Some unknown spirit from God knows where might be pretending to be Nee-sama.
Either they are speaking as gods solely for their own ends,
or they falsely believe that they themselves are gods.
It all makes sense.
Nagi?
Why did you have to do this?
You were lying to me?
What the hell?
I have to go to school.
Letter:
I was lying to you all along
I'm sorry
- Nagi
Stay at home
after you come back
I won't get mad
Did she...
Did she really exist in the first place?
Good morning.
Shoes:
Nagi
Good morning.
Oh, hi.
What are you doing here? This place is for the second-year students.
I know.
Gosh, what's wrong? You didn't sleep at all?
Where's Nagi-san?
No idea. She may be absent today.
Weren't you with her?
Hello?
Nagi-sama? She's not here yet.
I see.
Senpai, have you seen her around?
Nagi-sama? I haven't. Are you looking for her?
Yeah...
Shino, Akiba-kun!
Have you seen Nagi-sama?
No.
I haven't seen her.
What's wrong? You two had a quarrel?
I'm sorry, but please let me skip club today.
Huh? Wait... Mikuriya?
Doesn't that sound serious?
Did something happen between those two?
You don't think...
Perhaps they're getting into a gal-game kind of development?
How can that be?
But does Mikuriya have the guts to do such a thing?
He doesn't.
But boys of that age are all wolves!
You don't know what might make them go wild!
Takako, you're more like a wolf yourself.
Mikuriya, I believe in you.
Jin!
Where's Nagi-san?
She's absent, haven't I told you?
Is she sick? Should I go and make her porridge?
No, it's okay.
She's not sick...
You're not yourself today.
Tell me if something happened.
I'm sorry, but I'll be going home.
Jin?
Jin!
Jin...
You don't have to run away...
Hey, what's wrong with Nagi-san?
What's wrong?
Today's the second day.
Hey, did something really happen?
Wasn't it an illness?
What's happened? Did you have a fight with her?
Playing truant?
Hey...
...may not...
She may not be coming back.
Please watch the next episode of Kannagi too!