Who's there?
There's nobody there...
Tsukune, please.
I want to suck your blood.
No...
Thanks for the meal, Tsukune's blood is the best after all.
It seems like I'm getting addicted to it.
I got my blood sucked again...
I'll die of anemia if this goes on.
To think I can go to club activities today with Moka-san...
Tsukune!
Club activities start from today onwards, right?
I'm so happy to be in the same club as Tsukune!
Kurumu-chan...
I'm suffocating...
Kurumu-san is so sly!
Tsukune-san and I are in the same club too!
No, you can't.
I'm suffocating...
Tsukune is my "Destined One".
I'm going to make use of club activities to deepen our relationship and fall in love together.
I won't lose to you, Akashiya Moka.
Tsukune-san is...
Tsukune!
Hang in there, Tsukune!
Tsukune-san!
Did you hear about the serial peeping tom?
Yeah, I heard about it!
I'm too scared to even change my clothes!
Yeah.
When I'm changing, I always ask someone to keep a lookout for me.
That's a good idea.
Well then, we shall start the Youkai Academy's Newspaper Club activity now.
Are we the only members?
My, of course not.
Sorry.
See, he's here already.
I'm really sorry for being late on the first day of activities.
Nice to meet you guys.
I'm the club leader, Morioka Ginei.
Please call me Gin from now on.
You may be young, but you are a lady after all.
Indeed, pretty ladies complement well with red flowers.
Gin-kun is the only second year member here.
Also, we don't have any third year students here.
If you have any questions, feel free to ask Gin-kun.
You can count on me.
The staff meeting is going to start soon.
The rest is up to you, Gin-kun.
Leave it to me.
And so, let me introduce the Newspaper Club to you guys.
The main objective of the Newspaper Club is to distribute the school newspaper,
and to report any happenings in the school,
then write them in the newspaper.
For the sake of reporting, we must put ourselves on the line.
In short, we are very different from any other clubs!
Once you have joined, you have to prepare yourself.
He seems to be a Senpai you can count on, unexpectedly though.
Just kidding; don't be so tense and let's get along with each other.
If you have any material to report, speak up.
That's right, the serial peeping case!
Peeping?
I heard that there's someone peeping at the girls in the school recently
And he's so fast that no one's seen his face clearly yet.
Peeping is despicable!
He's the enemy of all girls and can't be forgiven!
Let us, the Newspaper Club, find the culprit.
If that's the case, we should first find people with information.
How do we find them?
The basis for reporting is...
Go around asking for information and...
Asking help from the public.
Senpai, is this high enough to stick the posters?
A little more will do.
Eh? A little more?
Yeah, a little more.
A little more?
Is this enough?
I'll help too!
You're still small so forget about it.
Wait till you get taller, okay?
He's carefree sometimes yet serious at times, what kind of person is Gin-senpai?
Still not high enough?
Okay, stay like that.
What is he doing?
Kurumu-san, Moka-san, are you guys okay?
Are you all right, Kurumu-chan?
My breasts are in the way...
He's peeping at their panties!
What are you doing, Senpai?!
Stop it!
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb with me, you peeped under their skirts just now, right?
Are you an idiot?
Do you think a person like me would do such a shameless thing?
What's wrong?
Nothing, he said that he saw your panties.
Eh?
Isn't that you, Senpai?
Tsukune!
Wait, it's a misunderstanding.
I did see, but it's all because...
What an idiot he is.
Sorry, I did that subconsciously.
It must hurt but I won't pity you.
Yeah, if you want to see it, then just tell me.
Kurumu-chan, that's not the case!
Wait a minute, Moka-san!
I hate perverts!
You're really dumb.
Thanks to you, the club activity has stopped.
Moka-san!
Geez, did he really see it?
This is so embarrassing.
Which one am I wearing today...?
What are you doing?
You'd better be careful.
That guy emits a dangerous aura.
It's an aura that's hiding a strong power.
You'd better be careful of that man called Gin.
The moon is beautiful tonight.
Almost as beautiful as you, Akashiya Moka.
Wait for me!
Like I said, yesterday was an accident!
I don't care if it was an accident!
I don't care about you anymore, Tsukune!
No way...
Although I'm not serious,
I won't talk to Tsukune for a while as revenge for seeing my panties.
Moka-san, listen to me!
Moka-san!
I don't care!
Are Moka-san and Tsukune-kun dating?
I'm not sure but...
I heard people saying that they saw Moka-san kissed Tsukune-kun on the neck.
Eh, really?
Kissed on the neck?
Tsukune...
This is no joke, Tsukune-kun!
Who's there?
A man plagued with bad luck.
Eh?
What do you think you're doing?
Doing this in broad daylight...
What...
I better take some precautions...
The only way to split Moka-san from Tsukune is...
I hate perverts!
Like I said, it's all a misunderstanding.
I just happened to be passing by, that's all.
It's useless...
They don't believe me...
I believe in you, Tsukune-kun.
Gin-senpai.
We're both guys, right?
Senpai...
Let's have a talk.
Seems like you're being disliked by Moka-san.
Yeah, that seems to be the case.
She completely thinks that I'm a pervert.
Hey, look over there.
Take a peek inside.
What for?
Don't you want to mend your relationship with Moka-san?
Get up there by climbing this drum.
Moka-san is a better woman than what the rumors say.
I fell in love with her at first sight too.
Akashiya Moka...
I'll definitely make her mine.
W-Why do you say that suddenly?
F-Female Changing Room?!
Peeping is bad, Tsukune-kun.
If I show this photograph to Moka-san, she'll definitely hate you.
What was that sound just now?
Your relationship with Moka-san will crumble!
Senpai, you framed me!
The window over there!
The serial peeping tom?
No!
There he is!
Peeping tom! There's a peeping tom!
Damn you!
This is unforgivable!
So you're the serial peeper, huh?
Hurry up and confess!
It's not that! I'm not the serial peeping tom!
What about just now, then?
Why were you at such a place?
That's right!
Tsukune?
Moka-san!
Is that true? Peeping...
No it's not! It's a misunderstanding!
Well I really did peep, but this wa-
He admitted!
Oh no, not again...
Wait up, Moka-san!
So it was you, after all!
You even admitted!
You're the enemy of women!
Get him!
Eh? Tsukune did?
I heard that he peeped at the female changing room,
the rumors are spreading like wildfire now.
That's just not possible.
Exactly!
How can Tsukune think of looking at girls other than me?!
A-Anyway, there must be some reason for this.
What kind of reason?
This what we, the Newspaper Club, will investigate!
What's wrong?
What are you doing here?
It's already nightfall.
Look. There's a beautiful full moon tonight.
Gin-senpai...
I heard about it... about Tsukune.
Even though he doesn't seem like the type,
the saying, "You can't judge a person by his appearance" applies here.
Is it true...
Is it true that Tsukune is the peeping tom?
I...
I understand that you want to believe him,
However, he was caught red-handed with evidence.
But...
Moka-san... you should just forget about Tsukune.
Let me comfort you tonight.
No!
That leaves me no choice then... I actually didn't want you to see this.
I don't know who photographed this,
But these photographss have been circulating everywhere.
This is...!
Moka-san...
O-Ow...
Photographs of the peeping tom in action.
You should understand now.
Tsukune... is your most hated pervert.
I'd like to believe Tsukune instead of these photographs.
Can you still believe him?
You're just lying to yourself.
You should just be more frank.
This is reality.
Tsukune is a lecher who specifically moved the drum for support in order to peep into the girls changing room!
How do you know about that?
Well if you look at the photographs...
All right.
Please take a look at these photographs.
What's wrong with them?
Only the top-half of Tsukune was taken.
We don't know what he used for support.
That's true!
T-That's...
Oh yeah, that's because I went to the scene after it happened.
Even though that was the first time I went there,
I knew immediately that he used it for support.
And you also knew that it was moved by Aono Tsukune?
Yes, those things weren't there originally.
Didn't you say it was your first time at that scene?
Why are you so sure that they weren't there originally?
You knew about the peeping spot from before,
and also knew about the drums being used for support.
Isn't that right?
Furthermore, you were at the scene when this photograph was taken!
Indeed, I went there before,
and also knew that the drums were used as support,
but that doesn't prove that I was at the crime scene.
Sure we can, Ginei-san.
W-What?
After the incident, those drums were taken away by the female students who were concerned of such a thing happening again.
In other words, the drums were only there from the time the crime occurred until immediately after.
Besides the people at the scene, it's impossible for others to have known.
There's more, Gin-senpai.
There are a few witnesses who testified that you moved the drums before the crime occurred.
Which means...
That's right.
The criminal is...
You!
Enough of this nonsense!
Since it's come to this, I'll use my power and make you my woman, Akashiya Moka!
Werewolves are violent and wild monsters.
They usually maintain a human form, but they'll turn into a wolf on the night of a full moon.
The stronger the moonlight, the stronger their powers are.
Moka-san!
Tsukune!
Werewolves are super monsters who can match up against vampires!
There's no chance in a direct confrontation!
You fool! Don't get full of yourself!
Tsukune!
If you don't want to die, just give up Moka-san, Tsukune-kun!
Just disappear!
Once the rosary on her chest is removed,
The vampire blood within Moka will awaken.
No way...
No way!
Red pupils...
A vampire?!
This is Moka-san's true form?
Beautiful... This is the best!
A vampire is fine too!
Even if I have to defeat you, I'll still make you my woman!
Don't be ridiculous, you bastard.
Where are you looking at? I'm over here!
He's fast!
He's extremely agile!
If vampires rely on power,
werewolves are monsters who rely on speed!
And the stronger the moonlight, the faster the speed.
The moonlight of the full moon tonight is at its brightest!
Werewolves are undefeatable on the night of a full moon!
Take this!
This is a werewolf, huh?
Give it up!
As long as a full moon is there, I'll definitely win!
Moka-san!
W-What?!
I was stopped!
B-But how?!
C-Could it be...?
Oh crap! The moon got covered by the clouds!
I can't use my power if the moon doesn't come out!
Hold on... Don't get cocky.
Even if the moon is covered, don't underestimate us werewolves!
I'll show you the power of a super monster!
Be my woman obediently, Moka!
You untamed dog.
You aren't fit to be my opponent.
Know your place!
I know my place now!
Somehow, this week's winner took 112 seconds to decide!
Extra!
Also, I never thought this would be our first piece of work, Moka-san-
You can't look up right now!
Hold up!
Take that!
I'm sorry Tsukune!
Are you all right?
It smells so good...
You can't do that, Moka!
That's right, Moka-san!
I...
I can't... resist anymore!
Kappuchu!
This is bad, Moka-san!
It seems like someone's observing me the whole day!
Could it be a stalker?
Stare...
Stare!
Kurumu-chan and Yukari-chan too?
Next, a Snow Lady and a Vampire,
and a kappuchu for you!