Thank you for waiting.
Is that all for your order?
Subaru-sama, come to this table next!
I'll be there momentarily.
Welcome.
Your order, please?
Please wait at your seat.
Is it time to change shifts?
Aren't your swimsuits a little too revealing?
They're covered by aprons anyway, so it doesn't hurt to adventure.
That's right.
It's called special service for our guests.
Let's start a war
Let's start a war.
Now, it's a date, so lead me properly!
Lead you? Why should I?
Because you're my date, obviously!
Oh, what? Don't you have any confidence with a girl?
You're a real chicken.
Doesn't the same apply to you?
Don't group me together with you.
I have plenty of experience, you know.
Then you should lead me.
What a boring guy.
Fine. I'll teach you.
When you're on a date, the guy is supposed to pay for everything...
Whatever...
Is it good?
It tastes even better when you realize you didn't have to pay for it.
You know...
At least tell me in advance if you're planning to come.
You're going to treat us to something, right?
Leave it to me!
Oh, how exciting.
This way!
Hey, you stupid chicken.
Huh?
When this date is over, I'll treat you to my homemade cooking.
What's this all of a sudden?
Let me do whatever!
I think it's a bit strange to be the only person getting treated for free.
Well, it's up to you, though...
What?
Didn't you find octopus inside?
I told you, we're supposed to pretend that we're dating!
Hurry up!
I'm embarrassed too, you know!
Fine, I got it.
Usami, what the hell—
Well-deserved.
Konoe?
I'll be putting you under observation.
Huh?
I'm your friend.
I have an obligation to ensure that my friend is having a proper and legitimate relationship.
Damn him! Messing around with two girls at once...
Calm down. Subaru-sama is male.
I don't care if he's male!
He's too envious!
How long are you going to keep following us?
Forever.
This is normal as a friend.
It's not normal!
Besides, we're dating!
Wha—
That's unfair!
I'll do this then!
"Animal Cafe"?
Shouldn't we take a break?
Agreed.
Thank you for waiting.
How cute!
Oh?
It's my brother and...
Usamin-senpai!
Welcome, my brother!
I didn't imagine this to be your class...
Usamin-senpai, I'm surprised.
I always thought you never knew my brother.
Sakamachi, do you remember how many times I've told you to stop calling me that?
Oh my, you're acting tsundere.
We're friends, right?
Hey! Quit it! I mean it!
Usamin-senpai feels so nice and smooth.
Idiot, quit—
Stop touching those places!
That's enough! You're supposed to be my kouhai, you know!
Usamin-senpai, please show up for club activities every once in a while.
Jirou, how about this?
Konoe-senpai, you came too!
So this is Kureha-chan's class.
Yes. What do you think about this strap?
We can have a matching pair.
Could it be that you're not on good terms with Kureha?
Rather, I envy her.
Envy?
She lives so true to herself.
Lively and freely, so honest with herself...
She has friendly family members like you.
Huh?
I've gotten tired of being with you now.
Why don't you go with Subaru-sama now?
Huh? What happened to the deal?
Just go already.
You don't find it fun being with me either, do you?
Well, you're right.
I'm going to go over to Konoe now.
Hey, which color would be nice?
I'll go buy it.
Yes.
Hey, you damn sheep!
Who are you?!
Nakuru. Nakuru's proper name would be Narumi Nakuru.
I'm a first year from the hobby club.
So another one from the hobby club.
Let me formally reintroduce myself, Sakamachi-senpai.
I am Narumi Nakuru, president of the "Warmly Looking Over Subaru-sama Group."
A "looking over" group?
Yes. Through my glasses, I can only see you.
The same goes for me.
Oh, my sweet glasses...
My masterpiece!
That group must be insane for having a president who draws stupid manga like this!
What part of this is stupid?
Every part of it!
Why are the glasses prominently featured like this, anyway?
Because glasses are the true symbol of human culture!
Here's a famous quote from a historical figure:
"If there's no bread, you can wear glasses!"
I understand that you like BL and glasses.
So then, what does that president have to do with me?
Run away.
Huh?
A secret battle between our Looking Over group and the S4 is going to be held soon.
Depending on the outcome, you may become a casualty.
If that's the case, I heard it was going to be all right.
Well, I think you shouldn't trust Usami-senpai too much.
What do you mean by that?
Didn't she bring you a deal?
She was trying to cause chaos within our Looking Over group by spreading rumors that you two were dating.
But our Looking Over group isn't easily shaken by something like that.
We believe in you and Subaru-sama!
So what, that plan Usami had was never going to work from the very beginning.
And so, Usami-senpai's part of the deal would have probably been...
Something like assuring your safety, right?
But you know, that's almost without a doubt a lie.
Because there's no way Usami-senpai can control the S4...
How careless of me.
I never thought you would hide inside a suit like that.
Is she telling the truth, Usami?
Sorry, Idiot-chicken.
I was tricking you from the start.
What are you trying to do?
Jirou, what's this all about?
If it's hard for you to say, I won't insist that you tell me everything.
But at least tell me what's going on. We're friends!
Right now, there's a war going on between your fan clubs at our academy.
It's between the Looking Over group that she leads, and the S4 group.
And if the S4 wins in the secret event that is going to be held,
I'll become a casualty.
So, what are you going to do?
What I should do?
Hey, you!
Yes...?
S-Subaru-sama?!
I have something I want to ask you.
R-Raw stuff...
Raw stuff? Sure, I like it raw.
What's going to happen?
Shush, don't speak a word.
Everyone, thank you for gathering today.
So then.
Let the war begin.
Sorry for my late introduction.
Hosting this event today will be the representative of the Shooting Star Subaru-Sama
and second year of our Rouran Academy, Suzutsuki Kanade!
What kind of joke is this?!
You idiot, stop shouting!
Oh?
Subaru-sama?
Pictures! Take pictures!
That fucking four-eyes!
He has great courage to show up here just to get owned.
Silence.
Let's not fight here.
The winner of the event will be able to conquer all of the losers, including what should be done with Sakamachi-kun.
The 1st Subaru-Sama Cult Quiz Tournament
Subaru, are you really fine with being on that side?
Yes.
I choose the side where no one will get hurt.
Right.
She's nowhere to be found. Where did she go?
Correct.
It's quite difficult.
The next problem...
The vending machine where Subaru bought drinks yesterday...
What is the name of the employee who fills it with cans?
Carlos Uehara!
Correct.
What a relief.
Damn it.
I can't even answer one problem even if it's about me.
Well, somewhere it started having nothing to do with you.
Next will be the final problem.
This will be for 5 points.
The team that gets this problem right will be the winner.
Now the problem:
Who was Subaru's first kiss with?
Ojou-sama!
Konoe, this is your chance!
Fight the embarrassment and answer it!
What? Are you serious, Jirou?
They are leading in points.
At this rate, Konoe-senpai will be tortured to death!
But...
Please, Konoe. This is my one and only once in a lifetime wish!
Jirou.
Huh?
Correct!
What?!
So then, let's watch this video clip showing the correct answer.
Damn you, go to hell!
Oh my.
Do something, Suzutsuki!
Something?
Like what?
Isn't it obvious? Otherwise I'm going to be murdered by them!
Go to hell—
Oh, how interesting that would be.
Sadist!
You're a sadist!
Well then, should I have asked who was my first kiss as the final question?
Oh my, what a problem.
Listen everyone!
The person I truly love is,
Suzutsuki Kanade!
No way!
What does he mean?
What about Subaru-sama?
Is he cheating?
Thank you, Sakamachi-kun.
But I'm sorry.
You surely are a good person, but honestly you're nothing more than being good.
While you would be great as a friend, as a lover you're a little...
What? He's being dumped?
You're such a good person!
So, I'm sorry...
Even though you are so good...
Wait, damn it!
Wait, please!
I'd like you to thank me, Jirou-kun.
Since I intentionally dumped you so badly.
Yeah, thank you.
But I'm kind of pissed, you know.
Since you made a false confession in front of such a crowd, even if it was for self defense...
I'm deeply hurt.
Oh, but that was...
So I'll have my revenge now.
I love you so much!
So, how does it feel, to receive the same treatment?
I'm sorry.
The Closing Night Festival is going to start soon.
Since you survived, don't you think you should enjoy yourself now, even if it's a bit late?
Hey, didn't you see someone called Usami participating in the event?
Oh, didn't you hear?
I thought she was your girlfriend.
You should have known the relationship between us already, right?
She quit the S4 before the event began.
It's true that she was a bit different from the others and didn't really blend in.
But since she didn't try to become friends with any of the members...
Jirou-kun?
What was all that about, Evil Rabbit?
I will trust in you,
so you should trust in me.
What kind of joke is this?
It was all filled with lies!
I'm sorry, stupid chicken.
I tricked you from the very start.
I don't get it at all. What were you going to achieve through all that?
This is my favorite place.
What is the 'School Quitting Letter' for?
I shouldn't have told you about this place.
During those days, Subaru-sama...
He was a lone prince that didn't allow anyone to get close.
And so I thought...
That he might be the same as me.
That's why I thought he... Subaru-sama might possibly become my friend.
But Subaru-sama had changed.
After he became a 2nd year, he made a friend.
Yes, that would be you, Idiot-chicken!
After he met you, he had changed!
And so I thought,
maybe you have some special power to do so.
Could you have...
In the end, I haven't changed at all.
And so I finally realized...
That Subaru-sama had changed by himself.
All right. That's where I'll finish talking about myself.
Oh, but let me say this in the end.
As I thought, I really hate you.
I hate Subaru-sama too.
And even more,
I hate myself the most because I'm like this!
Wait a second!
The school festival isn't over yet.
Where are we going?
I don't have-
We promised to pretend that we're dating until the school festival ends.
Let go of me, Idiot-chick-
Hey, are you all right?
Is something wrong with you?
Yeah. Since you told me your secret, I'll tell you my secret.
Secret?
Fear of women?
Oh what is with that embarrassing chicken constitution...
Don't laugh.
I am seriously concerned about it.
Isn't everyone amazing?
Because you know, they can't see into people's hearts, yet they manage to become friends.
I can't do that.
Someone like me who can only doubt others...
So was it also a lie when you said you'd trust in me?
And are you fine with breaking that promise too?
Promise?
You told me when I treated you to Takoyaki
that you would treat me to homemade cooking.
I believed in you and was looking forward to it.
Jirou, I heard everything from Ojou-sama.
Everything was a lie?
Yes, Jirou-kun loving me is of course a lie.
And it's also a lie that he is dating that girl, Usami-san.
But why?
That is because...
It was to protect me...
I'm sorry to have troubled you, Jirou.
Quit it, Konoe.
I was doing it out of my own will.
Right, Jirou-kun.
For this matter, you have a significant portion of the blame.
Yes. I'm sorry to have caused this misunderstanding.
So then let me reintroduce her to you.
This is Usami Masamune. She is a friend of mine.
I see.
If you are Jirou's friend, then you will be my friend as well.
Subaru-sama...
Nice to meet you.
Oh that's unfair, Usamin-sempai!
I will be dancing with Konoe-sempai!
Oh Kureha-chan, lend me your hand.
In return, I will lend you my brother.
It's especially for you, Usamin-sempai.
Treating me like an object...
Hey, Idiot-chicken.
What?
Will I change too?
No, I mean I want to change too!
I'll fix you.
Huh?
Your fear of women.
Why so suddenly...
Because you and I are friends.
Also from now on just call me by my first name.
Since that's normal for friends.
Now hurry up.
Masamune.
Once more.
Masamune. Masamune. Masamune.
What are you doing?
Let's get along well, Idiot-chicken.
Hey, Jirou.
What?
Let's do it.
What?!
Do what?
Well you know...
What men and women do together...
It's something like studying, shopping or something like that, right?
I know it's going to turn out to be something normal like that.
Close, but wrong!
Huh?
Next episode of Mayochiki, episode 7, "Let's Elope"
So I didn't get that part right.
Let's Elope