Let us assess the situation.
Yesterday, Daitetsu-kun stayed over at Mikuriya's place.
Something happened at that time which changed their relationship.
I won't hand Jin over to you!
A god does not approve of a man such as you!
According to Nagi-sama, it's something that even a god won't forgive.
Daitetsu-kun said that he wouldn't hand over Mikuriya, and Nagi-sama raged.
I get it now!
Daitetsu is the dom.
I knew it, I knew it!
What's that ominous phrase? I don't quite understand, but stop it!
By the way, Senpai...
Why are you naturally following this topic?
Search the net with the click of a mouse.
I've done my homework since the maid cafe!
Why do you have to study that?!
Your soul has been defiled!
What's wrong? It's my freedom to do so.
Isn't this a case where the sub is acting dominant?
Nope! It's the "begging for it" type dom.
I can't believe you're using phrases that I don't know!
"Begging for it" type dom?
"Begging for it" type dom means-
No! You can't teach her that!
Actually, I want to know what it means too.
What's with you, Akiba?
Stop trying to be clean all alone.
This!
Hey, doing that without my permission?!
What's this?
How shameless of you to bring something like this to school.
No, it's for reference!
That's all!
Oh my, what a variety of genres...
Even those targeted at females.
Pretty hardcore.
You've got it wrong!
I'm a person who checks out any artist who draws well regardless of genre!
What are these? Comics?
Tsugumi-chan, why don't you read them?
Hey, wait!
Stop!
Wow, the artwork is beautiful.
Do they sell these in bookstores?
These are self-published books.
This is no good, Senpai! You can't read this!
So cute.
Let... let me read those for a bit.
I can't face Mikuriya anymore!
Sorry, I haven't been making sure that things don't go wrong!
So, have you got the gist of "dom" and "sub"?
Yeah... more or less.
Actually, it's clear as day.
Even so...
It's wrong to look at Jin that way!
As a person...
But...
Can you say for certain that there's nothing between them?
Their closeness is not to be trifled with.
We're talking about Mikuriya who can't handle girls.
The insecurity of his adolescent heart might mess up his ideas of admiration and friendship,
and make him awaken!
No way...
That can't be... Impossible...
You and Daitetsu-kun really get along well.
What do you like about Daitetsu-kun?
What do I like about him?
He has many qualities that I don't have.
If anything...
His body, perhaps?
That?
So something does come to mind!
Since it's the opinion of a childhood friend, it must be true!
No, nothing comes to mind!
There's no way Jin would be interested in a man's body-
I'll go ask Jin in person!
W-Wait a minute, Tsugumi-chan, are you really going to ask him?
Whether Daidetsu-kun and him are...
How can I ask him?!
That whether Nagi is angry because Jin and Daitetsu-kun are a homosexual couple?!
Tsugumi-chan, keep your volume down.
That's not right, I want to find out the reason for their quarrel...
Homo, she said?
Homo? With Mikuriya-kun?
I guess this kind of stuff happens!
Even though they look like that...
I don't want to think about it.
Morning. We're really in the rainy season.
G-Good morning, Mikuriya!
It's the source of the rumor!
Mikuriya-kun is...
Everyone seems to be acting strangely.
They're cold towards me...
Has Nagi done something again?
She's always up to something when I'm not looking.
Her aura isn't normal. As I thought, she's...
Excuse me, but I don't swing that way!
Woah, so it's true!
I heard he's quiet, but skillful!
And he has a beast hidden within!
How did things end up like this?
It's all my fault!
Your mind's so full of Jin-kun.
That's right, let me bring you to a good place.
It's the perfect place for you right now!
The perfect place?
There.
Oh.
A customer I don't see often.
I'll get going then.
Eh?! W-
I finally got released from my part-time job.
I was looking forward to listening to confessions again, but all I get is this rainy sky.
I was troubled by the lack of customers.
Welcome, troubled sheep.
Come, confess your sins!
Are you not troubled by something?
Not at all.
Liar. It's written all over your face.
I can see you're troubled over Jin-kun.
I see... that's troubling.
It's hard to believe he'd be interested in men.
Looks like there's nothing I can do about it.
No hard feelings, but you should give up soon and-
Wrong!
You've got it wrong!
What I'm saying is...
It's so funny!
You're pretty careless,
but the seniors have quite some personality as well!
I understand.
I see, I see!
That's why you came to me.
You want to confess that you called him a homo.
That's not true! I just followed my friend here!
At any rate, it's not like anything good will come out of confessing to you.
I'd apologize to Jin in person if I were to do so.
Your mindset is admirable.
Childhood friends sure are alike.
What?
Just talking to myself. Don't worry about it.
Anyway, you have to clear up the misunderstanding.
You must let everyone know that Jin-kun is a normal boy that likes girls.
What should I do...
It's simple. Just let Jin-kun date a girl.
I'll go out with him.
Then again, it'll affect my activities as an idol.
Oh well, choosing love over that might be good too.
You're fine with it, right? Umm...
What was your name again?
It's Tsugumi! Aoba Tsugumi!
Of course I won't allow it!
In the first place, Jin has the right to choose...
Then, will you date him?
While you're right that the choice lies with him...
But between a familiar childhood friend and I...
Who will Jin-kun choose?
I can't see any reason...
why Jin would refuse her.
Jin will date Zange-chan in order to clear up the misunderstanding.
But it looks to me...
that she's only toying with Jin.
Then, will you date him?
That's the last thing that could happen!
It's Jin we're talking about!
We were together ever since we were children,
and we even played house together.
How can I have feelings for him?
Why does everyone have to see us that way?
After all, his father entrusted him to me.
That's right... I have to protect him.
This is not the time to be talking to Zange-chan.
I have to do something about it.
You've let your guard down, Author-Man.
It can't be... Tanabe-san!
How could you have become my enemy?!
It's a grave mistake to think that all supervisors are allies, Author-Man!
There is a universal truth nobody is able to resist!
Don't tell me that universal truth is...!
That's right; it's the deadline!
No answer.
Normally, he'd be back by now.
I can't believe the Tone Curve has no effect on you!
In that case, eat this!
Anti-alias!
I never thought you're able to use Anti-alias!
You haven't seen anything yet! Take this!
The TV is on...
Automatic Level Correction!
Is he asleep?
Eat your vegetables and be cheerful!
I'm all wet. I'll borrow a towel.
W-Why?!
I'm sorry.
You should've called for me first.
I said I'm sorry...
But isn't it careless of you to leave the door unlocked?
Nagi isn't back yet.
Nagi-san isn't back yet?
Yeah.
I see.
In the past, you've always left your door locked, right?
I rang the doorbell many times, but you never answered.
Yeah... I guess I did...
You were really troublesome back then.
Tsugumi, when we were still in junior high...
I'm back!
Jin!
Oh, it's Tsugumi.
It's a perverted woman.
Perverted woman?
Hey!
I see! Tsugumi, you're really something!
A surprise attack, huh?
I should try it next time.
What are you saying?! Stupid! Pervert! Idiot!
So, how was it?
How? It's ordinary...
What do you mean? Be more specific.
It's different from when he was a child...
You have my attention!
I'm interested too!
Hello! Sorry for intruding.
I sensed the gossip of Jin-kun's embarrassing stories, so I quickly joined in!
Just joking. Of course I came because I want to speak to Jin-kun.
But his embarrassing stories are more important, right?
Now then, please continue!
Are you an idiot?
So, Tsugumi-san, what was Jin-kun like as a child?
I remember there's an album...
He's now different from this?
Human growth is surprisingly fast!
Jin was really cute at that age.
What about now?
He's cute, even now.
I'm sorry, please spare me!
Hmm, Jin's past, eh?
I thought I knew his past, but it's still full of things I don't know of.
I know everything about him.
Now is a good chance to hear about it!
As a child, he was always mistaking his right shoe for his left.
Until he was about seven years old, he couldn't tell the difference between "ne" and "nu" in hiragana.
What a dumb child.
Wow, what's this?!
I fell and accidentally grabbed on to his pants.
Who took the picture?
My mother did.
It's a record of his growth in many ways.
This was during our elementary school graduation trip!
Jin fell into the Five-colored Swamp in Fukushima Prefecture.
What did he do to fall into it?
He was trying to get a picture of himself doing a Rising Dragon Punch at the edge of the swamp,
but he got dizzy!
Boys...
What about his junior high days?
Well, during junior high...
Hold it right there! That's enough!
End of story!
You're boring, Jin!
More embarrassing stories!
I'm confiscating this album!
I bet there are even more embarrassing stories in junior high!
No doubt about that.
He caused a lot of trouble during junior high. He was a delinquent.
Delinquent?
Shirt:
Good at fighting
Superior cat-ears (?)
The hell ya want, bastard?
He's not like that, don't worry.
He was at a rebellious age. He'd raise his fist easily.
Didn't I tell you to stop?
This reminds me. I had something to tell you.
Umm...
Can I ask you something first?
On the question of whether you're a homosexual...
That rumor is totally untrue.
I thought so!
In that case, I propose that I or Tsugumi-san become your girlfriend...
in order to clear up the misunderstanding.
Why am I also included in your plan?
Oh my, do you intend to remain as a bystander?
There's no reason for Tsugumi and Zange-chan to do so much for me.
It has nothing to do with you.
Nothing to do with us?
Don't tell me you haven't told him about the situation yet?
I was just about to...
What?
You see...
The truth is... There's something I need to apologize for.
You too?
What is it?
I caused a lot of trouble for you during junior high.
I want to apologize for that. I'm sorry.
Trouble?
Which one?
Like I said!
I was worried about my old man back then, so I flipped easily...
Oh, that. Why talk about that now?
Don't tell me...
You've always been bothered by that?
He hasn't changed.
You idiot.
Whenever you got mad, I always knew why.
I also knew why you cried or laughed.
So I was never afraid.
You're always you.
That's why it's all right for you to cry or laugh.
Really?
That's right.
I feel better now.
Really? I'm glad to hear that.
Is it such a shock for you?
Now it's your turn.
What do you want to apologize for?
Why you... you're too careless.
I'm sorry! I said it out loud without realizing it!
I'm really sorry about it!
If you think about it, it's only right for Tsugumi to act as his girlfriend.
In order to take responsibility for her actions as well.
But he also has me as a special candidate!
He's lucky!
You won't get bored, I assure you!
I think it's much better than serving Neesama in this house.
Zange-chan, you can't!
I-I'm not implying that I should be his girlfriend instead.
Let him decide then.
Jin-kun.
Who do you choose?
Tsugu-
You're so slow. Hurry up and decide, Jin.
It's never going to end!
I don't think there's a need for you to make a choice, is there?
You just need to show that you like women.
Both of you can hold Jin at the same time.
You're right.
We just need to flirt in public.
The person inside says it isn't a bad idea.
What? The person inside?
Here, Jin. Say "aah".
Eat mine too! This is a dish I'm proud of!
Look, it's Mikuriya-kun!
He's not only interested in men...
He's flirting with his childhood friend!
Even Zange-chan!
Everyone's stares are scary.
He goes after anyone in sight. I can't forgive him!
How's it? Is it tasty?
It's delicious...
Not only octopus, I've also prepared crab and dolphin sausage cuts!
This green pepper covered kneaded fried chicken is delicious even when it's cold.
My boiled and dipped vegetables...
are also delicious when cold.
It's still cold to begin with.
Have some pickled lotus root too.
It'll leave a nice feeling in your mouth!
There's something on your mouth...
There's something on your cheek here, too...
That's unfa... I mean, aren't you going too far?
I'm sorry, I lost my handkerchief, so it's an emergency measure.
I'll wipe it.
No! I'm in charge of the right side of his body!
I won't allow that!
That's unfair!
Yes, that's how it should be, Jin.
He's certainly the epitome of a playboy!
What's going on? What happened, Jin?
Jin will eat my boxed lunch!
Mine is more nutritionally balanced!
Mine is balanced too!
Order, in order please...
You only have boiled and dipped spinach!
I also have fried eggs!
A triangle-relationship, a square relationship, or a five-sided relationship?
Mikuriya is something to be feared!
He's even more than we had imagined.
You can't set up the flags like that!
Where have you gone wrong, Mikuriya?!
Is there anything I can do to help you?!
Oh! Another intertwining string found here!
A development I won't get tired of.
Mikuriya!
It went for the worst!
Strange...
On the next episode of Kannagi-
I'm going to sing my lungs out!