Newspaper!
It's the latest issue of Youkai's newspaper!
The latest issue just came out not long ago.
Please read it.
Give me a copy please.
Me too.
Strategy for final exams, eh?
The latest issue gives a good feeling.
Yeah, this is all thanks to everyone's effort.
Yay, all the newspaper are distributed!
Yahoo, The news report critics are good this time too.
Hey, how about we hold a celebration?
Like bring some snacks and such.
That's a great idea, Moka-san.
Agreed!
Huh? Where's Gin-senpai?
He was over here just now...
He must've gone to harass some female students, right?
Isn't this report interesting?
Actually, the newspaper club is recruiting some beautiful girls for modeling, wanna try it?
Just as she said.
So it's okay if we don't invite him.
He's an enemy of women!
Other than that, how are we going to hold celebration?
First, let's go to the store and buy snacks.
I want to drink some beverages.
Alcohol is a no though.
Well then, we will bring our stuffs to the clubroom after class is over.
And let's play Bingo after that.
You guys sure get along well.
The newspaper club that is...
Getting close with one another...I don't really understand that.
Hey! What's that suppose to mean?
Newspaper.
Are there any left?
It's a bit tattered, but if you don't mind...
Here.
What is it?
So you're Tsukune-kun?
You're cuter than I thought.
Bye then.
Who was that just now, Tsukune?
Ah, someone I don't know...
But she kinda pisses me off.
Yup, yup!
Now now,
Putting that aside, let's party hard after school.
Yeah!
Kurono-san.
Here.
Satou-kun.
Shirayuki-san.
Shirayuki-san?
Shirayuki-san is absent today too...
The girl from this morning...
Shirayuki-san, you finally came?
Well then, let me introduce her to the class again.
She's Shirayuki Mizore-san.
Due to some reasons she hasn't been coming to school,
So everyone, please get along with her.
Eh?
Then, let's meet up in the clubroom after we finish buying everything.
You better be looking forward to my handmade sweets.
Kurumu-chan, you're too close to Tsukune!
Hey, wait!
Who's there?
Hi...
You are...Shirayuki-san...
Anything I can do for you?
I read it; the news that you wrote is interesting as usual.
As usual?
Look.
When I was away from school, I always requested Nekonome-sensei to send me copies of Youkai's newspaper.
I've been gathering your articles into this scrapbook.
Oh I see, I'm happy...
How is it? I even wrote some comments about them.
What is this?! There's some strange and small words written in here!
I love the news reports that you write.
You always write from a weak person's view, which I can relate to.
Your personality and way of thinking is just like mine.
W-Wait...
You must be lonely, right? I also know how it feels...
Nekonome-sensei.
Yes?
There's a student in your class that's been refusing to come to school.
If I remember correctly, she's called Shirayuki.
It seems like she started to attend school today.
Yes, Kotsubo-sensei.
You'd better be careful.
Meow?
Refusing to come to school from the new term would basically mean that she has some major problems.
According to reports, due to her personality,
This has been a recurring problem since junior high.
Anyway,
I'd like you to watch her and not let the other students get any bad influences from her, Nekonome-sensei.
Yes...
Did you see it, Tsukune? The stone just skipped nine times.
Umm... Shirayuki-san...
I have to return to the clubroom soon.
No! Your throwing is too bad that you still can't make it skip more than 4 times, right?
It's already time for the party, and Moka-san is waiting for me.
Do you want to go back to that collusive club of yours?
No, rather, you just want to see Akashiya Moke, right?
If you were to go, I don't know what I'll do to that woman.
Shirayuki...san.
All you need to do is just be mine, Tsukune.
Tsukune sure is late...
Tsukune?
Shirayuki...san?
Tsukune won't be coming no matter how much longer you wait.
What are you...?
You're an eyesore.
If you don't exist, Tsukune will be mine.
What's with her hands? They're as cold as ice.
Stop!
Unfortunately, the "me" here is just an ice doll.
Isn't it well made?
Sorry, but please disappear.
Akashiya Moka.
All in order to fulfill my desire.
Tsukune!
This is...
I won't let you run away.
You are...!
I'm a Snow Woman,
and I can freely control ice.
What the heck is this?
Tsukune, we were destined to meet.
Because we're both loners, fate brought us together.
We will definitely understand each other. We'll warm our cold hearts.
Damn it!
You sure are persistent,
but as long as your body is frozen, there's nowhere you can go.
When that happens, you'll be all mine.
If this continues...
Tsukune...!
Tsukune!
Why, you are...?
By pure luck, I was able to save Moka in the nick of time.
But thanks to that, the cake mixed with love potion that Tsukune was supposed to eat was completely wasted!
Tsukune!
Don't hinder me!
Wait, the spikes!
Tsukune!
Are you all right, Moka-san?
Those who hinder the true love between Tsukune and me, should just all disappear!
Especially you, Akashiya Moka, you're the only one I can't...
No...
This is going to far, Shirayuki-san.
Why are you stopping me?
If it's you, you should understand how it feels to be lonely, just like me.
No! I'm not alone!
Tsukune...
That's why...
Don't tell me... you are rejecting my feelings?
Tsukune!
Shirayuki-san...
Where did she go?
Wait, the ice is-
Hey, isn't it funny?
Kotsubo-sensei, see you!
See you.
Be careful on your way back.
What are we going to do next?
Let's go shopping!
I want to eat cake.
Geez... students these days develop too quickly...
How outrageous.
Hey, is there someone still around?
You are...
Darn! The long awaited cake got all mushy!
Really...
But, this is pretty bad.
Even though the atmosphere became miserable,
It's still a celebration...
Damn it...
You sound like an old man.
There seems to be a commotion outside.
Ah, everyone, you were all still here?
Nekonome-sensei?
Did something happen?
Well... Shirayuki-san is in trouble now...
Shirayuki-san froze Kotsubo-sensei?
That's right...
He was found quickly, so his life isn't in danger, but...
B-But is there any proof that Shirayuki-san did it?
What proof do you want?
When we found him, Kotsubo-sensei himself said she did it.
Ririko-sensei...
She's an infamous problem child in the first place.
We should expel her as soon as possible.
B-But...
Where's Shirayuki-san now?
The entire faculty is looking for her right now,
And of course, she's getting expelled as soon as she's found.
Besides that, why did Shirayuki-san do such a thing to Kotsubo-sensei who's unrelated to this...
She must have been throwing tantrums after being rejected by Tsukune-san.
True... With that kind of personality, it's definitely possible.
It's my...
Tsukune?
It's my fault.
If I didn't reject her so harshly...
What are you talking about?
You don't have to worry about such things.
Shirayuki-san's just getting what she deserves.
But...
Nekonome-sensei!
I'll search for Shirayuki-san too!
D-Don't do it, Tsukune.
I couldn't tell Shirayuki-san something that I wanted to tell her.
I'm going!
Tsukune!
Excuse me-
What's with him, getting so worked up...
Ah, Gin-senpai...
Is there something you want?
Don't look at me like that!
I even brought some gutsy scoop photographs.
Gutsy?
Scoop?
Shirayuki-san!
Tsukune?
Shirayuki-san, Kotsubo-sensei is fine somehow.
It's still not too late,
so come apologize with me, all right?
You only did it in the spur of the moment, right?
If you repent, I don't think they'll expel you.
Shirayuki-san...?
Shirayuki-san?
You're too much, Tsukune.
I thought only you would be able to understand me...
Nobody...
Nobody understands me...
Why?
Why, why?!
WHY?!
Tsukune!
Moka-san!
This isn't good! Shirayuki-san actually didn't do anything wrong!
Huh?
Gin-senpai's photographs cleared everything up!
Look!
This is!
Kotsubo-sensei tried to do something despicable to Shirayuki-san while she was depressed!
That's why Shirayuki-san protected herself...
So that's what it was...
And yet, I...
I'm sorry, Shirayuki-san!
I didn't believe in you, Shirayuki-san...
Stay away...
Stay away!
I'm... lonely...
No one really understands me...
Loneliness...
Tsukune didn't understand me either...
Is this... Shirayuki-san's inner voice?
Everyone should just get buried under pure white ice!
What a terrible chill...
Shirayuki-san!
Hold on, Shirayuki-san... I'll pull you up right now!
It's all right, Tsukune.
Lonely... I'm so lonely...
Someone like me will inevitably live alone...
I...
I have something I didn't get to tell you yet, Shirayuki-san!
Something you didn't tell me?
I'm not alone anymore!
But that's because I made precious friends!
So what?
That's why...
Be my friend, Shirayuki-san!
If you died, there's no way you could be friends with me anymore!
Lies... What friends?
It's just a collusive relationship.
True friendship would be to die together.
Together...
I can't...I can't even control them anymore!
Tsukune!
Moka-san!
This is...
Once the rosary on her chest is removed,
The vampire blood within Moka will awaken.
Sorry for the wait.
Do not hinder me.
Do you want to die too?
That's right...disappear.
Worthless puppets.
The only ones that'll disappear...
Are you guys!
No way... How?
They were created from supernatural energy.
That's why they got dispelled by an even stronger force.
Thank you for explaining it in simple terms!
M-Moka-san...
Stop getting me involved.
T-Thank you, Moka-san...
I'm not going to thank you...
You snowy twerp.
If you wanted to die, why not try to fulfill something in your life first?
More like, your kick almost killed me...
This week's winner- no, even if there isn't one, took only 86 seconds.
Good work, ya'll.
However, thanks to everyone, Shirayuki-san won't be expelled!
Eh, w-why is it so cold suddenly!
W-When did you...!
Your hair...
I cut it short... Does it suit me?
Very much so!
Even though you're exaggerating, I've decided to completely make myself over.
I thought I'd start from my hairstyle first...
You're pretty photogenic too.
Let me take a photo...
Come to think of it,
you actually managed to take those photographs!
That's right,
thanks to those photographs, the accusations against Shirayuki-san were cleared...
I'm always looking around the school for scoops, that's why!
How's that? I have to maintain the reputation of "Newspaper Club Chairman", don't I?
Hmm, these photographs...
So that's your true intention!
Speaking of which, if you helped out while taking photographs, wouldn't the problem be solved?!
My, my.
But isn't this great, Tsukune?
Yep, I got saved by Moka-san yet again...
No way...
Somehow, I feel thirsty now that I'm relieved...
W-Wait, Moka-san....
Tsukune...
Stare...
Kappuchu~!!
Don't look!
Sine... Cosine... Tangent...
What happened to you, Tsukune?
Tsukune became smart!
Eh?
Next week, Mathematics and a Vampire,
and a kappuchu for you!