The Game Research Society
How about this?
[ August 27th ]
Oh, Ruri-chan's clothes fell off.
Why do we have to come all the way to school to play galge during summer vacation?
Well, I'm afraid that if we played it at my house, my parents might find out.
Suzutsuki-san!
Summer vacation has already started, so what brings you here?
I want you guys to make me a game.
Oh, a role-playing fighting game.
There is no hope in 3D anymore. The world will be saved by 2D.
When do you need it by?
The deadline is August 28th.
In other words, I need it by tomorrow.
That's impossible.
Subaru.
What should we do?
A-Actually, I didn't come all the way here to ask you because I wanted to!
That's like, the best 3D angel ever!
Ojou-sama...
Tomorrow, okay?
Tomorrow is the day.
Ah, I can't believe this! Hug me, hug me more!
This one's the best! With this, tomorrow will be perfect.
All right, tomorrow it is!
Let's eat
[ August 28th ]
Guten Morgen!
Mornin', Nii-san!
This'll be fine.
I'll be heading off now.
Kureha!
O' Hello, Nii-san!
I'm leaving for a while.
I won't be back until this evening.
Gotcha.
Happy Birthday!!
Thank you!
Sakamachi Kureha has turned sixteen today.
Congratulations.
Usami-senpai!
Okay.
Amazing.
Where did you get these from?
They're home cooked.
Did you make all of them, senpai?
I chose the menu and the ingredients.
You don't have to add unnecessary details.
All right.
Well, don't let it get cold. Eat up.
Yes, let's eat!
It's delicious.
As for that, Usami-senpai, you're very good at cooking.
It's nothing special. I live alone, so I have to.
I just heard some sort of dragging noise from that corner.
Well, it seems that "things" do get in this room.
What?
You mean something like a poltergeist?
Yes.
The girl that was living here before was dumped by her boyfriend.
Depressed, she knocked her head on the sink and got her hand bitten by her dog, and... and right at the very end-
Please, stop! I'm terrible with scary stories!
It's not that big of a deal.
The television just turns itself on sometimes, that's all.
I'm scared!
It doesn't hurt you, so it's fine.
Now, since we're all excited, it is time to open the long-awaited presents.
Clap, please.
This is sort of scary.
Glasses?
You look good in that.
The rim's curvature is okay.
The bridge is stable.
And there's nothing wrong with either temple.
The dazzle of the lenses and the bridge!
This pair of glasses has strong exorcising powers. It's able to exorcise any spirit.
Really?
Yes. If you have this, there is nothing to be afraid of.
Amazing!
Thank you for giving me these glasses. This is now the best present.
You're welcome.
"Kureha-chan, happy birthday."
Something along those lines...
Kya, Konoe-senpai!
Usami-senpai, did you make this yourself?
Yes. I am a textile arts club member, after all.
Thank you very much!
I will sleep with Konoe-senpai from tonight onwards.
Attention, please.
Now then, it's time for the second part of your present.
What could that be?
Take it away, Usami-senpai.
Wait. Are we really doing this?
Of course.
Script by Narumi Nakuru, "Memories of Class" version.
"Jirou-kin and Barusu, A Late Summer Night's Memories."
Let the show begin!
Whoa!
Barusu. Oh, how hard it is to believe.
That you are here in my arms.
Jirou-kin...
Please, hug me tighter.
Whoa...
Barusu!
Even if this is our last night together. My love for you is eternal.
Wow!
Wait, Nakuru. We're overdoing it.
Please bear with it for now. After all, this is Kureha-chan's birthday present.
J-Jirou-kin, I too, want to make you and your glasses my love forever.
And so, the two lovers made a promise with a kiss.
As expected of Usami-senpai.
What do you mean by Barusu and Jirou-kin?
It's obvious that we're portraying Idiot-Chicken and Subaru here.
Oh, is that so?
You can't see it?!
Attention, please.
Now, time for the third stage of your present.
We will move to the next venue.
The next venue?
Welcome back, Milady.
Kya, Konoe-senpai!
This is the next venue that we mentioned, Maid Heaven.
Two more years to go before you can watch 18+ hentai, Kureha-chan.
Congrats.
Did the two of you know it was my birthday?
Yes.
Wait, Nakuru. Why here of all places?
It's because...
Milady has reserved this place for the day. Please have as much fun as you want.
Here, Usagi-chan.
I wanted to see you in a maid's outfit one more time, my little rabbit.
Stop calling me "Usagi-chan"!
Now, please go ahead, Milady.
Then everyone, shall we begin?
Sure!
Here we go...
Happy birthday to you,
From me to you,
Happy, happy birthday.
Kureha-chan!
This is my present to you.
A gazing sheep!
Thank you very much, Konoe-senpai.
To meet you with a smile.
For this moment,
Your wishes will come true.
The meeting itself,
Is the best present.
Now, shall we go somewhere,
To a beautiful place.
Happy birthday to you,
From me to you,
Happy, happy birthday.
Congratulations.
Everyone, thank you very much.
What's wrong?
I suddenly remembered my eighth birthday...
[ 8 years ago ]
No! No! No!
Stop making a fuss.
Daddy!
I want to see Daddy. I want to see him.
Kureha, Ku-re-ha!
Here's your present. Happy birthday.
Yay! I will name this bear, Bro-Bear!
This is the best present ever, Nii-san!
My brother bought my present with all of the money from his savings.
Such a wonderful brother.
That Idiot-Chicken...
That's a nice memory, isn't it?
Yes.
Ahhh.
All right, my type is curry!
A lovely kiss for you, master.
I'm going to blow you away.
You can't wear panties as long as I am here.
I always wanted to play a game like this where I was the main character.
Luckily, I knew people who could make this.
I bet you forced them into making it through some evil scheme of yours.
Even so, why is that Idiot-Chicken is hardly wearing anything?
N-Naked?!
Well, to be precise, he is wearing underwear.
It is my brother, so it can't be helped.
Have no fear, the glasses are here.
I see.
Cats ears and striped thigh-high socks, attack!
Glasses and garter belt, attack!
That person does look like pervert.
For him to appear in a game hardly wearing anything, well...
It's all about being young and youthful.
I am not a cycle!
Jirou's only wearing his boxers and chasing his sister inside a convenience store...
What a development!
I don't understand what is what anymore.
Now!
Ah, I lost.
You want to take me on? You're sixteen years too early kiddo!
Jirou.
I have to let him win once, at least just in a game.
So harsh.
Onee-sama, let me have one more go!
Sure.
I won't lose this time.
Today is the best birthday I've ever had.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
That playground...
What about it?
Well, during my tenth birthday...
[ 6 years ago ]
I hate you, Mommy!
Toubara Park
Mother's waiting for us, let's go back.
It is your birthday party.
Nii-san!
I still remember his face when he came to pick me up.
I was so happy.
I see.
Jirou-kun is a good brother, isn't he?
Yes.
On my twelfth birthday...
We played video games the entire day.
On my thirteenth, we brought ice-cream at a dairy farm.
My fourteenth birthday was all about fireworks.
You seem to remember all of your birthdays.
I do.
How about last year?
What happened?
Last year...
[ 1 year ago ]
Today is, today is... yes.
The twenty-eighth of August.
Nii-san, where are you going?
Kurose says he got some tickets to a live show.
Man, we're so lucky. That's a platinum ticket.
Later, sis! I'm off!
Nii-san...
I'm back!
Welcome back, Nii-san.
Ain't this t-shirt great?
This was one of the last ones they had. I'm going to take good care of it.
Nii-san.
W-W-What is it?
You're so mean! You forgot your sister's birthday!
You're an idiot!
Sorry, Kureha. It's my fault.
Idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot!
Wait, please wait!
I'm sorry!
You idiot! You idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot!
That was what happened.
It can't be helped since Jirou-kun forgot about his only sister's birthday.
This year, my mother is abroad, so she's not home.
But I had everyone celebrate it with me,
so I'm really happy.
Say Kureha-chan.
Why don't you come to my house?
Why don't you stop being Jirou-kun's little sister and become my little sister instead?
What?
A Jirou that doesn't care about his sister's feelings has no right to be a big brother.
But Ojou-sama, isn't there something called a 'mistake'?
Then, why don't you become his little sister if you want defend him this much.
If I had to, then I'd rather be his little brother than his little sister.
I see.
Then again, it was my brother who came to my middle school opening ceremony in the place of my mother.
He also said, "It suits you very nicely" when I wore my high school uniform for the first time.
Furthermore, he's my partner when I train.
He's always treated me with kindness.
I should become his strength. After all, I'm already sixteen.
That is why, even if he forgot my birthday,
it's all right.
He always pays attention to me all the other times.
Thank you very much for today.
I will have the rest of the presents delivered later.
I wonder if Jirou-kun remembered his sister's birthday this year.
I'm sure that it'll all be okay.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Nii-san, can it be? Could it be?
Kureha, happy birthday.
Yay!
Say, can I open it?
Yes.
Yay, a big stuffed doll.
A cute, white doggy.
Sorry Kureha, but that's a polar bear.
Yay!
Thank you. Thank you, Nii-san.
Thank goodness.
You idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot!
I promised myself after seeing Kureha so sad that I would never make the same mistake again.
Kureha, sorry about last year.
Nii-san, this just might be the happiest birthday ever.
I'm so happy.
Say Nii-san,
I kind of feel like hugging you all of a sudden.
Can I hug you for a while?
Kureha.
I love you Nii-san!
It still came down to this.
In the end, HAPPY BIRTHDAY, MY SISTER!
Subterranean Rabbit
"Subterranean Rabbit"? What's with this weird title?
Here, a present for you too.
I thought it was something way shadier than this.
Come on, try harder.
Come on.
That Suzutsuki Kanade, like hell I'm going to lose!
I did it!
What is this?
Let go of me. There's only enough space for me.
Oh my, what an unsightly heart.
Game over, Usagi-chan!
Suzutsuki Kanade!
Ojou-sama, may I hug you?
Subaru, stop it.
Please! I want to plant this face of mine onto your chest and never move.
While I'm at it, I also want to kiss you.
I want to smell the tantalizing perfume of your ebony hair forever.
You can't.
I can't hold it in much longer!
Subaru, are you're also taken in by this side of me?
Everyone who hears that will get taken in as well.
The spell of the demon, the calling of magic, the cursed word.
That is...
Next episode of Mayo Chiki...
The 11th Story, Nyu.
Nyu!