I love you!
I've always been in love with you!
I wonder why people fall in love with one another...
I want to understand the secrets of love...
Please fondle them!
11th of September
Have you seen my treasure yet?
Yeah.
I highly recommend the girl with glasses.
Look! There's also a picture of her without glasses!
Don't you think she looks sexy like that?
Well, yeah.
She turns into a complete hottie whenever she takes off her glasses.
God this is so hot! She's Captain Hot!
You think so?
Anyway, why am I doing this?
What's this book?
What's wrong?
I found a boy's love book in my room...
So you really are...
Someone's here.
I'm going to hang up.
Hi. Bye.
Why are you closing the door on me?!
Let go or I'm going to call the police!
Why?!
You're a true pervert!
Are you trying to pass me off as an intruder?!
Now that it has come to this...
Help! I'm going to be kidnapped and imprisoned!
Hey you!
What do you want? Do you want to speak with Kureha?
No, I don't have any business with her today.
Anyway, you sure live in a nice house.
I don't know what to say to that...
Your room has a nice atmosphere.
I just heard something I can't let pass...
Ah... When I think about how fluffy your bed is...
How the hell do you know how comfortable my bed is?!
Well then, let's get to the point.
Hey!
I came here today because I have something to discuss with you.
Something to discuss?
You know, it's...
10th of September
Ah, what is it-
Here it comes...
Let's go!
Who are you?!
Unforgivable... How dare you look at me while I take a bath!
My glasses, which have a refractive index of 1.60,
a super water-repellent
multi-coated spherical surface,
visible-light transmittance of around 12-35%,
and a celluloid frame that guards against 99.9% of all UV rays!
Oh?
Those look like really valuable paintings.
Why are we here?
Would Subaru-sama like a scone set?
I didn't come here just to leisurely drink tea!
Where are the photos you took earlier?
Unfortunately, these aren't good enough to sell!
You intended to sell them?
We had an Overlooking Party meeting today.
If I don't earn some cash now, I won't... I won't...
I won't have enough cash to make and publish my own doujinshi!
Hey!
Oh, my my!
That is troublesome!
Ojou-sama!
I heard your story over the phone with Subaru.
Sorry!
Please scold her as well!
If only you had let me know...
I want to help you!
Thank you very much!
Ojou-sama!
Come on, Subaru, it's only a few pictures!
And in return, I want you to stop abusing my butler with your photo shoots.
As long as it's within my power, I will fulfill your request.
Yes!
Now, now! No pushing, no pushing!
This, please!
I'll take this one!
Wait right there, I want this picture!
Let go!
With this, my plan is coming along perfectly!
But...
I was in a slump and I couldn't get more than half of it done!
Is this an entire volume, Narunaru?
It's too thick. The stapler won't budge.
That's why I wanted your help!
Shouldn't you wait until you finish the volume before you sell it?
I can't do that!
I have fans who are waiting for my new book!
Fans?
Even I have a fan club!
But, honestly, it's a bit embarrassing.
Even their greeting has my name in it.
Their greeting?
Three! Two! One!
Nakuru, Nakuru!
Um, say something.
I don't want to do that!
Now, if we aren't able to finish this by tomorrow, the plan for the whole event will be be ruined!
Three! Two! One!
Nakuru, Nakuru!
Don't do that!
Sheesh, why am I even doing this?
Weren't you the one who flew in when I said I would pay you for your work?
I'll show my gratitude to Kureha-chan as well.
You mean these photos of Konoe-senpai are payment?
They're very precious off-shots.
They're great, Narunaru!
I would do anything to get my hands on these!
Is there anything else I can help you with?
Well, if you're offering...
Come in! My brother's not home because he's at Kurase-senpai's house today!
Really?
I wonder who's the Seme and who's the Uke.
No way! It's my first time in a boy's room!
The smell of a real boy!
The waste bin of a real boy...
And these are...
A real boy's porn magazines!
You Idiot-Chicken!
It seems that even he has an interest in women.
Triangle Love! This'll do!
I'll give him this magazine as thanks for letting me have a look inside his room.
Man, I'm out of ideas!
We still have a ways to go.
Wait up! How many do we need to make?
I need to borrow your shower.
Ah, then I'll get you a towel.
At this rate we won't be ready by tomorrow morning.
Should I call for more help?
Su-Subaru-sama?
And Suzutsuki Kanade as well?
I asked them for a little help!
Here!
That's our Konoe-senpai!
Thank you very much!
Good for you. You finished it on time.
Yes, I even finished the volume.
Is this the entire volume?
I wasn't able to write the continuation very well...
Well, we're going to head home now.
Let's go, Subaru.
Yes.
Ah! Wait, please!
Do you still have something for us?
I have something I want to ask Subaru-sama.
Me?
Well... I have something I'm confused about.
I don't know much about BL novels.
It's not about BL...
I don't know much about glasses either.
No, it's not about glasses either!
Hm? Then what are you worried about?
You're not being frank!
Uhm, it's...
Say it clearly.
Wait... Please wait a second.
A shocking truth.
A wild Narunaru appears!
Hidden fact.
The likes of which have never been seen before!
The real criminal's confession.
Something's wrong!
It's all right. I'll figure something out myself.
What do you mean?
Don't just stop halfway through when you're trying to say something.
Come now...
Morning is just a few hours away, now.
Let's do our best for tomorrow's exhibit.
Hey, you!
I'm good at writing fiction!
Jirou... I've always been in...
11th of September
Thank you for your purchase!
Why are we dressed like this?
Disguises are fundamental to stalking, Usami-senpai!
We need to blend in with the crowd to deceive our target.
That doesn't quite sound right.
I wonder what Narunaru's worried about.
Sakamachi...
She won't even tell us...
I wish I could be of some help.
We're all sold out now!
That was fast!
Three! Two! One!
Nakuru, Nakuru!
Thank you very much.
It might be more profitable than working part time.
I wonder if you think she looks cool.
Not a chance!
Following her... into a book store.
Anime shop.
Game store.
She doesn't seem that much different than usual.
No.
Haven't you noticed?
The ones she bought earlier were
boy-girl romance stories.
In other words, they weren't BL.
Exactly.
And on top of that...
Could this be, l-l-love?
Oh, if it isn't Kureha-can and Usami-senpai!
What are you doing?
Oh, hi there!
Stal-
We were just walking around because we're bored.
Huh... bra...
You sure have a large bust.
We'll find a size that'll fit you nicely.
We also have a full range of volumes.
It seems like they got bigger again.
Don't tell me this is what she was worried about...
It can't be, can it?
No!
Were you that worried about me?
Hm.
I want to be your strength when you're worried.
Kureha-chan!
Just say it.
We'll listen to anything you have to say.
Usami-senpai!
Then please hear me out.
Here!
Thank you!
Well, then. What's on your mind?
Um...
Hm?
Kureha-chan, Usami-senpai, what do you think of my bust?
I can't ask you two for advice after all.
Then who do you want to ask?
Senpai...
If it's him, then...
11th of September
And so I came to you for advice.
Damn that was long!
I mean... You were the one who put that BL book in my room?
Ah. There's a passage that's written exactly the way I imagined it, so please read it.
So what did you want to ask...?
Please go on a date with me tonight.
What?
I'm surprised that you agreed to it.
The date.
I thought you would just say no right away.
Thank you very much.
I took this chance to wear my extra-long cat ears.
You lost me.
The plan for today's date is a picnic under the sun.
It's already evening, you know.
Let's hold hands.
What the, you...!
Could this be your first date?
Nya-nya-nya-nya-nyaaa.
Oh crap!
Let's sit over there.
I packed a boxed lunch.
It looks good.
Thank you very much!
Ah, I know! I'll feed you myself!
Wha...?
Here! Ah...
Hehe, you just said "ahum".
I won't be tricked!
She's just a huge glasses junkie.
No matter how cute she looks, she's still an abnormal pervert!
Here!
Ah...
So, why do you need my advice?
Actually, I'm in a slump.
A slump?
In what way?
BL novels...
She brought it up! What the hell do you plan to do to me this time?
There's a reason for this!
I have a lot on my mind.
So I can't concentrate on my writing.
Hm?
Please don't laugh at me.
Sure.
What do you think when you see my chest?
Hey, what's with that cynical expression?
You see, there was an incident a while back.
An incident?
Someone confessed to me.
A confession?! Not a complaint?!
No!!!
It was a boy! My classmate!
He's someone who I don't talk to much.
But suddenly he said that he loved me and that he wanted me to go out with him.
Hmm. So what did you do?
I rejected him, of course.
I had already decided.
Decided what?
I had decided to give all of my high school life to BL novels.
So what does that have to do with your chest?
Honestly speaking, I didn't know
why he confessed to me...
I know I'm not one to say it, but I am not the type who is very popular among boys.
And so I wondered several things about myself...
I see...
Senpai!
What?
Please fondle my breasts!
WHY?!
I heard a rumor!
That... that... Breasts become smaller if you fondle them!
Where the hell did you hear that?
Am I wrong?
More importantly, why do I have to fondle your breasts?
I have a complex about my chest.
I'd like for them to be smaller.
Don't worry, everyone has one or two complexes.
Everyone?
I also have something that doesn't seem like it can be fixed.
You too?
Overall, males like to drool over big breasts,
but they won't fall in love with you for your chest.
Then please prove it!
Please prove with your body that boys don't fall in love with our breasts!
Prove it with your body!
If not, then... then...
I can't concentrate on writing my novels.
What kind of logic is that?
I asked you for advice because I thought you could help me.
I thought you would be able to save me.
If I bear through this,
you'll be able to get over your complex and stop worrying.
Yes.
I understand.
Come at me!
Here I go!
I can't give in!
Don't give in, Nakuru!
You're awesome, Senpai!
What the hell are we doing?
I'm rubbing my breasts all over you, but you're still fine.
You might be BL material!
No way in hell!
No!
Please don't stare at me so much.
She's cute!
Glasses, glasses...
This is... this is...
Gap Moe?!
Ah, I feel relieved now.
Thank you, Senpai.
Well, I'm happy to hear that.
Yes.
It feels like my glasses fell off for good.
This is also thanks to you...
What the... what the...
What is this?
He looks cooler than usual.
What's wrong?
I'm leaving!
Hey! Clean this up!
I said wait!
No!
Why!
Please leave me alone!
Nakuru!
What... what am I supposed to do with this?
No!
Help!