Oh my! This must be what they call a karaoke box.
What, Nagi-sama? It's your first time doing karaoke?
Yes, it's really unusual.
Haven't you ever gone with your sister?
I haven't, since our interests are different.
Rather, why are you here?
Why of course, because Jin-kun is here.
Umm, don't get too close to me.
Hey, get off of him. He doesn't like it.
Somehow you're so popular that it even seems deliberate, Mikuriya.
But why don't you look happy?
Oh, has someone entered songs already?
That's me. Since we can sing all we want, it will be in place of a BGM.
The first one has got to be this one!
Uh... this is in many ways... yeah...
When was that song from?
I'm sure it was before we were born.
Like I said, how long are you guys going to be standing there?
Come on and sit down already!
What is this book about?
We choose the songs that we want to sing out of the titles written here.
Jin-kun, how do you read this singer's name?
Where?
This one.
Well... hmm Ichiyao...
Sorry, I'm not really good with things like this.
What is this...
They're swirling hard, a lot of things.
Yes.
Well anyway, this karaoke is supposed to strengthen our friendship.
Everyone, be frank and lively!
Friendship amongst these members?
Quit chattering! It's a waste of time!
Who's singing first?
Geez, you guys can't decide!
Rock paper scissors, got it?
The losers start putting in songs!
So then,
Rock paper scissors!
あの日坂道で心跳ねた
ano hi sakamichi de kokoro haneta
That day, my heart skipped a beat on that hilly road.
日差しでじわじわ焼ける
hizashi de jiwajiwa yakeru
I am slowly scorched by the sunshine
夢の出来事にほっぺつねった
yume no dekigoto ni hoppe tsunetta
I pinched my cheek for what happened in my dream.
アナタの唇感じ、手の震え隠し
anata no kuchibiru kanji te no furue kakushi
Feeling your lips, hiding my shaking hands
精一杯の平気なふりの顔
seiippai no heiki na furi no kao
I tried my best to act nonchalant.
汗がキラリ光る
ase ga kirai hikaru
The sweat sparkled.
いつも不意打ちなあなた
itsumo fuiuchi na anata
You always strike without notice.
あたしだって意地があるから
atashi datte iji ga aru kara
But I have my pride, you know.
でもねいつか素直になりたい
demo ne itsuka sunao ni naritai
But someday, I want to become honest.
まだ眩しいあなた
mada mabushii anata
You are still dazzling.
もっと自然に近づきたいの
motto shizen ni chikazukitai no
I want to get close to you in a more natural way.
力ずくじゃ味気ない
chikara zuku ja ajike nai
But taking you by force is too boring.
でもね、これはこれで悪くない
demo ne kore wa kore de warukunai
But you see, this isn't bad after all.
ずっと隣にいてね
zuttotonari ni ite ne
Always be by my side.
アタシ、アナタの一番星になりたい
atashi anata no ichibanboshi ni naritai
I want to be the first star that twinkles in your evening sky.
A girl who isn't used to singing trying so hard is nice!
Takako, you're a pervert.
Well, thank you for listening.
Gosh, I hate being the first one up...
So, who's next?
Jin-kun, what kind of songs do you like?
Nothing in particular...
So then,
Next is Daitetsu-kun.
I've never heard Daitetsu-kun's singing before.
Come to think of it, neither have I.
So then, has god given two talents at once?
Let us hear it then.
Then, a ballad.
I believe you forever,
風の中を二人いつまで
kaze no naka wo futari itsu made
the two of us, in the wind, forever...
Amazing.
He's naturally good.
It's a charming bass.
This man is loved by the god of art!
まるでシネマのよう
marude shinema no you
It's like in the movies.
Is he getting Muse all for himself?
昨日の夢のよう
kinou no yume no you
It's like yesterday's dream.
幼い明日の日の
osanai asu no hi no
It's like memories
He's great.
記憶のように
kioku no you ni
from my childhood days.
Wow, so that's what this button does.
It's exquisite.
You were great, Daitetsu.
No, but I was nervous.
That was my first time singing.
That was your first time?
Well, there usually aren't many occasions where I can sing.
Jin-kun?
Where are you going?
To the bathroom!
Who's next?
It's me.
I put this in thinking you would sing it.
I won't.
Such a niche class of anime song.
Hey, what are you putting in a popular song for?!
Even I can read the atmosphere around here!
No! Put in anime songs, got it?
And ones that you would especially recommend!
What kind of embarrassment play is that?!
All right!
Excuse me!
ネオンサインが輝く都会の空
neon sain ga kagayaku tokai no sora
A city sky shining with neon signs.
汚れた夢で着飾る摩天楼
yogoreta yume de kikazaru matenrou
Skyscrapers wearing dirty dreams.
バイオレンスが蔓延る今夜もまた
baiorensu ga habikoru konya mo mata
In this night where violence crawls,
堕天使達が誘い笑う
datenshi tachi ga iznai warau
the fallen angels lure and smile.
胸の奥でくすぶっていた
mune no oku de kusubutte ita
Smoldering in the deep part of my heart,
He's naturally good and the song is quite natural.
Not fun.
怒り超え今旅立ってゆけ
ikari koe ima tabidatte yuke
surpass rage and go on a journey.
愛故に傷つけるくらいなら
ai yueni kizutsukeru kurai nara
If I were to be hurt because of love,
指の先から引き裂かれ
yubi no saki kara hikisakare
let me be ripped from the tip of my finger.
ああ、涙に溺れていたい
aa namida ni oboretai
Oh I want to drown in tears, oh I want to drown in tears.
Oh Mikuriya, good timing.
Order a Lemon Squash.
恋だけがただ１つなる絆なら
koi dake ga tada hitotsu naru kizuna nara
If only love is the one last bond,
想い出さえも邪魔なだけ
omoide sae mo jama na dake
even memories become obstacles.
One Lemon Squash please.
愛つろう裸のままで
aitsurou hadaka no mama de
Love nakedly.
Let's run away
Let's run away!
How was that?
What is that song?
An original video animation from 15 years ago.
An insert song in Youjyu Kishin Chaos Blade.
"Run away with you"!
That's my recommended song, damn you!
You guys got less excited, didn't you!
Right?
Don't underestimate an otaku, damn it!
Annoying.
Takako, you're the worst.
Who's next?
I-It's me.
You haven't chosen yet?
I've never done anything like this before so...
Oh, then why don't we do a duet together?
Hey, let's do it!
If I were to do something like that, I'd rather sing alone.
Throw-
劣悪の心　捨てて
retsuaku no shin sutete
Throwing away the inferior heart.
路地裏抜けて　走る
rojiura nukete hashiru
I run past the alley.
振り返るなよ捕まるぜ
furikaeruna yo tsukamaru ze
Don't look back or you will be caught.
昨日なんてないさ
kinou nante nai sa
There is no yesterday.
もう俺お前となら全部OK
mou ore omae to nara zembu ok
I'm okay with everything if I'm with you.
This is...
Not too good...
There's really nothing to comment about.
背中合わせの赤い薔薇
senaka awase no akai bara
A red rose being back to back.
Isn't it as expected of him in a way?
見上げた空沈むことのない
miageta sora shizumu koto no nai
The sky I looked up, not sinking!
孤独...
kodoku na
A lonely...
Excuse me.
そう突き抜けるような...
sou tsukiageru you na...
Yes, a piercing...
Here's your Lemon Squash.
Oh yes, thanks.
お前となら地獄まで
omae to nara jigoku made
With you, even to hell.
I will take away the plates.
ああ、切なさ焦がして
aa setsunasa kogashite
Oh the sadness burns.
Oh, these too please.
I will be wiping the tables.
ああ、背伸びの純情
aa senobi no jyunjou
Oh the pure feelings reach high.
Excuse me!
Encore! Encore! Encore!
Why you!
Mikuriya ran off...
Well that was pretty embarrassing, so...
He was exhausted by the second half.
But he did manage to sing until the end.
You're next, Nagi-san.
That's right. I'm excited!
You should give a bit of that courage to Jin.
Oh, but it might be enough.
Since you're already giving so much to Jin.
What do you mean?
The old Jin would never have sung in front of others.
Really?
Yes.
He seems to have changed a little after starting to live with you.
Don't worry about it too much.
It was your first time, so it's natural that it didn't turn out as you wanted it to.
It was your first time too, wasn't it?
That's true, but...
You're lucky you can do anything well.
I can't do anything right.
No need to rush.
You can improve step by step.
Everyone has their own strengths.
Daitetsu...
Whether it's singing or drawing,
you have your good points.
I'm sure of it.
Daitetsu, what are we singing next?
Eh, we have a next round?
I shall sing!
とうちゃんもじいちゃんもばあちゃんも
touchan mo jiichan mo baachan mo
Father, grandfather, grandmother,
たかしくんもマンドリルも
takashi kun mo mandoriru mo
Takashi-kun and the mandrill.
ブートキャンプにいくのなら
bu-to kyanpu ni iku no nara
If you are going to a bootcamp,
豆食え！豆！
mame kue mame
eat beans! Beans!
もりもり体がつくられる
morimori karada ga tsukurareru
It builds up your body vigorously!
壮絶な色気
souzetsu na iroke
A fierce sex appeal.
豆は畑のお肉なり
mame wa hatake no oniku nari
Beans are the meat from the field.
What the heck is that song?
Dokkoi Foods, the song of Hello Soybeans.
Oh, that advertisement song.
Why do you know such a song?!
They had it at Tatsuya!
I can sing the theme of Shirigiya Supermarket too!
Nagi basically only rents out songs like this...
She's of the ripe age, yet lacks the sex appeal.
Tatsuya, Tatsuya of where?
Being of the ripe age yet lacking sex appeal?
I'm sorry to interrupt you when you're getting all excited, but...
It's your turn right, senpai?
Since you can say all you want to everyone like that,
you must be such a great singer.
Well, how about we see how you do?
Oh no, Akiba-kun.
Takako is amazing when she sings.
きゅあきゅある～ん
Kyakyuaru-n
Kyakyuarun.
しゅがしゅがり～ん
shugashugari-n
Shugashugarin.
待ってて恋のキャプチャー！
mattete koi no kyapucha-
Wait for me, captor of love.
女の子はみんなバトルウィッチ！
onna no ko wa minna batoru uicchi
Girls are all battle witches.
ヘアピンカーブでアナタのハートにストライク！
heapin kaabu de anata no ha-to ni sutoraiku
A strike into your heart with a hairpin curve!
ページワン(1)最後に残ったハートのエース
pe-ji wan saigo ni nokotta ha-to no e-su
Page 1. The last card is the ace of hearts.
アナタの指先で上手に捕まえて
anata no yubisaki de jouzu ni tsukamaete
Catch me with your fingertips.
You are magician!
You are a magician!
きゅあきゅある～ん
Kyakyuaru-n
Kyakyuarun.
Disgusting.
しゅがしゅがりん
shugashugari-n
Shugashugarin.
Disgusting.
Pure Love 絶対 Shiny heart
pure love zettai shiny heart
Pure love absolutely shiny heart.
Disgusting!
きめきめりん Happy birthday!
kimekimerin happy birthday
Happy birthday!
But she's good...
She's good, but disgusting.
アナタまで飛べるかな？
anata made toberu kana
Can I fly up to you?
きゅあきゅある～ん
Kyakyuaru-n
Kyakyuarun.
しゅがしゅがり～ん
shugashugari-n
Shugashugarin.
調律将来 Heaven's Gate
chouritsu shourai heaven's gate
Control future heaven's gate.
Zange-chan, where are you going?
To freshen up.
奇跡だって呼び寄せる
kiseki datte yobiyoseru
I can even call a miracle.
待って
matte
Wait!
もったいぶらないでキスしてよ！
mottaiburanaide kisu shite yo
Don't put on airs; kiss me!
How was it?
How was it you ask, but...
Oh man...
What do you think?
I don't know how to answer...
An anime voice that's completely different from her usual figure.
Why is even her dance so perfect?
Uh, but the quality was so good it could have been cut as a single.
Only teens should be allowed to sing this song, I guess?
I'm still in my teens!
It's a counter-reaction.
Oh, I see.
A counter-reaction.
Sure she would make a counter-reaction.
What are you guys all in consent about?
It's just what I like, so what's wrong?
Just when I thought I would win by being the last one...
That kind of impact is cheating!
Don't you have a song you're good at?
Huh? Singing nursery rhymes at the karaoke is just ridiculous!
All right, I got it.
I'm sorry I said too much.
Then, let me do as I wish.
Since you also want to be liked by that boy too.
Why are you trying to sing continuously?
Because nobody else is singing!
But Zange-chan should be next.
She isn't back yet.
Did she get scared and run away?
What does that mean, Neesama?
You sure took a long time.
What were you doing?
Just a strategy meeting.
It's my turn on stage, eh?
Yes, we take turns.
A song reveals your inner self.
Places like these are the best chances to understand each other.
Dokkoi Soybeans is out of the question!
It's Hello Soybeans by Dokkoi Foods!
I, who am rumored to be making a CD debut, shall let you hear a true girl's song.
What is this turn of events?!
Jin-kun.
I don't mind being unable to sit beside you.
But, I would like a place in your heart.
Please listen.
Y-Yeah...
女の子はいつも寂しがり
onnanoko wa itsumo sabishigari
Girls are always lonely.
とっても苦しいの
tottemo kurushii no
They are always suffering.
そんなときにあなたを思い出す
sonna toki ni anata wo omoidasu
That's when I think of you.
Huh?
This is...
Bad.
きゅんと胸が鳴る
kyun to mune ga naru
My heart chokes.
But she's cute!
She's bad but she's cute.
She's the opposite of you in one sense.
微笑みがしっ！　それで舞い上がって
hohoemi gashi! sore de maiagatte
Make a smile! That causes me to flutter up
This is in one sense a counter-reaction.
天まで届くわ
ten made todoku wa
and I will even reach the heavens.
いつか迎えに来てねMy darling
itsuka mukae ni kite ne my darling
Come pick me up some time, my darling.
ずっと待ってるから
zutto matteru kara
I will always be waiting.
優しく触れてそっと抱き寄せて
yasashiku furete sotto dakiyosete
Gently touch me and embrace me.
そうよデリケートに
sou yo derike-to ni
Yes, delicately.
Hey!
でもその先は
demo sono saki wa
But beyond that...
Isn't that against the rules?!
It was made like this!
Jin seems troubled!
Get away from him!
You're not, right?
Does karaoke usually have such complicated matters swirling around?
W-Well...
No, I don't think so.
Oh, I guess time's up.
Too bad.
Finished? Then second round!
Here we go!
Huh?
Next, only duets!
Jin-
Daitetsu, let's sing together!
I'm sweating in a strange way now.
Yes, a strange feeling of fatigue.
Jin, what's the matter?
It seems like I'm forgetting something.
Shino-senpai didn't sing anything!
That's true!
That's unfair, senpai!
Shino?
You shouldn't let her sing!
Oh, why is that?
Because her eyes will open.
Right?
Yes.
But...
If you...
...really insist...
お魚ぴっちぴち
Osakana picchi pichi
The fish is live.
お肉はてっかてか
Oniku wa tekka teka
The meat is shiny.
自然お野菜「しりげや」
shizen oyasai shirigeya
Natural vegetables, Shirigeya.
奥様にっこにこ
okusama nikko niko
Wives smiling.
旦那様ほっくほく
danna sama hokku hoku
Husbands happy.
みんな揃って「しりげや」
minna sorotte shirigeya
Everyone, go to Shirigeya.
笑顔溢れる楽しいお店
egao afureru tanoshii omise
A happy shop filled with smiles.
あなたの街のパラダイス
anata no machi no paradaisu
Your town's paradise.
しりげや　しりげや
shirigeya shirigeya
Shirigeya Shirigeya.
総合スーパーしりげや
sougou suupaa shirigeya
General Supermarket Shirigeya.
しりげや　しりげや
shirigeya shirigeya
Shirigeya Shirigeya.
夢のスーパーしりげや
yume no suupaa shirigeya
A dream Supermarket Shirigeya.
しりげや　（しりげや）
shirigeya (shirigeya)
Shirigeya Shirigeya.
しりげや　（しりげや）
shirigeya (shirigeya)
Shirigeya Shirigeya.
総合スーパーしりげや
sougou suupaa shirigeya
General Supermarket Shirigeya.
しりげや　（しりげや）
shirigeya (shirigeya)
Shirigeya Shirigeya.
しりげや　（しりげや）
shirigeya (shirigeya)
Shirigeya Shirigeya.
夢のスーパーしりげや
yume no suupaa shirigeya
A dream Supermarket Shirigeya.
Next time on Kannagi....
Huh? Nagi?