Good morning, Jirou.
Mornin'.
So you came today as well.
You should properly lock your front door.
That is really careless of you.
Okay, okay.
Nii-san, we're out of shampoo.
N-NO!!!
It is Without a Doubt, in Bed
I think you two are really compatible.
You can overcome any obstacle with love.
Kureha locked herself in her room and won't come out...
At this rate, she's going to miss school...
If it is about that, then you need not worry.
Your little sister is right over there.
Kureha!
I was looking everywhere for you, Nii-san!
You-!
Did Konoe-senpai say anything after he saw me in my underwear?!
No, nothing at all.
No reaction!?
It's "boys' love?"
How did it turn out like this?!
You're dating Konoe-senpai, aren't you?
You are absolutely correct.
Subaru is madly in love with your brother!
Hey!
I knew it...
However, you should not worry.
Because, your brother is going out with yours truly.
Huh...?
You're lying!
I don't buy it!
The birthmark on his side.
He has a birthmark on his side, doesn't he?
H-How do you know?
We were in bed together, of course.
I-In bed?!
So that's when she...
B-But, Nii-san can't stand being touched by girls!
His nose will start bleeding immediately!
You can overcome all obstacles with love.
There's no way...
I want to cheer for you...
Since you might become my little sister in the future.
Let us get along, Kureha-chan.
Suzutsuki-senpai... No, Onee-sama!
Furthermore, I want Subaru to experience love with a girl.
That's why...
How about having a double date this coming Sunday?
Yo, Konoe!
Do not carelessly approach me from behind.
Do not worry.
This is just a stun-gun for self-protection.
It has been specially customized.
If you hit the right vital points with this‒
Why are you in possession of such a dangerous weapon?
Right now, I must focus on protecting Ojou-sama.
So, I cannot protect you as well. Please watch your back.
Later!
'Kay!
See you later, Konoe-senpai.
Mhm.
J-Jirou.
Um, what is it?
Huh?!
Oh, right. You're...
It's fine, just close your eyes.
I'll keep an eye out for you, so feel free to change in here.
Why does everything have to be so difficult?
You sure took your time.
Hey, you aren't thinking about something bad about me, are you!?
No, not at all.
Say, Konoe-senpai!
Could you teach me how to swim?
I'm not that good of a swimmer.
Liar!
I do not really mind.
It is fine with me, Subaru!
There are a lot of people here, but if anything happens, Jirou will protect you.
If Ojou-sama says so... I'm counting on you, Jirou!
Oh, ah...
What was up with Konoe just now?
I wonder how many years it has been since we last came here.
You've been here before?
Yes, when we were children.
Subaru and I were once kidnapped here.
Kidnapped?
Kana-chan, are you okay?
They wanted a ransom.
The incident was resolved swiftly, and all the criminals were caught.
But because of that incident, my movements have been restricted.
Subaru felt responsible for that incident.
However, it was my own fault that I was kidnapped.
She could not protect her mistress.
But she was only a child back then.
Ever since then, the distance between us only grew.
Similar to how you have gynophobia, Subaru has her own weaknesses as well.
Weaknesses?
Okay! Let's stop the chit-chat.
Hey, stop sitting around!
You are supposed to be my lover, right?
Uh... yeah.
Onee-sama!
How was it?
I think I showed him my good side!
The real battle begins now.
Let's come up with a plan!
Yes!
Subaru, I am a bit thirsty.
Can you go with Jirou and buy some drinks?
But...
It's fine. I am not a child anymore.
Understood.
You are on good terms with Kureha, aren't you?
Something like that.
I'm so jealous. I got into a scuffle with my father yesterday.
Why?
Because I told him that you pushed me down in the science room and got a nosebleed from touching my breasts.
So he said, "Bring me that four-eyed bastard!"
"I'll rip him to shreds and then lynch him!"
Of course.
Oh!
What's wrong?
This is bad!
Is there anyone here?!
Konoe, go get an employee!
Hey, Jirou!
It's a girl?!
Ayaka!
Mama!
Thank you very much!
Thank goodness!
Jirou!
I didn't flip out. If I had, it would've been bad.
I didn't flip out. If you had made me, it would have been bad.
"Stay by my side?"
That's right!
"Stand by me," means, "I want you to be beside me."
How's that? Isn't it romantic?
I don't get it...
I guess that's too much of a hurdle for a five-year-old.
Know this, Kinjirou. Your name has the character for "close" in it for a reason!
In other words, I want you to say to someone, "Stay by my side."
Someone?
That's right!
Your mother, Kureha, or someone you believe to be precious to you.
Become a man that can say, "I will become strong and I will protect you, so stay by my side."
"Stay by my side." That is a promise from Sakamachi Jirou to Sakamachi Kinjirou.
Father, have I still kept our promise?
Jirou, are you alright?
Ah, yeah.
I just met an acquaintance of mine in the gardens of Paradise.
I beg you. Stop making such crude jokes.
I was really worried about you!
And...
And?
N-Nothing at all.
Hm?
If you feel better now, let's meet up with Ojou-sama.
Quite a bit of time has passed.
You're right.
Here!
Someone told me to give this to you.
Hello, hello, can you hear me?
Who is this?
You're pretty composed aren't you?
Even though your precious master has disappeared, Konoe Subaru!
I am going to ask you one more time, who is this?
I am only going to say this once, so listen up!
You are speaking to the venerable Kidnapping Hunter!
Come here in ten minutes ,'kay?
If you call the police, it's game over. Got it?
Got it!
I will go by myself.
Don't be a fool!
This is all my fault, I cannot allow Jirou to come in harm's way because of this.
Don't joke around!
Man, youth is great! What good friends!
Well then, take care, little butler!
Hey!
What's this? Subaru's reacting the same way I do when I touch a girl.
Subaru has her own weaknesses as well.
Konoe, are you scared of blades?
Don't tell me‒Did the same thing happen in the previous kidnapping incident?
Yes, ever since that incident, my body loses its strength whenever I see a weapon with a blade.
I am a defective butler.
Not only was I not born as a male, but on top of that, I have a huge fear of bladed objects...
It might be strange for someone who is not able to protect her master to work as a butler...
However, I still want to remain as her butler!
Konoe!
I will make sure to save your sister, so wait here‒
I'm sorry, Konoe.
I'll do anything you ask afterwards.
Jirou...
Welcome.
Those two are behind that door.
Let's have some fun before that little butler arrives.
So his target is Konoe...
Don't die, okay?
You're not much of a fighter, you shitty brat!
Jirou!
What should I do?
Jirou... Jirou is‒
Not bad!
You're still standing after all these hits!
I didn't take all those beatings since I was five to just go down after a few hits.
No way...
Bring it on!
I'm gonna get back on my feet as many times as you want, you asshole!
It's "game set" for you already.
To be honest, I didn't want to go this far.
But I guess I have no choice!
Damn it!
I can't move!
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
K-Konoe!
Jirou, I'll take over from here.
You're pretty late, little butler.
Aren't you going to tremble in fear?
The last time we were here, you were shaking and cried your eyes out!
Just the sight of a knife startled you!
You were shaking like crazy just like a pitiful little sheep!
Is he the culprit who kidnapped Konoe and Suzutsuki?
But Suzutsuki said that they were all apprehended.
I'm different now!
I'm... I'm...
I'm a butler!
That's why I'm not afraid of your knife!
She did it!
Damn it, that was kind of cool...
Kureha!
Subaru... Jirou-kun?
I can't eat any more...
Ojou-sama!
My deepest apologizes, Ojou-sama.
It is because of my carelessness that you and Kureha-chan went through something so dreadful.
I am... a failure as a butler...
But you rescued me.
As your master, I would not be able to fire a butler as loyal as you.
Kana-chan...
What is it, Subaru?
Even though I'm such a hopeless butler, may I stay by your side?
Yeah, of course.
Stay with me, forever.
As a butler and as a friend, stay by my side forever.
This is an order, Subaru.
Yes. Understood, Ojou-sama.
Konoe-senpai...
Looks like it's over.
You!
You still have some fight left in you?!
Subaru!
Konoe Nagare.
Subaru's father.
And the Suzutsuki family's butler-in-chief.
In other words, he's my father's butler.
In other words...
It hurts!
So, you're awake now!
Your injuries are nothing special.
I did hold back after all.
You liar!
You hit me with all you had!
I meant that I held back just enough to not kill you.
What about Kureha?
Don't worry, the scenario was planned so that she would not get hurt.
"Scenario," you say...
Just to be clear, I hate you.
Don't worry, I hate you as well.
You sure don't hold back, you brat.
I'll repeat myself as many times as you want, you fool of a parent.
Nagare, you may leave now.
Understood, Kanade-ojousama.
Nagare and Jirou-kun are pretty similar to each other.
How exactly are we similar?
You both cherish your families.
However, Nagare is, well... overbearing and overprotective.
For Nagare, Subaru is his only immediate family, so it is to be expected.
His only family?
Subaru's mother passed away when she was only five.
It was a miracle that she even managed to give birth to Subaru.
Well, you told me before, girls can't become butlers.
Yes.
The members of my family followed this tradition, but Subaru rebelled against it.
She said that did not need a new mother.
It must have been scary for her.
The thought of her mother disappearing.
Was that why she was so desperate to become a butler?
I am sincerely sorry to have dragged you into this mess.
I thought that there might have been an improvement if she came into contact with someone similar to herself, like you.
So that's what today's kidnapping incident was about?
You are correct, Jirou-kun!
That voice was you?!
I am truly indebted to you.
Because of you, Subaru can stay as my butler.
Thank you!
You do not care much about Konoe's father, right?
Yes, that's right.
I did it because I love Subaru.
What?
It is true. Subaru was my first love.
Thank you for becoming my butler's friend.
Jirou, I am coming in.
What is it?
You said that you "would do anything I ask", didn't you?
When you hit me.
I-I-I did but...
I was really scared!
You rescued Suzutsuki, didn't you?
You're not defective anymore!
No! No! No! No!
That's not what I was afraid of.
I thought that I would never see you again when he tried to stab you.
I thought that Jirou, the first friend I made at school, might die on me.
I was really scared.
Sorry.
Idiot! Even if you apologize, I will never forgive you!
Become a man who can say, "I will become strong and I will protect you, so stay by my side."
Stay by my side.
Father, I promise I will become strong.
Are you alright, Konoe-senpai?!
I heard from Onee-sama that Nii-san might be holding Konoe-senpai in his arms!
Like hell I would!
Damn that Suzutsuki!
To tempt Konoe-senpai even though you're already going out with Onee-sama!
You are going out with Ojou-sama?
Laying your hands on Kana-chan is...
She's going to kill me!
You sure look pretty energetic.
You bastard! You framed me again, didn't you?
You sure have a bad reputation.
Anyways, come with me. You're a being held hostage!
What happened to that gynophobia of yours?
I can resist it if I only grab your sleeve.
There he is!
Wait up!
This is happening because of all that nonsense you told them!
But I am telling the truth as well.
Subaru really was my first love.
Ahh!!
When all is said and done, girls are still scary!
Hey, Konoe what are you doing?
I am "servicing" my master.
No way!
This does not embarrass me at all.
Sorry, but can I keep my precious "parts" tucked away?
No way, take off your clothes and throw them away.
Next time on Mayo Chiki,
the fourth story:
Don't stare so much...
Don't Stare So Much...