Today is just the start of another day at Youkai Academy.
Dad, Mom,
and my cousin Kyou-chan.
It's already been a month since I enrolled into Youkai Academy.
How many letters have I written that can't be sent out?
I've already lost count.
It's a little weird....
No, this is a really weird school.
In the beginning, I didn't know what to do,
but now, I've made some friends and I'm very happy.
But is it really fine for me... to continue like this?
Well then, please turn to the next page...
Aono-kun, please read this page aloud.
Aono-kun?
Tsukune...
What should I do!?
All you have to do is read it out loudly.
What was wrong with you earlier, Tsukune?
I just spaced out, that's all.
If that's all then it's fine, but please tell me if there's anything troubling you.
Because we are...
Moka-san?
Tsukune...
Moka-san...
Tsukune..
You smell nice...
Moka... san?
Just a little, all right?
No!
Gee, don't you think you're sucking Tsukune's blood a bit too often?
Don't tell me the reason he spaced out earlier was due to that?
But I didn't suck that much yesterday...
So, you did suck his blood after all!
No, that's not it.
Moka-san is a vampire after all, so sucking blood is her nature.
Tsukune!
If that's case, I will...
No!
If Tsukune kisses Kurumu-chan, who is a succubus,
Tsukune will then become your slave!
Yeah, they are right after all.
Moka-san is a vampire and Kurumu-chan is a succubus.
And I'm just a...
Oh?
Are you Aono Tsukune from Year 1 Class 3?
Yes, but...
I won't forgive you.
You are our enemy!
Wait a moment... Your enemy?
If you don't understand, I will explain it to you then.
Formation... Set!
And!
L.O.V.E, CUTE Mokyuu-san!
We won't lose to the likes of you!
Kurumu, love, love, lovely, Kurumu...
C.U.T.E Yukarin! Moe, moe, huu huu!
Mokyuu, Kurumu and Yukarin, don't tell me it's...
Indeed, I'm the leader of the Akashiya Moka-sama Fan Club, Kasahara Kouzou!
Furthermore, I'm the leader of the Kurono Kurumu Fan Club, Taira Gouzaburou!
And I'm the leader of the Sendou Yukari Fan Club, Naga Kubisaku!
Together we are called:
Love Love Alliance.
Wee~ That was so lame, I fell!
I need to go and take out the trash.
Wait!
We shall show you our Fan Club Alliance terror!
Divine punishment! Divine punishment! Divine punishment!
Ouch, ouch.
He does resemble a human but he sure is weak.
It's like he's a human in the first place.
A weakling like you is not fit to be with Mokyuu.
Is he using some weird tricks?
No, this is... Magic?
You guys, don't bully Tsukune-san!
Lucky!
It's Yukarin!
Tsukune!
Are you all right?
Kurumu...
Mokyuu too?
What are you guys doing to Tsukune?
I saw them ganging up on Tsukune!
That's so mean!
Those who bully Tsukune-san shall not be forgiven!
Magical Stick!
That's enough already, stop it!
Tsukune-san!
Tsukune.
Let's take this chance...
and retreat!
Hang in there, Tsukune.
I'm really sorry.
Be it this or that, this is entirely their fault!
I'm fine.
Gee, what a mess this had been.
No, if I was a bit stronger to begin with,
I won't be a bother to everyone.
A weakling like you is not fit to be with Mokyuu.
Not fit, huh...
Hello, I know nobody is listening, but...
Can anyone hear me?
What should I do?
A weak human who relies on girls to protect himself.
Is it really fine for me to continue to stay in this academy?
Our enemy, Aono Tsukune!
I'm going to completely defeat you!
My Yukarin photos have increased...
Her smile is really captivating...
I want Kurumu's photos...
As long as we clear off Aono Tsukune, who is bugging our goddesses,
we can take as many photos as we want!
By doing that, by doing that...
Mokyuu's smile will then only belong to me.
Mokyuu...!
Kurumu~
I'm a bat!
Hey hey, don't you think those three have been hanging around us a lot lately?
I just experienced something like that...
It's heavy...
Hey, who are you taking photographs of?
I'm taking photos of the ever-changing school!
That's my duty as a member of the photography club!
Even me too!
Vanilla essence, baking powder, liquor bottle.
Yahohoo!
It would be great if Tsukune likes it.
What was that?
He's still there...
He's here too!
1- 2- 3- 4... 2- 2- 3- 4
He's still looking at me!
Compared to your photos being taken, getting stalked by someone is a lot more mentally stressful.
Indeed...
Those guys are scary.
If they have obscene thoughts, we can just finish them off.
The problem is with Tsukune.
Yeah, yeah.
Would it be better if we consulted the teacher about this?
Speaking of which, wouldn't it be better if we escort Tsukune?
Escort?
Then we can finish them off if they appear again.
Strike to the stomach!
It's actually "killing two birds with one stone".
There's no need for it really.
But, Tsukune-san will get bullied by them again!
With regards to Tsukune's power, facing the three of them is...
I-I didn't mean that...
If Tsukune transforms, he'd be really powerful!
Although I don't know, but I'm sure that's the case.
It's all right Moka-san, I'll be going now.
Wait for me, Tsukune!
I'm sorry, Tsukune.
But everyone doesn't know that you are in fact, a human.
It's not that.
Even though it should be me protecting everyone,
I am the one that's being protected.
Tsukune?
I'm really...
I'm sorry, Moka-san.
Tsukune!
Cleaning, cleaning,
is so fun, is so fun!
Tsukune-san?
I wonder if Tsukune is angry...
Excuse me, Moka-san!
What's wrong, Yukari-chan?
I was sweeping the ground just now,
and I saw Tsukune-san walking as though he was leaving the school,
and somehow, he looked as if he was brooding over something while carrying his bag.
Brooding...
I wonder if that young man is still all right...
This is bad!
Tsukune is intending to leave this school!
4:44PM...
It's about time.
Moka-san...
What Moka-san?
You dare call our sacred goddess Moka-chan by her name?
Even though we don't know where you are headed,
This is outside the school boundaries!
We can do as we wish!
T-That form is...
W-What?
Are you trying to make fun of our fashion?!
I didn't really...
Indeed, we are monsters to be laughed at.
In that school filled with gorgeous and handsome girls,
There are no girls that would take us!
That is why...
We hate people who don't work hard and are so well liked!
We won't let you escape...
You don't understand the suffering of us smelly people!
Our idols are the only ones that can cure us of this sorrow!
We cannot forgive you for taking them away!
Let go of your hand- No...
Get your neck off him!
This voice is...!
You guys!
H-heavy... Why am I doing the flying again?
I'm sorry, I don't know the magic spell to make us fly yet.
That's beside the point, Kurumu-chan...
Tsukune is...!
Leave that to me!
Magical stick.
Tsukune!
I got rescued by Moka-san and the others again...
Idiot!
You're a big idiot, Tsukune!
We are friends, aren't we?
If we're friends...
Isn't it natural...
To help and be helped?
But I...
Have to be rescued by you even now...
That's not true.
I've been rescued by your kind words.
I've also been protected by you!
Yukari-chan... Kurumu-chan...
That's why we're even, right?
Moka...
Terrible...
Too terrible...
They're saying those things to him in front of us...
Monogamy...
Aono Tsukune, the one who violated the law of monogamy...
Only you...
I'll stick you to death!
It's coming!
Yukari... That undeveloped, yet-to-blossom, body of yours...
Will be wrapped by this long head of mine!
Kurumu!
Let us gaze at each other and create a world of love just for the two of us...
How would we gaze?
You're fat stalker!
Moka, even in a heavy downpour, even if enemies of skin or ultraviolet rays attack you,
I'll always become your umbrella of love!
You really don't have to...
Yuck!
At this rate, everyone will...
Hey, you bunch!
Even though you are in their fan clubs,
You're giving the girls you like a hard time!
That's just shameful!
Shameful, eh?
You, who say we're shameful, are the worst perverted monster of all!
I-I didn't go so far as to...
I almost forgot that...
The enemy we need to defeat is YOU!
Let's go!
We, the Fan Club Alliance's,
Ultimate attack!
Union of Anger attack!
Union!
T-This is...
Do you see this form?
Why don't you call me Big Bro?
Tsukune!
Tsukune-san!
H-Hang in there!
I'll...
I'll protect everyone!
It's impossible!
Even if it's impossible, I have to do it!
W-What in the world happened!?
This... This light is...!
Once the rosary on her chest is removed,
the Vampire blood within Moka will awaken.
You pile of trash!
These cold, yet beautiful, eyes...
The long, silver hair with huge monstrous energy...
This is, this is...!
Our true idol we've waited so long for has finally descended!
Idol-sama!
I see...
Trash will still be trash no matter where they go.
Such cold words...
P-Please scold us more!
Kurumu, Yukari...
Yes!
Idol-sama...
You two, help me out.
Understood!
All right!
Here I go!
Magical stick.
You idiot! Don't lose our balance!
Vanish, you trash!
We'll disappear...
Yes...
But Idol-sama is the true idol that we've been waiting for...
The 'Fan Club Alliance' is renamed to the 'Vampire Fan Club'.
This week's winner was decided in a surprisingly long time of 80 seconds!
I got rescued by Moka-san once again...
Tsukune.
Y-Yes...?
It wouldn't be good if you left.
If you left, I wouldn't have any food left, right?
On top of that, the other Moka would cry from loneliness.
I...
Even though I'd go "Yahoo!" if Moka cried, I understand her feelings,
You can't leave, Tsukune!
That's right, Tsukune-san!
I didn't really plan to go anywhere though...
Eh?
B-B-But...
I have some letters to send out, that's why I thought of asking the bus driver for a favor.
That means, you wanting to leave the school...
Was Moka-san's mistake in judgment?
Excuse me... here it is.
Such a simple request, sending just letters, are you sure that's all?
Yes!
What an admirable determination, young man.
Sheesh, how frustrating...
You mustn't go away, Tsukune...
I will, one day, become strong enough to protect everyone,
I promise, Moka-san.
Until then, I'll be parting with this phone that can't connect.
As expected of his choice...
But the path you've chosen is filled with thorns, young man.
As I was saying, even though the project was continually delayed,
The red telephone that can connect to the whole of the human world was finally installed in the small store.
Furthermore, the bus timetable has now been increased to once a day.
Isn't that great, Tsukune?
Moka-san...
Tsukune...
What a nice smell....
Tsukune!
We're still in class!
Kappuchu~
Ouch!!!
Yahoo! Pool, swimsuits, swimming!
W-Wait Kurumu-chan! Your eye-catching swimsuit is too dangerous!
Your swimsuit too, since it makes you look like a cute kindergarten child!
Next episode, School Swimsuit and Vampire,
and a kappuchu for you!