TL Note:
Hitsumabushi:
Eel-and-rice bowl, a specialty of Nagoya.
TL Note:
A parody of Calpis Water,
a Japanese uncarbonated soft drink.
That's enough!
I did it for your sake!
You said you liked it! So I did it for you, thinking that you'd be happy!
If you're there, answer me.
I don't even want to talk to you!
I'm going to open it.
Hey, don't force it closed!
You too, don't open it without my permission!
This will be my territory from today on!
What are you, a kindergartener? So dumb.
You won't understand.
Do you know how hurt and betrayed I feel?
Forget it. I'm going to live here from now on.
I'm never going to come out.
How is that possible? What about food?
I'll stock up on Oishinbou.
How many days worth of that did you bring in there?
Besides...
You'll have trouble with the toilet and such.
I'll get by.
You can't! And don't do it there!
What's wrong?
You were so loud that you made me drop my Oishinbou!
You're blaming that on me?
I stepped on it!
See? A person can't possibly live in a closet.
Come out, will you?
I'm not a person; I'm a god.
I'll show you that I can overcome this hardship.
Do whatever you want!
I will!
I'm going to do my homework! Don't disturb me!
I won't!
Text in book:
Jin is an idiot
Why you!
These are fried eggs.
These are fried vegetables.
These are fried vegetables and eggs.
I'm sorry for bothering you every week lately.
Don't worry about it.
What's the matter?
She's hiding in the closet because of that?
Since when?
Since this morning.
Yesterday she kept whining and throwing a tantrum.
That can't be helped. It's your fault after all.
Hi, Nagi-san.
Is that you, Tsugumi?
I've heard all about it.
I know that Jin was mean, but he has apologized.
Why don't you forgive him?
He doesn't mean it!
Of all things, he had to do that while I was taking a bath...
It's true that it was thoughtlessness on his part...
...but he's feeling bad about it right now.
Besides, staying in the closet too long is bad for your eyes.
You don't need to worry about that.
I have this purification staff.
Oh, I see...
A stick that's useful even in the dark. A slick stick!
But it's not healthy if you don't get sunlight.
You'll also get thirsty if you shut yourself in, right?
I told you not to worry.
I have my Oishinbou and Capilus.
Capilus?
You took my Capilus!
Did not!
Why would you tell such an obvious lie?! Mine's gone!
I didn't take yours! I picked it up!
Are you an elementary school student?!
Jin, give me a minute.
Oishinbou in my right hand.
Capilus in my left.
With these, I can fight for another ten years.
Lemon flavor, huh?
Why is she so mad? I don't get her.
Well, women are delicate.
This time, I'll talk to her alone.
Who cares if she doesn't come out.
You shouldn't say that.
You're the cause of all this.
If Nagi-san doesn't come out, you can't use the closet, right?
It's not like there's anything important...
See, what did I tell you?
What's inside?
All of them have big tits.
No, nothing really.
Anyway, wait in the other room.
You have to apologize when she comes out.
Nagi-san, I...
Jin isn't here, so let's have a girl-to-girl talk.
It's useless.
TL Note:
When the sun goddess Amaterasu was hiding in a cave,
"Yasakani no Magatama" was the kind of jewel that the gods hung on a tree to lure her out.
My resolution is as strong as the Curved Jewels of Yasakani.
I understand how you feel.
If the same thing was done to me, I would get mad too.
We need some kind of mental preparation too, right?
You think so too?
What's even more irritating is that he didn't spare a thought for my feelings!
Well, it wasn't that bad...
If not for what happened last night...
I'd have been able to accept Jin!
I'd even be glad...
But yesterday...
What he did yesterday is unforgivable!
If only it had happened on another day...
He was too cruel!
Jin, it's your fault!
Because of your own selfish ideas, you toyed with a woman's innocence, you beast!
All men are wolves!
And go throw this away!
What did you go talk to her for?
It's natural that she'd get mad.
Frankly, your recklessness is so great that you don't even fear gods.
Well, I know that's true...
But I did it thinking that she would be happy.
You need to follow the necessary procedures for something like this.
Well, I've had similar experiences before.
In a gal-game.
Anyway, I'm counting on you.
All right. I'll think of something.
I'll get ready and head over to your place. See you later.
Thanks. Laters.
How was it?
He said he'll come over later.
I see.
It's been a long time...
...since we've been alone like this.
Is that so?
I've been pretty busy since she came here.
Mega Milk tits?
Oh.
You're early, Akiba...
Oh, my sister is doing something like that?
No wonder the house felt so quiet today.
Which means...
The two of us are alone, right?
Jin-kun!
Hey, hey! Can't you see me?
The fried egg person?
My name is Tsugumi!
Oh, pardon me.
So, Jin-kun, shall I help you drag Neesama out of there?
I have a good plan.
It's so hot.
Nagi.
W-What?!
About what happened yesterday night...
We'll work something out.
So please come out.
You think I'll fall for that?
Even if you try to lure me out with sweet words, things won't go your way!
All adults are liars!
Look, Jin-kun.
She lacks understanding, so just leave her alone.
Is that Zange?
That's right.
But now that you've become a closet princess, anyone outside is none of your concern, right?
That's right. I have no more interest in the secular world.
You heard her. Jin-kun, you should forget about Neesama.
No, that won't do...
Let me take care of you from now on.
Let's do a lot of fun and embarrassing things.
W-What kind of embarrassing things?
It's too embarrassing to say.
What are you thinking of doing?!
Huh? I must be hearing things.
TL Note:
Zashikiwarashi:
A type of Japanese ghost that stays in someone's house.
Or is it a Zashikiwarashi?
Oh well, let's not bother about the imaginary voices, let's do a lot of embarrassing things now!
W-Wait! Zange-chan!
Even if it's just a ploy, they're going too far!
I see. You're trying to arouse my interest and drag me out while I'm peeking, right?
I won't fall for your trick!
Zange-chan, isn't this just an act?
No, you mustn't say that! Neesama will get suspicious!
Whether she gets suspicious or not, is this for real?
Poke, poke.
No choice, huh? Let's change this into a documentary.
What are you doing...?
This is a non-fiction story based on existing people and organizations.
There might be a portrayal of extreme scenes. Viewers please be warned.
Now~
Don't move, Zange-chan! This could get dangerous!
You're so cute, Jin-kun!
If we don't get serious, Neesama won't come out!
We can't do this, Zange-chan!
Don't take me for a fool!
If I get tricked by your acts and come out, you'll say "gotcha" and catch me, right?!
I won't get tricked!
Eh? Jin? Zange?
Jin-kun, look at how much you've discharged.
Hey! What were you doing?!
Huh?
Jin!
I'm sorry, I got too engrossed in the act.
Are you all right?!
What an idiot.
Hello. This is Mikuriya-
I can't answer the phone at the moment.
Please leave your message after the tone.
What's Akiba doing?
If I hadn't stopped them then...
Zange-chan... What a scary girl.
We didn't do anything.
I know!
Wasn't it a pity, Jin-kun?
What do you mean by that?!
A love comedy, huh?
A love comedy, indeed.
Maybe if we got here sooner, we could have been able to see an lyrical and erotic event.
Looks that way.
It's a shame that Takako lost her way.
I can't help it. This is the first time I've been to Mikuriya's place...
If I remember correctly, you're Nagi-tan's younger sister...
I'm Zange-chan!
Anyway, why are you here?!
We heard about the situation from Akiba-kun.
I was thinking of returning the KamaPure game that I borrowed from Akiba-kun.
But because he said that he suddenly had an errand related to you,
we decided to meet here.
And you just barge into my house like that.
KamaPure is that thing at my part-time job the other day...
Yup. It's the game in which the cosplay was based on.
Want to look at it?
Okay.
It's cute.
Too-shy-shy-girl.
Takako, you're a pervert.
Akiba-kun's a low-life.
This is such an ordinary room, just like Mikuriya.
A room with absolutely no special traits resembles his artistic style.
Mind your own business.
Nagi, the president and the vice-president are here.
Takako? Why?
I rushed here because of you.
Sorry to intrude.
I see... Sorry for making you come all this way.
Hey, this place is getting a bit cramped with the number of people increasing.
It's hot too.
You can go home any time you want.
How cruel of me!
Tsugumi, you're such an idiot!
Nagi-sama, I've heard about yesterday's incident.
But you're not a person who should live the rest of your life in such a dark and cramped closet!
You have a duty to heal all the fanclub members with your cheerfulness and beauty!
You're the light of hope!
Since I've come all this way, you should come out!
Show me how you look in your home clothes!
You've showed your true intentions with that last sentence, Takako.
Now, Nagi-sama, come on!
No.
Looks like I've failed.
You give up too fast!
Well, this is a rare occurrence. It could become hot news on the homepage.
Seriously, what did you come here for?
Jin!
Don't be hasty!
If you don't leave your house, you can't grow taller!
Why is Daitetsu-kun here?
I called him just in case,
but it seems he got the wrong idea.
Don't be so upset!
Whether you're good at drawing or not is not important!
What's important is your passion!
You know...
Why are there so many people here?
I hope Akiba gets here soon...
It's really getting hot in here.
I'm getting thirsty from the heat.
Nagi-sama? Are you fine in there?
I'm fully prepared.
I knew it!
This place is more comfortable than I expected!
I should make this place my new shrine.
You've finally appeared, you little impurity!
Don't come near me! I'll exorcise you, you...
Nagi!
Ouch!
Nagi?
Don't come near me!
Hey Mikuriya!
Don't let it get away!
Even if you tell me that...
Don't look! Go away!
Oh my.
This way?!
What?!
Daitetsu-kun! Get a grip!
Akiba. Come quickly...
Akiba!
Akiba...
Akiba~!
Mikuriya~!
So,
why is the all-star cast here?
I'll explain the situation to you later.
Akiba-kun, I want to return this.
Okay.
Akiba, hurry up and give me that thing.
Jin.
What exactly is going on here?
Actually...
It was on TV yesterday, wasn't it?
Heart-throbbing Cat-filled Land.
Oh. That was cute.
Nagi liked that show.
But she was taking a bath.
So I recorded a video for her.
But Nagi had already recorded something-cutie in that tape...
It's Lolikko Cutie.
She had already recorded that...
And I recorded over it.
She got mad, saying that she hadn't watched it yet.
So that's why she shut herself up in the closet...
That's forgivable.
Yesterday was the climax of the
Imposter-Cutie Chapter, after all.
Were you watching that program too?
Sort of. There were episodes where I was impressed by the animation directors and special effects.
Oh...
What's with that disinterested reaction of yours, when this is the subject of discussion for today's incident?
Nagi. Akiba-kun brought Lolikko Cutie for you.
Really?
Of course! If you ask me, yesterday's episode was led by one of my favorite animation directors,
With his connections, a lot of
original illustrators are gathered.
Fans should know this...
Let's skip the explanations.
Check it yourself.
Akiba.
What's this?
DVD?
No, it's Blu-ray.
It's a Sony!
Are you serious? I don't have a DVD player in my house!
The best quality drawings have to be recorded with the best video quality.
But don't panic, Mikuriya.
I expected this, so I've also prepared a video!
Then you should've brought it out first.
Nagi, it's the video.
I'll leave it here,
so take a look.
Jin. What's this?
This is... a video, right?
It's a video. A Beta one.
Beta?
What's that?
It's a Sony.
Everyone went home.
I remembered something.
In the past, there were many times I couldn't watch,
because my old man was watching baseball.
It might not have meant anything important to him,
but to me, it felt really unfair.
I wonder if I've done the same thing to you.
But I really thought you'd be happy.
If someone did that for me, I thought I would have been very happy.
Even though it was a failure...
It was my fault. Come out.
You're hungry, aren't you? Let's eat together.
Just like always.
I'm sorry!
Huh?
All right.
I understand!
I shall let bygones be bygones this time!
You... Don't ever come out of the closet!
Mr. President!
Someone, call the doctor, quickly!
You don't deserve to be called a member of the Lolikko!
I like boobs though.
You too! How long are you going to keep staying with a visual figure like that?
The eel fillets are disappearing from the world!
I'm late, I'm late!
I have two lives.
That means all!
All of a sudden!
Sorry, sorry for everyday!
Guuun~
I've always been sorry.
Actually, I have three lives.
What's happening?
Didn't the curse wear off?
Please watch over me, Senpai!
Same here!
A godly episode was it?
The next episode of Kannagi is...!
Hey don't record over it!