I won't forgive evil!
Magical Funny Stone!
W-What?!
What is she fighting against in the first place?
Evil.
Like, more specifically...
The Evil Magic Association.
A group trying to use magic to make this world descend into chaos and fear.
An association?
Try harder!
What happens if she loses against them?
Is it even something this girl has to do in the first place?
I don't know about the specifics.
Huh? Even so, it's still interesting?
You don't even know what they're fighting for.
It can't be helped!
I only started watching it after I came here, didn't I?!
Akiba said he would let me see the first 13 episodes, but not yet.
Hey! Because you said stuff and distracted me, I didn't get to see the good part!
S-Sorry...
No other choice.
Magical Handsome Stone!
Clean up!
Was it like this?
Magical Handsome Stone...
Nice! That's it!
However, you can learn a lot from the TV.
In order to fight a stronger enemy, we need to power up.
Yeah.
So I was thinking...
My purification wand needs a power up now.
Those are two separate matters.
It's still usable.
"Still usable" means that it's dangerous.
Besides, you've been playing around too much recently.
Going to karaoke...
Watching TV...
I...
I was thinking of starting again tomorrow.
Say that to my face!
If you don't have anything to feel guilty about.
Anyway, those kinds of goods are replaced randomly to prevent the viewers from getting bored.
Just fix it up and keep using it.
Got it?
What?
Magical Handsome Stone.
Clean up.
Hey! If you eat all of the chicken from the lunch box, all we're gonna have is rice!
I can't understand a word you're saying!
Give it back!
I have an important announcement today!
Actually, I, Zange-chan, am making a CD at the moment!
Ah! Does that mean you will be making your debut as a singer?
No, that hasn't been decided yet.
So I'm recruiting a studio to help me debut!
Here's the address.
Hey, Zange-chan! Please don't use our program without approval!
I've already made the lyrics and music, so please help me!
That karaoke must have gotten to her.
Honestly, she's too impressionable to be a god.
You're one to talk...
Hello?
How dare a man like you be together with Zange-chan...
I can make her much happier!
So don't-
What's the matter?
Just a prank call.
There have been a lot lately.
All regarding Zange-chan.
Being a playboy must be tough.
Hey, in the first place, you-
Hello?
A man like you isn't suited for my Daitetsu-kun!
The only one who can understand his feelings is me!
Hey!
Now, then...
I guess I'll take a bath.
After all, I'll be busy exterminating impurities from tomorrow on.
You're doing that on purpose!
Quite some time has passed since then.
I'm out now.
Jin!
Jin.
Well, yeah. If it's around 3,000 yen, you can buy it.
After school tomorrow.
It's fine.
Eh?
This is fine.
Starting tomorrow, I'll exorcise like crazy again with this!
I'm counting on you too!
Eh?
I don't know!
I won't forgive evil!
Take this!
Nagi!
Ouch!
S-Sorry!
Jin!
Ouch...
I have such bad luck...
Look, that's him! The one in the love square!
That bisexual guy?
Is that for real?
I heard it's his camouflage.
He doesn't look too bright.
Why does he look all messed up?
So that's what a battlefield is like.
Jin!
Daitetsu.
I've said this many times, but being with Nagi-san is-
It might be better if I didn't see you for a while.
What?
Just beware of that woman!
Got it?
It's ugly jealousy.
So he is bisexual!
Mikuriya's "popular season" has arrived.
Popular season?
Yes.
The "popular season" is...
...a season when someone becomes popular for no apparent reason.
It is said to come once in a lifetime, regardless of character or physical appearance.
But the scary thing is the counter-reaction that results.
If people go through extremely popular seasons when they are young,
it is said that they will never be popular again when they are adults.
In other words, a physiognomy of troubles with women.
Certainly, there have been some instances that reflect that.
For example, the injury you got today.
Don't you think it's unbelievable that you'd just fall out of the window due to carelessness?
Th-This is...
Now that you mention it, you've
been getting a lot of injuries, lately.
You usually have a bandage on.
Jin is just too wild with his own body.
Even though I always tell him to take care of himself...
Is something possessing you?
Don't say unpleasant things like that.
Something possessed, eh?
Let me exorcise that for you!
Troubles with women?
A popular season, eh?
A high school boy should be dancing for joy in this kind of situation.
Is Mikuriya a blockhead?
He lives with Nagi-sama at home.
Tsugumi-chan and Zange-chan come up to him at school!
What kind of event flag filled school life is this?!
This would be a situation where I couldn't stop drooling!
It can't be helped if some girl he doesn't like comes up to him.
If he had a true love...
What's going on? Calling me out to a place like this...
I've reached my boiling point...!
Whether it's being a homo, a bisexual, or covered in bandages,
it's all your damn fault!
Oh. Yeah.
I'll admit that.
Troubles with women?
I think it might be true.
Come to think of it, Tsugumi saw my precious last time.
Your "precious"?
At this rate, I'll be killed!
I demand better treatment of myself!
I've been putting up with things up until now, but that's going to change starting today!
What's with you all of a sudden?
I've believed in you as a god,
but my body won't be able to take it at this rate!
From now on, don't do anything without consulting me first.
Although it is my fault for not questioning you until now.
We've gone a long way without making things clear.
First of all, what do you want to do that requires you to stay at my house?
Make that clear, please.
It's exactly as I've been saying up to now.
I'm here to exorcise impurities.
Gathering belief is for that purpose as well.
I don't really understand this impurity thing.
What is it?
Something that can be found anywhere?
It doesn't look like a spider or a centipede for sure.
It isn't normal for them to look like insects.
So it isn't normal to have this many insects?
That's right.
Only in our town?
Why?
Who knows.
Do you mean you don't know?
You can't not know.
They just appeared all of a sudden?
I don't know...
You don't even know when they first appeared?
I don't really know.
It seems like you're hiding something from me.
Then let me at least ask you this.
Why do they look like insects?
It was a moth today, right?
I don't know.
I see.
So, why is it bad when impurities show up?
Bad things happen when they possess you.
I become impure when I touch them.
So, you're exorcising impurities that are here for some unknown reason...
...because they might cause bad things to happen, right?
What the hell is that?
That's no different from that anime yesterday.
Have you ever thought about why you're even doing this?
Shut up!
What's with you?!
I told you not to ask!
Have you forgotten already, bird-brain?!
She got mad again.
This always happens when we talk about stuff like this.
You've always been evading my questions like that,
but it ain't gonna work today!
I'm the one getting hurt here!
At least give me a reason!
If you don't know, then think about it!
Nagi-san?
Hey, hey.
Yeah, I heard about it.
Who knows.
What kind of reaction was that?
Like pushing on a curtain.
Like driving a stake into rice brans.
It's so hazy.
What is this feeling?
Everything is left unclear and ambiguous.
I think you should pull yourself together.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
My mistake. I heard rumors that you were triple-timing my daughter.
My emotions got the better of me.
How about some tea?
No, as long as you no longer misunderstand, I'm okay...
I've had enough...
So that was your circumstances.
I thought it was strange as well.
My daughter choosing a man like you...
Umm... Sensei...
I'd like to ask your advice about something.
It's actually about Nagi.
Oh, about Nagi-kun?
Is it something I can help you with?
What is it?
She is a god!
A god?
She said so herself.
Stupid Jin...
Why am I so irritated?
I see... So she's a god.
This is the first time I've heard that she was a god.
Was she a god?
Yes.
Well...
A god, huh?
A god...
Umm...
I've heard stories like this before.
Should I say... she's a bit too receptive?
There are people whose personalities change due to certain incidents.
There's a theory that it's a mental disorder,
while others call it spiritual.
I don't really know.
Some call it "being possessed by demons" or a spiritual medium.
But there are times when the other personality tells lies...
In the name of gods or demons.
Is Nagi a ghost?
I can't make conclusions with words like that...
But I've heard that lowly spirits try to pass themselves off as noble beings.
Of course, I haven't concluded that she is one.
I just gave an example.
But what if that were the case?
What should I do?
If we consider occurrences from overseas,
there are possible methods such as exorcism.
But they are...
They?
I don't think they are anything evil.
Nagi-kun materialized from the statue made from the sacred tree, right?
Yes... well...
Japan's Shintoism has more diverse beliefs compared to those of other religions.
Should I say free-thinking?
There are fewer laws like the belief of an absolute god, or the prohibition of idol worshiping.
First off, there are no other cases of having infinite gods.
To face up to them,
the first thing to do is to understand their identity clearly.
Identity you say...
I don't think they are evil.
But even if they call themselves gods, we can't be sure.
But Nagi herself says that she is a god.
She only says that herself.
Do you have any clues?
Or any proof that she might be a god?
I can't refute that.
She definitely looks mundane.
From what I see, her actions and words are quite ambiguous and vague.
That might be how she got used to this lifestyle.
This is what I think.
Either they're speaking of gods solely for their own ends,
or they falsely believe that they themselves are gods.
The soil here is my body.
" The tell-tale sign
of used goods     "
My followers are my beloved children.
They are all cute.
I love them all.
How cute they are.
How happy they are.
Grow up healthy.
That is enough to satisfy me.
How fun this is.
How happy I am.
Being a god is a good thing.
Ouch.
For the sake of the land, I have to exorcise the impurities.
They are troublesome.
Only in our town?
Why?
Well, who cares.
He doesn't understand himself?
That's right.
Jin joined the arts club saying he wanted to search for himself.
Although I think it's pointless to just copy Daitetsu-kun...
You won't understand yourself in just 15 years.
Yeah, you're right.
I don't understand either.
But I hope he finds what he's looking for.
I wonder how you can find it.
There's no point in thinking about it, right?
Eh?
When you don't know what to do, you should just act according to your emotion and intuition.
That's what I always do.
Yes.
Trying to think about things I don't understand is meaningless.
Act according to emotion and intuition.
Geez.
I always have to bear the brunt of your selfish actions.
You understand?
I don't have any choice after all.
Thinking about this is meaningless.
Why won't you explain it to me?
When I'm looking after you so much!
Shut up!
Don't ask me that!
I don't have to think about things I don't know!
Being here!
Living like this!
What's wrong with that?!
What do you want me to do?!
Are you going to doubt me as a god?
You're always evading my questions like that,
but it ain't gonna work today!
At least tell me the reason!
Think about it if you don't know!
I see...
I don't even know the answer myself...
I wasn't aware of the very fact that...
I know nothing about myself.
In any case, if you don't know anything about her, you should find out.
Excuse me.
She claims to be a god, yet you know nothing about her...
How could you have lived with something unknown like that for so long?
I guess I'm not one to talk though...
Eh?!
Only this?
The enshrined deity is unknown?
This unknown identity is going way too far.
How am I supposed to find this out?
If there's nothing in the official records...
I'll have to go directly to the related people.
Huh?
Nagi?
Next time on Kannagi...
What happened, Jin?