Well then, I'll head to the bath.
I guess I'll join you.
Let's see...
What's this about? I'm at the onsen right now.
Subaru-sama, please...
That is...
The prize from the contest.
You'll do anything because I have this ticket, right?
Yes...
Would you please read this book aloud for me?
Of course.
How exciting!
Jirou-kin and Barusu,
Eloping!
What?
Jirou-kin, it's my first time.
What is this erotic novel?
Yes, at that place, take your glasses off...
Barusu...
Jirou-kin...
Wait...
You don't need to...
Y-you d-don't ne-need to take them off...
I - can - fly...
It's my First Time
It's my first time
Subaru!!!
Why do I have to be in such a situation?
Jirou?
Why are you in the male's bath?
You know exactly why!
I guess.
I somehow managed to fool them by saying Punyuru had returned.
I see, sorry.
I will leave first.
Go ahead, Jirou!
I understand.
Father?
Jirou, come here quickly!
You were here, you brat!
Oh!
Just when I thought there wouldn't be any people here...
Say, how do you know my daughter?
What?
We're just friends and close classmates.
Nothing more, nothing less.
Well, if that's all...
I knew you didn't have a relationship with her...
Lately, she has been having fun attending school.
You seem to be quite worried.
Where would you find a parent that doesn't care about their child?
I mean, I am talking about that cute Subaru of mine!
Seeing your face really pisses me off after all.
Like hell I will stay in the same bath with you any longer!
Let's wait here until he leaves.
Yeah...
Why did you come here?
Wha...
You said it's a training camp for eloping or curing my gynophobia or something like that.
Even your father came as well.
It seems like there was some sort of reason for coming here.
Say Konoe...
Hey, brat!
What is it?
You're still here?
I found something that perfectly resembles a girl's underwear.
Whose is this anyway?
A-Actually I'm that type of person.
What kind of excuse is that?
Subaru's underwear were like this as well...
Why the hell do you know that?
Don't tell me...
What?
You bastard!
You had this type of relationship with Subaru?
Wait...Calm down!
Shut up, you brat!
Konoe!
I wonder if Punyuru-chan will come here...
I'm sure of it. Yes...
Say, I am having temporary memory loss for some parts of last night.
Why was I sleeping in the bath, I wonder...
Do you know something?
No...
Say, is Punyuru-chan really coming?
I wonder...
You are only leaning your neck that way!
W-Well...
Then why is your neck bending like that?
I wonder if I had a stiff neck while I slept...
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Oh!
We were a bit late...
I was choosing glasses, so it took a while.
Punyuru-chan!
I wanted to see you!
Well, yes...
Where is Subaru-sama?
I had him run some errands.
Hey, did something happen?
Now let's go!
What!
Wai- Hey, let me go!
Wait up, Suzutsuki Kanade, why are you holding hands with idiot-chicken?
Because he is my fiancé.
Like I said, you were lying right?
it can't be helped...
Let me tell you the real thing...
He is actually a gynophobic.
Why do you know that?
Hmmm, you seem to know as well.
Hey!
Say Jirou-kun, won't you play the shooting game in that shop?
How about you as well...
Hmph, bring it on.
Hey!
YES!
Ah, sorry, I shot and killed the rabbit.
You mean shot and dropped, right?
And, I'm Usami, not a rabbit!
Ah, you were here!
Since there are more people...
There will be an event soon...
What is this event?
A yukata beauty contest.
It's a battle royal.
What is that?
There is a fireworks display at the end.
It's something to look forward to, right?
Right, Punyuru-chan?
Hey, I don't see her here.
She was with her just awhile ago...
Hmm...?
Where is Konoe?
Would you like to know?
I will now do a tongue twister...
Butler's art of erasing memory...
Butler's art of erasing...
Barusu, I want to see everything of yours!
Go back...
Don't interfere.
Interfere?
What is Konoe doing?
None of your business.
Nothing like that!
I am her friend.
Tomorrow is the anniversary of her mother's death.
The young master of Takanashi's house is near here.
Takanashi?
We ran off to get married!
Lots of things happened when we married.
That's why she is sleeping in the graveyard of the Takanashis'.
If Kanade-ojousama goes out on a trip, then Subaru must follow.
So if she does that, Subaru wouldn't be able to visit the grave on the anniversary of her mother's death.
Then Suzutsuki was doing this for Konoe?
Nagare!
Ojou-sama!
I also want to participate in the event.
Please go and enlist me.
I understand, Ojou-sama.
Did you hear all of it?
Yeah...
She said she wanted to keep it a secret, from you at least...
What do you mean?
That is a secret.
What?
That's a problem between you two.
That's why I had to get rid of Nagare.
Do your best.
Jirou-kun!
Jirou!
Why?
I heard...
About your mother.
I see...
Takanashi Family Grave
My mother was always worried about me...
Wondering whether I would make proper friends or not.
Just as my mother had worried about, I never had any friends.
I was always unsociable and distant from people...
It can't be helped.
You were always hiding the fact that you were a girl...
You tried not to be in contact with anyone in order to prevent them from discovering your secret.
Sorry Jirou, please leave me alone.
I didn't want to come here with you.
Konoe!
Jirou!
You idiot!
Let me go!
Come on now...
You're afraid of girls...
If you do this, you'll fall unconscious again!
So what?
Don't hold it in!
Tell me everything...
Jirou!
I don't want her to be worried anymore.
That's why.
Even though I decided I wouldn't cry...
I wanted to introduce you to my mother.
As my first friend.
But she's not here anymore...
I would be reminded of it if I came here with you...
I was sure I would cry.
That's why I didn't want to come here with you.
I see, sorry.
Say, Konoe...
Can you introduce me to her?
About me, to your mother.
Yes...
Mother...
Sakamachi Kinjirou, he is Jirou.
He is... my friend...
Whoa-
Thank you Jirou, you are my...
Morning, brother!
What the...
I'm surprised you hit your head after falling down when you went to pick up Punyuru-chan!
I must go now...
Where to?
To the battle royal!
So you're competing as well?
Since the grand prize will be a large stuffed sheep plush doll.
Konoe loves that as well...
And a kiss from the Yukata beauty contest.
What?
I want to reintroduce the Yukata beauty contest winner...
Takanashi Punyuru-san!
Yay, for the silent sheep!
What is that?
I definitely won't let you win!
What?
Because I can't accept someone like you receiving a kiss from Punyuru-chan!
I won't accept that type of development with anyone but you and Subaru-sama!
Ok, everyone that's a battle royal participant...
Line up at the starting line...
Kill, kill, kill, kill... Kiss, kiss, kiss... Kill, kill...
The rule is very simple...
If you're hit with a single bit of paint, your game is over...
The winner receives the grand prize and kiss from the Miss Yukata beauty.
Hey!
Now then...
Start!
First the solo players...
Ah!
Kureha!
Brother!
Sorry!
You idiot!
We don't have time to do that!
First we have to deal with her!
Here she is...
Nakuru!
Ah, senpai, you were over there!
What's wrong with her?
This is bad!
That girl gets drunk from drinking carbonated drinks.
Huh?
Usami-senpai is a very maiden-like person...
Dodge and take, drunken fist stripping!
What! Drunken fist stripping?
She has this drunken behavior of being able to strip someone while she is drunk...
Usame-senpai!
What is this?
When did you?
I saw an opening!
She wasn't much...
If it's battle of strength, then I am on top of you.
These eyes that wear glasses can overcome anything.
No way!
Here, here, here!
Kureha!
As if you could win against my tickling attack...
Eh?
Next is your turn!
You don't have to worry cause I'll leave your glasses alone.
Only the glasses, just wonderful!
I can't lose.
At any cost.
I will win!
Don't move.
Suzutsuki!
Looks like we were the only ones left...
When did you?
If you surrender, I'll consider letting this hostage go...
Hostage?
No, that is just cruel!
What sins have they committed?
No!
Stop!
I surrender!
So please!
Here!
No, darling...
What the, this is a... déjà vu?
Hey, my glasses!
That was just a dummy!
I prepared them because I thought something like that might happen.
Man, how good are your preparations?
Say, Jirou-kun...
Get away from me!
You tried your best even though you were a chicken.
You were cool for a moment there.
I can't have you win...
The one who won the battle royal is...
Suzutsuki Kanade!
So you were awake!
Where is this...
Don't misunderstand me.
You didn't get up so...
I didn't have any weird intentions by it...
I wasn't secretly watching your sleeping face...
Where are Suzutsuki and the others?
Nakuru-chan went on a rampage, undressing people around her since she thought your glasses were broken...
What?
Ojou-sama went to tell her that they weren't, so everything will be fine.
I think it will go smoothly.
I see...
Ah, that's...
Ojou-sama gave this to me as a present.
Good for you.
Yes.
It's creepy after all.
Creepy?
You don't get its loveliness?
Unfortunately, not at all.
Have a proper look!
Everything is so lovable about this!
I got it!
Are you sure?
Really, I do!
Please stop that!
Oh!
I kind of feel like the summer is about to end.
We're still in the middle of August.
Yes, but the summer will end in an instant.
I feel lonely that the summer vacation will end but,
but I can live with you or Ojou-sama when the second term comes around.
I had lots of fun.
Well it seems that the second term will be be a hectic one as well.
I am already used to it.
That has become our everyday.
Right? We'll always be friends!
Oh!
I don't like this.
I don't want to be just friends...
I can't take it any longer!
It's coming out!
It would go out!
No way!
Because...
I can no longer hold out!
Seriously?
It can't be helped, right?
Stop!
Aren't you ashamed?
Something like being embarrassed...
Jirou-kun, please watch over me!
What kind of shyness play is that?
What are you saying?
What I'm saying is...
Next time on Mayo Chiki:
Episode 9: I will go out on a journey for awhile.
I will go out on a journey for a while