Subaru, I'm coming in.
O-Ojou-sama, please wait one moment.
You're not dressed yet?
I apologize.
I'll fix it for you.
Sit over here.
Are you nervous about starting the second semester?
No, that's not...
Liar.
Look, your heart's beating so fast.
Did something happen recently?
You really shouldn't take it all upon yourself, Subaru.
It's nothing really.
Does it have something to do with Jirou?
Did he ask what pattern you have on your underwear?
Just kidding. However, please tell me if you have something on your mind, okay?
Nyu!
It's the new school term!
Makura Hold!
Texas Clover Hold!
Buster Crack!
I have morning practice, so I'll be heading out first, okay?
Jeez, even though I'm used to it, getting it in the morning is tough.
Morning...
Morning.
Let's go.
Do you still think that I'm going to leak your secret?
I believe in you, Jirou...
as my best friend.
We're best friends.
Is that so?
But I apologize.
Hm?
I didn't heal your gynophobia.
If it were that easy to heal, I wouldn't have gone through the trouble.
You're right.
Ojou-sama said we should pursue newer, more extreme programs this semester.
I humbly decline.
It can't be!
Move!
You again?!
Jirou, look out!
Konoe?
I just remembered when I performed CPR on you.
Oh yeah, I kissed her...
Are you okay?
It can't be.
What are you doing?!
Two guys kissing?
And in the open too!
What are you getting so excited for, Idiot-Chicken?
I just happened to land like this when I dodged.
I said to move.
But what's up with that bike?
I bargained for a restoration.
Are you okay Subaru-sama?
Why is your tone different with him?
I'm not injured. How about you?
I'm f-f-fine.
I'm sorry!
P-Please take this as an apology.
Excuse me!
What was that all about?
What should I do with this?
Why don't you just eat it?
Since Usami just ate from there, wouldn't that be an indirect kiss?
Let's hurry, or else we'll be late.
S-S-Sorry!
I-It's fine.
It's a miracle!
For you to have finished your homework!
Of course I did.
You were able to copy it as compensation for working at the maid cafe right?
Ehh?
Yeah, that's right.
How did you know?!
Actually, I have the ability to remember everything I hear.
You sound scary right now.
Ojou-sama, class will be starting soon.
Thank you.
Oh yeah, Jirou-kun.
You're going to eat lunch with Subaru, right?
Let me join you as well.
Here you go.
What an amazing lunch.
You don't need to hold yourself back.
I'll split it up.
Along with Subaru's.
Ojou-sama, allow me do it.
It's fine.
Eat.
Here you are.
How is it?
Delicious!
This succulent meat covered with a creamy sauce has an incredible flavor.
What kind of food is this?
It's just an ordinary cream stew.
It's hot.
Konoe?
Ah! Stop!
It's hot.
Suzutsuki, why is Konoe acting like that?!
Maybe it's the white wine I used for the flavor.
I didn't add that much, but she still ended up like this.
She's too sensitive!
What's wrong with being sensitive?
Oh, he got dirty with sauce.
Subaru, clean it up.
Understood, Ojou-sama.
Stop!
This sauce is delicious.
Right?
Please stop.
But it's good.
Suzutsuki, do something.
If I do something, this won't be considered treatment.
Hey, I'm your best friend, right?
I also think of you as my best friend.
So please stop.
I don't want to ruin our relationship.
Ow!
Shut up!
It's your fault for saying that.
Saying that?
Jirou, I have something to tell you.
I...like...
What are we going to do about her?
Suzutsuki?
We should let her rest a little.
Can you take her to the nurse's office?
This isn't a girl.
I want to turn into a bug. Turn into a bug!
What was she going to say back then?
What a sight for sore eyes.
It's only the beginning of the semester and I've already seen something great.
A bespectacled man carrying a battle-weary boy holding on for dear life-
Shut up!
Jirou-kun!
If it's about Konoe, I let her sleep in the nurse's office.
Oh...
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Nyu!
Nyu...
Hey, what was that cute voice?
I heard it too.
Hey Suzutsuki?
Are you okay?
Are you not feeling well?
Why would you ask that?
Because you...
...said "nyu."
Y-You're just imagining things.
Think about it.
There's no way I would let out such a voice.
But...
Stop being persistent.
I told you it's nothing nyu.
Nyu?
You're wrong nyu.
There's a reason for this nyu.
Stop looking at me so pitifully.
Nyu.
It was your voice?
What? It's completely different from that other cute voice.
It was my voice nyu.
Don't mess with me!
Nyu.
Nyu~
Something's wrong with my throat.
Are you okay, Jirou-kun?
Let's go to the nurse's office nyu.
Let's hurry.
Nyu~
Are you really okay?
Yes...
The truth is... I have a secret that the school doesn't know.
Secret?
Yes nyu.
Jirou-kun, this is...my...only weak point.
Menyu.
Milking cow.
What did you do to the nurse?
After I slapped her cheeks a few times, she left nyu.
While crying.
With a wad of cash again?
Sort of.
But what was that before?
They're hiccups.
Hiccups?
Right nyu.
When I get the hiccups, they don't stop nyu.
See, like this.
It just sounds as though you're adding "nyu" to the end of every sentence.
My hiccups seem to have a personality nyu.
They mostly occur at the end of the sentence.
But why is that considered your weak point?
How should I say it...?
Because the people around me think I'm cute nyu.
What?
You put it so bluntly, but I never thought you'd praise yourself in the process as well.
Quiet nyu.
Well, it is cute.
Really.
Jirou-kun, help me stop these hiccups nyu.
Eh, sure.
Huh?
I tried to hug you?!
Ojou-sama's hiccups are devilish.
Konoe?
You may not believe me, but people who hear Ojou-sama's hiccups,
especially the boys, are attracted to them.
That's a lie right?
It's true.
They even caused an incident once.
An incident?
Around ten years ago, Ojou-sama was still in grade school,
when she was invited to a party.
Please let me stop Ojou-chan's hiccups.
As a last resort, the SP couldn't control the crowd and they had to rely on the
Tokyo Metropolitan Police.
In the Suzutsuki household, this is referred to as the Hiccup War.
What an enormously exaggerated and stupid story.
A similar incident happened four years ago but Subaru calmed the war nyu.
Oh... That's just like her.
Yes, Subaru's the best butler nyu.
Thank you very much.
What are you doing?
How cute...
Subaru?
This isn't what you think, Ojou-sama.
It's not that I think the cool Ojou-sama that I know would let out such a cute voice.
I understand, so let go nyu.
It's fine if I hold-
This is wrong.
Sorry, I'll let go immediately.
Konoe, are you alright?
Jirou, shut up!
Or what? Are you trying to take my cute Ojou-sama away from me?!
What are you saying all of a sudden?
I won't forgive that.
I'll END you!
Calm down!
Subaru, go to the mansion and bring the equipment to stop my hiccups nyu.
You have that kind of equipment?!
But leaving your side is...
Having you suddenly grab me doesn't help either nyu.
That's true.
Then, excuse me.
Are you worried about Subaru?
Was it okay to let her go?
I wanted her to leave nyu.
Think carefully.
If I called and asked someone to bring it, it would be over too soon.
Then why?
I wanted to be alone with you nyu.
Jirou-kun, I want to know nyu.
What happened between you and Subaru nyu.
The way Subaru acts toward you...
You should've noticed too nyu.
What did you say to Subaru nyu?
I d-d-didn't say anything.
Liar.
If you won't tell me...
Stop!
Ow...
What's this?
It's the equipment to stop the hiccups.
I brought it from the mansion.
Wasn't that way too quick?
But Jirou, what's up with your clothes?
And Ojou-sama too.
It's nothing, Subaru.
Jirou just tried to take advantage of me.
It's you who tried to take advantage of me!
Well, my hiccups stopped so let's go back to class.
When did it stop?
Let's go, Jirou-kun.
It stopped so suddenly.
You did say that it's your only weakness.
Did you do it on purpose?
Girls hold many secrets nyu.
But Jirou-kun, you really are too nice.
It was fun being alone with you.
What are you saying?
What's that supposed to mean?
What?
It's not like I really meant-
Suzutsuki!
Ojou-sama!
Konoe!
Suzutsuki!
Are you alright?!
I'm fine.
Ojou-sama, can you stand?
Yes...
Ojou-sama?
Ojou-sama?!
Suzutsuki-san's in trouble.
What?
They even have a hospital under their management?
You're making too much of a fuss over a sprained ankle.
Just to make sure, please get a thorough check up.
I'm very sorry.
Even though I was with you.
It's fine.
It's not your fault.
It was my carelessness.
But...
I'll tell father too.
That's why you don't have to worry.
I will bring you something to drink.
Konoe.
You look like the one that's seriously ill.
Hey.
What's wrong?
Hey...
What the hell are you doing?!
Old man!
You look like you want to be admitted.
It's not what it looks like!
Subaru.
I'm sorry. Even though I was with her, I allowed her to get hurt.
Go home and rest.
No, I will stay at the hospital.
I'm telling you to go home and rest.
But, I have the responsibility of taking care of Ojou-sama's belongings.
I'll do that.
You're not a butler anymore.
Why, old man?
She let her precious Ojou-sama get injured.
It's obvious that as a butler, she has to take responsibility.
Subaru, you've done well.
You gave it your all.
So rest now.
Wait!
I won't forgive Subaru if she quits
because Subaru is the best butler.
Ojou-sama, this has already been decided.
I'll tell my father.
I'll definitely persuade my father.
It's impossible for Subaru.
And if she stops being a butler, she doesn't need to be a boy.
If Subaru goes to school as a girl, she would...
Ojou-sama, where are you going?
It's obvious. To see my father.
Ojou-sama, it's fine!
Subaru...?
Thank you for taking care of me up until now.
Although I wasn't perfect, being your butler really...
Made me happy.
Jirou-kun, please!
Konoe!
Wait, Konoe!
Let go!
Like I would!
Even if I fall, I won't let you go.
Jirou...
Don't shoulder everything by yourself.
Your feelings of sadness.
Your feelings of regret.
Let me shoulder them.
I'll bear anything.
After all, I've been putting up with Kureha's techniques every morning.
Jirou...
But it's okay.
Now you don't have to keep the secret.
So it's time to say goodbye.
I'm at my limit...
Konoe...
I'm not a butler anymore.
I'm not a chicken-
You're not?
I'll be a beast now.
I'll be a bold and wild man.
Let's go, Konoe.
Jirou!
Leave it to me.
Okay, but make sure to put it on.
I know...
Put it on thick.
If you don't, I'll...
You really do have to put mayonnaise on takoyaki.
Next on Mayo Chiki Episode 12:
The Butler Who Got Lost and I, the Chicken.
Can the two of us start over again?