Do you think I'll let you score any more points?
Here I come!
This is for Moka-san! Drive Shoot!
It's over! Victory by one point!
Tsukune...
Moka-san.
Is this really fine, Tsukune?
I'm so happy, Tsukune.
Moka-san...
This is the first time you've given permission for me to suck your blood.
Kappuchu!
Thanks for the meal. Thank you, Tsukune.
You're welcome...
Does she really understand my feelings?
You're going to be late if you don't hurry.
I don't think so.
Tsukune's blood... Delicious.
Everyone, let's join a club!
Club?
It's over! Victory by one point!
Tsukune...
Moka-san...
The purpose of this school is to let demons adapt to human society.
We must be same as humans.
Let us gain a deeper understanding of humans by
working in their society and coming in contact with their art.
To perfectly transform into a human, you must first have a clear understanding of them.
You guys must constantly be vigilant and not let others know your true form.
About that, Teacher...
Yes?
Your tail.
There's a lot of clubs here...
Let's go Tsukune, let's join the same club.
Let's take some paranormal pictures together...
No!
Acupuncture.
We are the Mummies club.
Ah!
If you want to create love potions, you must join our Chemistry club.
Come, Moka-san.
Please drink this.
Please hug me.
Does this school not have a decent club at all?
There's no way it would!
My name is Ichinose Tamao.
Let's swim together.
It's a swimsuit.
And all of them are cute.
The Swimming club seems to be normal.
So far, the Swimming club only has female members.
Any guys who join now will receive special services from the seniors.
How about you, do you want to join the Swimming club?
Let's take a look, Moka-san.
I had experience with soccer... no, I have gone to swimming school before.
If it's swimming, perhaps I can show Moka-san my good side.
Tsukune, you're so cool!
And...
Does it look good on me?
Of course.
Tsukune?
Anyway, let's go take a look first.
But I... with water...
Looks like she's not interested, how about you come over and take a look?
I will take good care of you.
In many ways...
I'm going too!
What beautiful legs...
Idiot, what's the use of getting excited over legs? Look at the breasts, the breasts!
I wonder if Moka-san... Doesn't know how to swim.
Don't give up, be patient.
Something good will come soon.
Moka-san's swimsuit.
Geez, what's Tsukune thinking, being all flirty?
You move your arms like this.
Erm... Senpai...
What's it, Tsukune-kun?
Don't you think you are a little too close?
My... You don't like me?
Tsukune-kun, you're cute.
Come Tsukune-kun, move your arm once more.
S-Soft...
Enough of this!
Moka-san?
You joined the swimming club just to get close to the girls, right?!
No, it's a misunderstanding.
What's to misunderstand? I can't stand this anymore!
I'm leaving first!
Let me explain, Moka-san!
I won't!
Moka-san!
It's like a children's fight, how boring.
What men and women need to do is merely "snatch" and "grab".
Do you understand the meaning of that?
This is the Swimming club, if you don't want to swim then leave.
You are so bothersome.
Water...
Wait up, Moka-san! Moka-san!
Tsukune, I've come to the swimming club!
What the-
I came too!
It's the hot chicks!
How is it possible? Idiot, I'm happy.
It's voluptuous...
How warming.
Tsu-ku-ne, teach me how to swim.
Umm, Kurumu-chan, your breasts are...
Oh my, my breast are hurting.
This is my chance! I must make Tsukune mine today.
Is this swimsuit a little too small?
Tsukune-san, please teach me how to swim too!
I won't let Kurumu-san get her way.
What are you doing? Tsukune is mine!
How is that possible?
Give it up, flat-chested girl.
It's not like bigger is better.
It's really too big...
When I was your age, they were already about this size.
I heard that big breasts sag earlier.
You're saying that my breasts will sag...
You little brat.
What are you doing, you milk cow!
Now, now...
Shut up, Tsukune!
You don't even wear a bra yet!
That doesn't matter!
You...
Moka-san...
You idiot, why did you go near the pool?
It's natural that you feel this way when you come into contact with water.
Water is a vampire's weakness.
Water has a strong purification effect, which is why vampires fear water.
When our demonic powers clash with water, then...
This is also the reason why Moka-san washes her face or something, she uses water which has been neutralized by herbs.
Your body is also a host for me!
You must calm down and not let that man fool around with you.
Tsukune...
Everyone! It's starting!
I don't know why my tears can't stop flowing.
I should be happy but my tears came flowing again.
It hurts!
Yahoo!
I won't forgive you!
Lets go, everybody!
Yahohoo! I'm first!
Hey! You're getting in my way!
Oh my, I didn't notice...
White and black...
No, we must settle this between the whites and reds!
Let's go!
Yahohoo!
Hey Yukari-chan! That's cheating!
Your huge breasts are just too much!
Moka-san...
You seem depressed...
Is the performance of our Swimming club not up to your standards?
No, that's not the problem....
How about going for a swim with me?
I'll let you forget all your frustrations.
Yahohoo!
N-No~!
Don't even think of going back to the Swimming club.
Do you still want to experience that feeling again?
Stop having relationships with humans.
That guy doesn't even understand you a single bit.
He doesn't think of you at all.
No way... Tsukune isn't anything like that!
Even if you go to the Swimming club,
you can't swim together with everyone anyway.
That's all right.
I only want to be with Tsukune.
Do you care about Akashiya Moka that much?
Forget about her and look at me...
How about it, Tsukune-kun?
Ichinose-senpai...
Just call me Tamao.
You know, I've had my eyes on you since school started.
I've always been fascinated by you.
I'm sorry, Tamao-senpai.
I really have to go... I have to find Moka-san.
Oh my... You can't do that.
I won't let anyone escape.
T-This is...
Don't blame me...
For luring the guys into the water then sucking their life energy out.
This is originally how mermaids survived.
Mermaids are known as the unlucky monsters of the sea who cause sea troubles.
They are also very famous amongst seafarers.
It is rumored that they lure humans with their beautiful bodies,
causing them to sink their ships.
T-Tamao-senpai!
Haven't I said before?
I've had my eyes on you since school started.
Because you... Smell just like a human!
Hogging him is unfair...
Give me some too...
Me too...
Tsukune!
Tsukune-san!
Move aside!
I'll take care of you if you get in our way!
This is...!
Tsukune!!!
Wait for me! I'll rescue you right now-!
You idiot! Do you want to die?!
Seems like the rumors are true.
Akashiya Moka's true form.
Water is a vampire's weakness!
If this goes on, Moka-san will...!
Moka-san!
I won't let you escape.
You're mine.
Let go!
Quickly! Take this chance!
Moka-san... Just for me...
Just to rescue me...
You jumped into the water...
Once the rosary on her chest is removed,
The vampire blood within Moka will awaken.
You dare...
You dare do as you wish?
Such an oppressive feeling...
I've never expected it to be such,
but you're still a vampire after all.
Take this!
I won't let you girls do as you like!
Heh.
Mind your own business.
What're you talking about!?
Since you're weak in water, just be frank and accept others' help!
You poor thing...
Getting such a reaction just from getting wet
must feel very painful, isn't it?
Stop pushing yourself and just die.
You don't have to care about me.
I can finish a small fish like you even with my eyes closed!
Small fish?
I won't lose even if I die!
Water is a vampire's weakness, yet water is a mermaid's territory!
You have no chance of victory!
Take this chance and beg for your life!
Don't make me laugh.
You're too slow!
You actually fell for my trap so easily...
You're really a fish after all.
Die!
Know your place!
I actually got defeated so easily...
This week's winner was determined in 85 seconds!
That's obvious though.
The air isn't a mermaid's territory.
Exactly!
Are you all right?
Even though the vampire power was released,
I guess the water drained Moka-san's power-
Don't be so smug.
You don't understand her at all.
Someone as selfish as yourself has no right to be beside me.
The other Moka is crying.
The one who didn't understand her was actually me...
Moka-san didn't come the next day...
It's also called that, for example, his favorite would be fish or something...
I'm sorry, Moka-san!
I...
If Tsukune wants to join a club, just join the Swimming club.
Even though I can't swim, I can cheer for you from the poolside!
You can't do that! What if you got splashed by water?
I... I don't want Moka-san to be in danger because of me.
I'll be fine! If you'd like-
No! You definitely cannot join the Swimming club!
No way...
Why don't you both join the Newspaper club instead?
Newspaper club?
That's right, I'm the advisor!
The Newspaper club is fine too!
I finally found new members!
Hold up! I'm joining too!
Me too!
Oh my! There are four!
Shizuka's so happy!
We'll be in the same club with this, right Tsukune?
Kappuchu!
This is bad!
Tsukune-san was kidnapped by the peeping tom!
Eh? It'd be great if Tsukune peeped at me!
Eh!?
If this is the case, let's prove Tsukune's innocence!
Next episode, the Newspaper Club and a Vampire,
and a kappuchu for you!