Ah, those meat balls look tasty!
Give me one.
Sure, here you go!
I'll trade you my tamagoyaki.
Are you going to stop by the station on your way home?
I heard the new macaroon is on sale.
That's a good color after all!
Does it use gloss?
No, just the lip.
How nice! Where did you buy it?
Go Out With Me
Get out of the way!
Safe!
Ahhh, I thought I was dead.
Hm? My glasses?
Crap, that probably would have been my deathbed!
My school's uniform?
Umm, hello...
Thank goodness, she's alive.
What should I do? I crashed into a person!
I have to call the police!
No, I'll just pretend it didn't happen.
Well, I'm actually fine.
Wah! Why are you still alive?
A-Are you truly human?
You're quite the rude one.
My body can withstand more than an average person thanks to circumstances at my house.
You're a student at my school, right?
What's your name?
Why are you asking me that?
It was an accident after all.
I should at least know your name, shouldn't I?
No, I don't want to tell you.
Then what year are you in?
Second year.
So, the same as me. What class are you in?
Why did it have to end up there?!
H-Hey, what are you looking at?
Well, there's something I want down there...
Something you want?
It's a bit hard for me to retrieve it.
Would you get it for me?
Why should I do such a thing?
If you don't want to, I could get it myself, but...
Eh? Wait, could it be...?
Stop!
NO!!!
What are you doing all of a sudden?
Shut up, you pervert! Why would I let you strip me?!
Strip you?
Die! Eat shit and die!
Huh? W-
Woah! That was close...
What's that?
My glasses.
Could it be...
That was what you wanted to get?
That's right. What the heck did you think I wanted?
Why didn't I realize it before?
Pink~
You're not much of a fight, even though you're her older brother are you?
How do you know about Kureha-
I really, REALLY can't believe this.
Why does it have to be you?
It's coming out... Something's coming out!
Hey, tell me.
Why does someone like you...
have to be Subaru-sama's friend?
What?
Since I asked you, I'll tell you my name as well. I'm Usami.
Rabbit?
Not "Rabbit!" I'm a Roran Academy second-year, member of the textile arts club.
Usami Masamune!
Textile arts club, is it?
Nurse's Office
It hurts!
Damn, that girl!
Are you all right?
Konoe?
Jirou, I was startled!
I was surprised to have found you lying face-down on the road.
I even brought you to the academy.
Were you hit by a car?
Well, something like that.
What?!
I'm all right. I didn't get hurt.
I see. If you say so, then it's fine, but...
Say, Jirou, you said things in your sleep that I couldn't quite understand...
Sleeptalking?
"Please forgive me, my queen!"
"If you keep stretching me like this, I might start to see a whole new world!"
Or like,
"I'll give it back! Please forgive me already! Oh my lord!"
And there is...
What she did earlier went straight to my subconscious!
Could it be that your heart is in turmoil?
There's no problem!
Now that I think about it, where's Suzutsuki?
Wasn't she with you?
She's in class.
That's right.
Have you been avoiding her?
To be more precise, ever since the end of the Golden Week.
If you have something that is bothering you, then tell me about it.
We're friends, right?
I can at least give you some advice since we're friends.
Konoe!
But there is one condition.
Condition?
I want you to go with me to the school festival.
School festival?
Ojou-sama seems to be busy organizing the event.
I was told to enjoy the festival and not worry about her, but...
I don't know how to have fun at a school festival.
That's why I want you to go to the school festival with me.
You're such a fool.
Don't worry!
Let's go together, to the school festival!
Thank you!
I am sure it'll be a fun school festival!
I guess so.
Okay. I will listen to whatever is bothering you!
Let’s see...
You don't need to be so stiff!
Please listen to me without jumping to conclusions.
I'm a butler.
I won't get startled by the little things.
Say whatever you want.
Then, here I go!
Actually, it's about my first kiss.
Why are you saying such things now?
Could it be, Ojou-sama?
I was surprised, because it was rather sudden.
I am surprised as well!
Because that was my first!
She said the same, but...
Is it the truth?
Don't say foolish things!
It really was my first time!
Of course! My bad.
I wish I had a chance to do this all over again.
What did you say just now?
Like I said, I wish I had a chance to do this all over again.
You want to do it again?!
Right now...
Right now!?
Well, we certainly are alone.
But I still can't accept that!
Okay!
At any rate, why...
Hurry up!
Eh?
If you're going to do it, then do it fast!
Do what?
I never thought you were such an uncooperative person!
What are you going on about?
Like you said, a kiss.
You said you wanted to do it.
Eh...what?
Here I go!
What are you doing?
Ojou-sama...
This is not what you think.
I don't mind what you do,
but please be careful.
In this place you are a male, so...
My deepest apologies!
Morning, Jirou-kun!
I feel like it has been a while since we have spoken like this.
I'm going to go back to class ahead of you guys.
No, I won't let you escape.
Bitch, you know I'm gynophobic!
And this is part of your therapy.
You came all this way to do that?
No.
Our class finally decided on what to do...
So I came to tell you!
What is it?
A Crossplay Café!
A Crossplay Café?
Everyone wants to see Subaru cross-dress.
You like to dress up cute,
don't you?
Now then...
You dropped something.
That was inside my shoe locker.
You received a love letter in this day and age?
What do you think?
Of what?
What would you think if I were to accept the confession?
Well, I don't think there's a problem if you go out with him.
I see.
Say Subaru, what would you do?
If I were forcibly kissed by the sender of this love letter?
I would kill him.
I would never forgive anyone who would do that to Ojou-sama.
Thank you, Subaru-kun!
I can count on you!
Are you all right, Jirou-kun?
You look a bit pale!
Do you want to take some aspirin?
I'll even give it to you mouth-to-mouth
Well then, I will see you later, Jirou-kun.
After I have declined the confession, I will return to the classroom.
Well then, take care.
This all happened because of her!
Damn you, you ill-mannered rabbit!
Who is ill-mannered?
You!
I have important things to talk to you about!
Dododko dodosko, mayiichuunyuu!
Do these knee-highs and this slender upper body belong to Konoe? What?! It's me?!
Go out with me.
What?
Not, "What?" I'm telling you to go out with me.
To be more precise, I want you to pretend to be my boyfriend.
At least until the end of the school festival.
Let me tell you right now; you do not have any right to refuse.
What's your problem?
Is there something you have a problem with?
Of course I do.
You called me out here just to mess with me.
It's obvious that I called you here for a serious conversation.
This is my favorite spot.
This is where I can be alone.
And...
This is where I saw Subaru-sama for the first time.
To be honest, it was love at first sight.
Eh?
Do you know what S4 is?
It's Konoe's biggest fan club in the school right?
S4...
Shooting Star Subaru-Sama.
I'm a member of that group.
So that's why she was acting that way earlier.
During this year's school festival, there's a secret S4 event.
What do you mean by a secret event?
A war.
We, the S4 and the Watching Over Subaru-Sama club are going to have an all-out war.
What does that have to do with me going out with you?
If you, who is believed to be dating Subaru-sama, are now going out with a girl...
It'll shake up the other group that wants a Boys-Love relationship.
So you do understand.
But I don't get why I have to take part in this.
Of course, I won't ask you to do this for free.
When we win, I'll vouch for you and tell them not to touch you ever again.
What? You don't want that?
Are you dissatisfied with my looks?
No, you're really cute, but...
R-really?
T-then it should be fine, shouldn't it?
Well, it'd still be a problem for me.
Sakamachi Kinjirou!
Sakama Chicken Jirou!
Don't call me by my full name!
A chicken, just like your name.
Are you that afraid of angering Subaru-sama?
Huh? Why would I anger Subaru?
There's no use in playing dumb.
The reason S4 and Watching Over Subaru-Sama are fighting is because you're going out with Subaru-sama.
I'm telling you, that's a misunderstanding.
But you guys are so friendly with one another.
And you guys eat lunch together.
Huh? That's normal for friends.
Subaru-sama isn't normal.
Other than his master, Kanade, he stays away from everyone else.
But you, she let you get close to her for some reason.
That in and of itself is abnormal...
Hey...
I have proof.
Where were you looking from?
When I went out shopping,
I happened to see you.
You gave him a stuffed animal as a present.
And it looked like you were about to embrace him.
No, that's... uh... my...
That's right.
It's your hobby, isn't it?
If you didn't make him do such a thing...
Subaru-sama is acting more feminine...
There are rumors spreading about his feminine side...
If they find out she's a girl, Konoe will be...
That's right.
I made Konoe do it.
So delete that picture!
You won't get off that easily.
You have no choice but to go along with my plan.
If you don't, I'll spread this picture around the whole school.
Jirou?
Konoe? Why?
I was looking for you because you weren't in class.
Who's that girl?
Shu-Shu-Shubaru-sama...!
Hey, say something.
You can't expect a normal student like me to converse with him!
You explain it!
What do you mean by "you explain it"?
Just say that you're my boyfriend.
Eh?
What are you two whispering about?
I'll introduce you.
Her name is Usami Masamune.
This might sound sudden, but we're dating.
That's not a very funny joke.
Konoe...um...
What are you to Jirou?
Why don't you say something?
We're really dating!
We even promised to be alone together during the school festival.
Eh?
Jirou, is that true?
During the school festival, you're going to be on a date with her?
Yeah...
You even promised...
Jirou, you liar!
Ko-Ko-Ko-Ko-Konoe...
Are you okay?
I'll pretend I'm your boyfriend until the end of the school festival.
So don't spread that picture around.
I know...
Then after school, let's practice dating.
Since you're my boyfriend, go shopping with me.
I need to buy something for the school festival.
What is Class B doing?
A swimsuit café.
A scorching hot adventure!
A swimsuit café?
That's why I'm buying a swimsuit.
Then go shopping with your female classmates.
I don't have any friends.
Time to try it on.
You can come in.
But only your head.
Hurry up!
You're my boyfriend, right?
Sorry to barge in!
How is it?
Weren't there any other ones, like a bikini?
How could I wear such a thing in front of my classmates?
Well, it isn't bad.
Really?
Then I'll go with this.
If you don't take your head out now, I'll cut it off.
Buy this for me!
Why should I?
B-Because I'm not even in the swimming club and if I bought this full-blown swimsuit, it'd be embarrassing.
What if they think I have some weird hobby?
I'm not in the swimming club nor am I a girl!
Buy it yourself.
Just buy it for me.
I refuse!
Here!
Hey!
This swimsuit is kind of warm.
She just wore this.
What are you being silent for?!
You're not smelling it, are you?
Idiot! Pervert!
Like I'd do that!
Here...
I'm going this way...
The train station is that way.
I'm walking home.
It would take at least an hour from here.
It's a waste of a train ticket.
And I need money to repair my bike.
I have to be frugal this month.
Bye.
I'll walk home too.
I've been skipping training.
You'll get home late.
Well, Kureha said that she'd be late because of the school festival.
How about you?
I...
It doesn't really matter.
There's no point in going home early.
Sakamachi Kinjirou.
Huh?
Sakama Chicken Jirou.
Like I said, don't call me by my full name.
We have to think of what to call each other.
We have to be friendly with one another or it'll be awkward.
Friendly...
Usamin!
Do you want to get kicked off of here?
No, please don't! Really!
Hey, until the school festival ends, you and I are dating.
Which means we're lovers right?
Then promise me one thing.
Promise?
No matter what happens...
Believe in me.
Huh?
I'll believe in you too.
So...
Believe in me.
Okay, I'll believe in you.
Hey.
Usami is fine.
Eh?
Call me by that name.
You don't need to add the honorifics.
Friendly?
That's fine with me.
You're Idiot-chicken.
Huh?
Idiot-chicken.
Being an idiot and a chicken, doesn't that suit you perfectly?
What about it suits me perfectly?
I'll be counting on you Idiot-chicken.
That's name-calling!
Hey, Jirou-kun.
I want to do something that starts with "S."
Start the laundry?
What are you saying?
Something more tempting.
Shakespeare!
Something more exciting.
Um... sexual harassment?
I'm already doing that to you.
You are?!
I'm sure you don't have personal experience...
You don't mean...
Se-Se-!
Next time on Mayo Chiki:
The Sixth Story: Let's Start a War.
Let's Start a War