Maybe she's gone...
Can't be, huh?
Why am I getting nervous?
Crap, I'm too dragged into her pace.
Let's go all out-
What are you doing?
It broke...
I stepped on it when I was half-asleep.
This stick is weak.
Jin, go buy me a new one.
Me?
I want a tougher one.
One that can withstand an elephant's stomp.
Go find a stick which isn't so unlucky.
No! I don't want to!
Yesterday was really embarrassing!
I won't forget that woman's expression. Not in this lifetime!
This is an instant adhesive. The usage instructions are written on the inside.
Remember to spread some newspapers, okay?
And your breakfast is in the kitchen.
I'm going to change.
Please leave.
He sure is busy.
Remember to place the dishes in the water after eating. I'm going out for a bit...
Jin!
Jin! Over here, hurry!
Aren't they so?
Aren't they so what?
They're so cute! I don't know why, but I feel like crying!
I want to squeeze them! Hug them! Cuddle them!
I woke up to their calls this morning!
They were purring so earnestly!
I couldn't hear anything though.
Oh yeah, I heard a stray cat just gave birth recently, are these its offsprings?
Jin, I just thought of something!
Let's keep them.
Rejected.
Why?!
I heard they have a mother. A grey cat with stripes.
You can't kidnap cats, can you?
Besides, our house is a rented one, so keeping pets is forbidden.
But...
I've already said no.
Anyway...
I'm going to withdraw some money now.
Keep still, okay? Eat your breakfast.
Breakfast...
At least... at least give them some milk!
You can't feed the kittens cow's milk.
Your breasts are too small to give any milk, so give up.
"Haw haw haw haw haw"... that's what you're thinking, right?
I'm not thinking about that.
Maybe a bit.
If a kitten doesn't drink milk for one day, it'll die of dehydration!
We just need to check them once in a while.
I don't want that!
I want to keep them!
A god? She sure doesn't behave like one.
I'm back.
I TOLD you to spread some newspapers, didn't I?!
This isn't like what you're thinking!
How do I explain it... I don't know about this?
The truth is, I have split personalities, so this was her fault...
Cook up a better lie next time!
Wow, what's with this perfect adhesion!
Now what? It's been quite a while so it's totally glued on!
A cloth hanger.
There's no such ornament in a dining table!
He's acting a bit strange.
Is Jin okay? It's tough for a boy to be living on his own.
He definitely needs a cute childhood friend to support him.
Hang it up yourself!
And why aren't you bothered by me handling it?
I am busy, and it takes the same effort anyway.
It's just that I don't feel like doing it. Besides, if I get seen by others...
Tsugumi!
The one talking to you on the phone yesterday?
Who is she?
I'm done for! She's the person that you shouldn't be meeting the most!
She's Tsugumi, my childhood friend.
My father entrusted me to her...
If she finds out that I'm cohabiting with a woman I don't know, it's over...
Could it be...
That I'm causing trouble for you?
You're so late to notice that!
You've been causing me trouble since yesterday!
Anyway, I'll go explain to her.
Stay here!
Don't do anything unnecessary. Got it?
Um...
Tsugumi. It's a long story...
I only knew her yesterday-
You don't need to explain...
Huh?
No, I don't mean that.
I shouldn't be interfering in your relationship...
But if you skip school like that, I'm not sure how to answer to your father...
As I said...
Hey.
I apologize for my impertinence earlier.
I'm Jin-kun's relative.
My name is Nagi.
Huh?
Relative?
I'm Jin-kun's half sibling, born from a different mother.
Huh? No way! Nobody told me about that before.
It's not a surprise that you'd be shocked.
Jin-kun also came to know of me only yesterday.
But that can't be! You were behaving differently just now...
That was the other me.
Huh?
In the family I was raised in, even laughing aloud is prohibited.
It was strict and insular.
The constant pressure caused my personality to split into two.
I am deeply sorry to have shown you a disgraceful side of me!
Oh no!
And that's the explanation?
I can't bear to stay in that house anymore!
I know that it is selfish of me, but this is the only place I can go to!
I'm sorry! I've misunderstood you.
But won't they come to take you back soon if you stay here?
That family only think of me as a burden.
They'll just pretend that I've simply vanished and not inquire to the police to look for me.
How could that be?
You're joking, right?
Oh my, that looks very delicious.
You can stop pretending already.
I can't believe you're so articulate, leading her along like that.
Oh my, and I thought you finally understood that the stick situation was not Nagi's fault.
Uh... really?
Nagi really knows nothing about that stick.
Please don't berate her for it.
Huh?! Split personality?!
Is it really okay to take her in?
Your father is working right now and you can't contact him, right?
Well... but I don't have a choice.
It's hard to believe such a thing could happen.
But it's possible, taking your father into account...
Someone's talking about you, Father.
Say, I'd like you to keep her situation a secret as much as possible.
She hopes you do so anyway.
I understand.
I can't just go on telling others about something like that.
But that's only if nothing happens.
You were entrusted to me, after all.
Okay.
This is far enough. Remember to eat the side dishes.
Sure. Please send my regards to your mother.
Omelets...
There are omelets in there, so eat them, okay?
Okay...
See you at school tomorrow then.
Damn it!
I can't take it off!
It's no use. Looks like I'll have to get some detachment solution.
Damn, how did it get stuck so cleanly in the middle?
That made me laugh my ass off!
While I was applying the adhesive, my hand slipped!
It made a beautiful half-turn and scored a ten-point landing!
It was magnificent, but I just burst into laughter!
I rolled around laughing for a while after that!
Wow...
Wait a minute... why are you talking about that incident?
Oops.
I've let the cat out of the bag.
You tricked me, you swindler!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I did that out of impulse!
Don't use your polite speech again! Are you a god of misfortune?!
What's wrong with her?
Man, it's gross.
It's horrible, I saw it directly with my eyes!
It was there since forever.
Poor thing...
Looks like it's hopeless...
Isn't that the kittens' mother?
I woke up to their calls this morning!
How long ago was she not around anymore?
This morning? Or even earlier?
If a kitten doesn't drink milk for one day, it'll die of dehydration!
If only I had listened to her...
You've dried up, haven't you.
Such ill fate.
That's right, you don't know what hate is yet.
Cross the river.
Will the earth of the netherworld be too hard for you?
Nagi?
You're Nagi...
Aren't you?
That was...
I'm hungry.
Will this do?
It'll be troublesome to prepare something else now.
It's troublesome, so how about noodles?
Nice pun! Oh you!
You'll be fine if you're this energetic.
Say...
The kittens... died, didn't they?
You're right... Such a pity.
From what I saw, you've taken those kittens into your body...
What was that? What happened?
You were also acting like a different person.
After that you fell unconscious.
You ask too much!
I'm a god. Of course I'm able to use powers that are beyond human understanding.
Do I need to explain each and every detail to you?
Know your place, child of humans!
Can you just give me an explanation?
After all, I'm the one who carried you into the house.
That cup noodle is also mine.
I never asked you to save me!
Hey, what's with that attitude of yours?
Are you an elementary school student?
I'm worried about you-
That's enough, stop asking!
A follower like you is a few hundred years too young to be worried for his god!
What's wrong with you? I won't help you again if anything happens!
I don't need your help in the first place!
Look who's talking! Without me, you don't even have anything to eat!
I don't want your crap!
Get out!
You've been doing whatever you wanted since yesterday!
I don't care whether you're a god or not!
I had enough!
I'm not going to put up with your bullshit any longer!
If you're not happy, leave!
Fine, I'll leave!
So pathetic.
This is so stupid.
Jin's the one at fault.
Because he asked me such weird things...
What's this? There's something frilly attached to it.
Someone must have forgotten it and left it here.
But this is strange...
Strange, strange!
I've seen this before! It's used to decorate the altar in my house!
Brats.
Don't touch that!
Sis, who are you?
Me?
I'm a priestess.
Priestess?
I exorcise bad demons with this.
Aren't you just a weirdo?
Who's the weirdo?!
Ow Ow Ow Ow!
She's weird.
I knew she's a weirdo.
Miss Weirdo, we're going to play, so don't bother us.
Okay. Let me join you then!
What do we do?
I'm fine with that!
You have so many toys!
What's this ball?
It's a superball!
You don't know?
Don't tell me if you collect seven of these...
Nothing like that.
Look!
Wow! This is a wonder!
Um... I think I'll go home.
Miipu, you're saying that again!
You're always like that lately. What's wrong with you?
Are you not feeling well?
It's not that...
But these days I can't enjoy myself...
And things just aren't going well...
Father and Mother are quarreling too...
Quarrels happen every day in my house too!
Never mind, just leave him alone. I don't care about him.
I'm sorry!
Miipu!
Stop right there, Miipu!
Your troubles are within the jurisdiction of a priestess...
so how about it?
What?
There's an impurity clinging onto your back!
Now's the time for an exorcism!
I thought she's a weirdo, but she's a fraud?
That's not right! She's a religious person!
Mama says that they'll ask a lot of money for offerings.
I won't take any money from you!
Hurry up and show me your back!
An impurity is a naughty, naughty bug.
In your case, it looks like a frog.
Humans can get along well with impurities in their daily lives.
But impurities that have turned into bugs are distinctly different.
They are beings that have solidified from people's hatred and negative emotions.
When they possess people, they turn into misfortunes.
But as long as we have this purification staff!
A purification staff is a god's cleansing-
Your explanation is too long.
And it's annoying.
Hurry up and do it!
Kids nowadays... Well, fine.
It's just one impurity, I can beat it without Jin's help!
I just need to finish it off in one attack.
How... how absurd!
Wait!
You...
Don't run!
Stop!
Can you see anything?
Stop running!
Nope.
Alright.
Keep still.
This is the end!
How cunning! It's got intelligence?
My ball!
Retrieve it, weirdo!
I know! Wait there, brats!
Where did it go?
It's coming for me!
I should go and call Jin...
No! I can't ask him for help after how I've treated him!
Damn it!
A place out of people's sight.
A simple terrain.
An enclosed space with no blind spots.
Come at me anytime, you impurity!
I'll give you a clean hit with this purification staff!
Just like Sharapova returning a ball.
It's coming.
Now! My ultimate attack!
I can't see it!
I can't see it at all!
Is my plan backfiring on me?
But luckily...
Its accuracy is low.
Jin!
Geez, stop wandering around!
You made me look all over for you.
Here, hurry up and kill it.
Okay.
A beautiful girl, a land deity and a guardian deity!
I won't forgive the impurities!
Stop that.
You should've lured the ball to a place where it can't bounce around, like a grassland.
Well...
Besides, you have poor reflexes, don't you?
Even though you kick people.
Umm... are you mad at me?
Yeah.
But...
Knowing what kind of person you are, I resigned myself.
I'm used to dealing with your type of people.
Where are we going?
We're going home.
I've bought you a rice bowl anyway, I don't want it to go to waste.
I don't have much of a choice, huh?
Why are you used to my type of people?
My father is like that too.
You have a weird father.
Look who's talking.
Did you get spanked by your father as a child?
With a weird father, your butt's got it tough.
What's with this god?
That weirdo's not back yet.
We got tricked.
My shoulder ache is gone.
Miipu, you talk like an old man!
Watch the next episode of Kannagi too!