Idiot-Chicken!
What are you doing, Idiot-Chicken?!
Masamune, why...?
I got a call from Suzutsuki Kanade.
She said she could contact neither you nor Subaru-sama.
Oh yes, I must go...
Hey wait, are you all right?
Wow, stripes-
Where were you looking at?!
S-Sorry!
Konoe, I'm coming for you now.
The Butler Who Got Lost and I, the Chicken
What are you doing, Idiot-Chicken!
Look in front of you!
Thanks.
Is Subaru-sama really here?
Probably.
How do you know that?
Because he's my best friend.
I see.
Best friend, eh?
Bye.
Idiot-Chicken.
Be... Be sure to bring Subaru-sama back!
Yeah.
I knew you'd be here.
Jirou...
The fireworks back then were beautiful.
What are you doing here?
I came because I was worried about you, obviously.
Let's go home. Suzutsuki is worried about you, too.
Even if I do, there isn't a place for me to return to.
That's not true.
Up until now, being a butler meant everything to me.
I don't care what you are.
Even if you quit being a butler,
it doesn't change the fact that you're my best friend.
Thank you,
but I don't want to go home today.
I understand.
You should be careful because the owner of this inn doesn't know about Subaru's secret.
Yes, I know.
It's too bad for you, Jirou-kun.
Why's that?
If it weren't for your special constitution,
you could have had your very first experience.
If that happens, I'll kill you! I'll murder you!
Murder you! Murder you! Murder you! Murder you! Murder you! Murder you! Murder you!
What's wrong, Jirou?
Oh, nothing...
You didn't have to stay.
I can't leave you alone.
Excuse me.
Please.
Oh, you still haven't eaten yet?
Sadly, I have not.
It's fine, Konoe-sama. Take your time.
By the way, how was it with Kanade-ojousama after that?
Well, that's...
Oh. Please, don't feel too bothered by it and be more optimistic.
I'll be laying down the futon later.
Futon? So it means we are going to be all alone?
What's wrong?
N-Nothing...
I see.
I'm going to go bathe.
Oh yeah, she usually uses the men's bath.
Are you asleep?
How can I sleep?
R-Right...
You can't sleep either, Jirou?
How can I sleep in a situation like this...
In a situation like this?
You know, all alone with a girl in the same room...
Then what would you normally do in a situation like this?
Well...
You could have had your very first experience.
I'm sleeping!
Jirou...
Huh?
Don't you want to do anything further than kissing?
First experience...
A-As a healthy man, I'd want to do that...
But I have this special constitution...
I'm okay doing it with you.
What?!
First experience...
First experience...!
I won't- do it now.
Huh?
It's more like...
I don't want to do it on impulse or because of a whim.
I want to do it only when I sincerely want to become one with the person I love.
With the person you love?
I see.
I-Is this a good idea?
You're so warm...
K-Konoe...
Konoe!
Konoe-!
I just wanted to sleep together.
I just saw my life flash before my eyes.
Thank you.
When I was little, my mother used to do this to me when I couldn't sleep.
I see.
I'm going home tomorrow.
I don't want to trouble you anymore.
But... I can't go back to being a butler.
You're fine the way you are, like a normal girl.
It's too stimulating, to actually be with her...
Hey, you didn't do anything to my daughter, did you?!
How was last night?
Ojou-sama!
Thanks to you, I had a fitful sleep.
Oh? That's good for you, Subaru.
Huh?
How unfortunate.
What were you expecting?
Ojou-sama, how are your injuries?
It's still a bit swollen, but I'm fine.
We'll go on and head to school.
Let's go back to the mansion first.
I'll give you a ride too, Jirou.
I was really worried.
I'm sorry, really!
But for you to suddenly go on a trip with Konoe-senpai...
Don't tell me, Nii-san... that you've awakened your homosexuality!?
Jus Face Lock!
Master Lock!
Original Baro Special!
Nooooo!
I haven't awakened!
I was so worried, Subaru!
Kosame?
You're supposed to say, "I'm home, Onee-chan!"
When did she become your little sister?
This touch, this softness... it's the best!
You used this confusion as a chance.
Kosame, let go of Subaru.
We have to go to school.
Ojou-sama.
Are you okay with this?
Yes.
Good morning, Jirou-kun.
What happened to Konoe?
Subaru...
transferred to another school.
First experience...
I've never felt anything like this...
Su...Subaru-sama~!
How could you quit being a butler?
An academy life without Subaru-sama... is like a homosexual without a partner!
Subaru-sama...
Konoe-senpai quit being a butler?
Everyone, go back to your seats.
I will introduce a transfer student.
Wow~!
What?
What?!
This is the transfer student, Takanashi Punyuru-san.
N-Nice to meet you...
Punyuru-chan, I'm so glad we got to meet you again!
Let's continue our conversation about glasses!
N-Nice to be with you, Narumi-san, Sakamachi-san...
Oh, you can just call me Kureha.
Which school does Konoe attend now?
Who knows?
Why are you hiding it?
Because...
Oh, Nii-san!
Punyuru-chan transfered to my class!
We're classmates!
N-Nice to meet you.
Punyuru, call me Kana-oneechan at school.
S-Sure, Kana-oneechan...
All right then, Nii-san, see you later~
Laters~
W-Wait.
L-Let's have lunch together, P-Punyuru-chan!
Nii-san tried to hook up with a girl!
Y-Yeah...
Are you fine with that?
You can reject him if you don't want to.
Nii-san has never been that popular with the girls before.
You don't have to pity him.
She said she was fine.
What?!
Why?
Why is Subaru-sama coming to school as a cross-dresser?
All right, see you later, Sakamachi-senpai.
Oh, wait, Punyuru-chan!
Geez, you could have told me about this beforehand.
Shall we get going too?
Oh?
Yeah...
Okay then, Jirou-kun, carry me like a princess.
What?!
It's hard for me to go down the stairs with this leg.
Oh, I see.
But why me?!
Subaru isn't around.
Whom else can I rely on?
Jirou-kun...
Huh?
Being treated like a princess isn't that bad after all.
Suzutsuki's body... is quite lighter and softer than I expected...
Her breasts are pretty big as well...
I'm sorry we're late for class.
It's all right.
Amazing, Punyuru-chan!
As I expected, girls with glasses have exceptional accuracy.
We can expect great things at the sports festival.
Oh? Yes...
Let's go.
Oh.
Jirou, sorry to have made you wait.
I thought you might not come.
A lot of boys kept talking to me.
I see...
What's wrong?
Wh-What?
You don't look too cheerful.
That's not...
You want to go back to being a butler, right?
I would if I could...
Konoe...
I thought it'd be fun being normal high school girl,
but I feel very lonely...
I thought I was the one protecting and supporting Ojou-sama,
but it was actually Ojou-sama and my job as a butler that were giving me support.
I understand. Leave it to me.
Jirou?
This extreme bloodlust...
It's coming.
You stole Subaru-sama's first kiss!
How could you have come here!
Because you were a failure, Subaru-sama had to transfer schools!
There!
Got it!
What?
He's good.
My mother is a professional wrestler.
And my little sister trains me every morning!
But I'm here today because....
I beg you to cooperate!
I don't care what you do to me!
But in order to save Konoe...
Please cooperate with me for the time being!
I want to talk to you about glasses.
If you don't mind, come to my house to have some fun!
Please assist us!
I'm begging you, please!
Please!
The Look Over Group and S4...
Oh, Nii-san?!
Please help Konoe so that she can go back to being a butler!
Please sign our petition!
I will help, too.
Masamune...
I want Subaru-sama to stay as a butler.
Nii-san, I will help too.
Me too.
Kureha... Nakuru...
Is this where I sign?
Suzutsuki...
I want Subaru to remain as my butler, too,
if she desires it as well...
Everyone....
Punyuru-chan, can you sign it too?
Please!
I-I...
Punyuru might not know much about Subaru.
However, Konoe Subaru is an outstanding butler who is loved by everyone.
Please.
Please sign.
With this many signatures...
I will take this to my father.
Please, Ojou-...
No, I mean Kana-oneechan.
Ojou-sama, here.
Thank you.
Konoe-senpai, good for you!
Congratulations on your return.
Thank you.
We have to let Punyuru-chan see Konoe-senpai in a butler uniform.
Punyuru had to transfer again.
What?!
But we'll get to see her again, right?
Until then, it's farewell to Punyuru-chan.
Why doesn't anyone realize this obvious disguise?!
But I feel happy for her.
Jirou-kun.
Thank you. You supported and protected Subaru for me.
I've always wanted to become a man who could protect someone.
You're a man who can protect someone important to you, Jirou-kun.
If something were to happen to me, would you protect me?
Y-Yeah...
I also-
Huh?
Nothing.
This is only the beginning.
I should sleep.
I wonder why Konoe told me to come immediately.
Konoe, what's wrong?
I wanted to thank you.
Thank me?
It's all thanks to you that I could be a butler again.
So... Thank you very much.
I'm also happy that you've cheered up.
Jirou, you are really kind.
Well, I came dressed like this because I wanted to thank you...
But you already did...
I don't mean that... I'm talking about the best I could do for you...
Close your eyes.
Aren't we good friends?
I want to thank you not as a butler,
but as a girl.
I want to repay you.
Wait.
You don't like it?
Of course not.
Then...
But you see...
So you don't want to after all?
Of course not...
Then...
But still...
Kiss already.
Otherwise, I would.
Ojou-sama...
So it was your orders.
W-Wait, you!
Geez.
If you don't cure your fear of women, you can't make any progress.
The tale of a wandering butler and a chicken without a pair has only just begun.
When will the story between one courageous boy and one devoted girl begin?
Kureha-chan, I want to become like you!
What? Really?!
So please squeeze my breasts.
Grope them and grip them firmly.
Are you sure? Here I go.
It hurts, but I will bear with it since I want to be like you.
You love me that much?
Yes, I love your itty bitty breasts!
What's wrong with itty bitty breasts?!
In the next episode, Mayochiki, Episode 13.
Please fondle it!