Hello? Jin?
Tsugumi? Are you free now?
Do you have to do something later?
No, nothing in particular.
Then can you help me with some shopping?
I see.
Then let's meet at the entrance of Hip Walk at 2:00PM.
Tsugumi-san!
Nagi-san.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
It's okay.
Umm... what about Jin?
Yes, he said he'll be counting on you.
I see...
You're a great help! I have no experience shopping at such places.
I would have no idea how to do it correctly.
Oh... Is that so?
You shouldn't, Tsugumi!
It's you who misunderstood!
Nagi-san isn't at fault!
Return to your normal self!
What's the matter?
No, nothing!
Umm so... What do you want to get?
First of all, some clothes.
A complete set of underwear too!
If possible, shoes or a bag...
I also want to look at some accessories as well.
So, what's your budget like?
Tada!
10,000 yen...?
Yes!
If there's any left over, I'll treat you to something!
Ex...
So expensive!
Why are all of them so expensive?
This shop is already quite cheap!
Gosh, she doesn't know anything about the market price...
What kind of wealthy lifestyle has she been living?
If I put a glittery heart-shaped keyholder sold at 100-yen shops on this bag,
can I insist that it's from Sama*tha Thava*a?
If you talk about Sama*tha Thava*a while wearing those anime clothes,
our already few number of female viewers will snicker.
10,000 yen...
What does he expect me to do with this?
You want clothes?
That's right. Right now, I can barely change my clothes.
You're a god, aren't you?
Can't you just make clothes appear?
Don't ask for the impossible!
I'm wearing these clothes merely because they materalized along with my human figure.
Because...
a human is always clad.
All right.
But you should have Tsugumi take you along on matters like this.
Here, 10,000 yen.
Can I really take it?
I was a fool to be so ecstatic!
Jin is such a penny-pinching miser!
Does he expect me get by with three sets of jerseys?!
Well, guys tend to go for the cheap stuff.
Hey, you wanted to look at some underwear too, right?
Let's go take a look.
I never knew underwear came in so many shapes!
These are completely different from the ones that I'm wearing!
Huh? They're different?
It's a big difference!
Jin should have bought this kind for me from the start.
Jin bought...?
Frilly and fluttery!
This is so cute! So cute!
Yeah, I think those feminine ones suit you!
Miss, you can try them on. Please go ahead.
Try them on? I will, I will!
Nagi-san?
Tsugumi-san, what's your cup size?
I'm... Umm...
My size fluctuates between B and C.
And how I especially become a C after I get fat...
This is Tsugumi, 15 years old, talking!
But Nagi-san is clearly smaller than me.
I may offend her if I tell her the truth.
I'm a C-cup.
Well, that's average among the Japanese.
Uh, okay...
What am I saying?!
Is... Is that so?
I never considered her feelings!
Average...
Idiot! Idiot! Tsugumi is a terrible woman!
Since this bra is so "roomy", that must mean...
In other words... No! I mustn't think too deeply about it!
If you're going to buy one, the prices over here are just right.
They're more for teens.
Is that so?
Right price, huh?
I'm being pitied!
What is this sense of defeat I'm feeling?!
Am I rubbing salt into her wound?
Gosh, Tsugumi, you're such a tactless woman!
Well then,
where is my size, a B-cup?
You're a B... That's unexpected-
Oh yeah, that's just about right.
Even though I say it's B, it's rather closer to C, I think...
Taking into account my growth in future, perhaps I can even go for a C.
Is this your first time here?
Yes.
Please come this way.
With your body, D might be too small for you.
Huh? But...
There are many girls who wear smaller sizes because they're shy.
But it's recommended to wear a size that fits your body...
Pardon me, but may I ask how old are you?
TL Note:
That's about 13 years old.
I'm a first year junior high student.
See, you're still growing!
I think you should choose a larger size.
Girls nowadays are so developed-
Nagi-san, that's a D-Cup-
Because I'm still growing?
Because I'm still growing!
Thank you very much!
I'll persuade Jin and get my revenge next time!
Next time, shall we visit a cheaper shop nearby?
Is that okay with you?
You can't wear three sets of jerseys all the time, right?
A girl needs a lot of things.
You're right! Three sets of jerseys is too little!
I'll talk to Jin as well.
Should I get a part-time job?
Jin.
Good morning.
I'm thinking of going to a maid cafe.
TL Note:
Tanabe Akira is the editor of the Kannagi comic, and he decides the vital parts about the plot, thus he had to be persuaded to make it a 'maid cafe' chapter.
Perhaps we can go if we ask the person-in-charge, Tanabe-san.
Leave such inside jokes to the commentary!
I'm serious! I'm really going!
But don't those shops only exist near the capital?
Hang on.
A maid cafe even opened up in this city.
In this provincial city?
While that does raise the question of "Why only now?", it's still a surprise.
Maid cafe?
Daitetsu, so you were here.
But why do you want to go?
If you ask me, that place is more for guys...
Only at a maid cafe can I rightfully stare at cute girls in frilly clothes.
It's just like you to think like that.
But if you like frilly clothes, you can just wear them yourself...
No, that's not it! You're missing the point!
I want to look at cute girls wearing the clothes!
Do you get me?
No, I don't.
But...
I'm hesitant about actually going.
You see, otaku-culture is a bit unique, isn't it?
So I'm wondering if I can get an expert to escort me there...
Just kidding!
Since just now, I've been trying very hard not to get involved in your discussion...
But why do you assume that all otaku are knowledgeable in that area?!
Huh? You mean it's not true?
That's prejudice!
You're wrong if you think that all otaku go "moe"!
Seriously... Misunderstandings arise when the media stereotypes the entire population based on a small minority!
Even the pronunciation is wrong to begin with!
If I nudge him in this way, he'll talk a lot.
I've never heard anyone say "moe" like that!
Or should I say, aren't those people just non-otaku making fun of us?
In the first place, who the hell would address an otaku as an otaku?
Hey, is it all right for me to go to a maid cafe?
Ah, that's totally fine.
There are many female customers anyway.
People who are not otaku also come often because they find the place unusual.
Oh, is that so?
Let's set the date for this Sunday then.
Everyone, keep your schedule open!
Huh?! We're going together?!
I'm really glad Nagi isn't here today.
Of course! You have to turn up!
I don't want to teach her this kind of weird culture.
She'll imitate it immediately.
Ah, they're here.
Good morning.
Hey, Akiba-kun!
Why did you choose to meet here?
It's closer than the train station.
Is everyone here?
Mikuriya! You didn't bring Nagi-sama along?
Obviously I couldn't bring her!
Well, okay.
Well then, Akiba-kun, be sure to explain things thoroughly for us!
That's why I called you here.
You're a bully.
But don't you seniors know a lot as well?
TL Note:
腐女子(fujoshi=rotten woman) refers to female otaku, particularly those interested in yaoi or boy's love. It's derived from the word 婦女子(fujoshi=lady)
You're fujoshi after all!
Huh? Lady?
Well, it's true that I'm a female.
Huh? Did I estimated them incorrectly?
Hey, what's that? Was that slang?
Hey, tell me!
Nope. If you're not, it's fine. In fact, just stay the way you are.
Hold it there, Akiba-kun!
Takako-senpai in her home clothes looks just like an office lady.
Maid café
Maidia
Maid Rice
The shop manager's
recommendation!
Today is a service day;
We're having a
special event
Welcome home, Master!
Welcome to Maid Cafe Maidia!
Looks like they're wearing maid clothes that don't look like maid clothes.
TL Note:
A title typical of a gal-game.
This is the cosplay of "Kamatte★PureHeart Trois ~Sunao Ni Narenai~"!
Looks like they're having a tie-up event.
Tie-up?
They do this often for the publicity as well as fans of the game.
My, I guess we're lucky then.
Not lucky at all! I came here to look at maid uniforms-
Please come this way!
But this isn't so bad.
Wow! Nice smile!
I'll take you to your seats!
Okay!
This is the first time I'm seeing a cosplay.
Daitetsu?
Uh... wait!
Senpai, please calm down.
So, what kind of sci-fi battle fantasy game is this?
No, it's just a modern-day drama...
Liar! Who would wear such unbelievable clothing in modern time?!
Now that's something you shouldn't say.
Anyway, please calm down.
Please place your orders if you've decided.
I'll have an iced coffee.
I'll have that too.
I'll have this apple cinnamon tea.
Daitetsu-kun, you keep looking down.
It's embarrassing.
Look!
What is it?
Did you see her?
Who? I was looking at the menu, so I didn't really notice...
Someone who looks like her? No, that's impossible.
Shoot! Why is he here?
Aoba-san! Please help with the hall!
Coming!
Why...
Why is Jin here?
And so is everyone from the Arts Club!
My friend got sick all of a sudden, but even so,
I shouldn't have taken her place for her part-time job!
If they see me in such embarrassing clothes...
They're here.
Yes. They are.
Furthermore, Nagi-san just happened to be working here...
I'm such an idiot to think that I wouldn't run into friends just because it's a maid cafe!
This isn't good. Why is Jin here?
I kept it from him because I'm sure he would object to me doing a part-time job.
If this continues, we'll have a big fight when we get home.
At worst, I may even get driven out!
You girls! What are you doing?
You can't keep the customers waiting!
Come on, hurry up! The customers are waiting!
Take the orders!
They've come out!
Awesome!
That's it!
What is this?!
Such high quality!
She looks like Arzelede-sama in every aspect!
The hair being genuine is amazing!
This is the first time I've seen one look that well replicated!
This kind of cosplay is limited to beauties!
Isn't the girl next to her good-looking as well?
Her hairdo says she's Malon-chan, right?
That girl has the same air about her!
I'm talking about her politeness when serving the customers and her lack of confidence!
Super-moe! Super-good-job! Super-very-good!
I'm so glad to have been a KamaPure fan!
It really is Nagi!
Hey, why is Tsugumi here as well?
Huh? Why? I've been set up?
A child caught in a trick?
Takako-senpai, look!
Just now I saw-
She joined the crowd!
I was so amazed at the excellent quality that before I knew it...
I was so amazed at the glamor and cuteness that before I knew it...
Why were you not surprised first that she was someone you knew?
That aside, what kind of surprise is this?
Mikuriya, you were trying to surprise us!
I didn't know either!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Here are your iced coffees and apple cinnamon tea.
Tsugumi-chan, you look cute!
Moe!
Stop that please.
It-It's not like I'm doing this kind of part-time job because I want to!
I'm only taking my friend's place because she can't show up.
Tsundere?
You're having it tough.
Hey, why is Nagi here?
The same reason as yours?
How should I know?! I was shocked myself!
I see.
Arzelede-sama, come here!
Can I take a photo with you?
I'd like to place an order!
Me too.
What? A part-time job?
That's so cunning! But it's certainly an effective method.
With this, she can get devotees in a short time.
I shouldn't let her do as she likes.
And I have confidence now.
Under the same conditions, I can collect more devotees than her.
That's because...
I look better in maid clothes!
Just watch! I'll interfere with her business and make her reputation drop!
Ah! Thumbtacks in my head-dress!
Just you watch, Nee-sama!
Text on the Omurice:
Netherworld
Sorry to keep you waiting. Here's your Omurice!
Excuse me, but which KamaPure character do you like?
Arzelede-sama, of course.
The gap in her nobility and her clumsiness makes her cute.
Yup, I agree!
She's doing her job far better than expected.
I'll taking the cups.
Yeah. For her.
Misaki-turn!
Then again, maybe not.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
As a clumsy character, she's functioning pretty well.
Are you hurt?
Hurry up and take it!
Stand closer.
Look here.
Nagi-sama!
Nagi-sama, come over here!
Don't just go to the other tables!
Serve your friends too.
Okay?
You have to let Mikuriya see you better too.
Come on!
Jin...
This is...
I can't...
I can't look at her in the eyes when she's this close.
Jin?
Don't come near me.
Jin, are you mad at me?
I'm only...
I'm telling you not to come near me!
Oh my.
Even though he was staring at her just now.
What's going on with that group?
I knew it! You must be mad that I took on a part-time job without your permission, right?
But Jin, I'm doing it for you-
It's not that!
It's not that...
Your clothes are too cute...
Too indecent...
So I can't look at you straight, so I'm telling you to stand back!
Realize that, you idiot!
At the maid cafe, a great shout of joy and embarrassment!
That was a good show!
Too-pure-pure-boy!
That couldn't be helped.
He didn't mean to.
But Mikuriya is a sinner.
To do that in front of Tsugumi-chan-
Akiba-kun.
You're right.
Master, help yourself.
Thanks.
Jin!
What's wrong?
What about the part-time job?
It's ended for today.
I thought I could catch up with you...
So I ran here.
I see.
You know... I just wanted to earn my own allowance.
I wasted some money the other day...
I can also gather devotees outside of school...
Is that so?
I'm sorry for keeping quiet.
But if you tell me to quit, I'll quit.
I'm not angry.
But... I didn't like it when you got your pictures taken.
That's all.
Then I'll quit!
Why? You looked like you were enjoying it.
But...
since you say so, I'll quit.
Huh? She quit?
Yeah, that's right.
You took her place.
What a pity! She was the most popular here.
Wait a minute!
I even canceled my job at the TV station for this part-time job!
I can't do anything about that.
There's no point if Nee-sama isn't here!
I'll quit too!
Come again?!
I won't allow you to quit!
With a local talent like you, our shop will run smoothly!
Nooo!
Manager, you're stronger than I thought!
Maid café
Maidia
Zange-chan
Commemoration
for newcomer
Zange-chan Rice
In Service
Letters on the Rice:
Zange
Also hairy!
Let me go!
Please watch the next episode of Kannagi too!