Geez, it sure is raining hard.
It's so damp and disgusting.
So that means the entire Honshu region is now in the rainy season.
That's what they say.
The weather will be unstable everywhere,
so please be on the lookout for sudden gusts, lightning, swollen rivers, and landslides.
It's going to be raining hard for a while.
Doing the laundry and stuff is going to get so tiresome.
Ah, I'll answer it.
What happened? Didn't you head straight home?
Well, I did but...
Oh, you can use the dryer.
Thanks...
So nice...
So like I said, I did head straight home.
But I noticed...
that I had forgotten the keys to my house.
I checked thoroughly whether the windows were locked or not.
From the bathroom windows to the ones on the second floor.
That was when I noticed a policeman waiting for me with his nightstick.
I explained that it was my house but I was taken to the police box.
Hey, do I really look like a criminal?
I'd rather get pointed at with a nightstick!
I want to scare an adult!
But little children will be frightened too!
I'm jealous! So freaking jealous!
Why are our builds so different when we've lived the same amount of time?
I want to be seen as a high school student for once!
I feel the same way too!
I'm sorry my clothes don't fit you.
No, this is fine.
Your father's was in the closet.
Oh, was it?
Which one?
The one on the left...
They really are living together.
Which one?
It feels strange.
You see, not that one but...
Deeper inside...
Don't stick to me so much!
That's because you're so dull.
You're so perverted these days.
Like the Maid Cafe thing the other day.
I-It's normal for a healthy boy!
Why am I getting all embarrassed?
It's just a conversation between a good brother and sister.
A normal inter-personal contact,
between people of such harmonious, prime aged...
siblings...?
In the first place, you're...
Are they?
What about that?
But Jin, I'm doing it for you-
It's not that!
It's not that...
Your clothes are too cute... Too indecent...
I can't look at you straight, so I'm telling you to stand back!
Realize that, you idiot!
It's even more unnatural to easily accept a sister who suddenly showed up.
Can't it be helped that he can only look at her as a woman?
But, that means...
A forbidden love?!
Am I dressed that cutely and indecently?
Yeah. I can't look directly at you.
But I'm your sister...
Aren't you even more indecent for looking at your own sister in such a way?
But I can't help myself,
since you're so cute...
J-Jin...!
Putting that aside, it's your birthday today.
I bought you a birthday cake.
Could it be that to buy that cake...
you've been working part time at the maid cafe?
It's not like that...
It was just on a whim.
Don't get the wrong idea, okay?
Thank you, Neesan.
This is the first time you've called me Neesan...
But...
Huh? What's this...?
Why does my heart hurt so much?
It must be...
the same reason why I don't want to call you Neesan either.
Jin...
Neesan, I actually love you as a woman.
Even if we're siblings, it doesn't matter.
I also think of you as...
Neesan!
Jin!
Wow, so great, just like those old dramas.
I don't know him anymore!
I never would've thought that he'd have a real interest in sisters...
How disgusting!
You traitor, Jin!
You're the worst!
Well, I fell in love with her.
Neesan, let's go to the ends of the earth together.
Yes...
What's wrong, Daitetsu?
We can talk in the living room...
S-Sorry, but I really wanted to make sure of one thing.
How do you feel about Nagi-san?
Huh? How I feel?
I'm not sure...
Well, I'd like it if she had more normal taste buds.
She's your sister, right?
Your sister. A real sister with actual proof, right?
Proof?
Then...
Well, I don't have any proof,
but she's definitely my sister.
My father always used to tell me that I had a sister...
Oh, really? He used to say that?
I thought I remembered hearing that you only knew about her existence since only recently...
Shit!
Oh no, that was my mistake.
I was able to get in touch with my father.
Then he said she was definitely his daughter...
I see.
So your father is coming back.
Shit, shit!
Uh no, he's not coming back...
Shut your mouth!
He's been studying too hard and his memory isn't really clear.
You'll catch a cold like that, so please take a bath.
I've prepared a set of clothes in the living room, so please use it.
And so, Jin and I have to prepare dinner, so please excuse us.
You really suck at lying!
You should leave the consistency stuff to me!
Your lies are full of loopholes.
I cover it up with my great acting so there's no problem.
Oh?
Since we've publicized that I'm your sister,
we have to go on with me being your sister.
I won't accept having to leave here because of your stupid errors.
I know...
This house with only children and no parents is convenient.
You also let me do what I like as well.
This is between us, but you seem to be able to support me financially as well.
You just need to think about how to let me live comfortably.
What? What is this?!
Being his sister was a lie?
Nagi-san is using this house for her convenience,
and Jin loves her.
In other words, this...
If you want me to tease you some more, pay up!
You hopeless guy!
Hopeless!
Jin is secretly paying tribute to an evil woman!
Pyramid-text:
Guy forcing tributes
Woman
Guy who pays tribute
Out of the question
So, please eat up.
Itadakimasu.
Itadakimasu!
Behind her innocent mask, she's actually...
I will discipline you!
You mongrel, you mongrel!
Scary!
But I shall not be defeated!
I will protect Jin!
Oh Daitetsu, you don't have to be that reserved.
It wasn't Nagi who made this.
It's pouch-packed.
See, isn't he suspicious of us?
Well, he always look this fierce...
I wonder.
Let's act like we're siblings from a happy family scene.
I guess so...
Jin, you're being rude.
You have a grain of rice stuck on your cheek.
That's dirty, Oneesan!
You deserve to be struck by lightning.
It is a waste of rice.
Well, that's true, but...
Besides, they say that seven gods reside in a single grain of rice.
You must consume them while greatly thanking the gods from above.
Look, there's another one here.
I can do it myself, Oneesan!
No.
But well...
Didn't that just have the complete opposite effect?
I did it just like they did in TV anime.
I... still have one thing I want to make sure of!
Wait, is this something I should be getting involved in?
This is between a man and a woman.
If I intervene and mess things up...
Umm well...
Did this come out of the closet just now?
This is the Spirit of the Tree statue you were planning to exhibit in the city contest.
Don't tell me this guy...!
Come to think of it, the face on this statue...
...resembles Nagi-san greatly.
Not at all!
Hey, is this Nagi-san?
He notices it!
Then, no more hiding and escaping!
I shall be prepared.
Yes, that statue is me!
It is me who is the Spirit of the Tree.
So it was like that.
So Nagi-san was the model.
He interpreted it like that?
What happened to that statue in the end?
Well, that was... umm...
I see. It didn't get finished.
I'm sorry, since you went through the trouble of getting me the Holy Tree from the shrine.
Don't worry about it.
I didn't ask for the Holy Tree.
Huh? What do you mean?
Well, since you said you wanted to turn the Spirit you met as a child into a piece of art,
I actually... stole it.
Really?
You did that for me?
I'm sorry about that.
I just thought I wanted to play a role in your passion.
So the sacred tree I secretly stole from the shrine...!
You deserve to be struck by lightning!
Huh? Déjà vu?
You stole it?!
Well, the construction people said they just were going to burn it.
I thought it would be a waste and-
That's called purifying by burning.
It means it would be disposed of ceremoniously.
Oh, really?
So you were the culprit who gave the sacred tree to Jin.
You thief!
A thief?
I was only doing it for Jin...
Shut up! What do you think a sacred tree is?!
Why is Nagi-san so mad?
Even if she is an occult maniac, this is too outrageous!
This woman!
This man!
I hate her!
I hate him!
You will be cursed.
According to my research, those who steal the vessel of a god have a high probability of being cursed.
Being involved in accidents and criminal incidents.
Strange phenomena and cases where they are sickened and eventually die. Cases like those aren't uncommon.
If you reflect upon your actions and repent, you might be forgiven but...
If you don't show quite a great deal of sincerity...
...it would be impossible.
It seems like Jin, who carved the statue, experienced strange phenomena.
Sooner or later, you too...
A dream?!
Unpleasantly realistic.
All because Nagi-san told me something like that!
Jin, wake up!
Huh?
The lights won't turn on!
Sooner or later, you too...
The circuit breaker didn't trip.
I guess the neighborhood must have a blackout.
Nagi must have surprised him.
She said she'd deliver divine punishment, but I hope she doesn't overdo it.
Oh, they came back on.
Hey Nagi, are you awake?
Hey, you did something to Daitetsu, didn't you?
Nagi, wake up.
I'm coming in.
Huh?
Nagi...
I just need to repent, right?
The shrine might be gone,
but will I make it on time?
I'm sorry! Please excuse me!
Please forgive me!
I won't do it anymore! I deeply regret it!
I beg you, god!
Has that girl done something silly again?
You don't have to appologize.
What you want to do with chip of wood is all up to you.
Rather, you have done well.
Be grateful for the fate weaved by humans.
Good boy.
God...?
My body feels so damp.
You don't remember anything from last night?
It's not that I don't remember, but...
I slept normally and just woke up like this.
That's called not being able to remember!
Last night, Daitetsu carried you home while you were unconscious!
Don't you remember?
Ah, that's right...
Now that you mention it... yes.
What do you mean, after I mention it?
TL Note:
This is a pun on Souieba (being told that) and Souireba (dentures).
Different from dentures.
Don't get them wrong since they sound the same.
I know. I understand.
You've gone unconcious like that before as well.
Aren't you hiding something from me?
No, I'm not hiding anything.
Don't lie!
You secretly went out to scare Daitetsu, didn't you?
What exactly did you do?
Cut it out, okay?
He isn't very good with ghosts and stuff.
And that aside, how could you go unconcious?
I've been thinking about this, but you are...
Shut up!
Stop prying!
I told you before!
Understand your place as a human!
Such a rude man!
Nagi says she remembers nothing.
Were you two hit by lightning?
No. I can't explain it well...
Umm... did Nagi do something?
Well, I think I have the answer, but...
No, I still can't explain it well.
What's with her?
It pisses me off!
Didn't something like this happen before?
It was right after she went unconscious.
I don't get it at all.
Did a god really possess Nagi-san that time?
Since she doesn't seem to remember anything herself.
It doesn't sound like a lie either.
So scary! So scary!
Still scary if it was a god.
What's with him?
Shh! Don't look at him.
No, it's too quick to consider it a spiritual phenomenon.
During that time, Nagi-san said that I didn't have to apologize.
She must have come to apologize for frightening me too much.
Yes.
That must be it.
After all, she's good at faking things.
That must've been acting.
How long are you gonna be shitting?!
Even if it were an act, I still don't understand her intentions!
Is she planning something to hide her relationship with Jin?
Crap! Am I being controlled by her tactics without noticing it?
Damn it, Jin!
Why didn't you come talk to me?
Is your relationship with that woman really that important!?
Jin...
Mikuriya and Daitetsu-kun are acting strange?
Yes, they are...
They aren't having a fight, but...
There's something awkward going on between them.
Ouch Daitetsu...
Huh? Jin and Daitetsu-kun.
Jin, I'm begging you!
What's going on? I can't hear well.
Let me hear it directly from your mouth.
About that...
I'm sorry, Daitetsu!
I can't answer that!
Wait, Jin!
It's just that I...
I wonder what it could be!
It's unusual for them to fall out!
Isn't it?
The two did come to school together.
Maybe Daitetsu-kun stay over at Jin's house last night.
I guess something must have happened during that time...
Young boys! The two of them! Sleepover!
Hey Sempai, what are you saying?
It's just that I...
I'd love to hear the following words!
Vice president, even you?!
We're just kidding.
Nagi-tan is there, so it's not like they were alone together.
Even if they were alone together, that would be impossible!
Can't we just ask them directly?
But someone like me can't...
I won't surrender Jin to you!
A god does not approve of a man such as you!
Huh?
Oh my.
Next time on Kannagi is... oops.