TL Note: Ruby says Oyakata-sama, which is "Master", but I'll keep it as "Oyakata-sama" for consistency.
Ruby, Ruby.....
You don't have to cry anymore.
You're not alone..
I'll always be here.
Pain, pain, go away!
Eh? Is there really a spell like that?
That's because I am a magic expert!
Isn't that only for grown up witches?
I am-
Come on you guys... my wounds aren't that deep, I should be fine in no time!
Ah, see, you are pushing yourself!
Hey, quiet down!
Master...
Are you awake now, Ruby-san?
Where am I...?
Here, this your share.
Don't worry, there's enough for everyone.
Using something like this to win me over...
It's not like that!
I just wanted to hear your story.
My story?
Yes.
About that hill.
What... that hill has long since been the refuge of us witches.
We were without conflict, and lived peacefully amongst ourselves...
Then, they just barged in selfishly.
Causing unnecessary destruction, doing this so-called development for their own selfish reasons...
They laid waste, broke down, and ruined everything!
The story about you cruel humans!
What's the point in listening to it now?!
Ruby-san...
Yukari-chan...
You can understand too, right?
About our own home...
In order to protect the Witches' Hill, we have no choice but to destroy the humans!
But that's...
I'm the only one left from our group...
But is it okay to kill everyone who's trying to take away the hill?
The only ones I'm killing are humans!
Humans and Monsters...
Are the value of their lives that different?
What's wrong with killing humans?
Isn't it fine to kill them?!
Those foolish humans...
Isn't there any other way? To live together without fighting...
It's pointless. Doing anything at this point is meaningless.
The Master will pass judgment on the humans.
The Master...?
Judgment, eh? That sounds like quite an egotistical person.
To say that hurting others to accomplish your own goals is okay...
Yeah, yeah, aren't you guys doing things selfishly too?
Isn't that the same as the humans?
Hey, that's...
Hey, is that how witches do things?
Witches are scary, aren't they?
Witches aren't scary!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, witch brats aren't scary at all!
There you go again!
Shut up!
Once that hill is taken, I won't have any other place to go!
Oh, that's all? If that's case, why doesn't Ruby-san just come to Youkai Academy also?
Yeah! Although you might feel a bit homesick and lonesome,
The student lifestyle is actually quite fun!
Let's study together!
And, after that, you can join the Newspaper Club!
Moka-san, nice!
Eh? There's gonna be two witches?
What about it?
Come on now, you guys...
Shall I cool your heads?
But for me... I can no longer be anywhere else.
Master...
Forgive me, Master!
I won't betray you ever again!
Eh?! Ruby-san went missing?!
Ruby-san...
Yukari-chan!
What?
Ruby-san!
I won't let you get any further on this hill!
No matter who it is!
Wait, there must be some other way!
She's right, Ruby-san! Let's think of it together!
Shut up!!
There're man-eating plants underneath the sunflower field!
These guys are faithful servants created by the Master to protect this hill!
Back down, Tsukune!
Shirayuki-san...
It's dangerous here, Tsukune-san!
Yukari-chan!
It's only one witch brat, why are you panicking?
Kurumu-chan?
I won't forgive anyone who touches Tsukune!
Shirayuki-san!
Even I...!
Don't worry!
I won't let one finger...
...touch you!
Moka-san!
Tsukune!
Cut everyone to shreds!
Ruby-san, please stop!
How dare you...!
Damn it!
Even if my opponent is a monster...
Even though I can hear Moka-san's screams...
But my legs won't even move...
Moka-san, please tell me...
What I can do... the things that a human can do!
There it is!
What?
That is...
A vampire!
Moka....
Moka-san...
You idiot... you're always overdoing it.
But thanks to you, I was saved.
Moka-san!
Young fool.
This week's battle took one second... huh?
Ruby-san!
Please stop already!
I will... protect the Witches' Hill!
That is my...
and also, the Master's wish!
What's going on?
They're bigger than before!
Tsukune-san!
Please, let Tsukune-san go, Ruby-san!
This is the Master's desire!
This is the Master's wish!
This is the Master's ambition!
Who is this Master...?
Master?
That idiot!
Moka-san? Hey wait!
Yukari, Mizore! Please take care of Tsukune!
Tsukune-san!
Ruby-san!
Tsukune!
Where are you going, Tsukune-san?
To the Master!
Master?
Tsukune!
Kurumu-san!
The Master is in that mansion!
Tsukune-san, look out!
Idiot! It's dangerous for you too!
Stand aside!
Shut up! Tsukune-san, hurry and go!
Thank you, Kurumu-chan, Yukari-chan!
Eh, you were pretty good for a kid.
Same to you, you can move pretty well, despite your load.
I guess so. It's the first time I felt jealous that you were a kid.
Having a big-breasted comrade is so troublesome.
I get it already, but we have bigger enemies to fight against, right?
Thanks, Shirayuki-san!
T-This is...
I see, these are what's controlling them.
Those demons...and Ruby-san...
This is...
You are... You are... the Master, right?
If so, please release Ruby-san! At this rate...
How long do I have to deal with these small fry?
Until we defeat them all...
If we suffer together, this is nothing!
Are you guys really saying that?
We're just saying it.
There's still so many...
Kurumu-san, Shirayuki-san, look!
Moka!
Ruby-san, we understand! We'll get off the hill immediately!
We won't trespass here ever again!
So please, forgive us!
What are you saying?! Whatever you say to her now is useless!
You shall receive punishment for hurting the Witches' Hill!
Wait!
Stop it, Ruby-san!
Tsukune!
Tsukune-san!
Idiot, run!
If Ruby-san does these things, no one will ever be happy!
Shut up! At least for the sake of the Master, I'll-
What are you saying? The Master isn't even here anymore!
What idiotic nonsense! The Master is inside the mansion!
Like I said, the Master inside the mansion is already dead!
That's a lie...
Ruby....
Master?
I may have became foolish.
What I've been doing is the same as the humans...
Master!
Please forgive me... I am making you alone again...
My dear Ruby, I will always be with you...
Always...
Ruby-san, you should have known as well!
That the Master is no longer here!
You just didn't want to admit it.
Your feelings of denial...
The other Ruby-san... no, the Ruby inside you... created an image of her within yourself!
No, no....
NO!!!
No way... don't, Ruby-san!
What? What do you mean?
If she uses that forbidden magic, she'll never return to her original form again!
No way...!
Ruby-san!!!
Ruby-san!
Die!
Everyone should die!
You're being too rash, Ruby-san...
What can we do? She can no longer go back...
No one can stop...
Ruby-san, please stop!
Tsukune-san!
My wand!
Wand?
Please throw me my wand!
That one?
Here!
Thanks a lot!
Kurumu-san!
Okay!
Moka-san is...!
You fool, did you think you would be able to defeat me with just this?!
This magic is not just powerful!
The current me is able to absorb the strength of other living things!
In others words, right now my powers are just like those of a vampire!
Moka-san!
Worrying is useless.  Leave it to Yukari!
Lyrical Magical: Happy Heart!
Destroy it, Mizore!
Now's your chance, Moka-san! Take her wand!
We witches can't use magic without a wand!
I don't know if she'll revert back... but please, Moka-san!
Ruby-san... Please save Ruby-san!
You're right... this idiot is worrying about her as well!
You bastard!
Everyone...Everyone just die!
Revert back to yourself!
What is Ruby's favorite thing?
My favorite thing?
Ummm.....Ice cream!
And after that...
There's still more?
Yup! This Witches' Hill....
Master!
Master, I love you so much!
In the end, we couldn't do anything...
If I had been able to hang on longer...
This isn't Tsukune's fault.
I'm so sorry for making you guys wait so long!
See? I got tons of delicious-looking fish...
Eh? It's already time to go back?
Sorry for being late.
That voice is...
Gin-sempai!
Hey, what's with this gloomy atmosphere?
Your club leader just finished his supplementary lessons, too!
You guys should be more cheerful...
What's up?
Ru...
Ruby-san!
What, you know her?
Yeah...
No way that's possible.
I only found this girl just recently by the beach.
Like she was possessed with protecting something.
Like she was protecting something...
Huh?
What? The road's different.
Let's go back...
There was actually such a beautiful hill in this place!
This place is a sunflower garden that has been endearingly important to the witches for generations.
Then, I'll also take good care of it!
I'll always, always take care of it!
Well, let's go back, to our home.
Yeah!
Wah, summer vacation is over!
Being emotional about it doesn't help!
Shall I make a whirlwind for your summer vacation?
Noo, anything but that!
Next time, New School Term and A Vampire
And a kappuchu for you!