Otter No. 11
Otter goes back to the sea!
OLIVINE THOLEIITE
My tail is made of Carbon nanotubes.
Fist as yours is like tofu.
Don't underestimate tofu... Yushida.
No,
Otter No. 9.
Indeed, I'm Otter No. 9.
Made for humans convenience... An abandoned Lost Number.
But I have changed,
By repeating remodeling myself,
I became an existence beyond humans.
I already don't need humans.
By ridding of humans,
we will be the kings of new world.
I won't let you.
PORPHYRITIC ANDESITE
You too are supposed to hate humans,
Why are you getting in the way?
You won't understand.
I'm Otter Human.
Not an otter nor a human... But Halfway.
But this is who I am.
You -who denied & remodeled himself- won't understand.
Don't give such unacceptable answers.
You shall be the prey for my tail.
Such tail shall not be used as an otter's tail.
I... Impossible.
My tail is Carbon...
Thank you.. No. 11.
I knew you would stop No. 9.
Hamada-kun!
I'm another Lost Number... Otter No. 8.
This place is not suitable for us.
Farewell.
I was happy when you called me "close friend".
Hamada-kun.
Farewell.
Mr. Otter.
I see... you saved Hamada-kun...
Thank you.
Mr. Otter, what will you do after this?
The supermarket near us needs a part-timer...
Here is not suitable for me too
I will go back.. to the home of everything.
I'm free.
The End.
La La La
Otter Otter  ...   Otter Otter
Otter Otter Otter No. 11
No. 1  has a little long beard
No. 2  has a good fur
No. 3  has big ears  ...  No. 4  has big chest
No. 5  has charming eyes
No. 6  has tried manicure
No. 7  has tried pedicure
No. 8 & 9  have no records
No. 10  has a 2-meters tail
And No. 11   ...   We are No. 11
Otter Otter  ...   Otter Otter
Otter Otter Otter No. 11
Favorite beefsteak well-done