Yeah! The ocean!
The ocean!
Rika's gonna draw.
Hey, that's my textbook!
This one is yours, Rika.
Here!
Textbook?
Mari, are you going to study
while we're at the beach?
Well, if I feel like it.
No way!
Bringing study stuff on a
summer fun day? Who even...
...does that...
Everyone enjoys themselves in different ways.
Right, Mari?
Yeah!
I'm sure Mari will do a lot of studying,
and become a researcher just like her father!
Huh? I don't know about that.
Well, we're almost there!
"Episode 8
Bell's Decision"
It's so big!
Isn't it extravagant?
Are you sure we can stay in this house?
My parents built it for fun.
It's a waste if we don't use it now and then.
Mari, take care of Rika, okay?
Okay!
"Miwa"
Miwa? Wait...
Are your parents from the Miwa Concern?
Oh, yes...
I never knew! So you're
very wealthy, aren't you?
My parents are my parents. I'm me.
Wow! The ceilings are so high!
Yeah!
Yahoo!
It really echoes!
Echoes!
Waka, want to explore the rooms?
Yeah! Let's go!
This way!
Do you think I could, too?
Rika, too!
Could you look after Rika, then?
Yes!
Rika, let's go.
Okay!
It's lovely!
How many rooms are there?
I dunno!
Oh, Rika, wait!
Come on now! Really...
Mom...
It's sparkly!
Yes, it is beautiful!
Get me one, Rei!
I think it's too high for me to reach...
The blue sky, the shining sea. It's so nice.
The salt air brushing my cheeks...
Summer days spent at an extravagant villa...
But why couldn't that jerk have come with us?
You mean Futa?
Huh?
Waka, you invited him, right?
I guess, but...
He said no because he had a soccer match.
It's hard being far away and
not getting to see each other.
Hey, now, you'll see him again
when school starts.
Here.
Ma'am, isn't it hard for you, not
seeing your husband for three years?
What?
Waka!
Oh, yes.
Well, we met while I was abroad.
And when he went back
to Japan, I stayed in Paris,
so we've gone a year at a time
without seeing each other.
A year? You're so strong...
Yeah.
He loves to be free, and hates
carrying things like cell phones.
So I'm used to not being in touch with him.
What? He doesn't even have a cell phone?
He never carries one.
Never carries a cell phone?
How old-fashioned...
Waka...
But cell phones are a
relatively recent invention.
So I find that rather normal.
Yeah!
When I was young, my husband
didn't have a cell phone.
We'd end up waiting on either side of the
Hachiko statue without seeing each other.
That close?
That's right!
I think that's because you're you, Mom.
Oh, really?
I wonder what Papa's doing now.
"The Year 1876
(What is Now) Boston, America"
Are you catching a cold?
I think someone's spreading rumors about me.
Your Majesty.
Thank you so much for
coming to view our classes.
The honor is all mine, Mr. Bell.
The visible speech system your father
invented was truly incredible!
Now, let's try speaking together.
--"One good turn deserves another."
You wouldn't think those children were deaf.
I would love to bring it back to Brazil.
Could I have a few of your books?
Certainly, Your Majesty!
I'll send them to you.
Thank you. Please, call me Dom Pedro.
Dom Pedro, then.
Mabel, your fiance is--
What?
The emperor's addressing you.
I'm sorry.
She's hard of hearing, too.
If she can't see your lips,
she can't understand what you're saying.
I didn't know.
Beautiful lady, I must be going.
Excellent work, everyone.
Now, let's head back to the classroom.
Yes, sir!
Thank you for your help before, Doctor...
Hayase!
Doctor Hayase.
You came all the way from Japan
to see our classes?
Well, I saw that code of yours.
I thought it might be useful for learning
pronunciation in different languages.
Exactly! Thank you!
Ow!
That's a rather strong handshake.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I wasn't thinking.
Mabel?
It's a telegram from Father.
From Mr. Hubbard?
Is there a problem?
He wants you to attend
the exposition, after all.
But I told him it was impossible, didn't I?
Alex, they're holding the
Centennial Exposition in Philadelphia.
I made special arrangements
so that you could exhibit
that telephone you developed.
My telephone?
Of course, you can display
your visual speech along with it.
Isn't that wonderful, Dr. Bell?
Yes, but...
If you demonstrate it at the exhibition,
it will spread awareness of the telephone,
and you'll likely be able
to make a business of it.
If you can do that, I'll officially
allow your marriage to my daughter.
Really?
I'm sorry, sir, but that invention
has room for improvement.
And I can't neglect my school
to perform the needed experiments.
You still haven't changed your mind?
I told you before:
Until I have enough people
that I can entrust this work to,
I cannot abandon my work as a teacher.
He who runs after two hares
will catch neither.
You should focus on promoting the telephone.
But they're both important to me!
Then I'll go to the exhibition myself.
You'll allow me to display it, won't you?
Understood.
That's true, but...
He said that the display alone
might not make the pitch to the judges.
That wasn't what we discussed.
But...
We'll talk later.
I'm sorry to do this in front of you.
No, I suppose we're both having trouble.
Both?
I'm also the type to follow my own path,
no matter what my wife says to me.
Even if you love your wife? I see.
Well, I guess they're different situations.
I'm the same way.
I love Mabel from the bottom of my heart.
But I just can't bring myself
to agree with her father.
In life, the question of what to prioritize
might be the eternal conflict,
no matter how the era might change.
What?
Oh, I mean, do your best.
Mr. Bell, I'll be rooting for you.
Thank you.
Was the wedding in Japan?
Yes. And the day after that,
he went away for six months.
Six months?! He's gone missing before, then?
Looks like it.
And this time it's three years?
That man of mine...
But at least he's grown up
enough to leave me a letter.
He'd been missing for four or five days,
so I went to his laboratory,
and found out he'd gone on a research trip.
Exhausting, isn't it?
Shun, does that book have
something to do with his research?
Oh... I'm not sure.
I see. That brings a lot
of things together, huh?
Yeah...
What things?
Oh, nothing. Nothing at all.
Hey, why don't we go swimming?
Sure!
Come on, let's go swimming!
Let's ocean!
That's grammatically incorrect!
Incorrect!
Mari, are you okay?
Yeah...
So you are here, Mrs. Hayase.
Fancy meeting you here.
Mr. Mikage?
Who's that?
Your new almond praline
cream puffs were delicious.
Thank you for your continued patronage.
Are those your children?
Yes.
This is Mr. Mikage, a customer at our store.
Hello.
Hello!
I'm a friend!
I'm Mizuki.
I see. It is summer vacation, after all.
That's right. If I might,
would you like to join me on a cruise?
A cruise?!
I have a cabin cruiser at the marina.
As long as you're here,
why don't we make a party of it?
What do you think?
My, I'd love to!
Mom...
Oh, I'm sorry. I've just never
been on a cabin cruiser.
Mama, what's a cabin cruiser?
It's a boat.
A boat! I wanna ride!
I'm glad. Then why don't you all join us?
If you insist, then we ladies
shall accompany you.
You're getting too carried away, Waka.
I just felt like acting like a lady.
Waka, you could be an actress.
Thanks.
But I'm gonna be a TV announcer!
Really? I didn't know that!
Because I never told you!
I see. So you have a real dream, huh, Waka?
And Shun, you want to be a doctor, right?
Yeah...
But lately, I've started to think
there might be other possibilities.
Huh? You won't become a doctor?
They're just possibilities.
I might be a researcher.
Oh? Like Papa?
Well, Mari, you work hard, too!
I don't even know what I wanna be...
What is the meaning of this, Mabel?
I came because you said
you had something to show me.
Please, get on the train.
Give the demonstration
at the exhibition, like Father wants!
Mabel...
I won't be able to marry you if you don't!
But you know very well that I have school...
The school will still be here
when you get back!
But this exhibition will only come once.
You're getting on, aren't you, Mr. Bell?
You're...
You'd better hurry. Go on!
I understand, Mabel.
But I'm still pursuing those two hares.
Okay!
Mr. Bell! Hurry!
Thank you, Dr. Hayase.
You always show up when Mabel needs you.
You're like her knight in shining armor.
I just felt like history might change
if you didn't get on this train.
History?
Well, no matter how I try
to protect the flow of time,
some things may yet remain part of history.
What are you talking about?
Oh, nothing. Just talking to myself.
But you can't fight a woman's tears, can you?
Does that go for your wife's tears, too?
That's right.
I haven't seen her tears in quite a while.
Mama, what's wrong?
Mari!
I was just thinking about Papa.
Papa?
Papa proposed to me on a beach near here.
What? Really?
He said that if you swear your love
in front of that setting sun,
it will last forever.
He'd made it all up, of course.
Papa...
But he said humans create
whatever they imagine,
and so he was going to create that legend.
I wonder what he's doing right now.
Good question.
Well, everyone, eat up.
The meat has cooked up nicely. Help yourself.
Thanks!
Hayase?
Yes?
Oh, I meant Mrs. Hayase.
Shall I call you Akira, then?
Okay...
I was wondering. Would you like to
work on developing premium desserts?
Premium desserts?
I know a lot of gourmets
for whom money is no object.
If you leave it to me, I could
expand your business even further.
I bet you could.
And of course, I'm very focused on my art.
But I want to offer my sweets
at reasonable prices,
so everyone can enjoy them.
Is that a no, then?
Yes.
There's no ambiguity with you, is there?
That guy's pretty hot, huh?
Oh, yes. If I were a single woman...
No way! Mom, is he your type?
Well, he's very handsome, isn't he?
So Waka and her mom
like that kind of guy, huh?
You don't, Mari?
I didn't say that, exactly...
Go ahead.
Oh, thank you.
Eat your fill. There's no need to hold back.
I will. Thank you.
What the heck...?
That's a lovely necklace.
Huh?
Um... thanks.
She got it from Papa!
Oh, did she?
Ms. Kuroki, we're out of meat,
so could you move this out of the way?
Yes, sir.
Talk to you later.
Right.
Oh, dear...
Mari, could you get a change
of clothes for Rika from my bag?
Oh, sure!
That lady... She was trying to steal it!
It can't be...
Shun!
Shall I?
Please do.
Mari, did you bring them?
Yeah!
Here.
Yes, you look very young.
Shun, I'm borrowing your book.
Seriously... Shun's way too gullible.
Just because she's pretty--
That hurt...
Darn it! Stupid Shun!
Did you hear something just now?
No.
Oh no! I'm transporting!
What do I do?!
Mari!
Mari disappeared!
What?! Mari!
Where am I? Whose page did I travel into?
What do I do?!
"Next Episode: Bell's Responses"
"Mari and Waka's Quick Science"
Mari and Waka's Quick Science!
Papa, what's this?
It's a speaker!
The foundation of the
telephone that Bell invented
is a connected pair of speakers like this.
It's not a microphone and a speaker?
The principle of the microphone
and speaker is the same.
So when you speak into one of the speakers...
Testing.
You're right! You can send
the voice between speakers!
What's the principle behind it?
"Sound is produced"
"Vibrations in air"
"Eardrum interprets the vibrations as sound"
Do you know how hearing works?
"Sound is produced"
"Vibrations in air"
"Eardrum interprets the vibrations as sound"
Um, you speak, and the air vibrates,
"Sound is produced"
"Vibrations in air"
"Eardrum interprets the vibrations as sound"
and that makes your eardrum shake,
and then you can hear it, right?
"Sound is produced"
"Vibrations in air"
"Eardrum interprets the vibrations as sound"
That's right.
"Sound is produced"
"Vibrations in air"
"Eardrum interprets the vibrations as sound"
It was Bell who thought of mechanically
converting that into electric signals.
"Sound is produced"
"Vibrations in air"
"Eardrum interprets the vibrations as sound"
"Transmitter"
"Receiver"
"Coil" "Electric current" "Magnet" "Paper cone (Diaphragm)"
On the speaker's end, the voice makes the
diaphragm shake, causing the coils to move.
"Transmitter"
"Receiver"
"Coil" "Electric current" "Magnet" "Paper cone (Diaphragm)"
This causes an electric current.
"Transmitter"
"Receiver"
"Coil" "Electric current" "Magnet" "Paper cone (Diaphragm)"
In other words, it's changed
the sound into an electric signal.
"Transmitter"
"Receiver"
"Coil" "Electric current" "Magnet" "Paper cone (Diaphragm)"
Just like the electromagnetic induction
we did with Mr. Faraday?
"Transmitter"
"Receiver"
"Coil" "Electric current" "Magnet" "Paper cone (Diaphragm)"
Yes. Then the coil on the receiver's end
reacts to the electric signal,
"Transmitter"
"Receiver"
"Coil" "Electric current" "Magnet" "Paper cone (Diaphragm)"
and the diaphragm vibrates and creates sound.
"Transmitter"
"Receiver"
"Coil" "Electric current" "Magnet" "Paper cone (Diaphragm)"
Sending your voice with electricity...
What a great idea!
Bell wanted to find a way to help
deaf people hear. That's how he thought of it.
So science can give form
to people's feelings too, huh?