"The Year 1876
(What is now) Philadelphia, America"
Well... I'll just be going!
I'm soaking wet.
But I'm glad I'm somewhere warm.
I'd better get home.
Papa?!
"Episode 9
Bell's Responses"
Huh? Where'd he go?
Now, now. Don't get so down.
Shut up!
I had plans for a telephone, too.
But that idiot Bell beat me to it!
But it's not as if every one
of your inventions has worked.
You've always bounced back from your failures
to keep trying new inventions. Right?
Isn't the most important thing
to keep moving forward?
I know that. It's obvious!
Papa!
Hey, Mari.
What are you wearing?!
Oh, well...
We were at the beach, and I happened
to touch the book and get sent here...
At the beach?
This is my daughter.
This is Mr. Graham Bell, Mari.
A pleasure to meet you.
You look nice and cool.
Is that Japanese folk clothing?
Huh?
Oh, sure... That's what we'll call it.
You do seem to know a lot.
I just love sweets.
Understood. Wait one moment.
--Lately, chocolate has--
--Mr. Mikage.
Excuse me a moment.
Brother...
Mari traveled through time?
Yeah. What do we do?
And Rika--
Waka, where's Mari?
Oh, well, um...
Big Sis disappeared into the book!
N-Not good...
What did she mean by that?
Um, well, you see...
What, indeed, did she mean?
I'm sure she'll be back soon, of course.
Shun...
That's the book my husband
gave you, isn't it?
Yes.
Please explain everything to me, Shun.
You're hiding something from me, aren't you?
This has something to do with
Hayase's research, doesn't it?
Akira!
Is something the matter?
So, Dr. Hayase, your daughter
is the one you were waiting for?
Oh, yes...
Huh? Papa, you were waiting for me?
No.
What the heck?
Don't worry.
The people you're waiting for
will appear too, I'm sure.
I hope you're right...
Who's Mr. Bell waiting for?
The judges.
He wants to demonstrate the telephone.
I see!
Speaking of which, what were you doing
with the book at the beach?
Was Shun with you?
Yeah!
We were all at Grandpa's villa.
Then one of Mama's customers
let us on his cabin cruiser...
Cruiser?
Yeah. He's apparently super rich.
His name's Mr. Mikage...
Mikage's there?!
Papa, you know him?
He really likes Mama, okay?
And he's handsome, too.
Oh, Papa! You neglect Mama too much!
Don't blame me if Mama leaves you while
you're searching for that book's secrets!
Huh?
--Don't "Huh?" me!
--Right this way.
My, how shameless!
Oh, wait a minute!
Mari, we should really do something
about that outfit, first.
Never mind. I'm going home anyway.
No, let me explain things in more detail.
Huh?
Is your daughter okay?
Yes, I think she went off somewhere to pout.
She's probably back home
with her friends about now.
I'm sorry.
I hope you're right.
Goodbye.
This is cute! Thanks, Papa!
Sure!
Now, how close are Mikage and your mother?
You want to know, huh?
I'd love to eat some ice cream!
Huh?!
Delicious! Right, Mr. Bell?
Yes.
Thank you for the treat, Dr. Hayase.
Oh, no problem...
Now, about Mikage and your mother...
Oh, I don't really know.
You don't know?
It seems like he comes by
her shop a lot, though.
Her shop?
Well, well!
You're finally worried about Mama, huh?
No.
She'll be fine. I trust her.
Huh?
A lot has happened between us,
but we've both supported each other
as we pursue the things we love.
Because we love what we do,
we'll both keep rushing, full speed ahead.
We both know that about each other.
Papa, that's not convincing when
you've left her alone for three years.
Really?
But I went to see her just this morning!
I returned the glasses!
Thank you, Mari.
No problem.
--Hey, Papa. I think I--
--It's so hot. I'm exhausted.
Yes, let's call the judging over for today,
and do the rest at another time.
N-No!
Well, if it isn't Mr. Bell!
Dom Pedro!
What a coincidence, meeting you here again.
Thank you for taking care of me in Boston.
Likewise!
Mari, as long as you're here, why not watch?
This is the pivotal moment when
the telephone is introduced to the world.
The pivotal moment?
Well then, I'll begin.
Please go to the next room.
This can still only be
spoken into from one end,
so I will speak to the emperor
standing in the next room over.
Dom Pedro, can you hear what I'm saying?
I hear him! I can hear him!
To be or not to be.
"To be or not to be."
That is the question.
"That is the question."
He talked through the machine!
Just like Mr. Bell said!
It's truly wonderful!
I'm so happy for Mr. Bell!
Papa, it gave me goosebumps!
Yes, by showing us all of these things,
I think there's something
the book wants us to do.
Huh?
The history of the telephone
relies on many strange coincidences.
Coincidences?
Mr. Bell was a teacher
at a school for the deaf.
To teach deaf people how to speak,
he wanted to portray sounds visually.
That's what got him started on his research.
Then on June 2nd, 1875,
something happened that inspired him to
discover the principle behind the telephone.
His assistant, Thomas Watson,
plucked a reed while trying to
remove it from an electromagnet,
accidentally sending the sound
traveling through the wire.
After that, he tried many
different configurations
until March 10th, 1876.
This time, Bell accidentally
spilled acid on his pants
and cried out.
That was the first time a person's
voice was transmitted via telephone.
And today, June 25th, 1876,
Dom Pedro, the emperor of Brazil, and
Mr. Bell happened to reunite at the exhibition.
Previously, the emperor had come
to observe his schools for the deaf.
What a lot of coincidences!
Mr. Bell must have been a lucky person!
I think there's more to it than luck.
Huh?
"When it comes to destiny,
there are no coincidences.
Before a man meets his destiny,
he builds it for himself."
Have you ever heard those words?
No. What do they mean?
The father of Mr. Bell's fiancée told him
that he should focus on
the invention of the telephone.
But because he wouldn't give up
on the school or the phone,
I believe that's the reason
he got this opportunity.
Because he wouldn't give up?
When you find something you love,
you don't want to give up on it.
I'm the same way.
Finding something you love is amazing, huh?
Have you found something like that yet?
Me? I don't know...
I'm sorry, Rei, to make you take Rika.
Leave it to me!
Rika, dear, let's go.
Okay!
We'll talk about the details inside.
Understood.
Dear!
Mama?
Um... Akira?
I'm sorry, Mari. She found us out.
It's not your fault, Waka. It's my fault.
Yes, it is.
Papa, I don't want to hear that from you!
S-So, Akira...
Are you well?
Oh, yes.
It has been some time.
You seem as well as ever.
Even though I saw you just last morning.
Last morning? When?
You clearly don't know how I feel.
I'm sorry.
But we swore our eternal devotion
on that beach before the setting sun.
Create what we imagine?
Yes. So I trust you.
Really. You just believe whatever you want.
But this is incredible.
I've never communicated like this before.
Mari, I'm starting to believe
that our time traveling
will some day connect us to something.
Papa?
Seeing Mr. Bell here confirmed it for me.
Investigate things you're curious about.
That's the entryway to loving something.
The entryway to loving something?
Oh, I guess it's time to go back.
Huh?
Dr. Hayase?
Mr. Bell!
Goodbye. I'm happy for you.
Mari, Akira, see you later.
I thought he was a curious person, but...
Your father went home, then?
Oh, yes.
I wanted to thank him, at least.
Thanks to Dr. Hayase,
I was able to move forward.
Papa?
My work with the telephone was a success,
and I didn't have to quit my school.
It was because of him
that I could pursue both.
I see...
Please convey to him my gratitude.
Okay!
Um, watching you and Papa
made me feel like I want
to work really hard, too!
Really?
I'm going to find something I love!
Wonderful!
There are many interesting
things in this world!
Please do your best.
Okay!
Well, then...
Huh? It won't turn?
Huh?! Why?!
What's wrong, Mari?
Brother! What's going on?
Mari... Wait a minute.
Strange. This has never happened before.
Mari!
Shun? Waka?
Mari?
Mama?
Mari, don't force it!
Huh? Shun? Shun!
No way!
Mari! Mari!
Answer me!
Shun, what's going on here?!
Mari will be able to come back, won't she?
That's right! Isn't it, Shun?
Brother, what are you doing?
I'll go to get her.
What?
I know where Mari is.
I'll travel with this.
Let me go instead.
Ma'am?
If I give her that, then at least
Mari can get back, right?
That's true...
I'll go.
Don't worry. I know how it works.
It'll work out.
No... I'll work it out.
Shun, take care of Mari.
Yes, ma'am.
Waka, can you watch these coordinates
on the TSS and support me?
Yeah.
Okay, I'm off.
If Mari and I don't return,
it will change the future
written in this book.
I don't think that will be possible.
What do I do? What do I do?
Mari, please, calm down.
No, no, no! I can't calm down!
Mari...
Shun!
I'm sorry for the disturbance.
N-Not at all...
Mari, give me your compass.
O-Okay!
This is it.
Oh.
It looks like water and sand.
When I fell into the ocean...
Okay.
I've managed to fix the error.
Thank goodness! That's the Shun I know!
Now we can go back, right?
Assuming we can reactivate
the armillary compass
and link it to the TSS, yes.
Waka, can you confirm the AM2 coordinates?
It's there! It's on the screen, Brother!
Yeah!
The world truly is full of mysteries!
Interesting!
Thank you.
I'll never forget this day.
Neither will I.
Well, let's go, Mari.
Okay!
It worked!
Hold on. So we can go back together.
Huh?
O-Okay.
Take care!
Mari!
I'm so glad!
Waka...
Mari, no!
Mari!
Mama...
Do you know how worried we all were?!
I'm sorry...
Never do this again!
Huh? But...
It's true that you've both leaped
into the past without fear before,
but there's a chance something like this
could happen again in the future, too.
Shun...
That's right! So make me a promise.
Never use this system again.
Okay...
Then give me the key to the laboratory.
And those, too.
Right.
And with that resolved, I'm hungry!
Me, too.
I'm sorry, Mama.
I guess I should have told you
about Papa sooner, too.
But I didn't want to worry you...
Thank you.
Well, everyone come by my house.
Rei and Rika are waiting for us.
I'll make something delicious.
Yeah!
Okay!
Mari, that dress is really nice.
Oh, but I left my bathing suit in the past.
According to the report,
that day, there was no trace of
Mari Hayase entering the laboratory.
Which means
she could have transported from
the beach to the laboratory?
Yes, sir.
It seems almost certain that he completed
the matter transporter.
Yes.
We can't turn back from this.
The die has been cast.
"Next Episode: Hertz's Pride"
"Mari and Waka's Quick Science"
Mari and Waka's Quick Science!
Bell's telephone converted
sound into electricity,
but he also tried experiments
to turn sound into light!
Into light?
Reflect a laser light off aluminum
foil attached to a paper cup,
and when that light touches a photocell
attached to a deck and a speaker...
Testing.
I heard a voice come from the speaker!
The reflected light is trembling?
The vocal oscillations are converted into
light oscillations and send the sound along.
Sending messages with light
would be really handy, huh?
But in this system, the light
disperses and weakens,
so you can't achieve
long-distance communication.
I see.
On the other hand, there's
a thing called a heliograph...
I know that one!
It's the kind that's light flashes, right?
Right!
You use the lengths of the light
flashes to send messages in code.
Just like Mr. Morse's code!
But this can't travel too far either, right?
Yes.
For a long time, it was impossible to achieve
long-distance light-based communication.
But thanks to the invention of optical fiber,
"Light" "Optical fiber"
"Light bounces back and forth as it travels"
But thanks to the invention of optical fiber,
"Light" "Optical fiber"
"Light bounces back and forth as it travels"
we can now send fast,
long-distance communications.
So eventually, the world was linked by light!