Why?
Welcome back from the
other side of space-time,
Mari.
Now...
Will you teach me how to use
this armillary compass of yours?
I asked them, but they're awfully stubborn.
Mari!
Don't tell him!
Pipe down!
What was that?!
You brat...
Stop it! Don't hurt them!
Certainly, I won't...
...if you do as I say.
Fine.
Mari...
You're a smart girl.
Mama... Where is she?
"Episode 11
Edison's Resilience"
I see.
"Episode 11
Edison's Resilience"
By touching the portraits in the book,
the armillary compass
takes you to that person's era.
Is that it?
You should have just made something up!
You do run your mouth, don't you?
I'd rather be a blabbermouth
than someone who ties
people up and threatens them!
I finally see how he did it.
Why could he auction off
the jade cup of Napoleon,
thought lost to the tides of history?
An invention that travels through time...
This could mean big business.
Business?
That's right.
An unparalleled travel experience
using cutting edge technology...
...time travel.
If we label it that way,
we'll have people climbing over
each other for a chance to try it.
In addition,
things lost to war and natural disaster,
like precious historical
documents, art, and sculptures.
If we could acquire them,
they could fetch
incredible prices at auction.
I won't let you abuse it like that!
Abuse?
What an awful thing to say.
Your husband is already doing that, isn't he?
The jade cup of Napoleon
that Mr. Mikage mentioned...
Someone brought it back from
the past and sold it at an auction.
It was likely Dr. Hayase.
Papa did it?
Hayase used the money from that
to pay back the money we had
invested into his matter transporter.
That idiot!
Just as your husband used it
to pay back our investment,
I will use this system for my business.
That's all it is.
When something is lost
in the course of history,
that means its role in history has ended.
To bring it back into the modern world
is like twisting the very fabric of history!
The trifling sentimentality
of the historian...
It means little.
What is needed in business
is the know-how to succeed.
Isn't that... Dr. Hayase's...
Hmm? What is it?
Um, did something happen here?
Oh, just a break-in.
Huh? A break-in?
Come on, now. Go on.
Futa, let's go!
R-Right!
What era is Dr. Hayase in now?
What will you do if we tell you?
I'd like to have a long talk with him.
He broke our agreement.
Broke your agreement? Papa did?
Dr. Hayase was developing
a matter transporter.
He had a duty to report
to us any phenomenon
that occurred during
the course of that research.
But he didn't do that.
If he returned the research funding,
doesn't that mean the contract is over?
Mr. Sekota there used to be
part of Hayase's laboratory.
He was involved in the development
of the matter transporter.
According to him, Dr. Hayase, during
the development of the matter transporter,
through some accident, received a hint about
how to use the system to travel through time.
In other words, at the time
he received that hint,
the contract was still in effect.
You sold out the secrets
of Hayase's research?!
That's awful!
But the doctor is far more awful.
He deceived me, developed
this incredible invention,
and hid it from me.
I must find him and receive recompense.
All I want to do is talk to him...
...in a businesslike manner.
Really?
Of course, as compensation,
he'll have to give this system to us,
and we'll have him help us with our business.
I'll ask you one more time.
What era is Dr. Hayase in?
Then I'll just have to go looking for him.
But she'll be coming with me...
...to every era I visit,
until I find the doctor.
Don't do it! Don't drag Mari into this!
It's Edison.
We lost track of Dr. Hayase
during Edison's era.
Edison?
Edison, the master inventor.
A great inventor and entrepreneur.
Then shall we head out, Mari?
Wait!
Don't move!
I told you where the doctor was!
Why are you taking Mari?
You might do something
to make sure I can't come back.
I want to make sure that you don't.
We won't do that!
In business, you always need
insurance in case of trouble.
She is my insurance.
Let go of Mari!
And having your daughter with me
will make negotiations with
the doctor proceed more smoothly.
--You coward!
--Stay where you are!
Well, here we go.
--Mari!
"The Year 1876
(What is now) Menlo Park, America"
Are we really in Edison's time?
"The Year 1876
(What is now) Menlo Park, America"
Probably, yeah...
It seems it is.
Your father is an impressive man.
What are you people doing here?!
Who are you people?
How'd you get in here?
Are you spies, come to steal my inventions?
Spies?!
You!
You've got a real scheming face on you.
He's got a good eye for people, at least.
Your inventions...
Does that mean you're Mr. Edison?!
That's right. I'm Edison.
Got a problem with that?
N-No...
So? What did you steal?
We didn't steal anything!
I see.
Good to hear it.
Get going now. I'm busy.
Um, well, er... I wanted
to ask you something...
I'm busy!
We're looking for some--
Then look for them somewhere else!
He's completely unapproachable.
This is a ticker, right?
Ticker?
It displays stock market quotes.
During the speculation boom
following the Civil War,
a trader's livelihood on Wall Street
required getting prices quickly.
Before then, stock information
was conveyed via
telegraphs using Morse Code.
But he modified it to display
using the alphabet.
Thanks to him, transaction
speeds increased rapidly.
It was the first of his inventions
that made a lot of money.
Money?
He was hoping to sell it for $5,000,
but it actually sold for $40,000.
For eight times the price?!
That shows how much the buyer
was able to foresee the value of the ticker.
You seem to know your stuff.
This is an electric pen.
This is... most likely
a prototype photocopier.
That's right.
You were my idol when I was a child.
Huh?
How old are you?!
I'm only 29!
Um...
There's some complicated
circumstances surrounding this.
--The truth is, we're from the future.
--Now that I look closer,
you have good, honest eyes.
Um... Um... Are you listening to me?
I take it all back.
He doesn't have a good eye for people at all.
Mr. Mikage...
He's honest when it comes to
business-- the best there is.
Is this a telephone?
I know this! It's Mr. Bell's!
Yeah.
I tried to make one based
on the one Bell exhibited
at the Centennial Exhibition in Philadelphia.
You made it?
As I thought.
It's really well-made. Bell's a smart guy.
As I recall, you were also
working on a telephone,
but Bell beat you to it.
And patented it, too.
Yeah.
It was frustrating, wasn't it?
What can you do?
But there's plenty of room
to improve the telephone!
First, the transmitter and receiver
being one-way is inconvenient.
It's one-way?
Look at that carefully.
You can send words through on that,
but you can't receive them.
Inconvenient, right?
Yeah.
So I'm working on a way
that you can hear what they're
saying while using the transmitter.
I think it would be really
convenient to have it be two-way.
I see!
And Bell's telephone
converts the vibrations of the voice into
electric current with an electromagnet,
but it can only carry the voice
about one kilometer,
and the sound is muffled.
I'm developing a microphone that
will make sound travel more clearly.
Carbon granules seem like they're
better suited than the electromagnet,
but I'm still figuring out
where to go from there.
I've tried out over 500 versions,
but it's not going well.
Five hundred?!
I'm getting so sick of it.
But even if I fail 1,000 times,
I'll keep going until I succeed.
This is... a phonograph?
That's a work in progress, too.
I thought it up while I was
working on the telephone.
If you can send a voice long-distance,
what if you could also store it?
He's so dynamic.
What do successful people have in common?
An indomitable will to fight,
forward-thinking ideas,
and unfounded self-confidence.
Having just one isn't enough.
Those who have them all succeed.
I know why Edison was a success.
To be honest, when Bell got the drop on me,
I was so depressed, I nearly
lost my will to keep going.
But I got some advice...
It was from an Easterner, like you two.
An Easterner?!
Yeah.
He said, "You've always bounced
back from your failures
to keep trying new inventions."
That person...
Was his name Eiji Hayase?
Eiji?
Was that his name?
Anyway, his words made me remember
that I was burning with the will to invent.
Where is that man now?
Huh? He's gone.
Gone?
He said something about
meeting me again in the future.
I didn't get it at all.
Future?
He said I was going to
bring light to the world.
Light?
He "wanted to be witness to
that moment," or something.
What a weirdo--
Excuse me.
H-Hey!
--Hey!
--Where are we going?
After Dr. Hayase, of course.
And if I may offer some unsolicited advice...
...if you're going to come late
to an invention's development,
first, make your own company,
and solicit investors.
Don't listen to what this bad guy says!
Bad... guy?
Sorry, but when it comes to business,
I say nothing but beneficial things.
Ow! That hurts!
Don't pull me!
My own company, eh?
You wanted to go after Papa,
but we don't know how many
years into the future he's gone!
Untrue.
Huh?
He's visiting the day Edison
brought light to the world.
In other words, the
invention of the light bulb.
Huh?! Mr. Edison invented the light bulb?!
Learn a little more history, would you?
I'm doing the best I can!
In 1879, Edison completed
the Edison light bulb.
Edison light bulb?
Yes, on October 21st.
The success of it allowed for
the first practical light bulbs,
and the technology was quickly
adopted across the world.
So, how do we travel to that day?
We can't.
Have you forgotten the position you're in?
Dr. Hayase moves where he wants to.
It can't be impossible.
I'll ask again: How do we
travel to October 21st?
Shun can do it.
The Mizuki boy?
You've been watching us, haven't you?
Yes.
Send us...
...to October 21st, 1879.
You hear me?
You'd better not try any funny business.
Hey.
Eiji has one of those armillary
compasses too, doesn't he?
Can't we get in contact with him?
According to my brother,
the armillary compass the doctor
has is from three years ago,
so it's synced to the system from three
years ago, and we can't communicate with him.
Quit whispering!
Settings complete.
Let's go.
"The Year 1879
(What is now) Menlo Park, America"
Two minutes!
That's the shortest one yet.
I know! You don't have to
report every little thing!
Mr. Edison! It's been a while!
Do you remember us?
You two... Get down!
Another one appeared...
Are all Easterners magicians?
Easterners?!
Papa's here, then?
Yeah, he's here.
He came out of thin air, just like you did,
and he broke my light bulb,
just like you did!
After we'd just set a record
for 35 continuous hours!
We're very sorry.
Okay, let's go again!
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir!
Um, Mr. Edison...
Shut up!
I'm busy.
Where is Dr. Hayase?
There.
The phonograph?
He told me to let his daughter
play it when she showed up.
Mari, I'll be waiting in
the warehouse out back.
That's Papa's voice!
Where's the warehouse out back?
It's out back, of course!
We're starting!
I'd like to witness this moment in history.
But I need to speak to Dr. Hayase first.
Is that it?
What's going on? Those clouds
appeared so suddenly...
Hey! What did you do?!
I didn't do anything!
What's the meaning of this?!
Brother?
Shun?
What's going on?
Hey! Wh-What are you doing?!
Stay right by my side.
Mari! Close your eyes!
Your reactions are surprisingly quick.
Papa!
Hayase...
What...?
Edison told you I was with her?
That's right.
But why were you able
to time travel with Mari?
The armillary compass!
Why do you have it?
Waka found it in the
basement of the laboratory.
It had fallen next to the machine, she said.
She said you'd probably
prepared it for her, but...
Could I have made it later?
But I've gotta tell you, Mom's super mad!
What? Why?
This guy in the past... Napoleon?
That guy's cup?
Because you took it and sold it!
She found out?
That's so bad...
I'm too scared to go back.
Papa...
I see.
It's better for me that you don't go back.
Then we could have the time travel
system all to ourselves.
Mari!
What's going on?
Let's run away!
What?!
It can't be...
This is...
"Next Episode: Cherished Scientists"
"Mari and Waka's Quick Science"
Mari and Waka's Quick Science!
He's visiting the day Edison
brought light to the world.
In other words, the invention
of the light bulb.
Huh?! Mr. Edison invented the light bulb?!
This is the light bulb Mr. Edison invented.
Before him, there had been issues
with the resilience of the filament,
and light bulbs weren't practical.
What issues?
Filaments of the time were primarily
made from processed charcoal,
"Filament"
and they produced heat
and light at the same time.
"Filament"
Let's experiment with mechanical pencil lead,
which is made from charcoal and carbon.
It's shining!
Actually, it's burning!
You can't use that...
To make light bulbs practical, they had
to do something to prevent oxidation.
Oxidation?
Oxygen is what makes things burn.
Is it possible... there's no
oxygen inside light bulbs?
This time, we'll fill the vessel
with helium to drive out the oxygen.
--It's not catching fire!
--I was right!
But it's slowly melting, isn't it?
Even if it doesn't burn,
the continuous heat put out
causes the filament to weaken and snap.
He performed thousands of resilience
tests to make a practical light bulb.
Mr. Edison's resilience
brought light to the world, huh?