Shiiwaku, manabi... Huh? Fu-re? Re-re?
What was this one again?
Hang on a minute...
"Characters you don't have to use the kun
reading for even if grammatically necessary."
What does that mean?!
You're not supposed to read them?!
Thanks for helping while you're
studying for your test.
Don't worry.
You gotta refresh yourself sometimes.
My mind was going blank.
Look how hard you're working!
I did really bad on my midterms,
so I at least want to work hard for the finals.
Really? That's a good attitude to have.
If there's anything you don't understand,
feel free to ask Shun.
I'm sure he can teach you a lot.
Huh? Wh-Why are you bringing up Shun?
He's so busy, I doubt he'd
have time to help me anyway.
Oh, really?
It seems like you two and Waka have all
been studying together a lot lately.
Waka's mother told me all about it.
Huh?!
Th-That was... Waka's idea...
Shun's being very considerate.
I really do love him.
Y-You love him?
"Episode 7
Morse's Inspiration"
Ayuhara! Ichikawa! Imai!
"Episode 7
Morse's Inspiration"
Yeah! Eighty percent!
Ichikawa, an 80 is nothing to yell about.
Hayase!
Sorry!
Himuro!
Fujita!
Matsuyama!
Mizuki!
She received the only perfect score
in the class today.
Minami!
Murakami!
Maybe I'm just not any good at school.
Welco--
I just came here as a customer today.
Don't worry.
On your favorites menu,
it said you have a special chiffon cake.
I'm terribly sorry.
We sold out of the Jersey Milk
Chiffon Cake this morning.
I see. What a shame.
I was hoping to take one back for a client.
A client?
Why would you...
The fund we manage for her
took a slight loss.
I was hoping to take it as an apology.
You, directly, Mr. Mikage?
I'm grateful to have such a
beautiful woman remember my name.
She's a sixty-year-old industrialist.
She's famous for her gourmet palate.
Consideration is more important when we fail
than when business is going well.
A woman with a gourmet palate?
In that case, what about our six types
of pudding, made with organic vegetables?
They're very popular with women
who are concerned about
ingredients, flavor, and calories.
Oh?
I'll take that pudding, then.
Thank you!
You don't have to get so upset.
It's just the usual, right?
But I really studied hard this time.
Mari. What's wrong?
She got her usual
awful score on our last test.
Waka! You don't have to put it that way!
Really?
B-Brother, what are you doing?
I found Dr. Hayase's thesis,
so I was reading it.
"Regularity in Dimensional Distortions
Caused by Changes in Electromagnetic Fields"?
I think this is the basis
for the machine he created.
It's written in Japanese,
but I can barely understand it.
Yeah... the vocabulary is too
specialized for me to understand.
Shun is so amazing.
He can understand it just by looking at it...
I don't actually understand it.
That's why I was looking at it.
If you keep looking at things you
don't understand, and keep thinking,
some day, it might all come together.
Really?
So? What's with the strings
of letters and numbers?
I believe this is the record of the
armillary compass's destinations.
I think AM1 may be the doctor,
and AM2 could be Mari.
Huh? Then we know
the last place Papa went to?
Hmm...
If I could grasp the system behind
these numbers and letters...
That's something you don't
understand yet, huh?
I'm afraid not.
I see.
Don't get so depressed.
We'll figure it out soon.
Right, Brother?
Yes, that's right.
Well, then... let's get started!
For now, I believe if you touch
any picture that's Morse or later,
you'll travel to the past.
Right.
“The Year 1825
(What is Now) New Haven, America”
So cold!
Huh?
Oh... um...
Oh, are you the scientist, Mr. Morse?
I'm not a scientist, but my name is Morse.
Who are you?
I'm Mari. Mari Hayase.
That's not what I meant.
You just came from a burst of light.
Oh, well...
Why are you crying, anyway?
My wife died last week.
When it happened,
I was off painting a portrait
of Marquis de Lafayette...
A portrait? Mr. Morse, are you a painter?
Yes.
Huh? What's going on?
Mari, until he invented Morse Code,
it seems he was a skilled painter
who gave lectures at universities.
But in 1825,
his wife died, and the news didn't
reach him at his place of work in time,
so he missed her funeral.
Brother...
This place on the monitor...
is it not synced with the book?
And these numbers here...
It really looks like the
history of AM1, doesn't it?
What is this?
Just who are you talking to?
Oh, um...
Mari, there's something I want to test.
Huh? What is it?
I'm going to rewrite the coordinates of your
armillary compass to match the doctor's.
What will happen then?
I think it will take you to
when the doctor met Mr. Morse.
I understand. Try it!
Matching up coordinates with AM2.
Battery remaining. Good.
How's Mari doing?
Wait a minute!
She's fine. No change!
Good. I don't think I'm missing anything.
Mari, let's go.
O-Okay!
Mr. Morse! You're going to make
an invention that will change humanity!
So don't be sad forever!
Sh-She disappeared?!
What happened just now?
"The Year 1832, on the Atlantic Ocean"
That hurt...
--Aren't you... that girl?
--Mr. Morse!
I thought you were an angel or something.
I started thinking about
a lot of things after that.
But I'm just an humble painter, after all.
I don't think I could create an incredible
invention like you talked about.
People with no talent,
no matter how hard they work,
will never accomplish anything great.
But...
Maybe I'm just not any good at school.
Luckily, I was blessed with artistic talent.
Thanks to that, I can live a decent life.
It's amazing that you can make
such pretty pictures with only blip-blops...
Blip-blops?
Oh, dots?
Thank you. I am a professional, after all.
Yes! I think that went well.
Yes. Thank goodness.
It's from Futa!
What could it say?!
What's going on with you?
Brother, you handle the rest!
H-Hey!
It's the ocean!
This ship is going from Europe to America.
Then this is the Atlantic Ocean?
Yes.
Now, now, everyone! Your attention, please!
I have here a piece of copper wire.
And if I wind it around the iron,
then bring it close to the nails...
...nothing happens!
However!
If I bring the tip of the
copper wire to this battery,
and run electricity through it...
How mysterious!
All I did was wrap iron with copper wire!
And it becomes a magnet
that attracts one nail after another!
And when I detach it from the battery...
Wow! Papa!
Oh! Mari! You came at the right time.
Help me out!
Huh? Help you out? W-With what?
Never mind! Just step over here!
Now, now. The next trick...
When I re-attach it to the battery,
it's a magnet again!
When it attaches, they stick!
When I take it off, they release!
This is the newest invention
of science, the electromagnet!
Mama! I want to do that, too!
You want to try? Step on up!
It worked!
Amazing, isn't it?
Now, these electromagnetic kits
sell for just one dollar if you buy now!
Perfect for a child's education!
Will it make them a doctor or a minister?
You're selling them?
What are you doing, Mari?
Sell them! Sell them!
Huh? Me?
Mama, buy one!
Thanks for your business!
No, we really can't.
Stop that. And give it back.
Huh? No, ma'am! Don't be like that!
Huh? Everyone? W-Wait!
Could I buy one?
Huh?
S-Sure.
Thank you for your business.
No matter how far away the line stretches,
it will attract or release
the nails just the same, right?
Yes, of course!
An electromagnet, huh?
Magnificent!
Mari. Thanks to you, I feel like I've been
able to see something I couldn't see before.
Thank you.
If I can make a picture with dots,
I'm sure I can make words with dots.
In that moment, Morse realized that
by turning an electromagnet on and off,
he could create words by
combining dots and dashes.
In other words, long and short signals.
This invention revolutionized
the speed of communication,
which had previously been done
with messenger pigeons and semaphores.
Electric signals opened the way to
long-range communication for the first time.
He came upon the idea
seven years after his wife's death.
And twelve years after that,
on May 24th, 1844,
Morse successfully sent the famous words,
"What hath God wrought,"
from Washington to Baltimore.
That's your father, right, Mari?
Erk!
W-Well, I...
I am an American doctor and scientist,
Charles Thomas Jackson!
Ch-Charles?
Well, forget it.
Thank you. You showed me an interesting
invention, Mr. Charles Thomas Jackson.
I'm so glad you believed me!
Huh?
Um, yes... You're welcome.
Huh?!
Papa... what are you doing here?
Huh? Oh...
On the way back from Europe,
he watched a demonstration
of the electromagnet on this ship,
and had the inspiration for Morse Code.
So?
Well...
The man who was supposed to
inspire him missed the boat.
Does that make it okay for a
time traveler like you to do this?
And how do you know that, anyway?
W-Well... before the voyage,
he had a bit too much to drink...
Papa...
How do you know that?
Well... he couldn't hold his liquor
the way I expected...
You were drinking with him, huh?
Well, I wasn't expecting him
to pass out drunk at two bottles!
That's ridiculous!
You're starting to sound like your mother.
Because I'm her daughter!
Even so, what are you doing here?
The coordinates to Morse in that book
should have been for 1825 in New Haven.
Shun rewrote the coordinates in the system.
That's Shun for you!
He's started to figure out
how the machine works, has he?
Don't try to change the subject!
Erk!
What are you even doing in the past, Papa?
I'm discovering the secrets of that book.
Huh?
The book... You mean, you didn't make it?
Certainly not!
I could never create anything like that!
Wh-What?!
I was just doing matter
transportation experiments,
and that book suddenly transported to me!
It seemed likely that it
came from the future. Yes!
Oops, sorry. Looks like it's time.
W-Wait! Papa!
I don't know what caused me
to go away for three years.
But I think it's destiny that you
got involved with that machine.
Huh?! What's that supposed to mean?!
What is it? Cut to the chase already!
Celebrate! We won the regional preliminaries!
The nationals are up next!
Thanks to you, I can study
and play soccer, too!
Thanks a lot!
Our soccer club is in the nationals!
It's a miracle!
Yes. It is delicious.
Excuse me.
We've discovered Akira Hayase's background.
She's the eldest daughter of Renzaburo Miwa,
president of the Miwa Concern.
When she was twenty, she moved to France,
and gained experience as a patissiere.
The Miwa Concern...
I see. So she's unlikely
to be swayed by money.
By the way, what about the book that appeared
during the matter transporting experiments?
It seems to be a book about the
history of magnets and electricity.
But that's all we know for now.
I see.
Would you like some, too?
Thank you, sir.
She took them all.
I see.
Shun Mizuki...
In 2025, he developed the Law of
Time-Space Abnormality Measurement
that made time travel technology possible.
In 2076, he successfully
invented the TSS limiter
which prevented time paradox variations.
Mari...
W-Welcome back.
What's wrong?
I'm such an idiot.
I can't understand anything Papa's thinking.
You're not stupid, Mari.
But... even if I study,
my grades don't improve.
I can't understand anything you guys do!
Everyone has lots of things
they don't understand.
That's why you need to keep thinking.
Stew over things. Investigate things.
Even then, there are a lot of things
you won't understand.
But if you keep thinking,
then one day, out of the blue,
everything will come together,
and you'll understand.
In physics, we call that
phase transformation.
Phase transformation?
Yes.
As water gets colder, there's an instant
when it becomes solid ice, right?
Yeah.
And at 100 degrees Celsius,
it becomes water vapor.
Yeah.
Even things that, at a glance,
seem like they're not changing at all,
if you keep pouring energy
into them, in one instant,
they'll suddenly undergo a physical change.
Study and inspiration are the same way.
If you keep thinking,
you'll undergo a sudden change?
Yes.
Lots of people saw that exhibition,
but why did only Mr. Morse
have the inspiration for the signal?
It must be because
he had been thinking about the
long-distance communication code for years.
There's no need to think
you don't have any talent
just because you don't
see results right away.
Shun!
What? What? What's with this vibe?
You'll be okay, Mari.
Yeah! Thanks, Shun!
Oh-ho! Not bad at all!
"Learning without thought is labor lost;
thought without learning is perilous."
I see you're working hard.
Yeah!
Just because my grades don't go up right away
is no reason to give up, I realized.
I see. That's very good.
Perseverance is important, right?
Yeah!
In physics, it's called phase transformation!
That's what Shun taught me.
Oh? Shun said that?
Huh?
That's my new almond praline cream puff.
Let me know what you think later.
Okay. Thanks.
Okay! Let's work hard!
"Next Episode: Bell's Decision"
"Mari and Waka's Quick Science"
Mari and Waka's Quick Science!
Just what signal did Mr. Morse come up with
after watching Papa's demonstration?
Yeah! I really want to hear about it!
These are the transmitters
and receivers used in Morse Code.
"Transmitter"
"Iron"
"Electric Current" "Receiver"
Pressing the switch of the transmitter
sends electricity to the receiver,
"Transmitter"
"Iron"
"Electric Current" "Receiver"
and turns the coil into an electromagnet,
which attracts the iron.
"Transmitter"
"Iron"
"Electric Current" "Receiver"
When the electricity is cut off,
the power of the spring pulls it away again.
"Transmitter"
"Iron"
"Electric Current" "Receiver"
Morse thought of using
this phenomenon to send signals.
"Transmitter"
"Iron"
"Electric Current" "Receiver"
Mr. Morse is so smart!
"Transmitter"
"Iron"
"Electric Current" "Receiver"
"Transmitter"
"Iron"
"Electric Current" "Receiver"
"Morse Code"
"Short" "Long"
"* This is modern Morse Code. It differs from the system devised by Morse."
And even more important
is that he figured out
"Morse Code"
"Short" "Long"
"* This is modern Morse Code. It differs from the system devised by Morse."
a system of long and short signals
to express letters and numbers.
"Morse Code"
"Short" "Long"
"* This is modern Morse Code. It differs from the system devised by Morse."
This is Morse Code.
"Morse Code"
"Short" "Long"
"* This is modern Morse Code. It differs from the system devised by Morse."
And that's how we were able
to send messages, right?
"Morse Code"
"Short" "Long"
"* This is modern Morse Code. It differs from the system devised by Morse."
And that's how we were able
to send messages, right?
"* This is modern Morse Code. It differs from the system devised by Morse."
Okay!
Then let's use electricity to send
some signals through the transmitter
"* This is modern Morse Code. It differs from the system devised by Morse."
in Morse Code!
Yeah!
"* This is modern Morse Code. It differs from the system devised by Morse."
Okay!
Is that an M?
"* This is modern Morse Code. It differs from the system devised by Morse."
That's an A?
R?
"* This is modern Morse Code. It differs from the system devised by Morse."
I!
W-A-K-A.
"* This is modern Morse Code. It differs from the system devised by Morse."
Which means...
Mari-Waka!