As a present for our
classmate Futa's birthday,
I went to Waka's house
to bake a ball-shaped cake.
But in Waka's brother Shun's room,
I found this raggedy old science book.
I had seen it in my dad's lab before
he went missing three years ago.
But then suddenly, the book...
"The Year 1600
(What is now) London, England"
"Episode 2 Sorrowful Gilbert"
Is this the harbor?
Yes, this is where I met the
Eastern man I mentioned before.
Then maybe...
Papa...
Papa!
Papa! If you're here, answer me!
Please! Papa!
Answer me! Papa!
Hey there! You okay, little lady?
Tha--
I'm sorry! Forgive me! I'm sorry! Forgive me!
James.
Dr. Gilbert!
Welcome back.
Sorry to cut to the chase,
but do you have what I asked for?
I did just as you asked. It's on the ship.
I can't say I understand why,
but the further north we went,
the sharper the angle became.
Oh? That's very interesting.
I wrote the details here.
Have a look.
Thank you. I'm very grateful.
Oh, this is nothing.
And thank you, Doctor.
No need for that.
That reminds me.
Doc, you mentioned earlier...
That Roman fellow...
Um, Bru...
Giordano?
Yes, that's it! Giordano Bruno, yeah?
Hmm?
Last month, the Church
in Rome put him on trial
to get him to take back his opinions.
Giordano, on trial?
Yeah. But he's been
locked up for seven years.
If taking back his opinion would set
him free, why doesn't he just do it?
I'm sure his pride
as a scientist is at stake.
It's not as easy as you make it sound.
Um... that thing you were talking about...
Yes. "The Earth revolves around the sun."
There's a Roman philosopher
who's very insistent on the matter.
What? About something that obvious?
Obvious?
I see. In your age, everyone knows that?
Yes...
That's wonderful.
But in our day and age,
the Church calls it heresy.
Oh, that's awful!
Church and astronomy have
nothing to do with each other!
"Our land was created by God, and all
the heavenly bodies revolve around it."
That's the Church's teaching.
He's saying it's a lie.
If people realized that, it would be a
threat to their position, wouldn't it?
Even so... there's no reason to
throw people in jail over the truth.
You're right.
"And yet, it moves."
Scientists have known that for over
fifty years, since Copernicus's day.
But we can't say it.
To those in power, inconvenient
truths must be crushed by force.
But that's awful!
Anything?
No good. I didn't find anything.
Maybe you have to get in from outside?
Yeah.
You want to check around the outside?
Well... Why don't we set up
a petition or something?
Thank you, my dear.
But as we're home now...
This is magnificent!
Interested?
What does it say?
It records the changes in the dip circle's
needle based on the ship's position.
Dip circle?
You played with it on the ship, remember?
It's a machine designed to record
how far downward the
compass needle is pointing.
A compass needle can point down?
Yes.
A sailor named Robert Norman
discovered that about 20 years ago.
But when I asked the sailors
about the angle it took,
they said it changed depending on the place.
What does that mean?
I don't know. That's why I'm investigating.
But Norman's findings did teach us one thing.
The theory that a compass needle
points to the North Star...
That can't be true.
Why not?
If the North Star were pulling
the compass's needle,
the needle wouldn't tilt down.
It would point up.
I see!
And if you went to the North Pole,
it would point straight up!
And it repudiates one more theory.
The theory of a magnetic
mountain at the North Pole.
If there were a magnetic
mountain at the North Pole,
then if the circle were in London,
the needle should be pointing at
about a 20 degree angle downward.
"20 degrees"
the needle should be pointing at
about a 20 degree angle downward.
But...
"20 degrees"
But?
Anything?
Nothing.
You two!
What are you doing there?
My sister says she dropped
her ribbon in the area.
I see.
But it's getting late. You should
go home and look tomorrow.
You're right. I will.
By the way...
Do you know how long
the lights have been on here?
Oh, I turned them on myself.
I thought having a little light
would make it easier to search.
Are you related to Mr. Hayase?
No, but my little sister is
in class with his daughter.
And I used to help
Mr. Hayase with his research.
I see...
Do you think I could have a look inside?
What? Of course.
Brother...
What's that?
A simple dip circle.
Or rather, a dip circle I made
based on this phenomenon.
I stuck this needle through
the center of the float
so that it balances parallel with the water.
But if I use this magnet...
...and do this...
Do you understand what happened?
Contact with the magnet
made the iron needle magnetic.
That's right!
Now the needle isn't parallel.
It's pointing this far down.
What does it mean?
If there were a magnetic
mountain at the North Pole,
here in London, the magnetic force
would probably not tilt the needle
further than 20 degrees.
But in fact, it's angled down
at about 70 degrees.
What does that tell us?
The magnet is under the ground?
"S Pole"
Yes, effectively.
Huh?
"S Pole"
And the results of that
investigation are useful.
Look at this.
The longitudes and latitudes
written here indicate
that the N pole of the dip circle's needle
points further down as you go north.
Then, as you travel below the
equator, it begins pointing up.
What? It points up?
That's right.
What is on the other side of the N pole?
The... S pole?
Right.
So why would the S pole point down?
Because there's a N pole under the ground?
Yes.
In the north, there's an S pole.
In the south, there's a N pole.
It's like the whole Earth is a giant magnet!
Wow! I see!
But the question is...
...how do we prove it?
What? You don't have enough?
What we have now is just a hypothesis.
It's not proof.
R-Really?
Science is interesting, isn't it?
The more you think, the more you investigate,
the closer you come to the truth.
The technology that brought you to this era,
was, I'm sure, the result of
a similarly lengthy process.
I believe that.
Humans create what they imagine.
Okay!
Thanks.
Not at all.
I'll go shut off the breaker now.
I'm sorry to take up all your time.
It's fine...
It'll be hard to do any
more tonight, I guess.
"Hayase Research Laboratory"
Well, take care on your way home.
Okay. Let's go, Waka.
"Hayase Research Laboratory"
O-Okay...
I see. So the doctor hasn't
necessarily come back.
Understood.
Continue investigating.
Contact me if you find anything.
Mr. Mikage, what's going on?
Nothing.
Mama...
Brother, what will we do?
Shouldn't we have asked
that policeman about Mari?
If we're going to let anyone know,
it should be Mari's mother first.
Good point.
I wonder if the doctor
disappeared like Mari has.
What?
Anyway, we can't let things remain this way.
Let's go to Mari's house.
Right.
I think it's ready!
Should I open it, then?
Okay!
Is this right?
Yeah, it's done!
It's done! What a great smell!
Are you sure it's all right,
with that much sugar?
It's fine! Look!
Good morning.
Good morning, Master.
Good morning!
I smell something delicious.
That's right!
Look at this! She's a cake-making genius!
Oh, no! I'm not that good.
Oh, these look wonderful.
You've been so hospitable,
and this is about the only
way I know to thank you.
Um... let's do our best together, okay?
Yes.
What's that?
Huh?
This? It's called whipped cream.
No, in front of you.
I thought I'd try out some ball-shaped cakes.
Today's my friend's birthday.
Well, that's back in my
own time, of course.
If you make it too big, then the batter
doesn't cook all the way through.
So I thought if I baked thinner cakes,
cut them into circles and layered them,
then coated them with fresh cream...
I see. That's it!
Mr. Gilbert! Mr. Gilbert!
I'll get it.
Thank you, Mari.
Huh?
You've inspired me.
Thanks to this cake,
I've figured out how to prove my hypothesis.
A model! A model!
Huh?
If I file down a magnet
into a model of the Earth,
it will unlock the secret
of the dip circle's needle!
This is incredible!
Master?
A letter from Rome.
From Rome?
Master?
It can't be. Why?!
Wh-What's wrong?
Giordano Bruno... has been put to death.
It apparently happened this month,
on the seventeenth of February.
"And yet, it moves."
There's only one truth.
Mr. Gilbert...
Is this still happening in your age?
Those who cry the truth, persecuted
and murdered by those in power?
What an inauspicious time we live in.
I never even thought about that.
Wh-What?
She disappeared...
She went home?
This is... the science of the future?
Brother, look!
It hurts...
Mari?
Waka?
Yeah! I'm back!
Oh, where have you been?
I've been so worried!
Stupid Mari...
Waka... I'm sorry I worried you.
You really did. But I'm so glad you're back.
Yeah.
That reminds me! How long have I been gone?
Brother? What time is it?
About half past eight.
So about three and a half hours?
That's all?
It was over two days over there.
I told you, I'm staying
at Waka's house tonight.
Waka's mom already agreed to it.
Huh? Hang on.
Um, Mama wants to talk to you.
Yes?
Oh, we're just fine.
What? I see. The PTA meeting next week...
Brother, how did it go?
Yeah, everything in the book has disappeared.
But it seems to be true that Mari
traveled back to London in 1600.
Look.
"William Gilbert.
1544-1603.
Inventor of the dip circle.
With an experiment using
an Earth-shaped magnet,
he proved that the Earth
was a giant magnetic body.
Afterwards, Gilbert became
the first person in the world
to clearly differentiate a
magnet's ability to attract iron
from the light attraction created
by static electricity in amber.
This discovery was one of the first stepping
stones to humanity harnessing electricity."
I'm so glad!
He really did get to prove it!
It's possible that Dr. Hayase's disappearance
has something to do with this book, too.
Yeah, I bet you're right!
What?
This is a homework assignment from Papa!
I'm going to keep searching
for the truth, like Mr. Gilbert,
and find Papa!
That sounds so fun!
Like a tour of famous times in history!
Take me with you, okay?
But only after we make Futa's cake!
Oh!
I forgot about that!
I hope they're not
getting in over their heads.
So bored...
Futa!
Are you sure you should be up?
Hey, you two!
As you can see, I'm just fine!
I was just in for tests. They should
let me out today if nothing comes up.
But your brother seriously saved my life.
I'll come by to thank him myself later,
but give my regards in the meantime, okay?
"Vending Machine Contains AED"
Okay!
But we have a reward for you, too.
"Vending Machine Contains AED"
Happy birthday to you! Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, dear Futa!
Happy birthday to you!
Wow, are you kidding me?
It's so cool! Is this my birthday cake?
After everything that happened,
I thought everyone forgot!
Waka would never forget!
But how did you even make this?
I got a lot of thinking done
at this old scientist's place.
Old scientist?
Yeah!
But I guess you're pretty glad humans
learned to harness electricity, huh, Futa?
Huh? What are you talking about?
Well, it's because scientists work
so hard to invent all kinds of things
that we can live the way we do now!
Science is interesting, isn't it?
"Happy Birthday, Futa"
What's with her?
She's been through a lot.
"Happy Birthday, Futa"
Yeah!
Look at this! It matches up perfectly
with the numbers James brought me!
You're right!
The Earth really is a giant magnet!
"Next Episode:
Franklin's Spirit of Defiance"
This is an incredible discovery!
"Next Episode:
Franklin's Spirit of Defiance"
"Mari and Waka's Quick Science"
Mari and Waka's Quick Science!
Mr. Gilbert said Earth was a giant magnet.
But I have no idea what he's talking about.
Me neither!
"Crust
Mantle
Outer Core Inner Core"
The Earth is made up of four layers.
"Crust
Mantle
Outer Core Inner Core"
The outer core is believed to contain
iron, nickel, and other things,
"Crust
Mantle
Outer Core Inner Core"
liquefied at high temperatures.
"Crust
Mantle
Outer Core Inner Core"
"Crust
Mantle
Outer Core Inner Core"
"Outer Core"
When the liquefied iron and nickel in the
outer core moves, it creates an electric charge.
"Outer Core"
This electricity flows in a ring through
the outer core, producing a magnetic charge.
This is why the Earth is like a magnet.
Oh, I thought there was just
a big magnet buried in there.
If you have a magnetized metal,
it loses its magnetic charge
at very high temperatures.
Oh, really?
We should experiment and see if it's true!
It's not sticking.
If we magnetize this nail with a magnet...
...it sticks!
Now let's heat this nail with a gas burner.
They fell!
The heat took away the magnet's power!
And since the center of
the Earth is really hot,
that proves there can't be
a giant magnet buried there!