Huh?
Waka, are you okay?
Y-Yes, just leave it to me!
See? It's going... Huh?
Hey! Hang on!
Waka, fight!
Work!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Why aren't you working?!
Waka, I'll do it later!
O-Okay. You can do it...
Waka, are you okay?
Hey, Mari! What are you doing?!
Stop it! Stop it!
Cream everywhere...
How delicious!
But it must have hurt to have
Mr. Mixer die in the line of duty.
No, I think it's still functional.
Really? Time for a miraculous recovery?
The batteries just ran out. They're old.
Mom's so bad at maintaining things like that.
It's so irresponsible.
You took it without asking.
You're in no place to complain.
It wasn't without asking!
I left her a note to say that
I was making crepes with Mari.
Here.
There it is!
Huh?
Well?
Yeah, it's readable now.
"Episode 4
Volta on the Battlefield"
But it doesn't say anything
about this machine.
"Episode 4
Volta on the Battlefield"
Shun, may I?
Nothing happened, huh?
I guess you can't go back to
somewhere you've already been?
The one thing that's clear is that this book
and that machine are connected.
And Mari's pendant, too.
After Mr. Franklin comes...
Alessandro Volta?
Huh?
I knew it...
What was that girl thinking?
"The Year 1800
(what is now) Pavia, Italy"
As I just explained,
"The Year 1800
(what is now) Pavia, Italy"
I have filled this with flammable gas,
"The Year 1800
(what is now) Pavia, Italy"
I have filled this with flammable gas,
plugging it with a cork.
Now, using this electrophorus,
I charge up the electricity, and...
Now, I'll release the electricity
inside this electric pistol!
Excuse me! Could you get
a little further away?
Incredible!
Truly incredible!
Magnificent!
Who are you? Where did you come from?
Um...
This is magnificent, Volta!
Are you a magician?
Volta?
He might be a great scientist!
She's gone again, huh?
Y-Yes.
Another traveler from
the future's Far East, eh?
Another?
A few days ago, a man
barged into my laboratory.
He said he was from the future.
I assumed he was mad.
Was his name Eiji... Eiji Hayase?
Eiji? I don't remember...
That man might have been my father!
He's a scientist, and... um...
...he'd be wearing a pendant like mine!
Are you okay?
I-I'm sorry...
Leone! What's the meaning of this?
It's the Austrian soldiers.
Please, have mercy! Please!
Shut up! Move!
Dad!
Darling!
Stop lollygagging! Carry it!
Darling! Speak to me!
Darling!
Those who refuse to help deserve no mercy!
Take it!
Stop it! Please stop!
Get out of the way!
Please!
If you take that, I can't do my job!
If you want to blame someone,
blame the French invaders.
Dad!
Darling!
That's awful!
To the north of this city,
the invading French army is fighting the
Austrian occupation forces stationed there.
Really. It's such an annoyance.
We're commandeering this for the war!
We've been dispatched here
from Austria to protect you.
Any who don't cooperate
will be treated as collaborators,
and shown no mercy!
What? What's this?
It's not Mari's...
Brother has that book.
Mari has her golden pendant.
Does that mean this is mine?
"Team Time Travelers"
Oh, Mari's dad!
Waka?
Huh?
Wh-What?
Help me find the manual for this machine.
You can look in those cabinets.
R-Right. Got it.
Welcome back, Professor.
What is it?
That man is back.
What?
Man?
Hey!
Papa!
Papa! Papa!
Mari? Is that you, Mari?
You smell like cake, just like your mama.
Are you really Mari?
Papa... you really were
traveling through time!
We hadn't heard from you for three years,
so everyone was worried!
Three years?
An armillary compass?
Mari, who gave this to you?
Who? It was you, Papa.
Did you forget?
Even if I'm gone, don't worry.
This armillary compass
will always show you the way.
I must be from before I gave this to you.
Huh?
I'm your papa from when you
were in elementary school.
Well, no matter.
The fact that you're here
means you found the
basement of my laboratory?
Yeah.
Right now it's a secret
between me, Waka, and Shun.
I see. Thank you.
But we don't know how to use that machine.
You don't know how to use it?
Then how did you get here?
Is that enough father-daughter time?
Yeah, it is.
My business with you is
far more important right now,
Mr. Volta.
Shall we ready the electricity?
No, not yet.
How is it?
As I thought, it's not moving them.
The appearance of that girl
inclines me to believe you a little bit more.
I'm glad to hear it.
I can't protect you if you don't believe me.
Protect me?
What do you mean?
Due to my clumsiness, Napoleon's return
to the Italian front was delayed.
If I don't protect you, history will change.
Napoleon?
Who's that?
In a few years, he will conquer Europe
and become its emperor.
Under his patronage,
you will make revolutionary
inventions and discoveries.
But as things are now, you'll end up
being shot by an Austrian soldier,
and die tomorrow.
Huh?
Ridiculous.
You're saying that because you're from the
future, you know what's going to happen?
That's right.
Wait!
Move! No mercy to those who get in our way!
P-Professor! The Austrian soldiers...
Out of the way!
Who are you people?!
Don't move! We'll shoot anyone who resists!
Excuse me.
Mr. Mikage.
We've discovered the source of the money
Dr. Hayase used to repay his research funds.
A jade cup of Napoleon,
which sold for $100 million
at Sotheby's three years ago,
was sent there by
Dr. Hayase to be sold at auction.
Napoleon's jade cup? Was it genuine?
Here's the expert's opinion from Sotheby's.
I believe it must be.
Investigate a little further.
Yes, sir.
Who are you people?!
This is a sacred university!
Even if you are the Austrian army,
this is no place for such
outrageous behavior!
Get out!
What did you say?!
Don't do it!
Wait! Don't resist!
Marco! How dare you...
Mr. Volta!
A French prisoner of war has escaped.
We received information
that he's hiding here.
Have you seen any suspicious individuals?
What? Me?
Oh, well... I guess I am.
You think you are?
Mari.
When I give the signal,
wind the knob at the bottom
of the armillary compass clockwise.
Knob? Like this?
Got it?
Y-Yeah.
Good girl.
And when you get back,
tell Shun to press the triangle button
in the middle of the keyboard.
That should teach him
the basic system controls.
Aren't you going back, Papa?
I'm going back to when
you were in elementary school.
I have to give you that armillary compass.
You two!
What are you talking about over there?
Mari.
Turn the...
...knob!
Papa!
You jerks...
You really shot, didn't you?
Electric Punch!
You won't escape!
Papa!
Papa, behind you!
If you want to shoot, then shoot me here!
But if you're willing to use a
weapon like this on someone...
...that means you're prepared
to die yourself, right?
That hurts, you know!
Mari.
I'll be fine, so go on ahead.
Okay!
What?
Sh-Sh-She disappeared!
We are the gods who protect this Earth!
Tell your superiors...
If you harm these people, I will
bring great ruin upon Austria!
Understand?
Now go!
Let me see.
The bullet is out.
Do you have alcohol?
Yes. I'll look after him.
Are they...
Don't worry. They're not dead.
A powerful electric shock has just
knocked them temporarily unconscious.
It's another new invention.
No... I shouldn't.
If that's from the future,
I don't think I should touch it.
I see. Very prudent.
What's...
They're plans for an electric generator
that uses two types of metal and brine.
Yes, I've heard of it.
This is where everything begins.
I'm glad I kept you safe,
Mr. Volta.
May I ask you one question?
How can you be unharmed
after taking all those shots?
Protective clothing made
from super-light metals
and artificial fibers.
It provides over five times the protection
as the same weight of steel.
That's how.
The future... it's like a fantasy.
Yes.
And just one last thing...
Science enriches society.
But if used in the wrong way,
it can cause irreversible problems.
I just wanted you to know that.
Speaking from personal experience?
It hurts...
Are you awake?
If you ever interfere with these
people again, I'll show no mercy.
I can appear at any time.
Remember that.
The future of humanity...
Interesting!
You mean you met the doctor from
before his three-year disappearance?
Yeah. I think so.
Is that possible?
Theoretically, yes.
It's possible that the pages of places
you've traveled to stop responding
to prevent a time paradox where
you meet yourself in the past.
This is all a little too complicated
for me to understand...
Mr. Mikage...
"100 Yen Shop
Star King"
Wait a minute!
"100 Yen Shop
Star King"
I'm gonna buy batteries.
"100 Yen Shop
Star King"
What's wrong?
The smell of the gunpowder was scary.
Mari...
I know I've mentioned this before,
but I don't think you should tell
your mother about time traveling.
I think it will just worry her.
Yeah. You're right.
I see.
So there does appear to be
something in that laboratory.
Can you seize the building
for contract violation?
I'm home!
Welcome back!
It's almost time for dinner,
so wash your hands and get changed.
Okay.
I set it!
Oh!
Well, take this too, then.
What's wrong with that girl lately?
The voltic pile.
Invented by the Italian physicist,
Alessandro Volta.
Cloth soaked in brine is sandwiched between
many alternating plates of copper and zinc.
This results in continuous electric
generation not previously possible.
This invention contributed greatly to
future experiments requiring electricity,
and the understanding of electricity itself.
This is the history Papa
was trying to protect.
Mari! Dinnertime!
Oh! Okay!
A mille crepes!
That's right! Sit on down!
This is my latest offering.
Taste-test it for me after dinner, okay?
Okay!
It looks delicious!
I hope it is.
A mille crepes cake is just made of crepes,
but what you put between them
changes the flavor and texture substantially.
It's been a bit of trial and error.
A mille crepes is kind of
like the voltaic pile.
What?
Oh! It's the first battery ever invented.
He tried stacking up all kinds of materials,
and after lots of trial and error,
he figured it out.
Alessandro Volta?
You're becoming a lot like your papa.
I am?
Yes!
Long ago, he said the same thing.
It was as if he'd gone to see it himself.
He told me all about the invention
and the history of its discovery.
Thanks to that, I'll never
forget that Volta person.
Mama...
Is Papa really off on a research expedition?
Oh, nothing. It's nothing. Nothing.
Anyway, let's eat dinner!
Okay! Let's eat!
Let's eat!
This pasta is really delicious!
"Next Episode:
Disheartened Faraday"
Really delicious!
"Next Episode:
Disheartened Faraday"
"Mari and Waka's Quick Science"
Mari and Waka's Quick Science!
"Copper Plate
Zinc Plate
Cloth soaked in brine"
The voltic pile Mr. Volta first thought of
"Copper Plate
Zinc Plate
Cloth soaked in brine"
is made of layers of cloth soaked in brine,
"Copper Plate
Zinc Plate
Cloth soaked in brine"
sandwiched between many
plates of copper and zinc.
"Copper Plate
Zinc Plate
Cloth soaked in brine"
"Copper Plate Sulfuric Acid Zinc Plate"
He later refined it to use
plates of copper and zinc
"Copper Plate Sulfuric Acid Zinc Plate"
placed directly in dilute sulfuric acid.
That's our modern-day battery.
"Copper Plate Sulfuric Acid Zinc Plate"
By the way, do you know
about this experiment?
Um...
Electrolysis of water, right?
Right!
When you apply electricity to water,
it splits it into oxygen and hydrogen.
"Oxygen Hydrogen"
This became possible with the
creation of the voltaic battery.
And if the hydrogen and
oxygen created this way
are locked in a tube and ignited...
It glows!
Is it cloudy inside that tube?
It's because the explosion
of the chemical combination
"Water vapor
H H
O" "Chemical Bonding Ignition" "H H O"
between the hydrogen and oxygen inside
"Water vapor
H H
O" "Chemical Bonding Ignition" "H H O"
creates water vapor within the tube.
"Water vapor
H H
O" "Chemical Bonding Ignition" "H H O"
"Water vapor
H H
O" "Chemical Bonding Ignition" "H H O"
It's believed that electricity
is generated at this time.
"Water vapor
H H
O" "Chemical Bonding Ignition" "H H O"
It's believed that electricity
is generated at this time.
"Electric Energy"
I know that one!
That's a fuel cell, right?
"Electric Energy"
"Fuel Cells are the Energy of the Future"
Right!
Fuel cells are being explored as
a next-generation energy source.
"Fuel Cells are the Energy of the Future"
They were created by thinking
backward from water electrolysis.
"Fuel Cells are the Energy of the Future"
The invention of the voltaic battery
led to the discovery of water electrolysis,
"Fuel Cells are the Energy of the Future"
which led to modern fuel cells!
Wow! Mr. Volta is amazing!
"Fuel Cells are the Energy of the Future"