I put on the armillary compass
I found in the laboratory basement,
which sent me back to
19th century London with Mari.
You've got to be kidding me!
This is the worst possible time,
when I'm still fighting with Futa!
There, we met the scientist, Mr. Faraday.
And then he used his electromagnetic...
um... rotation device...
for an experiment that proved a relationship
between electricity and magnetism.
But Mr. Farraday's patron, Sir Davy,
said this about his results...
These experimental results and your thesis
are both stolen from our research!
Wait, sir!
Things were looking real bad, but...
Sir...
Something happened, so I couldn't
even worry about that!
Where's Mari?
"Episode 6
Faraday's Resolve"
No... I don't like this...
I can't go home... I can't go home!
Go on, drink this. It'll warm you up.
As I understand it, when Mari
would go back into the past,
she would return naturally after a
certain amount of time had passed.
You came here this time
under the same circumstances.
Yet Mari returned to her own time
without you. Right?
Waka?
Hey, it's okay. When a
scientific experiment fails,
or presents a phenomenon
you've never seen before,
there's always a reason for it.
If we can figure out a reason...
Shut up!
What would you understand?
Science is all you talk about.
Look at the situation
your "science" has put me in!
I can't take this!
Let me go home! Send me home!
Waka! Calm down!
Let me go home!
It's no use. I can't find a single clue
about how to bring Waka back.
Shun! Awful news!
What's wrong?
She's panicking...
I'm sorry...
Mari...
I... I left Waka behind.
If I had only told her the way to get back...
I'm sure we'll find a way.
Waka...
Breach of contract? My husband?
Yes. I can't tell you all the details,
but Dr. Hayase may have
committed a severe breach
of the contract he signed with me.
Therefore, I want his laboratory opened
and a full delivery of all
his research materials to me.
His research materials?
What kind of contract did he sign?
There's no need for you to know that.
Just be quiet and comply with our request.
Request? This sounds more like a threat.
We don't mind taking this to the authorities.
Take it anywhere you want!
What was that?
Then I'll be able to have a good look at the
contract. I'll go through the whole thing.
Now, please leave.
I'm losing all my customers because of you.
This is obstruction of my business.
I apologize. We'll return later.
As apology for sending your customers away,
I'll buy a few things.
From here...
...to here.
No, thank you! I don't accept
such random purchases!
I work hard to make those
for people who love cake!
The layering in these mille-feuilles
was done with great care.
I can tell just from looking
how much time it took you.
This gâteau chocolat
has a hint of chocolat mon amour
from Dolce de Michelle in France, right?
They're very good cakes.
Thank you for your patronage.
Mr. Mikage... Are you sure about this?
She's a smart person.
Good morning!
Good morning! Have a good sleep?
Um... I...
I'm sorry to make a lady
sleep on the sofa,
but it was all I had.
I see.
I got tired from all the crying
and fell asleep.
Hold on. I can make breakfast.
Um...
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I... well... I took my anger out on you.
Don't sweat it!
Go on, wash up.
It wasn't just a nightmare...
Waka! It's done!
Wow! It looks delicious!
You haven't eaten since yesterday!
It's only natural.
Go on!
Th-Thanks.
First, eat a good meal.
You can worry about the rest after that.
Sure... Let's eat!
Delicious!
I'm glad.
I believe...
My brother's still back in my time.
Your brother?
Yes.
He's really smart and reliable.
Mari, too. She can be a scatterbrain,
but she really comes through when it counts.
Anyway, I trust them both.
I'm sure they'll find a way to help me.
I see!
I wonder how long it's been there...
I guess there's no way to get Waka back...
Waka must be feeling so lonely...
What's wrong?
I remember! Papa told me!
And when you get back,
tell Shun to press the triangle button
in the middle of the keyboard.
The triangle button?
Yeah! He said it would
teach you the system controls!
In the center?
This one?
Probably!
I was being careful not to touch things
when someone was in the past,
so as not to cause any trouble, but...
Would you like more tea?
Yes, please!
Faraday! Awful news!
What's wrong?
Sir Davy's been going around
everywhere since last night,
telling everyone you stole
his and Dr. Wollaston's research!
What?
I guess he didn't like that his apprentice
got results when he didn't.
Of course, we don't believe
you'd do something like that.
But it's been the talk of
the society all morning.
It's just a rumor... but it's possible
he may oppose your membership
in the Royal Institution.
Sir Davy has a lot of influence
with the Institution.
Yeah... And some people might use this
to curry favor with him.
Oh, no...
Wait, please! Sir Davy!
I swear, I didn't steal your research!
I got those results from my own experiment!
I will firmly denounce you
as a shameless fraud
who stole his patron's research.
Sir...
At this rate, you may be left unable to
take part in scientific study anywhere.
He wants to take science away from me?
Is that it?
Wait!
Please, wait!
W-Wait!
Please...
You were Faraday's...
His friend.
Please! Don't take science from him!
Did you come running after me to say that?
Pathetic.
He really does love science!
To take that from him... It's going too far.
He's getting what's coming to him.
You're a scientist too, aren't you?
Then... you know how painful it would be
to lose your scientific work, right?
Do not compare me to Faraday!
He can't even do math!
He hasn't had a day's proper education!
He can't do anything
except for running experiments over and over!
What's wrong with that?
What?
Getting results through constant experiments.
That's how he does science.
That's how he does the science he loves!
Losing yourself in something...
Losing yourself in just one thing...
What's wrong with that?
What's wrong with losing yourself
in what you love?
I'm back.
Mr. Faraday!
Where did he go?
How's it going, Shun?
Well, it says synchronization rate is 100%...
Brother? Mari?
Is that you, Mari? Can you hear me? Hey!
Waka!
I can hear you!
Hey, what's going on?
It's not on fast-forward anymore!
I see! The armillary compass and
the system have synchronized!
I'm so glad!
Waka! Listen close!
You know the knob
at the bottom of the compass?
Knob?
This?
Yeah, that!
If you turn that, you can come back here!
Really?
Yeah!
That's how I got back from Mr. Volta's time!
Thank goodness!
I thought I'd never make it home!
Now, now. Don't cry!
Waka, come back.
Okay!
What's wrong?
Hey... What's going to happen with
Mr. Faraday's discoveries and research?
To put it simply,
his discovery will be the basis
for the invention of the modern-day motor.
Motor?
Then cars and washing machines and stuff...
We owe them all to Mr. Faraday?
Yes. His influence won't stop
at the scientific world.
In a way, he's the man who laid
the foundation for all modern culture.
Waka?
Is it okay... if I stay here
a little bit longer?
Where are you, Mr. Faraday?
Mr. Faraday!
I've been searching everywhere!
Are you going to quit...
...quit science?
You can't quit. You can't!
What you're doing now will lead to some
very important inventions in the future.
In the future?
It's called a motor.
You invent that, and it
improves everybody's lives.
Motors have an incredible power...
the power to move things!
Waka...
You believe that science exists
to make people happy, right?
You love science, right?
Then you can't stop!
Come on now, Waka. Who said
I was going to give up on science?
What? But...
you'd cleaned up all your things...
And you were here, staring off
into the distance... so...
No, no!
I came up with a new experiment,
so I cleared off my desk
to make space for it!
Then why didn't you tell me that earlier?!
Sorry! Anyway, let's get started!
If running electricity
through the copper wire
can cause a magnet to rotate,
then thinking backwards from there,
you should be able to generate electricity
using copper wire and magnets, too.
Anything?
No reaction.
Let's run some electricity through it,
to make sure the galvanometer is working.
Working normally.
Okay, let's try it again!
No reaction.
Let's change the direction of the magnet.
What now?
Nothing.
What about now?
No reaction.
No use, huh?
It seems theoretically possible, but...
But not getting any result in an experiment
makes it a failure, right?
A failure? That's no big deal!
That means I get to try
an all-new experiment!
What should I change for the next experiment?
What result will come from it?
Just thinking about it gets me excited!
No matter how many times I fail,
no matter how hard it is,
I could never hate science!
Mr. Faraday...
So I'll never quit science, either.
Never!
I see.
Then I'll be going home.
Huh?
I see!
You found a way to get back, right?
Yeah!
Goodbye... Mr. Faraday.
Say hello to Mari. And your brother, too.
Okay!
Good luck!
Thank you, Waka.
Waka!
Mari!
Welcome back!
I'm so glad! I'm so glad!
So, so glad!
Thanks...
Welcome back.
Brother...
I'm sorry I worried you.
Did you do what you had to?
Yeah!
After conducting the electromagnetic
rotation experiment in 1821,
Faraday continued exploring the relationship
between magnetism and electricity
until 1831, when an experiment led him
to discover the Law of Induction,
which would later be
known as Faraday's Law.
The faster the lines
of magnetic force change,
and the more coils in the circuit,
the greater their induced current becomes.
That law became indispensable in
later thinking about generating electricity,
and became the cornerstone
of the study of electromagnetism.
Huh? This book...
Brother!
What's this?
What's wrong?
It didn't disappear.
Huh?
Morse. Bell.
No way!
Hertz. Edison.
Is it because we're
in control of the machine?
Or because our power source has switched
from a battery to a standard outlet?
I will not acknowledge it. I won't!
I will not acknowledge Faraday's assertion!
I'd advise you to stop, Sir Davy.
Is there something else you want?
Faraday will make enormous contributions
to the scientific world in the future.
And, Sir Davy,
your greatest contribution
will be discovering him.
You realize that, don't you?
"Intermediate English
Problems by Level"
What are you doing?
Wh-What do you want?
This isn't for club! I'm just taking a break!
I'm studying properly, I tell you!
It's upside-down.
I... I know that.
You won't accomplish anything by doing
such a half-baked job on everything.
What?
Next week is your match, right?
I got them to give you
permission to practice.
Huh?
But you have to get
80% or more on the next test.
That's the condition.
Where did this come from?
After practice, I'll teach you.
So get going, okay?
Futa.
What?
You're really good at soccer.
And... you love it.
So... you should aim
for the top... or something.
Huh?
Well, you know...
I'm telling you to work hard at soccer!
You know I will!
I'm going to the World Cup, no matter what!
And if I need it to get there...
...I've gotta work hard at studying,
too, even if I don't like it.
I know you'll make it, Futa.
Yeah!
Thanks, Mizuki.
Mr. Mikage.
You have a call from Mr. Sekota,
the research assistant you met with before.
Understood.
Yes? Mikage speaking.
You remembered something?
A book?
Magnets and Electricity...
"Next Episode: Morse's Inspiration"
"Mari and Waka's Quick Science"
Mari and Waka's Quick Science!
What was Mr. Faraday trying to accomplish?
Last time, he learned that changes in current
and magnetic field produce power, remember?
Yeah.
He was testing the opposite of that.
That the movement of a magnet
could generate electric current.
But it didn't work...
Later, he learned that by coiling copper wire
and running a magnet through it...
It worked!
Let's test it!
Wrap a coil around an acrylic tube,
pass a magnet through, and...
The needle moved!
"Structure of a Generator"
The truth is, when the magnet
gets close to the coil,
"Structure of a Generator"
it changes the magnetic field inside the coil
and causes electricity to flow.
"Structure of a Generator"
This principle became
the basis for the generator.
"Structure of a Generator"
This principle became
the basis for the generator.
When we rotate the handle of this
hand-cranked generator, attached to an LED...
So bright!
It turned on!
"Electric Current" "Power" "Magnetic Field"
There's a coil and a magnet
inside the generator.
"Electric Current" "Power" "Magnetic Field"
Huh? That looks like a motor.
Now, when we swap the LED for a battery...
The handle turned!
Which means the system is the same,
but the principle is reversed?
That's right!
Faraday invented the basic
principle behind the motor,
and from there, he arrived at
the principle behind the generator.
Thinking backwards
really can advance science, huh?