"Chiffon Cake"
"Cheesecake"
Did I wake you? I'm sorry.
Papa!
You'll catch a cold sleeping there, Mari.
I know. But I wanted to read
a little more of this book.
"Cheesecake"
I know. But I wanted to read
a little more of this book.
"Cheesecake"
I want to be like you and Mama.
I see.
Will I be able to, if I read lots of books?
Yes, you will.
Then you just have to think about
a lot of things and try them yourself.
Think?
Yes. Humans create what they imagine.
Imagine?
It means producing the things
you dream about.
Food and science are the same.
Papa...
"Episode 1
Gilbert the Sage"
It's so good!
It's got ricotta cheese in it
today, huh? It's so fluffy!
You got it! Your palate is
as impressive as ever, Mari.
Cake is so fluffy!
Now, now, Rika.
Being born a pâtissier's daughter
makes me happy as a clam!
Happy as a clam!
I wish Papa could have some of this, too.
He's like me. He gets so into
his work, he forgets to eat.
I wonder what he's off doing right now.
Aren't you worried, Mama?
The day after our wedding, I lost
contact with him for two weeks.
I was certainly worried then.
That's my papa...
But the lack of contact
is proof that he's doing okay.
Proof!
Okay, I'm off, Papa.
See you later!
"Incorporated Sekiei Academy
Aobadai Middle School"
Good morning!
Hey!
Waka! Good morning!
C-Come here!
Wh-What's going on, Waka?
What's with them?
What's going on, Waka? Some kind of secret?
Mari, you're good at cooking, right?
Y-Yeah...
Tomorrow is Futa's birthday.
What? It is?
Well, whatever. Yes, it is.
Anyway, he's in the soccer club, as you know.
I was thinking he might like a big,
round cake shaped like a soccer ball.
Wow, that sounds great!
But when I tried to make it...
It was too thick to cook
through properly, right?
I thought I'd had a great idea for once...
Then why not make a miniature version?
Absolutely not!
Waka Mizuki must do everything
boldly and grandly!
Even if it's just a cake
for a childhood friend!
I understand! I'll help!
I know we can make a great soccer ball cake!
Thank you! You know how to make one, right?
Oh... I don't.
What? Then how are we going to make it?
I don't know, but if we think it over,
I'm sure it'll work out.
Counter!
Really. Maybe I shouldn't have asked you.
Now, now. I'm told that most invention
only happens after a long series of failures.
That's not very convincing
coming from someone
who does trial-and-error answers for
tests we already know the questions for.
For instance, this.
It's about the way light reflects.
"Class 2-C, #20
Name: Mari Hayase"
For instance, this.
It's about the way light reflects.
"Class 2-C, #20
Name: Mari Hayase"
"How does your face look
reflected in the mirror?"
The answer:
"It looks cute!"
Where did that come from? The answer
is "with left and right switched."
Well...
It's hard to believe you're
the daughter of a world-class scientist.
By the way, is your father still away?
It's been three years.
But it seems taking aimless research trips
has been his thing for a while, and...
Even if I'm gone, don't worry.
This armillary compass
will always show you the way.
That's what he told me.
But three years is a long time.
Anyway, today's cake
won't take that long, at least.
I'll search the internet for how to make it,
so just follow the directions, okay?
Huh? Search the internet?
It's your idea! Let's think it over together!
We should use the
knowledge of our predecessors.
If everyone had to reinvent the wheel,
civilization would never advance.
But... But Waka...
Who's winning?
The next town over, I think?
But they sure can hit.
But you failed because you couldn't
find out the right way to do it, right?
Hey, Hayase! Mizuki!
It's Futa!
Futa!
Wh-What?
--Hey, Futa! You okay? Futa!
--Futa?
Coach! Ichikawa is... Coach!
Futa! Futa!
Ichikawa!
What wrong, Ichikawa?
Ichikawa! Hang in there!
Futa!
What happened?
--A ball hit him, and then...
--Futa...
Where did it hit him?
The chest.
Waka! Call an ambulance!
B-Brother?
Hey! Ichikawa! Ichikawa!
Don't move him.
Shun?
Calm down. An AED... do you have an AED?
An... AED?
I'll take over.
Okay. Please do.
Not good. He's in cardiac arrest.
One, two, three, four!
Five, six, seven, eight, nine!
I got it!
An electric shock is necessary.
Please move away.
There's going to be an electric shock.
Press the closed circuit button firmly.
I'm closing the circuit.
Checking status.
Futa!
Wait.
Further electric shock is not required.
Th-That hurt...
Futa!
M-Mizuki?
I'm so glad... I'm so glad!
You... Why are you crying?
Idiot! Forget it!
Waka! Futa, are you okay?
Why is she so mad at me?
Will he be okay, Brother?
Yeah, probably.
It caused a ventricular fibrillation, and
sent him into temporary cardiac arrest.
I see.
Shun, you're so reliable!
Well, I have cram school.
Take care on the way home, you two.
Okay!
He's so cool!
You can tell he's a future med student
at the top of his class!
You said it.
Well, let's get to making that cake!
Oh, yeah!
I'm borrowing your computer!
Are you sure it's okay to go
into Shun's room without asking?
Don't worry. I don't think he has
any dirty magazines or anything.
Wh-What are you talking about? Of course
Shun wouldn't have those things!
Are you so sure?
Well, even if he did, he'd
probably have them well-hidden.
Huh?
What's wrong?
This book. I've seen it in Papa's lab before.
Cake! Cake!
Huh? It's all in English?
William... Gilbert...?
Look at this, Mari!
This is the recipe I used yesterday...
But that one didn't go well at all.
Huh? H-Hey! Are you okay?
What on Earth?
Mari disappeared?
S-S-Someone! S-Someone call an ambulance!
Wh-What is this place?
But anyway... speak to me!
Hello? Hello?
She's just like Futa. What do I do?
Um... what was that machine called? Um...
Shun, help me!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
--eight, nine, ten!
--Dr. Gilbert! This way!
--One, two, three, four, five,
--Excuse me, everyone!
--six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
--Make way.
--One, two, three, four, five, six!
--You! What do you think you're doing?
Move. I'll take over.
O-Okay...
This man. Is he...
Miss. Miss!
Settle down. It's okay. I'm a doctor.
How are you feeling?
M-My head...
It looks like you hit it when you fell.
If it starts hurting very badly,
please come by my clinic.
I'm okay.
That girl came out of thin air,
and I was so startled...
I-I'm sorry! Um... I'm really sorry!
Waka!
Brother!
What happened? You called me so suddenly...
Mari... Mari suddenly disappeared!
What do you mean?
She was looking at that book...
then suddenly, her body started shining...
What should I do?
I understand. Anyway, try to calm down.
Okay...
"The Year 1600
(What is now) London, England"
I see. You're from the future, then?
Probably.
Interesting! A truly intriguing story.
Can you prove it?
Prove it? I don't know...
Here.
Thank you!
But is this really London in the year 1600?
Yes. That's right...
Forgive the late introduction.
I am William Gilbert.
I'm a doctor, as well as a scientist.
A scientist?
Yes. This world is full of mysteries.
And there's much that human
knowledge does not yet know.
I believe that bringing these things
to light and coming closer to the truth
will lead us to a brilliant future.
What delicious clotted cream!
This really is England!
But you do speak fluent English.
English?
If you really came from the future,
--you must have found the principle that
made it possible, and put it to use.
-- I'm not speaking English...
--you must have found the principle that
made it possible, and put it to use.
-- I'm not speaking English...
"English?"
"But I don't speak English"
"Isn't he speaking Japanese?"
It's Dr. Gilbert who's
speaking fluent Japanese.
"English?"
"But I don't speak English"
"Isn't he speaking Japanese?"
Humans can create whatever
they imagine, after all.
"English?"
"But I don't speak English"
"Isn't he speaking Japanese?"
Did you say "create whatever they imagine"?
Oh? Yes.
Y-You don't know a researcher
named Eiji Hayase, do you?
Brother! I think maybe
we should call the police.
No, if this book is the cause,
then Dr. Hayase's research may be involved.
My husband said he wanted
you to have it, Shun.
Dr. Hayase did?
Yes. He set out on
a research trip so suddenly.
But he wanted you to have that book.
"To Shun Mizuki"
"To Shun Mizuki.
I entrust this book to you
while I'm on my trip.
Keep it safe, and don't tell anyone about it
until you understand what it means.
Thank you. Eiji Hayase."
Brother?
What's wrong?
Anyway, we should go to
Dr. Hayase's laboratory.
Okay.
Hayase? Is he Japanese, then?
Yes.
I don't know if he's the doctor
you're speaking of,
but several months ago, I met a man
from the Orient who praised my research.
Where is he now?
I fear I don't know.
He came out of nowhere when I was at
the harbor hiring sailors for a job.
He mainly wanted a handshake, but...
I see...
But the words you said...
I'm sure he said them, too.
I thought it a perfect
phrase for a scientist.
What's the matter?
My father went missing three years ago.
The person you're talking about might be him.
Really?
Searching all alone in this
strange land for your father...
It must have been hard.
Thank you very much. I'm okay now.
Speaking of which, what research
are you doing, Dr. Gilbert?
Oh, that's right.
Right now, I'm experimenting to see
why a compass always points north.
I want to explain the mechanism
behind it and offer proof.
What? That's it?
I suppose that mystery has already
been solved in the future?
Mystery? But everybody knows that...
Really? Then please tell me!
Why does a compass needle point north?
Why?
Huh? Actually, why does it?
I've never even thought about it...
Hmm? Is something wrong?
Oh, no!
Now that I think about it,
I don't actually know.
I see. That's too bad.
I'm sorry.
Oh, it's nothing.
There are various theories on the matter.
For instance, this book says that
the needle is pulled by the North Star.
That's true! The North Star is
always in the northern sky...
But there's no proof of this theory.
Proof?
Yes. Without proof,
you cannot be sure it's true.
Some sailors believe that there's a huge
magnetic mountain on the North Pole.
But there's no solid proof of this, either.
I see...
Well? Why not help me with
my research while I'm here?
I can show you the way of thinking through
which the principles of nature are unlocked.
Okay! I will!
Okay. Then let's head out.
It's about time for them to come back.
What? Who are they?
You'll see when we get there.
Master?
To take her outside dressed like that...
Oh. Good point.
Do you have anything to put on her?
One moment, please.
"Hayase Research Laboratory"
How do we get inside?
It's somewhere around here...
There.
What?!
The doctor's very lazy.
He doesn't like carrying
a lot of things around with him.
But then why even bother having security?
No use? The lights inside
must have been shut off...
I can't breathe!
It's part of a lady's toilette!
Please try to bear it!
But still... if you draw it that tight...
I c-can't breathe...
But I can't believe you were walking
around in that obscene outfit.
In this country, any lady would be
embarrassed to show her legs like that.
Would she? Really?
Unbelievable!
Time out! Time out!
That should do it.
I nearly died...
Forgive the wait, Master.
Oh?
Oh, beautiful!
Now, shall we?
B-Brother! Look!
Is there something under here?
You're the one who used to
hang out here. Don't you know?
I never knew he had an underground room.
And it seems to be on a
different electrical system.
There must be a stairway to get down there...
Anyway, we can't do anything
unless we get down there.
Yes?
What? Lights on at Hayase's laboratory?
I see. Understood.
Find the doctor and take him
quickly into custody.
Let's have as little fuss as possible.
Finally back, are you, Eiji Hayase?
"Next Episode: Sorrowful Gilbert"
"Mari and Waka's Quick Science"
Mari and Waka's Quick Science!
Mari, you had trouble with Mr. Gilbert's
question before, didn't you?
Yeah, but...
But everybody knows that...
Really? Then please tell me!
Why does a compass needle point north?
Huh? Actually, why does it?
I never even thought about it...
Being a scientist means doubting things
believed to be common knowledge.
But what will Mr. Gilbert do next?
Waka? When did you get here?
I've been here the whole time!
Now, now. We'll find out what
Mr. Gilbert does next episode!
In the meantime,
let's have a little pre-study.
Have you ever seen this tool?
Never!
It looks kind of like a compass
stood up on its side...
Mari, excellent observation!
See? When you do this...
Ah! It is a compass!
I had a feeling that's what it was!
The principle is that a
compass turned on its side,
in other words, perpendicular to
the ground, is called a dip circle,
and it's a device for measuring the angle
between the horizon and the north pole.
But Doctor, what's it for?
Yeah!
That's what you'll find out next week!
Papa, is this segment just
a next episode preview?
Well, not exactly...