Regarding the Hayase laboratory...
We have identified a researcher we believe
was involved in his core research.
I see.
"Disheartened Faraday"
Thanks.
How did it go?
I'm banned from club activities for a week.
Banned from the club?!
In the meantime, I have to do these problems
"Intermediate English
Problems by Level"
In the meantime, I have to do these problems
"Intermediate English
Problems by Level"
and memorize all the
important vocab on the list.
It's nonsense! I'm out for a whole week!
Well, you did fail every
subject on your quiz...
Even Mari only failed one.
Stupid Hayase!
That traitor!
Sis, is your nose itchy?
I'm fine!
Catching a cold?
I don't think so...
It's more like someone's
spreading rumors about me.
Rumors?
Darn it...
I don't have time to study right now!
What are you talking about?
Hey, give that back!
We have a tournament next week!
Which is more important, school or soccer?
Soccer, duh!
Soccer's #1!
I'm exhausted. You don't
care about school at all?
Hey, I'm trying to become
a pro soccer player.
I don't need to study!
A pro soccer player?
What team are you gonna join?
I'll join a J1 team, of course.
Then I'll go overseas!
Italy or France, maybe.
You dummy!
If you want to join a foreign team,
you need to know how to
speak foreign languages!
English is the most basic of basics!
You can't even handle English,
but you want to go to Italy? France?
Don't make me laugh!
Th-Then... I'll just stick
with a Japanese team.
And when you go overseas for the
World Cup, what will you do then?!
Oh, I see! I know!
You're not interested in being a good enough
player to be chosen for the World Cup, right?
Then I guess it's only natural
that you suck at English.
Sh-Shut up!
You're only hurting yourself by not studying.
Studying should come first,
and soccer second!
What's wrong with losing
yourself in what you love?!
Futa!
November 7th, 1872.
The Mary Celeste departed
from New York, heading to Italy.
Then, on December 4th, it was discovered
adrift in the ocean near Portugal.
There was no sign of damage to the ship,
or of having being attacked by pirates.
But the eleven people on board,
including the captain's family, were gone.
No one knows what happened to them.
Shun! You're here!
Yeah.
What are you looking at?
Incidents of disappearances
all over the world.
Wow... You like that kind of stuff, Shun?
Not exactly.
I thought these incidents and legends
might have some connection
to Dr. Hayase's research.
That's all.
To Papa's research?
Yeah.
A man goes missing suddenly,
without explanation.
If it's actually because he traveled
through time or dimensions...
Traveled through time? You mean, like me?
Yes.
So if I investigate incidents of
possible time travel like these,
it's possible that I might learn
what the machine downstairs is, and why
Dr. Hayase gave you the armillary compass.
I think all this might be a message from him.
A message from Papa?
Gilbert. Franklin. Volta.
Why do these people appear in this book?
Why are you traveling into
the times they come from?
Mari!
Waka?
What's wrong?
Please! Send me into the past!
What?!
I don't mean the 16th or 18th centuries!
Just an hour or so ago!
What are you talking about?
I didn't mean to make Futa mad!
I was just worried about him!
And yet...
Oh, I'm so stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Calm down, Waka!
That's why... you have to send me back!
Let me meet myself before I talk to Futa,
so I can tell me to be nicer!
Please!
Huh?! Why do you have
that armillary compass?!
Oh, this?
Didn't I mention it?
I found it in the basement!
Why do you have it?
Well... with the way things were going...
It seemed like the right idea
at the time, I guess...
With the way things were going?
I'm a member of Team Time Travelers, too!
"Team Time Travelers"
I need an item of my own!
Team Time Travelers?!
W-W-We'll talk about that some other time!
Anyway, send me into the past!
Just an hour back!
Listen, Waka.
The system doesn't let us
go back whenever we want to.
We can only travel back to the eras
of the people in this book.
Lucky me!
Hey!
--Waka!
--Wait up!
God wants it to happen!
He wants me to go one hour into the past!
God, I will do as you ask of me!
Into the past... one hour ago!
Michael Faraday.
Lived from 1791 to 1867.
From the 19th century.
Huh?
I can't go that far back!
It's no use, Waka.
We can only go to the eras of the
people written about in that book.
Then find a page with Futa Ichikawa on it!
I don't think there's a page for Futa...
How do you know unless you look?!
What the heck?! They're all blank!
Don't be so reckless! You'll tear it!
Don't stop me, Mari!
I told you to stop!
They both... traveled?
"The Year 1821
(What is now) London, England"
Ow, ow...
Were you hurt, Waka?
I'm okay.
Where's Futa?
Where are we? The school?
I don't think so...
This is clearly another country...
Th-Then, you mean...
We're probably in 19th century London.
The era of Mr. Faraday from the book.
Huh?!
Wait! What are we going to do?!
Nineteenth-century London? In the
middle of the industrial revolution?!
It'll be fine!
When the time comes, we'll
return to our own time naturally.
I see...
And there's a way to get back
without having to wait.
There is?
Yeah!
Papa taught me before. See...
Excuse me, my ladies.
He's...
...a real hottie!
Not that! He's... you know!
Yeah, pretty old.
He's a hottie, but I'll pass.
No, Waka!
It's Mr. Faraday, the scientist!
Huh?
Oh!
You've heard of me? I'm delighted.
To hear you refer to me as a scientist...
Anyway, would you get down from there?
You never know when the owner
of that cart will come back.
Hey!
You two! What are you doing?!
Hey! Don't run away!
This way!
Darn it! What are you doing?!
We're sorry!
You mean Dr. Hayase didn't cancel
his research because it was a failure?
Yes.
On the contrary, it was nearing completion.
But one day, Dr. Hayase suddenly
declared he was stopping his research,
and closed his laboratory.
Yes. He gave me a high severance package
and even recommended me
to a new place of business.
But he urged me not to say
anything about our research.
What kind of system was it?
The matter transporter...
It was a mysterious device. You know?
Gambling is self-destructive.
You should play in moderation.
So, how was it mysterious?
Well, we managed to make an apple disappear.
But we couldn't send it
where we wanted it to go.
Oh?
But several minutes later, the apple
returned to where it had been.
And it was rotten.
Rotten?
After that, we stopped
the research for a while.
I don't know what happened after that.
I see. You've been a great help.
Thank you.
Take care.
Some kind of accident must have occurred
during the development
of the matter transporter.
Then someone resembling Hayase sent
a jade cup of Napoleon to an auction
to pay back his research funding.
It seems it is necessary to take
control of that laboratory.
Oh?
You came here from the future,
and you met Franklin,
who's even further in the past?
Yes!
You know the kite he used to prove
that lightning is electricity?
I made it!
How wonderful!
I wish I could have seen it!
Um...
Aren't you at all suspicious of our story?
Of course!
It sounds like an astounding dream!
But that just means science
has turned a dream into reality!
Science... turns dreams into reality?
I believe in the greatness of science.
The truth is, the other day, I had a
successful scientific experiment, too.
Today, I sent a thesis discussing
my results to a publishing company.
--This will change our understanding
--Hey, why can he speak fluent Japanese?
--of how electricity and magnetism relate.
--He's not. We're speaking
fluent English, apparently.
Huh? How?
I don't really get it...
Was that too complicated for you?
A picture is worth a thousand words.
Okay. I'll show it to you!
That's the Royal Institution.
It's my laboratory and my home.
Huh?
Sir Davy!
I'm sorry I went out.
Did you put together the report
I asked you for two days ago?
I'm sorry. I was almost done...
Were you occupied by some other experiment?
Yes.
Actually, about that...
You should just be doing what I tell you.
Yes, sir.
Sir!
If you wait a moment,
I'll put the report together.
Unfortunately, I'm going
to a play with my wife.
I don't have time.
Please turn it in first thing in the morning.
Yes, sir.
Ma'am...
It's been some time since we last spoke.
Who are those girls?
Oh. They're my friends.
They came here from far away.
I hope you'll be willing to hear them out...
What a vulgar display.
Uneducated men
often gather vulgar people around them.
Who was that? They were so mean.
That's Sir Davy, my patron, and his wife.
His wife has always disliked me.
Uneducated... Did she mean you?
That's what his wife calls me.
But you're a scientist, right?
It seems that a scientist who can't do math
is often the subject of great scorn.
Huh?
You can't do math?
Yeah.
But you're a scientist!
I come from a poor blacksmith family.
I never went to school.
But how is that possible?
How can you be a scientist without math?
Why do you say that?
Why do I...? Well...
Studying math is the most
basic of basics, right?
I don't know anything about math,
but I love science.
I can beat anyone for enthusiasm.
But... loving it isn't enough.
Because I love it, I can lose myself in it.
I can have a successful experiment
and get people to acknowledge me.
Science is all I have.
After all, even if I lack education,
I still have science.
Getting results in the field you love...
There's no greater joy than that.
Soccer, duh!
What's wrong with losing
yourself in what you love?!
I know!
I'll show you the experiment
I was talking about!
What's this?
I call it...
...an electromagnetic rotation device.
Electromagnetic rotation?
The wire rotates around the magnet.
Rotates?
Yeah!
Yes, without the power of wind or water,
with just the power of
electricity and magnets!
Electricity and magnets?
Last year, Professor Oersted of Denmark
discovered that electricity
had the power to move magnets.
When you bring a compass close
to an electrified copper wire...
...the electricity and the magnet
clearly interact.
Sir Davy and Dr. Wollaston
were experimenting to create
an electric motor based on that,
but it didn't work out.
So I decided to carry on their research!
Look at this!
If I put a compass here
and run electricity through it...
The needle moved!
Let's move it.
It moved!
I experimented with moving
the compass around,
and noticed a certain principle.
Well, what are the needles doing?
It's like they're surrounding the wire!
Yes! They don't all turn the same way.
They seem to surround it!
This is what I think--
If we pretend this bottle of ink is the wire,
when I run electricity through it,
it releases its power in a certain direction.
Its power?
In other words, magnetism.
Magnetism?
Now, attention, please!
Magnets and an electrified copper wire.
When their powers interact,
what phenomenon will we see?
Let's have a look!
It's moving!
Wow...
Do you see it?
See what?
The power emitted by the wire,
and the power of the magnet
interacting with it.
You're right!
I think I can see it!
Science is amazing!
The lightning rod reduced
damage caused by lightning.
And the voltaic pile...
What is it?
Sir Davy?
I stopped by the publisher,
and they showed me this!
This is...
...the thesis I submitted today.
You read it?
This is an outrage!
What?
This is one of the experiments
that Dr. Wollaston and I carried out
to devise an electric motor!
Y-Yes, sir.
But you stopped the experiment, so I...
When did I give you permission
to do experiments?
These experimental results and your thesis...
They're both stolen from our research!
Sir... Davy...
Hey!
Huh? The time limit's up already?
No way!
Now, of all times?
What do we do about them?
D-Don't ask me...
An overload?
You'll be dealt with in
an appropriate manner.
Be prepared!
Wait, sir!
Sir!
Sir...
Huh?
Where's Mari?
No way!
I'm back!
Mari? Where's Waka?
Huh?
No, no, no, no, no, no way!
I came back by myself?!
It must have something to do
with the system overload.
At this rate, Waka will...
Don't worry, Shun!
If she just turns the dial on the armillary
compass, she can come back here!
I see.
And Waka knows that, right?
I... I never told her...
Welcome...
Are you here for a cake?
Mari! Mari!
Waka!
Where did Mari go?
She went back... by herself.
Huh? Went back?
It can't be.
I don't like this! Help me!
Brother!
Mari!
"Faraday's Resolve"
"Mari and Waka's Quick Science"
Mari and Waka's Quick Science!
You got to see a real Faraday Motor?
I'm so envious!
Huh? That's a motor?
It's true that electricity
made it spin, but...
"Magnetic field"
"Electric current"
"Mercury" "Battery" "Power"
It's true that electricity
made it spin, but...
"Magnetic field"
"Electric current"
"Mercury" "Battery" "Power"
A Faraday Motor uses the relationship
between electric current and magnetic field
"Magnetic field"
"Electric current"
"Mercury" "Battery" "Power"
to generate power in a certain direction.
"Magnetic field"
"Electric current"
"Mercury" "Battery" "Power"
What kind of power?
"Magnetic field"
"Electric current"
"Mercury" "Battery" "Power"
Have you ever heard of a man named Fleming?
"Magnetic field"
"Electric current"
"Mercury" "Battery" "Power"
I know that one!
"Magnetic field"
"Electric current"
"Mercury" "Battery" "Power"
Fleming's left-hand rule, right?
"Fleming's left-hand rule"
"Power" "Magnetic Field" "Electric current"
Fleming's left-hand rule, right?
"Fleming's left-hand rule"
"Power" "Magnetic Field" "Electric current"
Fleming gave us an easy way to understand
the movement created by the relationship
"Fleming's left-hand rule"
"Power" "Magnetic Field" "Electric current"
between electric current
and the magnetic field.
"Fleming's left-hand rule"
"Power" "Magnetic Field" "Electric current"
What's that?
Place a magnet between two long metal rods.
Then place a short metal rod on top
and run electricity through them...
The rod moved!
The electricity is passing through
the short rod to the right,
"Electric current"
The electricity is passing through
the short rod to the right,
"Electric current"
and the magnet's field is pushing upward,
"Magnetic field"
"Electric current"
which produces the power
to move the rod forward.
"Electric current"
"Power"
"Magnetic Field"
which produces the power
to move the rod forward.
"Electric current"
"Power"
"Magnetic Field"
Wow!
"Electric current"
"Power"
"Magnetic Field"
Just like Fleming's left-hand rule says!
"Electric current"
"Power"
"Magnetic Field"
This setup is used in the motors
of many different machines.
"Electric current"
"Power"
"Magnetic Field"
And the vehicle that uses it the most is...
...the maglev train!
Yes! A next generation vehicle
that moves at over 600 km/h!
It's much faster than high-speed rail!