"The Year 1879
(What is now) Menlo Park, America"
What's happening?
"The Year 1879
(What is now) Menlo Park, America"
What's happening?
The weather was so nice earlier...
Focus already!
R-Right.
A thread of cotton treated
with soot for a filament.
It'll work.
Sir, it came from the warehouse.
What are those idiots doing?!
Can it be... This is...
What is that?
I don't know!
"Episode 12
Cherished Scientists"
I don't know!
But it could be a fissure in space-time!
"Episode 12
Cherished Scientists"
But it could be a fissure in space-time!
A-- A fissure in space-time?
Mari, grab on to the ladder!
Papa!
I'll be fine! You stay still!
But Papa!
Papa!
Brother, what's happening?
I don't know.
It could be a time paradox variation.
What does that mean?
I don't know all the details.
It's when something causes
a disturbance in space and time.
What kind of thing?!
I don't know!
Mr. Mikage...
Papa!
It's no use. I can't control it!
You can't bring them back?!
What if they're dragged into that thing?
They could be thrown to
the far edge of space-time.
Papa!
Mari! Can you hear me, Mari?
Waka?
Use the compass to get back here right now!
There's an abnormality in the system.
We can't bring you back from our end.
Is that Shun? What's going on?
The TSS is out of control.
Mr. Mikage...
Is there a way to get back using this?
Tell me!
How can we get out of here?
What?
Of course! This is the cause!
Mari!
You said the third armillary compass
was on the floor of the laboratory?
Yeah!
There were only two armillary
compasses at the start.
You have one. And the other...
What do you mean?
These two armillary compasses are the same!
Two copies of the same thing can't exist
in the same place at the same time!
Oh no!
Shut off the power!
No!
If I did that, they'd be lost forever!
Just shut off the power for now.
We'll fix that and then restart the program!
Restart it? How?!
There's no guarantee that we'll be
able to do that without a compass!
The system's going to catch fire!
You just want to let that happen?!
Stop it!
What are you doing?!
Let me go!
No!
Mari! Eiji! Come back quickly!
You said this is the cause since two
of it exist in the same place and time?
Then I'll return it to the 21st century.
At this rate, you, I, and
your daughter will all die!
Mari! Head back before me!
What about you? I won't go without you!
Papa!
Damn you!
Tell me!
You won't do it?
Stop it! Stop it!
How do I get back to the 21st century?
Mari, don't tell him!
I see.
--In that case...
--Mikage... damn you!
The dial! Turn the dial on
the bottom of the compass!
Mari!
The dial?
That's how you get back!
Nothing's happening!
Oh no!
I can't get back?
Shun, what's wrong?!
Brother?
The link's been severed.
I warned you!
You mean it's broken?
Then... Mari and Eiji are...
Mr. Mikage...
They can't come back?
Mari! Eiji!
Mari!
It's no use! I'm going to be sucked in!
Hayase!
You said the problem was having
two of these in one place?
Papa!
Then if one of them disappears...
You...!
L-Let go!
Papa!
What curious weather...
I told you to focus!
S-Sorry.
It died down.
Papa!
Are you okay?
Yeah, I think so.
Ow...
Is that how the armillary compass
ended up on the floor in the basement?
The compass that got sucked in
got sent to the floor of the basement?
Is that it?
Yes, most likely.
--Eiji?
--What?
The system re-established
the link automatically!
An overload!
I told you to shut off the power!
Shun!
Idiot! We'll burn to death!
This is ridiculous!
Burn to death here if you like.
I'm out of here!
Ms. Kuroki, let's run away!
I can't abandon Mr. Mikage!
B-But...
H-Hey! You two!
Wait!
Shun, Waka, you run, too.
No.
You've done enough, right?
Untie us already!
Can you stand, Papa?
Yes.
Hand it over...
The compass.
Hand it over.
Turning the dial won't get you back.
We don't know that yet.
If they do regain control of the system,
I'll need a compass to do anything.
I refuse.
A man like you wouldn't
use it for anything good.
What would you use it for, then?
Taking an educational trip
through the history of science?
What nonsense.
No matter what amazing invention you invent,
if you don't use it...
if you don't make use of it...
...it means nothing.
That so-called joy of discovery
that you scientists feel
is nothing but self-gratification.
Without men like me in the world,
your discoveries and inventions mean nothing.
They're treasures going to rot.
The joy of invention is nothing
but crude sentimentalism.
Shut up!
Invention and discoveries mean nothing?
Give me a break!
What would you understand?
Mari...
The scientists I've met have
gone through so many failures.
They've failed over and over again.
But they keep trying, again and again!
Science is interesting, isn't it?
The more you think,
the more you investigate,
the closer you come to the truth.
Well done is better than well said!
The future... it's like a fantasy.
Science is amazing!
Mari... Thanks to you, I feel like I've been
able to see something I couldn't see before.
Thank you.
There are many interesting
things in this world!
Please do your best.
Electromagnetic waves...
My research did this?
But even if I fail 1,000 times,
I'll keep going until I succeed.
They all believed in science,
and their own dreams!
Yes!
Please!
We create what we imagine.
That's what's so great about science!
Someone discovers something,
someone else picks up on that,
and it expands into more and
more discoveries and inventions!
Someone like you, who just uses
things other people made...
I won't let you insult them!
What?
We can get back?
W-Wait!
I see. So that's how it ends?
For a man who wanted to make
money off the matter transporter
to be tripped by an invention
used for making money...
Mari! Eiji!
Mari! I'm so glad!
Waka!
Eiji!
Akira! What's going on?
Mr. Mikage... Where's Mr. Mikage?!
I'm sorry.
It won't hold out any longer.
Get to safety, everyone!
No! Return Mr. Mikage right now!
I can't.
Give it up. It's too late!
Now, you two, come along!
Okay!
Mr. Mikage... Mr. Mikage!
Mr. Mikage!
Hurry!
A fire?! What about
Mr. Mikage and Ms. Kuroki?
They're still in the basement.
Along with the doctor's wife
and his daughter's friend.
Wait!
Hey! Wait up!
Mizuki! Mizuki!
Hayase!
Futa?
Hayase! Where's Mizuki?
Oh no... She was right behind me.
Futa!
What's wrong?!
Papa... Waka's still down there!
What?!
Waka!
Mizuki! Where are you, Mizuki?
Mizuki!
Mizuki, hang in there!
Futa...
Waka! Hey, Waka!
Waka!
Hurry up and go!
Right!
So Sekota was working with Mikage...
It all burned down, huh?
This is for the best.
What?
It is.
Mari.
Waka!
Are you feeling better?
Yes.
I got some rest in the back
of the ambulance. I'm fine.
I'm so glad! I was so worried!
I went back for the book,
and I breathed in some smoke.
Sheesh! What would you
have done without me?
Y-Y-You...
Thanks.
Futa, you're all red.
Okay, I'm glad we're all safe!
We are not!
Mama!
What are you doing?!
This was all your fault from the beginning!
Three years without a single call...
And you stole a cup from Napoleon?!
Well...
That wasn't stolen. It was a gift--
Shut up!
You are always so...
Sorry.
Welcome back.
Mama...
Thanks.
What's going on here?
What are you doing?
Hey... You okay?
It... It shouldn't have been this way.
I-I failed...
How could I have failed like...
What a failure...
Failure is an ingredient
for success, you know?
You know...
I need to explain to the investors how
the incandescent light project is going.
And they are getting a bit edgy after
waiting for more than a year with no results.
Remember, I built this
company on your advice.
Opportunity...
What?
It is when things go wrong
that there is a chance for opportunity.
You have a good point there!
Thank you very much.
Teacher, bye-bye!
See you tomorrow!
Mama...
Really, you're just too irresponsible.
I'm very sorry.
Now, now.
Mama! Sis!
Papa!
My, you've gotten big!
You all came to pick me up!
Yeah, we all came to pick you up.
Yeah!
Hey, Papa. What was that book, anyway?
Good question.
Maybe it was a magical book.
From the far-distant future.
Magical? Try to be a little more realistic.
All science and invention is like
fantasy to the people of the past.
The scientists tried to give form to things
that existed solely in their imaginations,
with unwavering hard work and passion.
Some day, someone will discover
the principle behind TSS
and put it into practical use.
Yes, most likely.
You read the entire book, right?
Yes.
I see...
Then you know what will happen
when it is put into practical use, too?
Even so, I will do it.
Even if it seems like that will
put things in the wrong direction...
...Mari will be there.
You can have this.
I don't need it anymore.
In 1910, when Edison
invented the toaster,
he used the press to publish the idea,
"Two meals a day is unhealthy.
We should all eat three meals a day."
From this, the practice of three
meals a day quickly spread,
and became entrenched.
And at the same time,
sales of the toaster rapidly spread.
He wasn't just an inventor,
he was also an
excellent businessman.
He was also an
excellent businessman, huh?
Mr. Gilbert, Mr. Franklin,
Mr. Volta, Mr. Faraday,
Mr. Morse, Mr. Bell,
Mr. Hertz, Mr. Edison...
I'm going to work hard, too.
Believing that someday,
I can create what I imagine.
Wow! The needle's spinning!
This was the principle on
which the motor was based.
Isn't science interesting?
Yeah!
When I grow up, I'm going to be
a scientist like you, Grandma!
I see. In that case...
...this is for you.
What? But isn't that
your treasure, Grandma?
Are you sure?
Yes.
You see...
This is a good luck charm for those
who wish to become scientists.
Thanks!
Wh-What is this?
What's wrong?
Well, um...
I can't find a book.
It was supposed to be here.
A book?
Yes.
It was about the history of inventions
that involve electricity and magnetism.
In its place, I found this...
I see!
Someone might be playing a prank.
I'll investigate right away.
No, it's all right.
That book has flown
away to guide someone.
Flown away to guide someone?
Yes.
To a girl... in the age of creating
what you imagine, right?
"Mari and Waka's Quick Science"
Mari and Waka's Quick Science!
This is the toaster that Edison invented!
It looks so fancy!
Huh?
It flipped out!
That's right.
It was simple, but it was made
to bake both sides properly.
How convenient!
And here's a percolator for making
coffee in a matching design.
It was sold with cups and sugar tins, too.
He made it part of a series!
And fans, and heaters...
...irons, curling irons...
...sewing machines... he continually
created new household electronics
to bring us an era of luxurious
lives through electricity.
Wow!
He really had it all coordinated!
All I knew about Edison's
inventions were the light bulb,
the phonograph, the copier,
and a few other things.
But he really invented so much, didn't he?
What was amazing about him is that,
for instance, when inventing the light bulb,
he also invented the socket,
the outlet, and the plug.
He always created
supplements to his inventions.
And many of those remain the same today.
Then this socket is Mr. Edison's invention?
Yes, that's right.
He made all kinds of things
he imagined practical!
Yes.
"Create what you imagine!"
He really did create what he imagined!
Yes! I'm gonna imagine things, too!
"Create what you imagine!"