Mari, where do you think you're going?
You promised you'd be
quiet at home for a while.
I... I know I did, but...
How's your summer homework going?
I'm working on it!
I just have my reading essay
and free research assignment,
and half of my English and
Japanese work, and my art poster left!
That's a lot.
But I still have lots of summer vacation!
And I really am worried about Papa!
I'm sure he's fine. He seemed entirely well.
But that was him from three years ago,
and he hasn't been back since!
What if something happened
to him in the world of the past?
Even so, that's no reason for you
to throw yourself into danger.
Then you're not going to do anything at all?
I'll worry about Papa.
So no more dangerous--
Hello?
Oh, yes.
What?
What does that mean?
Wait! Hello? Hello?!
Mari, watch the house.
"Episode 10
Hertz's Pride"
Mr. Mikage...
I searched around like you asked,
but I couldn't find anything that
looked like the matter transporter.
That can't be!
What is all this?
Why don't we ask someone directly involved?
Out of the way!
What are you people doing here?
Forgive me for calling her
without asking you.
You do work fast.
I appreciate it.
Mr. Mikage, what is the meaning of this?
We just came here to retrieve that
which our company's funds have paid for.
You know where it is, right?
I do not.
Then I have no choice.
Okay, all done!
English done. Japanese done.
Essay done. Free research project done.
Art poster done!
All homework done!
Waka, open up!
D'oh!
H-How did you get in here?
Well, you wouldn't answer your phone.
Oh, sorry. I turned it off.
So this was the only way I could
get here without your mom seeing me.
What do you mean?
I didn't tell Mama I was coming!
Well, I'm really worried about Papa!
That's no reason to come without asking...
You only just got out of a really
dangerous situation, remember?
I was really scared, yeah...
Huh? Shun? Shun!
No way!
But Papa might be going through
the same thing right now.
If Papa wants to come back and can't,
then I want to save him like Shun saved me.
Mari...
So first, I have to find the Papa
from three years ago.
But...
Please, Waka!
Lend me that book!
Oh, I guess I don't have a choice.
Thank you, Waka!
Huh? It was just right here...
Leave it to me.
My brother always hides
his important stuff here.
This is the next person.
Heinrich Hertz?
Oh, the EM guy.
EM?
Waka!
Oh no!
It's Mom!
Waka, are you there?
Yes! What is it?
Mari, hurry!
What? What's going on?
Oh, well... it sure is windy today, huh?
Are you okay?
Y-Yeah...
Hey, Waka... Did something happen
to Mr. Hayase's laboratory?
Huh?
There's a policeman there
forbidding anyone to enter.
What's going on?
"The Year 1893
(What is now) Bonn, Germany"
There!
I'm glad I wasn't in the water this time.
But where am I?
I know! There's a lot you want to ask, right?
But just wait a minute.
Let me put on my shoes...
Are you...
...Dr. Hayase's daughter?
Y-Yes!
I thought so.
But you're older than I was expecting.
Um, that's...
Yes, my family.
No, I mean, the color...
Professor!
Shall I turn on the transmitter?
Y-Yes.
Then I will proceed.
Oh!
My!
Getting to see the famous electromagnetic
wave experiment with my own eyes...
Thank you, Mr. Hertz!
Really, it's just a proof of concept.
And lately, I've been more focused
on cathode ray experiments.
Cathode rays?
What? Yes...
Mr. Hertz, you should cut back
on those experiments.
What?
I can't tell you to stop them entirely,
but just conduct fewer of them,
or keep your distance
from the cathode rays.
Just who are you?
Well, it's just, the effect
cathode rays have on the body...
Their effect on the body?
What are you talking about?
Mr. Lenard...
He warned me that day, and yet...
So Papa is here?
Yes, he came twice to my laboratory.
But what are you doing here?
I'm searching for Papa!
Searching?
Yes.
Do you know where he might have gone?
Dr. Hayase, you mean?
Yes...
If he's anywhere,
it might be the university.
University?
Bonn University, where I work.
He's always...
A-Are you okay?
I'm fine... Fine...
Papa!
Johanna...
Thank you for coming.
Hey, look at this!
What's this?
It might fix your cough!
I see. Thank you.
Who's that?
Oh, um, I'm...
The daughter of a friend of mine.
I'm Johanna!
Hello, I'm Mari.
Darling!
Reading is all well and good,
but it's time to get ready
to leave the hospital.
You're not going to go home
in your robe, are you?
Good point. I'll get ready right away.
By the way, Elisabeth...
Could we stop by the university
before we head home?
This girl is looking for her father.
Thank you!
There's a policeman at the front.
I don't think we can get inside.
That's awful... Where's Mari?
Huh? Um... Well...
She's in the past right now...
The past? What do you mean?!
Well, see...
She was in so much danger last time...
B-But she was really worried
about her father...
The fact that she was in danger before
made her want to help him even more.
Honestly...
Anyway, wait until I get there.
I'll be there soon.
Okay.
Waka? What's wrong? Waka?
Hello? Hello?!
Professor! You're out of the hospital?
Yes, I was just discharged.
By the way, has Dr. Hayase been in recently?
Yes... he was here this morning.
Oh? S-So...
Who is this girl?
She's the doctor's daughter.
Since you were off today,
he said he'd visit you at your house.
I see.
Let's wait for him at my house then, Mari.
Okay! Thank you.
Darling!
Is Johanna here?
There it is!
Mama?
Are you okay?
Darling...
I'm fine. You should find Johanna.
But the university is so big.
It might fix your cough!
The plant diagrams...
The garden?
There is a botanical garden
on the grounds. Could it be...
Mama!
Mama?
Johanna!
What are you doing here?!
Mama...
Do you know how worried we were about you?
Well... But...
No matter what happens,
you can't just run off.
But... But...
I wanted to make Papa feel better.
I know. I know.
I wanna help, too!
This is my job!
No! I wanna stir!
The cake's done! Mathilde, help me!
Okay!
Mama, is this okay?
Yes, it is. Thank you.
This should be very easy for Papa to eat.
Anyway, Mathilde...
Would you put the fruit topping on?
Okay!
Smells so good!
Yes!
Now I need to prepare
the herbal tea, and we're done.
What kind of herbal tea?
Chamomile and marigold.
I hear it's good for a cough.
No!
You need to put them on
more neatly! It's all messed up!
This is my job!
Give it to me!
--No! I'm doing it!
--Stop it!
Papa, I helped with the cake and the soup!
I'm so proud, Johanna.
I made the cake!
Yes, I'm proud of you too, Mathilde.
I made this soup with the
Plantago asiatica Johanna found.
Papa, eat it!
Thank you, I will.
It's just delicious, Johanna.
I'm glad!
Yes, it truly is delicious.
You two eat, too.
Okay!
Thank you for the food!
I'm full, so I think I'll go lie down.
You're leaving already?
I'll have more soup tomorrow.
Okay! Got it!
Oh, I need to lay out Papa's robe.
Eat up, okay?
Okay!
Darling...!
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize. You haven't
done anything wrong.
Perhaps this is what I deserve.
Don't be foolish.
Heinrich, I'm so proud of you.
Elisabeth...
But my research... what good will it do?
I'll get it!
Mari!
Papa! I'm so glad! I found you!
Y-Yes.
There's something I wanted
to let Mr. Hertz know.
What is it?
Excuse me.
Please come in.
You want to talk to my husband, don't you?
Thank you.
I'll let my husband know.
So would you please wait a moment?
Of course.
Listen, Papa.
After we parted ways at Mr. Bell's place,
the armillary compass malfunctioned,
and I almost didn't get back.
So I thought the same thing might have
happened to you, and you can't get back.
Hey... After we get back,
would you promise not to time travel again?
Mama's really worried, too.
R-Right.
I'm so glad! Then let's go back together!
I can't do that.
What?
Mari, do you know what Mr. Hertz discovered?
No...
What was it?
Electromagnetic waves.
The electromagnetic wave experiments he did
will later lead to the invention
of wireless broadcasts.
But he dies without ever knowing
the value of his work.
That's why I want to let him know.
Let him know what?
I want to use this to show him
the wonders of wireless transmission.
In other words, the wonders
of what he created.
But won't that change history?
It won't change history.
I'm just going to let him know.
And he's not long for this world.
His research is important.
I want him to know that.
Papa...
But my research... what good will it do?
Got it. I'll help, too.
Excuse me.
What's the matter?
You're from the future?
I'm sure you won't believe me right away,
but I feel like it's faster
to show you than to explain.
Could I take a photo?
A photo?
Go on, smile!
I'm taking the photo!
That's a good photo.
Th-This is...
Don't get too shocked just yet.
The real show is coming up.
I'm going to send this photo
to the next room.
Send it?
I'm using wireless transmission.
Wireless...
I'm going to stay right here.
But you can see the picture I
just took in the next room over.
The picture he took was sent to me!
This is...
Oh!
The electromagnetic waves
sent it from that room to this one.
This is something that
your research created.
Electromagnetic waves...
My research did this?
Yes.
Won't you believe me?
I believe you.
We believe in you.
So you should believe in
your work too, darling.
Believe in it!
Yeah!
My research... It's really...
Elisabeth, Johanna, Mathilde... Thank you.
Mari, I can't go back with you yet.
But I promise I will return to you.
So believe and wait for me.
Papa...
Now, go on ahead of me.
Now I'll return, too. Goodbye, Mr. Hertz.
Thank you.
Mari!
Welcome back from
the other side of space-time,
Mari.
Why?
Your mama's out late.
"Next Episode: Edison's Resilience"
She's late.
"Mari and Waka's Quick Science"
Mari and Waka's Quick Science!
Then I will proceed.
Getting to see the famous electromagnetic
wave experiment with my own eyes...
Really, it's just a proof of concept.
What was Mr. Hertz's experiment?
He was proving the existence
of electromagnetic waves!
Electromagnetic waves?
Waves created by electricity
and magnetism, right?
Right.
He theorized their existence based on the
equation of a physicist named Maxwell,
and proved that electromagnetic waves
move through space and expand.
Through space?!
Electromagnetic waves are generated
when electricity is flowing.
Then every other experiment before that...
Of course, they produced
electromagnetic waves.
People just didn't realize it.
Wow!
"The Types of Electromagnetic Waves"
"Radio Waves"
"Light" "X-Rays/Gamma Rays"
Depending on their wavelength,
electromagnetic waves
"The Types of Electromagnetic Waves"
"Radio Waves"
"Light" "X-Rays/Gamma Rays"
can be radio waves, light,
or X-rays or gamma rays.
"The Types of Electromagnetic Waves"
"Radio Waves"
"Light" "X-Rays/Gamma Rays"
Wow, light is an electromagnetic wave, too?
"The Types of Electromagnetic Waves"
"Radio Waves"
"Light" "X-Rays/Gamma Rays"
Yes!
"The Types of Electromagnetic Waves"
"Radio Waves"
"Light" "X-Rays/Gamma Rays"
Light is just electromagnetic waves
on the visible spectrum!
"The Types of Electromagnetic Waves"
"Radio Waves"
"Light" "X-Rays/Gamma Rays"
Electromagnetic waves are
used in TV and cell phones,
and X-rays are used for
many medical procedures.
Wow!
And what are they measured in,
as credit for the great accomplishment?
Hertz!
"Hertz"