I see.
You wish to withdraw your investment
in the research in question?
I heard a strange rumor recently--
that Dr. Hayase has gone missing.
Missing?
What's going on with his matter transporter?
It's proceeding apace.
But we haven't had any progress reports.
This violates our contract.
You'll just have to trust me, I suppose.
Very well. I'll wait a bit longer.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Yamamuro is leaving.
Regarding the Hayase laboratory,
we have identified a researcher we
believe was involved in his core research.
I see.
"Episode 3
Franklin's Spirit of Defiance"
"Well done is better than well said."
"Supplementary Lesson"
This was famously said by Benjamin Franklin.
Hayase, can you translate it?
Huh?
Um, give me just a minute!
Get your supplementary lesson done ASAP!
We're meeting at the lab
to continue our search!
I can't do this "ASAP"!
I hate English!
Hmm. It seems to be
taking you some time, Hayase.
Okay. Ichikawa?
It means that actions
speak louder than words!
That answer is correct, but...
Um, this is just...
This is not fair.
"This is not fair."
Well, I think it's best to get your
language translated in real time.
Real time translation?
You do speak fluent English.
But that's no reason not to study.
I'm confiscating this.
W-Wait, Mr. Sato! Wait!
You can't just go straight to the red card!
Mrs. Mizuki! You're home already?
Listen to this!
Ugh, Mom's home already?!
I'm late! I'm late! I'm super late!
Huh? Mari?
Shun?
You're coming too, Mari?
Yeah.
Good day!
Welcome to our tea party.
W-Waka?
What do you think? Does it suit me?
You called us here for this?
Wow!
That's amazing, Waka!
That dress looks so good on you!
Thank you!
And these madelines and
biscottis look really good!
But the cute tea set is the best part!
Isn't that Mom's antique tea set?
Erk! Wh-What do you mean?
I just saw it looking lonely
in the back of the cupboard,
and decided to help the poor thing.
That's my Waka!
I bet the tea set must be so happy!
I hear good actions are the best!
Wh-Who said that?
It's something we learned in
our supplementary lesson today.
Oh, that's right. My notes!
Huh?
Where are my notes?
You can't find them?
Here?
As I thought, it's blank.
What kind of notes are these?
I can't read them!
Huh? They're totally readable!
Not readable!
Readable!
It's readable!
See? Shun says they're readable!
B-Big brother?
The basement room?
Shun...
Brother...
What is this?
Wow!
What is it?
But why did it open now?
It could be related to Mari's pendant.
What? My pendant?
Yes. The mechanism started spinning, right?
I think it's still spinning.
That reminds me... when I traveled
back to Mr. Gilbert's era,
it did the same thing.
What is that pendant?
I got it from my dad.
From the doctor?
Anyway, if the book's readable now,
the answer must be in there, right?
But only the first part is readable.
Huh? How come?
I don't know. But I can
read the Gilbert page.
Last time, I was flipping
through this part...
Nothing happened.
That's right.
He's the guy from our lesson today!
Mari?
Mari!
"The Year 1752
(What is Now) Philadelphia, America"
Hey, Peter, why the long face?
You're offending the girls.
How can you stand it, Doctor?
Stand what?
The way the church is acting!
Exactly how would installing a
lightning rod be an affront to God?
The church is the tallest building in town.
If they hadn't refused to install it,
we could have avoided some of
the damage from the lightning!
I guess they just don't trust me.
How can you say that?
You're a fantastic scientist!
And an amazing statesman, too!
Oh, you flatter me!
Look, listen to me!
That sounded close...
Mari?!
Brother... look!
Mari?
What's going on?
Are you okay?
Wh-Who are you?
Huh? M-Me?
I'm John.
John?
Um... who are you?
I'm Mari.
Hey, where am I?
Huh? The master's laboratory.
Master?
Yeah, Dr. Benjamin Franklin. Do you know him?
Benjamin Franklin?
I see... I'm back in time again.
John! Sorry I'm late!
Wow, it's really coming down out there.
Master!
Master?
I've discovered a beautiful girl!
A pleasure to meet you.
I am Benjamin Franklin.
Huh? You?!
What's wrong? Dazzled by my good looks?
That's not it!
No need to be shy!
I'm not shy!
Well, maybe I'll show you
an interesting experiment
that'll unravel your heart a bit.
Are you even listening to me?!
Sure!
But I'm getting ready for an experiment,
so your confession of love
will have to wait for later.
This is a Leyden jar.
Right now, if I bring this
metal instrument near it...
Nothing happens.
However!
If I use a cotton rag to charge this
glass rod with static electricity...
...and transfer the electricity to the jar...
...and move the metal
instrument close once again...
...the electric charge stored up in
the Leyden jar flew into the rod!
Incidentally, if you sharpen the tips of the rod,
it can receive electricity
across an even greater distance.
Wow, really?
Well? Falling in love all over again?
A-Absolutely not!
Good morning!
Something smells good!
Good morning.
Join me, Marie?
Sure!
Thank you so much!
That was delicious!
You're welcome.
I hope this 18th century
coffee agrees with you.
Go ahead.
Thank you very much.
Does that mean you believed
my story from last night?
No, I find it dubious.
It's hard to take it on faith that
you're from the future, Marie.
Um, it's Mari, not Marie.
Marie sounds nicer.
N-Nicer?
Huh? John...
Doesn't he go to school?
School? John is a slave.
A slave?
Are you saying... there are no
slaves where you come from?
Um... Yeah.
Then who does your cleaning and your laundry?
We have vacuums and laundry machines.
Vacuums?
What are those?
What are they?
They're machines that run on electricity.
The newest ones will move around
your room at scheduled times
and sweep up the dust
on the floor on their own.
With laundry machines, you just put
the dirty stuff in and press a switch,
and it does everything, from
washing to drying, by itself.
Wow, all with electricity?
Yeah!
Fantastic!
Is it really?
But here, cleaning and laundry
are done by slaves, like John.
Hey, speaking of which, how did
you get here from the future?
Um, well...
...I read a page about you
in a mysterious book.
What? Are they writing books about me?
Y-Yeah...
That's incredible!
I mean, that's over 250 years
into the future, isn't it?
I'm pretty impressive!
Y-Yeah, sure.
Okay!
Well, why don't we head out on a date?
D-Date?!
You're searching for your papa, right, Marie?
What's that?
Won't you at least take my arm?
No!
Oh, boy. Looks like it's going to rain.
Rain, rain, go away! Come again on Saturday!
Good, Laura!
Thank you very much!
It seems no one knew
anything about your papa.
I'm sorry, Marie.
I couldn't help you.
Oh, no... it's nothing.
Please don't apologize.
Really, I should be thanking you.
You're a charming girl, Marie.
Wh-What are you talking about?!
D-Don't tease me, please!
Marie...
Why don't we go look for a while?
Put the fire out now!
Get the injured into the church!
Dear! Dear!
Please, speak to me!
That's...
The cause of the lightning strike earlier?
Open the door!
John!
John... You went over there to shop?
Why does she care so much?
Everyone.
Let us pray that God's wrath calms quickly.
We must not rest.
Come, rise up!
No, John! You have to rest!
I need to pray.
Huh?
They've decided the lightning
is the wrath of God.
In the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Ghost,
Amen.
In the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Ghost.
--Amen.
--The Father, the Son...
...and the Holy...
John! Forget that! I need to cool your burns!
But God... will be angry...
You're wrong! That's not true, John!
God. Please forgive our many sins.
God... please forgive... our many...
What sins, exactly?
Marie?
Are you saying that John and the people
here have done something wrong?
Who are you?
Lightning isn't the wrath of God!
It's just electricity!
You people again?
If it's about your lightning rod,
I already refused to put it up.
Huh? How come?
It would prevent damage
from lightning strikes!
It would let the lightning's
electricity pass safely by!
Mr. Franklin, tell them! Tell them
that lightning is electricity!
Marie...
Very well.
But well done is better than well said.
Father.
I will prove to you that
lightning is electricity.
If I succeed,
will you consider installing
a lightning rod on the church?
Doctor!
You're safe?
Peter! Prepare a kite.
What? A kite?
Doctor. You mean...
There's someone here I have to convince.
Lightning is electricity.
The power of science can
reduce the damage it causes!
John...
I'll prove it to you, okay?
Mari...
Um... that kite for your experiment...
Could I make it?
Okay, it's done!
Th-That's a kite?
Yes! It's called a yakko dako!
I once won an award for a kite
I made over winter break, actually.
Everything ready?
Yes, more or less.
Then it's time.
What's that?
A kite, she claims.
Excellent. Very artistic!
Forgive the wait, everyone.
Right now, this jar is
completely unremarkable.
I'm going to charge it with the essence of
lightning, and show you a mini lightning bolt!
What is the essence of lightning?
Thank you for the question, my lady.
The essence of lightning
is the electricity stored up
in those thunderclouds.
I'm going to use the key attached to
the string of this kite to draw it in
and store it inside this jar.
It's coming!
Now the essence of lightning
is stored in this bottle.
It's time to unleash it.
Unleash it?
Yes! The real show is just about to start!
I'll show you a little lightning strike!
I hope this proves to him that lightning
is a scientific phenomenon, but...
Please, go well!
Huh? W-Wait a minute...
He did it!
Do you understand now?
Wow!
The future... It's amazing, Marie.
Mari?
That hurt!
Mari!
What's wrong?
What are you doing, Mari?
Huh?
Waka!
"The father of American independence.
He spoke up for the abolition of slavery.
And he's also famous for his
experiments with lightning."
So you were researching
about Benjamin Franklin?
Yeah!
Wow. And he's on the 100 dollar bill, too?
But is this really Mr. Franklin?
He was a little handsomer when I saw him...
Yeah, you're right.
What's that?
I was translating Mr. Franklin's famous phrases.
It's useful for studying English.
Huh? Mari, you study English?
Yes, I do.
I never liked studying before...
...but I guess being able
to learn things really is amazing.
Okay! It's so wonderful.
I'll do my best for your support.
Waka... Please say it in Japanese.
"Next Episode:
Volta on the Battlefield"
"Mari and Waka's Quick Science"
Mari and Waka's Quick Science!
Franklin said that lightning was
really electricity, remember?
I'm going to charge it with
the essence of lightning,
and show you a mini lightning bolt!
Now let's try the same thing
with modern technology!
Huh?
What's that machine?
Look at this!
If we move this little ball of metal
towards this big ball of metal...
What's that?!
It's true!
It's just like Mr. Franklin's
experiment with his Leyden jar!
This is a Van der Graaf Generator.
Van der Graaf?
"Static Electricity"
It uses the friction between
two rollers powered by a motor
"Static Electricity"
and a rubber belt to create
and store up static electricity.
"Static Electricity"
and a rubber belt to create
and store up static electricity.
It's making artificial lightning!
But static electricity...
Is that the same as the
electricity we use every day?
Okay, let's test it!
If we channel it through
a fluorescent light...
It lit up!
Wow! Wow!
The static electricity stored
up in that metal sphere
can even light up a fluorescent light bulb!
I see!
So lightning really is electricity!