Shion! Shion!
Ah, Suou... I'm glad you came.
What happened?
I have remunerated the necessary price, that's all.
More importantly, I have a favor to ask.
Can you take me outside?
I want to see the moon.
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
Nee dareka oshiete
Hey, someone, tell me
Minna sou na no kana?
Is everyone like that?
Kyou ga shiawase nara
That they 'feel it's good enough
Sore de ii to omoeru tte
if they're if happy today'
Osanai koro ni wa
When I was young
Tashika ni atta yo
They certainly existed
Yume o oikaketeta
I pursued my dreams
Demo sore mo tooi kioku
But that's also a distant memory
Kotae no nai mainichi ga
The each unanswered day-
Tada sugite iku jikan ga
The time that is simply passing by-
Kore kara saki dou naru no darou?
What will happen beyond now?
Wakaranai...
They don't know...
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
Was Suou really here?
Yes, but she went somewhere else with Shion.
No way...
Yes, to meet Izanami.
Why didn't you stop her even though you knew that?
If Izanami and Izanagi meet...
...the prophecy will come true and the world will be ruined.
However...
There are times when you must meet, regardless of the outcome.
What are you talking about?
Oh right, I haven’t told you anything.
I'll explain it all,
but before that, let's get out of here.
They’ve found this place, too.
This is my remuneration.
I heard it from the girl called Youko.
That your true goal is to prevent the prophecy from coming true.
But I don't care about that.
I will kill Izanami.
That's enough, Hazuki.
He didn't kill Youko.
Huh? Nobody's here.
Did Youko lie to me, even though I was so nice to her?
Of course not.
Shizume did that?
He put her body into the ME Squeezer,
and analyzed the data up until her death.
There's no mistake.
He’s joined the CIA and betrayed us.
Currently, the outside of the Gate is surrounded,
and every international agency in PANDORA, including us, is under their authority.
Please go.
I'll take care of the traitor.
BK201.
Izanami is waiting for you.
Get in.
Where are you taking us now?
When did I?
That's my line.
July went to see her.
Her? You mean Suou?
Right, because this is the Gate.
A place where all your wishes come true, eh?
We're going. Hold tight.
We've lost Alpha team's signal.
"Defeat your enemies using one of their own."
Hurry up with the squeezing process!
Find out from the professor's memories where they're heading to!
She's an empty shell.
Empty?
Her soul has already awakened and is heading to the center of the Gate.
Only her empty shell is lying there.
We were too late.
And so were you.
What is this place?
This is where Professor Pavlichenko and I built the supercomputer.
Suou?
No, Shion?!
Yes, they look like Shion, but these specimens aren't even dolls.
What were you doing here?
All the memories of the world recorded by the doll network,
and all the memories of mankind from the ME network are here.
Why?
I couldn't see it any more.
Ever since I bet everything I had on Shion-kun's plan.
A plan...
For that, we tricked MI-6 and CIA to make them force Shion and the professor out of Russia.
That's not the moon.
That there is proof of mankind's existence.
Shion-kun copied it by using his powers.
An alternate...
I heard everything from Dad.
That I was born two years ago.
And how my memories were created by you.
Did you like my present?
If I didn't have that memory, perhaps I wouldn't be here now.
That memory was also my dream.
I always dreamed of going back to that day,
and I realized that you wanted the same.
You're mistaken.
I just injected it by thinking it was a normal, human-like memory,
It would have been awkward to release you into society without a memory like that.
That is not my dream.
Even though you've become a contractor, you perceive your surroundings with your emotions.
You think so?
Yes.
Contractors don't think like that.
At least, I don't.
Perhaps I was influenced by the friends I've been traveling with.
Friends, huh?
That very word is alien to me.
So I'm not one either?
Am I-
No.
Because to me you are...
What's going on?
A contractor.
Izanami forced him to commit suicide.
Suicide?
So Izanami did that too.
Yin...
Shion?
Shion! Shion!
Where am I?
She stopped her awakening by herself?
Yes.
On the day we retrieved her, we were planning to kill her.
But on that very day, her reactions as Izanami stopped.
Aware of her powers should she awaken, we hurried and sealed her with this.
Until you destroyed it...
We hoped that she would go back to sleep on her own.
But that miracle didn't occur again.
I'm not blaming you.
Mankind had no chance in the first place.
Ever since the Gates appeared on this planet.
Yin...
Let's end this.
Episode 12    The Ark of the Star
Shion!
Where are you? Shion!
July?
Yes, go straight.
This way.
Aren't you surprised?
I am.
The mission's been aborted. Go back.
The higher-ups made an agreement with America not to interfere.
I won't come with you.
I like being with Suou.
An evolving doll?
Very well.
Do as you wish.
July!
Wasn't Mao with you?
July?
This way.
What?
What's going on?
The two of them have met.
The two of them?
Izanami and Izanagi.
So it's started, huh?
Oh, fancy seeing you here.
Did you have fun doing this?
Come on, be honest.
You're that kind of a woman.
A pervert, just like me.
Detecting the formation of several dimensional rifts at the center.
Hell's Gate is opening!
Send all troops to the center!
We won't let them humiliate our country in this matter any further!
He's there.
Shion!
Shion! Shion!
The deal is complete.
Here's your present.
Look at the world I've made.
You’re not making any sense!
Give my regards to Papa and Mama.
Sis...
Shion?
Shion! Shion!
What did you do to him?
What did you do?!
I granted his wish.
July!
Hei knew you would become like this.
That's why he said he would put an end to this, and left me.
At first I didn't understand what he meant,
but now I'm sure he meant this.
We promised to put an end to our problem.
The meteor core...
is going to break.
An experiment?
Yes.
There was a problem with our plan.
Even if we use the ME to input memories into a copied human,
those memories wouldn't stay very long.
Until we used the meteor core.
In other words, Suou's very journey was an experiment to make sure her memories wouldn't fade away?
Yes.
So, now that she's lost the meteor core...
She'll start to lose her memories.
No...
No!
Don't...
Stop it!
Don't erase them!
I don't know of any other Suou.
Whether you're a copy or not, you're the only Suou I know.
They are my memories.
Suou.
Don't erase them!
Who are you?
You won’t need this where you’re going.
Where are we going next?
We'll always be together, right?
We can travel again, right?
Yes, we will.
Liar.
I'm not lying.
I'll always be by your side.
Hei...
Hei.
Yin.
It's not too late.
Kill me.
Hey! Wait for me!
Are we going to Suou?
I don't know if we will make it in time, but if this place is the Gate, my wish will come true!
Don't forget that you will lose something.
Don't just stop like that.
What?
BK201's star...
Oh, no!
This is bad!
I'm going to be late!
That's why you should wake up a bit earlier.
But last night was the best night to see the Gemini meteor cluster!
Hey, you two! Don't forget your lunches!
Ah, thanks.
Dear, your hair is standing up.
Thanks.
How about waking up a bit earlier yourself, Papa?
I'm off!
Good morning!
Something is missing.
I wonder when I started thinking that way.
Whether I'm together with my friends, or with my family,
I always have the feeling that something is missing.
My friends say that I'm longing for someone.
But, it's not like I'm feeling lonely at all.
Instead, I have this reassuring feeling that I’m always protected.
By someone I haven't met or seen yet. Someone I can't even imagine.
But I have the feeling that I know him very well.
And I believe that one day, I'll meet him.
Farewell.
It's moving away.
She's there just like Shion wished.
Yes.
July is with her, too.
It's over.
Everything.
No.
This is the beginning.
Yes.
That's why I asked you to join us.
Hi! Want a ride?
Kureteku yuubae ni senaka osarete
My back is pressed by the darkening glow of dusk
Y-You're...
After that, we left the Gate as if we were running away.
America took control over the streets of Tokyo to restore their former glory.
Arukidasu kage ga shimesu hou e
I start walking toward where my shadow points
And the Syndicate operating from the shadows completely ceased to exist.
Taenai ikutsu mo no deai to wakare o
Repeating the many, ceaseless encounters and partings
Another Gate has opened.
Let's go! Let's go!
What is the thing that was prophesied to be born from this?
Kurikaeshi doko e mukau no ka
Where do I head to?
Hito wa dare mo mayoinagara
For all people, while they are lost,
And how will it affect the world?
tsumi to iu na no sadame o seotte
they bear the fate known as sin
Sore de mo nao ikiru imi o shiru darou
Nevertheless, I'll still learn of the meaning to live, right?
In a not so distant future, we chose to walk the same path for the sake of something that's predestined to happen.
Bokura wa sou Day by Day
That's right, Day by Day,
Ironically, people called us the Syndicate.
ashita e tsuzuku michi no tochuu de
we're midway on the road leading to tomorrow
Ever since then, I've heard nothing about him.
Now Say It Again kimi to futari no mama
Now Say It Again, though it'd be great if
Yet I still believe... that he's alive.
irareta nara ii no ni naa...
I could remain together with you...