To Stop
The War
Between
Napoli
The Yakuzas
and
The Gangsters...
I'm now being forced
to fake being the boyfriend
of the boss's daughter.
That's the least of our problems.
I never
knew
that
it would be her.
Y-Your dad's a gang boss?
And you're the heir to a yakuza syndicate?
This is the boss of the Beehive gangster outfit.
Ardelt Kirisaki-Wagner and his daughter, Miss Kirisaki Chitoge!
I've heard all about you from your father.
It's great to finally meet you, Raku-kun.
No, no, no, no!
I'm never getting together with this guy! Absolutely not!
That's right, Dad! It'll never work out with a maniac like her!
That's great and all, but it's the only way we can prevent this war.
And besides...
Mistress!
What the hell?
I've found you, Mistress!
So it's true. These Shuei-gumi rats really did kidnap you!
C-Claude!
Fear not, Mistress.
As an executive leader of the beehive, your protection is my highest priority!
Therefore I've taken it upon myself to come rescue you!
Well, well, if it isn't one of the Beehive's top dogs!
Don'tcha think you're way outta line?
I've been goin' easy on you so far, but...
This time around, you'll get no mercy!
You damn apes!
I'll teach you what happens to guys who mess with our precious Mistress!
Look, calm down, kiddo.
I think there's been a misunderstanding!
Hm? B-Boss! What are you doing here?
Nobody kidnapped the girl. You couldn't be further from the truth.
In fact...
These two are head-over-heels for each other!
What...
What the hell?!
Boss.
Is this true?
Of course! And we've given them our blessing.
Young Master! You've finally snagged yourself a girlfriend, eh?
Oh, man, we've been worried about you for the longest time!
Not having a single girlfriend at your age...
This calls for a celebration!
Well, hey... um...
Mistress!
Y-Yes?
You've grown up, and I've failed to even notice!
My dear Mistress, over the years I've guarded you, you've become a fine young lady!
I wouldn't be your Claude if I weren't overcome with joy!
Uh... no... You were never "mine"...
This changes everything!
For you, Young Master, we'll gladly declare a ceasefire!
Same goes for us.
Let us throw our full support behind her, so that she may date him peacefully!
H-Hey, hold up, you guys! Since when are we a couple?
Why should I have to date this gorilla woman?
Th-That's right! Who'd want to date this bean sprout?
Hey, punk.
Did I hear you wrong? You didn't really call our lady a gorilla woman, did you?
You bastard!
What do you think you're doing to our Young Master?
If you touch a single hair on his head, you're a dead man.
Hey, Young Master.
Are you two... really boyfriend and girlfriend?
Th-This is bad.
Wh-What now? What do we do about this?!
Don't ask me!
At this point, playing along is our only option!
It's all or nothing now! We'll have to fake it!
Yeah.
Of course we're totally hot for each other!
I meant that she's as strong and sweet as a gorilla!
I just wanted to show you that our love isn't just any love.
Right, honey?
Oh, there you go again, darling!
Don't confuse them like that!
But of course, that's what I love about you—your skin's as snow-white as a bean sprout!
My darling!
Well, how 'bout that? So you two are head-over-heels in love, after all?
How did we end up like this?
Can't you see it's no use complaining?
There's no way we're getting out of this now.
I know we're a couple now, but what are we supposed to do?
How should I know?
It's not like I've ever dated anyone before.
Neither have I, for your information. Not once!
Really?
W-Well, what can I say?
I'm not so good at things like romance.
I don't really get it.
Hey.
Thanks for finding this, by the way.
It would've been awkward if we broke it off like that. That's all.
Well, now you can go ahead and show me your eternal gratitude!
So, what's the story?
I mean, it really seems important to you.
Is it a keepsake from someone who died?
No, someone gave it to me. A long time ago.
A long time ago?
When I was a kid... I was traveling overseas with my dad, and...
I got pretty close with this girl I met.
She told me, “We'll meet again,”
and gave this to me as a token of our promise.
I can't remember her name or what she looked like.
All I remember is our promise.
Maybe I'm just hoping that if I hold onto it, we might actually meet again.
I know you hate me for that, though.
Dwelling on the past and all...
What I hate is the kind of guy who keeps brooding over past mistakes
and other things that he can't possibly change.
But I can't say I hate romantic stories like yours.
Anyway, we're gonna do something about this situation ASAP.
I can't stand the thought of dating you!
I could say the same, you moronic bean sprout!
Young Master, you have a visitor!
Good mornin', Young Master.
G'morning!
Good morning!
G-Good morning, darling!
Sorry to spring this on you,
but would you go on a date with me right now?
Episode 2: Encounter
A—
A date?
Why should we?
Why, you say?
Because that's what couples do!
Caution
Beware of Stalkers
Oh, jeez, what have I done to deserve this?
We're not getting out of this, remember?
What are we going to do?
Don't look at me, I don't have a clue!
Isn't it the guy's job to escort the girl around?
You really are thoughtless!
You really know how to piss someone off at every turn.
That said, I've never really gotten up close and personal with a girl, let alone gone on a date with one.
How should I know what to do on a date?
Wait a sec.
Of all the dates with Onodera that I've fantasized about,
the ideal one had us sitting at a fashionable café and talking to each other,
then going to see a movie together,
eating dinner together,
and finally taking a walk in a gorgeous park together.
What is this? So gross!
What kind of crappy beans are these? Are you all retarded?
Ugh! How can you live with yourselves, charging 600 yen for this!
What's this? Could this meat be any more rubbery?
Still tastes okay, though. One more, right now!
I want to see this!
Truck
Destroyer
I saw the commercial, and it has the mother of all explosion scenes! Looks rad!
No, we have to see this one!
Meow
It's a four-handkerchief tearjerker and it's a current blockbuster!
Well, I guess this is what couples usually watch.
She's already asleep!
Despite everything...
Even a girl like her...
can look kind of cute when she's asleep.
As long as she's not talking or moving.
Well, just a tiny bit.
I'm thirsty. Go buy me some juice!
Right now!
What?
I take it back! She's not cute at all!
Hey, hey! Yeah, you!
You're pretty cute!
Hey, you free? Wanna go to a café with us?
Unfortunately, I happen to be waiting for someone right now.
Wait, a bean sprout's technically a vegetable...
What are you talking about? You're funny, aren't you?
Look, just hang out with us, 'kay?
We'll show you a great time!
You ignoring us?
Oh, come on, we know you're alone.
What's wrong? Your boyfriend stand you up?
Poor thing! We'll take good care of you!
Gotta say, you do have an amazing ass!
It's turning me on!
Wait, you're half-Japanese, aren't you? Did your friends ditch you?
Hey, we get it. We get it.
Don't worry, we'd never do that to you. You understand Japanese?
Hello! Hello!
Oh, hey! My apologies.
See, she still doesn't understand a word of Japanese!
What the...
My bad. Sorry to keep you waiting, Kirisaki!
Come on, let's get out of here. This way, this way!
Wait...
Where do you think you're going?
Why did you stop me?
Were you trying to play the hero who saves the girl from the bad guys?
I hate to break it to you, but in two seconds those guys could've been—
That's not the point!
You need to pick your battles! That's all!
Don't get the wrong idea. I'm not defending those guys.
If you whale on creeps who aren't even worth whaling on,
that's as good as admitting you're on their level!
Don't be such a lame-ass!
What the... Who are you to talk to me like that?
You don't have to tell me! As if I'd ever give those guys the time of day!
It might have been for the briefest moment,
but for the first time in my life, I held hands with a girl.
Oh, for crying out loud.
I knew it'd be like this! This date sucks!
Not only did you bore me to death, but you had to start lecturing me too!
Talk about a buzz-kill.
Excuse me?
Even so...
I wouldn't really call it the worst of the worst.
On a scale of 1-100, today's date,
after adding in double bonus points...
I guess I'll give you a score of 1.
Where are you going?
To the restroom. Don't ask why, retard!
For the first time in my life,
I let a guy lead me by the hand.
I was so careless!
I really can't seem to figure her out. What's her deal?
Seriously!
Oh, man, if only I was on a date with Onodera!
That would totally be a dream come true!
Did you say my name?
Wh-What a surprise!
I just saw you and was about to say hi.
Did you see me first?
What are you doing here?
O... O...
Onodera!
What are you doing here, Ichijou-kun?
Wh-What am I doing? What about yourself, Onodera?
Me? I just finished shopping with my friends so I'm on my way home.
This is quite the surprise!
I was about to say hi and surprise you,
but then all of a sudden, you said my name first!
W-Well, hey, I was just...
What... were you thinking about?
So anyway, something's off about them, you see?
Yeah... I'm getting the same vibe.
The two of 'em are acting weird.
Yeah, like there's no sign of them being all into each other like they were at the Yakuza's house..
They're like an unnatural couple.
Plus, they were arguing and all, which raises more suspicions.
N-Not good...
This is bad!
We have to do something, or all of today's suffering will have been for nothing!
Time to really lay it on thick!
Oh, darling! Thanks for being patient!
So sorry! I took way longer than I thought.
Ki... Kirisaki-san?
Huh? Did she just call you... "darling"?
Uh... Um... Let's see...
If she's calling you darling, then that means...
You two are... uh... dating each other?
N-No, no, no!
Why would I be dating her?!
Yeah! That's right! Who'd ever date him?
N-No good!
Everyone's...
watching!
But I don't want Onodera to think we're dating!
I can't let that happen! But... what am I supposed to do?
Hey.
That's right!
We just started going out the other day!
I'm telling you, he's totally smitten with me!
K-Kirisaki!
Come on! Play along with me!
I know it's embarrassing in front of a classmate,
but what else can we do?!
Yeah! If it were just any classmate, I'd play the hell out of this role!
Anybody but Onodera... Just not Onodera!
I-I see. What a surprise. I had no idea!
D-Damn it! What am I supposed to do?
Right? Isn't that right, darling?
What? Who's smitten?!
I have no clue what she's talking about!
Oh, come on! I just had a lovely dinner with my darling.
It wasn't my idea!
She insisted she wanted to eat meat!
Would you believe this boy? Every single weekend, he asks me to the movies.
I just happened to have tickets, that's all!
Not to mention, I'm actually the type who prefers to go alone.
Look! I'm warning you, knock it off!
And anyway, this girl drools while she dozes off at the movies, you know!
Hey, I almost forgot.
I just remembered something I have to do! Gotta run, darling!
See you later, Onodera!
What? Oh, right.
Are you sure you want to let Kirisaki-san run off by herself?
Yeah, it's all right. I'll catch up soon enough.
Everything makes sense now.
Although I wasn't able to trip them up today, I'm convinced now!
There's definitely something fishy going on.
Just you wait, you little scumbag twerp!
I'll personally crush any fly that gets near the Mistress!
H-Hey, listen, Onodera... We're...
Not really like that, okay? The truth is, we're not a coup—
I get it, Ichijou-kun.
You don't have to say any more, okay?
I totally understand.
You shouldn't deny it, though.
Even if you're just hiding your embarrassment,
but you might hurt Kirisaki-san's feelings.
Wh-Wh... Hiding my embarrassment?
Yes.
I think you two are perfect together!
It's so obvious that you're infatuated with each other!
N-Not good! She's totally convinced that we're a couple!
Why are the gods subjecting me to such an ordeal?
Oh, sorry! You were in the middle of a date, right?
I'll be on my way.
Wait... No... Um...
Right.
Now's the perfect chance. We're alone.
O-Onodera!
Yes?
Is it all right if I ask you just one question?
Have... Have you ever...
I was wondering if you'd ever seen this pendant before yesterday.
Like, maybe when you were little.
No. Never. Not once.
All right, I have to go now, okay? You'd better not keep Kirisaki-san waiting,
Ichijou-kun!
My bad!
Sorry I kept you waiting, Kirisaki!
How dare you show your face, gutter-bug!
What do you think you're doing?
Do you have any idea how humiliating that was?!
But you, on the other hand!
I know that, so just hear me out...
Bean Jam Store
Here, this is for you.
What is it?
Well, it's a... um... you know!
My way of apologizing.
Because... I screwed up.
Wow, you're more straightforward than you look.
So? What is this, anyway?
Yeah, well, it's called a dorayaki.
It doesn't taste like the ones from my favorite shop,
but trust me, it's still pretty awesome. Try one!
I hate it.
I'm home!
Welcome back, Kosaki!
I used a new recipe for these dorayaki. Do you want to try one?
No, I think I'll pass. I'll be in my room.
What do I do now?
I lied to him.
Now what?
Asking him will be all the more difficult.
Ichijou-kun is this type of person
Together on animal care duty.
You've been taking care of all these animals by yourself?
I have to say, you didn't do half bad, considering how many there are.
No sweat! They're practically family to me!
I bet you've been waiting for this. Chow time!
How 'bout it? Looks yummy, right?
You guys are such a helpless bunch!
Looks more like they hate you.
And so...
Exactly how many animals do you have here?
About ninety, if I had to say?
Ninety?! Is this a zoo?!
So like, do they all have names?
Yeah, some of them. I've only decided on half, though.
Only half?
I thought they were your family.
How naïve. It's precisely because they're family!
Naming them is a very delicate process!
What's wrong, Divine Spacer Kuniyoshi?
That's too long.
Kirisaki-san is this type of person
Why don't you try naming them, then?!
Don't come up with anything funny, though.
Me? Name them?
I guess I could.
In that case, this little one is...
Probably Number One.
That one is Number Two.
This one is Number Three.
And this one here...
Ah, forget it.
At any rate, since you're also in charge of raising them,
at least get to know the ones that already have names.
Look, this is Rodriguez IV, the turtle.
Really? I wonder how he'd taste grilled.
And this chicken is Kato the Crusher.
Yeah? Which parts are the juiciest?
What?