Who are you?
Do you want to know more about what happened in Vladivostok?
The body of an MI6 agent,
the involvement of the CIA,
and the illegal Japanese intelligence agency that's rumored to exist.
Actually, you know that better than me.
From the way you talk, you seem to know why BK201's star disappeared.
Who knows?
I heard some dangerous anti-contractor weapon was used.
An anti-contractor weapon?
As the name implies, it's a weapon that can take out contractors.
I believe you have seen something similar to the prototype two years ago.
How...
Have you heard about the Mitaka document?
The thing you're looking for, that mysterious document, is in the hands of a certain organization.
The key word is "Izanami."
Wait! How do you know what I'm looking for?
What is the Mitaka document?
Make a wish upon a star.
Upon a tiny, little, red star.
"May I meet BK201 again."
Red star...
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
Nee dareka oshiete
Hey, someone, tell me
Minna sou na no kana?
Is everyone like that?
Kyou ga shiawase nara
That they 'feel it's good enough
Sore de ii to omoeru tte
if they're if happy today'
Osanai koro ni wa
When I was young
Tashika ni atta yo
They certainly existed
Yume o oikaketeta
I pursued my dreams
Demo sore mo tooi kioku
But that's also a distant memory
Kotae no nai mainichi ga
The each unanswered day-
Tada sugite iku jikan ga
The time that is simply passing by-
Kore kara saki dou naru no darou?
What will happen beyond now?
Wakaranai...
They don't know...
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
The projectile is off by 2 cm.
Well, it's a pretty good shot from this distance.
There are three rounds left.
Does that mean you can only use this monster three more times?
No, each time it manifests, I have one round in the chamber and five in my pocket.
It's just that I have to maintain it since the warping and scratches don't disappear.
You're pretty enthusiastic about this, young miss.
Yes, absolutely.
Go eat.
Are you going to pass on lunch and save money again?
I won't eat anything strange again.
I'll become stronger.
I need to become stronger before I run away again.
And in order to realize that, I have to overcome my dislikes.
Something proper, eh?
What do contractors eat?
Raw meat?
Did you hear that from your son?
What?
Me being a contractor...
I could tell without asking him.
Besides, Michiru-san was a contractor too.
Michiru-san?
A man.
I had the right to board Noah's Ark.
My parents nagged me on that too.
So I thought it wouldn't be a bad experience to see the world.
She was good at making sweets. She was a normal housewife.
I guess it happened when Norio was three.
She became a contractor, and by the time her personality started to deteriorate,
she was gone.
I wonder where she is and what she's doing now.
There you go.
Tasty?
Yum!
Have as much as you want.
The liver creates blood, you know.
Especially now that you are—
Oh, right.
I'll give you that.
My star is cryin'!
I, who hath been born beneath the scorching and passionate star, have to finally remunerate...
with my love for you!
H-Hey!
Hey! Hold on! Wait a second!
Hey, did you know? My mommy's a contractor!
Isn't that cool?
Our meeting must be destiny at work!
Your love for me?
What do you know about me anyway?
Tell me all about yourself, then.
As I said...
You sparkle brighter than the fake stars in the sky.
Let's board Noah's Ark together!
Give her a mission?
It's not about the reward.
She'll only slow me down.
She has a better aim with a rifle than I have, but...
that's really all.
I can do that mission alone.
What did you do?!
Lebanon gave me an earthenware pot and gas burner.
Earthenware pot?
She really is impulsive.
When she opened it, there was a cockroach inside.
Then "bang"!
Why?
Because I hate bugs now.
You're going to hit me again, aren't you?
I know.
Just do it.
But in exchange, hit me on the left side.
What?
The right side is still hurting from the last time.
I won't be able to move properly if there's no balance.
Hurry up.
You're so irritating.
Hey, you'll freeze to death.
A cockroach, eh?
It must be because of her friend.
Even though she's used to her new powers, what happened to her friend must really have shocked her.
She was saying things about love and stuff.
She was really worried about her friend.
I doubt there's anyone she likes though.
I hate you.
So I'm the same as a cockroach, huh...
Guess this is the warmest room here.
What's up with her?
Even though she's a contractor, there's no pattern in her behavior.
She didn't lose interest in her hobbies, either.
There were too many things she didn't know.
Perhaps she wasn't really what you'd call an adult human.
And then she became a contractor.
A contractor who's accumulating social experiences...
Yeah.
She's probably accumulating more experience to help her make logical decisions.
She's still a kid.
Good night.
The Mitaka document... Izanami...
Why am I believing her?
But that's the only clue I have.
Ichinose-san.
Chief Kobayashi is calling for you.
You've got new orders.
We want you to transport an important object from a facility in Sapporo.
Codename: Izanami.
I'm here to chase after BK201.
Or are you saying there's more behind this order?
Of course there is a reason we can't be careless.
We've been informed by our agent in Sapporo.
He spotted BK201 in the company of some kids.
He's in Sapporo?
Episode 5
The gunpowder is drifting away, so is the life...
At least knock.
Someone's here.
Pursuers?
How many?
Three. One of them is a contractor.
I'll draw their attention.
You three escape through the entrance while they're distracted.
We'll regroup at the usual place.
What's this?
BK201 was living here?
Yes, with a girl.
Girl? Not a boy?
Yes. Unless he was cross-dressing...
According to the family register, Shion Pavlichenko had a twin sister.
But we know nothing about her.
She might have been killed by the FSB.
If the person with BK201 is truly a girl...
You're jealous?
We have to go.
The people at the research lab are awaiting you.
It smells great.
According to dad, it's around here.
That's...
Hey!
Who is he?
Wait!
Should I kill him?
No.
I don't think he will cause any problems.
Mom!
They're too careless.
We'll practice sniping.
Hey, is that the first thing you say?
Shoot that.
Without lying to me.
I don't understand why I should kill it.
That's why I can't shoot.
As long as it moves... it doesn't have to be a living target, right?
I don't understand the reason, so—
There is a reason.
To eliminate your irregularities as a contractor.
Why are you crying?
I don't know.
I don't know...
I saw her!
It was her!
That was mom—
You took the flowers in the bathroom, didn't you?
That's not the problem!
Sorry! We're in the middle of an important family discu—
Let me use your oven.
We don't know who BK201's client is,
but it's certain they hid him here to target the goods.
Normally, we would have transported it by air,
but BK201 gets close to his target by blending into the crowd.
There are too many people at the airport.
We'll transport it by water this time.
Geez, that's no fun.
We should just get it over with already.
Says the bum who got his ass kicked by that little kid...
That really hurts...
We'll check the Izanami.
The security is really tight in here.
This way.
Wish upon a star.
Found it.
It won't be long before our wish and her wish come true.
This is...
Izanami?
What are you doing?
These are weeds.
They're edible.
My dad taught me that.
Here.
I shot a hole in the hotel's wall and made us stand out.
So...
She's trying to apologize?
How is it?
As long as it's nutritious, it doesn't matter how it tastes.
So it tastes so bad you have to think the taste doesn't matter.
Refill.
You've got a mission.
I see.
Perhaps a bit hard for a first mission.
If...
If you pay me...
A reward?
Aren't you spoiling your handyman?
I'm paying her in advance.
As a contractor, you take on missions and get paid.
It's very simple.
That's why I can definitely do it.
This is a terrible night.
A ship from Section 3 will enter the harbor.
If I can destroy the goods before it arrives in the harbor, there won't be a problem.
If I fail...
you'll shoot when they're unloading the goods from the trucks.
...it is...
...Izanami... the trucks...
Kureteku yuubae ni senaka osarete
My back is pressed by the darkening glow of dusk
Arukidasu kage ga shimesu hou e
I start walking toward where my shadow points
Taenai ikutsu mo no deai to wakare o
Repeating the many, ceaseless encounters and partings
Kurikaeshi doko e mukau no ka
Where do I head to?
Hito wa dare mo mayoinagara
For all people, while they are lost,
tsumi to iu na no sadame o seotte
they bear the fate known as sin
Sore de mo nao ikiru imi o shiru darou
Nevertheless, I'll still learn of the meaning to live, right?
Bokura wa sou Day by Day
That's right, Day by Day,
ashita e tsuzuku michi no tochuu de
we're midway on the road leading to tomorrow
Now Say It Again kimi to futari no mama
Now Say It Again, though it'd be great if
irareta nara ii no ni naa...
I could remain together with you...
I saw a whale, but I didn't take a picture of it.
I thought it was pointless.
Why, though?
Now that I think of it, I should have taken a picture.
Woah! It's so big!
Hey, is that a whale?
No! Whales are much bigger!
And they spurt salt water!
Salt water?
Is that salty?
Oh boy, you really don't know anything.
No!
I know that much.
Come on, don't fight.
Look...
Everyone's smiling.
Yeah.
That's right.
No one gets angry when they are in an aquarium.
Their hearts melt when they see the fishes swim happily.
All right, what do you say about some ice cream?
Yep! I want one with three balls!
I want one as big as a whale!
A whale?
The foamy meringue shines pearl gray.
Inside the warm oven a golden life is conceived.
The warm, sweet taste doesn't bring back memories from childhood.
It's time to set sail.
It would have been better if we had never met.
I didn't need any memories at all.
And then... the journey continues.