Summer
I can't believe you got rooms this close to the beach.
A friend of mine said he had to cancel, so he gave me a great deal.
Summer will be ending soon, you know.
Wouldn't it suck if we didn't go to the beach at least once?
Aren't you just here for the girls in swimsuits?
I'm so glad we were all able to make it!
I've never been to the beach in Japan before!
I don't think I've been to one since I was in North Carolina.
I only saw it, but my last time was in the Maldives, I believe.
What are you two, celebrities?
I'm going in first!
Hey, you!
Yippee!
All right!
Episode 18 - At the Beach
Oh, my!
Seishirou-chan, what a girlish swimsuit you have on today!
What brought this on?
I said I'd be just fine in my suit...
but the Mistress picked out a swimsuit that's beyond embarrassing!
We're at the beach! What are you complaining about? Deal with it.
This is why breasts are so unnecessary!
Now, now. You're blessed with a great body, so have a little confidence!
What the hell are you doing?
I knew it! They're bigger than mine. How outrageous!
Hey, you're right. Look at that resilience! You really are incredible, Tsugumi!
Mistress, how could you?!
Lucky!
They probably forgot that they're with a couple of guys.
So?
What have you been up to, anyway?
A! C! C! B!
B! B! Whoa, is that an E? Magnificent!
Did I just spot an F?
Just as I thought, the beach is beyond awesome!
Excuse me, Raku-sama!
Would you mind coming here for a moment?
Whenever I get a sunburn, it wreaks havoc on my skin.
So I was wondering if you could...
rub some sunscreen on me, please?
Wait, why me?
What about... that guy who's always waiting on you? Have him do it!
As of today, Honda has a strong aversion to sunscreen.
There you go again with another of your whoppers!
Hey, you! What's the big idea, hitting on my darling?
If you need sunscreen, why don't I rub it on for you?
Me, too! Me, too!
I appreciate your kindness,
but I have the feeling that unless Raku-sama does it, it won't be effective.
Now then, Raku-sama...
I am counting on you, all right?
But I never said I'd do it!
How dare you get love-struck over her!
What? But I'm not!
Jeez! What's wrong with him?
Always fawning over every girl!
I wish I knew why I have to feel so irritated.
This is...
Relationship Charm
Effects
1. You shall be blessed with a good relationship.
2. Your unrequited feelings shall bear fruit.
3. A man may propose marriage by offering his
relationship charm to a woman.
You can have this.
Jeez, what a total moron.
He's the one who wanted it so badly that he bought it, so he should know its effects!
I'm the one who made a complete fool of myself!
But...
If he really had proposed...
What... What would I have done?
Yeah, right! Not a chance!
Especially not with him!
Something that ridiculous would never happen in a million years!
We're just faking our relationship!
So...
Why didn't I turn it down right away?
All righty, why don't we figure out how we're handling dinner?
'Cause we're renting a grill tonight.
Okay!
So the two lovebirds are working together, huh?
I'm counting on you, Raku!
Ugh! Why am I teamed up with you?
So I'm basically on my own, huh?
Come to think of it,
after all's said and done, ever since I've been in Japan,
I've been spending all my time with this guy, haven't I?
Well, since we're pretending to date,
I guess that's only natural.
Right, it looks like we're having a barbecue tonight,
so you should be able to help out too, right?
Don't insult me! I can handle any kind of cooking!
Where do you get all that confidence?
All right, I'm gonna peel these,
so you just chop them into bite-size pieces as they come. Can you do that?
Sure I can...
Is that a yes or a no?
Hey, you! What the heck?
Would you mind not touching me all of a sudden?
But you were the one who...
I was only trying to pick up that vegetable! It's your fault for putting your hand there!
Well, that's true, but...
Did I really do something that bad?
Just be careful next time!
Sure, I will, but...
What? What is this?
Why am I getting so flustered just because our hands touched?
We're always holding hands and stuff anyway,
when we're acting like a couple.
Our hands only touched. That's normal, remember! Normal!
Ouch!
Oh man, I knew you'd cut yourself. You need to be more careful.
Here. Let me see it.
I've got a Band-Aid.
I'm fine, thank you! This is nothing. All I have to do is suck on it.
Just give me your hand!
You're still a girl, you know? You wouldn't want that to leave a scar, would you?
Let's dig in!
This is awesome! Gotta give you props, Raku!
And here I thought that barbecue would taste the same no matter who was cooking!
Well, the difference lies in selecting your products and preparing the meat!
You're so wonderful, Raku-sama!
Ichijou-kun?
Can I sit next to you?
Onodera? S-Sure.
Did something happen between you and Chitoge-chan?
Well she seemed... a little down today.
Oh, you thought so, too? No...
Nothing really comes to mind.
I see.
Where are the others?
Whoever lost at rock-paper-scissors has to clean up. Chitoge-chan's with them, too.
Gotcha.
This is kind of incredible, don't you think?
Back in junior high, I never thought I'd be coming to the beach with you like this.
Me, neither.
And we never had a real conversation, either.
But wait, Onodera. I thought you couldn't swim!
Did you really enjoy coming to the beach?
Yes, it was fine.
Because doing that is what I enjoy most about the beach.
You applied your Japanese confectionery skills here?!
Did you have a good time, Ichijou-kun?
Yeah, I enjoyed myself all right.
Although I do wish I could've spent more time goofing off.
The ocean looks beautiful, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
I don't know why,
but whenever I talk to Ichijou-kun, I suddenly feel so alive.
I guess this is love.
I wish I could stay with him longer.
I wish this moment would go on forever and ever.
All righty, why don't we head back to the inn now?
Where are Raku and Onodera?
I'll go look for them!
Hey, there they are.
Hey, Kosaki-chan!
Hey, Ichijou-kun.
Could we kiss?
What did she just say? Don't tell me...
What did I just say?!
Oh my god! What did I do?
Was that just a thought that crossed my mind?
Or did I actually say it?
I'm pretty sure I said it!
What am I gonna do? How could I?
What should I do?
But we had such a nice vibe going on! My imagination just went wild!
And I then I blurted it out!
What should I do? I'll bet he thinks I'm totally weird!
Suddenly asking to kiss him...
He has to be creeped out now!
Why hasn't Ichijou-kun said a word all this time?
Oh crap, was I asleep just now?
My bad, I didn't get that much sleep last night.
Did you say something?
No, nothing in particular.
Is that right?
All right, Ichijou-kun, I'll be heading back first.
You come later, okay?
No, I can come with—
What the...
I had to have misheard her just now.
I mean, I don't think Kosaki-chan would ever say anything like that.
In such an intense atmosphere...
There's no way.
Could we get kimchi?
Something like that... I thought they were having a more serious conversation, but...
I wonder what they were talking about?
Could we get kimchi?
But it didn't sound like she was saying anything else.
It couldn't have been some other language.
I just can't imagine it.
So Kosaki-chan actually likes spicy food, huh?
What are you doing?
N-Nothing!
What am I doing here?
Why is it so hard to approach him now?
Until just a few days ago,
everything was just fine.
Why didn't you come back with Ichijou-kun last night?!
W-Well, I...
Chitoge-chan!
Is something wrong?
You seem kind of down since yesterday.
Kosaki-chan?
If you'd like, we could talk about it.
Did you have a fight with Ichijou-kun or something?
Well, fighting is a daily thing for us, though.
Hey, Kosaki-chan.
This isn't about me, but...
Let's see, in other words...
This friend of yours, whenever she's around that "certain" person...
Her heart starts racing suddenly, it becomes hard to breathe,
and she can't talk to him like she normally does. Is that right?
Yes.
Seems like it started recently, out of the blue,
and she can't figure it out herself.
I wonder if she's talking about Tsugumi-san?
Well, to be perfectly frank...
Yeah? What is it?
I believe that she has a crush on him.
What? C-C-C-C-C-Crush? What?!
Yes, that's what I think.
You don't think so too, Chitoge-chan?
If this happened suddenly after things were normal at first,
then that's probably what's going on.
A crush, huh?
A crush? Did she say a crush?!
But if that's true, then everything would make sense.
No, forget it! This is impossible!
Kosaki-chan?
Oh, sorry!
I was just wondering if you and I used to chat like this when we played together ten years ago.
You know, like your dad said. Remember?
Years ago, you, Ichijou-kun and I used to hang out with each other.
I think, somehow, I'm starting to see why these days.
When I talk to you, it makes me feel a little nostalgic, you know?
Like, we must have played together like this back then, too.
Yes! I get the same feeling!
You can come to me again anytime, okay?
Thanks!
I'll get you some kimchi as a thank-you gift sometime!
Kimchi?
Yay, that was fun! That was a really deep conversation.
Kosaki-chan's such a nice girl!
Scumbag! Die! Scumbag!
Thank you very much!
But... a crush, huh?
Is that even possible?
I mean, we're talking about that bean sprout, of all people.
Sure, I don't think he's been such a bad guy lately.
If I have a crush on him, then that means that I'm in love with him, right?
No way, no way, no way, no way!
On second thought, that's impossible! Not a chance!
What am I thinking? There's no way! No way!
But if it's impossible...
then tell me why...
my heart is pounding.
Hey, they're lighting up!
No better way to end the day than with sparklers, right?
I'll share with you!
I've never seen a sparkler up close.
What in tarnation am I supposed to do with these dang things?
I don't see Mistress anywhere!
But she was just here a second ago.
I'll go look for her.
That's all right, Onodera. I'll go.
Seriously, what's she up to, anyway?
Sure, she's been acting strange since yesterday, but...
I can't do this.
Just being near him makes me freak out!
Oh man, this can't go on forever!
If this keeps up, how can we go on pretending to be a couple?
Stay calm! Stay calm!
Come on, Chitoge, settle down!
If this sparkler doesn't fall, I win. If it doesn't fall, it's not love.
If it falls, it's love... maybe...
Clear your mind. Clear your mind, Chitoge!
What do you think you're doing here?
What's your problem?
Nothing. I'm not doing anything in particular.
Nothing's wrong.
If nothing was wrong, you wouldn't be alone in a place like this.
Not someone like you.
I'm taking one of your sparklers.
What? Don't talk about me like you know me!
What do you know about me?
No, I do know some things about you.
It's only been a few months, but you and I are together at school,
on our days off... practically every day.
So I can tell that much, at least.
Don't do that!
Don't do what?!
Shut up!
That's so unfair!
Damn it, what's got you worked up?
Is there something on your mind?
As a special favor, I wouldn't mind being your sounding board.
It's not as if I have any particular issue.
Can't be honest with yourself, huh?
Don't act like you're my friend!
You and I are a fake couple, right?
I mean, you probably dislike me, don't you?
Now where's all this coming from?
Well, I guess I'd have to say yes.
Though, it's not as much as when we first met...
Then how about you?
Do you still hate me?
Of course I hate you!
I hate you, I hate you, I hate you, I hate you, I hate you, I hate you, I absolutely loathe you!
Is that right? Well, I can't say that doesn't depress me a little.
Hey... if we...
If we had dated for real, do you think it would've worked out?
What's up with that all of a sudden, huh?
That was out-of-character.
Never mind!
Just answer the question.
What the hell is wrong with her today?
She's not acting like herself today. Something must have happened!
Wait, why am I feeling so self-conscious too?
This isn't good! I already have Onodera!
Why do I get so nervous around this girl?
Also...
Has she...
Has she always looked like this?
Are...
Are you kidding?
Of course there's no way it'd work out!
To sum it up, you're just not my type, okay?
You're ungraceful, violent, and you're hardly charming.
We'd probably fight all the time like we do right now!
For starters, you could be more girlish, like, feminine!
I'm telling you...
Oh, just shut up, will you? I get it, so just shut your mouth!
Sorry.
Oh... Hey!
After that, right up until summer vacation ended,
Chitoge and I didn't say a single word to each other.
Thank you very much!
Take that!
And now the new semester has started.
Screw Chitoge.
Ever since that night on the beach, she's been ignoring all my calls and texts.
What the hell's going on?
What's up with her, anyway? Why's she so mad?
Wait, actually, was she upset to begin with?
Damn it, why am I the one getting pissed?
It looks like Ichijou-kun is upset about something.
I wonder if he's still fighting with Chitoge-chan.
Oh, man, I can't take this! I'm totally clueless!
Not that I could ever tell what she's thinking to begin with...
If we were really dating, do you think it would've worked out?
Answer me.
Sorry...
What the hell did she mean by "sorry"?
She's never apologized to me after a fight till now.
Don't tell me she's never coming back to school.
Morning...
H-Hey...
You could at least get in touch with me.
Ignoring me is a little too harsh, don't you think?
Sorry, I just had a lot going on.
How frigid is that?
What are you so mad about? Talk to me, will you?
If you don't tell me, how will I know?
I'm not mad or anything.
Hey, we'd better pipe down. Homeroom's about to start.
What...
What the hell?
What's with her attitude?
Until today, even if something happened the day before,
hasn't she always acted like nothing happened the next day?
But this isn't like any of those other times, is it?
All right, listen up!
Okay, I'd like to start the discourse on the Culture Festival that our school will host this year!
Holy crap! Don't tell me Maiko's in charge!
Don't you dare start planning something freaky!
Shut up! Since I've nominated myself to the Culture Festival Committee,
I'm gonna produce an unforgettable, mind-blowing Culture Festival!
After stringent voting, it has been decided that our class will be putting on a play on the day of the festival.
As for the title that we've picked...
It's Romeo and Juliet!
Today, I'd like to do the casting.
All right, what do you think about this?
This is my own personal suggestion, but for the main roles, Romeo and Juliet,
how about casting our class's very own item...
Ichijou Raku and Kirisaki Chitoge? What do you say?
H-Hey! Hold up, damn it! Hey! Shuu!
No objection!
I'm not doing it.