After an utterly impartial drawing,
it has been decided that the role of Romeo will go to Raku, while Onodera-san will be Juliet!
What?! Why does Raku of all people get to be Romeo?
Onodera-san?
Please give your role to me.
Surely you don't mind, do you?
I want to play Raku-sama's heroine!
If you are in agreement, then why wouldn't you give the role to me?
Please, please, please, please, I beg of you!
Why not?
I expected as much...
U-Um... I'm really sorry! Because...
The thing is, I was actually hoping to play...
the main character.
Is that right? Then I suppose there's nothing to be done.
In that case, I shall settle for the role of understudy,
in case you're not able to perform on the big day.
Would that be all right? Maiko-san?
Yup, that'd be totally fine.
Onodera, I didn't know you were into drama and theater.
I guess... Um...
J-Just a little?
Oh, crap! Is this for real?
Onodera and me as Romeo and Juliet?
I never dreamed that I'd get to play Onodera's love interest!
What am I gonna do? Sure, it's just a play, but I'm still freaking out!
But...
Gloom
Episode 19 - The Play
All right, rehearsal starts after school, so report to the classroom, guys!
Right! Okay!
She left.
Hey, hold up, Chitoge!
What?
Don't "what" me! Why are you leaving already?
Well, I'm not in the play, and I don't have anything else to do.
That's not what I'm talking about.
We gotta go home together, or else people will get suspicious!
We're supposed to be
crazy in love, remember?
One day won't make a difference.
That's not the point.
Why did you turn down the role of Juliet?
You and I are supposed to be a couple, you know.
Well, that's simple.
I didn't want to do it.
Are we done here? I'll be heading home, then.
Hey! What's the deal with your attitude these days?
If you've got a bone to pick with me, just say so! Tell me why you're mad!
If you just dump on me like that without telling me why, how am I supposed to know?
Did I do something to you?
Did I say something that rubbed you the wrong way?
Maybe I can't solve all your problems, but you could at least talk to me.
I told you already.
There's nothing wrong, and I'm not mad.
I also told you, "Don't act so familiar with me."
You and I aren't even a genuine couple.
Who said we have to chat like good friends when nobody's looking?
See you.
What the hell was that?
I was just worried about you, that's all.
Huh? Ichijou-kun? Where have you been?
Rehearsal will be starting soon!
Whoops, sorry.
I was just about to head over.
So Ichijou-kun and Chitoge-chan are still fighting.
No, no! You can't think about such things!
It's like my mind can't help going there!
But I wonder what that picture was really about?
How does Ichijou-kun really feel about Chitoge-chan?
Teacher's Room
Here are the handouts I've collected.
Hey, thanks!
But really, who knew you'd be playing Juliet?
You took me by surprise.
What brought about this change of heart?
I bet you're going to be a perfect fit for it.
I need to make sure I get a good look!
Oh, no. I'm not that...
Sensei? Where did... you get that photo?
Oh, this?
Remember our field trip last semester?
This is a photo from that trip.
Look, over here. That's you, right?
I screwed up and got a shot of you in your underwear, see.
Ichijou spotted it, and brought it back to me.
I'm pretty sure none of the other kids saw it, so don't worry, okay?
Who knew he was such a gentleman?
Ichijou-kun did that?
Whoops, not good! Forgot that Ichijou swore me to secrecy.
Listen, Onodera, don't tell anyone, okay?
So that's the story.
Ichijou-kun was looking out for me when he brought that photo to the teacher.
And here I was worried sick.
Don't act so familiar with me.
Damn it! Oh, forget her! I don't care about her!
I've got Onodera already.
You can't just shame her, can you?
All right, I'm gonna break a leg if I have to!
O Juliet! I love no one but you!
No, Onodera...
The next line is, "And I you, Romeo!"
R-Right, that's my line! Sorry!
What am I going to do? The second I found out that I was wrong about the photo,
I couldn't help but feel really self-conscious.
An idiot among idiots...
All right, then, let's take it from the top!
O Juliet, there is no longer anyone in my eyes but you.
My, I'm overjoyed to hear that!
Likewise, Romeo-sama. Let us marry without further delay!
OK! Cut!
Argh! Damn it, Tachibana, how many times are you going to interrupt?
Oh, my. I'm disrupting you? Far from it!
Recall that I'm Juliet's understudy. As such, I must get my practice in!
That doesn't give you the right to butt into Onodera's rehearsals.
Not to mention, all the lines you're spewing are wrong.
This is a tragedy about two hostile families whose respective heirs fall in love,
but aren't allowed to get married, you know!
Well! That's exactly like our own situation!
But worry not, Raku-sama!
Our families both approve of our union,
so if you were only willing to...
I told you not to make such bold declarations in public!
You'll cause trouble for me!
You vixen! You better back off!
I've told you repeatedly that he's Mistress's boyfriend!
Oh, but that hardly matters now, does it?
After all, she's not playing Juliet.
All we need now is...
Did we have enough cloth?
Umm, yeah, I think we're good.
Hey, we need Scotch tape!
Oh, crap! I made up my mind not to think about her.
Oh, that should be enough!
Oh, I guess it should!
I'm gonna focus on the play.
All right, why don't we call it a day!
Could all the performers gather round?
What's going on, Shuu? Are we gonna have a meeting or something?
No, no, Raku-kun, this is way more important than any meeting.
It's the costume-fitting you've all been looking forward to!
Holy crap! Are these really hand-made?
Of course, courtesy of our very own Sewing Club!
However, I myself played a part in procuring the materials.
Girls Changing!!
Boys don't come in!!
What? Why don't I have a costume?
Girls Changing!!
Boys don't come in!!
Because you're the understudy, Tachibana-chan.
Girls Changing!!
Boys don't come in!!
Of course we went with Dera-chan's measurements.
Girls Changing!!
Boys don't come in!!
Onodera's costume?
Wh-What's it like?
Ichijou-kun?
H-How cute is that?! She looks awesome in that!
What the hell?
She's absolutely adorable!
Does it look okay?
Y-Yeah... I mean... I think...
It looks great on you.
Thank you.
You look great too, Ichijou-kun. Very cool!
Really? Well, thanks!
Yes, really.
But damn, these costumes are well-made.
Like, they're really elaborate.
How would she look if she wore...
Hey! Why am I thinking about her again?
Moron!
And then...
No way! What do you mean? No way...
Unbelievable, right?
Why should I have to hide?
Damn it, this isn't going to work.
But she's the one with the nasty attitude.
Hey, Chitoge! Chitoge!
What?
Don't "what" me! I can't take this anymore.
That Four Eyes is totally suspicious of us.
We better let him see us acting chummy at least once.
Our guys are also worried that we haven't been seeing each other.
I know that you don't feel up to it, but...
At least while he's got his eyes on us, we should.
No. I'm through pretending to be close with you. I'm through being your girlfriend.
Knock it off, will you? This doesn't just affect the two of us!
Did you forget? If word gets out that we don't like each other,
then our families might start a war!
And if that happens...
Oh, shut up!
I just don't want to do it!
Why are you being so defiant about it?
I don't want to have anything to do with you now.
I don't want to talk to you, and I don't want to be near you.
Is that why you turned down the role of Juliet, too?
That's right! Me? Play Juliet to your Romeo?
In your dreams!
Your girlfriend?
Me? Play your girlfriend?
You and I are just two total strangers, aren't we?
Our families? Our situation?
Well, I don't care about any of that anymore!
What are you saying?
Two total strangers? In my dreams?
Why should I...
Why should I have to take all that?
Is that how you've felt all this time?
I always felt... You and I...
Having to fake being your boyfriend,
finding out that we'd already met years ago...
I'm not quite sure how to put it into words,
but I thought we had a connection,
and I thought you'd been feeling the same, lately.
Oh, is that right?
Fine, I hear you loud and clear. Total strangers, right?
There was never anything between you and me.
That's what you're saying, right?
I never once enjoyed hanging out with you.
We haven't gotten any closer,
and all my memories with you...
They're completely fake, all of them.
I'll bet that even the memory of that day ten years ago
was just a misunderstanding on your old man's part, wasn't it?
At the very least, no way were you the girl I made that promise to.
If we can't even get along now, no way would it have worked out back then.
Let's just forget about the lovers charade.
It's not like we had an obligation to go through with it anyway.
If we talk it over with our fathers, I'm sure they'll under—
I-Ichijou-kun?
Sorry, Onodera.
I'm stepping out for a minute.
But...
To tell you the truth, I'm already used to getting clobbered by her. But...
Damn it... A slap across the face hurts so much more.
Stupid! Stupid! That stupid bean sprout!
Stupid!
I'm so stupid.
Even I...
Bonyari High School
Culture Festival
The day of the Culture Festival.
Our debut's finally here, isn't it, Ichijou-kun?
Break a leg out there!
Right. Well, let's just do our best.
I asked Ichijou-kun later... but he wouldn't tell me anything about that day.
What happened between them?
Will Chitoge-chan even come to see the play?
Oh, hey! Kirisaki-san?
Sorry! I'm from Class B next door, and we're totally swamped and short-staffed right now!
I heard that you might be free,
so if you don't mind, could you help us out?
Sure.
Oh my gosh, I'm so nervous!
After all, I've never set foot on such a big stage as this one! But...
I've got to do my best.
Ichijou-kun will be there for me, so I'll be all right!
I rehearsed like crazy, and I've memorized my lines,
so I'll be fine!
I'm going to look over the script one more time.
Hey! That's dangerous!
Don't worry! I'm almost done anyway!
Look out!
Onodera?
Yeah, you totally sprained it.
I think the bone's fine, but...
Onodera, I'm sorry, but you can't...
Where's the understudy, Tachibana?
Apparently Tachibana-san caught a cold and is absent today.
I shall go to the Culture Festival...
Well, that puts us in a bind, huh?
Sensei, I can still do it!
You might think you can do it,
but you can barely walk as it is. You need to sit tight.
Hey, Romeo over there!
You stay by your Juliet's side for a bit. Don't let her do anything rash, okay?
I'm going to try to come up with a plan.
Everyone, continue with your preparations. That's it, dismissed!
Are you all right, Onodera?
Yes.
Onodera, you must've really wanted to play Juliet.
I wonder if there's anything I can do?
What am I going to do?
What if they go ahead and cancel the play? After everybody...
After everybody worked so hard!
Look at this costume.
They worked so hard to make it for me.
If the play gets canceled because of me, everything... It's all going to be for nothing!
I'm such a moron.
Even when she's hurt, she's still thinking about others before herself.
Me, on the other hand...
No way is this your fault!
I'll be damned if I let them cancel the play!
What am I doing here?
How did things end up like this?
Just seeing his face makes me brood,
and I can't seem to tell him what I really feel.
Why did I say those things to him that day?
If we were really dating,
do you think it would've worked out?
Of course there's no way it would work out, dummy.
I mean, you're just so not my type, you know?
You're not graceful, and you're violent.
We'd probably be fighting just like this all the time, anyway!
He's right. We were doomed to fail from the beginning.
Because we're polar opposites after all.
Our relationship... is just a sham.
Oh, just drop it.
At best, he completely hates me right now.
I'm sure this means the bridge is already burnt.
Found you!
I'm begging you. Take Onodera's place as Juliet!
H-Hey, come on! Hold up a second...
What do you mean, take Kosaki-chan's place?
Tell me what's going on!
Onodera just sprained her ankle in an accident, and now she can't go on stage.
Tachibana's absent today, too, so at this rate the play's gonna get canceled!
There's no one else but you who could play Juliet!
Wh-Why me?
There's no way I can play Juliet! I don't even know any of the lines.
Yeah, but we don't have any other options!
I know you hate my guts. I get it.
But...
I have a feeling that you and I could pull this off.
You and I've been putting on a play with our relationship all this time, right?
Even if you don't know your lines, I know we have what it takes if we just ad-lib the details.
Please! Help me out here!
How dare you?
After what you said at the beach...
You said it yourself, remember?
That there was no way that you and I would work out.
I know that you didn't want to be in the play with me, either. Am I right?
Just give me a straight answer! You hate me.
Don't you?
What the... Did she just... Is she telling me...
...that all this time, she's been brooding over what I said that day?
I didn't mean anything by that. It's nothing we haven't yelled at each other before, right?
No, of course it's not the same, idiot.
I really hurt her back there, and that's why she's been sulking.
I don't hate you.
Sorry. I didn't realize that what I said at the beach hurt your feelings.
And to be honest, it still hasn't completely set in.
But I do admit that I was way out of line.
So this time I'll be straight with you.
You're just not my type.
You're ungraceful, violent, and you lack any charm.
We'd probably fight non-stop, so I don't think it'd work out.
That's my straight answer.
But!
I don't hate you, not by a long shot.
I see.
Okay!
So you don't hate me, huh?
If you drag me down, I'll make you pay.
Romeo.