Good morning!
Kirisaki-san!
G-Good morning!
The other day,
your favorite soccer team won, didn't they?
Oh, so you watched last night's game!
Yep, that's right! That makes three games in a row!
Really, that's awesome!
I guess you could chalk it up to the "Friend Notebook."
Ever since that day,
Kirisaki has been slowly warming up to the class.
Well, she wasn't the shy type to begin with,
so maybe she just needed a little help getting back into her natural state.
Man, life is good!
Now this is the high school life that I dreamed of!
Even plants and animals sound like a blast to me now!
Well, good for you.
Hey, listen to this!
The girls and I made plans to go to McDonald's after school!
Are you jealous or what?
Is that right? I go there a lot too, you know.
Now if only I could break up with this little bean sprout, my life would be perfect!
Back at 'cha, Princess Gorilla.
For the longest time, she would only give me hostile looks,
but these days, I think I'm beginning to see her smile more often.
What are you staring at, you super-pervert? You're creeping me out!
Nope, she hasn't changed at all.
C'mon! We're going to get this done ASAP!
Hey, you help out, too!
Those two are seriously sewn at the hip. I have to hand it to them.
Yeah. Good for them.
They're totally hooked on each other.
How is that good? Where does that leave you?
What?
You have a crush on Ichijou-kun, don't you?
H-How long... How long have you...
Did you really think I couldn't tell? I'm amazed.
B-But Ichijou-kun has a girlfriend, you know!
I'd only come between them!
Oh?
And here I was convinced this whole time that Ichijou-kun had a thing for you too.
Wh-What?
N-No way! He can't possibly have a crush on me!
Really? From where I stand, it's painfully obvious.
To be honest, I wished you two would get together already and get it over with.
It was pretty irritating, you know.
I wish you would hold back a little, Ruri-chan.
And besides, nobody said you're not allowed to go after a boy
just because he's already in love with someone else.
Well, be that as it may...
Don't you worry, Kosaki.
I'll set up an opportunity for you.
Huh? Wait! Wait a second, Ruri-chan! What are you going to do?
Ichijou-kun!
Oh!
We'd like to hold a study group in your bedroom today. How about it?
Huh?!
Episode 4: The Visit
Ah...
el
co
m
e
We've been waiting for you, Young Master!
W
I hear you've got a study group with your friends planned for today!
That's right, I do. Can you bring us some tea?
Coming right up!
How did I land myself in this mess?
I don't have the slightest clue why Miyamoto would suddenly suggest a study group at my place,
but that's not the issue at hand!
Onodera's coming over! Am I allowed to be this blessed?
Thank you, God!
Why are you tagging along, Maiko-kun?
Now, now, where's the harm?
We're eyeglasses buddies, see?
How dare you pair us like that.
Don't tell me it was actually Onodera's idea,
and she just got Miyamoto to ask in her place?
D-Did she just look away? B-But why?
Really! Thanks a lot, Ruri-chan for putting strange ideas in my head!
What should I do? I can't look him in the face!
I-It's... It's going to be okay!
Calm down, Raku! Remember, your house is the headquarters of a yakuza clan, the Shuei-gumi!
I'm sure she's just super nervous!
So jittery...
Huh?
My heart won't stop... So jittery...
What's got you worked up? Why're you so jittery?
What... I'm not jittery, or excited, or anything!
Oh, so you were excited, then?
I-I can't help it, can I?
I've never been to a study group with my friends before.
Is it a bad thing for me to get excited?
Wow! So this is your room, Ichijou-kun?
Hey, I haven't been in here in ages, either. Everything's still the same, huh?
Whoa, this room is tiny! And it kind of smells funny.
It does not!
How could she say that in front of Onodera!
It smells like Ichijou-kun.
Oh!
Oh...
She looked away again!
Oh, no! I did it again!
Young Master, your tea is ready!
Y-Yeah.
Thanks, Ryu!
Oh, I'll help, too!
Whoa! Are you all right, Young Master?
Whoa! Are you all right, Onodera?
S-Sorry! I'm sorry!
No good... I'm so on edge I have no clue what I'm doing!
Just cool your head, and focus on your work!
Hey, Ruri-chan, can you solve this one?
Hm?
Hey, Ichijou-kun! I'd appreciate it if you showed Kosaki how to do this.
R-R-Ruri-chan!
Oh, sorry! It's way beyond me.
But you solved one that looked even harder the other day!
Never mind, just go! And don't you dare come back!
P-Please show me how to do this problem!
Whoa! Can you believe this development?
Onodera and I are so close!
Can you solve it?
I-I think so...
Oh, crap! My heart's pounding so hard that math is the last thing on my mind!
The sound of my heartbeat is unbelievable!
I bet even Onodera can hear it!
Anyway, the fact is she's asking me for help.
So I gotta play it cool, and...
Oh? Hey, this is pretty tough.
Oh, that one!
You've got to substitute the variable a first, or else it's unsolvable.
What's your deal? Worry about your own homework.
I'm already done.
Huh? She assigned us three worksheets for homework—
U-Unbelievable!
And here I thought that I had the upper hand in schoolwork!
What were your grades like in the US, Kirisaki-san?
Mostly A's, I guess.
Hey, Onodera, I'm pretty good with schoolwork. Want me to help?
What?
You just take this, and do this...
Wow! That's amazing! I got it! Your explanation makes so much sense!
Heh!
Kirisaki, you'll pay for this...
Hey, hey... By the way, Onodera-san...
Do you have a crush on anybody?
Is that a question you just suddenly ask a person?
Suddenly? Look, it's freaking girl talk.
Huh? Was that a weird question?
R-Right now, I don't think of anyone like that.
I see.
Right now, I don't think of anyone like that.
I see! I see... So Onodera isn't into anyone!
Good job, Kirisaki!
I see! I don't have anyone like that now, either!
I really hope I can meet that special someone soon.
But it's just so hard, you know?
J-Joking, I'm joking! That was a joke!
H-Hey, that was mean, honey.
Don't say those things when you've got me!
S-So sorry, darling! I just wanted to tease you a little.
J-Jeez, what am I gonna do with you?
Oh, okay! You two sure are chummy!
Hey, hey, Kirisaki-san—can I ask you something, too?
Huh?
Spill the beans... How far have you two gone?
H-How? How? How? How far?
How far have we gone—what exactly do you mean?
Oh, come on, you know, ki—
You! Come with me!
Huh? What's gotten into you?
What's going on, Raku? You gave me a shock!
Listen to me! Now's as good a time as ever, so I'm gonna tell you the truth.
Now listen up!
Huh?
And don't you dare tell anyone else either!
I get it. So that's why you've been pretending to be a couple.
What the hell? So you were onto us? You knew we were pretending to be a couple?
Well, hey, it was pretty obvious from my end.
But to be perfectly honest...
Raku, I couldn't be more jealous!
How could you get a girlfriend before me?!
That was about when I figured it out.
That was right at the beginning!
Damn it, you humiliated me knowing full well that we were pretending?
Well, do you really think I could've resisted the urge?
This is why I didn't want to tell him!
So, you'd rather not have Onodera actually fall for your act the whole three years, if at all possible.
Well, yeah.
Then, hey, it couldn't be any simpler. Just tell her how you feel!
As if I could do something like that!
Really? I happen to think the odds are in your favor.
Huh?
Because Onodera has a crush on you!
What?
What... No way...
I mean, come on, there's no way she'd...
But...
You sure took your sweet time.
Uh... Yeah...
But if it's really true that Onodera has a thing for me...
We got a lot done, huh?
Yeah, we sure did!
How perfect would that make my life?
Hm...
This is bad, Young Master and the Mistress haven't gotten
very far in their relationship, eh?
He finally brings her home, but with a whole bunch of other friends.
Looks like it's time for us to give them a little nudge. Whaddya say?
Jeez, what's the big idea, randomly calling us out here?
I was enjoying myself, you know!
Well, apparently there's some expensive tea in the storehouse out back
and they want us to come get it.
Well, I guess it was good timing.
I mean, I was so self-conscious with Onodera around.
Just being in the same room made it hard to breathe.
Oh!
Is this the storehouse they were talking about?
Yeah, that's right. They said we can't miss it once we're inside.
What's wrong? Come on in.
You hurry up and get it.
What the hell? You could at least give me a—
No!
Okay, whatever.
I really can't figure you out...
What the—
Ouch!
Oh!
What... What the hell?
Please forgive us!
Go for it, Young Master.
This is as far as we can take you!
Hey! Damn it...
What do you think you're doing? Open the door!
They got us. This is why they called us.
Right now, I'll bet they're like, "This is as far as we can take you!"
or something.
Well, but still. There's a window and a ladder,
so it's not like we couldn't get out if we put our minds to it.
Are you okay, Kirisaki?
I'm so sorry! Thanks to my guys, we're stuck.
Hey, you've been unusually quiet for the last few minutes...
Huh... Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
Hey... Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
K-Kirisaki-san?!
Sh-Shut up! Just be quiet for a minute!
And if you look at me, I'll smash your face in, got it?
Hey, don't tell me...
You're afraid?
Geh!
I told you I'd smash your face in if you looked at me, didn't I?
I can't catch a break!
It makes me uncomfortable.
I've been afraid of dark, cramped spaces since I was little. Like this storehouse.
A long time ago I got stuck inside a washing machine and couldn't move for five hours.
How exactly did that happen?
I-I'm not clinging to you because I want to!
I-It's all I can do to keep myself calm.
If you get the point, then just shut up and let me keep clinging!
What the hell? She's totally different from her usual self!
Who knew that she had this side to her?
Looking at her now,
I finally realize that she's just like any other girl.
Until this moment, I'd never really thought of her as one, but...
Whoa, talk about in-my-face!
What am I gonna do? I can hear the whisper of her breath!
Her eyes... are glistening with tears.
Damn, her eyes are so big, they're adorable. And check out those eyelashes!
There's the scent of a shampoo I've never smelled before as well.
Plus, I can feel her warmth on my back!
Her lips are sparkling... and they look so soft... for some reason.
I know I've ignored her till now, but this girl's pretty hot!
Wait, what the hell am I thinking?
When I've already got... When I've already decided who to give my heart to—Onodera!
I mean, being alone with a girl in this situation in a locked room like this
is already questionable in more ways than one...
Hey!
Hey, see that?
A ladder!
Can't we use that to get out through the window up there?
Huh?
Sure, we could probably get out that way,
but are you in any shape to climb?
No, I guess not.
But at least if you got out first, and went to get somebody.
Don't be ridiculous!
As if I could leave behind someone who's in as sorry shape as you!
The last thing I need is for you to start sobbing on me afterwards.
If we just give it some time, they'll come back for us.
Anyway, I'm keeping you company, so don't give me that bravado!
What the...
What's with you playing the cool guy now?
You playing Mr. Cool isn't going to get us very...
Well, hey, excuse me for trying...
Then... Then, keep talking to me. I'm fine with anything.
If you go quiet again, I'll start to get scared.
Huh? What am I supposed to...
You know, like some awesome story, or...
You're really putting me on the spot, you know!
I can't just suddenly pull something out of thin air.
Oh! Okay, then... How do you feel about Onodera-san?
H-How? How do I...
Huh? You know what I mean.
She's a really great person, don't you think?
She's cute, and so sweet.
I have a feeling that she and I could be great friends.
Well, I admit Onodera's pretty great.
I mean, she's both caring and affable.
On top of that, she's hot, and well-groomed, and adorable, and feminine,
and she's got a beautiful smile...
She's absolutely the ideal girl, you know?
By any chance, do you think Onodera-san's...
Oh, crap! I gushed too hard!
the greatest?
I agree! She gives of this totally feminine aura!
You get what I'm saying, don't you?
Thank God she's so dense!
Come to think of it, a while ago Shu asked me something.
Why is everyone so hung up about whether you've ever been kissed or not?
Oh...
Who cares about that stuff?
Sure, being somewhat interested myself—I can understand, but still...
Well, don't look at me.
Well, the one thing I do know for sure
is that I'd rather die than have to kiss you!
Yeah? Right back at you!
As if you've ever kissed someone!
What the hell? Are you saying you have?
And for your information, I've kissed tons of people!
And overseas, kissing is our way of saying hello, so there!
We're talking about kissing on the lips, not your goddamn cheeks!
Shut up! What's so special about a smack on the lips?
A kiss is a kiss!
The difference between a romantic kiss and a friendly one is difference between day and night!
Oh, shut up, like you've ever done it before, either!
It's better than acting like a kiss on the cheek counts!
Shut up! You'll never kiss anyone as long as you live, anyway!
Who are you to talk, you gorilla girl!
Huh?
For some reason, I'm not that freaked out anymore.
I think I'm okay to climb the ladder now.
All right! In that case, let's get the hell out of here.
Whoa!
Hey! Look out!
M-Move...
You first.
Mistress!
Are you safe, Mistress?
You were taking so long to come home that I contacted the yakuza, and...
You punk... You two may be boyfriend and girlfriend...
But don't you think it's too soon for such antics?
This isn't what it looks like!
Oh! Ichijou-kun!
There you are! Thank goodness, I was worried—
Hey... Onodera?
S-Sorry for barging in!
And so, this adventure-filled study group...
Are you all right, Young Miss?
This is a huge misunderstanding!
came to a close, as I somehow lost many things that were important to me.
Ichijou Raku (bean sprout)
He's such a nag, starting to act like my superior...
Not only is he annoying, he can't stop lecturing me,
and he really, really pisses me off!
Ichijou Raku (bean sprout)
Don't you dare let this go to your head, all right?
Stupid bean sprout!
...He does have some good qualities.
...Possibly. Probably...
It could just
be my imagination.
He's a bean sprout, after all.
Maiko Shuu and Miyamoto Ruri
I'm going to use the bathroom, okay?
Go on!
So it's just the two of us now, huh?
Hey, hey, Ruri-chan, can I ask you something?
What?
Have you like, ever been kissed, Ruri-chan?
Just look at your face!
I am in no way obligated to answer that.
Anyway, when did I give you permission to address me casually?
Now, now, where's the harm? We're glasses buddies!
Cut that out!
Never mind that. You're Ichijou-kun's friend, aren't you?
Don't you think it's strange?
What's strange?
Him and Kirisaki-san, that's what!
It just doesn't feel like they're actually dating.
Don't say such things! It's cruel to a couple pursuing pure love!
I feel bad that I have to doubt Kirisaki-san, but I'm a little suspicious of those two.
I bet you know something about it...
Huh? Kirisaki-san? What are you doing there?
Just kidding!
I'm so gonna rip this guy a new one.
You've been deceived!
Um, where's the bathroom?
To the right of the stairs.