All right then, Raku-sama.
See you tomorrow!
Have a nice day.
Okay then, see ya.
Man, I’m tired.
kimi ni utai kikasetai koto
There's something I want to tell you
kowarenai you ni daiji ni shisugichatte sa
But I've been holding it too dear, afraid it might break
kyou mo meeru wo tsuzutte wa mata
Today I write you a message again
kuuhaku de nurikaete chigitte shimau no
Only to wipe it clean and discard it
konna itsumo wo fukitobasu kikkake wo
A chance to break this cycle
maneku bakari no yubisaki wo
Lies in my fingertips
tenohira de kasanete
That I'm holding up with my hand
ima wo kaeru koto wa tsurai koto mo aru kedo
Changing the status quo can be painful
tatoe piisu ga sorottemo
But even when all the pieces are gathered
kono te de michibikanakya
I still need to put them together myself
daiji na ima wo tebanasu no wa kowai yo ne
As much as I'm scared to let go of the present I cherish
demo machinozonda subete wa soko ni aru no
Everything I've been waiting for is there
soko ni aru no
It's all there
Work
So... it seems Tachibana has had some reason to leave early recently.
Huh, really?
Maybe she's got something to do after school.
That so? I never really noticed.
I see.
Oh hey, wanna head over to a restaurant?
I'm really in the mood for some fries.
That's pretty random.
It's okay with me.
Guest
Welcome!
Dear customer, how many in your party?
Oh,
My, if it isn’t Raku-sama!
Could it be you came to see little ol' me?
I’m so glad!
What are you doing?
Huh, so you're working part time at this family restaurant.
I really didn't see that coming.
Yes, my father said that I should learn what it's like in the real world so...
But... can you even hold down a part time job?
My, that's not very nice of you, Kirisaki-san.
You might have that opinion of me, but I can handle things better than most.
Tachibana-chwan! You need to be faster!
There's 7 orders waiting to be filled!
My, my, manager,
you know nothing good comes form rushing things.
You're not in a position to be telling me that!
Now I'm worried.
Anyway, let's get this order going.
I’ll have the french fries.
And I’ll have the anmitsu sundae.
Right away!
Do you think she's going to be all right?
Yeah... I don't know... Maybe?
All right. I guess I could check in while I'm up getting some more water.
Banabana Fair
Tachibana-chan!
You dropped another plate!
How many dozen does that make now?!
This can't possibly end well!
Marika
You're right, manager.
These plates are really slippery.
You should probably file a complaint with headquarters!
You’re the only one who has dropped this many!
Just leave it. Go take the food to the table for now...
And listen, no being rude to the customers.
Manager
Okay! Right away, manager!
And be sure to tell the customers about their food!
Understood!
Whoa there...
A minute ago...
Sorry for the wait!
Here you are!
This is your cheap piece of meat.
Hey!
T-Tachibana-chwan!
Yes, whatever could you want?
Well?
I... probably shouldn't have gone.
What?
Raku-sama!
Sorry for the wait!
Oh, it’s here!
And here you are.
And for you, Raku-sama.
Your anmitsu sundae.
Now just hold on a minute!
My, whatever is wrong, Kirisaki-san?
Don’t act like you don't know!
Why does he get so much more than me?!
Why do I only get one fry?!
And that mountain of ice cream! I've never seen one so big!
My, my, you sure are spoiled, Kirisaki-san.
Oh well.
Here's some ketchup on the house to make it up to you.
What do I do now?! It's rude to leave food behind!
Tachibana-chan!
You're needed at the table over here, please!
Yes, sir! Coming!
Do you two go to school with Tachibana-chan?
Huh? Oh, we do.
Sorry about our classmate causing all these problems.
That's just how she is.
Don't worry about it, I'm used to her.
Even with the way she is, she's a valued member of our staff.
Banabana Fair
Huh?
You see, while she may mess up countless times,
she never lets it get to her.
She’s always cheerful and bright.
And everybody just adores her.
So much so that some customers come just to see her.
Huh.
Manager
Just...
If she could just do her job a bit better I wouldn't have any complaints.
Do you want to know just how many plates she's dropped so far?
I don't even want to try.
Welcome!
Man, I'm hungry.
It’s been a while since we've been to a family restaurant.
What'll you have, Ryu-san?
R-Ryu! What are you guys doing here?
Oh, young master!
What a coincidence!
Uh, friends of yours?
Yeah... kind of...
Listen, Ryu...
You’d better not cause any trouble.
Don't cause any problems for the other customers!
Sure thing, young master!
We would never cause problems for you.
And for the others... yeah?
Crazy coincidences like that really do happen, huh.
Yeah, I just hope nothing happens.
Welcome!
Now then, what to order.
Yeah, these Japanese family restaurants have great food huh.
Don’t get carried away now, guys.
Well, well.
Didn't think we'd run into you here, Mistress.
That’s my line.
Rest assured, Mistress.
We've disciplined ourselves so as
to not cause you any problems.
I see. Then you better not.
Hey, what the heck is going on?!
Why are all my people here too?
How would I know?!
All we can do now is pray that nothing will happen.
Well, well,
if it isn't the Shuuei gang.
I was wondering where that awful stench was coming from.
Well, well, if it isn't the leader of the Beehive gang.
What a nice cologne you're using.
Do I detect a hint of pig piss?
What'd you say?!
Things are already getting bad!
H-Hold on just a minute! What do we do about this?
Dumbass, now that it's come to this there's only one thing we can do.
Hang on a second, you guys.
We just talked about this didn't we?
You need to behave yourselves.
We're in the middle of a date
and we'd like it if you didn't interrupt, okay?
Oh! I’m so sorry! I just lost my temper.
I'm sorry aswell, Mistress.
Raku-sama!
I'm on my break now so how about we have some tea together?
Tachibana!
Hey, kid!
Who is that girl?
I didn't know you had a lover.
Whoa! Hold on now!
Shut it, four-eyes!
With all the virility the young master has it's no wonder he needs more than one girl to be satisfied!
You guys need to cool it too!
Huh? Who are these people?
Jeez, you...!
Practice is finally over!
Man, was that tough!
I want a melon soda.
You sure do love your sweets, Captain.
What?
Are they... the riot task force?
What are they doing here?
Huh? What's this? Miss Marika!
Why are you here?
What?! She’s Commissioner Tachibana’s daughter?!
Oh, Migisuke.
What a strange place to run into you.
They’re Tachibana's friends?!
This is madness!
We've got our hands full with the Yakuza already,
if you mix in the police...
What's this? I thought I'd seen you before.
Why is society's garbage just sitting around here eating all casual-like?
Ah, I knew this was going to happen!
Well, well...
Fancy seeing the commander-in-chief of the riot task force here, too.
So I take it this means war?
Something needs to be done... and fast!
Claude, calm down!
Stand back, Mistress.
The Beehive never backs down from a fight.
Ryu, let's talk about thi—
Let's do this you bastards!
Attack!
Oh no! Oh no! What do we do now?!
They're messing up the restaurant more and more with every passing second!
I wonder what all this is about.
How can we run a business like this?!
Huh?
Guest
Cannot conduct business
Out of
Business
Guest
Out of
Business
Guest
Out of
Business
Guest
Out of
Business
Guest
Out of
Business
Guest
Out of
Business
Guest
Out of
Business
Guest
Out of
Business
Guest
Out of
Business
Guest
Out of
Business
Guest
Out of
Business
Guest
Out of
Business
Guest
Out of
Business
Guest
Out of
Business
Guest
Out of
Business
Guest
Out of
Business
Guest
Out of
Business
Guest
Out of
Business
Guest
Out of
Business
Guest
The restaurant can’t make any money
The restaurant will be demolished
I’ll be out of a job
I said knock it off!
Who... is this girl?
Tachibana?
Miss Marika!
You're in danger! Get away!
We'll handle—
What is wrong with you people?!
You're in a family restaurant!
You aren't the only ones in here you know?!
If you want to fight... take it outside!
Thank you for coming.
Wha...
For real?
Yeah, I really didn't expect that out of Marika.
I never thought you could be so brave.
But thank god you did it.
The manager appreciated it, too.
Tachibana-chwan! Thank you!
I didn't want you to see such a shameful side of me.
But I'm surprised you, who's never cared about anything
outside her own interests, went that far for some part-time job.
Huh?
That's so you, Raku-sama.
You're right. I'm actually working this part time job for a very special reason.
I wanted to keep it a secret, though.
A secret?
Yes, you see...
I thought I'd save up for our wedding ceremony!
I want to earn what's important to me through sweat and hard work.
And one day, I want to have enough money saved up to build
a big white house with a spacious backyard on a small hill overlooking the sea!
And have a big dog and two children!
I want the first one to be a girl!
That’s so like you, it’s not even funny.
Do you know how much time you'd have to spend working if you want to buy a house through a part-time job?
Geez, stop going on about stupid things like that
and think of a better way to use your—
My, Raku-sama...
I'm serious about what I said.
Huh?
Now then, you two have a nice night!
I can't help but admire her.
Yeah...
I’m home.
Today was quite tiresome as well.
What about you, Ra-kun?
What kind of house do you want to live in when you're older?
Hm? A house?
Well, one where you can see the sea,
someplace high up.
A big house too! With dogs and lots of other animals!
And it’ll have wings and walk around!
Salary
Change
Ｓｈｕｕｅｉ
Ｇｒｏｕｐ
Happy          New        Year
New Year's Day.
Chitoge said she'd be coming by to say hello,
so we figured we'd eat at my place.
Young master!
Ichijou
You have a visitor!
Ichioka
Oosera
Imamura
Hanoi
Bon
Kibou
Shimozuru
Kira
Mukae
Good grief.
She really doesn't need to stop by just to say hello.
Morning, Chito—
ge?!
Happy New Year!
Happy New Year, Raku-sama!
Hey, Raku!
Happy New Year!
Happy New Year, Ichijou-kun.
W-Why are you all here?
And you're all wearing kimonos!
So? Did we surprise you?
After talking with everyone, we figured we'd all just go together,
and since we're all here, we thought we'd go to the first shrine visit of the year right after.
Hold on, I'm not sure I have enough food for everyon—
Young master! Just heard from the miss. She said she made enough food for everyone!
Hey, hey, hey. You're in on this too?
Coming in. Welp, That's that.
Hey, hey, hey!
I'm so jealous, Raku.
You get to have an armada of cute girls at your place for New Year's.
That sounds so nice.
I wasn't planning on everyone just showing up.
By the way, do you normally lounge around in clothes like that?
This place is so nice.
What’s with that notebook?
Does this look weird?
Nope! Not at all!
Good.
Coming in!
I'm in his room again!
This food looks amazing!
Welcome!
Treasure
Sushi
Well yeah, it was so sudden that it took me by surprise, but Shuu's right.
It's really nice having all these girls at my place for New Year's.
It’s like aroma therapy!
Where should we sit?
I'd guess wherever we’d like?
Then, miss, you sit over here.
It’s like aroma therapy!
Hey, darling,
got any sweets or the like?
Some kind of dessert...
Go get one.
You really eat a lot.
Jeez.
When are we going for the shrine visit?
Let's just take our time.
Did we even have anything sweet here?
She doesn’t like Japanese sweets so...
Hm?
Chocolate?
I guess this'll do.
I don’t really know what this is, but it's good.
Hey, honey, I found one.
Thanks!
Guys, pass this around!
Hey! Let’s play karuta! Karuta...
Jeez, everything's so peaceful.
Huh? What was that sound just now?
Huh? Honey, what's wrong? Weren't you going to play Karuta with everyone?
Hey, darling...
Have you ever kissed a girl before?
What?!
What's with you all of the sudden?
Well, I haven’t, but...
I already told you that before—
Then,
want to kiss me?
What?!
W-What's gotten into you?!
Do you even know what you're saying?!
Hey, what’s wrong?
Your face is kind of red.
Hm?
It's the chocolate I brought up...
Whisky Bon Bon?
D-Don’t tell me...
You’re drunk?!
This is ridiculous.
You're that old and you haven't even kissed a girl yet?
That’s so lame.
So like, I could kiss you, if you want.
Come on, let's kiss. Kiss me!
Ah! Calm down, Chitoge!
You wouldn't normally be asking that!
Come on, please?
I don't want a kiss from you!
Come on...
Not happening!
I said no!
But you kissed Marika!
Hey, Raku.
What've you been doing?
Shuu! Good timing!
Listen to me—
What? Off Whisky Bon Bons?
I had two or three myself.
I guess Kirisaki-san is, like, super bad with alcohol.
Hm, but...
There's something about girls who can't handle alcohol.
They're just so cute!
What is he going on about at a time like this?
What's wrong with you?!
Shuu!
Tachibana?
Rakkun’s here!
Rakkun! Rakkun!
Tachibana! Don’t tell me you too...
Rakkun.
The crazy Rakkun.
Kidding.
But... that wasn't funny.
Say "uncle", Maiko-san.
Say it.
If you don't your glasses are going to break.
Tachibana, stop! He’s done!
Crap! This is worse than I thought it'd be!
Ichijou Raku.
Huh? Oh, Tsugumi!
Glad to see you're okay.
Y-Yeah. Of course.
Um, Tsugumi-san. What are you...?
Your lips look so soft...
Nope! She doesn't seem okay in the slightest!
T-Tsugumi... what are you trying to...?
Huh? What do you mean? I'm just going to put my lips against yours.
"Just going to put my lips against yours"?
Hey!
Seriously!
Wait! Wait!
Hey, Tsugumi!
Your lips aren't as soft as I thought they would be.
That was a close one.
Looks like you have your hands full, huh, Ichijou-kun?
Huh?
Oh, Miyamoto!
I knew you’d be all right.
I just had a feeling.
Yes, of course.
But Japan is in a sticky situation right now.
What?
Our growing pile of national debt is at its breaking point.
Female Employment Rate
Male Employment Rate
Rate of Increase for Employment
(Right Hand Scale)
Females
Males
There are still no signs of improvement in our current employment rates.
3,000 000
People
Number of Births
First Baby Boom
2,700,000
Birth Rate
Total Fertility Rate
Population
Statistics
And the fact that Japanese birth rates are in decline is causing all kinds of bad things to happen in society.
43rd Year of the sexagenary cycle
1,360,000 People
Second Baby Boom
2,090,000
1,210,000 People
Plus, all the government cares about is raising the taxes!
And—
Aging & Declining Birth
Self-Sufficiency
This is bad. Miyamoto's had it too!
Tax Increase
Recession & Economic Crisis
Pension Failure
Cumulative Debt
And there's still no sign of improvement for—
Oh right! Onodera?!
What happened to Onodera?!
Ah! It’s Ichijou-kun!
Yay!
It’s Ichijou-kun!
O-Onodera, are you okay?
She sure doesn’t look like it.
I’m kind of... really light headed... it feels great.
H-Hold on a minute. I’m going to go get everyone some cold water.
Yeah... it's really hot in here...
What?
W-What's wrong with you?!
Stop! Stop!
Huh? What am I doing, you ask?
Huh?
Ichijou-kun, untie this for me.
It's just so hot in here.
Come on, take my clothes off.
No, that's impossible!
Operation   Off / On
Dry
Auto
Fan
Louver
There! I turned on the AC!
It’s on now!
You're no fun.
Huh?
Ichijou-kun, your skin’s so pretty.
Just like a girl’s.
It’s so nice. I’m jealous.
So smooth.
Stop it!
And your hair’s so slick and soft.
Let me touch you some more.
I can't do this! I can't stop her!
I can't stay here any longer!
Temporary retreat!
Hey.
Can I ask you something?
What?
Ch-Chitoge?
Do you... like me?
What?!
Well, come on, do you or not?
Well I mean...
Of course I love you.
As "lovers", yeah?
That isn't what I was asking!
You know, like when a guy and a girl like each other.
I mean, we're lovers right?
Then...
Tell me you love me, dummy!
But I just did!
I'm scared...
“I love you...” You have to say it right.
If you don't then I'll have to tear your clothes off and have some fun.
What?!
What's that? I'll join in too.
Me too.
I’m going to do it.
W-Wait, you guys!
Calm down and let's talk about this!
Please, just leave me be!
Tsugumi!
Wait! what are you guys going to do to me?!
Please, don't do it!
Please! Help me!
Hel—
Why was I sleeping?
You all just showed up today...
And then...
Huh?
I can't remember anything.
I feel like I had this really scary dream.
Well whatever. My head kinda hurts anyways.
I’m going get a little more sleep.
Nothing happened today.
Isn’t that right, everyone?
Right.
kirameki dashita yume wo
Those twinkling dreams...
nozokikomu kagami hajimete no hyoujou
I peek into the mirror, and see my expression for the first time
sugu saki no tobira akete mitai na
I have an urge to open that door that lies right ahead
naname ni rouka wo yokogittara
I cross the hallway diagonally
guuzen no ito ga (kimi to)
And the thread of coincidence (with you)
butsukari karamaru
Ties me up with you, and we bump into each other
mado aketa te ha
The hand that opened the window
koi wo watashi yori
Bearing my love
rikai shiteita you de
As if it understood
kimi he to tebutta
It gestured towards you
mousou daiarii tokimeki dashite saigo ni nokoru omoi
After the diary of delusion makes my heart flutter, the feelings that it leaves behind...
donna? donna iro? hoshii kotae kaiteinai
What kind are they? What color are they? The answer I seek isn’t written inside
seorii nani mo wakattenai noni
Theories cannot comprehend anything
sagasu mirai kitto matteru hazu
I’m sure the future I’m searching for is waiting out there somewhere
kioku tadotte ima no atarashii yume tsukurou
Let’s pursue our memories, and create a new dream starting now