Falling in love is such a pain.
You're constantly on an emotional roller coaster, overreacting to the smallest of things.
I mean, if you're brave enough
it can all be yours.
I've never fallen in love before.
But by observing
through these glasses, I can tell who likes who.
Huh?
Where are...
my glasses?
I want to hear your memories unfold, so this is for you
kioku ga hiraku oto kikitaikara kimi ni sashidasou
No matter how precious this feeling may be
aa konna nimo taisetsu na omoi mo
The sands of time are going to cover it up
toki no suna ga ooikakushite
And make it ambiguous
aimai ni shiteshimau
But don't say that fate is a cheap word
keredo unmei nante kotoba wa cheap da nante
Since you're always laughing by my side,
issho ni waraiatteru
You could be the one
kimi ga sono hito dattari surunokana
See, everyone slowly forgets something
kitto minna daiji na koto
No matter how important
sukoshizutsu wasureteikukara
So can I entrust you for a bit
kimi to no omoide wa
With my memories of you?
wazuka dake demo takusaseteyo
I have the last missing piece of this incomplete puzzle
sorouhazunai puzzle kakushiteta saigo no kakera
I want to hear your memories unfold, so this is for you
kioku ga hiraku oto kikitaikara kimi ni sashidasou
Losing Something
Huh?
You lost your glasses, Miyamoto?
Apparently.
While in the hallway, I noticed my glasses were dirty.
I went to the classroom to grab my cleaning cloth,
but when I got back...
Huh?
I, of course, assumed they fell into the courtyard
and went looking for them.
But they were nowhere to be found.
You don't have your glasses on.
Of course it'd be difficult to find them.
All right. I'll help you look for them.
Where did they fall?
I'm grateful.
I wonder if there's anyone else who can help us look.
Like Chitoge-chan, or Tsugumi-chan.
Those two said they had plans today. They just left.
Tachibana has also gone home.
Yahoo! Did I hear you say you lost your glasses?
I'll help out too!
No thanks.
I don't want to be in your debt.
So cold.
We're glasses-buddies, aren't we?
Don't lump us together because of that.
No, wait! Don't try and find your glasses!
Because you look amazing without them, Ruri-chan!
Let's go.
With three of us on the job, we'll find them in no time.
O-Okay.
Miyamoto!
Ruri-chan!
Are you all right?
Is your vision really that bad?
My vision's gotten much worse lately.
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
Ichijou-kun, could you go on ahead?
I'll catch up later.
Huh?
That's not me!
This is serious, isn't it?
I'll stick with you,
so let's go look for them together.
Sorry for the trouble.
Ah! Ruri-chan, look!
I found your glasses! See? See?
Oh? Where in the world were they?
Too bad!
These are actually my glasses!
Fooled ya!
I thought you couldn't see!
Maybe someone brought them to the staff room.
I went there earlier. No luck.
I'm going to wait a little longer, then I'll go check again.
So they fell somewhere around here?
I think so.
If they fell over here,
we should have been able to find them right away.
Oh, here they are!
Huh? Really?
Tanaka
My mistake. It's a slipper.
How, even for a second, could you mistake those for glasses?
That's a water bottle!
Certain
Victory
That's a daruma doll!
Certain
Victory
What are those things even doing here?
We can't find them anywhere.
If they're not here, where are they?
Flash!
It's possible I dropped them over there.
Huh? You have another idea for where they might be?
Behind the special-use building.
There's a dark thicket where people seldom go.
I was there earlier
doing head-shaking exercises.
What are “head-shaking exercises”?
Onodera
I may have dropped my glasses there.
Sorry, but since my eyes are of no use,
could the two of you go and look for them?
What? Did that actually happen?
Didn't you put them down by the window?
H-Hang on!
Ruri-chan!
What are you saying?!
There's no need to set it up so the two of us are alone!
Eveen 'do you'd lak it.
Now's your chance to speak with him in private.
I'll be fine.
Don't waste this opportunity.
No matter what you do there, no one will hear you.
It's the perfect place to pounce on someone.
Kosaki.
Huh? What are you talking about?
That's Ichijou-kun!
Geez!
I'm going to check the staff room.
Someone might have finally brought them there.
See you later!
She just can't be honest about it.
What were you talking about just now?
Oh, nothing.
You sure say weird things sometimes.
That is only your perception of it, Ichijou-kun.
Come to think of it,
it's rare that I get a chance to talk to Miyamoto.
It's just like in middle school.
I guess it's been different since that day at the pool.
H-Hey, Miyamoto.
What is it?
I-It's a little sudden, but...
Does Onodera have anyone she likes?
Why do I have to be the one to tell you that?
S-Sorry I asked!
You really haven't noticed?
Huh?
Who Kosaki likes.
There is someone!!?
P
Someone that     she likes!!?
That Onodera likes!!?
P
What a blockhead.
He's either completely clueless
or an idiot.
Come over here!
I thought Kosaki was the same.
So why...?
You are truly blind.
Even more so than the glasses-less me.
If you gave a little more thought to the girl
who's always by your side...
By my side?
You mean Chitoge?
I mean Kosaki!
There's no way you still haven't figured it out.
Why are you two so...?
If you would just pay a little...
a little more attention to her...
Even I noticed...
It's obvious...
Can you really not see it?
If I pay more attention to her?
Is she saying I'm not paying attention to Onodera?
What do you mean?
I'm not paying attention?
On the contrary, I'm watching her every day!
You're not looking!
I have no idea what you're saying!
Can't you make it simpler?
I'm getting annoyed...
What I'm saying is...
The person that Kosaki likes
is y-
Tada!
How's it going? Found your glasses yet?
Certain
Victory
Shuu, what the hell are you doing?
I just happened to spot the two of you...
So I thought I'd listen in.
What are you doing here?
I told you I don't want your help.
I'm not here to help.
I'm heading home.
Huh? Maiko-kun?
Onodera, how'd it go?
No use.
No one's picked them up.
Maybe they're still in the hallway.
Then let's go check upstairs again.
Ruri-chan, we're going to check upstairs.
You stay here.
Okay.
Thank you.
There's no point in trying to force it.
So you did do that on purpose.
What's so wrong with it?
They both like each other.
I just want them to tell each other.
It's irritating to watch them.
Isn't it kind of me to help them out?
It certainly is kind to help them out.
But...
At the end of the day, they have to be the ones
who work up the courage to confess.
Why? The result would be the same.
It may seem that way, but in reality, it's different.
When it comes to emotions,
things that you acquired on your own
and things others helped you acquire are weighted differently.
You act as if you're an expert.
Even though you've never liked anyone.
That's not true. There's someone I like.
Ah, I see. Don't care though.
Personally,
I'd love to see my dear friend
overcome that hurdle and find happiness.
Because Raku's a great guy.
I feel the same.
Hey, Miyamoto!
Your glasses!
We found them!
What happened? You're all banged up.
Where were they?
Well, you see...
I never would have thought they'd be there.
It really was somewhere we'd never look!
Yeah! Not a place you'd expect to find glasses!
Where were they?
It was all thanks to Onodera
that we were able to find them!
No, it was Ichijou-kun who gave me a hint,
so he's the one who found them!
Oh no, not at all!
But just what was Miyamoto trying to tell me yesterday?
I'm not paying attention to Onodera?
That's great!
Onodera has somebody she likes?
Since she let that slip...
I couldn't sleep a wink last night!
What am I going to do?
Farewell!
Ichijou-kun.
Hm?
When I said Kosaki has somebody she likes...
I was joking.
Damn you, Miyamoto!
That was a cruel joke!
Oh? What was so cruel about it?
N-No, it's n-nothing.
Well, that's all I wanted to say.
Thank God!
I don't know how, but Onodera doesn't have anybody she likes!
I'm going to sleep like a baby tonight!
Yahoo!
Ichijou-kun!
Have a minute?
Yeah! What is it?
I guess I'll let you off the hook this time.
Since we're glasses-buddies.
Shrine Maidens
New Years Eve.
My dad asked us to work at
one of the neighborhood shrines.
Damn it's cold!
But my old man sure is a slave driver.
Even though we've finally got a holiday.
Is the priest here an acquaintance of your dad's?
Heh. Well I, on the other hand, am stoked.
Huh? Why?
That's because...
Raku-sama!
What do you think?
Do these shrine maiden clothes suit me?
You look great, Marika-chan!
They look really good on you!
I wasn't asking you.
This is what I'm talking about!
It's all about the shrine maidens! The shrine maidens!
You don't often get to see such a cute shrine maiden!
You ought to be grateful to your old man!
I don't get it.
Hold it right there! Tachibana Marika!
Don't ditch your work!
You've been taking breaks whenever you want!
Seishirou-chan, you look amazing too! So pretty!
And you guys! What do you think you're doing?
Get back to work!
We're on break!
You sure are in high spirits, Shuu.
If you're going to laugh, go right ahead.
Huh? What is there to laugh at?
No... well... there's not...
I finally finished changing.
That sure took a long time.
What?
Sorry to make you wait, Ichijou-kun.
What the hell? What's wrong with you? Are you okay?
Ichijou-kun?
I'm fine. Totally fine.
Shuu...
Shrine maidens...
sure are great.
Right?
Now that I've seen everyone in shrine maiden outfits,
let's get back to practicing the Lion Dance, Raku!
Ruri-chan, nicely done.
Oh! That girl in traditional garb is cute as hell!
I-don't-really-care-what-you-look-at-
but-you're-pissing-me-off punch!
What's wrong? Are you sick?
I don't think so. But I've been unusually cold all day.
All right, I'm heading out.
Keep up the good work.
Yeah, you too.
Yeah.
Have you finished changing, babies?
Oh, Priestess.
Yes, we're finished.
Okay, okay. Those look good on you.
Sorry for the sudden request.
Your job isn't that difficult.
Try and enjoy it.
Okay!
This priestess is a bit of a free spirit.
By the way, that boy over there with the black hair...
Is he a friend of yours, baby?
Huh? Oh, you mean Raku?
Yeah, he is.
He's no good.
Leave him on his own, something bad's bound to happen.
What do you mean?
What's wrong, Onodera-san?
Oh, sorry. It's just...
This priestess is an incredibly famous spirit medium.
She's been famous for generations.
It's been said that during our grandparents' time,
there's no one who didn't know about her.
I hear she helped out my grandmother time and time again,
and even helped out when the city was in crisis.
Oh?
How embarrassing...
listening to stories of the past.
U-Um, is there something evil following Ichijou-kun around?
Yes, there is.
It might give us some trouble.
But there's nothing strange about...
Huh?
What the hell? Bird poop?
Man, you've got no luck today.
Or rather, in a way, you're having a crappy day.
Don't go making stupid puns!
Why is there a banana here?
Raku!
The stairs!
Hey, Ma'am.
What is it that's clinging to him?
That'd be... did anything really great happen to him this year?
It seems that he's being haunted by the spirits of unpopular boys.
If we don't clear up this misfortune before the year's end,
it might cost him his life!
H-His life?
Before the year's end...
Today's New Year's Eve... That's impossible!
Relax. Evil spirits can be exorcised in many ways.
If you feel like helping out,
I must warn you of one thing.
You must not let him become aware of his misfortune.
Otherwise, the exorcism won't work.
Actually, pummeling him on the
New Year's Eve bell would work the fastest.
It's an incredibly effective tool for exorcisms.
If possible, let's use another method...
Then there's no helping it.
Throwing salt at spirits of that level won't work, but maybe this will...
That's...
This is a talisman I wrote for exorcising spirits.
I've only got one,
but if you stick this on him, any kind of spirit will be dealt an instant K.O.
Understood.
I'll do it!
I just have to place it on his body somewhere, right?
No. You can't just place it anywhere.
You have to place it at a point below the navel.
A place that produces energy
and expels evil from the body.
In other words...
Yes. His butt.
Splenius
Deltoid
Greater
Rhomboid
External
Oblique
Semimembraneous
Biceps
Femoris
Trapezius
Infraspanitus
Teres
Major
Latissimus
Dorsi
Gluteus
Medius
Gluteus Maximus
Iliotibial
Band
Gracilis
Splenius
Deltoid
Greater
Rhomboid
External
Oblique
Semimembraneous
Biceps
Femoris
Trapezius
Infraspanitus
Teres
Major
Latissimus
Dorsi
Gluteus
Medius
Gluteus Maximus
Iliotibial
Band
Gracilis
Splenius
Deltoid
Greater
Rhomboid
External
Oblique
Semimembraneous
Biceps
Femoris
Trapezius
Infraspanitus
Teres
Major
Latissimus
Dorsi
Gluteus
Medius
Gluteus Maximus
Iliotibial
Band
Gracilis
Splenius
Deltoid
Greater
Rhomboid
External
Oblique
Semimembraneous
Biceps
Femoris
Trapezius
Infraspanitus
Teres
Major
Latissimus
Dorsi
Gluteus
Medius
Gluteus Maximus
Iliotibial
Band
Gracilis
Splenius
Deltoid
Greater
Rhomboid
External
Oblique
Semimembraneous
Biceps
Femoris
Trapezius
Infraspanitus
Teres
Major
Latissimus
Dorsi
Gluteus
Medius
Gluteus Maximus
Iliotibial
Band
Gracilis
Splenius
Deltoid
Greater
Rhomboid
External
Oblique
Semimembraneous
Biceps
Femoris
Trapezius
Infraspanitus
Teres
Major
Latissimus
Dorsi
Gluteus
Medius
Gluteus Maximus
Iliotibial
Band
Gracilis
Splenius
Deltoid
Greater
Rhomboid
External
Oblique
Semimembraneous
Biceps
Femoris
Trapezius
Infraspanitus
Teres
Major
Latissimus
Dorsi
Gluteus
Medius
Gluteus Maximus
Iliotibial
Band
Gracilis
Splenius
Deltoid
Greater
Rhomboid
External
Oblique
Semimembraneous
Biceps
Femoris
Trapezius
Infraspanitus
Teres
Major
Latissimus
Dorsi
Gluteus
Medius
Gluteus Maximus
Iliotibial
Band
Gracilis
Splenius
Deltoid
Greater
Rhomboid
External
Oblique
Semimembraneous
Biceps
Femoris
Trapezius
Infraspanitus
Teres
Major
Latissimus
Dorsi
Gluteus
Medius
Gluteus Maximus
Iliotibial
Band
Gracilis
Deltoid
Greater
Rhomboid
External
Oblique
Semimembraneous
Biceps
Femoris
Infraspanitus
Teres
Major
Latissimus
Dorsi
Gluteus Maximus
Iliotibial
Band
Gracilis
Splenius
Deltoid
Greater
Rhomboid
External
Oblique
Semimembraneous
Biceps
Femoris
Trapezius
Infraspanitus
Teres
Major
Latissimus
Dorsi
Gluteus
Medius
Gluteus Maximus
Iliotibial
Band
Gracilis
Splenius
Deltoid
Greater
Rhomboid
External
Oblique
Semimembraneous
Biceps
Femoris
Trapezius
Infraspanitus
Teres
Major
Latissimus
Dorsi
Gluteus
Medius
Gluteus Maximus
Iliotibial
Band
Gracilis
Splenius
Deltoid
Greater
Rhomboid
External
Oblique
Semimembraneous
Biceps
Femoris
Trapezius
Infraspanitus
Teres
Major
Latissimus
Dorsi
Gluteus
Medius
Gluteus Maximus
Iliotibial
Band
Gracilis
Splenius
Deltoid
Greater
Rhomboid
External
Oblique
Semimembraneous
Biceps
Femoris
Trapezius
Infraspanitus
Teres
Major
Latissimus
Dorsi
Gluteus
Medius
Gluteus Maximus
Iliotibial
Band
Gracilis
Splenius
Deltoid
Greater
Rhomboid
External
Oblique
Semimembraneous
Biceps
Femoris
Trapezius
Infraspanitus
Teres
Major
Latissimus
Dorsi
Gluteus
Medius
Gluteus Maximus
Iliotibial
Band
Gracilis
Splenius
Deltoid
Greater
Rhomboid
External
Oblique
Semimembraneous
Biceps
Femoris
Trapezius
Infraspanitus
Teres
Major
Latissimus
Dorsi
Gluteus
Medius
Gluteus Maximus
Iliotibial
Band
Gracilis
Splenius
Deltoid
Greater
Rhomboid
External
Oblique
Semimembraneous
Biceps
Femoris
Trapezius
Infraspanitus
Teres
Major
Latissimus
Dorsi
Gluteus
Medius
Gluteus Maximus
Iliotibial
Band
Gracilis
Splenius
Deltoid
Greater
Rhomboid
External
Oblique
Semimembraneous
Biceps
Femoris
Trapezius
Infraspanitus
Teres
Major
Latissimus
Dorsi
Gluteus
Medius
Gluteus Maximus
Iliotibial
Band
Gracilis
Splenius
Greater
Rhomboid
External
Oblique
Semimembraneous
Biceps
Femoris
Trapezius
Infraspanitus
Teres
Major
Latissimus
Dorsi
Gluteus
Medius
Iliotibial
Band
Gracilis
Splenius
Deltoid
Greater
Rhomboid
External
Oblique
Semimembraneous
Biceps
Femoris
Trapezius
Infraspanitus
Teres
Major
Latissimus
Dorsi
Gluteus
Medius
Gluteus Maximus
Iliotibial
Band
Gracilis
His butt.
Do you have a minute, Raku?
Oh, Chitoge?
What's up?
Uh...
I have a favor to ask.
Huh?
Can you shut up and take off all your clothes?
No-no-no-no, what are you saying?
Take off my clothes?
Isn't it okay if I just take my shirt off?
No... like I said...
Take it all off, even your underwear!
Eh?
Quit being so fussy!
Hurry up and take it off!
Stop!
What are you doing?
It's fine, so come on!
Ah! The talisman!
Huh? What's that?
Looks like she failed.
The precious talisman...
Ma'am, let me try next.
I'll do anything!
Let's see...
If something else were to be effective, it'd be...
Hug him for an entire minute.
Huh?
I made those shrine maiden outfits.
They may contain a tiny bit of purification power.
W-What's with that?
That role should definitely be m-
I'll do it!
Ichijou-kun.
Hm?
Oh?
Onodera.
Perfect timing.
Listen to this:
Just now, Chitoge suddenly...
Don't say anything.
Just stay still.
It's okay.
What the hell was that?
Let me do it!
Calm down.
It's a no-go.
He wasn't purified.
Even though I did my best!
Oh, crap! The New Year's Eve bell has started to ring!
Yaki Dango
Chocolate Banana
When this bell rings
Fried Frankfurters
Sweet
Mild
Sake
Sweet
Mild
Sake
it means the year is about to end!
When that happens, I can't guarantee the boy's safety.
We're out of time!
N-No way!
Ma'am, isn't there any other way?
We'll do anything we can!
Guess we've got no choice.
I'll use my trump card.
If you make him drink this blessed water,
it'll definitely purify him.
You might still be able to make it in time.
However, it won't be effective unless it's fed to him mouth-to-mouth.
M-Mouth-to-mouth?
M-Mouth-to-mouth means...
M-Mouth-to-mouth means...!
In other words...!
Ki...!
Tachibana Marika's gone!
Eh?
Taiyaki
Egg Crackers
Lottery
What?
Tachibana?
What's with that face?
What are you doing?
HoldP
itP
rightP
thereP
Tachibana!P
What the hell are you doing?
You're freaking me out!
Rao-ama, peas wae!
Now that I look closely, there are three more following her!
They're charging at me the same way!
No so fas, arika! Won low you iss im!
We
won't
please!
Oh?
Real? So you're one iss im hen?
Do
you
intend
to
steal
Raku-sama's
lips
instead
of
me?
ell... I ges...
Uguu!
That's
!!!
How the hell are you guys talking to each other?
That's just scary!
Damn it! Why do I have to run?
Give me a break!
Ah! Raku-sama!
Raku?
Ichijou-kun?
Ichijou Raku!
Oh, I see.
So that's what happened.
Thanks, you guys.
I can't begin to show you how grateful I am.
Thank you.
You got that because you were resisting us.
I'm just glad we were able to do the exorcism.
Now you'll be able to greet the new year in good health.
I'm not sure I can agree with that...
So it seems that's what Onodera was doing back there.
I'm a little disappointed.
But maybe I should consider myself lucky.
Oh boy.
He's definitely been purified.
But it looks like his trouble with women
has only just begun.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
kirameki dashita yume wo
Those twinkling dreams…
fukinuketa kaze ha erimoto wo toori
The wind that blew past my collar
mada dare mo shiranai haru wo yobikomu
Ushers in the spring, though nobody is aware
me ga atta shunkan waraiai
The moment our eyes met we made each other laugh
houkago nandomo (kimi no)
After school, I often passed the time (with you)
tonari de sugoshita
By your side
soratakaku natte
When I heard that voice
koe kikoetara
Drifting high into the sky
tooi shourai ki ni natte
I felt uneasy about the distant future
shiroi kanousei sawatta
And felt the vast possibilities
souzou daiarii katakoto datte taido de wakaru noni
The diary of imagination may be incomprehensible but even though I get a sense of it from the tone
zenbu zenbu mitai honto no koto tashikametai
I want to see it all, all of it, and confirm the truth
memorii kakaekirenakutatte ii ima no watashi
There’s no need to hold on to all my memories, the me of right now
motto motto soba de kimi to itai kara kiite
Wants to be by your side more and more, so listen
kirameki dashita yume wo
To those twinkling dreams