Zaws
Zawsze
Zawsze in
Zawsze in love
(F
(Fore
(Forever
(Forever in lo
(Forever in love)
You keep the lock.
And I'll take this key.
We'll wear them all the time,  and treasure them forever.
Someday, when we're all grown up and meet again,
I'll use this key to unlock  what's been tucked away.
And then...
Okay.
We'll
We'll get
We'll get married.
We'll get ma
We'll get marri
We'll get married
We'll get married.
Episode 1: The Promise
All right.
Hey! Breakfast is ready, ya bozos!
Yo! Good morning, Young Master!
Ichijou Raku
Damn! Deeeelish!
That's our Young Master for ya, the master chef!
Nothing beats a breakfast cooked by our beloved heir apparent!
Who're you callin' "heir apparent"?
I keep telling you guys...
I'm never gonna join the yakuza!
Huh? No way!
I want to graduate from a top university,
get a nice civil servant job,
and walk the straight and narrow, looking right up at the sun!
My god... You sure like to make a ruckus every morning.
Dad!
Hey, Boss!
Good morning, Boss!
Raku, before I forget...
We need to sit down and talk about some important matters sometime soon. Don't forget.
Important matters?
All right, Young Master! We wish you the best of days!
The best of days!
Oh, yeah. Almost forgot, Young Master...
There's a new gang that's starting to stir up trouble on our turf.
New gang?
Keep your eyes peeled, young master.
I'm so over this day-after-day violence!
Man, what I would give to have a nice, tranquil life.
Now that I think about it, I spend so much of my time studying to get into a good school,
that I almost never socialize with girls, let alone date them.
Well, actually...
I did have a girlfriend. Just that once, but still...
Until now my life has been a never-ending struggle.
Oh, crap! I'm going to be late!
But this particular day,
was the one that changed everything.
From this day forward...
my daily struggle would become all the more agonizing.
Sorry! I'm in a hurry!
I'm really sorry!
Wh-What was that?
Hey, Raku... Whoa! Hold up!
Ichijou-kun? How did you hurt yourself?
Are you okay?
Your nose is bleeding!
Oh, hey! Onodera!
I-I'm fine, I'm fine. Totally fine!
What? You were the victim of a hit-and-run by a girl?
Get real!
Who just jumps over a fence and knees a guy in the face?
I'm serious!
Wait a sec. I'll get you a band-aid.
Onodera, you don't have to do that, really.
Of course I do! What if it gets infected? Come on.
There.
Whoa, Onodera's so close.
Maybe this injury isn't so bad after all.
Good for you, Raku!
Shut up!
Onodera Kosaki
Today started off in the worst possible way,
but at least I got to chat with Onodera. Maybe it's not all that bad.
Okay, class! I'd like to introduce you to our new transfer student!
Come on in, Kirisaki-san.
All right.
Hello, everybody!
I'm Kirisaki Chitoge. I just moved here from America.
My mom's Japanese and my dad's American, so I'm biracial.
But as you can see, I speak Japanese just fine,
so please don't hesitate to talk to me!
Wow! She's so cute!
That is one hot babe!
Check out those legs! She looks like a model!
She says she's half-American! I've never seen anyone so hot!
All right, why don't you find yourself an empty seat in the back for now?
You're that...
That barbaric girl!
Bar...
...bar...
...ic...
Girl?
Hey!
Who're you calling barbaric?
You nailed me with your knee in the courtyard, remember?
Well, I apologized, didn't I?
I barely bumped into you,
so quit pretending it hurt, will you?
What do you mean, barely?
I nearly blacked out!
Oh, did you? You should get checked for low blood pressure!
I'm apologizing, if you haven't noticed,
so why don't you just let it go and stop being such a crybaby?
In what world is that an apology?!
Monkey girl!
Who are you calling a monkey girl?
Kirisaki Chitoge
Okay, I'm counting on you, Ichijou.
Stay away from me, got it? Your impotence might be contagious.
Right back at you! The last thing I want is to turn into a monkey like you!
I didn't say anything!
My first day with the new girl
Damn it, what's her problem?
I've never met such a barbaric, annoying girl!
She's nothing like Onodera, or that girl I made that promise with.
We never did meet again, not even once.
But man... If only Onodera and I were like that...
Yeah, right!
It must've been when I got that swift knee to the face.
Why should I help you find it?
Well, I lost it because of your thunderous knee,
so you're partially at fault here, too.
I keep thinking it over, and that's the only time it could've happened!
What's the matter, Ichijou-kun?
Onodera... Well, I just lost something important.
You did? Can I help?
Oh, no!
It's her fault that I lost it, so it goes
without saying that she should help.
What did you say?
So, what kind of pendant are we looking for?
The chain's about this long, and there's a lock shaped like this on the end...
Isn't that...
You've seen it somewhere?
Oh, sorry. I could be mistaken... Probably...
Fine. If I help you look for the pendant,
will you promise not to talk to me in school—ever again?
I can't stand guys who get worked up about every little thing.
I'd hate for anyone to think I was friends with such a petty guy.
Oh, right, I forgot to tell you something, Ichijou.
I'm putting you in charge of helping Kirisaki adjust to her new school,
so I've decided to let her help you...
take care of the school's pets. Thanks a bunch!
Why is this happening to me?
Hey, you promised not to talk to me, remember?
You think we can accomplish anything without speaking to each other?
Besides, we're not actually in school.
Oh, spare me.
Damn it... Why the hell do I have to work with this bitch?
Come on! We're gonna use the extra time to look for your pendant!
You don't have to tell me!
My second day with the vicious woman
Gosh, Japanese is confusing...
Here.
What's this?
My notes from Japanese class.
You were having a hard time keeping up, weren't you?
I thought I told you not to talk to me!
Who asked for your help, anyway?
You goddamn bitch!
My third day with
the barbaric girl
Yo, Raku. When did you and Kirisaki-san get so close?
What gave you that idea?
Well, everybody sees you together a lot.
Plus you have that thing after school.
And to top it off, your conversations have that friendly vibe going on...
Friendly?
How is she friendly to me?
Look, Kirisaki-san's a knockout babe, you know?
A lot of guys are curious about her.
Like, why'd she choose this school of all places?
Or why'd she move at such an odd time? Stuff like that.
A knockout? That thing?!
Awesome!
She turns more ape-like by the second.
What the hell are you doing?
See if I ever help you again!
I said I was sorry!
Kirisaki-san!
My fourth   day with the    acrobatic girl
Man, that hurts...
Jeez, that gorilla woman!
What kinda upbringing makes a person that belligerent?
Big Bro!
We had another run-in with that new gang on Third Street!
What the hell? That's the third time this week!
Well, not that I'm one to talk.
Here you go, Ichijou-kun.
O-Oh, thanks!
You've been getting pretty roughed up, lately.
I'm telling you, that new girl will punch you at the drop of a hat!
You say that, and yet you're still so nice to her.
That's what I admire about you, Ichijou-kun.
You even offered to lend her your notes, right? I saw you.
Y-You did, huh?
Whoa! I didn't know she was watching!
I'm so happy!
Oh, I wanted to ask you...
That pendant you're looking for... Where did you buy it?
Actually, someone gave it to me, a while back.
Ten years ago, I think.
Y-You take really good care of your belongings, don't you?
I made this promise, you see. It's an important keepsake.
A promise...
My sixth day with the gorilla woman
Oh, for crying out loud, we're never going to find it!
Shut up. You're the one who said that you don't like whiners, remember?
Come to think of it, why did you move here at such a weird time, anyway?
Why do you wanna know? No reason.
Because of my parents' work.
So what do your parents do?
What's it to you?
Why should I have to give you of all people my life story?
I'm going to look over there.
Okay...
Wait...
This scent...
It smells strangely familiar.
Somehow, it makes me feel nostalgic.
A scent that I've always been familiar with...
But where is it from?
So that's the new gang, huh?
Is it just me, or is this getting worse by the day?
My seventh day
with Kirisaki
You're late, Kirisaki.
Hurry up and give me a hand.
Jeez! I can't take it anymore! I'm so over this!
Wh-What the hell's your problem now?
You'll never guess what some girls from class were asking!
Hey, Kirisaki-san... Are you dating Ichijou-kun?
I mean, you guys look like you're getting along so well,
and I hear you've been hanging out together after school, too.
That's what!
What the...
Who... the... hell would get along with you?!
The only reason I'm with you after class is because I'm nice enough to join you in this ridiculous hunt! Nothing more!
The committee meeting ended early today,
so maybe I'll help Ichijou-kun look for his pendant.
Give me a break!
Are you forgetting that you're the one who knocked it out of my hand?
Only because you weren't holding onto it like you should've been!
Seriously! A grown man so torn apart by the loss of a pendant!
Does losing your favorite teddy bear keep you up at night too?
What? Did some girl you had a crush on give it to you or something?
You're unbelievable!
Dwelling on something so far in the past...
How girly can you get?
I bet whoever it was doesn't even remember you anymore!
That's beyond lame!
It's totally absurd!
You shut the hell up!
If that's how you feel, then you don't have to help me! Just get out of my face!
Fine by me.
I went and did it.
I blew my top in front of a woman.
My eleventh day  with Chitoge
I bet whoever it was doesn't even remember you anymore!
It's totally absurd!
Damn it!
Ichijou-kun!
Kirisaki-san is asking for you.
Why does she want to see me over here?
That girl...
That's not Kirisaki, is it?
Ow! What the hell was that for?
A-Are you all right, Ichijou-kun?
Is this my...
Is that yours?
Yeah.
But why did she have it?
Kirisaki-san kept looking for it after she left.
She made sure to keep it a secret.
She told me not to tell you, though.
Translate it if you can!!
I fulfilled my duty.
So don't talk to me anymore. Scum bastard.
Chitoge.
I can't read it, but it's clear that she's making fun of me.
She's not the least bit cute.
Whatever.
She's incredibly annoying, but I guess she's not all bad.
And besides, she did have a point.
Maybe it's about time I put this promise behind me.
No...
No, you can't!
Ichijou-kun, you made a promise with someone, right?
If that person remembers the promise, too...
then it would make them really sad if you gave up, right?
Even if it was ten years ago, and you were just kids...
You never know. Maybe it's still important to her.
Onodera?
Wait... There's no way...
Oh... Sorry! That was a strange thing to say!
Uh, no...
Thanks, Onodera. I think I feel better now.
You're right. It doesn't matter if I see her again or not.
The fact of the matter is that it's important to me.
And I'll continue to cherish it.
Thanks for everything, Onodera.
All right, see you later!
Sure, see you later!
I couldn't bring myself to ask him... again.
I'm such an idiot.
I'm home!
Hey, is that you, Raku?
What's going on, Dad? This is pretty sudden.
I told you we have important
?matters to discuss, remember?
I'm sure you know about our recent skirmishes with that other gang,
but it looks like we're headed towards all-out war.
What? Are we gonna be okay if war breaks out?
Which brings up my next point!
Actually, the boss of the other gang is an old friend of mine.
And I hear he's got a daughter the same age as you...
And so, Raku, my boy.
I was wondering if you'd mind becoming an item with that girl?
Oh, come on. All you have to do is fake it.
If the heirs of each gang are in love,
the young guns would put an end to their squabbling.
N-No, even if that'd work, you've got to be kidding me!
No way can I do that! After all, I...
You what? Do you already have a girlfriend?
Dad...
Sorry, but there are lives at stake here.
Complain all you want, but you're not getting out of this, got it?
All right, then! Come on in!
What, she's already here?
Well, I guess there's nothing I can do.
And it's supposed to be an act, anyways.
It'll probably be all over in a couple of days.
I told you!
It's not like I've decided to go through with it yet!
Yeah, but I hear he's quite the stud, you know?
What? No, no, even still!
Huh? That voice...
Now, then. This young lady is going to be your girlfriend.
I'm still not mentally prepared.
In that instant, the pieces all fell into place.
Why this girl had transferred in at such an odd time of year,
why she was reluctant to talk about her family,
and why the scent she gave off seemed so nostalgic to me.
That's right, it's the smell...
of gunpowder.
This young lady here is Miss Kirisaki Chitoge.
Starting tomorrow, you two are going to be girlfriend and boyfriend
Three  Years
for the next three years.
And so that's how two kids with no chemistry became a couple.
This fake love of ours would end up guiding me to that promise made ten years ago...
but I had no way of knowing that yet.