...can you hear this?
If you're listening to this, then you're somehow related to Hei.
If the past hasn't changed, that is.
I don't understand it...
I'm not blaming you for shooting her.
Don't shoot, Suou!
What the hell?
I don't get it!
Hey, are you okay?
That sucked big time! Support, my ass!
No one wants that homo side-gag-character!
Really, they've got to be kidding us!
Just when I was in a good mood and everything was going right, shit had to happen!
Yeah! That director won't be getting away with this that easily!
H-Hey! Look!
Doesn't she look like her?
You know, "Maurice of the Rose: The Crying Jar and Elephant's Trunk!".
You mean Caravaggio from that movie?
Exactly!
The one with the sick, psycho-lover vibes!
Well, she indeed looks sick.
We have to take her home, Kiko!
Uh... I'm not into little girls...
Hold on, that's a crime!
Go and get her!
Yikes! That pink haired girl!
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
Nee dareka oshiete
Hey, someone, tell me
Minna sou na no kana?
Is everyone like that?
Kyou ga shiawase nara
That they 'feel it's good enough
Sore de ii to omoeru tte
if they're if happy today'
Osanai koro ni wa
When I was young
Tashika ni atta yo
They certainly existed
Yume o oikaketeta
I pursued my dreams
Demo sore mo tooi kioku
But that's also a distant memory
Kotae no nai mainichi ga
The each unanswered day-
Tada sugite iku jikan ga
The time that is simply passing by-
Kore kara saki dou naru no darou?
What will happen beyond now?
Wakaranai...
They don't know...
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
We found it on the roof of a building that was 100m southeast of the crime scene.
We've also found the empty 14.5mm cartridge.
A PTRD, huh?
Can we conclude that it was materialized by Izanagi's power?
We haven't even confirmed whether that kid is Izanagi or not.
Or even what the kid's gender is.
So we have to strip the kid naked, huh?
Is that kid just a decoy?
Does that mean the real Izanagi is somewhere else?
Perhaps he's already in Tokyo.
Hey, look at that PTRD.
The scope and bolt are on the other side.
The kid in Vladivostok wasn't left-handed.
We can't rule out the possibility that Izanagi and Professor Pavlichenko could be here already.
Maybe they're planning to regroup in Japan?
BK201 won't necessarily have the same plan in mind.
The first thing he's going to chase after coming to Tokyo is most likely...
Izanami.
You're awake?
Where am I?
I can't say this is the best choice,
but it's better than making your cold worse.
Where are we?
Does someone you know live here?
Well, you can't really say that I know them...
Saying this hurts a little, but they aren't bad people.
You can't come out yet!
...I guess.
Messier code: UB001. Amber.
A contractor who has the memories of the future.
Leader of the contractor terrorist organization EPR.
A former member of the MI6.
There is also evidence that suggests she acted with BK201 in the Heaven's War.
I didn't know much about her back then.
But she saw everything.
As well as what came after that.
You can easily get the CD if you're working for them.
Open that with an analysis program.
The keyword is Izanami.
Izanami...
So these are... the Mitaka documents?
I want you to read them.
And tell them...
Hei will be at the end of that path.
You need to tell them, so they won't make any mistakes.
T-Thank you.
Oh, please. No need to thank us.
You were nice enough to give me clothes to change into.
And on top of that, such nice clothes.
She's really happy about this.
You don't see that everyday.
Could she be a natural-born cosplayer?
I think this is our good deed for today.
What do you say we go out?
Yeah, sounds great! Where should we go?
Ikebukuro.
She has great taste, I'm telling you!
She just asked to go visit Ikebukuro!
Perhaps she has been always wanting to walk the Maiden Road when she was in Russia.
Whoa, those pictures are awesome!
So your mother is a photographer?
It would be great if she can come with us to the next event to take more pictures!
But...
She's just kidding.
It's not like we can ask for a professional to show up...
I don't know where she is.
I was separated from her when I was still a young child.
Damn! You made me cry!
I see!
You traversed through borders to find your mother!
The further away someone is, the dearer they become.
What the hell is this?
What does it look like? A flying squirrel, of course.
Momonga.
No, it's just that it's staring at me with a wicked look.
Maybe you pissed him off in your previous life.
Anyway, let's go and find her mother!
Uh... it's not like that...
It's not going to happen.
Why not?
What were those tears for?
Those are two different things altogether.
We're professionals.
We won't work for free.
She wouldn't be here if she had money!
Hey, aren't we partners?
Don't try ripping them off with your usual tricks!
H-Hey! Don't badmouth me!
I have...
I have some money, so get me to Ikebukuro...
Roger! We'll do anything in our power to find her!
This is a tear-jerking, special reunion!
Aye, boss!
Uh... Excuse me...
Wow, Tokyo is nothing like Russia.
Man, this place sure has changed.
Nope. Looks like she isn't there either.
She hadn't been back for a while, in fact.
That's going to be a real problem.
What are we going to do?
Not to worry. We've still got something up our sleeves.
Let's go to the next place.
Yeah!
Are they harassing me?
Why does the editor of that photobook have such a cat-filled place?!
He just changed his job.
The publication industry was hit by the bad economy too.
If she hasn't stopped there, she's probably at a photo shoot.
A photo shoot?
It's a real pain when she's at a photo shoot.
She has a fondness for freedom, like a cat. She would wander off somewhere and you could never find her.
What kind of pictures has she been taking lately?
Let's see.
Lately, she seems to be obsessed about the Gate.
That's right?
What's right?
I've got it!
Got what?
I see it, I see it, I see it now...!
Boss, are you okay?
Oh my, that's so lovely.
It's like the Buddha's last moments.
Why are you hiding Izanami's whereabouts even from us?!
If BK201 finds out where Izanami is located, he will definitely go after her!
Now that BK201 has lost his powers, he's merely a gloomy gigolo!
We cannot throw this chance away if we want to catch him!
I never expected you two would be in agreement about this.
I'm not really hiding it just from you two.
Everyone who's been in contact with her has had their memories erased.
There are only a few people, including me, who know her whereabouts.
I would imagine that no one will be able to see her again.
Sheesh, he's really a party-pooper.
What's up?
You feeling warm down there because you can't see him, despite the fact he's so close?
Let's go and search a bit more in the meantime.
Maybe someone else other than the Director might know where Izanami is.
We can't rule out that BK201 won't do the same.
I want to see BK201.
But if I were to trust the Mikata Documents...
Izanagi looks at the false bottom of the sea, waiting for Izanami.
Izanami will eventually cross it, and those two will meet again.
When they meet, Heaven and Earth will be split asunder,
and the Hell's Gate will appear.
From there will come something alien.
And conflicts will continue forever.
Such an abstract story.
But I have a bad feeling about the meeting of Izanagi and Izanami.
Episode 9    The Meeting Comes Suddenly One Day...
I wonder why...
I wanted to meet my mother that badly when I was young...
But now...
How many kilometers do you think we need to walk to find it?
You got a plan?
Hold your horses, now.
That's it!
There's no mistake.
She took the picture from here.
Her mother will come back here for sure.
But the photo album is out already.
You've still got a lot to learn, Kiko.
She already started with this theme.
She won't be done until the construction is finished.
Both photographers and detectives are the same.
That's what makes a professional different.
So when will she come back? How long do I need to wait?
Overseas?
Like another country?
Tough luck, huh?
She usually reserves a room a week before her shooting.
Do you know when she'll be back?
I'm afraid I don't know that.
She isn't really a resident here.
Oh, there is a room that's freed up, though. What do you say?
Mom stood here and took the photo.
She was...
Suou.
So you're Suou-chan?
Um... who are you?
You want to meet your mother?
A good woman can read other people's hearts after a certain age.
You've got to be kidding. That's absurd.
Your mother will be returning to Japan tonight at eight o'clock, at Haneda airport.
How do you know that?
It's good to have someone you want to see again.
I just wanted to meet you. That's it.
Who do you really want to meet now?
I want to meet...
Things don't look good.
Your mom's gone overseas.
She's coming back.
On a plane that lands at eight o'clock tonight.
Who said that?
A woman.
Didn't you run into her?
We didn't see anyone.
Hopefully we'll find something here, right?
Hold on!
What?
Hazuki and Youko are supposed to go to Haneda, right?
Yeah, I heard it was to pick up some goods.
That information has been leaked!
Over here! Come on!
Wait!
You don't have to rush! She won't be here before eight!
Besides, can you really trust that woman you supposedly met on the roof?
As long as it's not coming from your mouth, it's safe to assume that it isn't wrong.
You little bitch...
Very well. Please wait here for a moment.
We'll call you when it's ready.
Thank you.
Did you forget about your grandfather?
Well, I can't blame you.
After all, I kicked you out of the house.
I'll wait outside.
Wait.
Take this.
Your mother Mizue doesn't have much time.
Won't you go and see her?
It has to be that flight.
You'll get to see her when that plane lands!
Oh, your heart is racing already!
Racing?
Thanks for pointing out the obvious.
After that much sprinting!
That's not what I meant! Right?
I know that too, but...
You should know that contractors don't feel anything toward their relatives.
If you had hated me for that and kicked me out, I would have forgiven you.
I am your...
No... I was destined to walk the path of the underworld as a mere servant of a silly lineage.
After becoming a contractor, I've realized for the first time how stupid it was to put my life in jeopardy.
I hated you because of that.
I'm no longer your puppet. Simple as that.
You're Sawasaki-sama from the Ministry of Internal Affairs and Communications, right?
Yes.
It's ready. Please come this way.
So you're not going to forgive me.
When I heard that I could see you again, I had some hopes for you, but...
You heard?
Youko!
Did she just leave? Aren't you with her?
Um... are we in the right building?
Excuse me.
No way!
Stop!
Li-kun!
Put Youko down.
Neither of us will have the advantage if you're carrying the hostage.
Let her go.
Wait!
Why...
How could he see through me that easily?!
Did I drop my guard...
No... was I distracted?
No way!
They said there's some trouble on the runway.
I don't care anymore.
I don't care if I don't meet her.
No way!
Weren't you so excited a moment ago?
Mommy!
There is... there is no God!
Look! Even this old fart with terrible body odor dreams of his mother!
There isn't anyone who wouldn't be happy to see their mom!
Mama...
How...
Mama!
I missed you!
Let's go, Kiko.
Come on, it's the tear-jerking scene!
It would be uncomfortable to stay any longer.
Their affection isn't some kind of reality show.
It's something everyone holds dear to them, deep inside.
Oh my, you've become a splendid adult to say that, Matsukichi.
Thanks, mom!
Gah! How do you know my real name?!
Hey! Wait!
I'm so happy, Shion!
Kureteku yuubae ni senaka osarete
My back is pressed by the darkening glow of dusk
Arukidasu kage ga shimesu hou e
I start walking toward where my shadow points
Taenai ikutsu mo no deai to wakare o
Repeating the many, ceaseless encounters and partings
Kurikaeshi doko e mukau no ka
Where do I head to?
Hito wa dare mo mayoinagara
For all people, while they are lost,
tsumi to iu na no sadame o seotte
they bear the fate known as sin
Sore de mo nao ikiru imi o shiru darou
Nevertheless, I'll still learn of the meaning to live, right?
Bokura wa sou Day by Day
That's right, Day by Day,
ashita e tsuzuku michi no tochuu de
we're midway on the road leading to tomorrow
Now Say It Again kimi to futari no mama
Now Say It Again, though it'd be great if
irareta nara ii no ni naa...
I could remain together with you...
What do you want to eat?
What do you like, Shion?
You got it wrong again, Mama.
Maybe it's because of my clothes.
I'm not Shion.
You can't be...
I told you, I'm Suou!
No way!
You're not Suou!
You can't be her...
because she died... eight years ago!
When she was about to learn the truth, there was nothing left.
Mother, father...
the memories of her siblings, everything...
When she knew everything was a lie,
she begins to run into a dark cave.
Into the void of nothing.
Seeking for the light.
Just running recklessly.
And then... she holds onto something.