We will meet soon.
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
Nee dareka oshiete
Hey, someone, tell me
Minna sou na no kana?
Is everyone like that?
Kyou ga shiawase nara
That they 'feel it's good enough
Sore de ii to omoeru tte
if they're if happy today'
Osanai koro ni wa
When I was young
Tashika ni atta yo
They certainly existed
Yume o oikaketeta
I pursued my dreams
Demo sore mo tooi kioku
But that's also a distant memory
Kotae no nai mainichi ga
The each unanswered day-
Tada sugite iku jikan ga
The time that is simply passing by-
Kore kara saki dou naru no darou?
What will happen beyond now?
Wakaranai...
They don't know...
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
Good morning.
Morning.
What are you making?
Pelmeni? You're making pelmeni, right?
Yes.
Let me help you.
No need.
Why?
I'm really good at stuffing them.
Come on, Hei. You can make the soup.
I'll take care of this.
Are these steamed buns?
Are you blind? It's pelmeni.
A Russian dish.
Look, the soup is there.
It's tasty.
Isn't it?
The meat buns.
Like I said, it's pelmeni...
Guess I'll follow July.
Who cares if they're big?
They taste the same.
We'll move separately today.
Are you going somewhere?
I have something to take care of.
Let me help you.
Don't you have things you gotta take care of as well?
I'll take care of my own problems.
You'll come back, right?
Promise me that.
I'll take care of my own problems, too.
So...
Okay.
BK201 killed Youko?
Are you sure?
He's the one who kidnapped her.
There's no mistake.
He probably got Izanami's whereabouts out of her.
In other words, Youko knew.
Hazuki and I will take care of this matter.
You two will find out where Mikhail Pavlichenko's kid is.
Do it as soon as possible.
Are you leaving us out of this, despite what happened?
One of our comrades was killed!
Let's go, Misaki-chan.
Outsiders should stay out of this.
Izanagi looks at the false bottom of the sea, waiting for Izanami.
Izanami will eventually cross it, and those two will meet again.
When they meet, Heaven and Earth will be split asunder,
and the Hell's Gate will appear.
From there will come something alien.
And conflicts will continue forever.
That's what was written in the classified Mitaka Documents.
I was told these were the memories of the future.
If this is true, something terrible will happen when Izanami and Izanagi meet.
That sign will become an unsinking crescent moon.
And then, when it becomes a full moon, it will be Izanami's last month of pregnancy.
I see, you've investigated this thoroughly.
As you're concerned, the final phase of the predictions has started.
I didn't tell you about this to avoid unnecessary confusion.
In the past, one interpretation of this has even led to a war.
The Heaven's War?
Correct.
Izanami's awakening cannot be stopped.
We have only one last measure to prevent that.
We have to capture and kill Izanagi,
before he meets Izanami.
He must have gone to see Yin.
I'm talking about Hei.
The Yin we knew and the one that's feared as Izanami now have completely different personalities.
Some people say she evolved, but Hei doesn't care about that.
He thinks that he changed her.
So that's why he wants to bring an end to this.
That's why I have to do it, too.
I've got to settle this too.
I'll meet Shion and talk to him.
This place is quite lonely for the last stop of the journey.
Who's there?
Papa!
Suou.
How?
Didn't they kill you?
That was a copy.
A copy?
Just a doll that was created to protect me from bad people.
It wasn't the real me.
Suou?
You're the same as me...
I'm a copy too.
How do you know that?
I met Mama... and heard that I had died.
She's as irresponsible as ever!
She doesn't know anything about me and Shion.
Papa...
I don't know what she told you, but think of it differently.
You are not dead.
You are standing in front of me, with your feelings and memories.
It's true that your body died.
But you've been revived!
Thanks to Shion's power.
Shion's?
You didn't create me?
Do you remember how Shion became
a contractor two years ago?
Yeah. We were in Siberia that night.
After hunting, we made a fire and drank warm soup.
And then... Shion became a contractor.
Was that a lie too?
It's true that a star fell.
But what happened afterwards is a bit different.
First of all, Shion has been a contractor ever since he was born.
He was special from the beginning, eh?
And you were never there.
Shion!
Shion! Shion!
Suou...
At first, I was unable to understand what happened.
His power is to create copies of things.
But he had never copied a human before.
Let alone, himself...
Hey, she's a girl!
Yes! That's why she is Suou.
She isn't Shion.
All copies that Shion created had one thing different from the original.
I don't know exactly what, but it matters not.
Then... what about my memories?
Why do I have my own memories?
That's because I used the ME to extract and transfer those memories plus the memories Shion created.
Of course, only with memories up until you were five years old.
So the memory of the aquarium...
That's a present from Shion.
That's not a present.
That is...
I have to see him.
Where is he?
Suou.
Please, Papa! Let me see him!
We've found Professor Pavlichenko's kid.
Toshimaku, East Ikebukuro.
Toshimaku, East Ikebukuro... and what?
I don't know.
Someone seems to have interfered with our doll system.
What? Is that even possible?
I've heard that the dolls were connected to each other, though...
So it was true.
By the way, Professor Pavlichenko argued that the ME had a similar network structure...
What do you think?
Why are you bringing that up?
I thought it fit the situation.
Anyways, let's go to Sunshine.
Knowing the general location is enough for us to figure out the rest.
I'm sure my lovely honey is here.
What's wrong?
They're coming.
Who's coming?
Okay.
July?
Hey! July!
I see.
We can't do anything if they've been discovered.
Tell their doll the escape route.
We already did.
I see. Good girls.
They’ve found out about this place, too.
Really?
Oh. That Sun Tzu fan is pretty good after all.
Episode 11
The bottom of the river dries
as the full moon appears...
Are those legs a reward for me?
Huh? Daddy is with you?
Man, this has got to be my lucky day.
All right. Come to daddy.
I'll take good care of you until they grow some hair.
What the hell are you talking about?
Your legs of course.
Hair doesn't grow there.
It does, when you grow up.
If you are as old as me, like this.
I don't think so.
I'm not a boy.
You're a boy, aren't you?
Looks like this moron is the only one who thinks that you're Shion.
Holy cow! The momonga is talking!
Is it really that surprising?
Get down!
Hey! Chill!
Follow me.
Was I the only one who got fooled?
I got them.
Papa.
What do we do now?
We can only run towards the direction of that weirdo.
This will do.
You are...
Sorry, but you won't be able to do anything even if you go right now.
Who are you?
Wait! She's not our target.
W-What was that?
Nothing less than expected from Professor Schroeder.
He's unequaled when it comes to creating useless tools.
Or so I'd like to say, but it lacks power...
He told me it would vaporize the target.
Who are you?
We can talk about that later.
Right now, we should get ourselves out of here.
This place is going to turn into a bloodbath.
Those are...
Now that there's no Syndicate, America wants to regain its authority.
Why is America involved?
They want Izanami and Izanagi.
Why? Aren't they...
Yes, but they see them as some kind of energy resource.
Anyway, let's leave this place to her and withdraw from this area.
She's been trained for these kinds of situations...
by the Black Grim Reaper.
Papa...
Where are you, my lovely honey?
It's that pervert again.
Hurry...
Leave me behind.
What are you going to do?
Leave this to me.
I'll be right back.
Mao, take care of Papa.
Hey!
Suou!
Hey! My lovely honey! Come out already!
That makes quite an impact.
Shit!
You finally did it!
My lovely honey!
Lovely...
Phew... now that was dangerous.
I was about to get killed.
I'm sure some people will get turned on by that moaning...
But I don't have a fetish for that.
Nope.
You won't be a naughty kid.
What the hell!
Fuck! I can't rub it off!
You won't die anyway, right?
Suou!
Stay with us, Papa!
It's too late for me!
No way! You're coming with us!
It's okay!
No, it's not!
Yes, it is.
I was really happy to see you grow up...
Wait! Are you satisfied with just that?!
I'm... I'm no longer the kid I was!
I'm a copy and a contractor.
I'm not the girl you used to know.
You will be always my Suou.
Papa...
Don't let go of that until Shion says so.
Papa? Papa!
Hey! I heard a voice.
He's dead. We've to go, Suou!
Suou!
Wait.
Every defeated enemy should yield some reward.
His memories are valuable for us.
Aren't you a little late, CIA?
BK201...
Die!
Kureteku yuubae ni senaka osarete
My back is pressed by the darkening glow of dusk
Arukidasu kage ga shimesu hou e
I start walking toward where my shadow points
Taenai ikutsu mo no deai to wakare o
Repeating the many, ceaseless encounters and partings
Kurikaeshi doko e mukau no ka
Where do I head to?
Hito wa dare mo mayoinagara
For all people, while they are lost,
tsumi to iu na no sadame o seotte
they bear the fate known as sin
Sore de mo nao ikiru imi o shiru darou
Nevertheless, I'll still learn of the meaning to live, right?
Bokura wa sou Day by Day
That's right, Day by Day,
ashita e tsuzuku michi no tochuu de
we're midway on the road leading to tomorrow
Now Say It Again kimi to futari no mama
Now Say It Again, though it'd be great if
irareta nara ii no ni naa...
I could remain together with you...
I never expected that I'd go to the Gate through this route.
Is Shion Pavlichenko really up ahead?
That's what they say.
And who would they be?
Someone is here.
Yikes!
Hey... why are you here?
They guided you?
Hi, Ricardo.
Stop calling me that.
I'm no longer your lover or anything else.
You're as cold as ever.
T-The squirrel talked!
I'm a momonga, damn it!
And, where is she?
Huh?
Where did she go?
She was here a moment ago.
Their feelings have connected.
This is the Gate. The place where wishes are granted.
But also the place where you lose something.
Where is this place?
Shion?
Shion!
Shion...
Flowers were just wildly blooming there.
When the Gate of Hell opens, the dreams of the future will flow through.
The crimson moon is a wish for destruction.
Whose dreams of the future are they?
What dreams does a contractor have?
It is just the dark abyss.
And that's the beginning of the journey.