Don't!
Did we get them?
Yep, although we only got BK201.
Wow! It's just as Professor Schroeder's hypothesis predicted.
Now's your chance to get away!
Oh boy...
All your mischief makes my heart throb, my dear prince.
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
Nee dareka oshiete
Hey, someone, tell me
Minna sou na no kana?
Is everyone like that?
Kyou ga shiawase nara
That they 'feel it's good enough
Sore de ii to omoeru tte
if they're if happy today'
Osanai koro ni wa
When I was young
Tashika ni atta yo
They certainly existed
Yume o oikaketeta
I pursued my dreams
Demo sore mo tooi kioku
But that's also a distant memory
Kotae no nai mainichi ga
The each unanswered day-
Tada sugite iku jikan ga
The time that is simply passing by-
Kore kara saki dou naru no darou?
What will happen beyond now?
Wakaranai...
They don't know...
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
Yin!
Hei.
Don't! Yin!
Farewell, Hei.
Yin.
Let go! Let go of me!
Did you save me?
How should I know?
Youko-chan! That's enough!
It too hot when it's that close!
Sorry, but this is my first time doing moxibustion.
First time, eh?
That's quite interesting.
Maybe along with this boring remuneration we can pass the time by...
Oww!
Sorry, my hand slipped.
Liar!
Don't come in without even knocking!
Same goes for you.
So, what did the chief say?
He told us to continue with the mission and obtain Izanagi by any means necessary.
If we can't accomplish the mission, we will be eliminated.
Oh geez, just when I've found a misbehaving cutie...
Wait, would having a tragic past score me more cuteness points?
Pervert.
Why did you kill my dad?
Say something!
You know something, don't you?!
Who were they?
Why were they looking for Shion?
Why did you have to kill my father?!
If you hate me that much, go ahead and kill me.
You're right about that.
But I'd rather die than be a murderer!
What a pacifist...
There are no replacements for anyone!
Since everyone is unique!
Yet you...
I bet you're the kind of person who can kill friends and lovers without batting an eye!
Shut up!
What...
What the hell is going on?
Everything was normal up until yesterday.
Suddenly everything is all messed up!
Why?!
I don't want to die!
Nor do I want to see other people killing or getting killed!
I've... I've had enough!
So they called me in this early in the morning just to clean up the mess the colonel made?
What exactly do they expect me to do with so few people?
Have you requested for more personnel?
The brass just doesn't understand how important this is.
Right now, there is only one novice available
Seems like there's no choice but to mobilize a large conventional force...
That doesn't make us much different from the colonel then...
Major.
Should we capture him?
Do you know Shogi?
It's a Japanese game.
Unlike chess, you can use the captured pieces as your own.
So she cried herself to sleep.
Well, that's to be expected. Up until two days ago, she was just a normal middle school student.
Aren't you surprised?
I am.
So it's true that your memories reside outside of your body.
Yeah.
Well, it's only a periodic backup
so I've only heard the conclusion of what happened in Tokyo.
So who are your owners now?
Same as yours, Hei.
The CIA?
No.
Yes. Her.
I've just come to issue you a change of orders.
Tanya!
Nika.
Sorry.
My mind can't keep up with the changes in my body.
I'm sure something bad will happen again if we're together.
I don't care.
We're together again.
Everything will be okay, Tanya.
What are you doing?!
A whale?
I'm waiting for you.
It's from Shion.
In Ikebukuro?
Ikebukuro?
Where's that?
In Tokyo.
Near Hell's Gate.
That place is off-limits.
Is Shion there?
Stand up.
Do you want to go to Japan?
I'll take you there.
Episode 3    Vanishing into the Snow Fields...
Nope, it got disconnected.
But it rang, right?
Yeah.
I hope Suou is okay.
Were you able to trace it?
That's enough, Tanya.
They tracked us through your cellphone.
What's that light?
A surveillance spirit?
Don't look at it.
It'll notice you.
It's the train over there.
Try to get on without getting noticed.
It'll depart in five minutes.
Tanya...
Why?
I made a deal with them.
I'll be rewarded and guaranteed a position if I capture you.
What about Nika?
What happened to him?
Why are you...
Answer me, Suou.
Where's Shion Pavlichenko?
Answer me.
Stop it, Tanya!
Why?
Stop!!!
Seems like we're too late.
What do we do?
Oh well...
Guess we'll just have to go wild.
Mao, take care of her.
Take care of her?
Wait, Hei!
Damn, don't blame me if something happens!
Petya! You...
There is no time for you to be surprised. I'll explain later.
Let's go, missy.
We're going under here.
Come here. You can climb up right?
Good.
He'll act as a decoy and distract them.
We'll escape during the chaos.
Time for departure!
Beware of accidents!
Major!
Fire!
Too bad. I missed.
No way...
What's going on...
Why? Why is this...
Die.
Don't!
Stop it, Tanya!
Aren't we friends?
Yes, we were friends.
But I didn't even know that you had a little brother named Shion.
Does he really exist?
Or are you Shion?
That's...
Even though I let you live...
Nika!
Don't tell me...
Tanya!
Let's go back home, Tanya.
Stop it!
Please stop!
Tanya!
No...
Not that...
It can't be...
She has awoken.
It has begun.
The end...
has begun.
It's begun.
All contractors...
should just die.
120° to the left.
3 meters up.
10 centimeters more to the right.
20° to the right.
3 meters down.
Shit!
110° to the right, 50 centimeters down.
What's your name?
July.
Hey, Hei! He's a...
Come.
"With three advantages, there will also be three disadvantages" sums up our situation, Madame.
Oh, hello, Mr. Smith.
What brings you here today?
I was wondering if you knew where the Black Grim Reaper is?
You're not going to tell me that the all-knowing CIA doesn't know, right?
If you're here to discuss business, then I'm all ears.
Information is my commodity.
My motto is "As long as I receive the proper payment, I will provide information to anyone at anytime."
"Thus, though we have heard of stupid haste in war."
I expect a prompt reply, Madame O'Reille.
His star really disappeared!
If his star fell, that would means he's dead.
I've never heard of one disappearing.
Are you sure you didn't make a mistake?
But...
Sorry, I'm a bit busy over here.
Just give up on him. Find yourself a new guy.
Kanami...
I think this is a good opportunity for you.
Kirihara speaking.
Chief!
Ah, er... I mean Kirihara-san.
It's been a while.
Saitou, do you have time?
There's something I wanted to ask.
Yep, I've got all the time in the world.
What is it?
It's regarding BK201...
Ah... I'm sorry but I can't give out information about contractors to anyone outside the department.
Ah, right.
If they find out that you were still in touch with someone who was exiled...
That's not what I mean!
Chief Kirihara, you're still the boss to me!
Sorry. I'll call you another time.
Chief.
Have you heard of Section 3?
Section 3? No...
Please be careful.
If they ever show up, don't listen to anything they say.
What is it?
I'm on the phone!
Well...
Nice to meet you.
My name is Kobayashi.
Ministry of Internal Affairs and Communications?
What do you want?
Two years ago, internal information from Public Safety was leaked anonymously to the Internet,
and exposed the existence of contractors to the world.
But there were no traces found of the so-called Syndicate from which the information was leaked.
Have you heard of Section 3?
Ministry of Internal Affairs and Communications is just a cover.
Our objective is to exterminate the remnants of the Syndicate.
and for that purpose we've been authorized to use any means necessary.
And what is it that you want from me?
BK201 isn't dead.
He's still lurking in the darkness.
You won't be able reach him from where you are now.
Come.
Chief! Chief!
Kureteku yuubae ni senaka osarete
My back is pressed by the darkening glow of dusk
Arukidasu kage ga shimesu hou e
I start walking toward where my shadow points
Taenai ikutsu mo no deai to wakare o
Repeating the many, ceaseless encounters and partings
Kurikaeshi doko e mukau no ka
Where do I head to?
Hito wa dare mo mayoinagara
For all people, while they are lost,
tsumi to iu na no sadame o seotte
they bear the fate known as sin
Sore de mo nao ikiru imi o shiru darou
Nevertheless, I'll still learn of the meaning to live, right?
Bokura wa sou Day by Day
That's right, Day by Day,
ashita e tsuzuku michi no tochuu de
we're midway on the road leading to tomorrow
Now Say It Again kimi to futari no mama
Now Say It Again, though it'd be great if
irareta nara ii no ni naa...
I could remain together with you...
Aren't you drinking a bit too much?
That's none of your business.
Hei, what happened to Yin?
I will...
I will kill her.
Contractors must remunerate after using their abilities.
I have become a contractor.
Without a destination, they drift into a city to the north.
The reflectionless surface of the blue lake.
The echoes of the gunshot are a requiem to the lost souls.
A fabricated smile is a false remuneration.
With each meeting comes a farewell.
There is no longer any reason to seek warmth.
And yet... he smiled.