A secret passage,
a hidden room.
They were all prepared by Professor Pavlichenko to hide the existence of his son,
and to escape in case of an emergency.
There are also traces of tampering in the family registry.
And not only once, but twice...
Why would he go that far to hide his son?
We don't know.
Perhaps it's related to his research that he's been secretly conducting.
You mean that ME network drivel mentioned in the report?
If that was feasible, we would both be jobless.
There are pieces missing everywhere.
It was the case with Professor Pavlichenko's corpse, too.
The DNA proves that the body was indeed his.
But the ME squeezer was only able to extract a day's worth of memories.
How do you explain that?
Were both analyses wrong?
What?
We got this a moment ago.
It's from an SVR agent in Japan.
What?!
This was taken 26 hours ago...
In Tokyo.
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
Nee dareka oshiete
Hey, someone, tell me
Minna sou na no kana?
Is everyone like that?
Kyou ga shiawase nara
That they 'feel it's good enough
Sore de ii to omoeru tte
if they're if happy today'
Osanai koro ni wa
When I was young
Tashika ni atta yo
They certainly existed
Yume o oikaketeta
I pursued my dreams
Demo sore mo tooi kioku
But that's also a distant memory
Kotae no nai mainichi ga
The each unanswered day-
Tada sugite iku jikan ga
The time that is simply passing by-
Kore kara saki dou naru no darou?
What will happen beyond now?
Wakaranai...
They don't know...
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
Ishizaka Kanami - Friend
Who are you waiting for?
How did you...
Why are you here?
That's my line.
I thought you would be in the archives,
yet you are here in this creepy place.
Oh, wasn't this place the hive of the dolls?
Are you looking for Izanami-chan?
At least you were discrete enough not to call your friend.
The lines are obviously tapped, and would cause that person a lot of trouble.
And you might be able to notice now that
you're already being watched.
A surveillance spirit?
You're lucky there aren't any power lines here, though.
We took all the know-how after the astronomy division was closed.
And now we've got Izanami.
What are they planning anyway?
Why are you telling me this?
We're in the same boat.
A grunt like me won't be informed of anything important.
I want to know what the higher-ups are thinking.
So? Wanna partner up with me?
Not only do you have the Japanese Public Safety on your ass,
but the CIA which you betrayed and the Russian organization, too.
It won't be easy to get out of Hokkaido.
A transporter?
Of the underground.
They'll help if we pay them.
Can we trust them?
It's the same with an informant.
We do business if we both have common goals.
It's that simple.
Is it cold?
Hey! That's not a nice way to greet people!
They're 200m ahead.
There's an inspection ahead.
Take a different route.
Is he a doll?
Yes.
If they are checking this place too, I don't think there's another way out of Hokkaido.
I'm pretty sure they have covered every path.
We'll have to think this thoroughly before we get to Hakodate.
That has its price too, of course.
There were some deviations in the plan, but we've managed to get Izanami.
If I'm not mistaken, they tried to kill Izanami, right?
It looked that way, yes.
We're still investigating who's behind this and where the information was leaked.
Thank you.
Is it true that Izanami's father is here?
As expected. You've already heard about that.
You've got to drink it all.
It's delicious.
So far, we've only received information that we found a matching person.
We're still investigating that matter.
The time stated in the Mitaka documents isn't that far in the future.
We have to hurry.
While there's no moon...
You're Ikuta's...
How is your family doing?
I've never had one.
I see.
Okay, I'll contact you again when I get it.
We'll meet at the usual place, okay?
Yeah.
How about a tattoo?
It'll boost up your manliness.
I don't want one.
Hey, that looks pretty good.
Now we just need a photo to plaster on this.
I see you rented another strange car again.
Dolls are unexpectedly easy to distinguish.
The blizzard is still at it.
Seriously...
I can't believe I'm stuck here in Sapporo because of a blizzard.
I don't care if it's a car or a train, just get me to Tokyo immediately.
The bullet train isn't working either.
Perhaps you should take an express train?
Though, there's no need to rush.
This is pathetic.
The people out there don't give shit about anything.
Is this little lady a contractor?
We use the contractors that are trained in your organization.
You aren't from the consulate?
We're from foreign affairs. Their allies.
Have you heard about that incident in Sapporo?
We haven't heard anything. Not even which organizations were involved.
According to our investigations, we believe a Japanese agency is involved in that incident.
But we have received this from an eyewitness.
BK201.
And two kids.
We believe it's the doll and the girl that were mentioned in the report.
It's Suou.
We can most likely find our target if we watch them.
We've got a skilled contractor to mark them.
Ilya Sokolov. I think you've heard of her.
What?
I don't want to hear that name.
He's indeed skilled.
So much that he sickens me.
Pardon me.
When you speak of the devil...
We just got information regarding a smuggling route for dolls.
Isn't eating that ice cream making you cold?
What about you? You just wolfed down all those dishes earlier.
What?
A white guy!
H-Hello!
C-Can you speak Japanese?
Really?
What were you drawing?
What's in there?
The remains of a child.
He met with an unfortunate accident while he was on a trip to Aomori by himself.
And his family?
His father and sister are in the car behind me.
My condolences.
Can I take a look in the coffin?
Eight and ten...
Got it.
As promised, I've taken you to Sendai.
You'll board the Cassiopeia at 04:30.
I think they won't be thoroughly monitoring at that time.
If you're worried you can switch trains at the local station.
Can we take July out for now?
There'll be inspections at Aomori too,
so it'll be a hassle to get him back in there.
Leave him like that.
Yeah. He's just a doll.
Open your eyes.
Aren't you lonely being alone in this coffin?
You should speak up if something is bothering you.
What are you doing?
Doesn't it hurt?
It does.
Then say that.
Sorry.
What's that? A flat tire?
So it was a setup?
Yeah.
They're in the doll business.
So she was after July from the start.
Shouldn't we chase after them?
Chase? For July?
I mean...
You got attached to him?
I need him when I use my powers.
It's a waste of time.
I don't want you to use your powers.
Why?
Why are you so cold toward July?
He's merely a doll.
But in Yin's case, you acted so...
So...
Shut up.
With your powers gone, you will need her-
Don't worry about that.
Besides, we don't know where they're headed.
It's July's surveillance spirit. He's asking for help!
No way!
Wait, Miss!
Damn, I can't take my eyes off of you for a second!
Episode 7    The Doll Sings to the Dancing Snow
I was teasing July a bit earlier.
But I couldn't really tell how he felt.
That's because he's a doll.
But he's lonely.
Lonely?
That's what I feel.
Otherwise he wouldn't have sent that surveillance spirit.
I'm sure the fragments of our hearts won't disappear.
Regardless of if we're dolls or contractors...
July!
Mao, we'll get off at the next stop.
We'll get onto another car.
They'll take good care of you.
Little boys as dolls are pretty popular.
That place.
He's gone.
We can get in from there.
Go scout that place.
Me?
Hey, aren't you the professional here?
Yes, missus slave driver!
More like an animal driver.
Understand your surroundings.
Almost anything can be used as a weapon.
Hey!
Geez.
What the hell is he doing?
I've got to get her away from him.
Can you do that by making some noise?
Yes, but are you planning to go in with that?
If I use my rifle, the police could come.
Thinking rationally, aren't we?
Oh well.
Who's that?!
Is someone there?
What?! What's going on?!
That's enough!
Stop!
Stop it!
We have to rescue July!
Are you okay?
It's dangerous if some amateurs try to deal with dolls.
Every country wants a skilled doll,
so doll smugglers are always in touch with intelligence agencies.
Feels good, huh?
It's like an opiate for the brain.
Your pain fades away; you feel sleepy.
And then, you stop breathing.
I've been looking for you!
What are you doing?!
Let go of me!
Close call.
So you're a contractor as well.
Let's go!
Stop it!
Is this squirrel a contractor too?
Squirrel? I'm a cat!
Well, now I-
You're coming along too.
Don't! Don't follow, July.
Look.
Those who're killed by me are lucky.
They die dreaming of something pleasant.
How long has it been since you've stopped dreaming?
I'm asking you how long you've been a contractor.
You're still not aware of all this?
I'm really saved by not being able to dream.
I used to often dream of the women I killed.
I murdered them in atrocious ways.
The complete opposite of how I'm killing now.
I enjoyed watching their suffering.
You beast!
Hearing that from an animal is funny.
But now it's all pointless...
Or better said I've stopped killing them in an irrational way.
I can't do it anymore, because I've become a contractor.
Isn't that ironic?
Feels good, eh?
Just die like that?
Watch out!
What the hell?!
How did you find us?
Did you call the informant?
Wasn't that a bad idea? Especially in this situation...
Um...
If you want to thank someone, thank July.
July!
You okay? Hurt?
A bump?
Ouch.
Thanks.
Kureteku yuubae ni senaka osarete
My back is pressed by the darkening glow of dusk
Arukidasu kage ga shimesu hou e
I start walking toward where my shadow points
Taenai ikutsu mo no deai to wakare o
Repeating the many, ceaseless encounters and partings
Kurikaeshi doko e mukau no ka
Where do I head to?
Hito wa dare mo mayoinagara
For all people, while they are lost,
tsumi to iu na no sadame o seotte
they bear the fate known as sin
Sore de mo nao ikiru imi o shiru darou
Nevertheless, I'll still learn of the meaning to live, right?
Bokura wa sou Day by Day
That's right, Day by Day,
ashita e tsuzuku michi no tochuu de
we're midway on the road leading to tomorrow
Now Say It Again kimi to futari no mama
Now Say It Again, though it'd be great if
irareta nara ii no ni naa...
I could remain together with you...
You're awake already?
Let's get ready.
For hunting, you have to get to the spot early to camp.
I won't forget the glitter of that summer day.
The sunlight making its way into the room through the window...
The spray of water trickling down your blond hair...
The echoes through the cold wall.
A distant memory of laughter. The fault of a memory.
A memory takes place.
The silver train runs.
And then... we cannot go back to that day.