Distance: 250 m.
Wind speed: 1.5.
Blowing from the right to the left.
Don't stop your breathing.
Slowly... Quietly...
Shoot.
Shoot!
With the passage of time, feeble humanity has evolved.
We traded our fangs for wisdom, and claws for tools in order to live longer.
Papa...
We will be tested soon.
When that time comes, you can't hesitate to pull the trigger.
That's okay!
I'll protect Suou.
Shion.
That was the last time I saw his real smile.
On the night of the Tokyo Explosion...
Shion became a contractor
and as remuneration, his legs were paralyzed.
That's why I swore that I will protect him.
If this is a test, I'll pass it with flying colors.
I am his older sister after all.
But...
I didn't realize...
the true test had only just begun.
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
Nee dareka oshiete
Hey, someone, tell me
Minna sou na no kana?
Is everyone like that?
Kyou ga shiawase nara
That they 'feel it's good enough
Sore de ii to omoeru tte
if they're if happy today'
Osanai koro ni wa
When I was young
Tashika ni atta yo
They certainly existed
Yume o oikaketeta
I pursued my dreams
Demo sore mo tooi kioku
But that's also a distant memory
Kotae no nai mainichi ga
The each unanswered day-
Tada sugite iku jikan ga
The time that is simply passing by-
Kore kara saki dou naru no darou?
What will happen beyond now?
Wakaranai...
They don't know...
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
Shion Pavlichenko.
Hand over the meteor core.
A contractor?
Hurry! Run!
There are no enemies at the back of the house.
Good evening.
Erm...
Zdravstvuj.
Ni hao.
Guten Abend.
Do you understand me?
Did you understand any one of those, cutie?
Who the hell are you people?
Ah, so you speak Japanese.
That's great.
I don't like being rough, you see.
I'll be grateful if you be a good girl and come with me.
Petya!
Hey!
Come, Petya!
Such a naughty girl.
Papa...
Shion...
Shion!
How?!
Shizume-san! Hazuki-san! Hurry!
Man, she was such a cutie!
Playing hide and see—
Youko!
Y-Yeah!
I-It's troublesome, isn't it?
Having to kiss a guy to remunerate for using your pow—
Just removing the bad taste.
Even the contractor you were bragging about is in a body bag now.
What do you say, Debry?
Looks like your subordinate wasn't even as useful as a bulletproof vest.
Colonel Kozroff.
Do you know how much it costs to train and supervise a contractor?
What a useless investment.
They're nothing more than monsters.
They're useless either as soldiers or as weapons.
I've ordered ME to erase the memories of the witnesses.
What about the professor's missing kid?
We're looking for him.
Broaden the area of the surveillance spirits.
Put all the bodies into the ME squeezer...
While they're still fresh.
Of course the creator, as well.
His brain is a precious asset of the state.
Coming!
Yes?
Thank heavens, you're home!
Please, Sasha! Let me hide for a whi—
Who are you?
ME?!
Tanya!
Where am I?
Nika Lobanov is in that room.
What did he do?
Theft and robbery.
We'll take him into custody. Please don't worry.
Suou?
Nika!
Do you know who I am?
Who you are?
Of course.
H-Hey! Suou...
Suou?
Episode 2    The Fallen Star...
"Thus, what enables the wise sovereign and the good general to strike and conquer,
and achieve things beyond the reach of ordinary men, is foreknowledge."
Looks like I've come to ask for your help again, Madame.
One of my men stumbled upon something in the Far East.
The organization has finally made its move to obtain Izanagi.
I was wondering if you knew anything about it.
I'm really grateful for business from the almighty CIA, however...
"Foreknowledge cannot be elicited from spirits," Mr. Smith.
"Know thy self, know thy enemy."
I'm just a coward.
What in the world is going on?
When I called the people from class, they've all forgotten about Tanya.
And there was a fire at your house...
Is your father okay?
Hey, Suou.
Darn, there's nothing useful here.
Eat something.
You haven't eaten anything, have you?
Hey, Suou...
That's enough pondering!
S-Suou?
I'm borrowing your desk.
Stop that!
That's a badass anti-tank rifle!
It's scrap!
Wait and see, old man in black!
When I arrived, the professor was already dead.
You're telling the truth, I hope.
Who were the people who intervened?
We're investigating them.
I'll let you know if we find anything.
There're so many missing pieces.
The CIA specifically hired you to deal with these kinds of situations.
You'll obey us,
Black Grim Reaper.
Wedding swindler.
The scum who ran away after tainting my sister and taking her savings.
Please contact me if you spot him.
Is it okay to be doing this?
It's easier to give birth than to worry.
A Japanese idiom.
Apparently my mom used it quite often.
And what does it mean?
It's better to take action than to overthink things.
That's so like you.
That secret base brought back memories, eh?
So you were still using it.
Actually I was planning to close it.
But...
You're strong, Suou.
I swore to protect him.
So...
Say, Suou.
You said that the military took Tanya with them.
Yes.
Suou, I...
I got it.
Thanks, Nika.
Don't be reckless.
I won't.
This is the witness report of the professor's kid.
Anonymous tip, eh?
There seems to be many people who should've forgotten about the past that we missed.
Should I report it to Major Repnin?
No need.
He probably has his hands full with the training of the new monster he got yesterday.
They've started to move.
All right, July.
Don't move till I come to pick you up.
To think you'd arrive before the information trickled in...
You saved me quite some time.
You're angry, aren't you?
Are you going to kill me?
Go ahead and try it!
Then your picture will be all over the Internet!
I arranged it that way.
You'll be in deep shit if I don't return!
I swear!
Shion Pavlichenko.
Hand over the meteor core.
Then I won't kill you.
You're lying!
Contractors are all liars!
You can't trust them!
Ow...
What are you doing?!
Where's the meteor core?!
No! What the hell are you doing?!
Pervert! Moron! Molester! Lecher!
You're...
Where's Shion?
Why did you kill Papa?!
Why did you kill Bella as well?!
How can you...
do it that easy?
If you're a human...
I'm a contractor.
Is that why you can kill people without blinking?
Is that what being a rational contractor is about?
Can you even feel pain?!
Do contractors lose even that?!
What exactly are contractors?!
What's so fun about being one?!
Why are there people like you?!
Freeze!
Put your hands on the wall.
You've caused us some trouble, Shion.
Come with us.
We'll take you under our protection.
No!
You took Tanya...
Stop it, gentlemen.
I'll be the one taking the boy.
A contractor?
To think he would just show himself like that.
I'm a magician.
I can't get in the mood without an audience.
Fire.
Mysterious, isn't it?
Don't let them get away!
Even though he tried to kill me just now...
Why is he...
The show starts now.
After them!
A contractor?!
Are you a friend of that guy just now?
Wrong!
Take care of the rest, Youko-chan.
Let me down! Hey!
When they find out that I'm not Shion...
They'll kill you.
This is the most rational decision in that situation.
A cigarette cannot go through a coin.
There's a hole in the coin.
The gimmick is that the hole opens and closes with a delicate spring.
That's my remuneration.
I have to explain my tricks.
It's really painful for a magician.
But thanks to that, I can use real magic!
Not done yet!
Don't run away by yourself.
Why?
Putting someone in a box and then piercing it with a saber...
There are several ways to do that,
but the places the saber will pierce are planned beforehand.
If you adjust your body properly, you can avoid getting stabbed.
I told you. I'm a magician.
There're no tricks or gimmicks!
He's distorting the space surrounding him, huh.
Therefore neither swords nor bullets will harm him.
Distraction?
Instead of attacking him with the knife, he went for the face.
Not bad.
Hazuki-san, we're ready.
Don't!
Hei...
Don't, Yin!
Goodbye, Hei.
Kureteku yuubae ni senaka osarete
My back is pressed by the darkening glow of dusk
Arukidasu kage ga shimesu hou e
I start walking toward where my shadow points
Taenai ikutsu mo no deai to wakare o
Repeating the many, ceaseless encounters and partings
Kurikaeshi doko e mukau no ka
Where do I head to?
Hito wa dare mo mayoinagara
For all people, while they are lost,
tsumi to iu na no sadame o seotte
they bear the fate known as sin
Sore de mo nao ikiru imi o shiru darou
Nevertheless, I'll still learn of the meaning to live, right?
Bokura wa sou Day by Day
That's right, Day by Day,
ashita e tsuzuku michi no tochuu de
we're midway on the road leading to tomorrow
Now Say It Again kimi to futari no mama
Now Say It Again, though it'd be great if
irareta nara ii no ni naa...
I could remain together with you...
BK201 has...
disappeared?
It's the terminal.
The place where everything ends.
The white snowfield is drenched with blood and gunsmoke,
and the decay of their first love drifts into the hell.
The scream,
the invocation, an uninvited spell.
When you wake up, the Grim Reaper drifts away with your dream.
The terminal.
That's the turning point of fates.
And then...
a light was set free.