This isn't personal.
We're just trying to live.
You're as good as I've heard.
Unfortunately for you though, your fight doesn't end here.
The Syndicate will...
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
No, it was nothing.
I see.
So you're on your honeymoon?
Congratulations to the two of you!
Thank you.
If you had made reservations ahead of time, we would've prepared the best room for you.
It's okay. We just decided to travel and didn't really plan a schedule.
This way, please.
Let's go.
Here's your room.
Please enjoy yourselves.
Use your surveillance spirit and stand guard.
I'll go find us a ship.
Don't open the door for anyone.
We'll leave this place in the morning.
How do I get to Taiwan?
From here by ship?
Yes.
Well, the ship here should take you there, but you'd normally take a plane.
That's great. So there is a way.
Don't worry!
After the Americans left, our relations with China have been great.
Still, I wouldn't recommend it though.
Why's that?
To tell you the truth, because it's garbage.
It might be fine with you, but I don't think it'll go well with the girl behind you.
She looks like she'll fall over if the wind blows, just like me when I was young.
That's why I can tell she wouldn't want to.
I won't say anything bad, but you should take an airplane.
I told you to stay in the room!
This place is safe.
She says so too.
I'll be the one to decide that.
I know.
Where'd you get that hat?
The man from the hotel lent it to me.
You talked with him?
Yes.
If you act carelessly like that, you'll leave behind evidence.
You can't be sure even with someone you trust.
Don't act on your own. Understood?
Yes.
Be sure to return that.
Oh, welcome back!
Were you able to get your hands on boat tickets?
Y-Yeah.
That's good to hear!
I'll go prepare some dinner for you after I finish taking these down.
Huh? Meals were included?
Your wife requested it.
You did?
Yeah.
All done!
Oh yes, you can take a bath beforehand if you'd like.
Ah, what a lot of work to do!
What did you say when you ordered?
"Enough for ten people."
There are only two of us!
It makes us look suspicious!
You've been fighting ever since we left Tokyo.
This place is safe.
Take your time and eat.
Yin...
I'll keep watch.
Come again!
Thank you.
Hei.
I envy you.
For what?
It's a honeymoon, but you're able to prolong your stay if you want to.
Well, it only happens once in your life.
Welcome! Are you looking for a room?
Yes.
Thank you.
Ah, did you want something?
Sorry! It's just so hot I was in a daze!
What's wrong?
It's nothing. Come on.
Really?
True, the smell is strong,
but with our secret curry you'll experience a mild taste.
I recommended trying this dish at least once.
Then I'll have this, this and...
this, please.
Very well. Please wait a moment.
Come on, kitty.
Hello.
Too bad.
We almost got along there.
Where's your wife?
Sorry, I wasn't sure what kind of relationship you had, so I asked the manager.
She's preparing to go out now.
Where will you be going today?
Nowhere in particular.
I guess it's because there's nothing here.
I used to spend my time here like that with someone I used to go out with.
And where is he?
Would you normally ask that?
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
It's better to let these kinds of things out than to keep them in.
He's probably having an illicit affair with a young girl right now.
Hei.
Oh, did I cause a misunderstanding?
Hei...
It was you? Don't scare me like that!
What are you doing?
What were you looking for?
She isn't Amber.
She only looks like her.
What are you talking about?
She's a contractor.
It's best if we leave this place quickly.
Believe me.
Hei...
You should believe in me too.
I won't leave you alone.
You're lying.
That's too bad.
Why are you leaving so suddenly?
No real reason. Just felt like it.
I see. That's okay then.
The truth is, yesterday, a lone man left in a hurry too.
There was a man staying here too?
Didn't I tell you?
No, it was a lady.
I'm pretty sure it was a man.
An illusion?
Sir?
We're leaving here now!
Yin?
Yin!
Sir! Is there something wrong?
Sir! Sir?
Get down!
Ah, sir, what's...!
Run!
Where's Yin?
We should have taken a plane.
I can't contact the building at the eastern gate.
For how long?
Five minutes.
So they got to them.
Regroup!
We'll have to see the Black Grim Reaper dead another day.
We have to deliver this doll first.
Yeah, it's me.
We're going to take the doll and leave. Now!
I know how many people can get on the helicopter! It'll just be the doll and me.
You take care of the rest.
You want me to take care of the rest?
You want me to risk my life for a doll when he's coming?
I would run away right away.
Why are you bringing this up now?
Your opinion and report from this morning are completely different!
I thought it over.
I acted like Amber as you told me,
but there's no way a contractor can quicken the evolution of a doll.
The Black Grim Reaper is here.
Did you hear?
Yeah.
Then get to work already!
If you say so.
So he escaped the illusion through pain.
Producing illusions is only one part of my power.
My core ability is the control of people.
Still, why did you come here?
It should just be a doll to you.
Im...poss...ible!
You're just... a doll!
Tell the Syndicate this:
No matter what your plan is, I will crush it.
Got it?
Yin!
Don't...
Don't leave me alone!
Hei...
A
Can you fly? ano sora ni kagayaku Ziggy Star
Can you fly? Ziggy Star shining in the sky
kowareta yume kieta ai torimodoshite Fly away
Claiming back my broken dreams and lost love Fly away
Can you try? nikushimi o jihi e to kaete
Can you try? Changing this hate into compassion
kawaita mune o nurasu Darker than Black
Soaking up my dry chest Darker than Black
utsuro ni hikaru kousou no mado
From hollow spaces the windows on the skyscrapers shine,
hatasenu mama no yakusoku
a promise that remains unfulfilled
muda ni nagareta chi to namida ni somaru kanashii Game
Dyed in pointlessly flowing blood and tears, this sad Game
Oh, Where is my friend? hitori yozora o nagamereba
Oh, Where is my friend? If I Gaze at the night sky alone
hoshikage ni yureru kimi no Sweet smile
Swaying in the starlight is your Sweet smile
Can you try? tachihadakaru kabe o kowashite
Can you try? Break the wall that is blocking your way
tabidatsu toki o kizamu Darker than Black
The time to begin is ticking by Darker than Black
Are you dead?
It was close.
My real body almost got exposed.
Either way, we now know how to act from today's events.
The doll is certainly evolving faster by being with that contractor.
Much too fast.
Soon, no one will be able to handle her.
Including him.
No matter where we run, there is no end to it.
We're just heading toward another hell: Kowloon, Hong Kong.
The white darkness captures Yin, and doesn't let her go.