Five minutes to curtain!
What should I name the way I'm feeling right now?
No.
The truth is, I already know what it is.
What? Why are you spacing out?
Come on, it's show time!
Huh? Well... Right.
Are you gonna be okay?
You're not nervous about your lines or anything?
I'm fine! I've memorized the important parts.
Looks like you're still a gorilla with a high-functioning brain.
M-My bad! It just slipped out! Like old times.
Are you mad?
Let's go. It's about to start!
How can she smile like that?
A few minutes ago, she wouldn't get rid of her sulky face.
Something strange is going on.
Episode 20 - Showtime
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for your patience.
The next program will be a play performed by Class 1-C...
Romeo and Juliet!
The story we're about to tell is a tragic love story.
Two families, locked in a deadly feud...
The Montagues and the Capulets.
Young Master!
Mistress!
Born into these families, Romeo and Juliet,
in a cruel twist of fate, happen to fall in love!
O Romeo, why do our parents fight with such bitter hatred?
Normally, I'm sure that like us, they could take each other by the hand, and love one another.
If they could only understand half of my love for you, Romeo-sama, I'm sure...
Amazing. All she did was look over the script a minute ago.
She's definitely...
What was my next line, Romeo-sama?
Hey, come on, Juliet!
That's a crucial line!
Well, what can I do? I have to start off with such tedious lines!
How am I supposed to remember them?
Don't trash the script!
What's going on? Are they allowed to say that?
But it's funnier this way, you know!
Hey, the crowd loves it!
This just might work out for them!
Way to go, Young Master!
Mistress! Give it all you've got!
Whoa! You're the star of the show!
Young Master, you're a stud!
We're recording this, all right?
Those fools! I told them not to come!
Crap! Now we can't afford to screw this up at all!
A-All right, Juliet!
I get that you're nervous, so let's take it from the top! Okay?
O-Of course!
Come on, show me the money!
Juliet doesn't talk like that!
Do your best, guys!
Come on! You can do it!
All righty, they're on a roll!
Romeo is about to sneak out of his mansion.
Not heeding the servant who tries to stop him,
he is trying to go see Juliet.
Are you really going, then?
The Capulet family is out to kill you.
No matter how grave the danger, I still must go.
Even as we speak, she awaits me on that balcony.
Romeo cannot be stopped.
However, it is at this moment that the servant makes a decision.
The truth is, this servant is in love with Romeo!
The servant, believing this to be the last time she'll ever see Romeo alive,
makes up her mind to confess her love!
Hey! I never saw anything like that in the script!
You rascal!
Hey, Tsugumi! Tsugumi!
Uh... um... Romeo-sama.
The truth is, I have been... for a long time now, Romeo-sama, I have been in...
Lo...
I'm not saying it!
You idiot!
Whoa! The confession ends in failure!
Contrary to her appearance, this servant appears to be quite bashful!
Where the hell is that tool?
Let me shoot him!
While this is going on, Romeo sets off to meet Juliet!
Ladies and gentlemen, a big hand for our courageous servant!
Let me shoot him!
Good for you!
Damn you, Shuu! That wasn't necessary!
Please wait, Romeo-sama!
What's this? Wouldn't you know, a mysterious woman has burst onto the scene!
Just who could this woman be?
My name is... Um... Josephine!
My Romeo-sama's true love!
Unbelievable! Out of the blue, Romeo is revealed to be a two-timer!
But I thought you had a cold!
Who saw this coming?
If this is true, then it's a far cry from pure love!
Talk about every woman's enemy! Romeo, you suck!
Not cool, Romeo!
You're a jerk!
Don't trash me for no reason!
Um... Josephine? You seem to have the wrong idea.
Oh, my! My ears deceive me! Have you forgotten?
After what you did to me!
When you told me you would marry me, was that a lie?
So these two have taken their relationship even farther than we thought!
How are you going to take responsibility for this, Romeo?
Damn you, Romeo!
Damn it, he's adding subplots left and right!
Making a girl cry!
You dog!
What he did to her? I wonder what she means by that?
Now, now, Josephine!
There you go again, putting me on the spot like you always do.
Marriage?
You know that's not possible.
After all, you and I are brother and sister! We're related by blood!
What a shocking revelation! These two are actually siblings!
A skillful retort, Raku-sama.
It's one shocking revelation after another!
But if it's true, these two can't possibly get married!
But when it comes to love, such things don't matter!
Let us get married, my dearest brother, Romeo!
Despite it all, Josephine is unstoppable!
What the hell are they doing?
The younger sister who so sweetly cares for her elder brother... Josephine!
What on Earth is Romeo going to do?
Try to understand, Josephine!
The road I'll be traveling is a blood-soaked trail involving both families.
I don't want to get my fragile little sister involved in such an ordeal!
No...
Romeo-sama, you would be so concerned about my health?
O my Romeo...
Raku-sama...
I adore you... after all.
Whoa! This is where the fragile Josephine makes her exit!
Oh, my! Raku-sama, you're so bold!
And so Romeo has fended off an unexpected assassin!
Sorry, Tachibana. I'll come visit you later, okay?
Romeo is now on his way to see Juliet!
Oh, man...
Wait, Romeo!
Not again!
I can't allow you to see Juliet.
I am Juliet's elder brother!
Friedrich!
What the hell are you doing?!
Rumor has it that you're a piece of scum
who thinks nothing of breaking women's hearts while two-timing or even three-timing them.
That's a gross misunderstanding!
I won't hand over my sister to such a man!
If you think you're going to see her...
You'll have to defeat me first!
Now here's yet another sudden twist in the tale!
Will Romeo find a way to make it safely to Juliet?
Hey! Uh, Brother?
What do you think you're doing? That's dangerous!
You stay out of this, Juliet.
This man is dangerous.
If only this man didn't exist...
I could have you by my side forever!
Whoa! It appears that Big Bro has a hardcore little sister complex!
What's the matter? You're totally helpless, aren't you?
Shut up! This isn't fair!
You're the only one who's armed!
It's over. Prepare yourself, Romeo.
I'm not gonna just lay down and die, damn you!
You're pathetic, dirt bag!
Falls
DANGER
Whoaaaaa!
Thanks to their furious battle, the castle walls have collapsed!
Who would have thought?
They're both buried under the rubble!
Are they safe or not?
Romeo!
Aha! There's Romeo!
Romeo is on his feet!
The winner of this duel is Romeo!
I'm coming for you... Juliet.
Seriously, he's such an idiot.
Look at him! He's all beat up.
Always, always such a huge...
No, no, I'm the idiot.
All this time, I've just been too afraid to admit it.
But...
It's about time that I did.
O Romeo, wherefore art thou Romeo?
If only you weren't Romeo, the son of the Montagues,
nothing and nobody would get in the way of our love.
Romeo, doff thy name, and for that name which is no part of thee, take all myself.
I take thee at thy word.
Call me but love, and I'll be new baptized.
Henceforth I never will be Romeo.
My beloved Juliet...
Yes.
I love you, too, Romeo-sama.
That's right.
The fact that I'm in love with him.
Good job.
There you go again with your clichés!
I wanted to try it, just once.
It's like pretending to be one of those girly girls.
Making it obvious doesn't score extra points.
We made it work... somehow. Right?
Didn't you see the audience's reaction?
I gotta give you props for pulling off something like that without even rehearsing.
You even had most of your lines down.
Man... If you only knew how hard I had it learning my own.
I like it! Shower me with more compliments!
Sure, sure! Awesome, totally awesome!
It's kind of similar, don't you think?
The play... and our own story.
Our families feuding with each other...
And the two respective heirs...
Being in love...
Well, the biggest difference is that we're not really in love.
If that part's not the same, then they're totally different stories.
True, you're right about that.
Sorry...
for how I've been lately.
For going crazy on you.
Sorry...
for my nasty attitude and all.
for saying mean things,
and slapping you across the face.
I'm sorry.
I'll go back to normal now.
Back to the way I was before...
I'll go back to being my usual self,
like before.
When we were polar opposites in every way,
the fake couple that hated each other.
I'll go back to being that person.
So please... um...
Will you forgive me?
I don't see a problem with it.
If we're a fake couple that hates each other, then it's only natural that we'd fight.
But you just told me that you didn't hate me by a long shot.
No, listen!
You're the one who just brought up hating each other.
Then, were you lying to me?
No, no! What are you talking about?
Listen, do you want me to hate you or not? Which is it?
Jeez...
What about you, then?
Don't you hate me?
Me? Well, I...
absolutely abhor you.
Listen, there's still time,
and I haven't seen much of the Culture Festival yet.
If you're gonna twist my arm, then I'll keep you company.
What's it gonna be?
Jeez! Guess I have no choice.
Where the hell did that smile come from?
Seriously...
She's so cheerful now, you can't tell she was sulking before the play.
Hey, look! It's Romeo and Juliet!
You're right!
We saw the play!
It was fantastic!
Good job!
Why did she do a total 180 on her attitude?
I don't hate you, not by a long shot.
Does this mean she's been so pissed at me all this time because she thought I hated her?
But that would mean...
All right, everybody!
Cheers!
Man, that was a roaring success!
I heard that everyone was raving about our class!
Pass the juice around to everybody!
We've got lots of snacks, too!
Hey! There's our leading lady, Kirisaki-san!
Good job!
You did that pretty much on the fly, didn't you?
How did you learn your lines?
I have to say, I was even a little moved!
Well, for a moment there I wasn't sure how it was gonna end up,
Thanks!
but we gotta hand it to our famous couple!
They really brought their A-game, didn't they?
So did you two make up?
More or less, I think.
But hey, you sure gave us a shock!
The way she slapped you last week,
the whole class was like, "Are they history?"
For real?
Thanks!
But you can rest easy.
I did you a solid and told everyone that you'd realized you were a masochist!
You pig!
How the hell did you come up with that vicious excuse? Damn you!
By the way, how's Marika-chan?
I just stopped by to see her.
Talk about pushing yourself too hard.
Raku-sama!
Sprained your ankle? On the day of the play?
Sorry, I didn't get to play Juliet.
This is funny to you?
What were you thinking? This was your chance!
Hey, you want a crepe?
I'll go get you one.
Aha! Found you, Maiko Shuu!
You weasel, where do you get off making that narration?
Whoa! Seishirou-chan! Now, now...
That was just me spicing things up!
Spice my ass!
Hey! Come back here! I'll spice you up, you bastard!
Ichijou-kun?
Here. Sorry, but would you mind giving this to Kosaki?
Scum! Trash! Low-life!
I don't mind, but why?
You'll shoot a hole in me!
I'm going to get busy scarfing down noodles right now. That's why.
Onodera!
Ichijou-kun!
Here, Miyamoto wanted me to give you this.
How's the ankle?
Oh, it's fine.
So you two made up, huh?
Huh? Yeah.
Well, we managed somehow.
Thank you, Ichijou-kun.
If you hadn't talked Chitoge-chan into it,
I just know that I would've regretted what happened today forever.
None of that was your fault, Onodera.
The one who wanted to play Juliet more than anyone else,
was none other than you, right?
Yes, well, that is true, but...
Did you feel that strongly about it?
You know, about playing Juliet...
No, actually...
Um...
I guess so. Yes, I was.
It was a totally personal reason,
but the truth is, I think I wanted to play her no matter what.
Because I had a feeling that it was going to be a really special memory for me.
That badly?
Hey, Onodera!
Listen, if you really want to...
This is amazing!
What a beautiful sunset!
There's nobody around here, so I thought we could just have at it.
Yes! I'm still a little embarrassed, though.
All right, then.
Okay.
Wow, this is still pretty nerve-wracking!
I'm embarrassed too, you know!
All right.
My beloved Juliet.
I despise everything that keeps us apart.
Why would the gods put us through such an ordeal as this?
O Romeo, why do our parents fight with such bitter hatred?
Normally, I'm sure that like us, they could take each other by the hand, and love one another.
If they could only understand half of my love for you, Romeo-sama...
I'm sure...
Alas, Juliet, it is time to say goodbye.
Ichijou-kun.
Thank you! You made me happy.
Really, really happy!
It is time to say goodbye.
Tomorrow at sunset, I'll come see you at that balcony again.
Will you promise to wait for me there again?
Ichijou-kun, you botched your line.
Sunset, just as the fallen leaves start blowing in the wind.
Come back here, you!
It's our first, unforgettable high school Culture Festival,
and the curtain has rung down.
Seishirou-chan, you can't fire that indoors!
kirameki dashita yume wo
Those twinkling dreams…
fukinuketa kaze ha erimoto wo toori
The wind that blew past my collar
mada dare mo shiranai haru wo yobikomu
Ushers in the spring, though nobody is aware
me ga atta shunkan waraiai
The moment our eyes met we made each other laugh
houkago nandomo (kimi no) tonari de sugoshita
After school, I often passed the time (with you) by your side
soratakaku natte koe kikoetara
When I heard that voice drifting high into the sky
tooi shourai ki ni natte
I felt uneasy about the distant future
shiroi kanousei sawatta
And felt the vast possibilities
souzou daiarii
The diary of imagination
katakoto datte taido de wakaru noni
may be incomprehensible but even though
I get a sense of it from the tone
zenbu zenbu mitai
I want to see it all, all of it,
honto no koto tashikametai
and confirm the truth
memorii kakaekirenakutatte ii
There’s no need to hold on to all my memories,
ima no watashi motto motto soba de
the me of right now
kimi to itai kara kiite
Wants to be by your side more and more, so listen
kirameki dashita yume wo
To those twinkling dreams