Yum!
This is great!
Don't eat so fast.
It should be enjoyed leisurely with the afternoon tea.
Wait... I don't have time for this!
Mom! Mom is here!
And you say that with sponge cake all over your mouth.
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
Nee dareka oshiete
Hey, someone, tell me
Minna sou na no kana?
Is everyone like that?
Kyou ga shiawase nara
That they 'feel it's good enough
Sore de ii to omoeru tte
if they're if happy today'
Osanai koro ni wa
When I was young
Tashika ni atta yo
They certainly existed
Yume o oikaketeta
I pursued my dreams
Demo sore mo tooi kioku
But that's also a distant memory
Kotae no nai mainichi ga
The each unanswered day-
Tada sugite iku jikan ga
The time that is simply passing by-
Kore kara saki dou naru no darou?
What will happen beyond now?
Wakaranai...
They don't know...
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
You've still got it, Michiro-chan.
Nice to meet you! I mean... uh...
I'm always looking at your picture...
That makes me sound like some fanboy!
I hadn't planned on coming here,
but I had no choice since it's for my remuneration.
A girl came here, right?
Yeah! Isn't she pretty?
I'll introduce you to her!
Maybe you'll become her mother-in-law some day!
You know, with those classic fights between bride and mother-in-law.
You're a strange kid...
welcoming the mother who abandoned you.
Isn't that because of his good upbringing?
He's a free, heaven-sent child who's not restrained by common sense.
Upbringing, huh...
It'll be done in twenty minutes.
You're leaving already, Mom?
What about the celebration?
I have never been much of a mother, but I'll tell you this...
Don't get too involved with that girl.
You'll get hurt.
Darn! Mom got NG'd too!
NG?
You've barely even gotten her to notice you!
Oh, that's right! I was flirting with her!
Hold on! Norio!
Michiru-chan...
Even with my guidance...
there are times when you just get hurt anyway.
A whale?
Hei, how is it going?
The signal is unstable...
What's wrong?
Nothing. I'm just imagining things.
Hei's going in the wrong direction.
Wrong direction?
They're here.
I got trapped...
Looks like you're cut off now, BK201.
I thought Misaki-chan's methods were a bit troublesome,
but you really fell for it.
I guess that's what you call fate.
Looks like we can finally fight one-on-one,
BK201.
It doesn't hurt at all!
Hei, what's wrong?
That's strange.
Why don't you zap me?
Why so stingy?
Hei, what was that?
Can you hear me?
Where's BK201?
Don't interfere, Misaki-chan.
I'm in the middle of having fun!
Capture him alive!
I have something to ask hi—
Open the rack.
Hei couldn't have been...
July, which truck is the cargo in?
In the third one.
In that large container.
In there...
You just keep running.
If you just try to buy time, you'll get my honey killed!
I taught her how to protect herself.
Who are you talking about?
You got another mistress already?
I'm talking about that doll, Izanami.
Doll?
Don't tell me.
There's a naked girl in the container.
A human?
No one told me about that.
And we're supposed to destroy the goods?
Don't worry.
I hit the crane, too.
The crane? This is a human!
I'm a contractor. I can do it.
Damn it!
What's wrong?
I've found something interesting.
Izanagi?
Probably.
Don't destroy it.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Get out of there!
She's coming that way.
You're no match for her.
Run!
To eliminate your irregularities as a contractor.
I have to shoot her...
What are you saying, young miss?
He told me to shoot.
Hey! What's going on? July!
I know her. I've met her before.
What?
The Scandinavian doll with silver hair.
That's...
Why? Why is she...
Beats me.
More importantly, let's get it rockin'.
Hey, now! That's cold!
Hey, are those contractors?
Don't look at them!
If you don't ignore them and just pass by, they'll eat you alive.
Hey, is there a contractor above us?
Psst! Ignore him!
It'll take your hair!
Huh, wait!
The truck...
I took it...
Where did they go?
July, the measurement...
What are you doing?!
That broad is already over there!
Distance: 1500.
Wind velocity: 3.
Blowing from northwest.
5mm to the left.
Don't shoot!
Don't shoot, Suou!
Yin?
Send half of the men to back up Hazuki and capture the enemy.
The rest will confirm the status of the goods and continue with the transportation!
Retreat along the eastern route. If I don't make the rendezvous point, it's all up to you.
Hey!
Go!
BK201 can release electricity in any direction he wishes.
Facing him underwater is...
Are you sure?
No need to worry.
The analysis of the data we took in Russia is correct.
BK201 has lost his abilities as a contractor.
Episode 6
The Fragrance is Sweet, the Heart is Bitter
Are we going to leave him behind?
We'll wait for him to contact us and regroup.
And if not, then yes.
Who's Yin?
A doll who used to be part of our team.
Part of our team?
She and Hei have a history together.
History...
Thanks for earlier.
Man, she's nowhere to be found.
Figures...
I didn't know anything about her...
Norio!
Sorry, I don't feel like wasting my youth with you guys.
Awesome! She's having a death match with a contractor!
She's facing some old woman!
Don't tell me...
it's already come to the mother-in-law versus bride fight?!
Suou!
I don't plan on hurting you.
My son would get pretty angry at me too.
Don't come!
Come with me!
With you?
Come.
Stand back!
No!
You need to talk!
There's no need for a catfight amongst women!
A surveillance spirit.
What?
Mom!
Mom! Mom!
Mom...
Why...
Norio...
Did you do this?
Why did you kill my mom?
Because you're a contractor?
How can contractors kill people just like that?!
Let's go.
You knew it, didn't you?
Yes.
But I didn't expect them to use a submarine.
She always comes up with these crazy traps.
What do you want?
You can't follow my orders unless you know my objective?
Contractors are unexpectedly wet, huh?
I won't work for you.
I can't trust you.
That's my line.
You've been telling me how you were going to kill that doll with your own hands.
I'm so disappointed.
Contractors are murderers.
Even though he gave me the order...
Why couldn't he kill Yin?
Because of their history?
Maybe. Why don't you ask him?
That submarine seemed to be headed to Tokyo.
But why Yin?
She was there when that contractor died.
Yin's surveillance spirit.
So it was all Yin.
Yeah.
And now we're going to Tokyo.
Now our routes match, young miss.
Tokyo...
Hei.
Did you lose your powers?
Anti-contractor weapon...
So this stole BK201's powers.
I'm impressed you've guessed all that.
Who are you people?
What's Section 3?
I can't tell you, but...
It's better if you don't see me as an ally.
If BK201's doll, Izanami, is here...
Yes... he'll come after us.
Where's this place?
Just something adults do.
Some people have a second house somewhere.
July, please put some sugar in it.
What are you looking at?
He called that contractor "mom."
He said he liked me.
He hates me now, I'm sure.
Thanks.
What kind of feeling is love?
Don't shoot!
Don't shoot, Suou!
He called my name.
I can't bear eating weeds again.
Where did you get the ingredients?
We won't have our vitamins without vegetables.
And I hate canned food because it stinks of metal.
This will make the smell go away.
Don't shoot anymore.
Why?
It doesn't fit you.
You're out of alcohol, right?
Yeah.
You're going to buy some?
I won't shoot.
So... please don't drink alcohol in exchange.
Are those your terms?
I'm going to buy vegetables.
Wait!
Norio!
I wrapped the remaining cake. It's still soft.
I won't eat that!
You knew this day would come when Michiru-chan became a contractor.
You finally met her. Isn't that good enough?
No! Not at all!
Even if you meet for a second,
that second just passes by.
You might meet again somewhere.
Isn't that good enough?
Oh, Ama-no-Iwato.
See each other?
What the hell?! I'm still in shock!
This picture is the only memory I have of my mom!
I'll keep thinking about her!
I can't forget that girl, either!
I keep thinking of her! So...
Make sure to eat up.
You'll become a good guy.
Hey! Don't eat all of it.
Kureteku yuubae ni senaka osarete
My back is pressed by the darkening glow of dusk
Arukidasu kage ga shimesu hou e
I start walking toward where my shadow points
Taenai ikutsu mo no deai to wakare o
Repeating the many, ceaseless encounters and partings
Kurikaeshi doko e mukau no ka
Where do I head to?
Hito wa dare mo mayoinagara
For all people, while they are lost,
tsumi to iu na no sadame o seotte
they bear the fate known as sin
Sore de mo nao ikiru imi o shiru darou
Nevertheless, I'll still learn of the meaning to live, right?
Bokura wa sou Day by Day
That's right, Day by Day,
ashita e tsuzuku michi no tochuu de
we're midway on the road leading to tomorrow
Now Say It Again kimi to futari no mama
Now Say It Again, though it'd be great if
irareta nara ii no ni naa...
I could remain together with you...
What's wrong?
Nothing.
The blizzard obstructs the path and blocks the darkness with a pure, white blanket.
After the wandering there's only suspicion and solitude.
The sympathy you hold on to is just another trap.
A doll will not talk.
It's not even alive.
The sound of your heart that you're not meant to hear.
And then... no one will be left to notice.