Seriously!
What are you going to do?!
It's already summer vacation!
You haven't made any progress whatsoever with Ichijou-kun yet!
I just don't understand how you can be so spineless.
After all the help I gave you, after you got all those chances,
how can you possibly not make any progress?
I'm sorry.
I wish you'd take the initiative to try asking him out yourself once in a while.
Well, not that I think you're capable of such a thing, Kosaki-chan.
But at this rate, you'll never get anywhere.
U-Um, Ruri-chan.
What?
You see, the thing is, tomorrow...
I invited Ichijou-kun to my house.
Episode 16: Typhoon
The other day
End of Semester Ceremony
Ichijou-kun!
H-Hey, Onodera. What's up?
Do you have a second?
Um, uh, well...
Um, do you... have any plans this weekend?
Are you free, by any chance?
D-Don't tell me she's about to ask me out!
The thing is... I wanted to ask if you could take on a part-time job.
Oh, it's just a job.
A job?
You see, one of our employees has an emergency and can't come in.
My mom said it'd be best to find someone who's a good cook.
And so, since you're the only one I know who can cook...
If you're interested...
Here I was, thinking that I wouldn't be seeing Onodera for a while because of summer vacation...
I've never had a part-time job before,
but today I'm gonna show Onodera my good side!
Japanese Sweets
ONODERA
I sure haven't been to Japanese Sweets Onodera in a while.
Excuse me...
What did you say?!
You don't have a single product in stock?
That's not my problem!
Do something about it! Isn't that your job?
Do you hear me? Make sure you have it by this evening!
I'll head over there myself to pick it up later. Got that?
Unbelievable!
Dammit... We should be okay as far as baked goods go,
but what am I going to do about the raw sweets?
What are you looking at?
What's a student doing in my shop?
Go suck on a lollipop!
Uh, no... Actually...
Mom!
Wait, wait! That's him!
He's the temp!
Kosaki...
G-Good morning, Ichijou-kun.
Thanks for coming in today.
Th-Thanks for having me.
Whoa... That uniform!
She is one cute shopgirl!
He's the guy?
I was wondering who it could be when you said you knew a great cook.
But it's just one of your classmates?
Not to mention, he's kind of a bean sprout.
Kosaki.
What I was looking for was someone who I could throw to the dogs with no problem, you know?
Ordinarily, the kitchen is a
professional's sacred realm.
To even think that a mere high school student can cook...
But Ichijou-kun's not like that at all!
I'll have you know that Ichijou-kun cooks his family's meals by himself, every single day!
And we're talking about a ton of food!
Um... Enough for dozens of people, all by himself!
Well, if you insist...
Why don't you whip something up, then?
I'll determine whether or not you're up to the job.
If it's no good, I'll send you packing. Got it?
What?! Just like that?
Well, I did take a crash course in Japanese sweets,
but that doesn't mean I can pass...
Give it all you've got, Ichijou-kun!
Let's see, next is...
He's wiping the condensation off the bowl to be thorough.
It looks like he doesn't have a clue about Japanese sweets,
but he's no newbie when it comes to cooking.
Uh... I'm done.
Uh...
Did you say your name was Ichijou-kun?
Yes...
All right. Marry my daughter!
Hey, at first I wasn't so sure,
but you brought home a surprisingly worthy man, didn't you?
Man?!
Ichijou-kun's not really that kind of—
You're always spacing out, so I was starting to worry!
But this kid, he's got what it takes,
and he'll make a great heir to the family business, don't you think?
I told you, it's not like that!
Well, we can talk about it later.
I guess I can kind of trust him now.
Kosaki, show him how to make bean jam paste and the easiest sweets.
I'll be in the shop till noon.
But really, you...
You should see your face when you're in front of a guy!
Not only that, but to took this opportunity to introduce me to a guy.
My little Kosaki...
You. Little. Devil.
Mom!
See ya!
That mother of yours is something else.
Sorry, Ichijou-kun.
Please forgive her.
All right, come with me. I'm going to show you some stuff.
And next... You add some granulated sugar to this dough over here...
But really, Onodera, I can't believe you remember every little step.
I guess you help out a lot, making stuff like this, right?
Nope.
I don't actually get to make anything. I'm pretty awful at it.
Ever since I was little, I've always thought it looked fun, so I watched.
That's probably why.
Well, they did let me try making some myself one time, but...
Everyone who ate my sweets ended up keeling over,
and the shop was shut down for three days!
She's had her deadly touch forever, then!
But the one thing I did get praised for was my finishing touches,
and since I've been helping with that all this time, it's become my area of expertise.
See?
Whoa... Awesome!
Hey, I'm done mixing.
Does this look about right?
Oh! Just like that! It looks so yummy!
You perfect the taste, Ichijou-kun, and I'll perfect the shape.
That way we'll make some great Japanese sweets!
What was that just now? A proposal?
Y-You want me to marry into this family?
Kosaki! I'm stepping out for a bit, so watch over the shop!
Okay!
Hey, just look at us now! Can you believe the great vibe we've got going on?
I almost want to stay here forever and start a family!
Welcome!
Hey! So you're holding down the fort today, Kosaki-chan? Lucky me!
Hello, Yoshino-san.
Thank you for your patronage!
Would you like your usual?
You certainly have a good memory!
What do you say? How about we go on a date sometime, you and I?
Oh, please! There you go again!
Your change comes out to 615 yen.
Oh, uh, thanks.
See you around, Kosaki-chwan!
Seriously! Flirting around like that at his age!
He's always like that.
Hey, Ichijou-kun.
Do you still go out on dates with Chitoge-chan?
What the—Why would I go out with her?!
What do you mean, why?
U-Uh, sure we do!
Of course we do!
I mean, we are going out and all...
Um, Ichijou-kun...
I guess you haven't heard.
I know that you two aren't really boyfriend and girlfriend.
I knew it! I thought it was strange.
How did you... Since when?
Chitoge-chan told me quite a while ago.
I was sure that you already knew.
I can't believe that moron!
If you're gonna tell Onodera, then let me know, damn it!
I see...
Ichijou-kun never knew about it.
That's why he acted like he was in a relationship even when we were alone.
But then, why would he hide that photo?
Did you say something?
No, nothing.
Seriously?
Onodera knew all this time that we weren't dating?
Hold up. If that's the case...
Then does that mean I'm in the clear to tell her how I feel about her now?
No, no, hold on a second! No way it's that simple!
Gotta get the timing right too and all...
Seems like it's gotten really windy outside, huh?
Yeah, you're right.
Come to think of it, they just said on the news that a typhoon was coming.
It's starting to come down.
It's getting pretty heavy. I wonder if your mom is all right.
Yes? This is Japanese Sweets Onodera.
Mom?
Wait a second, Mom!
Is something wrong?
She says she can't make it back because the weather's too bad.
And to look after the shop...
Oh, man. Well, I can understand why, though.
She also said...
It would be too dangerous for you to go home,
so I should have you stay the night.
What?!
She wants me to stay the night?
Me, spend the night at Onodera's?
B-But... Onodera, isn't there anyone else home?
Dad had some business to take care of and won't be coming home.
My little sister lives in a dorm.
You have a little sister?
I never knew that—
Wait, what am I saying?!
Is this for real? A night alone with Onodera?
Can I really stay the night here?
Come on, no way! Of course I can't!
I can't just spend the night at a girl's house alone with her.
Sorry, but can I borrow an umbrella? I can handle a little drizzle on my own.
What? But—
Whoa! The roof tiles are coming down!
Watch out! Better not wander around outside too much!
H-How did this happen?
Rather, how does Onodera feel right now?
She's gotta be uneasy about this, right?
This is bad!
What am I going to do? I can't help but grin!
Just knowing that we were going to work together was almost too much for me to handle!
What should I do? I can't stop my face from going slack!
Y-You can't do this, Kosaki! You can't let him see you looking so pathetic!
Come back! Come back, normal face!
All right, perfect!
Um, so what do you think we should do, Ichijou-kun?
Um... about dinner?
Why are you smirking, Onodera?
U-Um...
There was this really funny TV show on yesterday,
and I randomly remembered it!
Oh, no! What am I gonna do? I can't hide it at all!
I knew it. She's probably nervous.
I-I can't let myself panic.
Just change the subject...
Okay, why don't we talk it over and decide?
Come up to my room, and—
Did I really say something so audacious?
Are you really okay with that?
Letting me come up to your room?
O-Of course I am!
Because it's n-nothing special, okay?
But wait here a second. Let me tidy it up a little!
And I also want to change!
S-Sure! Don't rush on my account, okay? Just take your time.
Listen to that! She's totally cleaning up.
Febreze
Will this do, I wonder?
Guess I'll go with this!
I'm making him wait. I should hurry...
Sorry! Thanks for waiting! You can come up now!
I've never been in a girl's bedroom before.
Who would've thought Onodera's would be the first?
Just make yourself at home, all right?
So this is Onodera's room.
I-It's really cute.
And it totally smells great, too!
Oh, I'll be back with some tea.
Just wait here, okay?
The bed that Onodera sleeps in every night...
The desk where she studies...
Hell, this is where she just changed...
Stop imagining things like that!
You'll lose all sense of reason!
No way!
Is this a photo of Onodera's crush?
I know I shouldn't look at it...
No, of course I can't look at it!
It's totally wrong!
Thanks for your patience!
I've brought us some tea—
H-Hey, thanks! I really appreciate it!
Help yourself.
So what should we do?
We still have some time.
Want to talk about something?
Yeah, good idea.
Want to play a word-chain game?
O-Onodera?
H-Hold up! It's still too early for that!
That's what you do when you've completely run out of things to talk about!
It's a graveyard where conversations go to die!
Right, you're right. Sorry!
I guess suddenly being thrown into such a situation is pretty nerve-wracking.
Normally, I wouldn't have any problem talking to you.
Damn it! Onodera's struggling just as much as I am!
I gotta man up and find the right topic...
I know!
Do you have your yearbook from junior high, maybe?
That might be the most surefire topic of them all, but hey, at least it'll get the conversation going.
Good idea!
Hold on a second!
Wow! This really brings back memories, doesn't it?
Just six months ago, we were junior high students.
I wonder what you call this feeling.
Hey! Look at this.
The ball game tournament when we were first-years!
That was when I got to be friends with Ruri-chan.
Oh, is that right?
You and I have been in the same class since we were second-years.
Although it wasn't till the third year that we actually started talking...
Here's Onodera again. Man, even as a junior high student she was adorable.
Hey, here she is again...
Here, too...
I gotta give myself props!
No matter how tiny she is, I can always spot Onodera.
I guess that makes me a little happy.
What?
I'm not in any of these photos, am I?
That's not true. See, here you are!
You're right.
And here... and here...
Here you are again!
Oh, and look, there you are again!
You're amazing, Onodera.
I can't believe you spotted such tiny images!
Well, it's because you stand out, Ichijou-kun.
I mean you were popular with the girls, weren't you?
No I wasn't! If anyone was popular, it was you!
Not me, by a long shot!
It's because you're really nice, Ichijou-kun!
I am not!
It just might be that you haven't realized it yourself, you know.
Not a chance.
When I was in junior high,
I knew at least one girl who had a crush on you.
No way! Who was it?
That's a secret.
I can never tell you.
You can't just say that and not tell me! That's not fair, Onodera!
We've already graduated, so it doesn't matter, right?
I'm not telling! Not unless that girl gives me permission.
When did you meet Maiko-kun?
Oh, well, we actually go way back.
We haven't been able to get rid of each other since kindergarten.
Really? That's amazing!
You know, actually, talking to Onodera is really fun.
If only this moment could last forever and ever.
What's the matter, Onodera?
It stopped raining.
Typhoon No. 16 has swerved way off its original course,
and is now heading towards the sea to the east.
God damn it! Curse you, typhoon!
Can't you take a hint at all? Damn it!
Right, then I'll be heading home after all.
It isn't right for a guy and a girl to spend the night alone in a house.
Damn it! I want to spend the night!
I want to talk with her some more!
Oh, Onodera... Aren't you gonna stop me from going?
Don't go!
Yes, you're right.
It would be kind of weird for you to stay when it's stopped raining.
Of course it is. You're right.
Of course it's weird. I knew it all along! I not crying over it!
Thanks for today. I had such a great time!
Hey, so did I.
I wonder... when I'll get to see her next.
That part-time job was only for today,
and it's still summer vacation.
What's wrong?
Well, come to think of it, you and I...
We talk a lot at school, but now that I think about it, we don't—
Go, Raku!
—know each other's e-mail addresses, do we?
That's right! Now that you mention it, we don't.
Okay, why don't we exchange them now?
Hold on a second, I'm going to set up the infrared.
A-All right! Sure you don't mind, Onodera? Thank goodness!
I'm so happy that I built up the courage to ask!
Okay, I sent it!
R-Right!
I never expected Ichijou-kun to ask me.
That makes me happy!
Things have been going so great today, divine punishment could be waiting for me!
I had such a good time today.
When will I get to see him again?
Ichijou Raku
When we were in junior high,
the girl who liked you was...
Ichijou Raku
It was me.
Just... kidding...
All right, see you later, Ichijou-kun.
Good night!
Right! Call me anytime you need my help again!
Nearly two years after we met, I finally got her e-mail address!
So freakin' happy!
New Message
Kosaki
Onodera
New Message
Kosaki
Onodera
Would it be too shameless to send her a text right now?
No, it should be okay!
I'm sure we both had a blast talking, and I want to keep talking to her more than anything right now!
All right! Sent!
Here it comes!
Kosaki Onodera
1 New Message
Inbox
Kosaki
Onodera
I enjoyed it too.
Good night.
Inbox
Kosaki
Onodera
I enjoyed it too.
Good night.
Huh?
Good night? Is that all?
Don't tell me that us having a blast was just my imagination!
No, there's no way...
After all... Th-That...
I did great today, didn't I?
Ruri-chan might even praise me.