I saw a whale when I opened my eyes...
So I thought I would take a picture...
But I thought better of it.
Why did I even entertain such a thought?
There is no reason to want a photo of it.
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
Nee dareka oshiete
Hey, someone, tell me
Minna sou na no kana?
Is everyone like that?
Kyou ga shiawase nara
That they 'feel it's good enough
Sore de ii to omoeru tte
if they're if happy today'
Osanai koro ni wa
When I was young
Tashika ni atta yo
They certainly existed
Yume o oikaketeta
I pursued my dreams
Demo sore mo tooi kioku
But that's also a distant memory
Kotae no nai mainichi ga
The each unanswered day-
Tada sugite iku jikan ga
The time that is simply passing by-
Kore kara saki dou naru no darou?
What will happen beyond now?
Wakaranai...
They don't know...
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
Here is your business card.
Ichinose Yayoi?
Third Chief Clerk of the Ministry of Internal Affairs and
Communications Statistics Office, Second Investigation Division.
Nice, you can say it without stumbling or mispronouncing.
As expected of an elite officer from public safety.
U-Um... Nice to meet you.
My name is Sawasaki.
I'm Shizume.
Nice to meet ya.
Hazuki.
Either way, names are just aliases in here.
You'll be working with them.
A pleasure to meet you.
You seem displeased.
You don't like us?
Whether I do or not doesn't matter. It's my job.
Perhaps this poster will catch your interest?
This is the man whom we assume is BK201.
Lee Shenshun.
The self-proclaimed Chinese exchange student who was hiding in Shinjuku Okubo two years ago.
Correct?
Yes.
He has been working for the CIA the last few years.
He left the syndicate and is working for the CIA now?
But it looks like that's all in the past now.
The CIA is also frantically searching for him now.
But his star disappeared.
He's alive?
Unless it's his ghost we fought.
What happened?
Well...
The details are still unknown.
We are continuing our investigation in order to find out what happened.
That's why you're here.
Your priority is the capture of BK201, and Shion, Professor Mikhail Pavlichenko's son.
Shion?
The cutie that BK201 is dragging along.
What's the meaning of this, Chief?!
How can you resign without telling me...I mean, anyone?
Guess you could say I needed a change of scenery.
I no longer have a place with the police.
You called the other day too.
I hope you didn't get yourself into anything dangerous.
Chief?
Please tell me, Chief!
Kirihara! What-
You got her name wrong.
Wait? What?
Here you go, Yayoi.
Getting information from your friends in public safety?
That's meaningless.
All information from the police, public safety, and the military should all be accessible here.
I appreciate your advice.
What are you doing?!
You're being frigid.
You should feel through your body.
Your lover won't notice you if you only rely on your brain.
Lover?
I can't believe you're remaining chaste for BK201.
Cut this out!
Darn, I just got rejected.
To think we are able to see cranes at the ruins of the Heaven's War...
Close the curtain.
We'll be in the city soon.
What?
Nothing.
You're pooping there again?
Isn't your sphincter a bit too loose?!
Stitch it together already!
Geez...
Oh my.
Hello!
Hello.
You sure look delicious!
Something smells...
Oh, pardon me.
I want to be good friends with you.
So, what's your name?
We just recently moved here.
I'm Lee Honshik.
A pleasure to meet you.
These are my siblings.
Oh, siblings...
See you later.
They certainly are multicultural...
Smile dammit.
Smiling isn't in my programming.
Why are we doing this?
To comply with our client's wishes.
I will train you to be an agent.
What do you mean by training?
Don't ever talk back to me.
That is, if you want to survive as a contractor.
You're off by 18cm to the left.
Wind velocity: 3.
Distance: 1200.
2mm to the right.
They'll notice you if you shoot when there is no noise coming from the construction site.
Use your brain a little.
Change your target.
Look through your scope.
On the right.
Further down.
It's a mobile target.
A mobile target...
I couldn't shoot that time.
Distance: 300.
Wind blowing from southeast.
Wind velocity: 5.
2mm to the right.
Now I can...
My aim was misaligned.
If you're a contractor, come up with a better lie.
I won't miss this time.
What a brave girl.
Can she kill someone who's just annoying?
No.
I won't become someone like that.
But let me make this clear.
I'm going to Tokyo.
And that's the only reason I'm following you.
If you do any—
You just have to obey my orders.
Despite being a contractor, she's still a child.
If you don't hold back, she'll die.
Eat whatever you want.
I don't have any money.
What about you?
He used to eat so much, but now he only drinks alcohol, eh?
Hey Nori-chan, let's dance.
Dance?
Are you sure we're dancing?
Listen up, boys!
You're not dancing because you want to! You're being made to dance!
Nothing will happen if we just fool around here!
We should go and find something bright and shining!
Something that will make us feel alive!
Here we go with Prof. Norio's sermon.
Hey, I'm serious.
It's all cool, Norio-chan.
Will you listen to me?
What? What?
It's a girl.
Oh, it's just a kid.
You'd fuck anything that has a hole, eh?
I won't deny that.
Eek! Pedophile!
Creep!
I've found it!
Something that makes me feel alive!
That guy.
You know him?
I guess there is no way...
So I'm staying at a love hotel with a kid, huh?
Well, it's not a bad place to hide.
Is that enough for you?
Who's he?
Who's the client?
What's the training about?
He's a contractor, isn't he?
Why is he doing this?
So many questions.
Let me ask you a question then.
Why don't you run away?
I haven't been asked to keep track of you.
I will, one day.
It's just...
I need money.
I see.
So you're not eating to save money.
That's a tear-jerker.
How lucky.
This hotel went bankrupt ages ago, so everything is up for grabs.
I can't say it's nutritious, but it'll make you full.
It's expired.
Episode 4    The Wavering Ark on the Lake...
Eh?
The terrorist attack at Vladivostok?
Ah, that.
Yeah, I heard it looked like a massacre.
There was a big mess with lots of casualties.
I heard that several contractors were involved as well,
but it's already been covered up.
Looks like the Japanese organization, CIA, and MI6 were all outsmarted.
Who are the ones responsible?
I don't know that yet.
This intel isn't worth the price I paid for it.
If you want more information, you'd better ask Madame Oreille.
Madame Oreille?
She's a legendary informant.
Apparently she has more ears than the normal person.
Thanks for the information.
I joined Section 3 to learn the truth.
Yet I haven't learned a thing about the mystery surrounding BK201,
nor can I find out anything about the organization I'm working for.
Why did BK201's star disappear?
Don't make any unnecessary moves.
Aim for the vital points.
Don't drop your guard.
Understand your surrounding.
Anything can be used as a weapon.
Evade the attacks with your upper body.
Don't think about any other movements.
And...
be prepared for anything.
Five more minutes.
That's magnificent.
Your stomach.
Undulation.
Draw your stomach in.
Focus on your abdominal muscles.
Just like the ocean waves.
Why do I have to do this?
Your core muscles are weak.
So is the balance between the abdominal and back muscles.
Dancing is the best way to train them.
What's wrong?
My stomach.
And?
I think it's because of the instant ramen I ate yesterday.
Ramen?
Hey.
Good timing.
Time to put your training to use.
Try escaping without using your ability.
Why?
I told you at the beginning.
Just shut your trap and do as you're told.
Don't kill them.
Hey, go on, Norio.
Shut up! Leave me alone!
Hey missy.
Wanna play doctor with us?
You're pretty cute up close.
D-Don't be rude to her!
Please don't be too creeped out by him.
He has a crush on you.
Are we playing tag?
She had to go and do that...
Hey, look at that...
It's moving in a way that it couldn't before.
Woah.
It hurts like hell!
Hey.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
What the hell do you think you're doing?!
Wait! She's a girl.
I don't care!
Hey, Hei!
I told you to stop it!
Violence doesn't solve anything!
She started it.
Hey, look!
Looks like the cops are here.
It's getting crowded here.
Hey, what are you doing here?
July, help Suou escape.
Go and buy us some time.
Hey, you!
Run!
Hurry up, Nori-chan!
Wait up!
Over here.
This way.
Geez, what's this feeling?
Hey! Uh... Sorry about earlier.
I... You know...
just wanted to talk to you.
I didn't want there to be any fighting.
What's your name?
Move.
Ah, I should tell you my name first before asking.
I'm Norio.
I feel weird...
I'm Norio. It's written with the "virtue" character.
I have to go...
I just felt it!
This sparkling—
Move!
A contractor?
Oh, it's you two.
H-Hello.
What's with that face?
Did you eat something bad?
That face isn't funny.
Don't you think that Noah's Ark is unfair?
For all of the animals, only one male and female pair of each species was allowed on board.
Such arrogance!
So what about the ones who're neither a man nor a woman?
Here you go.
You've just earned the privilege to board the Ark.
Tampon with wings prevents leakage.
That's the way the world works.
You can't fly without wings.
Pops, I'm hungry.
What? You know her?
What's up with him?
Puberty again?
I see.
He's like Nika.
Nika?
Ugh! What is it now? Mating season?
Being chased by a cat...
Karma is a bitch!
Where are the brats?
What are you doing?
You know, he didn't look like him or anything.
But his aura and expressions were like Nika when he confessed to Tanya.
That's the expression when you're in love, huh?
But I don't get it.
When Nika confessed, I felt my heart pound with excitement, even though it wasn't to me.
But now I don't feel anything even though his feelings were for me.
Because you're a contractor. Or better yet, you'll understand it when you become a woman.
I'm a woman already.
What?
You used your ability, didn't you?!
I can tell; even if you hide it from me.
I know it's pointless to come here.
But...
Good evening.
It's a pleasant night, isn't it, Ichinose Yayoi-san?
Who are you?
Or would you prefer I call you Kirihara Misaki?
How do you know my name?
Kureteku yuubae ni senaka osarete
My back is pressed by the darkening glow of dusk
Arukidasu kage ga shimesu hou e
I start walking toward where my shadow points
Taenai ikutsu mo no deai to wakare o
Repeating the many, ceaseless encounters and partings
Kurikaeshi doko e mukau no ka
Where do I head to?
Hito wa dare mo mayoinagara
For all people, while they are lost,
tsumi to iu na no sadame o seotte
they bear the fate known as sin
Sore de mo nao ikiru imi o shiru darou
Nevertheless, I'll still learn of the meaning to live, right?
Bokura wa sou Day by Day
That's right, Day by Day,
ashita e tsuzuku michi no tochuu de
we're midway on the road leading to tomorrow
Now Say It Again kimi to futari no mama
Now Say It Again, though it'd be great if
irareta nara ii no ni naa...
I could remain together with you...
What?
You lose your emotions when you become a contractor, don't you?
I hate you.
I see.
Even if it means being with someone I hate...
I'll do what it takes to meet Shion.
The overcast sky is bleak and grey.
The time flows too slowly for a child.
The unripe fruit remains bitter.
After you've lost everything is when you realize those were the happy times.
A life ends when you hear the echos of a gunshot.
And then...
a spirit appears...
without knowledge of what transpired.