Sorry.
So? How much did you see?
You saw my perfect body, didn't you?! I know you did!
I can't believe that you of all people would see me stark naked!
I-I didn't see anything, okay? I mean, that place was pretty steamy!
Really?
You're telling the truth, right? If you're lying, I swear!
I'm telling the truth!
Then what about that last thing?
What do you mean, that last thing?
If you don't get it, then never mind.
Of course I could never say it.
Not something like that.
A night has passed since the incident in the women's bath.
H-Hey! About yesterday...
Good morning, darling.
You'd better hurry, or they'll run out of food.
What's wrong?
Marital spat?
Not by a long shot!
What's going on?
She's surprisingly calm after yesterday's mess.
Was I the only one whose heart was racing, then?
Man, I was freaking out for nothing.
Seriously...
Why is my heart beating so fast?
By the way, Raku, have you heard about tonight's big event?
After we get back from the mountain, see, we'll be holding our usual test of courage.
Test of courage? We're in high school now!
However, this isn't an ordinary test of courage!
We're pairing up boys and girls with a drawing.
But wait, there's more! One rule above all!
Each pair has to hold hands the whole time!
What a magnificent tradition! Objections are not allowed!
Whaddya say? Doesn't that get you excited for tonight?
Wouldn't it be great if you could pair up with Onodera?
Yeah, right! I'd never get that lucky!
If I happen to draw the ticket pairing me with Onodera, how much would you pay for it?
Who said I'd buy it?
How about 2,000 yen?
Deal.
Episode 10: Lottery
So anyway,
whatever you have to do, you'd better make sure you pair up with Ichijou-kun! Got that?
Make sure? But I thought it was through a drawing...
Use your willpower or something to make it happen!
That's outrageous.
Look, Kosaki, are you going to let this field trip pass without making any progress?
It doesn't matter what you do, but unless you take the initiative,
nothing will change!
Didn't you say that you were going to show more courage?
But if I happen to draw his ticket,
I'm giving it to you, so your odds just doubled.
You'd better pray that this works.
Ruri-chan...
If you do pair up with him, all that's left is to overpower him in the dark!
Ruri-chan!
Come on...
But if I...
If I really do get to pair up with him...
What will I do, I wonder?
Oh, Ichijou-kun!
Right. Courage!
G-Good morning, Ichijou-kun!
Did you sleep well last night?
Hey, Onodera! Morning!
What's wrong?
U-Uh, nothing!
Hey, don't be late for assembly, Onodera!
Oh... right.
Oh, crap, this is bad!
I keep flashing back to those scenes from last night, and I can't look her in the eye now!
Huh? Is he avoiding me?
All right! Everybody, listen up!
We're beginning our annual test of courage!
You ready for this, punks?
Okay, we'll be here having a drink,
so out of respect for our students' autonomy...
Well, just do whatever and have a good time, okay?
Sensei, did you just...
Test of courage, huh?
Oh, right, you're afraid of the dark.
Hey, will you be all right? Don't cling to me the whole time, okay?
I-I'll be fine, thank you! It's not like I'm going to be alone or anything.
I feel sorry for whoever gets stuck with you.
How strong's a gorilla's grip again?
Want me to test it out on your noggin?
Please don't. You'll break it.
All right, ladies first! Please draw your tickets!
Well, here I go.
All right, you're up next, boys!
At last, the moment where my life meets fate!
Do I get to pair up with Onodera, or not?
Come to think of it, what number did she draw?
Not that it'll do me any good, but it'd be nice to know.
Ahem. Ahem. A-hem!
Hey, so you drew a 12, huh, Kosaki?
Kosaki drew a 12! Kosaki drew a 12!
Onodera drew a 12!
Okay, come on, 12!
Miyamoto? I don't know what's going on, but now I know the number!
I see. Number 12! If I can just draw a 12...
Okay, who's next?
I'm counting on you, Raku!
Number 12, okay?
I know it's a long shot anyway,
but just let me draw a 12!
Come to me!
Come to me! Number 12!
Hey, calm down!
Other Pair
Why did I get you?
Apparently, there aren't enough boys, so I'm playing one.
Other Pair No.2
If you get scared, you're free to throw your arms around me, Kirisaki-san!
Well, I hear my grip is as powerful as a gorilla's. Still game?
On second thought, you can throw your arms around some nearby tree, Kirisaki-san!
Are you serious?
Did I just exhaust a lifetime's supply of luck?
I-Ichijou-kun!
I'm glad we're partners!
Hey, yeah, likewise.
Oh, man, still no good! I still can't look her in the eye!
Um, are you sure you're okay with me?
Oh, I mean, you know...
I was wondering if you're actually fine with me as your partner.
I mean, when I tried talking to you this morning...
Um, I was kinda wondering if you were avoiding me or something?
N-No, of course not! That was just me, uh... You know!
Spending the night in the same room as the girls...
That made me nervous, see...
That's all there is to it!
I-I see!
Sorry, that was a weird thing to say.
I see, thank goodness!
I was afraid that you hated me.
Wh-What the hell?
That face she's making is too cute!
Hey, don't be a dummy, Onodera! Come on!
I see I was mistaken!
Hey, luck is on my side, after all! I'm so gonna savor this lucky time!
For God's sake, there's no way that I could ever hate you, Onodera!
I mean, I...
You what?
He's paired with Kosaki-chan, huh? Look at him fawning over her.
Hey, what should we do?
We're in trouble now.
It's too late to look for a substitute.
What's going on?
Kirisaki-san!
Well, the thing is, one of the monsters got a stomachache.
So we're looking for a replacement, but so far we've had no luck.
A monster, huh? Well, I'm too scared of the dark.
I guess I won't be of any help.
Oh, man, what are we gonna do?
Now that everyone's paired up, no one's going to want to be a monster.
We came up with so many ways to scare everybody too!
If we don't have enough people, the timing's gonna be all messed up!
Rather, we didn't have enough monsters to begin with!
At this rate, our test of courage is going to flop!
Oh, man, what are we gonna do?
Whatever happens, happens, I guess.
Thanks, you saved the night, Kirisaki-san!
Okay, we have to get to our spots right away, so follow me!
Basically, all you have to do is have a good time, 'kay?
Here's your flashlight!
Huh? Kirisaki-san?
Everything's gonna be okay. I have a light, everything's gonna be okay.
Hurry! Hurry!
It's about to start!
I know, I know!
Okay, I have to go over there,
so you scare 'em good here, Kirisaki-san!
What? What? What? No way!
I'm staying here by myself?
Weren't you going to stay with me?
It's all right. It's all right...
After all, I've got a light.
What?!
I-I... I'm fine! I'm fine!
I'm not scared! I'm not scared!
I might not be able to see them, but there are people all around me, so I'm not sc...
What?!
For crying out loud, why do I have to go through this?
Isn't there anyone who'll save me now?
Why did he just pop into my head?
Why would he need to save me? I'm not...
Well, maybe just a little... I might be just the tiniest bit scared.
I...
Because I... you know!
I know that you have your good parts too.
Wait, I didn't mean that in a weird way!
As a friend! As a friend!
Oh, I see. Thanks!
Pair number 12, please get ready!
Hey, that's us.
All right, wanna get going, Onodera?
Oh, right, we're supposed to hold hands.
Onodera's hand is...
soft, and...
warm.
I can tell that Onodera is a little nervous too.
O-Okay, wanna get going, Onodera?
Okay.
All right, I've gotta act cool for Onodera,
or I might never get a chance like this again!
Oh my God, I'm a wreck right now!
This isn't the first time I've done this,
but it's still making me nervous as hell!
Keep it together! Calm down, Raku!
Oh no! I'm sweating!
My hand is as sweaty as hell!
Wh-What am I gonna do?
I hope Onodera doesn't get creeped out!
I-I-It's not what you think, Onodera! This is, um...
See... My heart is pounding so hard that...
Huh?
Onodera's face is kinda red.
Don't tell me that she's nervous too.
Hey, Raku!
Damn it! Right when we were in the moment.
What do you want, Shuu?
Hey, have you seen Kirisaki-san?
Chitoge-chan?
The thing is, she kinda disappeared on me a while ago.
Hey, if you're looking for Kirisaki-san,
I just saw her go into the woods. Wearing a ghost costume!
Ghost?
I just heard this myself, but one of the monsters got a stomachache, so they asked her to be a ghost.
Is that right?
She said yes? She's afraid of the dark! What was she thinking?
Oh, there you are! Maiko-kun!
Huh? Adachi-chan?
Hey, hey, is everything all right?
A ghost shouldn't be out in the open.
Did Kirisaki-san come back here, by any chance?
Well, you see, we asked
Kirisaki-san to play a ghost,
but I forgot to change the batteries in her flashlight.
I thought I'd give her new ones if she had noticed and came back here.
Hey, hey...
Without a flashlight, the woods are pretty much pitch black.
But she should be fine. We're talking about Kirisaki-san here!
Hey, wait, she's
Oh, sorry. Of course you're worried, Ichijou-kun!
You're her boyfriend after all!
Don't worry. These woods actually aren't that big, and it's not like there are any wild animals running around.
Yo, don't you want to see Kirisaki-san in a ghost costume?
Hell yeah, Kirisaki-san's so hot that I'd bet she'd look good in any costume!
What'll you do if she's scares you?
If I get scared, I might just throw my arms around the ghost!
Moron, you wanna get slugged?
Sure, if it's something she decided for herself, then she's probably okay.
But...
Hey, no way!
You think?
Damn it... Guess I got no choice.
Ichijou-kun?
I'm sorry, Onodera. I'll be right back.
Ichijou-kun!
One sheep, two sheep...
Three sheep, four sheep...
Five...
Ugh! I can't take this anymore!
I'm done fooling myself!
I'm scared out of my pants!
Oh jeez, how did I end up here, anyway?
I just want to go home!
I can't stop trembling. I feel so powerless.
Come to think of it, I went through something like this when I was a kid.
H-Hey, Tsugumi-san, aren't you gonna save...
F-Forgive me!
I-I'm a total mess when it
comes to this kind of thing!
What?
What was that just now?
Oh, wait, I remember now.
That entry in my diary... When I fell into the crevice...
Back then, I was so scared I couldn't even cry out.
All I could do was sob until I wore myself out.
But then, after some time, he came for me.
That's right! He always came for me when I...
August 15.
Today, I was careless and fell inside a crevice in the rocks.
I cried because it was so dark and narrow,
and then he came to save me.
He always comes when I cry.
You're a ghost, so stop crying.
Bean Sprout!
Are you all right?
More or less.
Man, don't try to do the impossible.
You tried to play a ghost when you clearly couldn't handle it.
But they were in a bind!
What was I supposed to do?
You moron! All you did was make everybody worry about you!
Try thinking about the consequences before you do something for once!
Then does that mean you did, too? Worry, I mean?
Of course I didn't!
Hanging in there, Kirisaki?
If you're tired, we can take a break anytime, so just
"Chitoge."
I said you can call me "Chitoge"!
Hey, you sure you're okay?
Don't tell me you have a fever.
Huh?! Shut it!
Don't get any crazy ideas, now!
Last night, when we were in the bath, the girls told me.
We still call each other by our last names,
even though we've been dating for a while.
That's why, see...
This is to make sure no one suspects us from here on out!
From now on, I'm gonna call you by your first name, so you'd better do the same, all right?
R-Right...
She took me for a ride there.
That was pretty out-of-character for her.
Hey! Do you understand what that means? Say something!
I-I got it, okay?
Um...
Ch-Chitoge?
Yes, Raku?
Wh-What are you staring at? Don't look at me!
I'm not staring, damn it!
On our way back, we ended up getting lost,
and by the time we made it back,
the Test of Courage had already ended.
In the end, I'd squandered my chance to be alone with Onodera.
Mistress!
Mistress! We were so worried about you!
Tsugumi! You guys!
Forgive me, Mistress! I should have never let this happen to you!
Aw... aw...
Tsugumi-san told us what happened.
You went after Chitoge-chan, didn't you?
Onodera!
I'm so sorry, Onodera! I even told you that I'd be right back!
That's all right!
As long as Chitoge-chan is safe.
I can't believe I blew my chance like that!
But at least Onodera forgave me.
Oh, right, Mistress.
What would you like to do about the day after tomorrow, the make-up holiday?
Don't you remember?
You said you wanted to visit the place where you met your first love.
We have no school the day after tomorrow,
so I can make the arrangements right away.
What a bummer, right, Raku?
Shut up!
I think I'll pass, on second thought.
It can wait. I have time.