There aren't many Russians who hate the summer sun.
We thoroughly and innocently enjoyed those short summer days.
Suou wins!
You've got to be kidding me!
I won!
Sore loser!
Hey! Sasha!
Sorry.
Sheesh, Suou!
So how was it? Did that break help you?
Madame?
Why are you here?
Looks like you took a little break from the search.
I guess it's not that easy to find... the memories of the future.
Memories of the future?
That's what the Mitaka Documents are sometimes referred to as.
Doesn't it sound romantic?
Memories that you can still change.
Would such memories be a blessing, or perhaps a curse?
Such a contractor does exist.
Have you ever heard about it?
Now then, I suppose I should go for a swim.
Hold on.
Why are you telling me this?
Just a little token of my gratitude.
Thanks to you, I was able to obtain some information.
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
Nee dareka oshiete
Hey, someone, tell me
Minna sou na no kana?
Is everyone like that?
Kyou ga shiawase nara
That they 'feel it's good enough
Sore de ii to omoeru tte
if they're if happy today'
Osanai koro ni wa
When I was young
Tashika ni atta yo
They certainly existed
Yume o oikaketeta
I pursued my dreams
Demo sore mo tooi kioku
But that's also a distant memory
Kotae no nai mainichi ga
The each unanswered day-
Tada sugite iku jikan ga
The time that is simply passing by-
Kore kara saki dou naru no darou?
What will happen beyond now?
Wakaranai...
They don't know...
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
You can open the door.
Oh, you've skimmed the train.
Nothing less expected from the SVR.
You know what you're doing.
We'll find BK201's room soon.
There's no need for that.
It's more fun to leave him to her.
Ikebukuro, huh? That brings back memories.
Have you been there before?
Yeah. The sun felt like it would pierce through my body on that summer day.
What, don't you wanna hear my story?
Ah, I just remembered something.
I was there before, when I was a little kid.
I'll get us something to eat.
Don't open the door if the knocking isn't right.
I'm sure you know that getting rough here isn't a good idea.
I've always wanted to have a chat with you, Black Grim Reaper.
What's wrong?
Cockroaches.
Hold on! No friendly fire, okay?
I'll do something about it.
Don't move, July!
Shit!
This is bad!
Where is Hei?!
What? Is this too heavy for me?!
What?! An animal!
Crap!
Hey!
They don't serve alcohol in the morning,
so I had to persuade them in Russian.
Not interested in a drink?
You seem like someone who drinks like a fish, though.
I don't drink anymore.
Well, that's good, too.
Have you ordered your meal?
Since you're not drinking, feel free to order anything...
Thank you for waiting.
...anything you like.
Pardon me.
Where did it go?
Cut me some slack!
I feel like I'm Road Runner from those cartoons I used to watch...
Tanya...
Don't move.
This won't take long.
When you find a capable person, you'd do anything to recruit them.
It's like that no matter where you go.
We will pay you and treat you better than ever before.
It's a great deal for you no matter how you look at it.
Hence, I ask that you join our side.
This deal includes that girl too, I assume?
Well, that too.
I refuse.
That's quite a blunt answer.
It's not the response I expected.
Rationally speaking, there's no reason to refuse.
We know that she's a decoy.
There's no need to be fixated on that girl.
Or do you expect to find Pavlichenko if you're with her?
I killed Pavlichenko.
Oh, right.
It appears that you've been kept in the dark.
Of course, this puzzles me even more.
You aren't getting attached to that girl or anything, are you?
Think whatever you want.
Is that all?
Wait.
We've already captured Suou.
If you leave now, we will take her, even if it means stopping the train.
We've got another trick up our sleeves.
This remote control will detonate the explosives on this train.
It's up to you to believe me or not.
But I'm sure you're not one to make any rash decisions.
Why I didn't kill you?
I want to know why you didn't kill me back then.
You had several chances to finish me.
Perhaps I would've shot you.
I'm sure, I would have...
If Hei wasn't there...
I see...
But I'm really glad I didn't.
Why?
'Why?', you ask. Because we're friends.
That's not a valid reason.
There are times when we hate each other exactly because we're friends.
I used to hate you.
You were closer to Nika than you should've been.
I didn't have a crush on him...
I wanted Nika to look at me.
I remember thinking that.
However, I cannot remember exactly how I felt...
I remember...
that I liked Nika.
that I killed Nika.
Episode 8
The Sun Sways on a Summer Day
Oh, you've got such great taste.
Starting off the day in a cafe, huh?
I'll have a banana parfait.
Is stalking people your hobby, or what?
Given a choice, I'd rather chase after the young virgins.
There's your serious look again.
I was just kidding.
I'm different from BK201.
I'm sure you've heard about someone who helped an adolescent girl escape, out of love.
I wouldn't know if it was out of love.
Oh, we're getting jealous now?
The more I dig, the more interesting it gets.
That doll, Izanami, has an incredible power.
I'm glad you see it my way.
Fundamentally, I trust contractors.
They won't do something illogical, like getting innocent people involved.
But lately, I've heard of a lot of contractors with irregular behaviors.
Have you heard that there's been a good number of contractors who committed suicide in the past few years?
Not only that, but it was caused by a single doll's powers.
Izanami sends contractors to heaven.
Rumor has it that this doll posses such a power.
What they actually plan to do after securing it...
Don't tell me Section 3 is...
Hey, I didn't say who...
Well, I told you something interesting,
so I expect something in return.
Something in return?
It's written all over your face that you've found something out, too.
I really want to obtain that doll.
If possible, I want a certain contractor to commit suicide.
I told you that I trust contractors,
but if you ask me whether I like or hate them, the answer is that I clearly hate them.
I got a call a moment ago.
A contractor named Ilya that the SVR dispatched has just died.
Did you kill him?
If yes, I feel like embracing you.
He was a complete psycho from top to bottom.
My dear niece was murdered by him!
It was a clear, midsummer morning.
Since then, I haven't been able to love the summer sun again.
Can you understand how I felt when he killed her, even though it was out of duty?!
We hope you enjoyed your ride.
In fifteen minutes, we will be at our last stop, Oomiya.
What did you do, then?
Didn't you think of revenge?
I...
What were you afraid of?
That you would meet the same fate?
Or were you looking for profit?
That man was indeed a psycho.
Not because he was a contractor,
but because he was a failure as a human that he became an abominable contractor. That's all.
And you can't do anything outside your logical understanding, despite being a human.
You don't have the guts to kill the passengers!
Commence the plan!
Stop the train and get Suou out.
Tanya?
Sheesh, making me run through the whole train...
W-What the hell is this?!
Run, Suou!
Tanya, where are you?
I'm chasing after Suou!
Don't let her escape!
You have to capture her!
Affirmative.
July, where is Suou?
July...
Just give up and come with me.
Tanya...
Tanya! You got her?!
Can't we talk this over?
I'm afraid not.
Very well.
Tell me.
Did you kill Ilya?
Tanya! Stop it!
Stop it!
Tanya!
Don't shoot, Suou!
Tanya...
Suou!
Suou, did you?
N-No...
You would have been killed if you hadn't shot.
It's fine if that's the only way to protect yourself.
It's okay?
But I didn't shoot!
Let's go.
You're going to catch a cold.
Wait!
I don't get this!
You're not making any sense!
Which is it?
Should I have shot? Was I supposed to shoot this time?!
You told me not to shoot back then!
Wasn't that for me?
That's enough.
I'm not blaming you for shooting her.
Hey! Wait!
Where are you going, Suou?
Hey, wait! July!
What are you going to do, Hei?
Hey! Hei!
It's so cold...
I wish it was summer.
Maybe it's better this way... so I can live without hating the summer sun.
Either way, we can no longer have fun like when we were kids.
Get me up.
Yes, indeed.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
I've confirmed your referrer.
Thanks.
You cannot prove my existence, or my involvement with the Syndicate.
You still don't know how big the Syndicate is.
If I hadn't met with the contractor who had seen the future,
then this would be the only lead.
But there's nothing particularly odd.
I hate doing this...
What was that?
Kureteku yuubae ni senaka osarete
My back is pressed by the darkening glow of dusk
Arukidasu kage ga shimesu hou e
I start walking toward where my shadow points
Taenai ikutsu mo no deai to wakare o
Repeating the many, ceaseless encounters and partings
Kurikaeshi doko e mukau no ka
Where do I head to?
Hito wa dare mo mayoinagara
For all people, while they are lost,
tsumi to iu na no sadame o seotte
they bear the fate known as sin
Sore de mo nao ikiru imi o shiru darou
Nevertheless, I'll still learn of the meaning to live, right?
Bokura wa sou Day by Day
That's right, Day by Day,
ashita e tsuzuku michi no tochuu de
we're midway on the road leading to tomorrow
Now Say It Again kimi to futari no mama
Now Say It Again, though it'd be great if
irareta nara ii no ni naa...
I could remain together with you...
Tokyo might be colder than Russia...
I told you, you'll catch a cold if you don't change your clothes.
Hey, Suou? You listening?
Hello everyone! Doing well-nya?
Due to popular demand, I've returned, even if it is embarrassing.
Kayanuma Kiko here!
Good evening XXX. When you need assistance, please call us anytime.
I'm the great detective of your heart, Kurasawa Gai.
Anyways, next week we'll be in the city of Haneda and both of us will be there!
Once again, we will fulfill your desire.
Get ready to camp in front of your TV next week!
Say... aren't we a little out of place in this show?
If you think it's your duty, you've lost, Boss.