2 Years Ago Siberia
Look! A shooting star!
Really? Where? Where?
Papa, is it true that your wish will be granted if you say it three times before the shooting star disappears?
Well, that's what people believe in Japan.
Your mom told me a long time ago...
That there are other charms that can make you pretty or make you grow taller.
Really?!
What are you wishing for?
Top secret!
Papa, is it also true that every time a star falls, someone has died?
Perhaps.
Well, it was just a fairy tale back when we were able to see the true starry sky.
Look! Another one!
What? Really?!
May...
Papa!
So it has begun...
Shion!
Suou...
That happened two years ago.
On the night of the Tokyo Explosion,
Shion became a contractor.
2 Years Later Vladivostok
Secondhand smoke is more poisonous than what you inhale.
The smoke you inhale contains 5.3 to 43 nanograms of dimethylnitrosamine, which is a carcinogen.
While secondhand smoke has 680 to 823 nanograms.
There's eleven times more quinoline in the secondhand smoke than what you inhale.
Which translates to 18,000 nanograms.
Still, telling a Russian to quit smoking is a bit pointless.
Of course, rationally thinking, it's best for me to quit. I know that.
But that's quite unlikely as I'm not going to be one of those rumored contractors.
Thanks.
Hey, did you know?
When a star falls, it means a contractor has died.
Nope.
Do they even exist?
Want to see one?
Hell no.
Aren't they kind of dangerous?
I've had enough of hell.
Huh?!
Why is it wet?
Welcome.
Glen Deveron 1968. Straight up, please.
Come again?
Your thirty-three year old sherry cask.
I heard that some dead stock was found in the back of this bar.
How do you know that?
Thanks.
Good night.
April, right?
And you're August 7th, the man called "The Magician."
Some intelligence has been leaked to the Russian authorities.
The FSB will carry out a raid in two days.
Okay.
I'll give up on the data I couldn't collect.
Where's July?
He's already here.
Okay.
All right!
I love you!
You always hang out with Suou, don't you?
I've had my eye on you.
I can't get you out of my mind.
Oh, that's Nika.
I'm stupid and I always get into fights.
But I'll treasure you!
I want to cherish you!
So... Uh...
P-Please go out with me!
He's confessing to her!
Argh, what should I do?
What... What should I do?!
Are you sure?
Tanya...
Am I good enough for you?
Y-Yes!
Are you sure? You really like me?
Yes.
Yeah!
Hell yeah!
Can we walk home together today?
Sure!
Later!
Suou?
You okay?
What are you do-
D-Did you see us?
Yeah. Clearly.
No, no! I wasn't peeping!
It was just a coincidence!
H-Hey, you're holding a camera!
No!
Hey! Stop it!
But you looked really cute!
Look.
Cute...
But are you okay with this?
I mean Nika is...
Mine?
Not at all!
We're just both in the photography club.
Who wants that delinquent...
Uh... Of course, I mean...
He's a cool guy.
He's a bit of a hothead and is a year older, but not mentally.
And his common sense is a tad different...
But he's super nice to kids.
He's really a good guy.
I promise you.
Thanks, Suou.
So your world is all rosy now, eh?
Sheesh, stop it!
Suou! Tanya!
What are you two doing?
You have cleaning duty today!
Ah, right!
We're coming!
There are several times in your life when your world changes overnight.
I still don't really know what love is.
But I think Tanya has grasped its meaning.
We haven't once seen the true starry sky. Not even once.
One day thirteen years ago, gates appeared in Tokyo and Brazil.
The one in Tokyo is called Hell's Gate,
and the one in Brazil, Heaven's Gate.
Near the gates there are unknown substances and phenomena beyond belief.
Thus, no one was able to go near them.
What are you doing?
People are looking at you.
So what? This isn't a macro lens.
I wasn't talking about that.
She meant your panties.
I'm wearing tights! There's nothing to be embarrassed about!
Yes there is!
The world has changed a lot.
And there was a great war, too.
This area wasn't too affected by the war,
but the change has started here, too.
Hey!
Welcome back, Suou!
What's wrong?
I'm home, Bella.
A stray cat was after Petya!
Yeah?
We have to be on guard, then.
Sorry,
the professor said he was busy again today, so he will be at the lab.
I made a lot of food, so make sure to eat all of it, okay?
I will.
Oh, Bella! You know what happened?
Someone confessed to Tanya today!
Really? Who?
It's Nika!
Boy, that was a shocker!
What? Really?
Isn't he your boyfriend?
No! Not at all!
Oh, yeah?
I was pretty sure about that.
He isn't!
So, you have someone you like?
I told you, I don't! Sheesh!
The true starry sky vanished when the gates appeared.
The sky we see now is fabricated.
And I know...
That the stars in this sky are the lives of the contractors.
It's me.
I'm coming in.
Yeah, sure.
Welcome back, Suou.
Thanks, Shion.
Love, huh?
That's one emotion that's hard to understand.
It's just a reaction caused by the secretion of hormones.
But people still rely on it.
That's not true!
It's a wonderful feeling!
W-What?
Nothing.
I was just thinking that you're blessed to be able to dream like that.
What? Are you making fun of me?
Just saying people need to wake up from their dreams.
Just like Mom and Dad.
Check this out. It's Mom's photo album.
Looks like she's doing well.
Say, Shion.
Let's go to Japan and visit her one day.
Why?
Huh?
She's a mere human who's absolutely unnecessary to me.
Papa.
I told you not to stay too long in that room!
But, Papa, he's my little brother!
My twin brother!
Shion doesn't care if you're family or his sister.
You'll just get hurt if you don't understand that.
Why?! He's a part of our family!
You still buy her albums?
Mama is...
She's waiting!
So-
Suou!
Wake up from your dream.
Time only moves forward.
There's no way back.
Suou!
Contractors don't have hearts.
What do you think, Petya?
Hey!
Petya!
Episode 1   The Black Cat Doesn't Dream of Stars...
There are several times in your life when your world changes overnight.
Without warning or anything.
What's wrong, Tanya?
It's not like you to be late.
It's nothing.
Tanya!
What's wrong?
Tanya's acting strange.
Tanya...
Tanya!
Wait!
Let go.
Hey! What's wrong with you?
You didn't meet up with me this morning, either.
Why?
Did I do something wrong?
I realized it was pointless.
How so?
I don't even plan to bear your child,
so going out is pointless.
I didn't confess to you for that!
Then tell me.
Get your act together!
What's wrong with you?!
If you don't let go...
Lancernopt synchrotron radiation...
Tanya!
A-A contractor...
Teacher!
Tanya!
There are no symptoms to indicate a person has transformed into a contractor.
It's sudden.
The contractor's personality and behavioral patterns deteriorate remarkably and they end up causing a scene.
Soon after, the state agency takes the person into custody,
and they erase the memories of anyone who was in contact with the contractor
using the ME that Papa is researching.
Tanya... don't...
Papa.
Why are you here, Shion?
You've created quite a few secret passages in this house.
So if either one of us was in danger, we could escape immediately.
It's time, Papa.
You...
I have remunerated.
Suou.
Shion!
Come to my room, Suou.
Bella?
Freeze!
All activities at this laboratory will be halted.
Don't touch anything.
Change.
You won't stand out with my clothes.
That's a charm.
Always carry it.
Shion?
As long as you have it, we will meet again.
Get out of the lab.
Bella knows the escape route.
Bella?
What do you mean, Shion?
What's going on here?
They're not after me?
Don't ask questions.
Goodbye, Suou.
They've raided the house.
I'm escaping.
Roger that.
Get it back as planned.
The priority order is Shion, the professor, and the data.
Gotcha.
I've lost the primary target.
Looks like he's escaped.
July, do you know where he is?
No.
There's no glass in that room.
Okay.
What about the professor's room?
Someone's there.
Is it Shion? Or the FSB?
Neither.
An adult.
Asian.
He's wearing a mask.
A mask?
April, we're being tapped.
Cease all radio communication.
We'll go with plan C.
Who are you?
Why?
I ask the questions here.
Where's the meteor core?
Shion?
Where is he?
He's gone.
Then you are of no use to me.
Professor!
Shit! He's dead.
He isn't wounded.
There's no vomit or any other traces.
It can't be...
I'm April from MI6.
I'm sure you've heard of it.
What happened, Shion? Why is he dead?
Bella.
Suou?
Where is he? Where's Shion?!
I don't know.
Come with me.
Stop right there.
You'll have to come with me.
If you're a good girl, I'll give this to you.
Oww!
Stop it... I don't want to eat so many hamburgers to remunerate.
It's pointless.
Damn, I'm gonna wake up with muscle ache tomorrow morning.
So you're a contractor...
Such a pain...
Sorry about that.
You!
Kureteku yuubae ni senaka osarete
My back is pressed by the darkening glow of dusk
Arukidasu kage ga shimesu hou e
I start walking toward where my shadow points
Taenai ikutsu mo no deai to wakare o
Repeating the many, ceaseless encounters and partings
Kurikaeshi doko e mukau no ka
Where do I head to?
Hito wa dare mo mayoinagara
For all people, while they are lost,
tsumi to iu na no sadame o seotte
they bear the fate known as sin
Sore de mo nao ikiru imi o shiru darou
Nevertheless, I'll still learn of the meaning to live, right?
Bokura wa sou Day by Day
That's right, Day by Day,
ashita e tsuzuku michi no tochuu de
we're midway on the road leading to tomorrow
Now Say It Again kimi to futari no mama
Now Say It Again, though it'd be great if
irareta nara ii no ni naa...
I could remain together with you...
BK201...
A star falls from the fabricated sky.
A life disappears after an ephemeral glitter.
The red flames erase the bonds that have formed,
and burns everything to ash.
A cold blade pierces the heart,
and the girl roams through the freezing city.
A fallen star never regains its radiance.
It only fades further.
And then... Another star falls.