Are you ready?
Start.
That was quick. Looks like you haven't lost your edge.
By the way, how far have you gotten with the Shuei syndicate's heir?
Got any dirt on him yet?
You villain! What do you think you're doing?!
If I'd known you were a girl, this would never...
No, nothing yet.
I see.
Once you've confirmed that he and Mistress are not truly in love,
take him out.
Is that understood?
Naturally!
That rude and insolent mongrel deserves it!
Ah, you've finally seen him for what he truly is.
Yes.
Mistress deserves someone much better than him.
That's a shame, because you're actually pretty cute.
What's his deal, anyway?
Episode 8: Happiness
It's been three days since our notorious transfer student, Tsugumi Seishirou, started attending.
All right, then. Allow me to introduce myself once more.
My name is Tsugumi Seishirou.
It may be masculine, but I'm a bona fide girl.
I've heard that you two are friends of Mistress's.
Mistress?
I realize that you've shown her much kindness,
and I apologize for not thanking you sooner.
No, no, you're exaggerating.
That was a shock, though! I thought you were a boy too.
You did? I could tell all along.
You could?
Morning, Kirisaki-san! Damn, why are you always so hot?!
Who the hell are you? How dare you act over-familiar Mistress!
Hey, hey, hey! He's my friend too, kind of!
So Tsugumi's a girl, huh?
Oh, well, at least all the girls going gaga over her will shut up.
Hey, hey... Why are you dressed like a boy, Tsugumi-san?
Why don't you come chat with us over here?
As you can see, it didn't take her long to start fitting in.
And just when I'd thought my life would return to normal...
Tsugumi started keeping a watchful eye over me.
For the last few days, I haven't been able to get anywhere near Kirisaki.
Well, not that it's all that bad, so it shouldn't bother me.
Hey, honey. The teacher says we gotta go buy food for the animals.
Why do we have to do it?
For God's sake...
Don't people usually order that stuff and have it delivered?
Yeah, but we've got a lot of rare animals.
Our only option is to buy it directly from the pet shop that's around here.
You go by yourself!
But it's too heavy!
Wait, Mistress!
Mistress! Allow me to go shopping in your stead.
I can't allow you to take on such chores!
Tsugumi, where did you come from?
Come, Ichijou Raku. We can't waste any time!
Hold up, I'm not ready!
This is my chance!
I'll find out once and for all whether Ichijou Raku really is Mistress's boyfriend or not!
If they turn out to be a fake couple like Claude-sama says,
then I'll personally take care of him.
Oh, that's right.
Tsugumi! Hold on a second!
What?
What's gotten into you?
Why...
Why is this happening to me?
Didn't I tell you to act more feminine?
If you go in that outfit, people will mistake you for a boy again!
B-But...
What am I gonna do? She took all of my weapons, too.
I mean, never mind! This get-up is just too embarrassing!
I kind of feel like everybody has been staring at me since we got here.
Do I look that strange in this outfit?
No, "strange" isn't really the right word. It's more like...
You're a knockout in that dress.
Seriously...
Are you mocking me?
When she actually dresses like a girl...
What the hell?
not to mention that look on her face...
It's white.
It's like she's a totally different person.
These guys are so fluffy...
What are you staring at, freak?
I'll gouge out your eyeballs!
For God's sake, if we're all done here, then let's get...
Watch out!
Let go of me, imbecile!
Do you have a death wish?!
Sorry! I wasn't thinking!
What's the matter?
Your entire foot's chafing! You've never worn heels before, have you?
That must've been killing you for a while now!
Why didn't you say anything?
You fool!
If I were to whine over such an insignificant degree of pain,
how could I ever serve as Mistress's bodyguard?
Only a fool would make herself endure unnecessary pain!
Jeez! Guess I'm gonna have to...
Hey, what are you—
There!
I-Idiot! Idiot! Idiot! Idiot! Put me down!
You don't have to do this! I can walk on my—
Hell no! Now that I know, I won't let you.
Just calm down, will you?
Seriously, what's his deal?
Just when I think he's my enemy, he treats me so nicely, tells me that I'm cute...
He really...
By the way, you and Kirisaki grew up together, didn't you?
How long have you known each other?
Let's see... We were like five or six when we met, so it's been about ten years at this point.
Back then, Mistress also seemed to have found her first love.
She often told me about the boy with a grin on her face.
First love?
But she told me that she'd never fallen in love before.
That just goes to show that she doesn't trust you, doesn't it? Serves you right!
Oh, is that so? Then what about your first love?
M-My first love?
As if I'd experience such a thing!
What? Really? Not that I would know...
I don't have a "first love."
Never have, never will.
Serving Mistress is my mission, and that's what makes me happy.
And didn't you hear me the first time? I've abandoned my womanhood!
As long as Mistress is happy, that's enough for me.
But...
If you're the kind of person who can devote herself like that to someone,
then I'll bet you anything there's someone out there who'll fall in love with you.
In other words, it means that your first love has yet to bloom.
I can't even imagine...
the look on your face when you actually fall in love.
Anyway, I'm sure that it'll come a lot quicker than you think.
I swear, you're the most infuriating man I've ever met.
You'd better not think I owe you for this!
Owe me what?
Ready, set,
go!
By the way, about the Shuei syndicate's heir...
What's wrong? Your concentration's shot.
My apologies.
How's your mission? Has he changed at all?
No, there's nothing different about him.
I see. Carry on with your mission, then.
Right.
There's something strange going on with me lately.
I told you! You don't have to follow me everywhere!
That's not how this works.
My job is to follow and protect you 24/7.
And besides, I finally have a chance to spend time with you, Mistress!
Hey, good morning, darling!
Yo, honey!
Morn—
What's wrong, Tsugumi?
It's... nothing.
Don't come near me! Don't touch me! Don't talk to me!
The Three Principles?
She really hates my guts.
Shall we be on our way, Mistress?
I'll carry your books.
There's some dust on your shoulder.
What's wrong with you, Tsugumi?
Was I being too touchy-feely? Sorry!
Something is wrong with me.
You need advice? What's up?
Oh, it's actually not that important, but...
The thing is, I've been feeling strange lately.
These physical changes seem to come about only under certain conditions,
and they're like nothing I've ever experienced before.
Oh, really? What kind of changes?
You see...
My pulse skyrockets, but only in front of a certain person.
It feels like my heart's being crushed, and my face grows hot,
and whenever that person is around, everything I say turns to gibberish.
Tsugumi... that's not...
some kind of serious disease or anything, is it?
Maybe you should go to the hospital or something.
No, I don't think that's what it is.
Insensitives
Seriously, what's going on?
Despite these incredibly abnormal changes to my body,
I wouldn't say it's unpleasant.
In fact...
This is bad! How can I be so nonchalant about this?
There's a high chance this will come to interfere with my mission!
Maybe I'll try asking someone else.
That's the first I've ever heard of those symptoms.
There's nothing I can do.
I recommend that you get yourself examined by a professional.
I suppose keeping fit is another part of your mission.
Be ever vigilant!
R-Right! I'm very sorry.
No dice, huh?
I wish I could have that photo, too.
But of course, Seishirou-chan! Needless to say, that's...
But wait, by any chance, are you talking about Raku?
How can you tell?
Hey, you! What's so funny?
Don't laugh! Do you hear me?
Stop laughing!
Isn't that...
It's got to be that, right?
Oh, my, it must be nice to be young!
I wonder why.
No matter who I ask, all I get are vague answers.
What exactly am I going through?
But that's...
Yeah.
You mean you have an idea what it could be, Onodera-sama?!
"Onodera-sama"?!
You can just call me Kosaki!
U-Uh, most likely...
It means that you're "in love," Tsugumi-san, wouldn't you say?
What?
This has to be a mistake!
Why would I fall in love with a guy like him?
Not possible! Not in a million years!
Well, I don't really know who you're talking about.
But conventional wisdom tells me that it's love.
Kosaki's actually going through the same thing herself!
Hey, Ruri-chan!
You're in love at this very moment, Onodera-sama?
Really? What kind of person is he?
Um, well, he's...
Look, there he is.
That hurt.
S-Sorry! But you asked for it, Ruri-chan!
Love... Love, huh?
Me, in love with a guy like him? That's impossible... Unthinkable!
That's a shame, because you're actually pretty cute.
What the hell am I thinking?!
Something like that just doesn't happen!
And he's Mistress's boyfriend, for crying out loud!
As someone who serves Mistress, I couldn't possibly hurt her.
Darling...
Something Like
Forbidden Love
Damn it, damn it, damn it!
What are you thinking, you insolent bastard?! I'm such an insolent moron!
Damn it... What on Earth is wrong with me?
Hey, hey... What are you doing?
You slammed your head into the wall. Are you okay?
It's not what you think!
Why did she hit me?
I'm so tired.
What am I supposed to do?
Protecting Mistress in such a state...
No good. I'm getting more and more confused.
Oh, there you are, Tsugumi!
Well? Did you find out anything?
Mistress!
I was told that it was love.
Love?
Oh, I see! Now it all makes sense, don't you think?
You think so too, Mistress?
Well, you said your heart starts racing, and you can't talk in front of that person, right?
Don't you think those symptoms match up perfectly?
Please, that's not what this is!
Hm, it's not, huh?
Well, I wouldn't know, since I've never experienced it myself.
What are you talking about? You have Ichijou Raku, your boyfriend—
Absolutely right!
I meant that I had little experience, okay?
There I go again! That was close.
And besides, that isn't your only experience with love, right?
You have your first love too, remember? The boy from ten years ago.
So you've forgotten after all?
Not that I blame you...
Did you just remember?
Oh yeah. Why did I forget it until now?
Come to think of it, years ago I did have a...
Brings back memories, doesn't it?
Back then, you would sneak out of the mansion every day to go see him.
You really caused us a lot of trouble.
I see... My first love from ten years ago...
He must be the boy that I made a promise to.
What did I promise him?
I have a feeling that it was something really important.
Hey, Tsugumi, do you remember that boy?
I can't remember his face or his name.
I don't know... I don't remember those details, either.
But it seemed like you were in love in the sweetest way.
I thought it was quite wonderful to love somebody so wholeheartedly.
S-Stop it, you're embarrassing me.
I see, so I guess I was really into that boy.
Wait, forget about that for now. Weren't we talking about you?
If it's not love, then what exactly are those symptoms?
Well, I think it's...
Tell me about those symptoms one more time.
Uh, first of all, whenever a certain person is around, my pulse...
Doesn't that mean that you're in love?
It does not, you fool!
Why?
But to think that I actually had such a bittersweet experience myself...
I mean, who knew?
Well, you said your heart starts racing and you can't talk in front of that person, right?
Please, that's not what this is!
I wonder if my heart started racing back then, too.
Well, I'm sure that he doesn't remember anything about our promise, either.
I've never seen anybody who'd remember a kid's promise from ten years back.
This is ridiculous!
I know. I wonder if I still have any mementos from back then lying around.
Ouch, ouch...
Is this... my diary?
Chitoge
Age 5
Five years old... That's just around the time that Tsugumi said I fell in love.
But why is it written in Japanese?
Yeah, Mom and Dad did teach me Japanese, but...
Were we living in Japan back then?
July 30th.
I promised to play with him again tomorrow. I can't wait till tomorrow!
"Him"? Him...
Is he the boy who was my first love?
August 2nd. Today, something terrible happened.
I was playing on the mountainside when a big dog nearly attacked me.
I hurt my ankle, and couldn't run away.
Huh? This story... I know I've heard it before.
I was really, really scared,
but he came to rescue me, and he protected me!
I was so happy!
That's right!
Now I remember!
I was attacked by a stray dog in the mountains as a child,
and he saved me then.
That day, he got a bad cut on his forehead.
I stayed by his side, nursing him until the cut healed.
August 5th. He ended up with a tiny scar, but he seems to be better.
We made a date to play again.
August 9th. I snuck out of the mansion to see him.
Today, we went out together. It was fun.
August 12th. We played in the river today.
He caught a huge fish, and it was fun!
August 15th. Today, I was careless and fell inside a crevice in the rocks.
I was crying because it was so dark and narrow, and then he came to save me.
He always comes when I cry.
August 18th. I had fun today, too.
I can't wait to see him again tomorrow.
I sound like I had a lot of fun...
Having never fallen in love before, yet dreaming about it for so long...
And to think that I'd already experienced such a wonderful love as a child...
I wonder what kind of kid he was. What's he doing now?
Oh, well, I'm sure there's no way that he remembers me, but...
August 21st. I went out to play with him again today.
I think I wouldn't mind getting married, if it was to him.
What the heck am I writing?
Farewell
Farewell?
I see. So this is when we said our goodbyes.
Tomorrow, I'm getting on a plane with Daddy.
But first, I'm going to make a promise with him.
A promise that we decided together...
Promise?
There it is! What on Earth was that promise about?
Why didn't I write the rest?! For crying out loud, write everything down, Chitoge!
Oh, man, I want to know! I want to know!
What's this? It was stuck inside the book.
A key?