Welcome!
Young Master, why don't you take a break now?
I'll be fine.
I'm getting time off later anyway, so I at least have to earn it.
What's that you got there?
Snacks. I'm gonna take these to the guys manning the other stalls.
Young Master... You're too much!
What a stand-up fella!
As long as they give me some time off tonight,
helping them out is no big deal.
Tonight I have a mission of the utmost priority that I can't afford to fail!
Specifically!
Romantic Relationship
I have to get the super-ultra matchmaking item—a romantic relationship charm!
Word on the street is that it's super effective!
Romantic Relationship
Just carrying it will bring you success in love!
What a godsend of a charm!
I hear it's so popular that it sells out in seconds!
I'm gonna do whatever it takes to get one!
And then Onodera and I'll finally...
Sorry!
What do you think you're doing?
Right back at you...
I'm here to enjoy the festival, nothing more.
Why should I have to see your face on a day like this?
Well, I'm just here to help out my guys with their stalls.
Hey, Young Master!
My bad, could you bring 'em these beers, too?
Hey! If I'm not mistaken, isn't that your girlfriend there, Young Master?
This isn't right!
I can't believe you've been working so hard when your girlfriend's here!
How thoughtful of you!
No, wait, hold up!
Please, leave the stall to us!
We can handle it! You've got nothing to worry about!
Taking your girl to a festival has to be in a guy's top three fantasies!
This is a golden opportunity for you!
All right, go have yourselves a good time!
Episode 17 - Festival Day
Why does this keep happening to us?
Why are you asking me?
Oh, come on! I was so looking forward to this!
Okay, now I'm gonna eat like there's no tomorrow!
If you're playing my boyfriend, then treat me!
I want to eat some takoyaki!
Why do I have to treat you?
Look. There's another takoyaki vendor over there, so let's go to that one.
Huh? Why?
Hey there!
Oh! Young Master!
You're on your break now, huh? Thanks for your hard work!
I'd like some takoyaki. Do you mind?
Of course not! Take as many as you want!
What's wrong? I guarantee that they taste top-notch.
You really have a ton of people in your household, don't you?
Yeah, and they've got a ton of stalls out again tonight.
And you get everything for free?
Eat-all-you-want and play-all-you-want?
Well, I wouldn't put it that way, but I guess so.
Hey, Raku, would you like to go out on a date with me now?
You've got some nerve, you brat!
But it'd be free, I'm telling you! Free!
Wouldn't you be like a walking free-pass?!
How awesome is that?
Look, aren't you supposed to be a refined young lady?
At least treat me like a living creature, would you?
Oh, man.
Takoyaki, cotton candy, taffy, frankfurters!
Was that just my imagination?
What should I do? I just hid without thinking!
Was I expecting any different? It's Festival Day, after all.
If they're pretending to be dating, of course they'd come together.
I wonder if anything will change if I manage to buy a relationship charm today?
Oh my!
Why, if it isn't Onodera-san!
Good evening!
Have you come to purchase the Super Miracle Love Item, the Relationship Charm, as well?
What? No, I'm not here to...
Oh, my.
Look who we have there.
What a bitter pill to swallow!
Just the other day, he readily turned me down when I had invited him to join me.
Perhaps we should go disrupt them?
Hey, you can't do that!
Come to think of it, I spend a whole lot of time with her.
I've had to fake this relationship ever since I met her.
What a weird face!
Seriously, we have the strangest connection.
Hey! Look over there! That girl's really cute!
Absolutely gorgeous blonde hair!
Is she biracial?
What a great body! I'm so jealous!
We get it already,
so wipe that smug look off your face!
Yeah, but that boyfriend of hers is a real tool.
Why would she go out with a guy like him?
To toy with him, why else?
You really know how to tick someone off!
Jeez...
Wow, people really do think we're a couple.
But we've been faking it for so long, so no wonder, huh?
But I wonder why she isn't wearing a yukata?
I know, right? She'd totally rock it too.
Hey, are these yukata things really that great?
Well, I guess they are.
To each their own, though.
They seem to be enjoying themselves, don't you agree?
They do.
Grr! How am I supposed to scoop anything with this flimsy paper?
Then don't do it. You wouldn't know how to take care of it even if you succeeded.
This is a rip-off!
No! I want one!
You're hopeless. Here, gimme that.
But it's almost totally ripped.
That's amazing!
How did you pick them up with just a tiny piece of paper?
I used to get to practice these things all I wanted at my house!
Hate to break it to you, but on Festival Day, I have no equal!
Oh? Good to see you, Young Master.
We always get our asses handed to us when you show up.
But we've got some big game for you this year!
What is it?
Check it out!
Hey, that's a Nishiki-goi!
Got it!
Please... Come again next year...
Wow! I can't believe you did it!
Actually, I think I'm more shocked than you are.
Here you go.
You wouldn't know what to do with a whole bunch of them.
So just take two for now.
I'll show you how to take care of them another time.
Okay! Thanks!
No, no.
Huh?
Looks like there's a huge crowd gathering over there.
Crap! I forgot about the charms going on sale!
Alas, it's finally show time.
Onodera-san, if you'll excuse me, I'll be going now.
What?
Let's go, Honda! Open up a path for me!
As you wish!
Tachibana-san is something else.
In so many ways.
But to be able pursue her love so aggressively...
I think I'm a little... jealous.
All right! I'm gonna do whatever I can to get one too!
Sorry, Chitoge,
but there's something I really want to buy over there,
so would you wait for me around here?
Wait for you where?
We'll definitely get separated in this huge crowd.
Yeah, you're right.
No way around it! Come on!
Now we won't get separated even if we dive into the crowd, right?
I'll go with you.
After all, you're my free pass to everything.
Come on! Let's get moving!
A-All right!
Damn it why do I feel so self-conscious?
Ugh, there's too many people!
I'm here to buy a relationship charm because I'm in love with Onodera, you know!
Are you okay, Chitoge? Make sure you don't let go, okay?
This is no time for my heart to start pounding!
Almost there... Almost there...
All right! I did it! I bought one!
Hey...
Did you buy one yet? C'mon we have to hurry—
Chitoge!
Oh, crap! Where did she go?
Hey, there she is!
C'mon, didn't I tell you to hold on?
Ch-Chitoge turned into Onodera!
What's going on here?
Where's that bean sprout?
I-Ichijou-kun!
What are you doing here?
And what about you, Onodera?
Is that a relationship charm?
So you came here to buy one!
Um... Well...
How about you, Onodera?
Did you come here to buy one of these, too?
No, no... I'm not here for anything.
I just happened to get swept up in this crowd.
Huh? Come to think of it, where's Chitoge-chan?
Weren't you two together?
Huh? Oh... well...
We were together till a second ago,
but then we got separated in this crowd.
Seriously... Is she gonna be okay on her own?
Hey, bean sprout! Where are you?
Jeez, can you believe that bean sprout?
And he was even nagging me so hard to hold on!
Now that I look again, there seem to be a lot of girls in yukatas.
Anyway, let's get out of this crowd.
It's impossible to look for her like this.
Okay.
But seriously, the second I bought that relationship charm...
Who would've thought I'd be alone with Onodera?
Is this the power of the relationship charm?
No way, right?
I'm actually kinda glad, even though I feel bad for Chitoge.
Why the hell should I feel bad for her?
She's got nothing to do with us!
I couldn't buy a relationship charm,
but I got to be alone with Ichijou-kun.
I'm just a little bit happy.
To be honest, I'd love it if this could last for a while.
I'm so sorry—
Ichijou-kun, you dropped your relationship charm.
Hey, my bad.
Whoa, it totally fell apart.
O-Oh my gosh!
Are you all right?
Yeah.
S-Sorry! I must be heavy.
I did eat some cotton candy just now.
No, you're totally fine.
I never dreamed this would happen!
I'm overjoyed and embarrassed at the same time!
All right. Now these should hold together for the rest of the night.
Thanks.
Okay, I'd better go look for Chitoge.
Okay.
Huh?
What's wrong?
It's gone! Your relationship charm's gone!
It was here till just a second ago.
Look! Over there!
Crap!
Hey! Where do you think you're going with that?
Ichijou-kun!
Hey! It stopped!
Now's my chance!
I had my hopes set on procuring a relationship charm, yet they were sold out.
What a pity.
Tachibana!
Oh, if it isn't you, Raku-sama!
I'm so delighted to see you on such a night!
Listen to me, Tachibana! Don't you dare move a muscle!
Well, look at you, Raku-sama!
Have you finally decided to switch over from that woman to me?
Of course, I'm always open to...
Now, listen! Stay absolutely still...
But... But Raku-sama, that would be...
Do you not believe that, um, this is too sudden?
What? No, really!
Well, I am happy, but...
This ain't no good!
Damn it! I screwed up!
Come back here!
I went to the trouble of lining up,
yet I failed to buy a relationship charm.
Well, not that I really needed one.
It's not as if there's someone I have feelings for.
Damn it! What's wrong with this total lemon of a gun?
If I had a real firearm, I'd need just one shot!
What was that? A cat?
Tsugumi!
Oh, it's just you.
What do you want?
Did you see a calico cat come this way?
Oh, a cat? He went that way.
It did? Thanks!
Here! Your intel fee!
Come back here!
Come back here, damn it!
Guess that makes us 0-96 in pickups this year.
C'mon, Maiko. Why don't we call it quits?
Is this...
Just look at how hot she looks from behind in that yukata!
That's gotta be a babe!
All right! This time, I'm gonna succeed no matter what!
Hey, young lady over there!
I wonder if Kosaki was able to buy a relationship charm.
I just know it came running this way.
Hey, is this yours, by any chance?
Hey, it sure is! Thank you very—
What is it?
This is that thing you just bought a little while ago, isn't it?
Seriously! You need to keep a
better eye on your belongings.
When... did you change into that?
I had Claude rush it over to me just now.
Why the sudden change of heart?
Does it really matter? I was just a little intrigued, that's all.
So I tried one on, but what's the deal with this?
The sash is too tight and makes it hard to walk.
What's the allure of wearing something like this?
Not to mention, I can't even tell if it looks good on me.
Well, I think it looks great on you... Really great.
Oh, really?
Maybe I'll try wearing it again next year.
Relationship Charm
Effects
1. You shall be blessed with a good relationship.
2. Your unrequited feelings shall bear fruit.
3. A man may propose marriage by offering his
relationship charm to a woman.
Relationship charm?
Oh, that thing he bought.
3. A man may propose marriage by offering his
relationship charm to a woman.
When a man gives one to a woman, he's proposing, huh?
So that's what it means, then.
Not that I think he'll ever find someone to give one to!
Jeez! What's with you suddenly wearing a yukata?
That's cheating! You made a move after the fact.
Wait, what's she cheating at?
This relationship charm...
Sure, I finally got my hands on it,
but it's not something that a guy should carry after all.
This belongs in the hands of a girl.
And besides, I did cause her some trouble.
Hey, Chitoge.
What?
You can have this.
Wait... What?
What's with your reaction?
Well, I mean... It's just... Why me?
Well, of course...
Wh-What's wrong? Why is she so flustered all of a sudden?
And her face is slightly red...
Hey... No, no, what's the meaning of this?
D-Don't tell me that you're actually serious?
Why wouldn't I be serious? Take it.
What? You're serious? Whaaat?
N-No way! What's going on?
What the hell is he talking about?
Serious... If he's serious, then this is basically a proposal!
But why? Then, does he have feelings for me?
Who knew! So she wanted a relationship charm that bad, huh?
S-Since when...
Since when have you been seeing me in that way?
Since when? Well, I didn't realize it myself till just now.
What? No way! So it was on impulse?
Pretty much.
No way! So that means that he only just realized for the first time that he was in love with me!
And he proposed to me out of the blue?
Well, they do say that love is a sudden thing.
Is that how love works?
I don't know how to handle something this sudden.
What's wrong?
Oh no! I put my sash on in a hurry, and now it's unraveling!
What?!
A-Are you gonna be okay?
Come on, give it to me. I'll support you.
Hey! Don't come near me, you moron!
What am I gonna do? It's falling apart even more!
I don't know how it's supposed to be tied, but I can hold onto it for you, okay?
No! Stay away! I don't have any underwear on!
Why don't you have any underwear on?!
What? Well, aren't you supposed to wear yukatas without underwear?
That's a popular misconception!
Hey! You just pictured
something dirty, didn't you?
You better cut it out, you pervert!
Like hell I did!
I can't hold on anymore!
Oh, come on. Just calm down, will you?
Hey! Don't you dare touch me!
I can't help it! Stop whining, will you?
Seriously! If you hadn't given me this thing all of a sudden, this never would've happened!
What's that got to do with it?
If you suddenly ambush me with a charm like this, it's too hard to accept.
Like... I need a little more time to think it over.
Think what over? What are you talking about, anyway?
Relationship Charm
Effects
1. You shall be blessed with a good relationship.
2. Your unrequited feelings shall bear fruit.
3. A man may propose marriage by offering his
relationship charm to a woman.
Relationship Charm
Effects
1. You shall be blessed with a good relationship.
2. Your unrequited feelings shall bear fruit.
3. A man may propose marriage by offering his
relationship charm to a woman.
It's not what you think!
My sash!
I just had no clue about any of that, all right?
I... I didn't give it to you with any questionable motives!
I don't want to hear it! Look away!
I wish I could've stayed with him a little longer.
Who knew... that my Raku-sama was such a sensualist!
Yum.