What is this?
It's a statement from the group responsible for the attacks.
They're demanding public recognition of contractors,
as well as greater authority and rights as contractors.
Is this really what they said?
I don't know. However, there's no denying that acts of terrorism have been committed
and that a group called the Evening Primrose exists.
Evening Primrose...
Is BK201 related to them in any way?
Kirihara, what I'm about to tell you is strictly confidential.
Don't tell anyone.
Sir!
The leader of this terrorist group is a former MI6 conspirator known as February, Messier Code UB001.
Five years ago, she was in the front lines at Heaven's Gate.
It didn't look like he went out to see an ex-girlfriend.
Did he look like a man who wanted revenge?
Officials were concerned that he still had feelings for her,
but it seems they were worried about nothing.
I guess we should observe him a little longer.
What happened between those two?
It's best you don't know for your own sake.
I guess it can't be helped. I'll give you a hint.
Hei was betrayed by that woman,
and the rest of his team died in South America.
The first star ever recorded at that time was hers.
A myriad of stars began to shine as if they were reacting to her.
Included in that group was BK201.
Immediately following that incident, a 1,500 kilometer radius of South America disappeared from the face of the Earth.
Cheers!
Hey, you guys! That's enough!
There's no hope for any of you if you start drinking during the day.
What are you talking about?
Drinking while the sun's out
is what the gusto of life is all about!
Geez...
My, off to work?
Yes.
It's good to know that you have your priorities in order, Li-san.
Not really.
Hey, handsome! Why don't you join us?
Ah, sorry... I have to go.
Why not? Live a little!
Hey! Don't drag an honest young man like him into your worthless lifestyle!
Come on, now! On your feet! Go! Meeting adjourned! Move! Go!
Party crasher.
Sir, please wait!
You can't leave until the bill has been taken care of.
I told you that I forgot my wallet!
I'll bring it tomorrow, okay?
But, sir...
That does it!
Hold it right there.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Sakurai of the Nakazawa family.
Nakazawa family?
Pay your bill and get the fuck out.
You're asking for trouble if you start pissing me off.
Let your fists do the talking.
E-Excuse me...
You're in the way!
Hey, you... Are you making fun of me?
You bastard!
Stay still!
Are you all right?
You fucking punk!
Um... Please calm down...
Hold it!
M-My store...
Amazing...
I'm going to kill you.
Stop it!
Do you really want to die?
Aniki!
You're making quite a scene, sir.
One must pay his dues.
Who are you?
Get up!
Here.
Thanks.
Um... I'm...
Sakurai Kenji-san of the Nakazawa family, right?
I'm Li Shun Sheng.
Li-san...
You're Chinese, as I thought!
"As I thought?"
Wasn't that Chinese martial arts?
You were dodging the enemy as easily as a butterfly.
I bet you could have taken care of him even if Aniki didn't come, Li-san.
You'd shout "acho!" while doing it, too.
No, I don't think so.
Come on, you don't have to be so modest.
Kenji.
Nice job!
Thank you very much!
Kenji, a gangster who's been underestimated isn't much of a gangster.
I'm sorry!
Thanks for looking out for him, man.
Well, it's part of the job.
Take this and treat him to a decent meal.
Thank you very much!
Let's go.
Nice job!
Here you go.
Are you sure you're okay with this?
It's really good.
You sure do eat a lot, don't you?
Could this be the secret behind your strength?
Like I said, it isn't.
Stop being such a tease and tell me.
Are you really sure you were okay with beef bowls?
Since I have some money on me, I can take you to gentlemen's clubs if you're interested.
No, I'll have to decline.
I see. Distancing yourself from women is the secret behind your power.
Um...
Don't worry. I'll make sure we reach your house.
But...
I caused a lot of trouble for you today, so I insist.
What the...
That's strange...
Sorry for the trouble.
It's okay.
You don't have much, do you?
Well, all I do is sleep when I come back.
Li-san, what do you do with your spare time whenever you're not working?
Nothing.
Nothing?
Didn't you come to Japan to train?
No, I came to study.
Oh, you're a student?
What the hell was that?
Oh, the usual.
The usual? That noise just shook the entire room, you know.
It's pretty early, too.
It's probably the same people from last night.
Can you even focus on studying with this noise?
It's not a big deal once you get used to it.
You're practically at their mercy!
Let me resolve this issue permanently.
W-What is it?
What do you mean, "what is it"?
Who are you?
Sakurai of the Nakazawa family.
Nakazawa family?
Hey, hey, hey! What the hell were you thinking, playing a guitar that loudly in a shoddy room with paper-thin walls?
Who did that?
What the hell were you thinking?
What are you going to do about that?
Yeah, that'll do.
Let's have lunch.
I bet you're all hungry from causing this ruckus.
Itadakimasu.
You're from the Philippines?
Are you working in Japan by yourself?
Yeah. My parents and siblings are still over there, so I send them money every month.
It must be tough.
Not really. The Japanese are all rich perverts.
I bet.
Why are you in Japan, rock star?
I'm a missionary who came here to preach about the essence of rock.
Wow! Essence, huh? That's pretty far out, man.
Why, you little...
How about you?
I came from Israel to study Japanese animation.
You came all the way here just for that?
What are you saying? Japanese anime is the best in the world. Besides...
Yeah, yeah. Your explanations are always too long, so let me stop you right there.
This is a pretty diverse apartment, isn't it?
Yeah. I'm fluent in seven different languages because of these tenants.
Wow, this place sure is interesting.
Maybe I should live here, too.
Right, Li-sa...
You've got to be kidding.
You just ate tons of beef bowls...
Do you want seconds, Li-san?
Ah, please.
Isn't he done yet?
Thanks for the meal!
Now that we're full...
Let's start the second round!
Are you guys in?
Booze? Great! Right, Li-san?
Sorry, but I have an appointment to keep.
That guy is really unsocial.
We barely talked to him until today.
Well, whatever.
Some people don't like to interact with others. Come on, let's drink.
Is that so?
Don't you think there's a lonely aura emanating from Li-san's back?
Episode Seventeen A Love Song Sung from a Trash Heap... (Part One)
Hitotsubashi, it's not that I dislike a man like yourself.
I'm honored.
However, I will not tolerate internal feuds.
I don't understand.
Don't play dumb!
Ohshita.
I know you've been taking Ohshita's territory.
Rest assured. I have no intention of inciting this conflict any further.
Stay out of sight for a while. I'll eventually assign you to a proper position.
I know about your potential more than anyone else.
Is that clear?
I'll make sure it's engraved within my mind.
Hitotsubashi, you say?
Did he show up at the club already?
Yeah.
Keep an eye on it.
The goods should be brought there within the next few days.
Be careful not to interfere with the transaction.
We know it'll all be in vain if we screw up the deal.
That aside, who is that kid?
Kid?
There's no need to worry about him.
Are you sure?
I don't want any distractions during the mission.
I know.
Oh, welcome back.
Where is everybody?
They fell asleep.
Good! Thank you for everything.
For what?
You provided me with shelter from the rain.
I could have called for a cab with that hundred grand.
I didn't think about that.
Li-san, you're a strange person.
Let's meet up for a meal sometime.
Okay.
Good evening.
Oh, it's you, Li-kun.
I had trouble reaching you since you don't have a cell phone.
Sorry for the late notice, but we won't be able to work for three nights, starting today.
What happened?
Construction work. Remember the problems we were having with the bathroom?
Oh, I see.
You'll be on paid leave while the construction's going on.
That's very kind of you.
A-Aniki, what did you just say?
I said I'm going to divide the organization.
The organization...
I'm indebted to the boss, but he's become senile.
A gangster in need of stability isn't much of a gangster.
Why are you telling me this?
I have a job for you.
Kenji, come with me.
A-Aniki, what is this?
It can't be...
Hey.
Are you surprised?
Aniki!
Wake up.
A-Aniki, this is...
A doll.
Doll? She's human!
Wrong.
It's a state-of-the-art doll that will do anything it's told to do.
There are rich people out there who want these kinds of toys.
Take care of her for the next two or three days.
If you don't feed her, she'll die.
You'll have to take care of her excretions, too.
She's precious merchandise.
Make sure you keep her clean.
Merchandise...
I'm counting on you.
Don't get caught up with dirty thoughts.
Um...
Why did you get him involved?
The merchandise might become tainted unless an idiot like him takes care of it.
Don't worry. He doesn't have the balls to betray me.
I thought I'd have to kill someone since he said he had a job for me.
Hey, you. Where did you come from?
What's your name?
You don't understand Japanese, do you?
Don't look at me like that.
What are they going to do with you?
BK201-related information? I already told you everything I know.
I'm sure you have, but it still doesn't make sense for some reason.
The mysterious group that calls itself E.P.R., their statement,
and BK201.
Are they enemies or are they working independently?
What's his objective in the first place?
We don't know anything,
yet they're telling us to go after them.
Say, did Hoshimi-sama say anything else?
Any new analytical data...
Hey, that's enough.
I was pulling all-nighters until a little while ago.
I don't want to talk about work while I'm home.
Sorry.
Misaki, aren't you off-duty tomorrow, too?
Yeah, why?
You're probably not doing anything, so why don't you come with me?
What the...
Are you sure you weren't noticed?
We're not that careless.
Why's the doll missing?
Who knows? It was probably stolen from them, I bet.
Stolen, huh?
You might be right.
What do you mean?
There's been internal conflict within the Nakazawa family recently.
Yin, can you find it?
Damn.
What are you going to do?
Let's back off.
It's best not to look into it too much.
Whether we continue the mission or not isn't a decision we can make.
I'm going to submit a request, so everything's on hold until then.
Li-san...
I'm sorry!
Can we use your place as a hideout?
The jewel in hand gives off a clear, uncolored glow,
its purity calling near the specter of devastation.
Their two worlds were never supposed to have crossed.
They have nowhere to go, and their flight will continue without end.
They didn't even want to know what lies ahead of them.
And so, the boy lies down in the trash heap.
Episode Eighteen A Love Song Sung from a Trash Heap... (Part Two)