We've sealed off all the entrances around the airport.
However, there is still no sign of BK201.
He took a boat and escaped by sea.
How do you know?
No one can escape from our system.
I'll notify you when he has landed.
Standby at the airport.
So he used the doll system.
That's what we used to observe you.
Even with that system he's so proud of, he still couldn't capture BK201.
I wonder why...
Hey! Hold on!
I thought you would give me a ride!
Ah, I'm so lonely.
My Suou is already dead!
Mama!
Don't call me that...!
Filthy abomination... you're driving me crazy...
Everyone is smiling.
That's right. Nobody is angry in an aquarium.
No...
That's not it! The mom I knew always used to smile!
Let go of me!
Let's go to the aquarium!
Maybe then, you'll...
Aquarium? What are you talking about?
Hey!
You guys...!
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
Nee dareka oshiete
Hey, someone, tell me
Minna sou na no kana?
Is everyone like that?
Kyou ga shiawase nara
That they 'feel it's good enough
Sore de ii to omoeru tte
if they're if happy today'
Osanai koro ni wa
When I was young
Tashika ni atta yo
They certainly existed
Yume o oikaketeta
I pursued my dreams
Demo sore mo tooi kioku
But that's also a distant memory
Kotae no nai mainichi ga
The each unanswered day-
Tada sugite iku jikan ga
The time that is simply passing by-
Kore kara saki dou naru no darou?
What will happen beyond now?
Wakaranai...
They don't know...
Tsukiakari no michishirube
The moonlight's guiding sign
Kumo o koe boku ni todoke
Reaches me over the clouds
Susumu beki michi o terashite yo
Illuminate the road that I must advance on
Kyou ga donna ni kowaresou de mo
No matter how broken today looks
I have to go.
To the aquarium?
Both Mom and Shion smiled at that place.
I want to go back to those days.
Keep it a secret.
Keep it a secret... between us.
Synchronization noise in the interior system detected.
The probability of surveillance has fallen drastically.
What?
There are several tiny holes in the network.
What's going on here?!
There's no way I'd find him by blindly looking around...
All right.
Good morning.
You'll catch a cold if you sleep there.
I heard that you were accompanied by a male doll, but I didn't expect it to be him.
How have you been?
Normal.
I see. That's the best.
Isn't BK201 with you?
He...
He becomes violent very easily, forces me to do some strange training,
and is a good for nothing drunkard.
But he stopped drinking.
You're a girl, aren't you?
So you thought I was Shion too.
I'm not Shion.
I might not even be Suou.
What are you saying?
No way...
Maybe you mixed it up?
The area around the aquarium has been off-limits for thirteen years now.
Here you go.
And you too.
Am I mixing it up?
This is yours, right?
Mom taught me how to fold this.
There's no way I'm mistaken.
I remember everything as if it was yesterday.
About my mom and the aquarium...
Maybe it's related to Mikhail Pavlichenko's life and death.
But my father's already...
Looks like I've got a lot of things to figure out.
My god... how did this happen?
So that's her mother...
She's younger than I thought.
Her ankles are so slim. Very nice.
Those ankles...
Miss, you have some pretty nice ankles.
I appreciate your compliment, but I guess you didn't notice this.
Yes, the contrast between your growing belly and slim ankles is mesmerizing.
Take my hand. It would be bad for the child if you were to fall.
Thank you.
Are you in Japan for business?
I'm here for sightseeing.
I used to study here.
Oh...
Then I'd suggest you quickly return to your country.
Pretty soon, you won't be able to see the sun here.
And then... a few days later after I left Japan...
Yes! It's her!
Yes?
Are you Makimiya Asako-san?
Please excuse me for coming here without prior notice.
I'd like to ask you some questions regarding Mr. Mikhail Pavlichenko.
You're from the Syndicate!
The Syndicate? Did you just say the Syndicate?
How do you...
Go away!
I don't have anything to do with him or the Syndicate!
Please wait!
Are you...
Don't tell me... that Professor Pavlichenko is a member of the Syndicate?
Who are you?
We're working to stop the Syndicate.
They have been lurking in the darkness.
But we'll definitely unveil them!
Please... tell me what happened between you and the Syndicate.
And about Suou and Shion.
I've met her twice before.
The first time was in Ikebukuro.
And the other time was...
when I joined the Syndicate, and went to a university in Moscow as a contractor.
The professor was researching something interesting at that university.
But nobody knew a thing about it.
I was hired as an agent for another faction
and infiltrated his lab.
That day, I took Shion and Suou to the university.
I just wanted to give my husband his lunch.
Did you see that? That's what it becomes.
Um...
Those ankles...
I did it!
Whoa, you did great, Suou!
I know!
Mom, I have to pee.
All right, let's go.
Suou, are you coming too?
I'll be here!
I want to make more.
When Papa's work is done, I want to give it to him.
I see.
At that time, the Syndicate's internal conflicts had reached a point of no return.
I was framed...
That day, at that place.
Mama.
Mama!
Mama, Suou...
Suou...
Suou!
Suou died in that explosion...
She died!
Episode 10    You Smile on that Fake Street Corner
Answer me!
Where is Yin?!
Yin?
Yin...?
Izanami!
Izanami...
Iza... na... mi...
No! Izanami... can't meet with Izanagi!
Why?
A big disaster...
Evolution...
The old woman that holds the memories of the future...
The various different futures she recorded...
Various?
The world is running...
A dreadful memory written in the Mitaka Documents...
And... and then...
I have to protect Hazuki-san.
I just want to know about Izanami!
Answer me!
Where's Izanami?!
Izanami will kill the contractors...
The 18th Research Lab...
I have to stop her...
Or else... or else Hazuki-san will....
I'll stop her.
I thought I was done with you.
You've done your job splendidly.
What?
You brought her to Tokyo, didn't you?
But letting her go alone...
A bullet was found in an incident at Oomiya...
as well as an anti-tank rifle, modified for a left-hander.
Poor little red star...
I wonder how Section 3 is going to treat her.
I searched for Suou after the explosion.
I ran... and ran... and then...
I saw him using the ME on her lifeless body!
Mikhail!
What are you doing to our child?!
I'm doing this exactly because she's our child!
She'll be ours forever!
Forever?
Forever.
Hey! My body is dog food now!
What are you going to do?!
Stop! Asako!
You will regret this! Asako!
Shion!
Shion chose not to come with me.
I cremated Suou's body, and returned to Japan with her ashes.
And today, Suou... no... her fake clone appeared in front of me.
Fake?
She looked like Suou...
Her downcast look and pale lips...
She was like a perfect clone.
Was it Shion's power?
Shion Pavlichenko's... power?
He defiled her...
He's crazy!
She's a monster, created from his demented mind!
Hey! Suou!
Thank you for helping us!
I thought you ran away.
There's no place for me to run.
I wasn't as shocked as I thought I'd be.
Maybe because I'm a contractor?
Or just a copy?
I don't think these things matter.
You should cry if you want to.
Let's go.
Where?
Leave everything to me.
I'll guarantee your safety.
I-
No! She's...
Why are you in Section 3?
Answer me first!
Where's Youko?
Don't! She's...
She tried to capture you.
Yes! But she gave me steamed buns!
Let's go.
Li-kun!
Youko...
Youko... I...
I will kill BK201...
Why did you come back for me?
If you were able to kill someone, you wouldn't need my help anymore.
Why don't you be honest and apologize to her?
I see.
I can't shoot people, hence I can't become a real contractor.
Because I'm a copy...
You used your power?
Yes. I copied it while I was there.
It's a little bit smaller though.
I wonder if Suou will be happy.
About what?
The fabricated memories we gave her.
A day with her family at the aquarium.
She’d be hurt even more if she found out the truth.
She has to learn what pain is.
I wonder what color her pain would be.
The orange glow of a crescent moon.
We can see the river from here.
The river in Sapporo was bigger and flowed faster.
This is my memory, right?
I have a favor to ask.
What?
I want you to call me like back then.
Back then?
Don't shoot, Suou.
I want you to call out my name.
Why?
Please.
I don't know of any other Suou.
Whether you're a copy or not,
you're the only Suou I know.
Suou.
Why am I crying?
It hurt when you didn't believe me.
It was much more painful than when you hit me.
I don't know so many things.
When you called my name, I was so happy.
But I found out that it was to save Yin...
And I was confused...
You killed my dad.
You're a good for nothing, violent drunkard.
A scumbag!
Yet, I feel so lonely without you.
Why do I feel like this?
Mao! Tell me!
Why?
Why, you ask...
Don't worry about anything for now.
Let's just sleep tonight.
Thanks, Hei.
She cries a lot for a contractor, huh?
Is she incomplete, because she's a copy?
She can't control her feelings properly.
Perhaps...
How much do we know about contractors?
You're right.
But it's precisely because she's incomplete that she's in love with you.
So, why did you come back?
Does she resemble your sister?
Perhaps I saw myself in her.
We're led by ignorance and incompleteness...
Yet...
both of us don't have the time to be swayed around.
Don't tell me... that is...
Kureteku yuubae ni senaka osarete
My back is pressed by the darkening glow of dusk
Arukidasu kage ga shimesu hou e
I start walking toward where my shadow points
Taenai ikutsu mo no deai to wakare o
Repeating the many, ceaseless encounters and partings
Kurikaeshi doko e mukau no ka
Where do I head to?
Hito wa dare mo mayoinagara
For all people, while they are lost,
tsumi to iu na no sadame o seotte
they bear the fate known as sin
Sore de mo nao ikiru imi o shiru darou
Nevertheless, I'll still learn of the meaning to live, right?
Bokura wa sou Day by Day
That's right, Day by Day,
ashita e tsuzuku michi no tochuu de
we're midway on the road leading to tomorrow
Now Say It Again kimi to futari no mama
Now Say It Again, though it'd be great if
irareta nara ii no ni naa...
I could remain together with you...
Hey, what is that?
Is that...
The moon?
It's out.
Yes.
It's pretty.
Within the golden soup is a hidden taste, made out of bitter memories and bittersweet premonitions.
Salty tears flow down and stain our cheeks.
The morning that we split up has come again.
Also known as the Gate of Hell.
If you go there, it is a place where your wish will be fulfilled.
If you go there, it is a place where you will lose something
And so, the curtain for the last act raises.