Health Products
Specialty Store
Fureai Road
Ice Cream
Evenin', granny.
BEEF
Prices
Children            200 Yen
Adults                 800 Yen
Hello there. It's been a while, Raku-chan.
Men’s
Women's
Our bath is a bit out of sorts, so I came to use the one here.
Of course, please take your time.
What's this? My, you sure have grown.
You're looking more and more like your father.
Men’s
Women's
I'm not exactly... happy to hear that.
Excuse me!
So this is a bathhouse?
What a nice atmosphere.
Welcome.
Hm?
R-Raku!
Wh-What are you doing here?
I could ask you the same!
Heavy
Light
Water Pressure Control
Battery
Exchange
Fuse
Pilot Light
Hot Water
Shower
Please be sure to turn off the fuse.
If kept on, the battery will run out in 1 month.
Push down and turn
Reheating
Beware of Heating
While Empty
Reheating
Beware of Heating
While Empty
Push down and turn
Reheating
Beware of Heating
While Empty
Push down and turn
Beware of Heating
While Empty
Push down and turn
Beware of Heating
While Empty
The bath at my house is out of sorts.
Is yours in the same boat?
Of course not.
I've always been interested in visiting a bathhouse, and this is the only large one in the area.
I see. So it's just a coincidence?
Don't you dare try to peek!
Like I'd want to.
kimi ni utai kikasetai koto
There's something I want to tell you
kowarenai you ni daiji ni shisugichatte sa
But I've been holding it too dear, afraid it might break
kyou mo meeru wo tsuzutte wa mata
Today I write you a message again
kuuhaku de nurikaete chigitte shimau no
Only to wipe it clean and discard it
konna itsumo wo fukitobasu kikkake wo
A chance to break this cycle
maneku bakari no yubisaki wo
Lies in my fingertips
tenohira de kasanete
That I'm holding up with my hand
ima wo kaeru koto wa tsurai koto mo aru kedo
Changing the status quo can be painful
tatoe piisu ga sorottemo
But even when all the pieces are gathered
kono te de michibikanakya
I still need to put them together myself
daiji na ima wo tebanasu no wa kowai yo ne
As much as I'm scared to let go of the present I cherish
demo machinozonda subete wa soko ni aru no
Everything I've been waiting for is there
soko ni aru no
It's all there
Bathhouse
Still, who would've thought...
Coming to the same bathhouse on the same day...
Raku!
Could you lend me some soap?
There isn't any over here.
Chitoge?
Are you on the other side?
Yeah, I am. Hurry up.
Here, catch.
Thank you!
Geez.
Still...
To think that a girl I know would be on the other side of this wall.
It's making me kind of nervous.
Wow, what a humongous bath.
Look, Honda!
There's a sauna, and over there is a herbal bath!
Don't get so carried away, Mistress.
M-Marika?
What are you doing here?
Come now, Honda. Let's wash our bodies over there.
Hey... wait up, you.
This is my first time coming to a bathhouse.
I've been wanting to try it out for some time now.
Lies...
That makes me angry for some reason.
Good grief. What's with all these coincidences?
Hm?
What are you talking about?
Hey! You still using the soap?
Give it back!
That voice is...!
Raku-sama!
T-Tachibana?
Why are you also...?
I never thought I'd run into you here! I'm so happy!
Shall I wash your back?
W-Wait—
What do you think you're doing?
Are you an idiot?
Oh, do you intend to get in the way?
What are you looking at?
You...
Pervert!
Why...?
It's been a while since we've been to a bathhouse.
I know. It's nice once in a while, isn't it?
I can't believe Chitoge and Tachibana followed me here.
I'd better not linger here too long.
Oh no, I forgot to bring my shampoo.
What am I going to do? Can you lend me yours, Onee-chan?
You really are helpless, Haru.
That was a nice bath.
Ah, you're done, Raku-chan?
Huh?
I'm sorry, Raku-chan.
I need to step out for a little while. Could you man the booth 'til I get back?
Huh?!
All you have to do is stand here.
And maybe work the register.
N-No, wait, this is all too sudden!
Also I'm a guy!
What if something were to happen in the women's bath...?
Nothing will, probably. We usually only get seniors, so don't worry.
Coffee Milk
Well then, I'm counting on you.
W-Wait—!
Damn.
Why did this have to happen?
Well, I doubt anything will happen.
Attendant, could you come here for a second?
Yes, what is it?
Oh dear. Today's booth manager is such a cute boy, isn't he?
The faucet in the women's bath is broken.
Could you fix it?
Huh? B-But, I'm a guy...
It's fine, it's fine.
You're a cute little boy, so we don't mind!
N-No. W-Wait!
This is bad.
Chitoge and the others are in there.
Isn't it about time you got out?
Oh? Couldn't I say the same about you?
Oh my.  You're such a gentleman!
That's so lovely!
Could you direct me, please?
First, head straight forward.
I'd better not see anything I don't have to.
Otherwise, Chitoge's going to pummel me.
Ichijou-kun?
Why? Why is Ichijou-kun here?
Take a few more steps forward, and it'll be on the wall to your right.
Good luck!
Let's see, a few more steps forward and...
To the right...
Uh... on the wall... the wall...
N—
Don't—!
I'm here!
What do you think you're doing?
Why are you walking around the women's bath like it's no big deal? Are you insane?
And what were you trying to do to my sister?
If you lay a hand on her, I swear I'll—!
This voice... is it Haru-chan?
Then, does that mean Onodera is also...?
You're unbelievable...
Geez!
Get out of here already!
Sorry! My bad!
It's pretty noisy out there.
What's the matter, Kirisaki-san?
Finally had enough?
Don't make me laugh.
I can go for another three hours.
Aren't you just about at your limit?
I've barely used up five percent of my strength.
Well I've only used one percent.
I can't believe Onodera and her sister are here, too.
Why today of all days?
Attendant, can you come here for a moment?
All right!
What is it this time?
Well, two girls passed out in the sauna.
Can you go and check on them?
She was talking about you guys?
We'll leave it to you.
The floor's slippery, so be careful.
Geez.
What were you guys doing?
Making me look after you.
What an awful day.
Hm?
It's going to fall off any second now!
Stop!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Raku-chan.
Oh?
Passed out, despite being the attendant, huh?
Raku-sama.
Hurry up, Black Tiger!
Excuse me!
Service
This feels great!
I've always wanted to go to a hot spring with everyone!
It's like it's our own secret hot spring.
By the way, where are Ichijou-kun and Maiko-kun?
Open Air Hot Spring
Horny Paradise
Endless Imagination
Sexiness Galore
Nudity Galore
There's a men's bath on the mountainside.
If they try to come and peek, they'll get a face-to-face with my fists.
I don't think we have to worry about Ichijou-kun...
By the way, Tsugumi-san.
Could it be...
Your breasts have grown again?
Huh?
Eh?! They did?
Please, let me feel them!
Watch out for
Peeping Toms!
Well, this is quite...
Me, too! Let me!
W-Wait, stop—!
Paula-san, your skin's so white!
It looks really smooth.
Could you please stop staring?
Your skin is real pretty, too, Haru.
Hurry up and...
Take everything off!
Come on!
I can do it myself!
Huh? Fuu-chan, your face is red.
We haven't even been in the hot spring, yet you're already dizzy?
Hm? Not really.
What's that?
It's a geyser! This is the first time I've seen one!
That's pretty cool.
What did you all do with your clothes and the stuff you were carrying?
We should keep everything in one place.
Watch out for monkeys!
A monkey might come and swipe something.
Really? I kind of want to see them.
Watch out for geysers!
This should do the trick.
Now then, let's all enjoy the hot springs!
Huh?
Wha—?
Wow. This is a pretty nice looking hot spring.
While
there’s
hot
water,
feel
free to
I wonder if Onodera and the other girls are already bathing.
I don't think anything will come up this time, so I can relax.
Come to think of it, where did Shuu go?
He said he'd be here soon.
Hm?
What?
What was that sound just now?
Found it.
Geez, why did it have to land over there?
Isn't that the men's bath?
Our cell phones and bags were in there.
More importantly, our clothes went along, too.
We can't go anywhere without them.
But doesn't that mean...
everyone's underwear is in there, too?
If Ichijou-senpai finds them...
Let's go retrieve it before that bean sprout finds them!
If we all work together, I'm sure we can pull it off!
Right!
What was that sound earlier?
It's really bothering me.
Geez, why do I have to sneak into the men's bath looking like this?
It looks like he hasn't noticed our bag yet.
If I move quickly and snatch it up, this'll be over in no time.
What's that sound?
Mistress, now's your chance!
Nice one, Tsugumi! Now, while I have the chance...
Oh crap.
Is there a snake or something?
I need a stick or so—
Gyah! Don't look this way!
What was that splash just now?
Shuu? Is that you?
Oh crap!
We have to help her!
Distraction!
Ah! What is it this time?
Wh—?
What the hell? What's going on?
Are you all right, Mistress?
Thanks. You saved me.
I'll go next.
No, me! I'm going next!
Oh no! The bag is going to fall!
What should we do? It'll fall any moment now!
Crap, We have to hurry.
Is is some kind of weird animal?
I need to finish up here quickly.
Look! I think Senpai is about to wash his hair.
Now's your chance!
Oh, I'll go now!
I can't believe I'm standing in front of Ichijou-kun looking like this.
What am I doing?
Hm? Shuu?
Good timing.
Could you hand me the soap over there?
Shuu?
It's Shuu, right?
Huh?
That feeling...
Shuu?
Huh? There's no one here.
What's going on?
Sorry.
You're kidding.
Then, just now...
The one passing me the soap was...
Friend.
That idiot! Don't fall, don't fall!
Chitoge-chan! If you lean too hard it's going to...
Huh? What are you guys doing there?
G—
G-G—
Get amnesia!
I've kept at it for two hours!
They'll never expect me to come climbing up this steep mountain!
Here I come, garden of the goddesses,
Shangri-La!
Huh?
Why... isn't anyone here?
Huh?!
omoi no sokudo hayamatte
My feelings are picking up speed
oitekareta kotoba jikan ga nagai yo
Time drags on and words get left behind
kimi no jishaku ni tsukamatte
When I was drawn in by your magnet
shiranai watashi shitta doushite kurushiino
I, who was ignorant, became aware. Why is it so painful?
wagamama bakka de
You’re always selfish
kowagari de
You’re always afraid
kimi ga daiji de
But because you’re so precious to me
aa kawaikunaritai no
Ah! I want to be dear to you
meibii ashita no hiroin ha
Maybe tomorrow’s heroine
koi wo hakobu kamisama no kimagure no sata shidai
Will depend upon the whims of the god who bears love
donna mondai ga narande donna taisetsu tsukuru no
No matter what kind of problems come along, no matter what you deem important
kimi no kokoro sotto oshiete
Whisper your feelings to me