Just what are you...?
Where's Yin?
You're not Yin.
Where is she?
I'm...
No! You're just an observation spirit!
Why do you say that?
You're the one who changed me.
The spirit?
It doesn't matter, does it?
Even if I'm like this?
Hei.
Yin...
I'm glad.
Where is this?
So you've come to.
You're...!
He saved us.
This way.
Stop!
Don't worry.
If we wanted to kill you, we would've already done so.
We just want to talk to you two.
Stay here.
Okay.
Come in.
What do you want?
Why did you save me?
We didn't exactly come to save you.
We just didn't want them, formerly of the Syndicate, to have that doll.
Formerly?
The Syndicate no longer exists.
They are nothing but a mob trying to take claim to all the scattered powers.
The threat to contractors is now gone,
thanks to Amber giving her life so that you could choose the third option.
It may be hard to believe, but there are many here like you and me on the run from the Syndicate.
This is the truth.
Why are they after Yin?
She's a doll evolving at an unusually fast pace.
There are those who wish to know the reason why, and it's not just them.
And that includes me.
And all the more reason to since it was predicted more than 50 years ago in books.
What do you mean?
According to the books, a woman will awaken and obtain the power to change the world.
And what they want is that power.
Why Yin?
You're as oblivious as ever.
There's one thing I want to ask you too.
What is that doll to you?
Forget it.
Amber might have seen this future too.
Whether you stay here or leave is up to you.
Yin.
Tell me.
What's happening to you right now?
I don't know.
Something is trying to talk to me.
Something? Your spirit?
Not exactly.
Is it possible for me to talk to it?
Not now.
Is there anything I can do?
Yin.
When it feels that you're near me, it begins to talk to me.
All you can do is leave me.
Let's split up.
If my being with you is hurting you,
there's nothing we can do but leave each other.
No.
Even if we split up,
I won't be able to forget about you.
That child was born from contractors.
Whether it's a blessing or not, it doesn't have any powers.
It's a strange place.
Free from the binds of human society,
these contractors rationally came to an agreement,
and gave birth to the most unpredictable thing.
The leader here once called for the evolution of contractors.
Is this a result of that?
I was told the future of contractors lies here.
It's quite different from what I expected it would be, but it doesn't seem to be a lie.
We're new to this place too.
We were scouted from Hong Kong, just like you.
Nice to meet you.
Here you go!
Thanks.
Sorry...
What are you doing?
That's my question!
I almost got killed!
If she hadn't stopped them, I'd have been dead already!
Sorry for getting you involved.
Hey, that's not like you.
Still, what's up with this place?
They all act like contractors!
They are.
Everyone?
That's right.
Contractors who believed in their future.
Stop? Why?
Compared to Hong Kong, her mind is stable and she seems to be quite calm.
She is no doubt Izanami.
Just as I told you, the Syndicate is in a bad position,
and by stimulating another awakening, you will be able to fulfill the former leader's wish that they couldn't carry out.
What's there to hesitate about?
You seem to be misunderstanding something.
We fought with Amber so that contractors wouldn't go extinct,
not to stand above humans and rule.
You won't be able to do anything if you're scared, Amagiri!
You're a real punk.
Amagiri is an idiot.
Yes, he is.
But you seem more like an idiot to me.
Me? An idiot? How so?
What are you planning to do with the doll?
So, you're against it?
Now that we know that she's Izanami, we have orders to kill her.
I just can't agree with that order.
If she awakens, the world will break down.
It's already broken as it is.
So you're saying it's okay to make it even worse?
I don't think it is. I don't want to die yet.
Even if it breaks down, it doesn't mean that us contractors will die.
I don't know about humans though.
I don't know what you heard from the Madame, but she's human.
I only heard one thing from her.
We're humans that couldn't become dolls.
Basically, we're defects.
You're just trash, doll.
Can I talk to you?
Sure.
We've found out who the people in Hong Kong were dealing with.
It was a Japanese secret service agent, but we don't know their name or who they belong to.
And there are rumors that an agency will be formed in Japan that consists of contractors.
Whether they're related or not, I don't know.
They are probably after the doll too,
and from what I know, they've gotten hold of a lot of information.
I don't know how much longer this place will last.
Now would be our chance to strike.
Where's Amagiri?
He's not coming.
We're doing it with just us.
Did you see where the Black Grim Reaper is?
He's in the jungle now.
Doing what?
Weren't you going to kill kim?
Why? Why are you after me?
Because Amagiri said so.
You foiled our plans and killed Amber!
You're our enemy.
Yin!
Li...
What happened?
I don't know!
I was sleeping, and then I heard a loud cry!
I was scared, so I was hiding the whole time!
And when it quieted down, I came out and didn't see anyone!
Wait!
What the heck happened?
It's a baby.
Li!
What are you doing?
The baby is still crying!
According to the book, she will awaken and obtain the power to change the world.
Something tries to talk to me.
Something?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
There, there.
That idiot got me.
What happened?
It was the young contractor that was with me.
He couldn't wait for your doll to awaken any longer.
He injected her with something and made her unstable.
I should have realized it sooner, but it was too late.
I tried to go warn you and this is what became of me.
I can't stay in this dog any longer.
From what I saw, he was holding on to something,
and took your doll.
Where is she?
She's being followed.
Your doll hasn't completely awakened yet.
In the end, she stopped the awakening herself.
You can still make it.
So...
Go kill her already.
A
Can you fly? ano sora ni kagayaku Ziggy Star
Can you fly? Ziggy Star shining in the sky
kowareta yume kieta ai torimodoshite Fly away
Claiming back my broken dreams and lost love Fly away
Can you try? nikushimi o jihi e to kaete
Can you try? Changing this hate into compassion
kawaita mune o nurasu Darker than Black
Soaking up my dry chest Darker than Black
utsuro ni hikaru kousou no mado
From hollow spaces the windows on the skyscrapers shine,
hatasenu mama no yakusoku
a promise that remains unfulfilled
muda ni nagareta chi to namida ni somaru kanashii Game
Dyed in pointlessly flowing blood and tears, this sad Game
Oh, Where is my friend? hitori yozora o nagamereba
Oh, Where is my friend? If I Gaze at the night sky alone
hoshikage ni yureru kimi no Sweet smile
Swaying in the starlight is your Sweet smile
Can you try? tachihadakaru kabe o kowashite
Can you try? Break the wall that is blocking your way
tabidatsu toki o kizamu Darker than Black
The time to begin is ticking by Darker than Black
The battle continues, and the ruins are smeared in blood.
Are they after evolution or destruction?
Why was Yin chosen?
She slips through my held out hands, and falls.