Yesterday sucked!
I barely had any chances to speak to Onodera,
and then I got locked inside the storehouse with Kirisaki.
Whoops! Never mind that part!
Anyways, the issue at hand is that we were seen by Onodera!
Listen, Kosaki...
Whoa!
There's no use in wallowing in depression, all right?
But...
I just don't have it in me to go after a boy who already has a girlfriend.
It's so... It feels like it's something that you just don't do.
Well, not that you've done anything yet.
What are you going to do now? Give up, just like that?
What are they talking about? I can't quite hear.
Wait, you still have that key?
What?
Key?
Oh, that key from before...
I think she said it was the key to a bookcase in her house, or something.
Or do you actually intend to look for the boy you made that promise with ten years ago?
Wh-What did she just say? Ten years ago?
Promise? Does that mean...
Never mind.
In that case, I'll be glad to create an opportunity for you to find out how he feels.
It just so happens that I need to ask Kirisaki-san for a favor, anyway.
Huh? Wait... What are you gonna do?
I'm getting a bad feeling about this...
There's no question that Ichijou-kun has a crush on Kosaki.
Although it's just a woman's intuition.
Frankly, those two have been acting suspicious, too!
I'll discover the truth!
Episode 5: Swimming
Helper?
Yeah. You see, our swim team is pretty weak.
We've got a practice meet tomorrow, but we're a bit short on members.
I have no doubt that you're athletic enough.
If you don't mind, I'd really like you to join us.
Oh, that's totally fine with me! I love exercise!
Anyway,
Bea—Darling, why are you here?
Miyamoto, isn't this the girls' swim team?
Wh-Why am I here?
Because I have a favor to ask of you too.
Well, we'll get into that later.
Damn it... I can't get over that conversation about the promise!
I'm not in any shape to help.
Ru-Ru...
Ruri-chan!
Why did you register me as a swimmer...
when I can't swim at all?
There's no way I'll be of any help!
Huh? Ichijou-kun?
Oh my god, Onodera is as cute in a swimsuit as I imagined!
The key!
It's the same one that she dropped the other day!
All I heard was that Kirisaki-san would be coming.
Onodera did say it was the key to a bookcase,
but if that's all it is, there's no way she'd carry it 24/7!
Don't tell me... that key's actually...
Oh gosh, Ruri-chan! What am I supposed to do?
Why are you staring? You creep!
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Shut up! You pervert!
There's no way that Ichijou-kun could possibly have feelings for me.
And now Kirisaki-san is here with us too.
How am I supposed to act?
Also, this feels a little awkward...
after seeing them together yesterday.
By the way, what were you two up to inside that storehouse yesterday?
“In the darkness” of a “sealed room,”
“just the two of you,”
“in that position...” What does all that mean?
R-R-Ruri-chan! How can you ask that?
Th-That was a prank my guys played on us.
It was an accident, like... We kinda lost our balance.
An accident, he says.
She did it for me.
Thank you, Ruri-chan!
You guys were actually doing something indecent, weren't you?
Oh, no, we weren't!
We were not!
Hi there, Raku!
I hear that Kirisaki-san and Onodera are gonna help out the girls' swim team!
I came to watch!
Just look at you!
What a magnificent sight you are!
Ichijou-kun, about that favor I need from you...
I want you to teach Kosaki how to swim by tomorrow's meet.
So anyway...
Today we're gonna teach you how to swim. I'm Ichijou, and...
Right! I'm your other instructor, Kirisaki Chitoge!
Looking forward to working with you!
L-Likewise.
I never dreamed this would ever happen!
Oh, crap... I'm getting a little nervous!
I guess Ichijou-kun is teaching me how to swim.
I'm getting a little nervous.
Hey, Onodera, so you really can't swim?
Nope. Oh, Ruri-chan... She set this up without asking me.
But I wonder why she's making you help out when she knows you can't swim.
Who knows?
Um... I'm really sorry, Kirisaki-san, for making you do this on such short notice.
Don't worry about it!
I love these things!
Just leave all the hard work to me and forget everything else!
I can see why Ichijou-kun picked you.
You're such a lovely person, Kirisaki-san.
Oh, come now! You there, mademoiselle?
We may be indoors, but if you've got a swimsuit on, that means sunblock!
Shall I rub it on for you?
Huh? Huh?
Look, Maiko-kun... If you're gonna get in the way, would you mind going home?
Are you okay, Kirisaki-san?
Y-Yeah...
Oh, c'mon, Ruri-chan, you're such a spoilsport!
10,000 yen for a massage... What do you say?
You can pay me when you're rich!
Wait a sec, where's Four Eyes?
Isn't he staking us out today?
I mean, Shuu could've gotten himself shot just now.
Mistress...
How you've grown!
Your Claude couldn't be happier!
All right. I'm gonna start by showing you how it's done, so watch closely. Okay?
R-Right! Please, go ahead!
Well? Did you see that? Did you get the general idea?
Far too advanced. No help at all.
Why? I tried so hard to help her... so why?
A-Anyway, you can't swim at all, right, Onodera?
Let's start with the basics of the basics!
O-Okay...
All right, why don't we start off easy with some leg kicks?
Okay!
Wow, one-on-one swimming lessons with Onodera?
This was totally unthinkable until now.
Onodera's so close to me!
Her cleavage is showing a little thanks to her swimsuit being a little damp!
Hold on, I'm totally holding hands with her like it's the most natural thing in the world!
Onodera's hands... so soft and warm...
M-Make sure you don't let go, okay?
Onodera!
Sorry, Onodera.
No, it's my fault for not being able to swim.
No, it was all my fault.
What do you want to do now? Wanna take a break?
No, no, you're taking the time to teach me.
So I'll keep trying!
God damn it!
She's too damn cute!
I want to marry her!
Oh, hey. I'm gonna go buy some drinks.
It'd be wrong not to show my gratitude.
Is tea all right, Ichijou-kun?
Uh, yeah.
What a sweet girl!
All right! Now I'm pumped up to make sure Onodera learns how to swim!
Huh? Is that...
Onodera's key?
If this...
If this turns out to be... that key from ten years ago...
then Onodera's... the girl I made that promise with.
Yes...
Let's get married.
Damn it! What am I thinking?
But... if there was ever a time to find out...
it's right now.
Huh? What the... The key won't go in!
Was the head shaped like this?
I got you some tea, Ichijou-kun!
Hey, you! How dare you make a girl run your errands!
Huh? Ichijou-kun... that's...
What are you planning to do with the key to the girls' locker room?
You bean sprout... I knew you were a bean sprout...
but who knew you were such a perverted bean sprout?
It's not what it looks like!
It's not what you think! Just hear me out!
Yeah... Sure, sure. That's what they all say!
Come on, let's go, Onodera-san.
Hey, Miyamoto! I'm begging you! Please believe me!
Stare...
What's that look for? You're scaring me! Don't look at me like that!
I had no idea what that key was for!
Who designs a locker room key like that in the first place?
Oh, well, for some reason, they decided to go retro for the girls' locker room key.
Although, I hear it's just the principal's personal taste.
Taste?!
W-Wait, girls!
Ichijou-kun is saying that it's a misunderstanding.
Plus, I don't really see him as the type to peep on girls.
O-Onodera!
P-Probably...
Did you hear that? You'd better be grateful to Kosaki!
But in return, you're gonna see to it that Kosaki learns to swim by tomorrow, no matter what!
Because I'm letting you off the hook just this once.
Sure thing...
Thanks, Onodera, for believing in me.
Oh, no, don't mention it.
Hey, sorry about this, Kirisaki-san, but I'm borrowing your boyfriend.
Boyfriend?
Right, my boyfriend! N-No problem!
It's not like it's the end of the world for me!
What was that pause just now? And that reaction?
Could it be that... my hunch was right all along?
The Day of the Practice Meet
After all that, one day wasn't long enough for her to learn how to swim.
We practiced all evening long after school ended.
Good morning, Bean Sprout.
Hey, where do the athletes sign in?
Hey. So even you aren't audacious enough to wear a bikini today, huh?
I didn't have a choice yesterday!
It was on short notice, and I hadn't bought a school swimsuit yet.
Oh, wait! Could it be that you wanted to see me in my bikini, Darling?
My, what a dirty mind!
Seriously, if only you weren't a gorilla inside, you'd be perfect.
So? How far did you get with Onodera-san?
If she uses a kickboard, she can barely manage.
Then that means she hasn't learned to swim!
Lay off, will you?! How can you expect anyone to learn to swim in a single day?
As a matter of fact, I think I deserve some praise!
Sure, she might need kickboard, but she can swim 25 meters now!
I don't want to hear any whining coming from a boy.
If you take on a job, then finish it!
Isn't that what a real man would do?
Right where it hurts the most...
Good morning, Ichijou-kun, Kirisaki-san!
M-Morning, Onodera. Um... Are you okay?
Yes, I think so. I imagined myself swimming last night in the bathtub, too!
Well, don't overwork yourself. All you need to do is somehow finish the race.
Right! Thanks. I'm gonna do my best!
Why do you act so differently with her than when you're with me?
Why should I have to be nice to someone like you?
I could say the same about you!
All I'm saying is that seeing this blatant difference in treatment pisses me off!
Yeah, well, you treat Onodera and me differently, too!
Now you're asking for way too much, buddy!
I'm a lady, you know! You're supposed to treat me like a princess!
I didn't know someone who's a gorilla on the inside counted as a lady too!
What was that?
Are they fighting because they're close?
Or is it because they can't stand each other?
If I had to guess, I'd pick the latter.
But it's so different from their usual routine
that I just can't get a handle on what they really think about each other.
What... are they...
Look, they're still fighting.
Hey, you! Would it kill you to warm up a little?
What are you, my dad?
Please keep your voices down!
Really...
It's gonna be fine. After all, I practiced so much yesterday.
Plus, Ichijou-kun will be watching!
You can do it, Kosaki!
On your marks...
Holy crap, she doesn't know the first thing about being a sweet girl!
Hey, Miyamoto. Sorry about Onodera.
One day wasn't enough for her to master swimming.
Oh... Well...
He took it seriously? I was only joking.
Well, she should be fine.
She still gets to participate.
As long as she doesn't end up drowning or anything.
But Kosaki has always been unbelievably slow to learn anything, so...
Just kidding. This pool's shallow enough for her to stand in.
So there's no way that she'd...
Hey, see that?
Does that girl look like she's drowning?
Oh, crap!
Cramps! In both legs!
Would it kill you to warm up a little?
Kirisaki-sa—
That moron!
Hey! Look at that!
Are you okay?
I'll go get a teacher!
Get her up, fast!
Hey! Raku! Is Kirisaki-san all right?
I'm not sure. I don't think she swallowed too much water.
She's not breathing.
Not Breathing (A Lie)
What?
Raku, give her mouth-to-mouth.
What the hell?
Hey... Hey, wait a sec!
That's not something you leave to an amateur!
And why me?
Why you?
You're her boyfriend. Who else can we count on?
S-Seriously? Are you serious?
Mouth-to-mouth... Against my will?
I mean, come on, right in public, too?
Not to mention in front of Onodera!
No, this is an emergency, and every second counts!
No, but really...
Kiss Kirisaki...
Wait, am I an idiot or something? This is no time to hesitate!
If I don't do this now, I'm not a real man, am I?
Hail Mary!
What do you think you're doing?
Girls Locker Room
Ichijou-kun was something else, wasn't he?
Rescuing Kirisaki-san in such a dashing manner.
He looked so cool.
Do you wish you were the one drowning instead?
What? N-No, that thought never crossed my mind!
Just kidding.
Well, I admit that he doesn't seem to be just another loser.
At the end of the day, are those two on good terms or bad?
Their chemistry seems good and bad at the same time.
This gets more confusing by the second, huh?
The one thing I'm sure of now, though, is that they don't seem to actually be dating.
Wow, you brought that key with you?
I can't believe you'd hold onto a trinket from someone you met ten years ago so faithfully.
Well, it's precious to me.
Yeah, but all you remember about that boy is that he had a pendant with a keyhole, right?
To think that you don't remember anything else... Not his face nor name...
If you ask me, just hoping for a reunion with someone like that is a waste of time.
Isn't the love that you have here and now more important?
Your opponent is formidable too.
But... But you see, Ruri-chan...
That love from ten years ago just might be connected to my current love...
Ichijou-kun might have mistakenly thought that that locker room key was this key, you know?
If that's what happened...
Onodera and the others sure are late.
Oh, man, that was awesome!
Gotta hand it to the girls' swim team!
Shuu?
Hey, hey. By the way, Raku.
Which camp are you in?
Don't play dumb with me!
I'm talking about Onodera and Kirisaki-san's bodies!
I gotta say, I think I'm in the Onodera camp.
I mean, Kirisaki-san's breasts are the bomb,
but she's also a bit fleshy, you could say?
Not that I don't go for that, too... But hey, which do you prefer?
What happened?
Chitoge in Junior High School
I made Valentine's Day chocolates for you all!
They're works of art!
Thanks, Mistress!
Huh? Don't you think this chocolate's a little too bitter—
What the hell? It's too hard to chew—
I've always thought your chocolates are the best, year after year!
Aren't they? I get that a lot!
Raku, Junior High
School Student
Hey, Raku, did you get any Valentine's Day chocolates?
I'm about to get a boatload of them.
Yeah? That's awesome.
I'm home!
Welcome home, Young Master!
Well, how do you like this year's chocolates?
I think this year's turned out well, if I do say so myself.
Your chocolates rock, Big Bro!
Try mine, too!
Onodera, Junior High
School Student
I never did manage to give Ichijou-kun my Valentine's Day chocolates.
I made them myself too!
Hey, Kosaki, you have chocolates. Are you giving them to someone?
No, no... These are...
You're not giving them to anyone?
Then can I eat them?
Hey, these are pretty good for homemade chocolates!
You think so?
Teacher! Miyamoto-san suddenly collapsed!
What? Let me see. Oh, my!
She's foaming at the mouth! What happened?
Special
Skill
Kirisaki has been invited to celebrate the New Year at the Ichijou home.
Boring.
Young Master! We'd appreciate it if you would show us your specialty!
Right! Well, guess I have no choice!
Would rather love than be loved.
If that is the code of this household...
Don't ever show the enemy your back!
That is the way of a just man.
Now go brush your teeth!
This guy can really sing!
Just enka.