Gods from across the country gather at the Divine Assembly in Izumo.
There's a decent chance one of those gods knows Mikage's whereabouts.
Honestly! Where in the world could he have gone?
The test is to raise a daemon.
Wait... Oh, dear!
It hatched! Mamoru hatched!
A barrier against evil!
She's going to Izumo!
I wonder what's happening on this world
I fly through the sky into space
and circle the world
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday
With my periodic biorhythm
I'm like a washing machine
Just kidding
Yes, I'm spinning around
Around, around the world
Because there's no limit to my love
Spinning around, around, around the world
I want to tell you that I love you, even if it confuses me
Bam, bam, bam
You're not paying attention
Sometimes love keeps being one-sided
It's gotten so hopelessly complex
But I'll make it all true with a miracle
Hey, God,
I'm your god
I think
There is something I must ask.
The egg was supposed to take seven days to hatch,
yet when it cracked on the first day, it already had a base form.
I can only assume that you
planted it there from the start.
And your true intention was to
raise Nanami to godhood all along.
So you figured it out.
There's no fooling you, Tomoe darling. Teehee.
What are you up to?
Tomoe!
Huh? Where did he go?
I am here.
Oh, Tomoe, I need a little favor.
My necklace is caught in my hair and won't come out.
Get it off me!
It never ends with you.
If you need grooming, I'm your man!
M-Mamoru?
No way! So cute! He's like elementary school size?!
Pop a squat, and I'll get it off in no time.
Mind your own business, monkey.
Changed Back
Nanami asked me to get it off.
Behave yourself and stay a monkey.
Changed Back
Grab
What'd you do that for?!
Just forget it! I'll get Mizuki to take it off!
You really shouldn't anger your lady and mistress.
The God Goes to Izumo
If this is what it costs for three people to stay in Izumo, it looks like I only have enough for two.
That is fine.
We cannot leave the shrine unattended, after all.
I will come with you to Izumo.
The snake can attend to the shrine.
That's quite the plan.
Especially considering that between the two of us, I'm the expert on all things Izumo.
You may be the land god's familiar, but you've never attended the Divine Assembly even once, have you?
He hasn't?
With Tomoe's past as a wild fox, he'd surely be harassed if he went to the divine assembly.
He spared that disgrace by playing the housewife.
Oh, Lord Mikage, he was so kind and generous.
But the attendees of the Divine Assembly are gods, right?
It doesn't matter how bad you might've been in the past, Tomoe. There's no way they'd harass you.
That'd be so unbecoming of a god.
How can you even say that?!
Between us, you would surely get the worst of it in Izumo.
What?
I am very worried about you too.
What? What?
I really think I should go. You know, to confer Nanami prestige.
All the more reason I cannot
allow the unreliable snake to go.
As the primary familiar of the shrine, I should be the one to go.
You don't know the way, so you'd only slow her down!
You're one to talk! You barely know
your way around the mundane world!
Come on, you guys. Stop fighting.
No fighting!
Violence is forbidden!
If we really need someone to stay home, then we'll decide who goes...
with a game of shogi!
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Glooooom
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
Never
played
before
I'm off to go buy a plane ticket, and you two better
have this sorted out peacefully by the time I get back.
Nanami, there is no reason for a plane
when you have the Night Fog Carriage.
I'll take you on my snake.
No.
Vehicles not made for humans
don't make for comfortable rides.
Tomoe and Mizuki really need to chill out.
I mean, why would a god care what I do or don't do?
My apologies for the wait, Ms. Momozono.
One adult ticket to Izumo, correct?
Yes.
Whoops!
My bad, missy.
Not at all.
Whoa...
Oh...
A f-fox mask?
Hey! You're...
You are making a racket, Monjirou.
Ow.
Our mission is to obtain airplane tickets.
Do not get distracted.
Airplanes are lame!
Perhaps, but that is what he requested.
They're weird.
I don't wanna ride in a hunk of steel like this!
I'm steering clear of them.
Now, I just need to go to a pharmacy
to get motion sickness medicine, some toiletry, and...
maybe some snacks too.
Nanami!
Four bloodthirsty auras are coming this way.
Here, in the middle of town?
Yes, and they're none too friendly!
They're headed straight for you!
Run!
Run? But where...
T-Tomoe!
How...
How did that piece get here?
It looks like you've finally noticed.
While you were preoccupied with the
movement of my rook, I secretly moved
my bishop to put your king in check already!
Don't do that!
Ow.
We start over.
Who cares about the match anyway?
It's not like you actually want to go to Izumo.
Whether I want to attend is of
little consequence at the moment.
I can't help but worry, you know.
What if those around her spoke ill of you?
Nanami wouldn't be able to bear it.
Well, it serves you right, though.
I do not really care.
She has proven that she can handle adversity.
They're gonna catch up to us!
There's no sign of anyone in the park ahead! It's perfect!
I'll drive them back there!
Someone's here.
Hey, uh...
Nanami, they're here!
What?!
Sorry! Pardon me!
Please, stay still.
They're here.
Th-They're an incredible mass of miasma!
These guys aren't spirits. They're former gods.
Former gods?
They used to be gods, but they
were stripped of their godhood.
I'm facing gods?
Are you the human who was
invited to the Divine Assembly?
I-I am.
Unacceptable!
You are but a filthy human, yet you dare try to set foot in the realm of the divine?
You overreach yourself!
Decline to attend, little girl!
Do this, and I shall not disembowel you where you stand!
B-But technically, I've been invited because I'm the land god of Mikage Shrine.
I have to accept!
Mikage Shrine?
The one that houses that barbaric fox?
What did you say?!
A degenerate fox serving as a familiar! What rubbish!
As if a mere dumb beast has any value!
Human male, what is so amusing?
Has-beens, no longer counted among the gods, vilifying a human god is a comical sight.
You bastards should take a good hard look at yourselves.
You look for all the world like lowly spirits.
Silence, human!
That is what a human gets for opening his big mouth!
Mamoru!
Wh-What is this?!
You'd raise your hand against a defenseless human?
Is that something befitting of former gods?
Riffraff like you...
need to go back to where you belong!
Barrier against evil!
A-Are you all right?
I'm so sorry for getting you mixed up in this.
You're annoying me.
Quit making a mountain out of a molehill.
W-Wait! You're badly hurt.
Don't touch me.
A hospital...
We need to get you to a hospital!
There's something better than a hospital.
What?
Y-You seem fine, so I'll be going now!
Wh-What's the deal with that guy?!
So much for all her talk.
Uncooperative woman.
Master Kirihito!
We got the airplane tickets.
We obtained one of each kind of seat, window and aisle.
Master Kirihito, what happened to you?!
Never mind. I'll be all right.
What're you saying?
That is a human body!
It requires care.
Shut up.
I will not remain in this pathetic body forever.
I will regain my original body.
And when you do, this world
will belong to you once more.
Under the reign of Master Akura-oh.
Just a filthy human...
A degenerate fox serving as a familiar!
I can't believe how they acted.
What's wrong? You seem kinda down.
If it's about that pervert, don't let him get to you.
I'm okay.
If it's about me, I don't care.
But...
If it becomes about Tomoe...
I'm back.
I lost to
Tomoe.
Mizuki
Behold, Nanami.
I lost to
Tomoe.
Mizuki
I lost to
Tomoe.
Mizuki
I lost to
Tomoe.
Mizuki
I lost to
Tomoe.
Mizuki
I lost to
Tomoe.
Mizuki
I lost to
Tomoe.
Mizuki
I lost to
Tomoe.
Mizuki
I thwarted the snake's unscrupulous tactics to secure a brilliant victory.
This settles it. I will accompany you to Izumo.
No matter what happens, I will protect you,
so rest easy, Nanami.
No.
What?
Mizuki will be coming with me to Izumo.
You will attend to the shrine.
Got it?
What?!
Yay!
If something happened to Tomoe,
I'd lose my cool for sure.
Next part coming
right up
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
What is this?
You are about to depart for Izumo,
and I am the only one to see thee off?
You coming was enough, Himemiko.
Had I known, I would have
brought the entire clan with me.
Where art thy familiars?
Mizuki's gone ahead on his snake.
We'll be meeting up over there.
This is unexpected. Master Tomoe is to stay home?
Tomoe has to disguise himself as me and go to school while I'm away.
He wouldn't stop complaining, though.
Why should
I have to?!
Ah, that reminds me.
We took something called a "photograph" the other day.
And I am handing them out to those I consider close friends.
Kotarou
Numano
Himemiko
Wow, talk about romantic!
That's so cute!
We took it the other day when I went on a date with Kota.
It looks adorable, does it not?
It looks like things are going well.
And 'tis all thanks to thee.
Nah, I didn't really...
I, a spirit, am able to repeatedly meet with my beloved Kota
because we have thee, the god of matchmaking, on our side.
And now, thou art attending
the Divine Assembly in Izumo.
The very thought fills me with pride.
Thou wilt surely make a difference there also.
Take care upon thy journey.
I will.
Goodbye!
Isn't the classroom kind of cold?
Yeah.
I can't stop shivering.
The mood in here is super depressing.
Damn you, Nanami.
She passed me over to go alone with the snake, and for a whole week at that.
A whole week, alone with the snake...
I am amazed she can so casually go on a trip with the bastard who once attacked her.
And until just the other day, she was
blubbering about having feelings for me.
What utter nonsense.
To think that I...
Good morning, my little kittens!
Kurama!
Morning, Nanami.
What's this? Did you leave that
nagging fox back at the shrine?
Kurama's literally on fire!
Water! Water! Water! Water! Water!
I'm finally here at Izumo, the land of the gods!
Wow, this is amazing! It's a tourist spot!
They don't just have notable sights.
Freshwater clams! Eel! Prawns!
Since we came all the way out here, we should enjoy everything we can.
Ask me anything about Izumo, okay?
You're already here, Mizuki?
Yep, I got here an hour ago.
Well, I'd love to show you around, but there's no time right now.
The Greeting of the Gods has already begun.
Greeting of the Gods?
Yeah...
The gods are streaming ashore to gather at the Grand Shrine.
We'd better hurry too.
It is the place where all the gods gather just once every year.
The highest ranking shrine in the Province of Izumo, the Izumo Grand Shrine.
What a beautiful shrine.
The host is Ookuninushi.
So this Ookuninushi is the one in charge of the Divine Assembly?
That's right.
A god with such a large shrine dedicated to him...
I wonder what he's like.
Nanami!
This is...
Mizuki?
The bothersome Divine Assembly has begun.
Lady Inaho
Yet again, I must meet face-to-face with
bothersome folk to discuss bothersome matters.
You are one to talk, Lady Inaho.
The Three
Fumigae Gods
You will be snoozing through the entire Divine Assembly anyway.
War God
Takehaya
I expect that no one will arive late this year.
Amazing! So these are the other gods?
Are you that new human god?
What?
Show me your divine powers.
If a mortal like you has come to the Divine Assembly, surely you must have some skills.
Show me!
Skills?
Uh...
Mamoru's not here!
Squeeze
He's with
Mizuki
Make it quick.
Uh...
I have some skill with white talismans and barriers against evil.
But I seem to have misplaced my daemon for the time being, so I can't do that.
As for the talismans, I brought...
Oh, my bag! I don't have the talismans either!
The drum to gather has sounded.
Let us all make our way to the banquet hall.
You will get nowhere spending time with a human, War God.
Let us go to the Divine Assembly.
W-Wait.
They're so fast!
So Narukami was right.
It seems you really are an ordinary human with no talent or abilities.
You are an eyesore!
Stay out of my sight from now on!
Let's go...
to the hall of the Divine Assembly.
How many times do I have to tell you?
You're such a stupid guard rabbit.
I'm a familiar who came to accompany my god to the Divine Assembly!
Familiar though you may be, you shall not pass.
Ah! If I don't get inside soon, I'll lose Nanami!
Unless you are accompanied by a god, you cannot pass through the gate.
Wait here until your god comes for you.
I already told you!
She's new to this, so she doesn't know all the rules!
How could I of all people have
gotten separated from Nanami?
She's probably all alone and scared to death.
You can enter by piggybacking another god arriving late.
This meeting happens once a year!
There's no way some stupid god would arrive late!
Guard rabbit, I'm late! Open the back gate!
My skin was looking awful today,
so getting my make-up done took forever.
Lord
Otohiko!
Oh, my, what's this? How adorable.
Lord
Otohiko!
I hadn't planned for this.
I can't believe I got lost in here.
No matter how far I walk, everything looks the same.
Where did all the gods go?
I'm all alone, and without Mizuki or the Divine Assembly, I can't get to the meeting hall.
It's pathetic.
The light's going out! No way!
S-Someone...
Is anyone there?
A-Anyone?
Are you lost?
Come. I'll show you the way.
Who are you?
This is it.
Beyond these doors is the
chamber of the Divine Assembly.
Um...
You're not going to attend the meeting?
I'm not attending.
Are you afraid, Miss Human God?
Even if I go in there, there may not be anything I can do.
No god is truly omnipotent.
They have their strengths and weaknesses.
That's why each has a role to play.
A role?
Lady Inaho is not industrious,
and while the Three Fumigae Gods are well-learned, they have poor penmanship.
The War God is forbidding and aggressive, but he's a terrible singer.
Huh...
But each has something they excel at.
And so do you.
Of all the gods, you alone can see through the eyes of man.
You can sympathize with humans, sit next to them, and put your arm around their shoulders.
Kotarou
That is your strength.
No one else can do that.
Attend the Divine Assembly, and you will surely see.
Second Sight
So speak your mind proudly as a
participant of the Divine Assembly.
I will.
Thank you very much.
Oh, wait. At least tell me your name.
Even once I open these doors,
there will surely be something that I can do.
Pardon me for being late.
I, Momozono Nanami of the Mikage Shrine, have arrived.
So that is the human god that
Otohiko recommends most highly.
Now I see. Her eyes are so beautifully pure.
Dear little Momozono Nanami, I choose you.
Hey, can you hear me?
That night, I was looking
at the fleeting remnants of the day
The milky way spread across my vision
It was very beautiful
Hey, can you hear me?
I don't think I can talk to other people about this
I'll call up God, I think
If a new day hadn't begun
then yesterday's tomorrow would be today
and yesterday would be the day before
Preview
Here we are at the Divine Assembly.
I'm waiting for you
Every which way, there are gods! Gods! Gods! Gods?
I'll stay here
The boat is stopped here
And the host is the imposing Ookuninushi.
Meanwhile, Tomoe stays home and attends school.
Oh, dear, he's in a bad mood.
If today weren't today
Next time, "The God Falls into the Netherworld."
The God Falls into the Netherworld
Slip to Hell.