Brother!
You're here again?
Yurikano,
I promise you.
I will settle this war through negotiation,
and show the people in the Polyhedron federation,
not to mention Dizelmine,
the beauty of this ocean once again.
I'll pray for your success.
I'm going.
I don't get it.
You don't know the word "hideout"?
That's not what I meant!
Why do we have to hang out in a place like this?
Very soon, the main Kiss troop will rendezvous with us.
My ship's not gonna be able to hold all of us at once.
Then this is all a plan to take the Vox?
Easy, now! You three will stay away from the Vox.
Got that?
I'll contact you once everything is ready.
Be with Kiss!
Lag-Rin, Lag-Rin
That girl wearing sweats is somehow special
When she takes it off, she can be anything
In search of things she treasures, she'd go to the bottom of the ocean
She's brash to a fault and difficult for those around her
Lag-rin, Lag-rin
I'll come meet you right away
when I hear you call for help
Perfect!
Live life!
Rewrite fate and fly,
Fly away
On a brighter day
If sticking your tongue out and walking proudly gets you in trouble
burn and fly away
Try unite tonight
Lag-rin, Lag-rin
Departing Katsuura,
Heading to Kamogawa
What was that all about?
Do you guys do that kind of thing often?
Nope, that was a first.
He probably made it up just now.
And why do we have to take orders from him anyway?
That's what you get for becoming Villagiulio's lackeys.
I don't remember ever agreeing to that!
And whose lackey are you, dressed up like that?
You think I wanted to wear this?
I had no choice!
I was already in these clothes when I woke up!
I bet you think it looks good on you, too.
The hell I do!
Wow!
Look, you can see the ocean right outside!
Oh, there's a little kitchen too!
And a closet!
Hey, why don't we put up some nice blue curtains?
Just imagine waking up each morning feeling like you're at the bottom of the sea!
Can we pretend none of that just happened?
Huh?
Yeah...
That's a good idea.
Kamo Girl's
Oraga
86th Annual
Art
Oraga
86th Annual
Art
Oraga
86th Annual
Art
Oraga
86th Annual
Art
Oraga
86th Annual
Art
Oraga
86th Annual
Here it is, the Oraga Festival!
Oraga
Art
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
86th Annual
Oraga
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Art
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
Festival
86th Annual
Oraga
The Oraga Festival is one of the Sweats Club's most vital events.
The Oraga Festival?
It's an arts festival!
It's where all the classes and clubs get to show off their school activities to the public.
It's basically like a school fair.
Oh, a school fair!
So that's why they have all the food stalls and such.
So what will the Sweats Club be doing?
Wh-What?
Are you okay with just sitting around like this?
'Cos I'm sure as hell not!
You with me?
You guys...
Tell me, what else can we do?
Like I said, take the Vox and...
Except we all lost.
The three of us were undefeated back at the Academy,
and yet we still lost.
So we're supposed to just sit down and shut up?
Then we really are nothing more than Villagiulio's lackeys!
I'm not staying put just because Villagiulio told us to.
Huh?
Izo...
Tell me, just how do you plan to fight the Vox?
Huh? Well, that's...
Our fighting style is not effective
against Kyono Madoka, Vox Aura's pilot.
I've crossed swords with her,
so I know.
I sense a mysterious strength in that girl.
Just like Yurikano.
Don't compare her to Yurikano!
However, the chairman of Novumundus
prohibited Kyono Madoka from piloting the Vox.
That's because she's already in dangerous territory.
What's that supposed to mean?
They fear that, like Yurikano,
she might trigger something equivalent to the Tragedy of Militia Zodia.
Running headfirst into battle isn't the only way to fight.
Let's bide our time and wait for the right moment to strike.
Damn it!
86th Annual Kamo Girls' Oraga Arts Festival
We've done nothing but odd jobs...
Nothing wrong with odd jobs.
It's the duty of the Sweats Club
to have fun while completing the tasks with which we're charged!
Madoka,
you really don't mind about Midori?
What brought that up?
No point stressing out about it.
After all, she's been locked away.
That chairman isn't the type to change her mind.
You know that best, right, Lan?
Woof...
Say, can you pass me that green paint?
The Rokumonsen Of Death
Pardon me!
Together—!
I don't understand this at all.
And so, we have here...
What's that supposed to mean?!
Which is that at the time...
Everything's so boring.
of the crime, the town was...
Is this some kind of ceremony?
We are terribly sorry.
We were not aware that you had business with Sir Sasaki.
Don't mention it.
May I ask how you know Sir Sasaki?
We faced each other once.
However,
we were evenly matched, and so we called it a draw.
So boring.
I am here in all seriousness,
to challenge him to a duel.
Should I do it?
We're back!
Huh?
Where's Izo?
Is this...?
I will take your life!
He didn't say anything about going after the pilot.
Excuse me, please.
There we go.
Want one?
Uh, sure...
The train will be arriving at Platform One shortly.
Hurry!
We're gonna miss the next train!
It just keeps spitting it back out!
Array, how did you get through so quickly?
I used this!
The Chairman gave it to me.
The Foundation is covering all our expenses.
Couldn't you have bought me a ticket as well?
Sorry...
It's for my use only.
So why didn't you use it to buy yourself some clothes?
And so my grandson up and tells me...
"Grandma, you're wrong."
Can you imagine? Being lectured at by my own grandson, at my age!
How about another tangerine?
Thank you.
And so my grandson tells me
that he's bringing home his girlfriend next time.
If only I had my Ovid,
I got so nervous, as if it was happening to me!
I wouldn't have to put up with this.
Ouch.
Madoka's been a while.
It's probably taking longer than expected for her to get the supplies.
She doesn't show it,
but she's definitely feeling unhappy about Midori being locked away.
You're right.
The bond between the Vox and its pilot is very strong.
Ouch...
I wonder if it's like being separated from a friend?
A close friend at that.
Ouch.
What are you doing?
Where is Izo?
He must be out looking for the Vox pilot.
Where is Kyono Madoka?
Please, let me go.
Where the hell is she?
Kamo Hurls...
Kamo Hurls, you said?
All right.
Madoka's house is straight down this street...
The smell of the ocean breeze
is the same here as in De Metrio.
Welcome.
One fish sandwich, please.
Sure.
Huh?!
I'm coming!
That guy said "Kamo Hurls" and sent me on a wild goose chase.
What should we do?
Is this where I'm supposed to perform that ceremony?
Pardon me!
A pervert!
Thank you for the food.
It was delicious.
What's this supposed to be?
As you can see,
it's a Black Card.
Do we look like a shop that takes credit cards?
What?
You don't?
What can I do? I don't have any cash!
You can't dine and dash!
If you don't have money,
you'll have to work it off.
Thank you so much!
How can I ever repay you?
How about hurrying home and giving him a warm bath?
Thank you so much!
I'm glad he's safe.
Perfect!
Here.
Oh, thanks!
And you folded it, too!
Do you always wear a bathing suit?
Oh, I just happened to be wearing one today.
Say, haven't we met before?
No, I don't think so.
Your voice sounds so familiar.
Oh well, never mind.
I have to go shopping.
See you!
That's right...
I should have asked her where I could find Kyono Madoka.
Here you go.
I'm a guy, you know...
It doesn't matter.
We are terribly sorry!
Our students behaved very rudely towards you.
We didn't know you were here to see Madoka...
I'm sorry, but may I ask how you know Madoka?
I knew it. It's that ceremony.
Well...
It's...
We faced each other and found we were evenly matched...
Did you hear that?
They faced each other,
and found themselves to be a perfect match!
Ahem...
Now then, Miss Igarashi...
Yes, Captain?
We must get more details!
You girls...
Our Madoka Radar...
...just picked up an interesting signal!
I don't quite get what's going on,
but it looks like the ceremony is proceeding normally.
So that's the kind of relationship you have?
Yes, I'm here in all seriousness...
How did the rest go?
You're serious about her?
Yes.
I'm rooting for you!
So where is Kyono Madoka right now?
Madoka is at the Sweats Club...
What?
Who is this Sven Skaub?
Is it a man? A woman?!
Oh my gosh, is he for real?
Madoka's boyfriend is hilarious!
Sweats are...
What are "sweats"?
They're clothes, like what you're wearing!
Clothes?
And Skaub?
Who are you calling a scrub?
He didn't say that.
It's actually a club,
as in club activities you do, while wearing those sweats.
I don't understand what you're saying.
We don't really understand what we're saying either.
It all started when Madoka's mother...
drowned in the ocean.
Imagine, drowning while trying to save someone else...
Madoka was devastated after the loss of her mother.
That's when Miss Yoko...
Doesn't this taste good?
Uh-huh!
Want some, Madoka?
Cheer up.
That's right.
Madoka, wait!
It was after that, wasn't it?
That was when Madoka went back to her old self, and became even more outgoing.
She even started imitating Miss Yoko by wearing her sweats at all times.
Not to mention Ms. Machiko.
That's right!
Ms. Machiko worked together with Miss Yoko.
I remember now!
Although she kept insisting that she was just helping out.
The Sweats Club is all about helping out, so I wonder what was up with that.
Wait!
I said wait!
Now I got—
That's Madoka, the one you're looking for.
You shouldn't climb up so high that you can't get back down.
Madoka!
Your boyfriend's here!
Boyfriend?
Whose boyfriend?
Yours, of course!
Huh?
Did I have a boyfriend?
Where is he?
He was just here.
Maybe he got shy.
My sweats!
Thank you.
Here's your paycheck.
I deducted the cost of your meal already.
Did you find Izo?
What about me?
Where were you?
What's it to you?
You didn't try to do anything to Kyono Madoka, did you?
I lost interest, that's all.
What the hell are you doing?!
I must attend a ceremony,
so please pardon my appearance.
I need to inform you.
With regards to the Vox Retrieval Force that was dispatched,
they will be arriving a little later than planned.
Did something happen?
Nothing to be concerned about.
Our field commander fell for the enemy's diversion,
and has been forced to take a detour.
Then I'm to assume Kiss will be arriving here,
ahead of the Vox Retrieval Force?
I must attend the ceremony for the conquest of Sensimiria.
So, they finally fell.
It doesn't mean we won against De Metrio.
I wish you luck.
You should have just stayed quiet, back in the sanctuary of U-Go...
Villagiulio.
Oh, man.
Hey, you're late.
What are you doing?
Playing a game.
That's not what he's asking about.
It's just a game played by the people of this planet, but it's fun.
The main retrieval force from Le Garite is coming.
We'll destroy the Vox before that happens.
You're going to fight them?
That's right.
The Chairman has no intention of handing over the Vox to Le Garite.
Can you be sure of that?
Yes.
She doesn't intend to give it to us either.
Yeah, but...
And no matter how much of a fight the guys on this planet put up,
Dizelmine won't give a damn.
He will take it back without fail.
Just what do you want from us?
Nothing.
I just don't want you guys to do anything that could screw this up.
But from now on, what you do is up to you.
You can come with me,
or you can go.
It's all up to you.
I...
will destroy the Vox.
I'll never forget that the soul in my chest would never yield
Don't cry
Promise me, okay
Promise me you'll never cry alone
We will always be together, you know
If we do get sad, we will share our sadness
and be stronger through it
Yay yay yay!
I'll laugh soon, my friend
My friend!
This isn't for just anyone, you're special
I am sure of my own emotions
With an upright voice, I say
Hello!
Sing the song that you always sing
and put a little bit of courage into my heart
Yay
The sound of Geta shoes echoes through the dark night.
Click-clack...
The muted cry of a woman sobbing...
Behind the paper screen,
an ominous shadow creeps toward you.
And then...
Was that how the next episode is supposed to go?
Goodbye, Kamogawa