You just can't stand to be on your own!
Who isn't alone in this society?
There's no place for communities in this world
where everyone is watched over by the system and lives within the system's standards.
Everyone stays in their own little cell,
and the system tames them by giving them each their own personal serenity.
You're the same too, right, Kougami Shinya?
No one accepted your justice.
No one understood your anger, either.
So you turned your back on trust and friendships,
and you even abandoned the only place you could belong to in order to come this far.
And yet you laugh at my solitude?
But, you know, I highly value one who doesn't fear solitude—
you, who turned your solitude into a weapon.
#22: Perfect World
I would like to show
Cut open my skull
Look into my head
I don't know why I'm so harsh
I can't be so brash
I'm going to crash
'Cause I feel
I can always show my everything to you
If this moment was for me
I try to hear, lend my ear
Voices inside, one link to join it all
Again
'Cause I feel
I can always show my everything to you
If this moment was for me
I try to hear, lend my ear
Voices inside, one link to join it all
So it goes
Again
You never learn, do you, Kougami?
Hold it right there,
Kougami.
Please don't move.
Makishima is nearby.
Yes, I know. I'll apprehend him too.
Are you going to handcuff me here and go after him all by yourself?
I'm not that reckless.
This is locked in Paralyzer mode with the safety off.
You should be able to use it too.
Please help me catch him.
We'll use the Paralyzer on Makishima. Nothing more.
If you try anything beyond that, I'll shoot you in the leg.
I'm surprised.
Well, I'm not surprised to see you toughen up.
But you could stand to be a bit nicer about it.
Why are you so focused on making sure nobody kills Makishima?
Because it's illegal.
Because I can't overlook a crime.
Why are you going that far to obey the law
when that law can neither judge a criminal nor protect people?
The law doesn't protect people.
People protect the law.
People have always detested evil and sought out a righteous way of living.
The law is the accumulation of those people's feelings.
They're neither the provisions nor the system.
They're the fragile and irreplaceable feelings that everyone carries in their hearts.
Compared to the power of anger and hatred,
they are something that can quite easily break down.
All throughout time, people have prayed for a better world.
In order for those prayers to continue to hold meaning,
we have to try our best to protect it to the very end.
We can't just give up on it.
If there ever comes a time when everyone feels that way,
the Sibyl System will probably disappear.
There'll no longer be any latent criminals or Enforcers.
But...
Tsk!
Akane!
I wish...
you guys would stop insulting us...
already.
I see...
You are...
N-No...
This is between the two of us.
Kougami!
Everyone is alone.
Everyone is empty.
People no longer have any need of others.
You can always find a substitute for any talent.
Any relationship can be replaced.
That's the world I grew tired of.
And yet, for some reason...
I can't even imagine someone else besides you killing me.
Say, what do you think, Kougami?
After all this is done, will you be able to find a replacement for me?
Sorry, but I hope I never do.
This destiny must have awaited them since long before they had even met.
They were not like mere ships passing in the night.
It was not like they didn't understand each other.
They understood each other better than anyone else,
and each was focused solely on the other.
Kougami...
The outcome of the attempt to capture
Makishima Shougo was quite regrettable.
Does that mean I'm no longer needed?
We have no choice but to downgrade our assessment of your abilities.
However, that does not mean that you possess a negative net worth.
Rather, you are still an individual of outstanding value with regards to managing the Sibyl System.
What do you mean?
You have a healthy, strong Psycho-Pass,
as well as a clear mind and judgment.
We can say that your qualities are as close to ideal as they come
for serving as an example to the citizens of the coming new era.
Furthermore, you hold an emotional antipathy that is completely contrary to your theoretical assessment of the Sibyl System,
and that conflict continues to exist.
If we can establish a means of winning you over to our side,
we will be able to obtain valuable sample data for taking the governance of society to the next level.
What are you up to?
The true form of the Sibyl System is currently kept secret out of consideration for public opinion.
However, such obfuscation is nothing but a simple, short-term strategy.
In the long term, this course of action is not desirable.
We should eventually make the truth public.
If we can create an environment where every citizen still enjoys and accepts our governance
after they are made aware of our true form,
such an achievement will solidify the stability
and prosperity of the future human society.
Continuing to observe and analyze your movements
will provide us with valuable hints on how to build a methodology
for winning over the citizens in the future and getting them to adapt.
You think it'll all go as smoothly as that?
As long as you refrain from jeopardizing the secrecy of this information,
your life and your freedom of action will be guaranteed.
We hope you will cooperate with us.
If you wish to follow your own drive for
self-preservation, there is only one choice.
You're right. I don't want to die in vain,
and it's true that the current society cannot hold without Sibyl.
We feel that we can trust in your respect for the law when you make decisions.
Do you know the most demeaning thing you can do to the law that we should respect?
Creating and administering a law that is unworthy of protection.
You shouldn't underestimate humans.
We're always aiming for a better society.
One day, someone will come to this room to turn off the power.
We will find a new path. You can count on it.
There is no place for the Sibyl System in our future!
Akane Tsunemori...
Fight.
Struggle.
So that it may lead us to evolve.
2 months later
Hey, it's been a while.
I came to talk to you today,
since I've decided what I'm going to do next.
My Crime Coefficient went up to 140.
There's no longer any chance of recovery.
But it's not in my nature to sit around and mope in an isolation facility.
So I decided to go back to where I used to work.
You told me to take a different path.
Guess I didn't live up to your expectations.
I ended up being a terrible son in every way, didn't I?
But strangely enough, I don't have any regrets.
There's nothing good about being a detective.
But it's a job that someone needs to do.
Right... Dad?
Sorry to drag you out here.
That's okay. It's my duty to accompany Enforcers when they go outside.
Unlike Kagari, at least my dad was able to get a proper grave.
Division 2 was told to give up their investigation on him, right?
Yeah.
I don't think Kagari is alive.
I'm sure the top brass found evidence of that,
but they're trying to sweep it under the rug and keep it from the public.
I wonder where Kougami is.
When the collar comes off such a wild hunting dog,
he becomes no different from a wolf.
Now that he's back in the wild,
maybe he's living a comparatively free and easygoing life.
Would his life really be all that relaxing?
It's not like he took it easy as an Enforcer, right?
He was a perseverant, cunning man who didn't know when to give up.
No matter how bad the situation, he'll always pull through.
If anything, I'm more concerned about you, Inspector Tsunemori.
What? Me?
You're ever the worrier, Ginoza.
Let's look at the future, rather than the past.
A new Inspector will be assigned tomorrow, right?
It's unusual to hire a minor, isn't it?
We're partially responsible for that.
By the way, it's not important, but do you mind if I ask you something?
What is it?
Were your glasses just for show?
What?
I don't like how my face looks, especially my eyes.
But I don't care about that anymore, so it didn't seem to matter.
The face of Division 1 sure has changed, hasn't it?
Shu, Masa, Shinya...
They're all gone.
It means that old-fashioned guys aren't suited for this job.
Isn't calling them old-fashioned a bit harsh?
Why don't you call them romantics?
Do you think they might take comfort in that?
This is the Criminal Investigation Department, part of the Public Safety Bureau.
Access to this block is currently restricted to ensure safety.
Excuse me!
Are you Inspector Tsunemori?
Yes.
You've got rotten luck, having to deal with an incident right after getting posted.
I'm Shimotsuki Mika. I've been assigned to the CID as of today.
Pleased to meet you!
Sorry, but the CID is very short on manpower.
I'll do what I can to help, but you'll have to hit the ground running.
I'm aware of that.
I'm looking forward to the work.
That's what I like to hear.
That's...
The guys you're about to meet are humans just like us,
but they'll deal with crimes using criteria for judgment different from yours.
Their actions sometimes may be beyond your comprehension.
Trust them, but at the same time, be cautious of them.
If you underestimate them, you'll get seriously hurt.
They're what we call "Enforcers."
They'll be your subordinates.
Dominator Portable Psychological Diagnosis and Suppression System
has been activated.
There's no way I could love anyone,
but I wish to be loved by someone in turn
The world may not have
ended yesterday after all,
but we will not budge
from where we are
God, in favor of which parts have you left us?
I receive no reply
I never do
Are you still here?
You'll never walk alone
I walk with you
I will share all your sins
Together with you
I walk
a trackless path
Swann's
Way
The chain of justice—
the system— never ends...