Any word from Kyono and the others?
No, nothing yet.
Those girls...
Don't they know the position they're in?!
Regardless of what we say,
the Le Garite ship is out of our jurisdiction.
All we can do is pray for their safe return.
The chips they serve here for the princess are amazing. Even the salt on them tastes different!
"Good morning, chatty little bird!"
"And to you the honey bee, showing off energy without peer!"
"I have arrived, so please give him word."
"Tell the prince who has searched for me that I am now here."
"A very sweet maple syrup pie is—"
I thought I hid all my poetry journals.
Hey, I can't see!
Move, Miss Maple Syrup Pie.
Come on!
You didn't come on board just to ransack my room, did you?!
We're just waiting for you to get him to open that door.
Huh?
Your brother's the only one who can open it, right?
Right...
If Miss Yurikano's on board, isn't that the only place she could be?
Yes...
In that case...
You're scared, aren't you?
Scared?
You mean about the whole asylum thing?
It's not just that...
Did he really not tell you?
About Miss Yurikano being on this ship?
I didn't even know she was alive.
Ladies, if you would come with me please?
Back then we tried to fly with propellers that couldn't do it
We ran with bare feet, and now we see different skies
We always live
full of conviction
that we are misunderstood
You're precious to me
but lost at the same time
I'll get over it
Spin the wheel of fate
Inside the dew, like magic,
are tears and sunny days
I feel lonely now
I'm sure my dream will come true
and we will be together forever
Oh wow, what's all this?!
My brother did this?
Orbiting Above the Summer Skies of Kamogawa
I've been wanting to thank you two for quite some time.
Miss Madoka, in spite of being unaccustomed to aliens,
you accepted my younger sister warmly.
And Miss Muginami, you have put aside the differences
between our two nations to befriend her.
I would like to express my deepest gratitude today.
Thank you.
Brother...
But enough with the boring formalities.
Laffinty really did that?
Yes.
I told her she should put on undergarments,
but next thing you know, it started pouring.
Her blouse clung to her, and you could totally see everything.
Hey, this might be our chance—
Lan looked sexier than if she'd been naked!
Ask him.
When it comes to wearing wet clothes,
Lan would be the champion!
Fine...
Wasn't she, Madoka?!
Excuse me...
But can we see Miss Yurikano?
We came on board because we had some questions for her.
Questions?
Actually, we have some for you too.
What might that be?
Why did you keep Miss Yurikano a secret from Lan?
Madoka!
The incident on Militia Zodia brought us a second tragedy.
Yurikano was rescued from that destruction,
but as a completely different person.
She had no memories of me, Laffinty,
or even of her real brother, Villagiulio.
I didn't want you to see her in that state.
I felt I should wait until the Yurikano we once knew resurfaced.
But if being overprotective has hurt you,
I'm sorry, Laffinty.
Brother...
Yurikano is resting right now.
I'd appreciate it if you could wait to see her some other time.
Maybe the reason behind your brothers not getting along
has more to do with Giuvi's personality.
That's not true!
You think so?
But Lan's brother is just so different that what I was expecting.
Huh?
He's so gentlemanly and kindhearted...
The exact opposite of Giuvi.
That doesn't mean it's all his fault!
But you don't deny that they're polar opposites.
So what're we gonna do now?
He wants us to wait and see Miss Yurikano some other time.
But that means we can see her eventually.
Let's wait in Lan's room until she's well enough to see us.
We might even find more fun stuff in there.
Muginami, what about you?
Did meeting my brother change your impression of him?
I'm sorry, Lan.
Oh, Madoka!
What do you want to wear to bed? Pajamas or a nightgown?
Huh?
Madoka?
Umm...
Where am I, exactly?
I'm sorry. I didn't know this was your private garden.
Don't worry about it.
I had this place made to the exact specifications of the royal garden on my home planet.
We played here a lot when we were little.
Myself, Laffinty, Villagiulio...
And Yurikano.
Do you think
you could be friends again, like you were back then?
With Giuvi?
I still consider him my one and only best friend.
Then why?!
However,
the people of Polyhedron are my family, and I must protect them.
"Life is a miracle in and of itself."
Eons ago, when the first tragedy befell Earth,
our ancestors barely managed to escape and survive.
Their indomitable will has been
passed down to us in the present day.
But, there are many who take that for granted.
One of whom is Villagiulio.
If it means saving many of these miracles,
then I'm willing to make whatever sacrifices are necessary.
Do I seem that stubborn to you?
Huh?
Well, uh...
I'll take you to Yurikano.
Guerilla attack or not...
I can't let you go alone!
I keep telling you, this war is between the two of us!
That doesn't mean he sees it that way.
Oh, he will.
It's the only explanation I have
for why he would use such a cheap trick.
They've just informed me that she's all set to speak with you.
But I really wanted to see Miss Yurikano alone...
Come in.
Huh? Uh...
What's the matter? Don't be shy.
What is this place?
Lady Yurikano is over here.
We've been waiting for you.
Welcome, Miss Madoka.
You looked like a cute little doll when you were little, Lan.
How many times have I told you
not to go through my things?!
I can't wait for the day when my brother is able
to be with Yurikano like they used to be...
She couldn't replace you, Muginami.
She wasn't as much of a bitch.
I hope that some day soon,
you can all smile together like this again.
When that day comes, we'll take another picture together.
And this time, you and Madoka will be in it.
Madoka's been gone a while, huh?
I told my attendants to bring her here when they find her.
Maybe your brother caught her.
You don't actually think—
Wait!
What is all this?
Unfortunately, by the time we rescued Yurikano
from the Tragedy of Militia Zodia,
the majority of her memories and consciousness was left behind on the other side of Rinne.
Rinne...
Don't worry.
All you have to do is accept it.
Right...
I never expected her to come here.
Looks like some good will come of Yurikano going to Pharos after all.
We just need to embed Kyono Madoka's mind into Yurikano's empty shell.
Then we can destroy De Metrio even without the use of Vox Aura.
We won't have to extinguish
the hundred billion miracles that light up Polyhedron.
However, Miss Madoka will never be able to extract herself
from Lady Yurikano's body.
And I must shoulder her hatred,
along with those of De Metrio.
Miss Kyono is with His Majesty in the Deep Level Experiment Division.
Princess, I cannot allow anyone to interfere, even you.
I see, that's good.
Then restrain Muginami immediately.
Lan?!
Are you sure, Milady?
If Madoka is already in our hands,
I no longer need to pretend I'm protecting this woman.
Lan, were you planning this the whole time?!
Lan?!
Please!
Let me talk to Madoka!
Quiet down!
How could you, Lan?!
Lan!
Princess, you've finally come to understand His Majesty's anguish.
I've caused Brother and everyone in the fleet unnecessary grief.
Allow me to express my deepest appreciation
and words of encouragement to everyone here.
Your kind consideration touches us deeply.
Space Field Barriers 6 through 4230, sealed.
Sighting light-time stable.
Preparatory rotation of USHV Ring complete.
Connection in three, two...
Now connecting.
She'll be on her way soon.
Will I be able to see my friends again?
Why do you ask?
I just had this feeling...
Trust me.
All right, then...
Give my regards to Yurikano.
Sure thing!
To the valiant crew aboard
the Galaxy Expeditionary Force Flagship, "Vishwak,"
and to the troops who served aboard the other ships of our fleet
with fearless courage through thick and thin...
I,
Fin E Ld Si Laffinty, Princess of Le Garite,
take this opportunity to respectfully offer my sincerest appreciation.
To our flagship's junior and  senior officers
who have led our fleet, and our troops on the path to invincibility,
I offer my heartfelt gratitude and future glory...
And to our enlisted troops,
with your exemplary combat and battle skills...
Let me talk to Madoka!
Quiet down!
I offer my heartfelt gratitude and future glory.
Synchronous waveform stable, convergence completed.
Mental Detachment has been initiated.
So far, so good.
And to Hana, the stray cat down on Third Street
that comforted me in my darkest hour...
Hana?
I offer many thanks and future glory.
And...
Oh, right!
To Mr. Hiroshi from BWH,
who removed the carrots I loathed from my plate without anyone knowing,
I offer many thanks and future glory!
Also..
Um...
We should head back now.
And... Lest I forget...
The casual sprinkle of diced green peppers...
The not-too-thick, not-too-thin homemade salami with the best taste in the galaxy.
Mr. Hiroshi's special BWH pizza!
Come to think of it...
The day before yesterday, I had the strangest dream
that my left and right nostrils had switched places!
Nice, Lan! Hang in there!
Now that I think about it, it was so unrecognizable that I'm surprised I even noticed it!
Six, seven...
Bisgarbo count exceeding point eight!
I never expected her to go this far.
Incredible! This girl is truly incredible!
And, there's um...
Tweet, tweet, tweet, little early bird birdy.
Tweet, tweet, tweet, listen to it sing.
Good morning my beloved prince. Tweet, tweet, tweet.
Condition stable.
She's past the limit!
If all goes well, Lady Yurikano and Kyono Madoka will become one.
After connecting the nerve cutter to the consciousness strata,
the ego barrier will be automatically excised.
Set start-up to engage at the count of seventeen.
Auto start-up and all termination directives will be ignored.
This is it. This is how it should be.
Goodbye, Brother...
Dizel...
Why would you do that?
As long as I disappear off into the Rinne and close off its entrance,
it will prevent my brother and Dizel from fighting.
It was the only thing I could do.
In order to ensure peace to the Polyhedron for the coming millennium,
Dizel attempted to use my power to wipe out De Metrio.
Lan's brother tried to do such a terrible thing?
It's easy to blame Dizel.
But the real evil is me, who possessed such malevolent power.
Don't say that!
And if I'm to stop a king from fighting to save his people,
then it's my responsibility as a princess
to fulfill that mission in his stead.
Thank you for coming to see me.
Do those two know about this?
That you're shouldering the entire burden alone?
It doesn't matter.
This is the decision I made on my own.
But it wasn't something you really wanted to do, was it?
We should go tell them.
That way, they might change their minds.
I'm fine with how things are.
No, it's not fine!
Hello! Lan's brother?!
Moid!
Bring me and Miss Yurikano back to the real world right now!
Stop it!
Why?! The two of them haven't stopped fighting yet!
I said I'm fine, so get over it!
Guess I have no choice.
You're going to tell them whether I have to force you or not!
I said I don't want to.
There are some things I don't want to tell them!
Now I'm all fired up.
All right, no matter what...
No matter what!
I'll make you tell them!
I'll never tell them!
Madoka!
I'd like to close with these words:
I, Princess Laffinty, fervently hope that our nation and De Metrio
will move forward into the next millennium hand in hand.
You pulled a fast one on us, didn't you, Princess?
I only did what I believed was right as princess.
Something seems to be wrong with Dizelmine's ship!
Its exterior is distorting!
What's happening?
Miss Yurikano?
Madoka, what're you waiting for?!
We have to run!
Where am I?
Cap! Aura and the other Vox, they're...
Catapult deck opening!
We can't override their T.O. sequences!
Opening the top hatch!
Vox Ignis is on deck!
Shuttle locks for both Lympha and Aura are complete!
All units are taking off!
On the water's surface I see a light reflected that stirs my heart
When we realized our bond,
we were already deeply connected under the blue sky
We had so much fun, as in a daze, that time seemed forgotten
I prayed that there would be no end to the way we lived
I won't forget our days together, although time goes by,
and you are far from me now,
because you left behind a wonderful world
for me to wait in
Oh, no! I've switched bodies with Yurikano!
Take it easy, Madoka.
Why don't you bump your heads together?
It might reverse the process!
That's right! Just like the movies. Okay, here goes, Muginami!
Why me?!
Oh, good point. Then, Lan!
I'm not the one either!
Then who am I supposed to bump heads with?!
May This Voice Reach Kamogawa
With Yurikano!