A celestial nymph?
Uh, hi...
Who are you?
This sacred mountain is forbidden to women.
Who permitted you to set foot here?!
Forbidden to women?
Maybe that's why he looks so angry.
I-I'm so sorry. I wasn't my intention...
I'll leave now!
Stop!
Are you the one who made
these cherry blossoms bloom?
Why did you come here?!
You're hurting me!
What is your name?!
Answer me, or I will break your arm!
I wonder what's happening on this world
I fly through the sky into space
and circle the world
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday
With my periodic biorhythm
I'm like a washing machine
Just kidding
Yes, I'm spinning around
Around, around the world
Because there's no limit to my love
Spinning around, around, around the world
I want to tell you that I love you, even if it confuses me
Bam, bam, bam
You're not paying attention
Sometimes love keeps being one-sided
It's gotten so hopelessly complex
But I'll make it all true with a miracle
Hey, God,
I'm your god
I think
Master Jirou!
Jirou?!
He's the creep who hurt Botanmaru?!
Stop...
Master Jirou, so this is where you were.
You should return to the hall soon.
What is the matter, sir?
I'm merely surprised that a woman's arm can be so frail.
The God Sneaks In
What's his problem?! That guy's got serious anger issues!
Do you really think Brother Jirou becoming the Fourth will make everything better on the mountain?
There's no way!
That was a long bathroom break.
Where in the world did you go loitering about?
Tomoe!
What is wrong?
You are trembling!
What happened?
Trembling?
I am?
I'm so glad my legs didn't give way.
You met Jirou?
And you didn't suffer any injuries, did you?
Uh, actually, I'm the one who met him.
All he did was grab me by the arm,
but I guess this mountain is forbidden to women.
I had no idea and walked all over the place.
Thank goodness that nothing serious happened.
I'm over here!
I must say, I had heard tales of his violence,
but I never expected him to be such a brute.
Raising a fist in anger has always been his
first response. Truly, I should've known that.
I'll have a different restroom readied right away.
Grr
Suirou! Why won't you look at me?!
You must pardon me for that.
I've lived here for so long.
I'm not accustomed to interacting with women.
Especially beautiful maidens, such as yourself.
Beautiful, even
with a race paddle
Somehow, coming from this guy,
that doesn't feel like a compliment at all.
Beautiful, even
with a race paddle
That's why you didn't let me use your bathroom?!
I thought a woman should have the use of a clean flush toilet.
The one here is a pit latrine, so...
Great dinner topic.
But enough of that, Brother Suirou.
How about we talk about the
problems the mountain's facing?
Oh-ho! You even ate all your
pickled vegetables, Shinjurou.
So you can even eat vinegar pickles now.
Oh, these pickled vegetables are delicious!
That's when I was a kid.
Forget that. I'm talking about my sire's illness.
This is a miracle cure that Nanami
got from the medicine god in Izumo.
Peach Pills.
These might be able to cure even my sire's illness.
Have him take a few of these.
Once he's well, the mountain will go back to the way it was too.
Then Brother Jirou's succession won't happen either.
If they are what you claim, I do not doubt their potency, even against an illness as grave as the master's.
But you won't be able to deliver these to him.
He collapsed about two months ago.
Ever since then, he's been hidden away in some sanctum of the compound.
As Master of the Hall, Jirou handles the official duties, and security on the compound is tight.
No outsiders are permitted within.
Due to my banishment, that includes me as well.
We could entrust the medicine to an insider, but it's unlikely to reach its intended mark.
Jirou would be quick to stop such an operation.
He would do something like that.
Well, don't brood about it too much, Shinjurou.
Things have a way of working themselves out.
Have some apples or something.
Then you're fine with things staying like this?!
I'll go settle things with Brother Jirou!
I'll get him to let me see my sire in person!
No, that's dangerous.
I can't allow you to do that.
Brother Suirou!
I'm not a little kid anymore.
I came here because I thought
there was something I could do.
I'm not who I used to be.
Kurama...
No, this is still too much for you.
Why...
Shinjurou!
It's so good of you to return to Kurama!
Ah! How fine you've grown!
Uh... Who're you again?
It's me!
Oh...
I informed him of your return.
Shinjurou!
Shinjurou has return to succeed as the Fourth!
Is that not right, Shinjurou?!
Uh...
Hold on. Who said anything about that?
The master grows old.
Even if he pulls through this time, the future remains uncertain.
The question of a successor cannot be avoided.
Shinjurou, this is all for the sake of the mountain.
Surely, you wouldn't say no?
No.
I don't want to be the Fourth.
You returned because you were prepared to do so, didn't you?
Yes, that's right!
Clap
I think that's enough, Great Brothers.
Shinjurou hasn't been home in a long time, and he's still tired.
Leave the complicated matters for later.
Right...
Agreed.
Shinjurou, you should not let
their words weigh on your mind.
Shinjurou?
Sorry, Brother Suirou.
I'm going to go cool my head a little.
Do you think Kurama's okay?
I imagine he does not wish to succeed as the Fourth.
It's hardly surprising.
He's lived in the mundane world for seventeen years now.
Lady Land God, I'll take a small share of these Peach Pills for the master,
but I must ask you two to go with Shinjurou and descend the mountain early tomorrow morning.
You need not become involved in our affairs.
We're already involved.
We came to support Kura— to support Shinjurou.
We're not leaving until he says so.
When I was reunited with Shinjurou at the main gate,
imagine my surprise to see that he brought a woman.
I realized then that he was no longer the child I once knew.
He has grown so much while away from this mountain.
He's surely left behind an entire life in the mundane world that he can't abandon.
That is why expecting him to become part of the mountain is not fair.
Tell me, Lady Land God. Do you truly know Shinjurou?
What?
He has always faced his challenges alone.
Even if they overwhelm him,
he'll recklessly push himself, for he
can never exploit another's kindness.
I've been with him ever since he was little,
and he's never even come to me for help.
That's why the least I could do was to watch over him always, to save him from the heavy burdens.
Please take him home for me, before he
takes on the burden of becoming the Fourth.
You could never pull it off.
If you do not even know that someone is behind you until they speak,
forget about sneaking into that compound by yourself.
I was just thinking that myself.
Even from all the way out here,
the great hall feels domineering.
They've doubled their triple-layer barriers. Talk about overkill.
Let me guess. Brother Suirou wants you to take me home, right?
Perhaps.
For all my big talk, the truth is,
I wasn't prepared for any of this.
And Brother Suirou saw right through me.
It's so lame I could die.
So what is it that you wish to do?
Kurama!
Well? Come on! What's our plan?
I want to sneak into the compound and give my old man the medicine.
Would you... maybe help me do that?
Huh? Would I what?
I couldn't hear over the wind. One more time.
What?!
Shut up! I didn't say anything!
Hey, Tomoe, what did he say?
What did he say?
He asked for our help.
What the heck? Of course we'll help you!
Next part coming
right up
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Brother! Brother! Just one more chance!
Sorry, Fumimaru.
We can't have any feeble crows at the hall.
That's Master Jirou's policy.
Live outside or descend the mountain and make your life there.
First, it was Brother Usa, and now, even Brother Fumi...
He was a kind brother too.
Don't cry, Chiyomaru.
If they catch you crying, they'll throw you out too.
Once we grow up, we'll be culled mercilessly too.
It wasn't like this when the Third was well.
Once I turn eight, I'll be banished for sure too!
It'll be okay, Brother.
The Third will regain his health in no time.
That's what the celestial nymph sister said, so it'll be okay.
Our sister!
She made the eternal cherry blossom tree bloom!
So pretty. And warm.
Remembering her soothes my soul.
It makes me feel warmer.
Master Jirou.
I hear that you lost another crow.
This place has become awfully lonely, hasn't it?
Those without strength and those
weak of spirit are not needed here.
Only the strongest shall live here.
Never mind that. There should be a barrier cast upon this sanctum.
Where did you weasel your way in?
Oh yeah, there were barriers, huh?
But they were full of holes.
What happened? That is so unlike you.
A barrier in disarray is a heart and mind in disarray.
Perhaps your heart and mind are in a bit of disarray, Master Jirou.
Ah! A superbly laid barrier!
I would expect no less of you, Master Jirou!
You dare say my heart and mind are in disarray?!
I would never! That would be absurd!
Of course it is!
Toss
Begone.
My spirit is as strong as steel, and nothing can shake it.
Curse that crafty woman!
What could her name be?
The same room?
It is what it is.
You told him you were my familiar,
so Suirou went out of his way to be thoughtful.
Don't be a spoiled brat about it, okay?
Put yourself in my shoes.
I can't even get changed whenever I want to.
This is a pain for me too.
Good grief, talk about a brush with danger.
Who are you calling dangerous?! You're the dangerous one!
I'm wearing tons of layers so you can't jump me like last time!
You do that.
You are not a tidy sleeper,
and your hem often gets turned up.
What the hell were you looking at, you pervy fox?!
It is not as if I was trying to look.
All that matters to me is that
you remain where I can see you.
What?
So rest easy.
Though your clothes may be in disarray,
my heart and mind will remain unperturbed.
You are such a nasty fox!
Using the screen
as a shield
You guys awake?
Using the screen
as a shield
I got a map of the compound from Brother Suirou.
Tomorrow's the day we're sneaking in.
Ooh!
A powerful barrier surrounds the facility.
We don't stand a chance of getting in unless we're invited as guests.
There's likely to be even more
layers of barriers set up inside.
The caster is Brother Jirou, the Master of the Hall.
Once we're inside, we'll split up.
One group will get Brother Jirou drunk with this medicinal liquor, while the other group finds my sire.
Surely, it would be faster to simply do away with Jirou.
No!
I don't want to injure anyone in the compound.
And there lies the problem: how do we get Brother Jirou's side to invite us?
E-Excuse me, Master Shinjurou.
What the heck? You were still around, Botanmaru?
I-I...
Please allow me to help out as well!
Botanmaru...
No. You stay here with Brother Suirou.
If something goes wrong, there's no guarantee that I can keep you safe.
But if we're splitting into two groups, it'd be better to have more people.
Right, and as for who deals with Jirou and who searches for my sire...
Naturally, I will go with Nanami and search for Soujoubou.
I am her familiar.
You keep this Jirou fellow busy by yourself.
By myself?!
Now hold on a second.
Let's be more flexible in our thinking here, fox.
Jirou knows what Nanami looks like.
M-Master Shinjurou, please allow me to accompany you!
I said no, didn't I?!
Hang in there, Botanmaru!
You stinking fox!
A crow should deal with the crow!
Nanami is a fool, so she is useless if I am not by her side.
How dare you badmouth me so casually?!
I don't need you to come with me!
I'll...
look for Soujoubou with Botanmaru.
You two can keep Jirou distracted, okay?
You've gotta be joking!
Not at all!
I just had a great idea!
The perfect way to get Jirou to invite us in!
Nanami, that fool...
I was wondering what she would say, and... How is that a great plan?!
She never says anything good
when she has that grin on her face.
There she goes again.
Snug
This chit of a girl...
What about her did I fall for?
Potty...
Gotta... potty...
That Nanami...
After she was trembling so hard earlier in the day...
I'll go with Botanmaru, so I'll leave the rest to you.
You better not take advantage of
the darkness and come molest me!
As if I would!
Dammit!
She should just quietly allow me to protect her.
Because that is the only thing I can do for her.
Hey! Your bed is over there!
All that matters to me is that
you remain where I can see you.
So rest easy.
My heart and mind...
They were supposed to remain unperturbed.
T-Tomoe! What are you doing in my bed?!
Your bed is over there.
P-Please excuse me!
That scared me so much!
But I have this feeling, like he was holding me in his arms...
Did I imagine that?
Or was it...
Such a dereliction of duty, fox.
You're my familiar, but you didn't even help me get ready, and you're only crawling out of bed now?
Kurama! You look like a god! An evil one!
Well, yeah.
The crow who left the village returns as a land god?
We've got to put on a show if we're going to get them to buy such a preposterous story.
Even the surrogate leader Jirou can't ignore
an exiled brother who's ascended to godhood.
Let's make him welcome us
as supremely honored guests.
Onward! To the Kurama Main Hall!
But before we go, mind if I test to see if my land god powers really work, fox?
Try it. If you do not value your life.
All right! Act like a cat, spin three times in place, and meow for me!
Meow!
Nanami's proxy talisman is seriously awesome!
So this is what they call Sacred Word Binding!
Kurama, stick the talisman inside your clothes where it belongs.
No joking around. Pull it together, guys.
You are the one who is joking around. What are you wearing?
It's not like I had a choice!
Suirou said to hide that I'm a girl.
It's because of your unsolicited idea that I must now suffer the crow's...
Never mind that, Tomoe.
About yesterday...
It was dark, and I was half-asleep, so I might be wrong,
but were you holding me in your arms while I was sleeping next to you last night?
Could it be that you think of me as...
Sorry.
I was half-asleep as well.
And I mistook you for Tanuko from the tea house.
I just happened to be dreaming of enjoying myself at a tea house.
But thanks to you lacking any
breasts worth fondling, I came to.
So it is not as if I laid hands on you because I wanted to.
Do not get the wrong idea, okay?
Okay.
Nailed it.
You're a pretty hilarious guy.
We should go too.
Brother!
A party claiming to be that of Shinjurou has come calling.
Shinjurou? We're expecting no such guest.
Do not open the gate! Turn them away!
B-But...
All you common folk, I appreciate the welcome.
I am Shinjurou, eldest son of Soujoubou the Third.
As land god of the Mikage Shrine, I have come to witness the Fourth's rite of succession.
Take me to Jirou.
What is the matter, you common crows?
My lord and master has a short temper.
If you do not wish to be reduced to ashes, barrier and all, get moving!
I have received a letter from Suirou.
If a god has come calling, we have no choice but to welcome him.
Make your way inside.
All right.
Now's our chance to search for the master.
Lead the way, Botanmaru.
Come on, let's go.
There are barriers all across the compound.
And somewhere in this vast compound...
is Soujoubou!
Hey, can you hear me?
That night, I was looking
at the fleeting remnants of the day
The milky way spread across my vision
It was very beautiful
Hey, can you hear me?
I don't think I can talk to other people about this
I'll call up God, I think
If a new day hadn't begun
then yesterday's tomorrow would be today
Preview
Kurama and Tomoe made in through the front.
and yesterday would be the day before
Alcohol and sexual wiles, ooh-la-la!
I'm waiting for you
Huh? They got caught.
I'll stay here
Meanwhile, Nanami and Botanmaru find Soujoubou, but...
The boat is stopped here
Huh? Something's not right.
Next time, "The God Is Blindsided."
The God Is Blindsided
They're so doomed!