I'm taking you off this case, Kougami.
The body was eroded by a special kind of chemical.
Analysis confirmed that the chemical used
was the same one used in the case three years ago.
So after three years, the mysterious killer returns, huh?
This man?
The picture's filename was...
"Makishima."
My head is full of things
that I can never tell anybody of
In this perfect world
I roam, a lost being
This world is impossibly hard on me
It's an illusion that plays out before my eyes
Can I find its faults?
Plastic, all is plastic
Nobody is allowed to be insane
You're made of plastic too, like this beautiful world
In this beautiful world
there is something
that obscures all light for me
My heart tries to break out
and finds no answer
Secret kills for you
The secret remains for you
Don't show me a dark future
nor a world of pretense
Keep our motion secret
#08: The Rest Is Silence
The security...
has gotten really tight, hasn't it?
Two students fell victim in short succession to crimes that had the same MO.
If the academy doesn't take action,
they'll have to answer to the parents.
In addition, the suspect is Touma Kouzaburo, a former teacher at this school.
That narrows the Public Safety Bureau's investigation
down to this school, Ousou Academy.
I guess I'm bound hand and foot for a while.
Why did you only choose students within this school for your works of art?
This academy is a girls' boarding school.
What do you think of their education policy, Mr. Makishima?
It's out of date,
but that also makes it rare and therefore valuable... I guess.
In this day and age, if parents want their daughters to receive an education in an old-style environment,
this is the only choice they have.
Chastity and grace...
Traditional virtues that have been lost.
They comprise the educational ideology of Ousou Academy.
They're priorities that are not valued in boys, only in girls.
After having them instilled in us,
we're shipped out as a brand-name product— "refined, sheltered maidens"—
and purchased by men who seek a classic piece of furniture called "a good wife and mother..."
for a formality known as marriage.
Students in this school are all components
that will be processed into a piece of artwork called the "lady."
They are rough stones waiting to be polished and set.
They live sad and boring lives,
even though there are many other possible ways they could bloom.
That's an interesting perspective.
So that's the foundation for your art, is it?
Once your new piece is ready,
where do you plan to exhibit it this time?
Let's see...
I wonder where would be good.
I have to find a lively place that attracts the attention of many.
No leads at all, huh?
And there's more bad news to come.
I heard there are two second-year students who disappeared from the dorms.
The school contacted their parents, but they're not at home either.
They've gone completely missing.
This is strange, any way you look at it.
The campus and dorms are all under the kind of lockdown you'd expect in a military facility.
Is it even possible for him to get his victims out of the place?
To start with,
why is he only targeting Ousou Academy students now?
To Touma, this school is his old nest, so to speak.
Maybe he knows a secret path that can bypass security.
That could be it.
This academy is what, a hundred years old?
The buildings on the premises have gone through numerous renovations,
so their blueprints look terrible, too.
Could it be possible that the murder site and the killer's hideout both lie on Academy grounds?
I knew it! You're reading about the case.
This is Karanomori's doing, isn't it?
What do you think? You've taken a look at the reports too, right?
What do I think? Well...
Based on the chemical analysis,
it seems to me that it's even more likely that this is the same culprit from three years ago.
I think it's exactly the opposite.
The opposite?
Yeah. In the case three years ago...
Take a look at this guy, for example.
One of the victims.
He was a Lower House member suspected of corruption.
He was also alleged to have submit falsified reports of his Crime Coefficient, but he refused to have it re-measured.
When the media and the opposition parties questioned him,
he tried to dodge the questions with clichéd answers like, "I don't recall."
Then, he was found dead
with his skull cleanly cut open and his brain completely gouged out.
His hippocampus, the part of the brain that plays an important role in memory,
had been inserted into his anus.
Based on this and the way Sasayama was killed,
I'd say the culprit back then wanted the ways he killed and
exhibited the bodies to convey some sort of message.
There were four victims.
The places their bodies were found were...
underneath a Holographic display,
a luxury Japanese-style restaurant,
a zoo, and right above a stage set up for an idol's concert.
But this time, both bodies were found in a park.
A much more boring setup.
Boring?
There's no twisted humor in these murders, no message.
They're beautiful and devilish, and look like works of art,
but something critical is missing.
What is this "something"?
Originality.
Originality, you say?
Despite the elaborate form of these murders,
the culprit isn't sending a strong message.
Or at least, I don't sense one.
To Touma Kouzaburo, murdering people was just about preparing materials.
Up to that point, the current case is the same.
But from then onward...
the ways they worked on the bodies are totally different.
I get a totally different picture of this culprit.
He's highly intelligent and is assigned to a job with a high income by Sibyl's Judgement.
But he's quite young,
or he's someone whose mental age is young.
Considering the bodies didn't show many indignities of a sexual nature,
we can guess that he wasn't abused as a child.
Is that...
It's sort of like profiling.
Inspector, I'm applying for permission to go out.
What? But I have to accompany you.
Right. I'm asking you to come with me.
Tokorozawa Correction and Rehabilitation Center
What is this place?
Is this your first time coming here?
Well, I guess you'd have no reason to, would you?
Once you or Gino decides that I'm no longer of any use,
I'll be thrown in here and will never be able to leave again.
But what on Earth are we doing here?
If my hunch is correct,
the way the bodies were arranged in the current case was based on some original work.
So I'll ask an expert in that field about it.
From this point, patients with severe conditions who have Crime Coefficients over 300 are kept isolated.
In an emergency, poisonous gas can be released through the vents.
In other words, this place can be turned into an execution chamber any time.
That's terrible...
Even if these guys made it outside,
any Dominator would immediately judge them as worthy of execution,
so they'd be mincemeat in no time.
At least by staying behind bars, they get to keep on living.
Oh, hi, Doggie. Long time no see.
I see you've been drawing a lot.
I bet adding them to your back is tough even for you.
I may not look it, but I'm quite flexible.
If I've got a mirror, I can draw on my back with no problems.
Have you been watching the news?
I'm not interested in a world that doesn't show a proper appreciation for art.
I'm looking for artwork that's similar to these bodies.
Paintings, sculptures, films, comics... Even literature, if need be.
Oh, they're pretty good.
Those look just like Ouryou Rouichi's art.
Do you know the name?
No.
To think that even the name Ouryou Rouichi has faded away.
Back in the day, even if the art was designated as harmful,
someone would still preserve it in the online archives.
Are there no longer any kids with guts like that?
People like that would be behind bars with you,
thanks to the Sibyl System.
You're so cold-hearted, Ko.
Here. Can you see the resemblance?
His artwork always fetched a good price in my store.
That's because it wasn't just superficial, trendy art.
His work contained firm fundamental themes.
Thanks, that was a big help.
Let's check the investigation files.
Does Ouryou Rouichi bring up anything?
Let's see...
There's a student at Ousou Academy with the same surname.
Kougami! She's a blood relative!
Have you seen any suspicious people?
No.
I see... Then...
K-Ko!
Ah...
That idiot!
Please wait! There's a suspect among the students!
Huh?
Hey! What do you think you're doing?!
We repeatedly requested your tact and consideration during the investigation
so as to avoid placing unnecessary stress upon the students!
You are Ouryou Rikako, correct?
What of it?
Crime Coefficient is 472.
Enforcement mode is Lethal Eliminator.
Aim carefully and eliminate the target.
What're you doing?!
Stop it!
A-Are you guys insane?! She's a minor!
Well, sir... we don't have juvenile law these days.
That was close.
Thanks. Did Mr. Makishima also arrange this?
Yes.
Seal off the entire academy right away!
Use all the drones we've got!
We don't have enough? Do something!
That's... Kagami...
How is it possible that we can't find one single girl?!
The security here is very tight at the entrances and exits,
but there's a whole lot of blind spots inside the grounds.
Can you analyze the footage from the security cameras over the past few days to isolate Ouryou Rikako?
With help from the lab back at Headquarters, yes.
A basic image search like that shouldn't take too long.
Do it.
You mentioned the name Ouryou Rouichi, correct?
How did you find out such an artist existed?
Originality, right, Kougami?
What?
Well, that's because... the message the culprit was sending was too boring, so... by profiling, um...
Kougami.
Did you know that these two murders were not by Touma Kouzaburo from the start?
The culprit this time decided where to exhibit the bodies
based solely on where it would draw the most attention.
Touma Kouzaburo would never pick a park twice in a row.
Even so, we still can't say for sure that it was all done by Ouryou Rikako.
Either way,
we can't let someone with a Crime Coefficient like that run free.
Right?
Image search completed.
I'll browse through them.
Oh... Looks like she's a sociable girl.
She always has a few followers by her side.
Where's this camera?
The garbage disposal facility behind the dorm.
What was she doing in a place like that?
Kougami.
Did you know that these two murders were not by Touma Kouzaburo from the start?
The culprit this time decided where to exhibit the bodies
based solely on where it would draw the most attention.
Mr. Shibata, so you like music?
Yes. I'm always looking for new artists.
I really enjoy finding interesting new talent.
V-Vice Principal!
Student bodies have been found on Academy grounds!
What?!
So you were close to her, huh?
You can tell?
Yeah, from the look on your face.
I failed to tell her something important.
She kept talking about Yoshika...
She wasn't thinking about me at all.
I was the one who suggested she ask Ouryou Rikako.
I shouldn't have let her go alone!
It's as if I killed her myself!
Cry while you can.
Otherwise, your Hue will get cloudy.
There are too many things that can't be explained.
Ouryou Rikako's escape route,
that equipment in the basement...
No matter how you look at it, there's no way a high school girl could prepare those by herself.
There's something going on behind the scenes this time, too.
It's possible that, like you said—
This is odd.
What's the matter?
There's some damaged data.
When Kunizuka did the search earlier, all the recordings were fine.
Looks like the damage was focused on the art room camera's data.
It's all been destroyed.
Except this one. Looks like we can restore the sound.
Why did you only choose students within this school for your works of art?
The academy is a girls' boarding school.
What do you think of their education policy, Mr. Makishima?
Is this really the correct route?
Choe Gu-Sung?
Just in case, I'd like to ask you a question before this is all over.
Ouryou Rikako...
Do you yourself realize how you came to disappoint me?
What are you talking about?
What did I do?
Well... If you don't realize it, then I guess you can't reflect on it either.
As I suspected, it seems that I can't expect any more growth from you.
It's unfortunate. I saw great promise in you at first.
Sir... Mr. Makishima!
What on Earth do you mean?
I believe this is a line by Tamora, the Queen of Goths.
"So should I rob my sweet sons of their fee:
No, let them satisfy their lust on thee."
No service
Unable to access network
Wh-What's going on?
No service
Unable to access network
"The hunt is up, the morn is bright and grey,
The fields are fragrant and the woods are green:
Uncouple here and let us make a bay."
"They told me, here, at dead time of the night,
A thousand fiends, a thousand hissing snakes,
Ten thousand swelling toads, as many urchins,
Would make such fearful and confused cries."
"Listen, fair madam: let it be your glory
To see her tears; but be your heart to them
As unrelenting flint to drops of rain."
Oryou
Rouichi
No service
Oryou
Rouichi
No service
Oryou
Rouichi
No service
Oryou
Rouichi
No service
"So, now go tell, an if thy tongue can speak,
Who 'twas that cut thy tongue and ravish'd thee."
"Write down thy mind, bewray thy meaning so,
An if thy stumps will let thee play the scribe."
You too will be discarded one day when Mr. Makishima gets bored of you.
You don't have to worry about that.
It seems that you were a fox cub providing entertainment,
but just like him, I'm one of the players who enjoy the entertainment.
"Her life was beast-like, and devoid of pity;
And, being so, shall have like want of pity."
Was that okay? You really liked her, right?
Yeah... but I found a more interesting toy.
I'd like you to gather some information.
Look into the man from the Bureau
who visited this afternoon.
He's probably an Enforcer.
It seems his name is Kougami.
That's quite an unusual guy you've set your sights on.
Yeah.
His insight and ability to grasp the truth is most fascinating.
I get the feeling he'll be very entertaining indeed.
It seems all fairy tales are dead
In a hospital ward of brick stones
my voice is too coarse to sing
Outside in the foggy haze
a red moon glows
Look at me
Do not avert your gaze
Behind black bars
I was born
I wish there were a punishment for evil
Always I need you
Now, grant us justice
before chaos takes us all
Pay the price of fate and be rewarded, nameless beast
Black rain falls from the sky
and I remain forever unwanted
My crazed neurosis
pulls me towards the sinful hellfire
Now, mete out justice
Even my ever-bleeding wounds shall be my friend
Let's accept who we are and walk together
We, who are nameless beasts
This is a world where the mental state and personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed, these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are commonly called "Psycho-Pass".
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear
in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.