Kirius, our weapons systems are completely dead.
We don't even have enough power to create fireworks.
I see...
The propulsion systems are beyond repair too.
Damn it!
Don't tell me we're stuck on this planet!?
Izo! Come to the bridge!
Kirius?
The enemy has returned.
Lovely, lovely
The girl in the training suit is somehow special
When she takes it off, she can be anything
To look for something she treasures, she'd go to the bottom of the ocean
The surge of her emotions can turn her opposition into mist
I come to meet you as fast as I can
when your visions call to me
Perfect!
Live your life!
Rewrite fate and fly
Fly away
Oh and fly today
If it's dangerous to laugh at your foes as you advance
burn brighter and fly away
Try, unite, unite
Lovely, lovely
The Swimmers Of Kamogawa
Let me introduce the new transfer student.
Muginami
I'm Muginami!
Due to family circumstances,
she will be attending this school indefinitely.
I'm Muginami!
She'll be coming to class in regular clothes
until her school uniform is ready.
She's lived abroad for some time
and her grasp of our language may be a little awkward,
but be nice to her.
I'm Muginami!
Our school is so lax!
I heard that, Nogami.
Let's see, where should you sit?
Oh, I guess you can sit next to Kyono.
Umm...
Have we met before?
Now that you mention it, I think so...
I'm sorry, my mistake.
I'm Muginami!
Nice to meet you...
Kyono Madoka.
What the hell was the Security Team doing?
How did this girl manage to get into the Vox hangar?
And she's also transferred into Madoka's school.
What an unexpected turn of events.
How can they be so carefree at such a dangerous time?
They're doing this because of the times are dangerous.
"A Kamo Girls' student must not forget about war during a time of peace."
"Likewise, they must not forget about peace during a time of war."
Is that the school motto?
That sounds more like an Army motto.
Was her name Muginami?
The girl hanging around Madoka?
Yeah.
You're going to just let her roam freely?
It depends on how you view it.
Let's just say... I'm letting her swim around until she shows her true colors.
Kyono Madoka in Class 2-3.
Please come to the reception office.
Kyono Madoka of Class 2-3.
Huh? Me?
Please come to the school reception office.
Kamo Girls!
Fight, fight, fight, fight!
What!?
Kyono was the one fighting inside that robot?!
Ms. Iwabuchi, not so loud.
How can I stay calm?
What do you think you're doing to one of my students?!
I don't know what kind of organization you're supposed to be,
Novumundus Foundation Japan International
Risk Management Officer
Tadokoro
Novumundus Foundation Japan International
Management Group Chief
Risk Management Officer
Tadokoro
Syozo
Novumundus Foundation Japan International
Management Group Chief
Risk Management Officer
Tadokoro
Syozo
Novumundus Foundation Japan International
Management Group Chief
Risk Management Officer
Tadokoro
Syozo
Novumundus Foundation Japan International
Management Group Chief
Risk Management Officer
Tadokoro
Syozo
but you're out of your mind!
Nowhere in our school regulation does it state that
"A student can fight inside a robot."
Nor does it say, "they're restricted from fighting in it."
You're not going to allow this, are you?
She made the decision to pilot it.
Yoko...
Actually,
Nakaizumi was the one ultimately responsible
for Kyono making her final decision.
Why do you know all of this?
You said so on the cell phone—
You listened in on our conversation?
No...
Well...
Um...
She's correct.
It was my decision to pilot Midori.
Kyono...
Midori?
It's the name I gave the robot.
It's cute and easy to remember, don't you think?
Hold on.
Don't go giving it weird names.
That craft already has a name. It's called the Vox Aura—
You be quiet.
But if the aliens are after this robot,
wouldn't handing it over to them solve the problem?
Tadokoro, you can speak now.
Well, long story short...
They don't just want possession of the Vox.
They intend to use Vox's power
to conquer other planets.
Naturally, Earth is no exception.
And that's why you'll fight?
Yes.
And you expect me to believe such an outrageous story?
Whether you believe me or not,
it's a fact that Kamogawa was attacked and Kyono saved it.
Whether we like it or not, it looks like we've been thrown into
this so-called interstellar war.
Yoko...
Oh yeah! Why didn't I think of that option?
What...?
...Option?
If we hand over Midori, I don't have to fight, right?
You're unbelievable...
Huh? Huh?
Kyono, are you really okay with this?
Yes.
If you ask me, I don't think Madoka can pull off such a big task.
She can barely run the Sweats Club right now.
Yoko!
But this could be a chance
for the Kamo Girls' Sweats Club
to make its big space debut, right?
Space...?
...Debut?
Now that's an idea.
All right then!
Kyono, if you've really made up your mind, then give it all you got!
Show those aliens some Sweats Club spirit!
Right!
But on one condition.
What?
86th Annual Kamogawa
Girls' High School
Open Water Swimming Competition
86th
Annual
Kamogawa
Girls'
High
School
Open
Water
Swimming
Competition
And over there are the stars of today's event,
Kamogawa Girls' High School.
Madoka, you're going for the win this year, right?
Hmm...we'll see.
Maybe if I'm lucky.
If only I had my surfboard...
Then I would've been able to take the spotlight!
Too bad surfing isn't included in
the national sports competitions.
So you ended up accepting Nakaizumi Yoko's condition?
But on one condition.
What?
Madoka will continue to live at home
and attend this school.
That's two conditions!
You're not in any position to argue!
Damn it!
I hear it's a school tradition held since the school's founding,
but it looks more like a festival out there.
Why are they doing that at a time like this?
It's not like the ocean's going away or anything.
They're trying to make things fun and exciting.
I like it.
You sure it's not the girls in swimsuits that's getting you excited, Jim?
I bet you're recording this feed, right?
What? No, that's not...
Pervert!
You're wrong!
I don't even collect girl figurines!
Uehara,
has the emergency transport for the pilot been arranged?
Yes, sir.
Coordination between all relevant organizations have been checked and cleared.
Good.
James,
playback the video from five seconds ago.
Hurry!
Yes, sir!
Pause! Right there!
Not her!
Zoom in on the lower left!
Is that Laffinty?
It appears so.
My lady, what are you doing there?
I'm looking out for Madoka.
Here she comes.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Ready...
The swimmers are off to a strong start!
The 86th Annual Kamogawa...
Muginami is such a good swimmer!
Wow, check her out.
She's evenly matched with Madoka!
That girl...
She's the princess of Le Garite!
Someone!
You're kidding.
Don't tell me...
She can't swim?
I'm coming!
At this rate, I'll be pulled down too!
Hang in there!
She's...!
She'll be all right.
Thank goodness, Lan!
Madoka...
Their Memoria...
That's where they have it.
The first place winner is Kanae Ikuta from Class 2-2.
In second place is Azumi Takashiro from Class 3-1.
You were so close to winning.
Finally, in third place,
Eriko Tamaki from Class 2-2.
It's too bad.
But I found out something great in exchange.
Say, Muginami!
Want to come over to my house?
Huh?
Thank goodness you're all right.
I was worried after hearing that you almost drowned.
Don't worry. I'm okay now.
Sota.
Sota!
Yoko!
Whoa!
The guys here don't know what they're doing.
They handle the artifacts carelessly,
and the way they catalog items is disorganized.
They're worse than amateurs when it comes to archaeology.
Then who are they?
They are all people who specialize
in mechanical or electrical engineering.
Take a look at this.
What they have here
aren't just the artifacts we excavated in Kamogawa.
This one was discovered
at the bottom of the Atlantic Ocean in Bermuda.
And this was found
in the Indian Ocean near Madagascar.
Ignis represents fire...
Lympha represents water...
And Madoka's Aura
represents wind, huh?
The Sweats Club?
Yes.
Will you join?
I've been waiting for someone like you!
But...
I don't understand what you do.
If you agree to join, I'll explain it to you.
See,
it's more about being a comrade than a club member.
A comrade?
Yeah, people who share the same feelings.
Comrade...
I feel like you and I can become great comrades.
You're a great swimmer and your rescue efforts were amazing!
Comrades, huh?
Sure!
Muginami will join the Sweats Club!
Really? Yes!
Our very first Sweats Club member!
I'll learn how to swim too!
Lan,
when did you get here?
She's been here for a while.
Here you go.
Oh, it looks delicious!
It's to celebrate you joining the club.
Welcome.
Thanks to you, Muginami,
I can finally show my cousin who's boss!
It would've been great if Lan were also a student at our school.
Welcome.
Excuse me!
Oh, one moment please.
We'll have two fish sandwiches.
It's starting to get crowded.
Sure thing.
I'll help!
Please enjoy.
Over at BWH right now.
The waitress here is super cute!
Here's the order.
Roger that!
Business is booming, thanks to her.
You think she'd be interested in working here part-time?
Here you...
I'm sorry!
I-I'll get a towel...
Lan...
She's a klutz.
A klutzy waitress... I like it!
They have a klutzy and a cute waitress!
I'll take your plates away.
Madoka, do you think she'd be interested in working here part-time too?
Sorry for making you both stay and help until closing time.
Not at all. It was fun.
I'm so terrible...
I'm so terrible at everything.
So terrible...
Uncle...
Can you give them a ride home?
So terrible...
Sure thing.
Um,
I have...
no place to...
Say Muginami,
would you like to live here with me?
Uncle, is that okay with you?
Sure.
Huh?
Are you sure?
I have millions of rooms to spare!
I'm so happy! Thank you, Madoka!
It's my pleasure!
Easy, Muginami! I can't breathe.
That's so...
The head of Kiss comes to meet us in person?
Villagiulio...
Were you the one who attacked our ship!?
Say, schoolboys...
Would you be interested in teaming up with me?
All right.
Let me introduce another transfer student today.
Fin E Ld Si Laffinity
Woof.
I am Fin E Ld Si Laffinty.
But you can call me Lan.
Woof?
No, Lan.
Lan?
Woof...
Now that I'm a student at Kamo Girls' High,
I can join the Sweats Club too.
The Sweats Club?
She wants to join the Sweats Club?
Without any hesitation?
Kyono.
Yes?
I understand Muginami and Laffinty are both
going to be staying at your place.
Huh?
What?
Woof.
What?!
What's wrong?
We have an emergency, sir!
The prisoner is attempting to escape in the Ovid!
Close off Pharos immediately!
We won't make it in time!
I'll never forget that the soul in my chest would never yield
Don't cry
Promise me, okay
Promise me you'll never cry alone
We will always be together, you know
If we do get sad, we will share our sadness
and be stronger through it
Yay yay yay!
I'll laugh soon, my friend
My friend!
This isn't for just anyone, you're special
I am sure of my own emotions
With an upright voice, I say
Hello!
Sing the song that you always sing
and put a little bit of courage into my heart
Yay
You let Muginami have my room?!
What's the big deal? You're not using it anyway.
Where am I supposed to stay, huh?
That does it!
Why you—!
When did you learn a technique like that!?
How's this?
That's nothing!
Next time, on Rinne no Lagrange.
Episode Five, "Fight to the end: Kamogawa Death Match."
The Man Who Came to Kamogawa
What will become of BWH?