Lady Laffinty.
This way! Over here!
Please wait, Lady Laffinty!
Oh, look at what we have here!
In the language of flowers,
the Lagrange stands for freedom, charm, and distraction.
Did you know that?
Lord Villagiulio?
My apologies.
I was just thinking of your older brother on that ship and...
Does De Metrio always send such young men off to war?
No, your brother is an exception.
I don't like war.
I can't understand how one human can take the life of another.
Life is a miracle in itself.
You are kind, Lady Laffinty.
Your brother is in line to become the next king of Le Garite.
He may be forced into wars he has no desire to fight.
That is why...
You must never change the way you are,
and be there for your brother at all times.
Of course. And you too!
Yes, of course.
Why would I have a dream about my enemy?
Why now, of all times?
The ocean sure looks beautiful.
But...
it would look much better if that thing wasn't there.
Lovely, lovely
The girl in the training suit is somehow special
When she takes it off, she can be anything
To look for something she treasures, she'd go to the bottom of the ocean
The surge of her emotions can turn her opposition into mist
I come to meet you as fast as I can
when your visions call to me
Perfect!
Live your life!
Rewrite fate and fly
Fly away
Oh and fly today
If it's dangerous to laugh at your foes as you advance
burn brighter and fly away
Try, unite, unite
Lovely, lovely
The Man Who Came
to Kamogawa
Wow!
Did you make all this by yourself, Muginami?
I felt bad that your uncle always has to cook for us,
so I thought I'd help out for a change.
Please, help yourselves.
Thanks!
Oh, wow!
This is perfect! Absolutely perfect!
Yeah, it's delicious.
I could serve this up at the shop. In fact, why don't we?
Really?
I'm so glad you like it!
Lan, won't you have some?
No thanks.
I've got too much on my mind right now.
Guess my plan didn't work out.
What?
To be honest, I made this breakfast for you.
No way.
It's true!
Really?
Yes.
We live under the same roof, but Lan still won't open up to me.
I was hoping this would give us a chance to get to know each other.
So that's why you've been up since three in the morning?
Sorry. I knew that would only upset you, Lan.
I mean, you're a very honest person.
It's only natural that you'd get mad at being dragged into a friendship.
I guess I realized that, but...
Fine, I'll eat it!
You will? Thank you so much!
Okay, I ate it.
Wasn't it good?
It was...
Huh? I didn't hear that.
It was good!
Morning!
How do you like living with Madoka?
Oh, it's just too much fun! Right, Madoka?
It seems you're having a hard time dealing with her.
Right!
She took me by surprise this morning, that's all.
Never mind that.
Did you learn anything about Muginami?
No, there is no data in Le Garite matching her description either.
Any connection with the escaped prisoner?
Nothing. We don't even know how that one managed to escape in the first place.
Horoscope
Weekly: Cancer
Ah, just as I thought.
It says Cancers have to be patient this week.
What?
"Due to Pluto being in retrograde..."
No wonder bad things keep happening.
I'd better limit myself to two yogurts.
Continue checking the Le Garite database records on Muginami.
Lan!
Madoka is coming.
Contact me if you learn anything.
There you are!
What are you doing? It's your turn at bat.
Bat?
Um... here it comes!
Strike!
You're out!
That's what you get for scheming during class.
All right, give it to me!
I'll get revenge for Lan!
Don't get any closer to Muginami.
Huh?
She's a danger to you, Madoka.
Behind that cheerful demeanor,
she's scheming something very frightening.
Now hold on a minute.
What's gotten into you?
Muginami is a nice girl.
Remember how she rescued you, Lan?
That's...
Yes, she did, but...
No! I'm sure even that was part of her...
And she just hit a home run for you as well.
That means she's your comrade!
Fine...
I'll leave it up to your judgment.
Perfect!
Come on, let's go!
Wow!
Can we really use this room?
As you can see... it's a storeroom, but yes.
No, I think this place is perfect!
Oh really?
Then here you go.
When you're done, be sure to return it to the faculty office.
No problem!
Kyono!
Huh?
Now you're one step ahead of Yoko. Keep it up.
Right!
Yes! A room for our club!
I'm happy for you.
And it's all thanks to you two joining the club!
Then I guess we should start acting more like Sweats Club members, huh?
What do you mean?
The Student Council requested help with moving some of their stuff.
Muginami and I will handle that.
Huh?
And Madoka, you can take care of the groceries that Mr. Hiroshi asked for. Right?
Sure. Sounds good.
You sure?
In that case, I'll leave the rest to you two.
Roger that!
Woof.
Don't forget to lock up afterwards!
"Don't forget to lock up afterwards."
Do I sound like a club captain or what?
Perfect!
Shall we get going?
Come again!
Energy replenished!
Tonight I'll make a jumbo-size fish sandwich just like Uncle taught me!
Uncle?
I think that coat looks better on me.
Man, how many times we gotta go through this?
Huh? We did?
All right, then the next coat on sale is—
What are you doing?
Hey, Madoka!
This is my niece. Isn't she cute?
This is Giovu... Aw man, I bit my tongue again.
Hiroshi...
Y-Yes?
Drinking out here, in broad daylight? How bold.
Well actually, he and I had bit of an argument earlier and...
This is... uh...
It's our way of making up! Yeah, that's it!
Want a drink too, Madoka?
No thank you!
I got everything except the soy sauce and sugar. Now go!
See you.
Sorry about that.
You are so in my way!
How about now?
Huh? Wha—
Are you all right?
What are you looking at?
Madoka, I don't think you should be wearing anything besides white—
I see.
She really is cute.
This is the first time I've been to this town.
So I've been walking around to see the sights.
But I have to say the ocean view from here is the best.
Thank you.
"Thank you"?
By the way, what did you and my uncle argue about?
Well, there was only one left.
There's no need to argue
over something if it's just lying around, right?
Weren't we supposed to help out the student council?
What are you planning?
Planning?
What did you hope to gain by getting close to us?
I was wondering when you'd ask.
Lan, all you ever did was observe me from the shadows.
What do you mean?
Yours is here, right?
How can you have the Memoria?!
What's so hard about it?
I just stood naked in front of the Vox and then it poked me.
What do you intend to do with the Vox?
I don't know. Ask Brother.
Brother?
Brother said he wanted it, that's why I came to get this.
That's all.
You don't know the horror that the Vox is capable of!
Are you talking about the "Legend of the Demons"?
You know about that?
I don't know the details.
I just heard that it's really, really scary.
But it's just an old fairy tale, right?
By the way, did you tell Madoka about this?
Leave Madoka out of this.
Uh-oh, so you haven't told her yet?
I don't know, Lan, is that really a good idea?
I'll tell Madoka when the time comes...
Oh! I have a suggestion.
What?
Brother will be coming to this town soon.
Actually, he should be here anytime now.
Then this town will become a battlefield for sure.
I won't let you have your way!
Of course not.
Isn't that why there's going to be a war?
Anyway, war between us is inevitable.
So...
Let's enjoy this while we can!
Huh?
I meant our student life here!
I just confirmed it.
Like she said, Ignis has undergone Memoria.
How could that happen?!
And as for "Brother"...
What did you learn?
The same as Muginami.
There isn't a criminal that matches up.
Then it must be a codename.
Listen, find out who this "Brother" is, no matter what.
I understand.
"Brother"...
I'm home.
Welcome back. You're late.
You have a customer.
Giuvi...!
It's Villa. Villagiulio.
What brings you here?
As a token of my apology for upsetting Madoka,
I helped her pick up trash.
Then she said she'd treat me.
I did not!
I just said we deserve to have some good food after picking up all that trash!
Welcome back!
Hey.
How have you been?
Brother...
Brother?!
Brother!
You're so late!
I've been waiting for you this whole time!
I just knew you'd come here!
Muginami,
is he your older brother?
Yes.
Even though we're not related,
he's my brother!
Lan?
You're...
"Brother"?
Welcome back,
Lady Laffinty.
Lan...
He's our enemy?
That Shabada—
No, Madoka.
His name is Giuvi—
It's Villagiulio.
Then what about Muginami?
She's also our enemy.
But she doesn't seem that way at all.
Is it true that you're our enemy?
Huh?
Did Lan say so?
Answer me.
Those guys who came to attack us last time...
Are they also your people, Muginami?
No, they're—
You, be quiet.
I'm not your enemy, Madoka.
I'm on Brother's side. That's all.
Which means you're the enemy.
Maybe to you, Lan.
But this doesn't involve Madoka, does it?
After all, we're the ones at war.
How can you say this doesn't involve me?
Madoka?
Of course, it involves me!
We live together!
We go to school together.
We're in the same club together.
So how can you say this doesn't involve me?
I can't just go around having fun
when you and Lan are fighting right in front of me!
Really?
It was pretty fun for me...
Unlike Lan over there.
What?
I mean, we all woke up in the morning and ate breakfast,
and went to school and gossiped, then ate again.
In the afternoon, as we listened to the teacher's lecture,
we took a quick nap.
Then we did Sweats Club activities until evening.
Then we went home and helped at the shop.
Then we took a leisurely bath and
slept 'til the next morning.
We did the same thing every day,
but I'd never had such an easy life.
I loved every minute of it!
Easy?
Uh-huh.
Which is why I told Lan earlier...
We're going to have to fight sooner or later,
so we should enjoy this life while we can.
But Lan got upset and told me to quit fooling around.
How could you, Muginami?
Madoka?
I can't believe that's the way you thought about us!
Sorry!
But I really did have fun.
I honestly wished these days could continue for the rest of my life.
Then...
But that's not possible.
Right, Lan?
So please understand, Madoka.
This is our destiny.
Oh, excuse me. Go on.
And wake me up when you're done.
Oh, well...
This is getting boring.
Let's go, Brother.
Go where?
Why, back to Kiss where everyone's waiting.
Kiss?
That's the name of their organization.
Hurry up!
Since when did you become one of us?
Huh?
You can't pilot an Ovid,
nor can you handle a gun properly.
All you do is eat and sleep!
Brother?
We put our lives on the line fighting,
while you've had it nice and easy.
You have some nerve calling yourself one of us.
Oh, Brother...
Look at this. I have the Memoria for the Vox.
I know.
I know already.
Then why aren't you happy?
Why should I be?
Because you were talking with everyone...
About taking possession of the Vox—
So?
So I...
You took the remaining Vox for yourself.
Uh-huh!
Who the hell asked you to do that?!
Did you think that would make you one of us? Well?
Stop...
Did you think that would make up for all the free meals you got?
Brother, please...
Don't call me "Brother". It's "Lord Villagiulio".
Right?
Why?
Isn't it obvious?
Because you're a parasite.
Shut up!
Don't stop me, Uncle!
This jerk! This jerk just called Muginami a...
Get out.
Laffinty...
Give Moid this message:
Destroy every Vox in your possession by tomorrow morning.
Otherwise...
I'll destroy them along with that ship.
That girl is just like you...
Yurikano.
I'll never forget that the soul in my chest would never yield
Don't cry
Promise me, okay
Promise me you'll never cry alone
We will always be together, you know
If we do get sad, we will share our sadness
and be stronger through it
Yay yay yay!
I'll laugh soon, my friend
My friend!
This isn't for just anyone, you're special
I am sure of my own emotions
With an upright voice, I say
Hello!
Sing the song that you always sing
and put a little bit of courage into my heart
Yay
This is terrible.
Yes, it is.
What's so terrible?
Tadokoro, is that an insult towards your superior?
Huh? I didn't mean to...
Not good, Cap.
How can you say such a thing after seeing that?
What exactly are you talking about?!
Look at Commander Watabe's hair!
Oh no!
What a pity.
What should we do?!
The Wind, Fire, and Water Above Kamogawa