Hey, are you the bastards trying to make a power grab around here lately?
Akura-oh and Tomoe, I believe it was.
How about you show us what you've got?! Come on!
Why not? We've got time.
Why not indulge them?
You should have left well enough alone.
Nicely done.
Tomoe?
Tomoe?!
Tomoe...
Isn't it peaceful, Kotetsu?
Indeed, it is, Onikiri.
Lately, Lady Nanami has really come into
her own as the land god of Mikage Shrine,
and it seems she has been diligently practicing with talismans.
I am glad to hear that.
The shrine should be secure now.
How late do you intend to sleep?! Your food grows cold!
Wake up!
So peaceful.
I wonder what's happening on this world
I fly through the sky into space
and circle the world
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday
With my periodic biorhythm
I'm like a washing machine
Just kidding
Yes, I'm spinning around
Around, around the world
Because there's no limit to my love
Spinning around, around, around the world
I want to tell you that I love you, even if it confuses me
Bam, bam, bam
You're not paying attention
Sometimes love keeps being one-sided
It's gotten so hopelessly complex
But I'll make it all true with a miracle
Hey, God,
I'm your god
I think
Ah! I fell asleep writing talismans!
That is what you get for writing so many!
World
Peace
Isn't this a little unreasonable?
Oh, I'm going to be late!
Momozono Nanami is a high school student.
When her father ran away and left her without a place to live,
she went to the park and met Mikage the land god there by chance,
who made her the god of his former shrine, saddling her with all the responsibilities that came with the position.
Oh, wait!
Oh,
wait!
Honk
With the help of her familiars, Tomoe and Mizuki,
and the will-o'-the-wisps, Onikiri and Kotetsu, who serve as shrine spirits,
Nanami came to live the life of a god,
but there was just one problem.
The new term starts tomorrow.
The new
term starts
tomorrow.
You hasty fool.
You
hasty
fool.
What?
Ha
ha
She had fallen in love with Tomoe, her familiar.
I've Started the 'Being a God' Thing Again
I'm just gonna sleep today.
Why am I all nervous? And why'd I reflexively get up?
Oh, come to think of it...
I've heard that Lord Mikage's avatar is the butterfly.
Avatar?
Each god has the ability to dwell in a particular vessel.
In Lady Yonomori's case, it was plum blossoms.
And Lord Mikage has...
the butterfly.
Tomoe...
I wonder if he...
misses Mikage.
Hey, girl, long time no see!
The he-she guy!
Who are you calling he-she?!
He is Otohikogami the wind god.
Thanks for the intro.
Shimmery-Shiny
(You are welcome!)
I haven't seen you since the ritual dance.
I came to see your festival. However...
Well, it wasn't bad,
but I can't accept you just yet.
What?
You are being circuitous, Lord Otohiko.
Have you not come to deliver the summons from Izumo?
I have! Oh, Tomoe, it's been so long!
Okay, clink.
Every year, for one week in October, gods from all across the country gather at Izumo for a meeting.
With Mikage gone, there's one vacant seat, right?
So...
We got to talking about inviting you as his successor,
but even as a human god, you're lacking in skills, right?
We debated it quite a bit up there.
It may have been rushed, but you
are the god of Mikage Shrine now,
so, well...
We decided that you may attend if you can pass a test.
Attending the Divine Assembly would be huge for you, so try not to screw this up.
The test...
Count me out.
What did you say?!
You arrogantly decided that without my input.
Twitch
I don't want to go, so I won't!
Are you sure about that?
Gods from across the country gather at the Divine Assembly in Izumo.
There's a decent chance one of them knows Mikage's whereabouts.
What?
See ya!
Mikage's...
There is no need for you to go to Izumo.
Mikage's whereabouts are also irrelevant.
Morning, Nanami.
Look, look! Kei and I got matching cellphones!
They're adorable!
Yo, Momozono! It's the first day of the new term, and you're already here!
Do not touch her so casually, you foul brat.
I feel like this has happened before...
Are you all right?
Y-Yeah.
Tomoe...
Maybe he really does miss Mikage.
He-she guy!
It's Otohiko the wind god! Get it through your thick skull already!
Oh, so you've decided to take the test to go to Izumo.
Give. The. Test. Give. The. Test.
I thought you'd say that.
Hur-ry. Up. Hur-ry. Up. He. She.
Shut up!
This is your test.
You must raise a daemon.
Raise... a daemon?
This is a daemon egg.
It draws sustenance from its
keeper's chi and grows rapidly.
Until it safely hatches seven days from now,
keep it with you at all times.
If you can successfully raise a daemon that's to my liking, you shall pass.
He-sh... Otohiko, a question.
What's a daemon?
No. Seriously, no.
You're a land god, so look it up yourself!
A daemon or whatever this thing is...
I just have to get it to hatch, right?
Easy enough. I can totally do that.
Mikage Shrine
Probably.
"A daemon is...
power from the spirit world converted into a physical form allowing it to act upon things in this world."
I still don't really get it.
I am the one who does not "get it"!
I told you there is no need to go to Izumo!
No one asked you!
What is that egg?! Go return it!
No! No means no!
Guess what, Nanami? We got
two whole worshipers today!
Record of Worshipers
The egg!
It cracked! It's the first day, and it cracked!
Boo
hoo
Good
boy,
good
boy
A
a
h
It's all
over,
it's all
over
Now, now. Dear Mizuki didn't mean to do that.
Go easy on him.
What? No way.
Is the daemon about to be born?
Th-The daemon is a baby monkey?
It is an unfinished brute that hatched too soon.
You are not likely to pass Otohiko's test with it.
Give up.
It didn't go quite as planned, but...
Well, it'll work out somehow.
Do not run.
But we missed the bus!
Hurry up, will you?
Why did you bring the monkey with you?
What? Oh, it already hatched, but I've still got seven days.
Otohiko said that it draws sustenance from my chi, so...
If I'm careful raising you, I bet you'll grow up to be a great daemon!
This tiny vermin? No matter how you raise it, I doubt it'll be much use.
This little one needs me, and that's all that matters.
I'm good as long as it grows up healthy.
I am the one who shall be of use to you.
What?
Because I am yours.
Th-That's true.
Oh, come on. Let's hurry.
Or we'll be late!
R-Right.
My own words shocked me.
What the hell was that?
I am utterly thrown.
I am yours.
I am yours. I am yours. I am yours. I am yours.
What's up with her?
She's smirking all by herself.
What Nanami was researching at the library was technically still daemon related.
Why Daemons Are
Exploitation As Spirits
Little girl.
Why Daemons Are
Exploitation As Spirits
He-she guy!
Stop calling me that!
Haven't you noticed?
What?
Someone is very envious of a human god determined to go to Izumo.
Whatever will you do?
What?
Hang in there!
Otohiko!
What?
What? What?
Yo, yo, yo, yo, isn't Momozono here today?
Wh-What should I do?
Hiya!
Tomoe...
Are you all right?
Yeah...
I am the one who shall be of use to you.
I'm always...
Why Daemons Are
Exploitation As Spirits
the one who needs saving.
I can't go to Izumo.
Not like this.
Next part coming
right up
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
What is it? Why are you raring to go so early?
I'm going to get my divine
power up before I go to Izumo,
so I want you to stop fussing over me for a while.
You still plan to go to Izumo?!
Damn straight!
You're so helpless! You will only be humiliated if you go!
I know that!
That's exactly why...
Stop always fussing over me!
Hey! You guys are so mean!
You just left without me!
I'm going to school too!
Do whatever you want!
Do not look to me if another spirit shows up!
I will do whatever I want!
Tomoe, you worry too much!
You guys in the back, please be quiet.
What should I do? The shivers just won't stop.
That's what you're into, Mizuki?
Morning!
Oh? No one's here yet today.
I'm the first to arrive today!
That spider spirit may still be around.
Not to worry.
I brought the white talismans I made yesterday for such an occasion.
Sigh...
Purify
What are you so depressed about?
Sigh...
Purify
My divine power has gone up compared to before.
It better have.
Nanami!
Ami!
I-I-It appeared! A spirit!
What?!
Huh? It's not here.
It was right here, I swear.
I believe you.
Just leave it to me.
Here's a talisman to ward against evil. You'll be okay.
Nanami, we must talk.
Wow! A talisman! That's so neat!
As I expected, this is spider spirit miasma.
It has spread all over school.
This is too much for you.
Purify
I'll be fine. Purification is a land god's job to begin with.
I'm going.
Rely upon me.
I can't. Please stay out of this.
This tree...
The miasma made it wither away.
Purify
See? I can do it.
I can do it.
Library
The miasma is coming from where the spider spirit was vanquished.
Nanami.
Ami.
Will you be okay?
Yeah, I'll be done in no time, so you stay here.
I'll be fine.
Okay, be careful.
The devastation is terrible.
Nothing's changed since yesterday.
That should do it.
Do not trifle with me, girl.
What?
I have lived a hundred years.
Such petty magics will not work on me!
Nanami?!
What's wrong?!
Ah, delicious!
Stop...
I am restored!
My strength is coming back to me!
Don't come... inside me...
You stinking wretch!
Come out! I will tear you to pieces!
Dammit! Where did it go?
Has it grown from feeding on Nanami?
The darkness is spreading.
If I do not find it soon...
Huh? This is...
The nurse's office...
All I remember...
is the warmth of Tomoe as he held me close.
That was so scary.
The darkness has soaked into my hands.
It cannot be washed off.
What happened to you?
You're covered in blood.
Come.
I'll get you cleaned up.
It'll be okay.
You're all clean already.
I was in a terrible state when I first met Mikage too.
But why was I covered in blood back then?
Ami?
Nanami.
What?
You're okay. Thank goodness.
Ami.
I got swallowed up by that black thing in the library.
But I'm okay.
It just made me feel a little sick.
The doctor said I'd get better if I just lied down for a while.
You're so full of energy.
I guess mediums must be used to this.
Ami...
I'm sorry the talisman didn't work.
You're awful!
It's only been three days, but look at the mess you made.
You hatch the egg, and then you do this to the daemon.
You're going to demolish my reputation! Oh, boohoo...
He-sh... Otohiko!
I told you that this little one
draws from your chi to grow!
The vile miasma it absorbed has made it ill!
Mass-producing your cheap talismans is preventing it from healing!
And the same goes for the girl lying there.
Don't drag others into your mess if you can't handle it.
Who knows what would've happened if Tomoe hadn't come along?
I'm...
going to go try again!
Stop writing talismans already.
Right now, you'd only make scribbles.
It's a waste of chi.
But writing talismans is my only skill!
True. I know that, which is why...
You should consider this little one as your talisman.
Like writing on a talisman,
you can give this daemon a name.
That will become the daemon's ability and allow it to carry out your wish.
So what is the power you most desire?
The power... that I... most desire?
Just how many of them are there?
The smell of blood will not go away.
I may not be able to purify them...
but I can drag every last one of them into the open.
Mamoru
To protect
Mamoru!
To keep anyone from getting hurt...
To keep anyone from having to be scared...
How about calling him Mamoru?
Hm...
So it's a boy.
Mamoru
To protect
Where are you going?
He knows what his job is now.
Because he received a name.
You're the caster.
Go on, Momozono Nanami.
Mamoru...
There's a trail of golden light coming from under his feet.
It's clean!
He's cleaning everything!
Tomoe!
Come.
Let's get you washed up.
Goal!
This is... a barrier against evil.
Tomoe, did you see?
Mamoru and my perfectly in-sync parade run!
Mamoru?
That's his name.
Otohiko taught me how to use a daemon.
Thank you for saving me, Tomoe.
No...
Hey, can you hear me?
You saved me.
You pass.
Hey, can you hear me?
That settles it. You're going to Izumo.
That night, I was looking
at the fleeting remnants of the day
The milky way spread across my vision
It was very beautiful
Hey, can you hear me?
I don't think I can talk to other people about this
I'll call up God, I think
If a new day hadn't begun
then yesterday's tomorrow would be today
and yesterday would be the day before
I'm waiting for you
I'll stay here
The boat is stopped here
If today weren't today
and were that day instead, oh, that'd be nice
Preview
Gods from across the country will gather for the Divine Assembly.
She's even mastered a new skill with Mamoru, so it's onward to Izumo!
Hey, can you hear me?
Wait! What's up with these scary gods?!
And just who in the world is this guy?
Next time, "The God Goes to Izumo."
The God Goes to Izumo
I've got a bad feeling about this, ook!