One way or the other.
Okay!
Muginami, we'll be late for school.
Wait, Lan.
Where are your manners?
Well, you didn't wake me up.
Yes I did.
Let's go!
Lag-Rin, Lag-Rin
That girl wearing sweats is somehow special
When she takes it off, she can be anything
In search of things she treasures, she'd go to the bottom of the ocean
She's brash to a fault and difficult for those around her
Lag-rin, Lag-rin
I'll come meet you right away
when I hear you call for help
Perfect!
Live life!
Rewrite fate and fly,
Fly away
On a brighter day
If sticking your tongue out and walking proudly gets you in trouble
burn and fly away
Try unite tonight
Lag-rin, Lag-rin
86th Annual Kamo Girls' Oraga Arts Festival
Umm...
Could you repeat that?
Goodbye, Kamogawa
How about you, Lan?
Yes.
Oh well...
Okay, I'll tell you again.
These are the groups that the Sweats Club helped out for this year's Oraga Festival.
Which means...
all of them fall under our club's exhibit!
Oh, I see.
How did you come to that conclusion?
There's no point in trying to reason with Madoka.
And now, the Sweats Club will proceed
to check out all the exhibits!
Madoka, do we have to wear these sweats?
We're the Sweats Club!
This is our uniform.
Where the sweats are the master, the skirt is a servant.
Huh?
Was that a joke, just right now?
Forget it!
Lan, wait!
Shouldn't we tell Madoka?
We will confront the next enemy attack
with just the two of you.
Make sure Kyono doesn't know about this.
I think Mr. Tadokoro is right.
That old man can be quite thoughtful at times.
What are you whispering about?
Tell me too!
It's a secret.
Huh? Lan, you're so mean!
Forget about that meanie Lan, let's just go!
Huh? Huh?!
Muginami, don't pull!
The live concert starts in the afternoon.
Then let's check out the haunted house first!
Sounds good!
But I'm also kind of hungry.
I wonder if people will come to our café...
Don't worry.
You look perfect for the role, Michi. Be more confident!
You're so lucky, Sachi.
The Surfing Club attracts a lot of attention because you won the prefectural competition.
Well, that's true.
What'll we do?
I'm going.
There's no way I'll let Le Garite have the Vox.
I'm not going.
Fine, I've already given up on you.
It just doesn't sit right with me
to fight the Chairman and the people of this planet.
That girl has got you on her leash, that's all.
What?
So is that the extent of your feelings towards Yurikano?
Is that supposed to be a bad joke?
Just what did Yurikano hope for us?
When we first came to this planet,
I was determined to accomplish our goal no matter what it took.
But would Yurikano really want us to fight to avenge her death?
That's...
Is revenge worth the sacrifice of so many lives?
Wouldn't Yurikano's greatest wish
be to stop the Vox from causing any more suffering?
The Ghost
Mansion
You two helped this club with their makeup, right?
Want to go in?
No thanks, it's so silly.
Oh! You're afraid of ghosts, right, Lan?
Absolutely not! I did the makeup, after all.
I hate this, I'm leaving!
I want to go home, Brother!
Lan, are you all right?
Sorry about that.
Welcome!
Care to try some corn on the cob?
I'm leaving! I want to go home, Brother!
Lan, your eyes are all red!
You're mean!
Here!
Eat this and cheer up.
There are so many people...
I was so touched.
Me too.
Especially that last scene, where...
What? Is that you, Madoka?
No way...
What a transformation.
Oh, Madoka!
It's amazing! It's a huge hit!
And it's all thanks to you.
Oh, it's nothing.
I must say, when the lead actress is attractive,
the film just blossoms...
Oh, who are these two?
Huh? Oh, they're members of our club.
Marvelous!
Please! You both must be in our next film!
"Be in"?
Oh, just looking at you gets my creative juices flowing!
Oh...
Let's see, where to next?
Would you like to take a picture?
We'll print it right out for you.
Can you crouch down a little more?
Wow, she's amazing!
All her shots are double taps!
Raise the level of difficulty!
This doesn't even count as practice.
Asteria?
Ah, there you are.
This Japanese carnival is not as spectacular as I had imagined.
Well, this is a high school arts festival.
Asteria, what are you doing here?
Well...
Lan!
I found you at last!
Sachi?
Our club is in trouble! Please help us!
Huh? But...
Go, Lan.
This is a way for the Sweats Club to enjoy the Oraga Festival!
Okay.
Thanks, Madoka. We owe you one!
Wow, I didn't know Lan and Sachi were such good friends.
They are. You didn't know?
Muginami!
Yes?
Oh Michi, what is it?
I'm sorry, but would you mind helping us?
We're shorthanded at the Astronomy Club's café.
They need you, Muginami.
Go and help them.
Roger that!
Let's go!
Thanks, Muginami!
Well...
What should we do?
What is that?
It smells good.
Ah,
these are grilled eels.
Eels... Did you say eels?!
They're swimming around in there.
Th-This is...!
You actually eat those things?
It's so black and thin and long... slimy...
What is this? It's unforgivable!
How can eel taste so good?
Why was I never informed?!
I think you should decide either to be upset or to eat.
Kyono Madoka!
Y-Yes!
Bring me all the cuisine that is being served at this carnival!
What?!
I swear, why is it that the unhealthier the food looks, the better it tastes?
You're being overdramatic.
Listen carefully, Madoka.
The human body is made up of what you eat.
And our hearts and minds cannot work if we don't have a body.
Okay...?
To eat is to live.
We are connected to the universe by the food we eat,
the water we drink, and the air we breathe.
To put something into our mouths means to take the universe into our bodies.
Huh?!
Let's go.
Uh... What? Umm...
Thank you for waiting.
Our planetarium show is about to start!
The room will darken, so please hang on to your belongings and watch your step.
Wow!
It's amazing...
So pretty...
You were a huge help, Muginami.
Thank you!
Yes, coming right away!
Yes, please wait just a moment!
I know quite a bit about stars.
Really?
Yeah!
Then why don't you join the Astronomy Club, Muginami?
But I'm an alien.
We're going to do the Planetarium Café again next year.
So please join!
I don't know...
Aren't you going in?
They seem busy.
I'll try later.
Even though we used the ultimate weapon,
we were forsaken by heaven...
Ultimate weapon?
Is that me?
That's right!
You may not have noticed, but you're quite popular, Lan.
Welcome to
the Surf Club
Popular?
I was so sure that if you wore a wetsuit, we'd have a flood of customers.
I was too optimistic.
I can't attract customers when I can't even swim.
What? You were worried about that?
Then I'll teach you how to swim next time.
Really?
Yeah.
In appreciation for helping me!
Madoka?
Kyono Madoka?
Oh no!
What's on your mind?
Huh?
I should be happy seeing Lan and Muginami
making new friends and having fun.
But instead, I'm feeling a bit depressed.
And I was all by myself at last year's arts festival,
so I'm not sure why.
I see. Understood.
That was Tadokoro.
A large number of artificial objects have been spotted
approaching Earth at a high speed.
Pharos is...
It's moving into battle position
to keep this town out of harm's way.
I have to go!
To do what?
With Midori, I can...!
There is nothing you can do.
But Lan and Muginami are...
Those two are already on their way to Pharos.
That's...
Tadokoro ordered them to keep the assault a secret from you.
What?
He acted under my orders.
No!
That's a lie!
We'll be off
Lan        Muginami
Up until now,
you've run the Sweats Club all by yourself.
But now you have Lan and Muginami.
That's why you got upset.
You learned that they had spent some time on their own
and could experience joy without you.
You're remembering the fear of losing someone.
Do you think Madoka is mad at us?
This was the only way to protect her.
I guess we can't have Aura act up like the last time.
We made our choice.
To protect Madoka along with this town.
Do you mean, protect Kamogawa together with Madoka?
Or protect both Madoka and this town?
Both.
That's for sure.
Madoka!
Miss Yoko filled me in on the situation!
From Big Sis?
You're going to sea, right?
My dad's boat is in the harbor. Use it!
Sachi...
Thank you!
To fight means coming face-to-face
with the fear of losing something precious.
Are you prepared to confront that fear?
Lan! Muginami!
I'm...
I'm coming too!
You should have told me you were here.
They actually got a clubroom?
Those damn kids.
In our time, we had to do our activities without a room.
Are you sure about letting Madoka go?
I couldn't have stopped her even if I wanted to.
She's just like her mother.
I think you're more fixated on that than Madoka.
I just couldn't throw it away.
Machiko!
Commencing transport to the catapult deck.
Lympha now entering T.O. sequence.
Ignis now entering T.O. sequence.
Commencing Vox Ignis.
We're really going to
A.I Remote System check.
have to fight Brother this time, aren't we?
Probably.
If I hesitate again, Lan...
If you do, I'll smack you.
How scary!
Lan, you sound like Madoka.
That's right.
After all, we're...
Opening the top hatch.
...the Sweats Club.{timing might work better joined with the line two above this?]
Yes, we are.
Vox Lympha is on deck.
Vox Ignis is on deck.
Vox Lympha, Vox Ignis, cleared for take-off.
Let's go, Orca!
Okay! We're off!
Let's give it our all, Hupo!
What's the status of the Le Garite armada?
We lured them into the Starburst Region in the Thaddeus Nebula.
It will be difficult for them to escape from there.
Good work.
What are our losses?
The High Speed Cruiser Forzellhind was destroyed.
The Artillery Ship, Dahhau II, sustained serious damage.
And we lost ten Ovids.
That's less than our initial estimates.
But higher than my hypothesis.
I miscalculated.
You're too rigid with your estimates, Grania.
We are not the military.
Stay on course to enter orbit.
Operations will begin shortly.
Are you sure about this?
I'm sorry for what I'm about to make you go through...
It's all right.
Have you decided what to do?
We're coming.
However...
We're not following you.
We're following Yurikano.
Huh?
Do as you please.
I'm amazed that you kept it.
Shall we do it, for old times' sake?
Today?
Sure. It's the festival!
But getting it ready now?
A schoolteacher has quite a bit of influence, you know.
What do you want to do, Madoka?
Should I turn back to shore?
Please don't go back.
What?
I've...
decided to go!
I'll never forget that the soul in my chest would never yield
Don't cry
Promise me, okay
Promise me you'll never cry alone
We will always be together, you know
If we do get sad, we will share our sadness
and be stronger through it
Yay yay yay!
I'll laugh soon, my friend
My friend!
This isn't for just anyone, you're special
I am sure of my own emotions
With an upright voice, I say
Hello!
Sing the song that you always sing
and put a little bit of courage into my heart
Yay
I've decided.
We should take a picture, just like the Sweats Club.
Sounds good. I'm in!
No way. Why do we have to do something like that?
It's creepy.
It's because this might be our last chance!
A memento of the good old times, when the three of us were together.
That's not even funny!
Kamogawa's Last Line of Defense