I wonder what's happening on this world
I fly through the sky into space
and circle the world
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday
With my periodic biorhythm
I'm like a washing machine
Just kidding
Yes, I'm spinning around
Around, around the world
Because there's no limit to my love
Spinning around, around, around the world
I want to tell you that I love you, even if it confuses me
Bam, bam, bam
You're not paying attention
Sometimes love keeps being one-sided
It's gotten so hopelessly complex
But I'll make it all true with a miracle
Hey, God,
I'm your god
I think
Ah, now that hits the spot!
After not eating or drinking anything for two days, this rice porridge is like a dream come true.
And you even made arrangements for me to have a room while I was gone, Mizuki.
Gloom
The God Makes Her Second Romantic Confession
It's killing me.
I was supposed to accompany you, and yet...
I wasn't there for you in your time of need.
Crush this incompetent fool underfoot all you want!
S-Stop being dramatic. Where's Tomoe?
He carried me here, so he must still be in Izumo, right?
Beats me. Maybe out for a walk?
Oh.
It's only been a couple days,
but I feel like it's been a month.
Hm?
Mizuki! What day of the Divine Assembly is it today?!
It's, uh...
It's the fourth day, lady!
I'd grown tired of waiting, Lady Nanami.
You did well to return to the great
Ookuninushi only one day late, my darling.
Just as I expected.
Ookuninushi!
Chair and all?
Ow!
I have already heard of your deeds in the Netherworld.
Thanks to that, the phone at my desk has
been ringing off the hook with complaints.
I-I am so sorry!
All is well.
And poof.
After all, my missing Lucky Mallet has returned as well.
I will overlook your tardiness as thanks.
However...
Tomoe's actions upon using the Lucky Mallet to
reduce himself to a spirit were deeply reprehensible.
He'll be kept in the east prison for now.
What?
Allow me to deal with Tomoe.
You must now devote yourself to
your duties at the Divine Assembly.
Prison
Prison?!
But why?!
Tomoe is my familiar!
He is no longer a familiar.
With the bonds of the contract undone,
he has reverted to a dangerous wild fox.
I cannot let him run loose.
Do you mean to go see the wild fox, Lady Nanami?
I would advise against—
Too late for that.
It breaks my heart to see you like this,
locked away in a dingy cell.
You need not waste your sympathies on me.
And besides, these tight bonds are sadly necessary.
When I was a familiar, I was able to exercise self-control,
but I find that difficult in this form.
I thought that it was because I was
a familiar that I protected her, but...
Tomoe!
Lady Nanami.
Kotetsu.
Tomoe!
I heard from Ookuninushi that you were being kept in here.
Are you okay? They haven't done anything to you, have they?
What happened to your hand?!
You're hurt!
You are in the midst of the Divine Assembly, are you not?
What have you come here for?
I-I came to make you a familiar again.
You don't want to be stuck in this place forever, right?
That is none of your business.
I will decide whether I return to being a familiar or not.
Allow me some time to consider becoming your familiar.
I understand.
I'll try to negotiate with Ookuninushi to let you out of this place.
Tomoe is...
There you are! Lady Nanami!
The fourth day of the Divine Assembly is about to begin!
I wonder if Tomoe found it hard to be a familiar at times.
I finished.
Please register
these.
Was it something he had to put up with at times?
What?!
Help the War God with his!
Dump
If that's true,
Lady Inaho is making
slow progress.
I have to give this some serious thought...
It is because all
she does is sleep.
so that I'll be fine, even if Tomoe ends up leaving the shrine.
Other than holding back and not begging him to stay,
what else is there that I can do for him?
Please excuse me.
The matchmaking talismans...
War God? A deicide?!
Not to worry.
What?
The War God is currently recovering from his wounds.
My miracle cure, the Peach Pill, will heal any wound, after all.
Peach
Pills
Would you mind sharing a little of that medicine with me?
In exchange for what?
You weren't expecting to get it for free, were you?
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
Uh...
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
She was kind of
thinking of getting
it for free
How about the legendary limited edition sweet potato donut,
the Deluxe Peach Sweet Potato Donut?
Peach Sweet Potato Donut?
I've found something I can do
for Tomoe.
Oh?
So you're still caged up?
How long are you going to stay shut in here?
Where did you get in from?
Here!
Begone.
I wish to be alone.
I heard that you want to quit being a familiar.
It made Nanami very sad.
I'd rather you didn't cause my lady and mistress too much grief.
When I was a familiar, if she was smiling, I immediately felt reassured.
I always kept track of her whereabouts and rushed to her if she needed me.
No matter how far she might have been,
there was not a day when I did not think of her.
That was because I was a familiar.
That is the contract between god and familiar, is it not?
My contract as a familiar is broken and my being is no longer under the constraint of gods.
And yet,
why am I still consumed by her?
What is she to me?
Contracts and being a familiar have nothing to do with it.
Face it. She's just a girl that you like.
Now that the mystery is solved...
Here you go.
A parting gift from Nanami.
The Lord Mamori's Peach Pills.
She asked me to give them to you.
Though our paths may diverge,
I wouldn't want him to face more hardship.
He has a lot of enemies, so at the very least, I want him to have something that will keep him safe.
I cannot accept this.
I have feelings for Nanami?
One touch and I shall know the truth.
Do I desire this maiden?
Tomoe...
Don't go...
Zzz...
Zzz
So I...
have feelings for Nanami...
Tomoe's verdict is in.
Extenuating circumstances!
I'm so glad you're back to being a familiar!
You really did come to my room last night, didn't you?
You were awake?
Nope. I saw it in my dreams.
In my dream, you kissed me as I slept.
Never mind that! Hurry up and eat!
Rice porridge with your favorite shiitake!
What?!
I relayed to the cook that shiitake are your absolute favorite food.
F-Forget you!
This is a problem.
When Nanami's cheeks blush as
she speaks of her feelings for me,
I cannot help but want to tease her.
Nanami...
Boof
Could I sleep in your room starting tonight?
What?
When I used to serve Lady Yonomori, she always let me sleep by her side.
Sure.
No.
I wasn't asking you.
What's the problem? It's a big room anyway.
Familiars have their own sleeping chamber.
Observe the rules.
Then you could just sleep with us too, Tomoe.
The three of us together.
I said no, and that is the end of it.
Tomoe's kind of in a bad mood today.
I wonder if he didn't really want to become a familiar.
Are you all right?!
I have not slept much in the past few days thanks to my matchmaking work.
That's a lie!
There are so many of them!
If you'll let me, I can help you out.
But don't you have your own work to do?
Not a problem.
I have thirty parishioners, so...
Oh... Oh...
Inaho...
Why do you sleep every year,
knowing that this will happen?
This incident...
Charging you to feed the carp and calling it water under the bridge...
The Lord Ookuninushi is most magnanimous.
Tomoe!
I've been allowed a little break!
Let's go shopping in the mundane world.
I've been in the world of the gods ever since I got here,
so I haven't done any sightseeing in Izumo.
Wow! The Grand Shrine in the
mundane world is super busy too!
The Gods in Residence Festival is right now.
Greeting
of the
Gods
Festival
Gods in
Residence
Festival
Izumo
Grand
Shrine
Paying
Respect
It's the same place, and yet...
It's different.
It's kind of magical.
It doesn't say stuff
like "Great Luck."
Izumo
Soba
Noodles
The mundane world is great!
The two of us, visiting a matchmaking a shrine, having soba noodles...
This almost feels like a date, doesn't it?
Nanami...
Do you still care for me?
What?
I... I do.
Oh...
It's different from before.
I see.
Oh, but...
I get it, okay?
You don't have any feelings for me.
I don't have the wrong idea about it or anything,
so don't worry, okay?
It's okay to pour the broth into the next...
Oh, pardon me, miss.
Ugh! I stink of soba broth!
I should've washed my other shirt!
Would it be bad to attend the Divine Assembly in a t-shirt?
Hell if I know.
This is what you get for not always being fully prepared.
Panicking in such situations...
Are you taking that off?!
Huh?
What's wrong?
I'm wearing a camisole underneath.
It's the kind you can go out in.
Who the hell just starts stripping in front of a man?!
Do it privately in the back!
Huh?
Y-You don't have to yell at me like that.
You've seen me in camis all the time around the shrine!
You've been acting like a jerk all day!
And that is completely your doing!
Even this morning, you spoke of sleeping with the snake. You lack discretion!
What if he were to jump you again as he did before?
What the heck? You worry too much.
If that's the case, you could just come sleep with us too.
Enough already!
Do you really have feelings for me?!
If you are content to merely speak of being in love and whatnot, go recite it to a wall on your own!
What is it?
Why are you mad, Tomoe?
I don't understand what I did or why you're so upset.
Tell me why.
I'll understand.
I am very sorry, Nanami.
I was wrong.
Please do not let it concern you anymore.
You will catch a cold if you remain in this wet shirt.
I will take it off for you.
Strip
That's okay! I'll do it myself!
You do not have to, though.
'Tis a familiar's duty to look after his lady and mistress.
What is the matter?
You are wearing a cami-whatever underneath, so you do not mind, right?
And tonight, I will sleep by your side as you wish.
I am a familiar, so there is nothing wrong with that, yes?
Well, Nanami?
Are you still okay with this?
Go to hell, Tomoe!
Seriously, why is it that foxes don't
consider the possible consequences?
Oh, this isn't about you, Tomoe. It's about this friend of mine who's also a fox.
Hey, would you listen to me
complain without falling asleep?
When I touch her, I can tell.
Like, me too...
You know how I'm a divine familiar, right?
The sweet warmth of her body...
But there are some things that aren't in my power...
Next part coming
right up
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Day seven of the Divine Assembly.
At long last, the final day.
There!
I've finished a hundred of them, Inaho.
Zzz...
She hasn't gotten a single person done since two hours ago!
We tried to warn you.
I'm
Nomi.
Nomi was the one who fell victim last year.
Hi, everyone! Are you getting your work done?
Ohtsukuri Hot Springs
Here, a souvenir.
Otohiko, what about your work?
I finished it long ago.
Once you finish, you gotta go have fun quick.
Otherwise, you get stuck doing the work of other gods too.
What a joke, am I right?
That's exactly the situation I'm in right now.
How has the Divine Assembly been for you?
Did you at least learn a thing or two?
Yeah.
It's kind of incredible.
A person's destiny is one thread,
which links up with various other people's destinies.
Yes. Destinies intertwine and create bonds.
Everything is linked from the past to the present.
There are steps leading to every encounter people have.
Which means that us talking here is the result of something that's long been in the making.
Come now. It's the final day of the Divine Assembly.
Let's finish up our work beautifully and
have a well-deserved drink at the banquet!
Inaho has...
Was I able to properly fulfill your duties in your stead,
Mikage?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Otohiko prepared this for me for the banquet, but...
Do I have the sash tied on right?
Hmm, it's a bit big on you.
Incompetent.
Do you mean to attend the banquet looking like that?
I will dress you. Strip.
Snap
Oh
Forget it.
I'll ask Lady Inaho for help.
Tomoe, are you daft?
So how does it feel?
I'm curious to know what that's like.
You have been awfully belligerent as of late.
Because I don't find this funny.
I don't want to lose the lady and mistress that I finally found.
Don't get carried away and elope or anything, okay?
Do not worry about such nonsense.
I have no intention of involving myself with a human.
The Divine Assembly has safely come to a close,
and tonight will be their last night at Izumo.
This is amazing!
It's a grand gathering of the gods!
Everyone looks like they're having fun!
Maybe I'll let my hair down too.
You should!
You must be tired, so I'll be your escort!
Little girl.
You look good in that.
Otohiko.
Thank you for the kimono!
It was my pleasure.
You were in shabby clothes every day of the
Divine Assembly, so I was worried, you know.
Lady Human Goddess,
your hard work in carrying out your duties is appreciated.
But sake for me is...
It is a sake cup from the Lord Ookuninushi.
You must drink.
What should I do?
Nanami cannot drink yet,
so I will have it.
What?
Sure, be the hunk, why don't you?
I wish Tomoe would just die.
What?!
Nothing!
I want something to drink too.
That's...
That butterfly is...
In the darkness...
The one who guided me...
It really...
was you.
Hello.
We meet again, Nanami.
Yes.
Thank you very much for what you did.
Mikage.
Your efforts here are appreciated.
You're a whole different person compared to a week ago.
You did good work, Nanami.
Nothing makes me happier than to hear you say so.
I'm grateful to you for being good to Tomoe.
Please keep looking after him for me.
Oh...
Does that mean you're not going to see Tomoe?
He won't say it outright, but he wants to see you.
I can't see him yet.
If I were to see Tomoe now, my twenty years of absence will have been for naught.
Until he completely ceases to need me, I have no intention of seeing him.
Do you know why love between humans and spirits is considered taboo?
No.
The reason humans can fall in love many times over is because their hearts change with time.
The human lifespan is so short that they do not have
the time to become bogged down by one attachment.
But it is different for spirit kind.
They live for a long time.
Their hearts do not waver, and they never forget.
They live with the same love in their hearts for centuries.
As such, they do not have changes of heart without good reason.
There are likely many who grow old without ever loving another.
To fall in love with someone, to need them, is a highly risky proposition for spirit kind.
That was true for Tomoe as well.
By that...
Are you referring to Yukiji?
Yes.
Tomoe has a lot of history behind him as well.
I've used my powers to make him forget for now,
but things can't remain this way forever.
Then why did you bring Tomoe and me together?
Tomoe believes that humans are fleeting and frail,
and he fears becoming involved with them.
I think that you can teach him that humans are not weak.
I want to rekindle Tomoe's bond with humanity.
To have him take your hand, not mine.
I want to allow Tomoe to choose you.
Mikage!
But it seems he still has a long way to go.
Hey, can you hear me?
That night, I was looking
at the fleeting remnants of the day
The milky way spread across my vision
It was very beautiful
Hey, can you hear me?
I don't think I can talk to other people about this
I'll call up God, I think
If a new day hadn't begun
then yesterday's tomorrow would be today
and yesterday would be the day before
I'm waiting for you
Preview
With the Divine Assembly finished,
Nanami agonizes over her love for Tomoe.
I'll stay here
The boat is stopped here
That's when she gets invited by Himemiko for a girls' day out.
This kid she ends up running into...
If today weren't today
Oh, dear! He's got wings!
Next time, "The God Meets a Little Crow."
The God Meets a Little Crow
and were that day instead, oh, that'd be nice
Wings Fling Hazard!