UNTIL WE MEET AGAIN IN KAMOGAWA! MADOKA &amp; LAN &amp; MUGINAMI
WE ARE THE SWEATS CLUB FOREVER MADOKA &amp; LAN &amp; MUGINAMI
I'll come to see you, Yurikano...
Time for some answers!
If words won't work, I'll let my fists do the talking!
That was my Kamogawa Dynamite Bomber, taught to me by my Sis!
You've trampled on Yurikano's feelings enough!
Don't you two get it by now?
You both mean a lot to Yurikano!
She hated seeing the two of you fight.
But you both did it again.
You let her down!
That's why Yurikano had to leave again.
Madoka...
Not just Yurikano!
You hurt Lan and Muginami too!
Don't you see that?!
You've failed as kings!
Back then we tried to fly with propellers that couldn't do it
We ran with bare feet, and now we see different skies
We always live
full of conviction
that we are misunderstood
You're precious to me
but lost at the same time
I'll get over it
Spin the wheel of fate
Inside the dew, like magic,
are tears and sunny days
I feel lonely now
I'm sure my dream will come true
and we will be together forever
A Vow Made in Kamogawa
We're told it was destroyed during the subspace distortion that took place in the fleet ship.
So now, everyone knows that Dizelmine was plotting to attack De Metrio
using the Vox and Yurikano.
It certainly looks that way.
Will you still proceed with the Intergalactic Conference as scheduled?
Yes.
But it appears Dizelmine will not be joining the conference.
After coming all this way...
Let's just hope this doesn't turn into a trial in absentia.
Did you come here to mock me?
I resorted to using my enemy's sister as part of my plan.
But instead, I was thrown off by her confession.
And now, I have lost everything.
Are you done moping yet?
Don't you get it?
Don't you two get it?
I don't know all the complicated details of the Polyhedron problem,
but there's still time, right?
In that case, why not work together to find a solution?
I think you're despicable!
Isn't that what she said?
Not only did that girl punch two kings,
she even lectured both of us.
How's that for completely losing face?
And it was a pretty good punch too.
Unfortunately, she's right.
It's not just you.
What the hell have we been doing this whole time?
I don't care about what you think of me.
But is what happened between us
really worth shedding so much blood and so many tears?
I became king because this time...
I wanted to move forward together with you for the sake of the Polyhedron.
Can you find it in yourself to forgive me?
Unless we resolve our differences, my sister won't find peace.
I see...
Here at the Kamogawa Municipal Auditorium,
the Polyhedron Intergalactic Conference is about to begin.
As each of the various Polyhedron representatives arrived,
Kamogawa was in a festive mood,
but yesterday's accident aboard the Le Garite flagship,
in satellite orbit above Earth, has caused an uproar.
Sorry we're late.
First, regarding to the Polyhedron problem,
the fact that the incident will not take place for another millennium
has led our thinking astray.
Or rather, I alone went astray.
As all of you gathered here are aware,
it was my decision alone to use the power of the Vox and to resort to force.
I'd like to use this opportunity to apologize.
Without a concrete plan to deal with the Polyhedron problem,
I believe that right now, the best we can do is put our heads together
to come up with a solution.
Therefore, as a first step, King Dizelmine and I will join forces
to bring our two nations, Le Garite and De Metrio, together
to reaffirm and renew friendly relations.
Come on.
Right...
Does this mean the relationship between the two kings has been resolved?
So they've declared a ceasefire?
A perfect example of friendship cemented by quarrels,
don't you think?
Looks like the girls won't have to go out on missions anymore.
It does seem that way.
As a start, King Dizelmine stated that henceforth,
Le Garite would not use the Vox to solve the Polyhedron 1000-year Problem.
Isn't it awesome?
Who could've predicted that the Intergalactic Conference
would take such an exciting turn!
I agree. This calls for a toast.
Right, Tadokoro?
Yes.
20,000 years ago, the people who fled Earth were scattered throughout the Universe.
Today, through a strange twist of fate,
their descendants have returned to this planet and become one again.
So, what became of the Vox Core possessed by Le Garite?
To be able to stand here at that historical moment is a truly joyous event for humankind!
Does this mean it's finally over?
Yeah, I guess it is..
No, let's hope it is.
We still have a mountain of problems ahead.
I don't know how much we'll be able to do,
but all we can do is try.
Yeah...
Hey!
I saw it on TV!
You guys buried the hatchet!
Did you come all this way just to tell us that?
Yup.
Absolutely!
We don't want to get punched like that again.
Right?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Per...?
Perfect!
Miss Madoka.
Huh?
What is it?
I have a favor to ask.
Just a minute!
Here!
Instead of asking me, you should just tell her yourself!
Huh?
Do it!
Lan,
I'm sorry.
Huh?
I've done a lot of things to you, without thinking about your feelings.
Don't...
You have a great opportunity to learn from this planet.
Make the best of it by enjoying it as much as you can.
Big Brother...
All I ask is that you earn outstanding grades befitting a royal family member.
I will!
You've made fine friends.
Yes, you're right...
Brother.
Oh?
You're back to calling me that again?
I've been meaning to ask...
Are you all right with this?
Huh?
What're you talking about?
I mean, Miss Yurikano is your real sister, and I'm...
I'm...
just a...
You idiot!
Stop thinking about silly things and just do your best!
I'll be your big brother until the day I die.
Right!
These are images of the Vox deployment that took place the other day.
Have you determined why the Vox launched without their pilots?
I don't know anything for sure yet.
What's your opinion?
It's conceivable that they launched in response to Miss Kyono, thinking she was in danger...
I see...
Wait! Why are you here?!
Didn't you go back?
That's cold.
I have the Chairman's permission to stay.
Oh?
I hear you have a number of questions.
Especially in regards to Princess Yurikano...
All right, let's start with what just happened to the Vox?
As I said, they responded to her thoughts.
I think it was more a result of their training.
The sympathetic resonance between Aura, Lympha and Ignis has increased.
I'll bring up the actual numbers.
Oh, this is...
To me, it appears as though they are reflecting the girls' relationship with one another.
There's something I'd like you all to see.
Huh? Where's the Chairman?
forever
the
ATS
CLUB
Lan
Muginami
We are
SWEATS
ATS
Madoka
Lan
the
I'm completely lost.
I don't understand math at all.
It doesn't really get any more basic than this.
I was behind in my studies, so I expected you to help me...
I suck!
My, my...
All this brainwork makes my brain feel like it's going to explode.
Let's take a break!
Huh?
But we just took one.
Here. Snacks.
Wow! Baked sweet potatoes?
Good call, Madoka!
That aside...
What's with them?
Those three reek of depression.
I hope it's not contagious.
I think it's because of how Lady Yurikano disappeared.
It must've have hit them pretty hard.
Why are those three so committed to Yurikano?
The four of them were together
during their time at the Academy, so...
You think they were in love with Yurikano?
Hey...
Have either of you ever been in love before?
Huh?
W-What? Why do you ask?!
Muginami, why're you so flustered?
I-I'm not flustered....
See, back there, I was able to feel Yurikano's emotions very clearly.
About how much she cared about Lan's brother.
That must be love, right?
Wow...
Does that mean you know what love feels like, Madoka?
You're growing up, Madoka.
W-What?!
Even I know that much!
I think it's a bit different than loving baked sweet potatoes!
What?!
But why did Yurikano tell Lan's brother that
she thought he was despicable at the very end?
I wonder how your brother felt when she told him that?
I don't know.
My brother isn't one to show his feelings.
I sort of feel...
The moment you put feelings that you've kept inside you into words,
those feelings disappear.
That's why I can understand why he doesn't want to put his feelings into words.
What?!
Isn't it better to come right out and say that you love a person?
I'm sure they know.
If they share those feelings for each other,
they don't have to say it.
That's what I think, too.
All this is pretty grown-up stuff...
It's going over my head.
I've fallen behind in this too.
You'll be fine!
Here!
You have this, Madoka.
Hey! Stop making fun of me!
I've experienced one or two loves.
And another something else...
Huh?
What is it?
That makes three total.
That's not what I meant.
I realized one more thing that day, as well.
In her heart, Yurikano cares deeply not just for Lan's brother,
but for Big Brother Giuvi, Izo, Kirius, Array,
and for all of us, as well.
That's why it's our turn to answer Yurikano's feelings.
Can you two come with me for a second?
It's so beautiful!
It always feels great up here.
Lan,
what're you looking for?
Until
we meet
again
in Kamogawa
Madoka
Is that the one you two...?
We vow...
that we will meet again in Kamogawa some day.
You too, Lan!
Huh?
All right. I vow too.
Good.
As long as this lock remains here,
we must honor our vow, no matter what.
Looks like we made good on our vow, huh?
Yes.
And so!
Madoka?
I brought the three of us here again because I thought we could make a new vow.
A new vow?
What will we vow?
I'm thinking we should vow never to go to battle using the Vox again.
Those two made up, right?
There shouldn't be any more reasons to fight.
I, Madoka Kyono, vow on this lock:
that I will never use Midori as a weapon, ever again.
And I vow that neither Hupo nor I will ever fight again!
I vow here to use Orca for peace!
And!
Until we make good on our vow,
I will not graduate from the Sweats Club!
You sound so gung-ho, Madoka, but with your low grades,
isn't there a chance you might not graduate at all?
Huh? How can you say that?!
We are
for
ever
the
SW
EATS
CLUB
Madoka
Lan
Muginami
This is something we've discovered recently.
Is this a Vox?
Yes, it's likely.
We're currently deciphering its origin and the meaning of these ancient characters.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
He insisted on seeing it with us.
I brought a gift for you: milk buns.
Can you take a look at this?
What's wrong?
Please excuse me for a moment.
Continue with the analysis.
Understood.
You know what's written on that stone tablet, don't you?
It's a... record of my sins.
As you know, the Rinne has caused two tragedies in the past.
One is the Tragedy of Militia Zodia, brought about by Yurikano,
when she attempted to seal away her powers.
The other happened 20,000 years ago...
when the Earth was nearly destroyed when the Rinne blossomed.
The one who caused that tragedy...
was Queen Maycun.
And that would be you.
Hey, Sweats Club members!
Yes!
Mind helping us out after school today?
Sure. Consider it done!
Our club is back to three members again, so ask away!
That's a big help.
Just leave it to the Sweats Club! Right?
Woof.
Roger that!
Perfect!
The Sweats Club spirit! The Sweats Club spirit!
I won't leave you alone, hello and let's be cheery!
Who cares what's correct right now
First things first
Here in front of me is someone
who carries around a billion issues
I won't just shut up and leave you be
Lie down a while and you're fine again
Let's just stretch
I'm tired
Here, have some Kamogawa Energy
I'm back!
It's good to drink it all
It's good to drink two
Don't worry how much I drink
You ask me why I do so much for you
Isn't that obvious?
I do it because your dreams are wonderful!
The Sweats Club spirit! The Sweats Club spirit!
I want to help you, hello and let's be cheery!
What's wrong, Lan?
I felt like I was being watched just now.
Could that be the girl who's been around since "Days"?!
Question! What do you mean by "Days"?
It refers to "Kamogawa Days", also known as episode 12.5.
We've been watched for that long?!
No, you've got it wrong!
That's how long she's been in the background.
Kamogawa Balloons
You're not making any sense!