Okay!
I'm off!
Have some Kamogawa Soup.
It's good.
Thank you.
Thanks for waiting!
Shall we get going?
Yes.
We're heading out!
Where?
Isn't it obvious? To get revenge!
Why?
What do you mean, "why"?
Hey Uncle, look after her for us!
What?
Giuvigiuvio...
I swear...
You're going down!
Lag-Rin, Lag-Rin
That girl wearing sweats is somehow special
When she takes it off, she can be anything
In search of things she treasures, she'd go to the bottom of the ocean
She's brash to a fault and difficult for those around her
Lag-rin, Lag-rin
I'll come meet you right away
when I hear you call for help
Perfect!
Live life!
Rewrite fate and fly,
Fly away
On a brighter day
If sticking your tongue out and walking proudly gets you in trouble
burn and fly away
Try unite tonight
Lovely, lovely
The Wind, Fire, and Water Above Kamogawa
Sorry to keep you waiting, sir. I'm ready now!
Midori, taking off!
Kyono...
Yes, sir!
Who said we're going to attack?
What? But I just said it, sir!
Listen, that doesn't mean you can just get up and go.
Besides, how do you expect to win when you don't even have a strategy?
The one who makes the first move wins!
That's the first rule of the Sweats Club!
Get out of the cockpit and standby! That's all.
Hey, wait!
Now explain it to me again from the beginning.
So if we don't destroy all three Vox units,
he'll destroy them along with Pharos?
His objective is pretty clear.
What sort of person are we dealing with?
Did he really come all this way just to declare war on us?
He's debris.
Debris?
Space trash.
More accurately, he's ex-royalty from a planet that shared a longstanding alliance with us.
However, currently he's the leader of a criminal group that calls itself "Kiss".
You could say he's the enemy mastermind.
How the mighty has fallen.
You said we have until tomorrow morning.
Calculating the time since sunset yesterday,
that leaves us with only five hours.
Let's say we listen to his demand and destroy all the Vox.
Do you think the enemy will leave Earth peacefully?
Of course not.
We'll just be losing our only means of defense.
I got lost! This place is too big!
Mr. Tadokoro! You need to hear me out!
Muginami is my—
All right. That's enough.
"That's enough"?
Ms. Watabe, please find a safe area on the sea that is suitable for battle.
We'll head there once all civilian personnel have been evacuated from this ship.
I'm on it.
James, report the situation to every branch of the Foundation.
Coordinate with them to make absolutely sure
no ship or aircraft enters the airspace where the fighting will take place.
Roger!
Uehara...
Hurry and complete final checks on both Vox units
so that Kyono and Laffinty can fly at any time.
Roger!
Don't just stand there.
Huh?
We're going to fight to the bitter end!
Perfect!
Let's go, Lan!
I'm sure you understand,
but this doesn't mean you may attack immediately.
Woof.
I'm leaving the rest to you.
Yes sir!
Get revenge?
That's what this email from Dad says.
What's wrong?
No, never mind. It's nothing.
I don't understand this guy Villagiulio.
What do you mean?
Why did he bother to come all the way here?
Oh, now that you mention it...
Ta-dah!
What is that?
Let's drink it
and find out!
Hey, what's the big idea?!
It's so good!
Try some. It hits the spot!
No, I think I'll...
Then I'll try some.
It's important to try stuff like this
so you can get to know your enemy.
Kirius!
It tastes pleasant and refreshing at first.
But the moment it hits your stomach,
this overpowering sweetness hits.
I was right, Izo.
This planet cannot be underestimated!
Man, you're so dramatic.
It's pretty good, isn't it?
Hey, what did you go down there for anyway?
Two more hours 'til dawn.
You'll find out then.
What time is it?
Rest while you can or your body won't hold up.
I'll be just fine!
I'm fully charged with Energy!
Do you think she's all right?
You mean Muginami?
Well, knowing her,
I'm sure she won't let something like that get to her...
Of course it would! It would get to anyone!
I guess you're right.
Anyone would react that way after being told such a horrible thing.
He didn't use to be like that.
He was so noble
and caring.
The past doesn't matter!
After all, I don't know about that Giuvigiuvi's past!
Yes... You're right, Madoka.
Right now, I have every reason to fight him!
Let's kick his butt!
Then... here!
Let's get fully charged!
Thank you.
My wife... well, she's my ex-wife now.
But she also had quite a sharp tongue.
She always let me have an earful.
To be honest, it hurts even now, especially when I'm feeling lonely.
But during times like that...
And who might you be?
I'm from Novumundus Japan.
Novumundus Foundation Japan
International Management Group Chief Advisor
Balance T. Moid
Novumundus Foundation Japan
International Management Group Chief Advisor
Balance T. Moid
Novumundus Foundation Japan
International Management Group Chief Advisor
Balance T. Moid
If you're here for Madoka, she already left.
I have some business with her.
Enemy unit presence confirmed. All hands to battle stations.
I repeat...
What is the enemy mother ship's position?
It's maintaining relative velocity with this ship
and hovering above satellite tracking range.
Then why aren't they attacking?
I thought I ordered all noncombatant personnel off this ship.
Oh, don't mind us.
I'm related to that girl.
Put me on speaker with the two pilots.
It's almost daybreak.
The enemy is right above us.
They're practically sitting on top of us and we can't run or hide.
By the way, what's wrong with Laffinty?
It seems she drank too much Energy.
Aren't you supposed to dilute that stuff before drinking it?
I'm all right.
I'm good to go.
Just remember your previous battle.
The two of you can do this!
Attack!
Opening barrier walls numbers one and two.
Pilot's heart rate, blood pressure, respiratory rate, all normal.
Opening the top hatch.
A.I. Remote Systems are normal.
All systems go.
Vox Aura, Vox Lympha, take off!
Let's go, Midori!
Orca! Taking off!
It's not dawn yet, you two.
Madoka!
Are you kidding me?
Confirming multiple Ovid units launched from the enemy ship.
Their numbers are...
What is it?
The two Vox crafts are about to make contact with the enemy units!
Get the weapon prototypes ready for launch, now!
Yes, sir!
Where are Madoka and Lan?
They took off to get revenge for you.
Normally, one shouldn't sympathize with the enemy.
But after hearing your story,
even I felt like punching that man.
Villagiulio is a terrible man.
A subordinate risks her life to sneak behind enemy lines
and manages to steal their treasure.
Yet he shows no remorse in discarding her, simply because she acted against his wishes.
Even though he was aware of your sincere feelings for him.
How ungrateful of him.
Doesn't he realize that not everyone can achieve Memoria?
Hey, you have some neat stuff!
Be careful.
Thanks!
Man! There's no end to this!
Help is on its way.
Moid?
Cap!
There's someone in the cockpit of Ignis!
Put it up on the monitor!
Her?!
Get her off now!
I can't!
She's already entered the T.O. sequence!
She's taking off!
Brother...
I'm serious!
If you don't stop me now...
This will really, really
be goodbye!
Muginami?
She doesn't know when to give up.
Ignis's Vox System has been activated.
We can no longer control it with the A.I. Remote!
I find her to be quite gifted.
Don't you agree?
Who asked you to...?
You can scold me later.
Just what's so funny?
Brother, if this means goodbye...
It's okay... I'll just...
Is she planning to go in alone?!
Muginami!
Let's go!
Right...
Hold it.
You boys standby.
What are you talking about?
Are you planning to take on those three by yourself?
Harem night!
Oh wait. It's almost morning, huh?
It's another manned enemy craft!
Henceforth, it will be identified as enemy unit four!
That must be the one that appeared in Kamogawa last night.
Brother!
It's him!
This is goodbye.
Brother...
Giuvigiubaro!
Madoka!
Stop, Madoka!
It's my fault for acting on my own
without ever thinking about Brother's feelings!
Brother isn't to blame!
This is all my fault!
You...
stupid girl!
Are you still defending him after what he said to you?!
You should forget about someone like him.
You have no right to say that!
You don't know anything about me!
You haven't considered my feelings one bit!
No one asked you to get my revenge!
You talk big about wanting to help other people,
but the Sweats Club and everything you do...
You're only doing it for your own selfish reasons!
So that's what you think about me?
Until today...
This whole time?
Hey, what is that?
It can't be...
Yes, that's it.
Hey, what's...?
Madoka!
Is this what Villagiulio was really after?
Impossible! But for what purpose?
Or... is this just a coincidence?
The Rin-Ne has blossomed!
I'll never forget that the soul in my chest would never yield
Don't cry
Promise me, okay
Promise me you'll never cry alone
We will always be together, you know
If we do get sad, we will share our sadness
and be stronger through it
Yay yay yay!
I'll laugh soon, my friend
My friend!
This isn't for just anyone, you're special
I am sure of my own emotions
With an upright voice, I say
Hello!
Sing the song that you always sing
and put a little bit of courage into my heart
Yay
My sweats are gone!
Look in your bag.
It's not there!
What about the washing machine?
It's not there. Maybe someone stole them?
Muginami?
Did you...?
I didn't steal it.
Return it.
Now, now, Lan.
I didn't take it. I just tried it on, that's all.
But it was really tight around my chest...
Cloudy Skies, Followed by Kamogawa