I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Lag-Rin, Lag-Rin
That girl wearing sweats is somehow special
When she takes it off, she can be anything
In search of things she treasures, she'd go to the bottom of the ocean
She's brash to a fault and difficult for those around her
Lag-rin, Lag-rin
I'll come meet you right away
when I hear you call for help
Perfect!
Live life!
Rewrite fate and fly,
Fly away
On a brighter day
If sticking your tongue out and walking proudly gets you in trouble
burn and fly away
Try unite tonight
Lag-rin, Lag-rin
Cloudy Skies, Followed By Kamogawa
I told you, didn't I?
That you shouldn't trust her too much.
Do you agree with her?
That everything I do is for myself.
Do you also think of me that way?
Do you?
Of course not!
Of course not, but...
It's true that Muginami didn't ask me
to get revenge for her...
Because you're a parasite.
But that Giuvigiuvio said such a horrible thing to her!
It's Villagiulio.
How could she defend him and get mad at me for wanting to punish him?
I just don't understand her!
Whoa!
Hey, stop! This one's mine!
It's mine!
Shouldn't we detain her?
Whatever the reason,
Muginami's actions yesterday were nothing short of hostile.
I couldn't find her Star Registration code
among the planets aligned under the Polyhedron.
This implies that she comes from Planet U-Go, a remote penal colony.
And?
Unfortunately, that planet did not sign
the Organball Human Rights Treaty.
Meaning?
Any misstep in dealing with her could result
in diplomatic problems between our planets.
And besides, you saw what happened between those girls, didn't you?
In Le Garite, adults stay out of fights among children.
Is it different on Earth?
One more thing.
About that strange phenomenon that occurred with Vox Aura...
Research facilities worldwide observed an emission of abnormal energy.
What were those flowers that rained down back there—?
Don't get me wrong.
We don't know everything about the Vox either, Captain Tadokoro.
Just what does she see in Vigiuvigiuo anyway?
It's Villagiulio.
His hair is messy and he's very rude.
Awesome
Coat
Sold Out
And his taste in fashion sucks!
I thought Uncle Hiroshi was the only one in the universe who'd want a coat like that!
But I was wrong. There was someone else!
How could Muginami fall for someone like him?!
It just doesn't make any sense.
Don't you think so, Lan?
Lan?
He wasn't like that before.
Huh?
The Villagiulio I knew
wasn't like that when he was the crown prince of De Metrio...
A crown prince?!
Stop! You damn brat!
I said wait!
Wait, you brat!
Everyone thought he would be the one...
Not just the people of De Metrio.
The people of Le Garite thought so too.
Including me.
We all believed that he and my brother Dizelmine
would bring peace to the Polyhedron.
No way! Is Villagiuvio really that great of a guy?!
You're close...
Are you sure we're talking about the same person?
Yes... But he's changed.
The last time I remember him smiling was
when De Metrio and Le Garite were still close allies.
That was a long time ago.
Kyono!
Yes?!
So this is where you were.
I'm sorry. I was late because I had some space issues to deal with...
Oh wait, school's already over.
Never mind that.
Sweats Club, move out!
Okay...?
Get moving, Kyono.
So let me get this straight.
The Cooking Club is planning to host
Kamo Girls'
Autumn Hunger!
Gourmet Fighter Manmano
Eel
BBQ Party
This
Year's
Again This Year!!
Event
Date!
Location: Home Ec Room
a School Eel BBQ party in two days...
But when the fish shop brought over the eels,
they dumped it into the school pool thinking it was being used as fish preserve.
Is that right?
We need the Sweats Club's help in catching the eels.
Uh-huh...
We managed to catch most of them, but...
No!
As you can see, the girls are starting to lose their spirit.
Well, that's too bad.
By the way, where's Muginami?
Isn't she a member too?
W-Well...
We don't need her!
The two of us can easily manage something like this!
Let's get this over with, Lan!
Okay...
No, Madoka!
Don't run along the poolside. It's dangerous!
Kamo Girls!
Fight, fight, fight!
Fight, fight—
Here...
Got it.
Hey, stop it!
No, get off me!
My brother will get mad if he sees me like this!
Hey, come on!
Don't just sit up there!
Help us out, Ms. Machiko!
Say, Kyono.
Yes?
Tell me...
Where are your sweats?
And your signature front ponytail?
What happened?
I'm curious.
Did you leave it behind somewhere?
Your Sweats Club Spirit, that is.
Oh, not you too, Ms. Machiko.
I already have Muginami telling me weird stuff about...
You haven't considered my feelings one bit!
No one asked you to get revenge!
Oh no...
Madoka?
I wasn't listening to her.
Muginami was telling me how she felt all along.
You know the drill, right?
If you realize that you were wrong...
Apologize right away!
When you make up your mind?
Act on it!
But finish this job first, okay?
Lan, how many are left?
Huh? Um...one more.
Madoka! Watch out!
Madoka?!
Score!
I don't have a spare bra or underwear, so I'll just wear my sweats without them!
Wait, Madoka!
I can't!
No matter what he did to her, Muginami still stuck to her feelings of wanting to protect Villagiuvio!
That was close!
That means Muginami was full of Sweats Club spirit!
And I just picked a fight with her, forgetting what was most important!
I have to get back to Pharos and tell her!
Muginami, I...!
Madoka, listen...!
Um...
You first, Madoka.
Huh? Uh... Well... Umm...
You see... Uh...
Taking a nice hot bath at home is definitely better than using the showers at school.
You know, I never took a bath when I was a child.
Huh?
A place where all the garbage, trash, hatred,
and despair in the universe end up.
That's the kind of place Planet U-Go, my birthplace, was like.
There was only winter.
With a thick cloud hanging over our heads endlessly.
It was a colorless place.
Huh?
Aren't you going to take a bath with them?
Really? Then would you mind taking them towels?
No one trusted each other.
We were all desperate to protect ourselves.
It was all we could do, just to survive.
From as far as I could remember, the only emotion I knew was suffering.
I didn't know that there was anything else in this world.
Until I met Brother.
Villangiulion?
Villagiulio...
Brother taught me how to smile.
How to feel joy and heartache...
How to love someone...
He was the only reason I kept on living.
That's why I...
I'm sorry, Madoka!
I should be saying that.
I'm sorry, Muginami.
Where are you going?
Do you have somewhere to go to?
It's none of your business, Lan.
Yes, it is.
I'm the princess of the planet that deposed Villagiulio.
I don't expect you to accept me.
But Madoka is different.
Don't hurt her feelings by leaving without saying a word!
Don't you know that you're already like family to her?
There's no way she would...
You are family, Muginami!
We live under the same roof and share our meals.
We've slept side-by-side and taken a bath together!
Of course, you're family!
Are you listening, Muginami?
But I did a terrible thing!
Madoka, Lan, to both of you...
Can I really stay in this town with you two?
Is it really okay?!
Of course!
That's why these are my words too.
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
I don't understand you,
Muginami. Why? - Madoka
Thank you for thinking
about me. - Muginami
Thank you for becoming part of my family.
But... I didn't get to take a bath.
Huh?
To be honest, I wanted to take a bath with you too.
Come again?
In...
In Le Garite, when you become part of the family, everyone must take a bath together!
I don't think so.
Yes, it is!
I, Princess Laffinty, made the rule!
I just decided right now!
So we have to bathe... the three of us!
But isn't going completely nude here a little too bold?
No, it's not.
Let's bathe right now!
See?
That's a huge bath!
I'm going in...
First!
Yay!
Well then,
I'm going in second!
Hey! Wait for me!
Here I come!
Oh, how cute!
Thank you!
Well, you're all working so hard.
It's a way to show my appreciation.
Are you kidding me?
You expect us to wear this at work?
It's so embarrassing!
That's not true, Madoka!
You look like a waitress!
Huh?
Y-You think so?
I'm a bit embarrassed too.
It's a difficult style for you to wear.
Maybe I shouldn't have stopped you from leaving.
I mean, you have to have the right curves in the right places.
Hey, what're you doing?
There... That's more like it, huh?
Hey, what about breakfast?
I'll just eat this!
We're off!
I'll never forget that the soul in my chest would never yield
Don't cry
Promise me, okay
Promise me you'll never cry alone
We will always be together, you know
If we do get sad, we will share our sadness
and be stronger through it
Yay yay yay!
I'll laugh soon, my friend
My friend!
This isn't for just anyone, you're special
I am sure of my own emotions
With an upright voice, I say
Hello!
Sing the song that you always sing
and put a little bit of courage into my heart
Yay
I have a quiz for you!
What is it, all of a sudden?
Ever since I came to Earth, I've been nurturing a beautiful dream.
What is that dream?
You can tell us the answer.
Here's a hint: Kamogawa Sea World.
Tick, tick, tick... Too bad, time's up.
The answer is: Riding on the back of a killer whale.
A Lolita in Kamogawa
Ooh...