Give me a status report!
Ships from Le Garite and De Metrio are exchanging fire.
One of De Metrio's ships has lost control and is falling into our atmosphere.
It's coming down near this ship.
That's...!
A De Metrio ship?
What happened?
It was attacked!
Hey!
Ships that have lost their subspace fields can go ahead and break formation!
Tell them to avoid returning fire as much as possible!
Any response from Le Garite?
We're trying all channels, but they continue to maintain silence.
What's the meaning of this, Dizelmine?!
How could I even think of breaking my vow
and cease pursuit of my own path?
I had already decided that day to defeat him, and return the Polyhedron to its rightful form.
I will now fulfill my duty as king.
Back then we tried to fly with propellers that couldn't do it
We ran with bare feet, and now we see different skies
We always live
full of conviction
that we are misunderstood
You're precious to me
but lost at the same time
I'll get over it
Spin the wheel of fate
Inside the dew, like magic,
are tears and sunny days
I feel lonely now
I'm sure my dream will come true
and we will be together forever
Betrayal over the
skies of Kamogawa
Again, we repeat:
The government has just announced that hostilities have broken out
between De Metrio and Le Garite forces in orbit above Earth.
As a result of this fighting, a De Metrio ship has crash-landed on Earth.
Authorities are investigating the extent of the damage.
The government has called an emergency session
to seek immediate answers
from both De Metrio and Le Garite...
What do you think is going to happen now?
Incoming call: Dad
Dad?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm aboard Pharos.
Huh?! Right now?!
I see. Understood.
Effective immediately,
route all communications through here.
We received a communiqué
from De Metrio's trade representative.
What did they say?
Apparently, Le Garite has commenced simultaneous attacks throughout the entire Polyhedron.
What are you trying to do, Dizelmine?
You're going in Orca, aren't you?
I'm going to find out what happened.
If this is something your brother started...
We don't know that for sure, yet.
But if it is?
I don't know.
But if he did...
We'll have to find out for sure, won't we?
Muginami...
After that, we'll just wing it.
Lan, it's too risky going alone, so I'll go with you.
What took you two so long!
Madoka?!
Are you planning to head for Dizelmine's ship alone?!
Don't look at me like that.
You'll get wrinkles.
Just kidding.
At this rate, the entire Polyhedron will become embroiled in conflict.
I need to ask Dizelmine himself if that's his true intention.
With all due respect...!
You'll be in charge of the fleet until I return.
Lord Villagiulio...
Stop giving me that look.
I'll be right back.
De Metrio Lu Villagiulio...
Let's go, Arvirium!
A single Ovid has left the De Metrio flagship.
It's headed this way.
It's Villagiulio.
How predictable can that man get?
Your orders?
I will deal with him myself.
It's a courtesy I extend as king.
Understood.
King Dizelmine will be leaving.
Prepare Magoltul for launch!
Yes, sir! Preparing Magoltul for launch!
Dizelmine!
Not even a warning?
Some greeting!
Simply telling you wouldn't have convinced you, right?
Were you two going to leave me behind like the last time?
No, that wasn't our intention...
But this is between Le Garite and De Metrio...
That's where you're wrong!
Lan, you don't get it at all!
You and Muginami are my comrades!
Your problems are my problems!
If you're sad, I'm sad.
If you're happy, then I'm happy, too!
Does that make me sound creepy to you?
No, we never said that.
Besides, the three of us together vowed never to use our Vox for battle.
If we're going to break that vow,
the three of us have to break it together!
Madoka's right.
Muginami...
If the two of you were in trouble, I'd do the same thing!
Wouldn't you do the same, Lan?
Woof!
Big Sis?!
You're going to fly, aren't you?
Yeah.
I see...
Dad!
Hey.
Uncle Hiroshi?
He insisted on coming.
I packed you lunches, in case you get hungry.
Uncle...
I told him this wasn't a picnic, but...
Thank you, Boss.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Uncle Hiroshi.
The three of you are the pretty faces that bring business to my shop.
Don't go getting yourselves hurt, now.
Come back safely, so I can see your happy faces again.
Got that?
Yeah.
Yes.
We'll be going, then.
Okay! Now go get 'em, girls!
Let's go, Midori!
Orca, let's fly together once more.
I'm counting on you, Hupo.
Dizelmine!
Are you serious about starting a war?!
That's a stupid question.
What?!
Have I ever, even for a moment, stopped fighting to protect the Polyhedron?
Lord Villagiulio! We're sending support immediately!
Cancel that order!
Roger!
We'll...what?!
As long as he's saying that he's doing this for the sake of Polyhedron...
Then I must trust him, more than anyone!
Regardless of how badly I want to kill this bastard!
Lord Villagiulio...
Lady Grania!
What is it?!
A ship is emerging from warp up ahead!
More enemy ships?!
Why are you being so shy right now?
Quit hiding and show yourself!
Come on, I'm willing to listen to what you want to do with the Polyhedron, just like old times!
Damn!
You owe me one.
That you, Izo?!
Great, who is it this time?
That's some pretty sorry flying for the king of De Metrio.
Lax Lestorine Ha Kirius, here to assist in the name of honor.
What're you guys doing?
Who asked for your help?
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm only here to protect Kamogawa.
Kamogawa?!
I don't want this ocean to meet the same fate as De Metrio.
What a coincidence.
Same as us.
We knew a battle had begun
when we first came out of warp.
That's when Kirius said we were heading back to Earth.
He started threatening
the captain of the spaceship to turn back.
I didn't threaten him, I convinced him.
Right...
You "convinced" him by sticking a sword to his throat.
Relax.
We won't get in the way of any direct talks
between you two monarchs.
Let's go!
We won't allow anyone to destroy Kamogawa!
Feel the power of my swordsmanship
polished by the wild seas!
What's your next move, Dizelmine?
It's just the two of us now.
What do you say, let's be honest with each other?
Luckily, Moid's not here.
Moid? What are you talking about?
Don't try to hide it.
We have intel.
What's he been telling you this time-?
Are you insinuating that he made me do this?
Dizel...
It was all my own decision!
Me! The King of Le Garite!
A mode change?!
I'm getting a Vox reading that's not in our database!
What?!
Are you sure it's not a sensor error?
No, I'm positive!
Are you saying there's another Vox aside from Yurikano's Core?
Do you realize what you've done?!
Do you really want to control this world so badly?!
I listened to your plan to achieve peace through talks.
Not just once, but twice.
But to me, your vision of the future holds nothing but flaws,
and will end in failure.
What's needed is power!
You intend to create the world by yourself?!
You need to listen to other opinions—
I have no need of other opinions!
Especially not from the likes of you, who's only interested in personal gain!
Big Brother! Are you all right?!
Yeah...
Of course, nothing I say will convince you, when I look like this.
Madoka...
Laffinty...
Hold on, this is between me and...
No, Big Brother.
This is also our problem now.
Brother, please stop this.
Laffinty...
It's not like you to do things this way!
You love peace more than anyone.
More than anyone,
you wished happiness for the people of Le Garite and the Polyhedron!
Remember, life is a miracle!
Don't act like you know me!
You damn...idiot!
The enemy Vox has crash-landed on Maebara Beach.
She went for an axe kick right off the bat...
That was a roundhouse kick to the head.
An enzuigiri...
Vox particle readings are increasing.
You have the nerve to attack your own sister?!
Why? What's going on?
Why is this happening?!
I thought you'd made up with Big Brother Giuvi!
I thought you'd vowed to work together!
Answer me, Lan's brother!
Dizelmine!
I wasn't the one who betrayed the other first...
He was.
Huh?
Dizelmine...
He sided with them...
The people I despise more than anyone!
The ones who tried to destroy the peace of the Polyhedron,
by defying me with force!
Wait a minute!
That was a long time ago—!
Why did you do it, Villagiulio?!
Why?!
You, of all people, should have known!
The many sacrifices our ancestors had to make
to build the peace and stability that we have today!
Brother?
That life is a miracle in itself!
Dizelmine?!
What the—?!
Get me a damage report immediately!
What happened to Madoka and the others?
We're checking on them now.
No...
The Circle of Rinne...
"Feeding off a tainted heart..."
Oww!
Brother?
Big...Brother?
Screw the Polyhedron.
At this point, all I care about is killing you!
Big...Brother...
Big Brother!
Research institutes around the world are reporting changes in quantum particle levels!
What's starting to happen?
The same thing that happened 20,000 years ago.
If this continues, Earth...
No, the entire universe will be...
This is terrible.
Beyond terrible.
If you plan on doing anything more...
We will not forgive you!
Look out!
Let's go, Lan! Muginami!
The demon has risen!
Huh?
What?!
Madoka! Lan?!
On the water's surface I see a light reflected that stirs my heart
When we realized our bond,
we were already deeply connected under the blue sky
We had so much fun, as in a daze, that time seemed forgotten
I prayed that there would be no end to the way we lived
I won't forget our days together, although time goes by,
and you are far from me now,
because you left behind a wonderful world
for me to wait in
Okay, I have to admit.
We're in big trouble!
Where are we?
Could it be the nether world?
Did we die?
Madoka, could it be that we're inside the Rinne?
Yes, and the problem is...
There's no bathroom here.
Beyond the seas of Kamogawa
That's your problem?