Sachi, did you just see anyone leaving?
Huh?
I didn't see anyone.
Okay!
That's all for today!
P.E. monitor, please put everything away.
Roger that!
Huh?
Was there someone watching me just now?
Who's there?
Someone was just here.
I'm telling you, I'm positive someone was watching me!
Me, too.
Ditto to the right.
You're to the left.
I'm to your right!
Oh dear, do think it was a pervert or a stalker?
At an all-girl school?
Isn't that all the more reason?
Lately, I've felt like someone's eyes were on me.
It's suspicious that all three of us would feel the same way.
Do you think someone is after us?
Madoka.
Shoko?
Uhh... about the Sweats Club...
What is it? Does a club need our help?
No, it's not that.
The other day, the Student Council decided to reassign clubrooms.
And well...
You know that storage room the Sweats Club is using?
Could you vacate it?
Oh come on, Shoko.
That's not for storage, it's our clubhouse.
You want us out?!
Back then we tried to fly with propellers that couldn't do it
We ran with bare feet, and now we see different skies
We always live
full of conviction
that we are misunderstood
You're precious to me
but lost at the same time
I'll get over it
Spin the wheel of fate
Inside the dew, like magic,
are tears and sunny days
I feel lonely now
I'm sure my dream will come true
and we will be together forever
Kamogawa Balloons
You're kicking us out of our clubhouse?
But why?
You can't just tell us to leave suddenly. I won't go along with it.
We won't stand for the abuse of the student government!
The thing is,
the Sweats Club is not a formal, school-authorized club.
What?
You all know that, right?
Huh?
Is this true, Madoka?
Oh!
We might not be an official club!
I'm glad you understand...
Maybe we're not a club, but a group?
There, there.
You have it rough.
Huh? Huh?
Huh?
Common sense says
the school would never approve the Sweats Club's activities.
If they did,
that'd be like one of the "Seven Wonders" of the school.
But even so...
But we've been the Sweats Club
ever since our big sis Yoko started it!
The school never had any complaints.
Until now, they kept things under the rug and let things slide.
This school's too laid back.
I'm sorry it turned out like this.
That's okay.
It's not your fault, Shoko.
Besides, even without a clubhouse,
we're still the Sweats Club.
But I'm going to miss our clubhouse.
I know.
I thought that the Sweats Club and that room would always be there.
Hey, I just had a good idea!
We'll get the Sweats Club formally approved!
Oh...
Yeah, sounds like a plan.
How about it? Then there'd be no problem, right?
Well, yes, but to be approved as a club,
you need a minimum of four club members.
We can manage to find one more!
Sure.
Or you could always create a phantom member.
Phantom?!
However, of the four, at least one member
has to be a first or second-year student, or you won't be approved.
Then we'll find someone!
Won't you please come and join the Sweats Club?
Help preserve the tradition at Kamo Girls High.
The Sweats Club is currently recruiting new members!
Come join the Sweats Club!
We're gathering new members.
What's that?
You know, the Sweats Club?
I heard it was a famous group of weirdos.
Not weirdos. I heard aliens.
Come join the sweats club!!
Miss K-Kyono!
Yes?
I-I'm a first-year in group 3, student number 29, Reiko Miki!
Oh! Such a formal greeting.
Third-year, group 3, student number 7, Madoka Kyono.
I've been watching you.
Huh?
Then, that person who's been following us around, was that—
Yes, that was me!
Miss Kyono,
please let me join the Sweats Club!
What?
I wasn't expecting this to happen.
Well isn't this great, Madoka?
She's so stunned, she can't move.
Are you sure about this, Reiko?
Yes!
Please be good to me.
We did it!
We have a new member!
A new member!
Ootadai
Kamanuma
Oyama Fuduson
Ootadai
Kamanuma
Oyama Fuduson
Ootadai
Kamanuma
Oyama Fuduson
Ootadai
Kamanuma
Oyama Fuduson
Ootadai
Kamanuma
Oyama Fuduson
Ootadai
Kamanuma
Oyama Fuduson
Ootadai
Kamanuma
Oyama Fuduson
Ootadai
Kamanuma
Oyama Fuduson
Ootadai
Kamanuma
Oyama Fuduson
Ootadai
Kamanuma
Oyama Fuduson
Ootadai
Kamanuma
Oyama Fuduson
Ootadai
Kamanuma
Oyama Fuduson
Ootadai
Kamanuma
Oyama Fuduson
Ootadai
Kamanuma
Oyama Fuduson
Ootadai
Kamanuma
Oyama Fuduson
Ootadai
Kamanuma
Oyama Fuduson
I think we're done here.
Yup.
Okay, let's go help Izo.
Is it true they're broadcasting
the Tanada Night Festival at Oyama Senmaida to Polyhedron?
That's right.
Kamogawa is, after all, the most famous city on Earth.
We'll broadcast the Tanada Night Festival across the galaxy.
What better event to symbolize the friendship
between Le Garite and De Metrio!
Izo!
Hey, give me a hand!
We will.
Careful with that, Array.
It tears easily.
I'm not you, Izo.
I guess this is the last time I'll see this scenery.
You won't change your mind?
I don't know if we've done everything we could,
but I'm at peace.
We've done a lot since we've came here.
We were saved,
by this planet,
and by this city.
Yeah.
Okay, that completes the application procedure.
Now all we do is wait to see if the school approves us.
Yeah.
If we get approval, we get to keep our clubhouse.
Okay, now that that's done, let's get down to business. We have a lot of requests!
Right!
What's all the fuss?
If they have no bread, let them eat cake.
Nice!
A real princess does it with dignity!
Next! Lady-in-waiting!
Princess, the revolutionary army is...
Reiko, you're up!
Break a leg!
Yes!
Princess! The revolutionary army is approaching.
Cut! Cut!
Stop the camera!
I'm switching tapes.
Woof.
I'm so sorry.
Muginami, you look so pretty.
Okay, I'll need you too.
Right! Reiko Miki will do her best.
NO!
I'm sorry!
Oh my...
I'm so sorry!
En garde!
Woof.
Allez!
Mask touch!
That was incredible!
You're next, Reiko.
Do your best.
I will!
I'm sorry, my legs fell asleep.
Is she the clumsiest girl on earth or what?
Huh?
It's me.
Hey, are you free tonight?
Cheers!
That was good!
What's up? It's not like you to call me out.
What did you want to talk about?
Is it about a guy?
You know we're on the same boat, Yoko.
Guess we're both waiting for spring to come, eh?
Over here. Another medium draft!
One more medium draft!
Coming right up!
Then, did Madoka do something again?
You might say that.
It's about the Sweats Club clubhouse you showed me.
Oh, you mean that storeroom?
The Student Council wants them to vacate it.
Oh.
So to keep that room,
Madoka is trying to make the Sweats Club an official school club.
Is that even possible?
Thank you very much.
Should you be ignoring that boy over there?
Yoko! You know I...
Just ignore him.
He's not a kid.
Man, I really drink too much when I'm with you.
Machiko...
Did you call me out just to update me about the Sweats Club?
That's not the real reason, is it?
You saw right through me.
Then I'll just come out and say it.
Isn't it about time you free yourself?
Free myself?
You originally formed the Sweats Club
to cheer up Madoka who just lost her mother.
But I think,
the one who really needed the Sweats Club was you, Yoko.
You admired Madoka's mother.
But what Madoka is trying to protect right now,
isn't the Sweats Club from the past.
So?
She's not the little Madoka we used to know anymore.
But when I look at you,
I get the sense that you're still bound to the Sweats Club from the past.
It hurts me to see you like this—
Stop right there.
This is why I don't like teachers.
Why do teachers like to make assumptions about people's feelings?
Is it an occupational side effect?
I'm sorry.
That was a slip.
It's just the alcohol talking. Forget I ever said it.
I had fun tonight.
I should get going.
Today, we're helping the Chorus Club.
May I ask a question?
Sure. What is it?
When will I be able to pilot a robot?
Robot?
Isn't piloting robots and protecting Kamogawa what the Sweats Club does?
Huh?
I saw you fight in a robot once.
That's when I decided I was going to pilot a robot and protect Kamogawa too.
Thank you very much.
I think we should clear up the misunderstanding with Reiko.
But she just joined our club.
Without Reiko, we'll lose our clubhouse.
That's true, but...
I've made a decision!
The Tanada night festival
at Oyama Senmaida
Okay. The link is good.
Starting the broadcast to Polyhedron.
Wow! That's beautiful!
Miss Kyono.
Thanks for coming, Reiko!
Why are we here at the Tanada Night Festival?
Sweats Club work.
Kirius, are you ready?
Of course. Everything is perfect.
Watch, Reiko!
Awesome!
You know what Reiko?
Yes?
What we do in the Sweats Club is a little different than what you think.
Huh?
We don't just pilot robots.
We rode in the Vox and fought in order to protect everyone's—
no, our happiness.
But that's over now.
We'll never, ever be using the Vox for fighting again.
That need is gone.
The fighting has ended.
But...
I'm sorry to disappoint you.
But we still want you to be one of us in the Sweats Club.
Mommy, did you know?
That one's called Aura!
It's lovely.
Wow, look!
That's so cool!
Array! The balloon!
I'm on it!
Perfect!
Huh?
Madoka!
This isn't how it was supposed to go...
Miss Kyono!
Reiko!
How do I look?
Everybody, how do I look?
Huh?
What we do in the Sweats Club everyday,
we do for everybody's happiness!
Madoka.
What in the world are you doing?
Mr. Tadokoro? Madoka's in big trouble!
I'm so happy!
There's Lan and Muginami,
and now you too, Reiko!
But I want even more happiness!
That's why, Reiko,
I want you to find what makes you happy!
Then I'll do all I can to support you!
What makes me happy?
Happy, huh?
Umm, somebody!
Do you know how to bring this down?
I'm sorry!
Dropping out
Reiko.
After watching you last night, I made up my mind.
Made up your mind? About what?
I'm going to look for what makes me happy.
I've decided to start a robot club.
A robot club?
Yes!
That way, one day, I'll ride in a robot like Aura!
You made me realize that, Miss Kyono.
Thank you so much!
O-Okay.
Dropping out
Oh man! I got all excited for nothing.
Guess that's how it goes.
Farewell, clubhouse!
You know, Madoka.
What?
In that case, why don't we expand
the Kamo Girls Sweats Club all across the universe?
Hey! Great idea!
We'll expand way beyond the clubhouse. The Kamogawa Sweats Club, Space Branch.
Sounds like fun.
The royal family of Le Garite will lend its full support.
Really?!
De Metrio too!
Okay! Now that that's set,
We had another meeting after that one.
let's get our Space Branch started!
The reassignment will be postponed,
Kamogawa Sweats Club, Space Branch!
As I was saying, so you can keep on using this room.
Fight! Ohh!
About the newly discovered stone slab...
It might possibly describe the craft that caused the tragedy 20,000 years ago.
Why do you think that?
It's been bothering me all this time.
The cause of the tragedy 20,000 years ago was due to a single craft,
so why does the legend tell of three crafts?
Most importantly, a tragedy definitely occurred, so why does the Earth show no signs?
I just can't recall what happened
after my soul was torn apart,
and absorbed into the Rinne.
My soul that supposedly caused the tragedy.
It's been 20,000 years.
Okay, let's go.
Thank you for coming out all this way.
Moid.
The payment, please.
This.
What is it?
Impossible!
Yes.
It is the Memoria I was imprinted with 20,000 years ago
The Sweats Club spirit! The Sweats Club spirit!
I won't leave you alone, hello and let's be cheery!
Who knows if it's fun?
We're still trying to work that out
This is the youth of us three!
Our destined meeting happened in a split second
We're together when we walk ahead
We're together with each of the breaths we take
Look
We're together when we laugh from the bottom of our hearts
Is this friendship?
We'll be fine!
I won't press the issue!
I won't delve into it too deep!
We don't really have to know that
Why can we trust each other so much, you ask?
That's obvious!
We're comrades!
The Sweats Club spirit! The Sweats Club spirit!
I want to help you, hello and let's be cheery!
Okay! What does Christmas remind you of?
Christmas tree ornaments!
Christmas tree lights!
Cake with lots of frosting!
Exchanging presents!
Madoka, what about you?
Sweat!
Sweat?
Yeah! The Kamo Girls Sweats Club gets a flood of requests during that period,
so Christmas is a race against time!
I can't just stand around like this!
That's not what I had imagined.
I wonder what we'll be doing.
A white Kamogawa
for Christmas?