I wasn't prepared for any of this.
It's so lame I could die.
Well? Come on! What's our plan?
Surely, it would be faster to simply do away with Jirou.
No!
I'll look for Soujoubou with Botanmaru.
I just had a great idea!
And what might this idea be?
Take me to Jirou.
Make your way inside.
Now's our chance to search for the master.
That way!
Could their plan possibly work?
What, oh what, will become of Nanami and her friends?
I wonder what's happening on this world
I fly through the sky into space
and circle the world
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday
With my periodic biorhythm
I'm like a washing machine
Just kidding
Yes, I'm spinning around
Around, around the world
Because there's no limit to my love
Spinning around, around, around the world
I want to tell you that I love you, even if it confuses me
Bam, bam, bam
You're not paying attention
Sometimes love keeps being one-sided
It's gotten so hopelessly complex
But I'll make it all true with a miracle
Hey, God,
I'm your god
I think
You, attended by a familiar? Impressive.
I never expected a washed up crow like you to return a god, Shinjurou.
It's lovely to see you too, Brother Jirou.
I was told that my sire collapsed. Where is he now?
He's inside the sanctum, although he is extremely ill,
so allowing him to see his runaway son is out of the question.
So, land god or whatever you call yourself, you're no longer a part of Kurama, regardless of your name.
So this brute is the one known as Jirou.
True to tale, he has the physique of a bear.
And he laid those boorish hands...
on Nanami!
The God Is Blindsided
I will admit that our past is somewhat checkered, but let's forgive and forget.
I am here today to help you celebrate
your succession as the fourth Soujoubou.
As tribute, I come bearing the libation from the Heavens.
It would be an honor if you shared a drink with me.
From the Heavens, you say?
This is pure rotgut. The highest proof booze you can get from the mundane world.
If you're a lightweight, it's one, two, three, floor.
Are you talking about me?
Some piddly sake can't get me drunk.
Now go on, Jirou!
Since you are claiming to be a god,
you must be familiar with the celestial nymph I meant recently beneath the tree.
Celestial nymph?
The who?
I'm afraid not. It could've been anyone. Who knows?
No matter, then.
Lest we forget, this sacred mountain forbids any and all women.
Celestial nymph or not, I intend to teach her a harsh lesson.
This man...
Wow! This building is huge!
We haven't seen any other crows.
Plus, I feel like we've passed the
same spot a million times already.
Is everything okay?
Are we really making any progress?
Botanmaru?
It is all right!
Follow me, and it will be all right!
We have not lost our way!
Okay, okay!
What a bunch of bull!
Bam
You're totally lost, you pipsqueak!
Mamoru!
P-Pipsqueak?!
This compound is surrounded by that Jirou guy's barrier.
I can smell the rotten stink of his aura on everything.
Until the fox and his friend break Jirou's focus, we're stuck here.
Tomoe... Kurama...
Hurry!
Sake from the Heavens is not so bad after all.
What's the matter, Shinjurou? The bottle isn't empty yet.
So how are you feeling now, Brother? Good?
Of course.
Were you planning to get me drunk so you could exact some sort of pathetic revenge?
This must come as a disappointment.
Unlike your feeble spirit, I am not
one to be corrupted by mere alcohol.
Inebriation is just another sad form of weakness.
You're the one who insisted we drink.
You will finish this bottle with me.
This has gone far enough, Master Jirou.
In lieu of my lord and master,
I, Tomoe, will keep you company.
In deference to your wishes...
Why not let a celestial nymph pour for you?
Wobble
What?!
The barrier wavered!
The caster just lost his focus!
But why?
Who cares? Let's get going while we can.
What is the matter, Master Jirou?
You were speaking so eloquently earlier.
Was it you beneath the eternal cherry blossom tree, fox?
I was afraid my arm was going to break that time.
You are so rough, even in your treatment of women.
You?! A woman?!
My!
You're merely disguised as a woman! You're no woman!
Oh, you are awful!
If you have such strong suspicions,
ascertain for yourself whether I am man or woman.
Jirou...
As I suspected, this man is...
Amazing!
The webbing of the barrier was all over the place before, but it's disappeared.
Now's our chance. Let's go.
Yes, quietly so that no one notices us.
I have a bad feeling about this.
What in the world might Master Jirou be doing?
Soujoubou!
Master Soujoubou!
That's him?
He looks kind of frozen.
Land god! The Peach Pills! Quick!
Oh, right...
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Peach Pills... Peach Pills...
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry... Hurr...
Peach Pills won't make him better.
The crow boss's soul was extracted.
I don't think he'll wake up until his soul is restored to his body.
His soul?
But who would do such a thing?
17 years since descending the mountain.
See how I have grown.
I have completely settled into life in the mundane world and...
A large black feather...
This size...
Jirou?!
My gut was right.
It is as I thought, Master Jirou.
What?
For all that you said earlier, you fancy me, do you not?
What?!
Women are forbidden, and I am violating that prohibition and yet not a word of condemnation.
Don't be ridiculous!
What about you would I even fancy?!
Ah... This man is infuriating.
As if I, Jirou, would be led astray by some woman!
Then why not look me in the eye and condemn me more harshly?
When you saw that slip of a girl and saw a celestial nymph,
that was already checkmate for you.
That's ridiculous...
Why would I...
Why, you! Are you trying to dupe me while I'm drunk?!
Dammit! You are disgraceful!
If you're such a tough guy,
why don't you man up and confess your true feelings to Nanami?
Watching you...
is like looking in a mirror, and it infuriates me.
Nanami...
So that is the girl's name.
Master Jirou.
What in the world are you doing?
Your protective barrier has been compromised.
Yatori!
This is why I warned you.
And sure enough, a couple rats had snuck their way in.
Two crows and one monkey.
They seemed pretty shady to me.
I locked them up in the basement for now, though.
If we work them over a little, I bet they'll
spill the beans that they're co-conspirators.
Stop, Tomoe!
I beg your pardon, but I really don't have the
slightest idea of what you might be accusing us of.
For my familiar's misconduct,
I offer you my sincere apologies.
After all, he was once a lowly wild fox, so he doesn't know any better.
If you see fit to punish him, you have my permission.
Beat him, torture him, it matters not. You can do whatever you please.
Wait!
You damn idiot! Stinking fox!
Argh
We got captured, thanks to you!
What kind of goof was that, you nincompoop?!
If you had not stopped me,
Grr
Guard
I would have beat that bear-man to a pulp,
and that would have been that!
Beating people to a pulp isn't part of the plan!
How many times do I have to tell you, you moron?!
If Nanami has been caught, that changes the plan!
At any rate, I am going to Nanami.
I will tear this cage to shreds and...
It's no use. This is Brother Jirou's barrier prison.
Spirit powers are of absolutely no use in here.
We'll have to devise some way to escape.
Finding Nanami and the others is of critical importance.
We may not be able to save your old man.
I don't really care about my sire.
I've barely even spoken to the man.
That weirdo said Nanami and her group were put in the underground dungeon.
We'll have to go rescue them somehow.
Next part coming
right up
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Huh?
Th-This place...
Oh!
Botanmaru! Wake up! Wake up!
Here are the rats, Master Jirou.
To think that these stinking brats got the better of me...
Jirou...
I had my suspicions that Shinjurou was up to something,
but I never imagined that we had a traitor in our midst.
Botanmaru!
You cursed weakling!
Botanmaru! Botanmaru!
Now talk! What are you after?!
Raising your hand against such a small child...
How can you even talk about
becoming the fourth Soujoubou?!
The way to avoid pain is strength. That is all.
His weakness is to blame.
That is why he cannot fly even though he is already seven.
If you cannot live without someone's coddling,
death is the only solution.
Why?
It doesn't matter how strong you are.
No one can go through life all on their own.
Not even you.
It's not like you lived on the mountain by yourself without any help all these years.
Boy! You dare talk as if you know?!
I do know.
Even about how you stole Soujoubou's soul from him.
His soul?
What are you talking about?
What?
Now, now, Master Jirou.
Enough with the interrogation.
Leave the rest to Yatori here.
You can go deal with Master Shinjurou and the fox that you captured.
Tomoe and Kurama?!
And try not to let lustful thoughts sidetrack you this time.
Damn...
I will be counting on you!
The way he reacted...
It wasn't Jirou who extracted Soujoubou's soul?
Then who did?
Now...
I was certain the master's condition would never be discovered.
I pegged you as a simple crow, but clearly, you had me fooled.
So you're the one who did it?!
Why?!
Let me think.
I suppose I could tell you before you die.
Okay, so there's this guy I know who
trusted me to get him an obedient army.
And Kurama here fit the bill to a T.
As long as the boss gives the okay, the rest brainlessly follow his lead.
Closed
Off
A closed off and simple vertical society.
Simple
Vertical
Society
Simple
Vertical
Society
Nothing could fit my needs better!
Why, you! How did you do that to Master Soujoubou?!
How, you ask?
It is a letter from your son.
I was asked to avoid being seen
and deliver this to you in person.
How you must have worried for your only son's safety!
Yatori, was it?
Oh, yes?
I consider all the crows of this mountain to be my children.
I purposefully drew a distinction between them and my own son, Shinjurou...
but I treasure them all equally.
Yes.
He left himself completely open.
Even I never imagined that such a
cheap trick would bring him down.
You bastard!
This is the part where we conclude our chitchat.
I will tell Master Jirou that, having failed
your mission, you all took your own lives.
M-My feet!
You will quietly die here...
Just try it.
I dare you!
Evil deeds must not go unpunished!
Mamoru!
Th-This is not happening!
H-How can you be...
Barrier against evil!
I will get stronger.
Much stronger.
I'm taller than the others,
and my back and legs are sturdy,
so when I grow up, I'm sure I'll have the biggest wings of anyone.
That's what the brothers said.
If I train even harder,
I might become number one.
Jirou.
Admirable of you to stay behind alone to train.
Master Soujoubou!
I hear you won brilliantly for the first time in the sword-fighting competition yesterday.
My nose swells with pride. Just look at how big it is.
Just kidding.
You should not push yourself too hard and jeopardize your health, so go on back to your room for today.
Yes, sir!
Master Soujoubou.
The strongest crow on the mountain.
I am now that crow, yet I am so ashamed.
I'm even starting to see the celestial nymph in that four-eyed runt.
No matter how strong you are,
you can't go through life all by yourself.
Dammit!
I am about to become the fourth Soujoubou of Kurama.
Something is wrong with me today.
Daidaimaru, are you okay?!
Master Jirou!
Y-You idiots! This is what you get for not looking where you're going!
My apologies, sir!
Not even you.
It's not like you lived by yourself without any help.
Oh, dear!
Hey, is this cruel or what?!
A barrier against evil?! This is news to me!
Give back Soujoubou's soul!
I have it hidden somewhere deep within this compound where the crows cannot find it,
so if you get rid of me, you will never find his soul...
So that was a barrier against evil.
Master Jirou's barrier is still here, but Nanami made that man fly away like a piece of paper.
She's the scariest lady I've ever seen!
We're going to look for Soujoubou's soul.
Soujoubou
We'll use this white talisman and have it find his soul.
I was afraid it wouldn't be much help
in here since Jirou's barrier is so tough.
Why not? Your barrier against evil was working just fine.
That's it!
We're inside Jirou's barrier.
So if everything inside it is his, I just need to figure out a way to make it mine.
What are you crying for, Daidaimaru?
Please forgive him.
Daidaimaru is not feeling well today,
so we were about to send him to rest.
Please don't punish him. I, Chiyomaru, would rather take the blame.
You must stop this, Jirou!
Suirou...
This is stupid.
Master Jirou, there is trouble!
What is it?
A woman... A woman is running around inside the compound!
Move! Move!
Touch me, and you'll fall to the mundane world!
If I cast a barrier against evil within the compound, I should be able to cancel out Jirou's barrier.
This whole compound will be
surrounded with my power, not his!
Where's the woman?!
She went toward the West Wing!
The West Wing?
Master Jirou!
Toward the sanctum where I have Shinjurou and the fox locked up...
It must be her.
Look.
Where the woman passed...
is shining gold!
It's like a line of light.
It's pretty.
Shh! Idiot! Master Jirou can hear you!
Stinking fox, the crow guarding us hurried off somewhere.
I don't know what happened,
but isn't this our chance to escape?
Come up with some way to escape.
I know it must be hard with your tiny brain.
Oh, that's rich.
At least I have a brain!
You idiot! Your ears are doing all the work!
Your ears are bigger than your head!
4th Stupid Fight of the Day
Can you even hear me through that hair?!
Master Shinjurou!
4th Stupid Fight of the Day
I finally found you! I have come to rescue you!
Oh, good. Well done, Botanmaru.
Glad you're safe and sound.
My goodness!
What an impressive barrier prison.
How might I get you out, Master Shinjurou?
Where is Nanami?
Is she not with you?
Lady Nanami is currently running about to cast a barrier upon the compound.
Running about?
It seems Master Soujoubou is worse off than we thought!
Master Shinjurou, Lady Nanami and I saw him in the innermost sanctum.
Master Soujoubou's soul was taken by a spirit named Yatori, and he has become petrified!
Master Soujoubou was not
confined to his bed due to illness!
What?!
Yatori confessed to it all.
He claimed to have hid his soul somewhere on this compound where no one would find it.
It was all a plot to overthrow the Third and take control of Kurama.
What is this light?
The barrier prison is fading away.
A barrier against evil.
Nanami has finished casting the barrier just now.
Hey, can you hear me?
All right!
That night, I was looking
at the fleeting remnants of the day
The milky way spread across my vision
It was very beautiful
Hey, can you hear me?
I don't think I can talk to other people about this
I'll call up God, I think
If a new day hadn't begun
then yesterday's tomorrow would be today
and yesterday would be the day before
I'm waiting for you
I'll stay here
The boat is stopped here
Preview
Nanami's barrier made the compound all sparkly!
If today weren't today
She's really come into her own!
All right, we're going to find Soujoubou's soul!
and were that day instead, oh, that'd be nice
But Jirou's learned the truth
and gone to hunt for it himself.
There's no way we can let him get to it first!
Next time, "The God Received a Romantic Confession."
The God Received a Romantic Confession
What? Come again?