Tomoe believes that humans are fleeting and frail,
and he fears getting involved with them.
I think that you can teach him that humans are not weak.
I want to rekindle Tomoe's bond with humanity.
To have him take your hand, not mine.
I want to allow Tomoe to choose you.
Mikage!
But it seems he still has a long way to go.
What were you speaking about with Mikage, Nanami?
It wasn't anything important.
It was just a little bit of small talk.
I see.
They live for a long time.
They live with the same love in their hearts for centuries.
To fall in love with someone, to need them, is a highly risky proposition for spirit kind.
I'm human,
which means I'm gonna die
a long time before Tomoe does.
I really do want him to love me.
But that seems so selfish now.
Why did Mikage say
that he wants to allow Tomoe to choose me?
I wonder what's happening on this world
I fly through the sky into space
and circle the world
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday
With my periodic biorhythm
I'm like a washing machine
Just kidding
Yes, I'm spinning around
Around, around the world
Because there's no limit to my love
Spinning around, around, around the world
I want to tell you that I love you, even if it confuses me
Bam, bam, bam
You're not paying attention
Sometimes love keeps being one-sided
It's gotten so hopelessly complex
But I'll make it all true with a miracle
Hey, God,
I'm your god
I think
The God Meets a Little Crow
You look glum, Lady Nanami.
If you find it painful to part ways with me,
you could extend your stay.
Not like you have anything better to do.
Well, I still have school.
Though it was only for seven days,
you fulfilled your duties admirably.
You can return with your head held high.
Thank you very much, Lord Ookuninushi.
Ah, yes. I had promised to tell
you of Mikage's whereabouts.
But alas...
The truth is, even I was unable to ascertain...
It doesn't matter anymore.
It doesn't? So...
You don't need to find him?
Until Tomoe completely ceases to need me,
I have no intention of seeing him.
No.
Oh, I got you something.
They're blot sheets made of Izumo paper.
You had no time for sightseeing, right?
Get your girl power up with these.
Actually, Tomoe and I went out for a while yesterday.
Oh, good. I'm sure you found Izumo to be a fine place.
Well, since I carried out my important duties myself,
I'll treat myself and the ladies to a
long-deserved date in the other world!
Lord Ookuninushi!
Ookuninushi has a pretty set type.
You're terrible, Lord Ookuninushi!
You have me, yet you're going off to see women in the mundane world?!
The girls he's going out with are human?
I, Ookuninushi, love gods, humans, and spirit kind alike—any and all who are deemed to be women.
I believe in equal love for all! I will not choose!
Resolute
Ah! Lord Ookuninushi, you're the best!
Then...
Humans and spirit kind...
Could they ever be joined together?
I'm afraid not.
Well, if saying that could put a stop to such a love,
then one need not worry, for it will fade quickly.
It all depends...
upon the parties involved.
What is the matter with Lady Nanami?
She has seemed listless since the banquet.
She's probably tired.
The other gods will be staying for another seven days in Izumo,
so I wish I could've taken her to relax in the hot springs.
That's enough out of you.
The shrine can't be left unattended forever.
Then why don't you go back by yourself?
I'll take her to the hot springs.
I will remain with Nanami.
You go back.
And they're fighting again.
We are going home, Nanami.
Let's go to the hot springs together.
Get in.
Sorry, but can you guys go back without me?
I can't be close to Tomoe. Not right now.
It's like a wall's between us, and I can't get passed it.
She has a return flight booked,
so I'm sure she'll be fine by herself.
However, I'm kind of surprised you're actually
letting her stay somewhere so far away from us.
It's not like you at all.
Meanwhile, at the Mori residence...
Is this your weak spot, Montarou?
No, please stop that! It's Monjirou!
That...
Take that and that and that!
...cursed fox! I'm going to kill him!
Kikuichi, let me kill you.
I'll spend another seven days and remake you.
M-M-Master Kirihito!
Master!
What is the matter?!
It's nothing.
Tomoe...
Kirihito.
I am coming in.
Kirihito?
I wonder if Tomoe thought it was weird when I said I wanted to go home alone.
Nanami.
Himemiko!
What are you doing here?
Out shopping.
Oh, uh... Masatake, was it?
You're doing a great job there.
I'm Aotake!
Nanami, did thou return from Izumo just now?
Yeah. Thanks for coming to see me off when I left.
It was nothing.
Is that impertinent fox not with you, land god?!
Silence, Aotake! Do not use such language!
Tomoe and I traveled separately.
Nanami.
Wilt thou not go on a date with me?
What?
This is pretty good.
Aotake, deliver those to the Mikage Shrine.
Let us go, Nanami.
O-Okay.
My lady... My lady... My lady... Lady Himemiko!
I've started the "being a girl" thing
My sigh is like a violin playing
A red fruit has burst
I don't know you yet
(Don't know you yet)
3 for 1,000 yen
That is far too sexy !
I say, "I've never done this before"
Your gaze is an evil flower,
blooming in riotous profusion
Here is a bus stop leading to the forest, but you won't lead me
(You won't lead me)
When we link fingers we can feel the pulse of love
Ooh!
S-So cute!
(The pulse of love)
Ooh!
S-So cute!
A soft magic
(A soft)
(Magic)
Lips that lie
Yes, laid one upon the other
You know
Please, dear God
I want to be a bad girl
Right now I'm being good,
so I'm begging you
Let me be unfair for once,
and when I want to be good anyway,
blow up my skirt
and I'll go back
Looks like Saturday is going to be clear
I've started the "being a god" thing
Welco...
Oh!
Kota!
Long time no see, Kotarou.
Himemiko!
Kota, the usual, please.
Yeah, you got it.
Hey, I'm here too.
Manager! The usual!
You come here often?
Yes, I do.
"The usual" doesn't tell me anything!
So things are still going well with you two.
I'm relieved.
Nanami, did something happen in Izumo?
Thou can tell me.
What?
In Izumo, I was told...
that the gravity of our feelings is
different for humans and spirit kind.
You guys hold on to one love in your hearts forever.
Forever. Long after I'm dead.
When I thought about that,
I couldn't say frivolous things to Tomoe anymore.
Thou art incorrect, Nanami.
What?
If thou dost not speak, no one shall be happy.
My darling Kota and I are only
together because thou took action.
It has brought me such joy.
Your blessing allows us to share these forbidden feelings.
It is true that our lifespans differ.
That is precisely why my time with Kota is dear.
I do not wish to spend that time doing nothing and regretting it.
Dost thou not think so, Nanami?
I do.
I don't want to regret anything either.
Yeah.
I also...
want to cherish the time I have with Tomoe.
And...
I want to tell him that I love him.
I'm home!
Oh! Welcome back, Nanami!
You are late.
What manner of drivel delayed you this time?
Oh, Tomoe.
He's been waiting for you since morning. Isn't that right?
Shut up, snake!
I'm home, Tomoe!
Next part coming
right up
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Yatori?
Never heard of him.
This guy wants to meet with me?
A third-rate spirit, huh?
Oh, how I've fallen.
He acted all chummy and sent you an unsolicited letter. Such impudence!
Please, master. Permit me to research his past.
Ignore him.
We don't have time to waste on small fry.
Master Kirihito.
Can I chow down on these sweet potato and red bean buns?
Do whatever you want.
Yay!
Ooh, they look tasty!
I would like one as well!
Who the hell are you?!
F-F-Forgive me!
You were asked a question.
Y-Yes, sir!
My name is Yatori.
Word on the street is that you're trying to revive Master Akura-oh from his confinement in the Netherworld.
I am in favor of that. Allow me to
assist you in his righteous restoration.
I would gladly go get his body for you.
You would? Why?
A world ruled by Master Akura-oh is my ideal world.
Only he is worthy of ruling this world.
I do this solely out of loyalty to him.
Your intentions are promising, but can you do this?
So he hasn't realized that I'm Akura-oh.
What a terrific moron.
I don't see a shred of emotion in those eyes, yet he speaks of loyalty? What a joke.
Show me that you're not all talk.
Your apprehension is understandable.
Naturally, I have already made the proper arrangements.
To prove my loyalty, I will present Master Akura-oh with the sacred mountain of Mount Kurama.
I will take control of the crows of Kurama, and I hope to lead that force in his service.
He must take me for a fool.
I'll be waiting to hear the good news, Yatori.
However, he may yet prove useful.
Yes, sir!
I will not let you down. I swear it.
They were nice, weren't they?
They even shared some of their sweet buns with me.
Don't be so naive.
I could tell right away.
No matter how much he pretends, that human is Akura-oh.
It was so easy for us to get past his guard.
Oh, how the mighty have fallen.
They say that ill weeds grow apace, but...
You know, the nice ones don't live long.
Hey, who do you suppose Kirihito is?
He had such a calm demeanor in the Netherworld.
Not to mention...
You will likely never see him again.
Yeah, but the thing is, I ran into him
in town right before I went to Izumo.
Nanami!
Kurama's concert is today, and I won a ticket for you!
Really?!
Yep! One for you and one for Kei.
But Kei says she has a date and can't come, so...
Tomoe, want to come?
Tomoe, let's go!
Like hell.
Oh, come on, Tomoe!
Why must I listen to his singing?
My ears will rot!
Gleaming in the dark
Kurama's really cool when he's singing, you know.
As a fellow spirit, you should study Kurama,
since he blends into the human world so well.
No need!
Aw, jeez. Then I'll at least...
Smoosh
Were you the one who trampled over me, woman?!
You insolent fool!
I'm sorry! I didn't think anyone would be sleeping there...
Wait...
I am Botanmaru of Mount Kurama.
I was not sleeping.
I was listening to sounds traveling through the earth!
A crow?
So cute!
What business does a little crow have here?
I am searching for someone.
Master Soujoubou the Third's
son and heir, Master Shinjurou!
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Seventeen Years Ago
Master
Shinjurou
Seventeen Years Ago
Master
Shinjurou
Seventeen Years Ago
Master
Shinjurou
Seventeen Years Ago
Master
Shinjurou
Seventeen Years Ago
Master
Shinjurou
Seventeen Years Ago
Master
Shinjurou
He ran away to this world seventeen years ago.
This is how he looked back then.
His current whereabouts are unknown.
Master
Shinjurou
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
By now, he should have grown into a fine crow such as you see here.
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Do you know him?
No.
Go fly to Mount Takao and ask your fellow crow.
Hey, Tomoe!
Oh!
Splat
Botanmaru!
Are you okay? You're not hurt?
You insolent fool! You won't get away with this!
Cursed fox spirit!
What is this? So you cannot fly?
Oh, wait!
Ignore him.
No!
I can't ignore him!
Tomoe, you go home without me!
Take care of Mamoru for me!
Botanmaru.
Mind if I help you look for Shinjurou?
Tell me everything.
Botanmaru.
Are you crying again, Botanmaru?
Did Jirou beat you again?
Here, let me see.
Brother, I hate myself.
One of the kids born last year
is already much taller than me.
I am already six, yet my wings are not even fully grown.
Shinjurou was like that too.
Shinjurou?
Even though he was born to the Third.
Like you, he was a late bloomer.
And he was the first to be born in 500 years, so he
was judged harshly by those around him back then.
He often received beatings from Jirou.
But he was a child who never cried.
He was always sitting atop that rock.
There.
Right where you're sitting.
Where is Master Shinjurou now?
I don't know.
He was gravely injured when he was twelve, and he ended up descending the mountain.
No one knows where he is.
Grow strong, Botanmaru.
For we don't wish to lose you as well.
Some say that crows who descend the mountain are failures.
But I do not believe that.
Crows grow to adulthood in eight years,
but on rare occasions, there are late bloomers like me.
I am seven now, and I still cannot even fly.
I wish to see Master Shinjurou and speak to him about something.
If I can see Master Shinjurou who has now grown into a fine crow, I...
I...
What is it?
You're only seven, and you've had it so rough!
Let's find Shinjurou!
I just know that Shinjurou's become a fine man that you can admire!
Of course he has.
There he is! Master Shinjurou!
What?
Huh?
N-No way...
There is no mistake! The portrait from the treasury is an exact likeness!
No way! No way! No way! No way!
No way!
It...
It's Kurama?!
Gleaming in the dark
Wings of deceit
In the embrace of joyful rapture
I fall in madness
Glorious!
All is within my grasp
Kiss you, kiss me
Paradise!
Shadow... Die...
That is... Master Shinjurou...
The next song...
is a ballad I wrote just for this day.
Please listen.
"Wings Fling Hazard."
Something I wish for right now
If I had to say, there's only one thing
Dark red thread to stitch these wings
That's all I want
Nightly it creaks, my heart
In blinding darkness
I keep waiting for the moment I take wing
Even as I gnash my teeth
So the guitar's just a prop?
Oh, high in the sky, I spread the wings that will not open
This hazard of mine as I take wing
My heart is so flung free
I'll return for sure
Because this place is all I've got
So come on over here
I won't bite
Who would've thought Kurama was Soujoubou's son?
Preview
His old home is in a state of crisis, so Kurama ends up rushing back.
With Nanami and Tomoe, it's onto Mount Kurama!
But along the way, they're enveloped in a suspicious fog?
Next time, "The God Goes to Mount Kurama."
The God Goes to Mount Kurama
Come now. I won't bite.