I hope we can all be happy like this forever.
I'm coming!
I knew I wore this for a reason!
Lovely, lovely
The girl in the training suit is somehow special
When she takes it off, she can be anything
To look for something she treasures, she'd go to the bottom of the ocean
The surge of her emotions can turn her opposition into mist
I come to meet you as fast as I can
when your visions call to me
Perfect!
Live your life!
Rewrite fate and fly
Fly away
Try to unite
If it's dangerous to laugh at your foes as you advance
burn brighter and fly away
Try to unite, tonight
Lovely, lovely
Welcome to Kamokawa!
Kamokawa Girl's High School
Just what is the meaning of this?
On my way to school, I came across a girl drowning!
Why are you dressed like this?!
I told you! When I got back to shore, my whole outfit was missing!
Don't worry, though!
I always have these, see?
Then put them on!
Okay!
Kyono!
The paramedics called. They say she's fine now.
Perfect!
Sorry to bother you, Madoka, but can you come see me after school?
Oh, sure, around what time?
Whenever you're free.
The club president really, really wants to see you there for some reason.
All right, see ya then!
What, she wants to spar again?
The Sweats Club must be really busy.
Why don't you join, Michi? We're recruiting.
Thanks, but I'll pass.
Oh, hey, didn't you wear your uniform today?
I kinda lost it on the way here.
You're a walking disaster.
What's your problem?!
That's right. I forgot.
Really? But we're still in high school...
I... I can't make up my mind about our future yet!
Cut!
All right, let's change sets.
How was I?
You were great! That was just so cute!
I mean, I love you in uniform too, but this...
Sorry, I kinda...
One more serve!
Men!
Men ari!
I'm glad I could join you.
We got some good practice in before the meet.
Now all you need to do is join the student council or the kendo club,
and everything will be... How do you say, "perfect"?
But I'm already a club president.
I guess.
Good luck defending the title.
Kyono Madoka.
Yes?
You forgot these.
Who's she?
Finally a recruit for the Sweats Club?
No way.
She's got guts, at least.
Thanks.
A comrade.
I'm home!
Hey there!
Welcome back.
Hi, Dad!
What are you home for?
I haven't seen you in half a year!
The pain!
I give, I give!
What a slacker.
You're in high school now; dress properly.
I... I don't think that has anything to do with this...
We need to talk.
Panties. Off.
O... kay?
Don't move!
Uh, are you done yet?
Madoka. Do you value the life you live here in Kamogawa?
What's gotten into you?
Do you want to keep on living here forever?
Huh?
Sota  Serizawa
Got it.
If anything happens, call me right away.
Tokyo Marine University           Marine Archaeology Labs
Researcher
Yoko Nakaizumi
Perfect!
You scared me!
How long have you been there?!
Arf.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Sweats Club
So you want to join?
Yes.
I knew it!
Let's do this!
I knew at a glance that we'd get along great!
You're so kind! You even tracked me down just to return my uniform!
And that swimsuit of yours means you're ready to rescue people anytime!
This is my uniform.
Your uniform?
It's my duty to wear it at all times when I'm on a mission.
Wow, you sound smart!
I thought you were a comrade, but maybe you're already a higher rank than me.
What's a comrade?
Two friends who tread forth with a singular determination!
People... don't really use it that much anymore...
But my big sister enjoys words like that, so I picked it up from her.
It's a nice word.
Comrade, huh?
Become my comrade! If run into any kind of trouble, I'll help you out one hundred percent!
Very well.
We're comrades, then.
I'm Fin e Ld si Laffinty.
Oh, is that your name? You're not from around here, are you?
Call me Lan.
I'm Kyono Madoka. Pleased to meet you!
All right! Now there's two of us!
I have a question, Comrade.
There is one thing I've been having trouble with.
What is it? C'mon, let me help you out!
Can you pilot a robot?
That's Earth.
I'm sure of it.
The star which shines a brighter blue than even Demetria.
Our promised land.
You know what we have to do.
Let's go.
Wait.
L'Egalité may already have infiltrated.
Be ready to sortie on a moment's notice.
Jeez, fine.
You too, Array.
Who died and left you in charge, Kirius?
Do you see the ghost of a planet too, Yurikano?
This was just sitting here offshore?
No, it had to sail here.
Sail? It's a ship?!
This way.
Madoka, I'm coming in.
Hey, Dad, you seen Madoka around?
Huh? I thought I heard her come in a while back.
Don't worry, Auntie.
I won't let Madoka pilot a robot.
Hello?
Where are you?
Your cousin's here!
Dammit!
That's the robot?
Yes.
I thought it was gonna be...
You know, like this?
It's pretty, though.
Huh?
This looks familiar.
What was that?
Demetria.
Enemy at 2 o'clock, range 7000 meters.
All ships, prepare to intercept!
Fire!
Long ago, you made a promise with this robot.
That someday, if necessary, you would unite your hearts as one.
As comrades.
Comrades...
This is...
The enemy believes that this robot holds immense power.
Lan...
Who are you?
L'Egalité has sent me to protect both you and that robot.
Sent me... From space.
From space?! You mean you're—
Take-me-to-your-leader!
Yep.
Continue fire!
Don't hold up until that butler gives the word.
Izo... Are you seriously—?
What's wrong?
Izo?
Then that's—
Array!
I can't!
Why?
All I can ride is a bike!
We'll handle the piloting.
You just have to sit in the cockpit.
That's all?
That's all.
So you'll be in trouble if I don't?
Yes.
When did you arrive in Kamogawa?
Yesterday.
So you've never seen all the wonderful things it has to offer?
Right...
Then...
I've gotta do it!
Was that—?!
What's going on?!
Where's Madoka?!
Sota!
She's in that robot that just took off!
How's the pilot doing?
She seems to be quite excited.
Shall I patch her in?
No thanks.
It's under remote control anyway.
Just tell her to keep a hold of herself, no matter what happens.
You know, like her.
It's coming straight at us! Is it trying to ram it?!
Madoka!
This isn't working!
Here's where it gets fun.
Yes.
Sorry guys, I messed up pretty badly!
Hello? Anyone?
No way!
If I could just pilot it myself...
Yeah!
This feels icky!
Huh? What?!
It punched through a subspace field?!
Is that the legendary—?!
Vox!
You're not too shabby at kendo.
But let me show you how it's really done!
One! Two! Three!
Perfect!
I'll never forget that the soul in my chest would never yield
Don't cry
Promise me, okay
Promise me you'll never cry alone
We will always be together, you know
If we do get sad, we will share our sadness
and be stronger through it
Yay yay yay!
I'll laugh soon, my friend
My friend!
This isn't for just anyone, you're special
I am sure of my own emotions
With an upright voice, I say
Hello!
Sing the song that you always sing
and put a little bit of courage into my heart
Yay
All right, that's done!
Lan, why don't we get something to eat?
Sanga-yaki? Kamogawa soup? We've got wonderful sushi too!
I want my wife's home cooking.
I'm not your wife.
Really?
Yes! Really!
Whatever, I'll just have my uncle fix something up.
Let's go!
Comin' right up!
Kamokawa Spirit
Who was that?!