Muginami! That's dangerous!
Lan, you're so slow!
Why you—!
Out of the way! Out of the way!
Madoka!
Now you've done it!
Oops, sorry!
Muginami!
Roger that!
Here we go, Midori!
They're just like kittens.
It's mostly due to their craft's capabilities.
Even so, standard fighter planes are no match for them now.
Uehara!
Tell those three that they are not to fly into space.
Yes sir!
It's a good thing that Villagiulio hasn't made any moves lately.
However, we can't expect him to leave quietly.
You're right about that.
Cap, you have an outside call.
Okay...
This is Tadokoro on Pharos.
What?
At what time?
That means he's practically here!
Calling all Vox Units.
Return to base immediately!
Return to base?
What? But the fun is just beginning.
Just get back here, stat!
Mr. Tadokoro?
The chairman will arrive at Pharos shortly!
What chairman?
Our boss, the Chairman of Novumundus!
The Chairman...?
Lag-Rin, Lag-Rin
That girl wearing sweats is somehow special
When she takes it off, she can be anything
In search of things she treasures, she'd go to the bottom of the ocean
She's brash to a fault and difficult for those around her
Lag-rin, Lag-rin
I'll come meet you right away
when I hear you call for help
Perfect!
Live life!
Rewrite fate and fly,
Fly away
On a brighter day
If sticking your tongue out and walking proudly gets you in trouble
burn and fly away
Try unite tonight
Lag-rin, Lag-rin
A Lolita in Kamogawa
Where's Tadokoro?
That would be me.
So you are Syozo Tadokoro?
Asteria Lizamarie De Roschefall...
I'll be representing my great-grandfather.
Representing him?
He's getting older and doesn't like to travel long distances.
But we didn't receive a message.
Was there a need?
Oh no...
I guess there wasn't, really...
Mr. Tadokoro looks uncomfortable.
She's got more presence than him.
And you're the Vox pilots?
Woof.
You still do that?
It's a greeting.
I was lying when I said that was a greeting on Earth.
A lie?
You're Madoka Kyono?
Huh? Uh, yes.
Huh?!
You're so-so...
What?
I think you'll make good scissors.
Scissors?
You should have received detailed reports already.
Is there anything that concerns you?
No,
I've been briefed quite thoroughly.
But I wanted to hear everything directly from the people who were involved.
I wonder if Lan has met Asteria before.
It seems so.
She was the one who taught Lan about the customs on Earth.
But...
It was a lie.
"Woof" was a lie.
Madoka Kyono.
Tell me in your own words,
what happened during this incident.
Well, I don't remember very clearly...
But...well, we were having a little argument.
I lost my temper and got upset with Muginami and...
An argument?
Tadokoro...
The report I received
said the cause was due to differences in tactical decisions made during an extreme battle situation.
No, that was...
So, to be more precise,
these girls were fighting amongst themselves during a mission.
Is that correct?
Yes.
Wait!
If I can explain,
that was a very important and sensitive problem.
What kind of problem was it?
Well, basically,
it was about love.
Very well.
You all may go.
Who would've thought
a girl like her would bring the legend to life?
Lan, let's get on.
Madoka...
Would you mind coming with me?
Huh?
It's not like you to want to make a stop somewhere.
I know.
Don't you want to tell Madoka something?
You tend to be awkward about these things.
Is she right?
I'm concerned about something.
Concerned?
The Vox Legend.
Anyway, I want
a wider circuit laid between here and NORAD immediately.
What are you crying about?
You know you can be easily replaced.
By any chance, is the person on the other end of the line...
If you want to retain your position, listen to what I say.
It's the President of the United States.
My apologies, Miss Nakaizumi.
Not at all.
What do you think of this place?
I never imaged Pharos having a room like this.
I made them use lots of aged mahogany and oak.
I believe that being surrounded by steel and plastic corrupts a person.
I see...
Is she really younger than me?
I asked you to come here
in order to exchange information about Vox.
The Vox Legend?
Have you heard about it, Muginami?
You mean the scary story about Vox?
Yes.
What is it about?
I just know that a story exists.
20,000 years ago,
civilization on Earth once collapsed.
As an archaeologist,
what is your assessment of what the world was like 20,000 years ago?
That would fall under the Last Glacial Maximum.
However, there are no archaeological traces from that period.
So therefore you can't analyze it?
Not too long ago, my answer would have been "yes."
But the truth is different.
20,000 years ago, a superior civilization existed on earth.
We are
the descendants of those who left Earth during that time.
I see.
So in a way, you and Muginami are both from this planet.
Aren't you shocked?
Sure, I'm shocked.
But also a little disappointed.
I mean,
if you're both earthlings, this is like coming home for you.
Huh? Coming home?
They're so talented!
Anyway,
our ancestors left this planet 20,000 years ago
Wow!
after a great war took place.
It was because the Vox had lost control,
nearly destroying the world.
The giant green demon will sunder the heavens...
The giant blue demon will devour the stars...
The giant orange demon will spew out darkness...
Through countless sacrifices, they will rule the land.
Feeding off a tainted heart, they awaken from within the mind.
And the demons shall rise.
This poem has been passed down for generations in Le Garite.
My older brother used to scare me
by saying a giant blue demon was going to eat me.
A giant blue demon...
Is that something like the boogeyman?
New nations were established in a faraway galaxy.
And a pact was signed to preserve Earth, where man originated.
We established Earth as an inviolable neutral territory,
and severed all contact with those who remained.
For what purpose?
We feared that the Circle of Rin-ne forged by the Vox
would once again destroy the world.
Wait...
If that's what happened, then why did two come to this planet?
The situation has changed and the Vox has become necessary again.
Oh, I see.
But this has served to revive the legend as well.
The legend...
This is all very interesting.
But I don't know what I can do.
You are an archeologist and have researched the Vox for a long time.
We'd like you to shed some new light on this legend, from your vantage point.
I'm not a fan of science fiction.
Let me put it this way then.
A child who ran away
because of familial strife, returns now only to claim his inheritance.
What would you do if you were the parent?
I'd give him a good punch.
I'm glad we agree!
Thank you very much!
The giant blue demon...
Madoka, are you still awake?
Lan?
Yeah, come in.
Can I sleep here tonight?
Huh?
Sure, but what's wrong?
I thought you might be scared.
Huh?
I'll bet you're the one who's actually scared.
Am not!
You remembered the scary story from this afternoon and got frightened didn't you?
Really?
D-Don't be silly!
I'm not a child!
Look! A demon!
No!
Huh?
There, there, little Lan.
You don't have to be afraid anymore.
Midori isn't a demon, right?
The first time I touched Midori,
I had this nostalgic feeling.
I think I've known Midori from long ago.
I believe that meeting Midori was fate.
I love things like that.
It's so poetic.
It's illogical.
And demons are logical?
Shall we turn in?
Uh-huh.
Good night.
What are you afraid of?
Do I look scared?
If the legend is true...
This time, the Earth really may be destroyed.
That's why I want your help.
To prevent the tragedy
that occurred 20,000 years ago.
As of this moment, all operations associated with Vox Aura will be shut down.
I am banning Madoka Kyono from piloting Aura.
What?
Why is that?
Is it because I might cause Midori to lose control again?
Yes, exactly.
But...!
Please rescind your orders!
Lan...
You based your decision on a groundless legend that's never been proven.
I agree with Lan!
What's wrong with piloting Midori?
You two...
If you know the legend surrounding the Vox,
I shouldn't have to explain.
Continuing to operate Aura poses a risk that cannot be ignored.
I beg your pardon,
but I don't believe we can put up any resistance without Aura.
Please reconsider.
Request denied.
Set up a defense strategy immediately
centered on Vox Lympha and Ignis.
But...!
This is the decision reached by the Novumundus High Council.
It will not be changed.
Things won't go "perfect" this time around.
What will you do, Madoka?
Cap, it's Kyono.
Oh, you're here.
Mr. Tadokoro, what's this all about?
Laffinty and Muginami are responsible.
What?
They've locked themselves up in there and won't open the door
until we rescind the orders to shut down Aura.
What?
Why are those two doing this?
Didn't you put them up to it?
I didn't think so.
Well, those two are going the extra mile for you.
Lan...
Muginami...
Just what is all this nonsense?
As you can see...
They're just like children whose toys were confiscated.
It's no use, Cap.
All entries have been locked from the inside and we can't access them.
I'll go in and talk to them.
What?
We can't let this go on, can we?
How do you intend to get in?
From there!
I'm amazed that you thought of this.
You didn't have to come along.
Don't mind me.
It's the parent's job to spank children who don't listen!
Oww!
Why did you do that?
Why didn't you go along with them?
Huh?
I was quite sure that
if anyone tried to do something, it would be you.
I'm in too much pain to think of an answer.
We Oppose The
Shutdown Of
Aura
Hurry up and go!
Hey, wait! Don't push!
Madoka?
Ouch...
Hey Lan... Muginami...
That was quite an unusual experience.
Can't we ask you to reconsider?
Madoka and Aura are both essential to our team.
I'd be uneasy if it's just Lan and me.
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, you know...
Listen, you two.
Let's stop this.
Madoka?
I really appreciate what you're doing, but this isn't the way.
But that means we won't be able to fly together anymore.
It would be terrible if what happened last time repeats itself.
If it does, I'll stop it.
What if it doesn't stop?
Even if it doesn't stop, I'll make it!
That's what Madoka of the Sweats Club would say.
Yeah, yeah!
Maybe, but no.
The thought of you two getting hurt because of me is even worse.
I don't have the confidence to promise that it won't lose control again.
I'm just not that strong.
Besides, even if I can't pilot Midori,
it's not like you and Lan are going away.
Right, Ms. Chairman?
Is that the answer to my earlier question?
Maybe it is.
I only ordered Aura to be grounded.
Then I'll accept it.
Even if I can't pilot Midori,
nothing will change between us.
Thank you.
I'll be okay.
We will always be the Kamo Girls' Sweats Club.
Madoka...
Madoka!
Now I feel so stupid for doing this.
Don't be.
It made me really happy.
"Disregard it"?
Are you saying you'll overlook everything regarding this incident?
Yes.
But it was a serious violation of service regulations.
This is my decision as the representative of the Novumundus High Council.
By the way,
how are the preparations to equip Lympha and Ignis proceeding?
"Equip"?
Check it out immediately and get it done.
Yes, I will.
I'm going out.
Get the ship ready.
Ship?
You're coming too.
Huh?
Yes, Your Highness.
We must be even more wary of the actions of those who oppose
the blossoming of the Circle of Rin-ne.
In fact, since Villagiulio is openly taking action,
we cannot waste any time whatsoever.
Very well.
Then speed up the retrieval schedule for the Vox units as much as you can.
As you wish, sir.
Isn't it ironic, Moid?
Sir?
The light moves so slowly,
but time cruelly pushes us forward.
Array...
What the—!
Don't look at me like that.
I mean, just don't look, damn it!
Didn't I tell you?
He's the personal maid for the Chairman of Novumundus.
Maid?
But he's a guy...
A lot of things happened.
So what is your answer?
The answer is no.
We will not hand over the Vox to you.
What?
Are you sure?
You'll live to regret it.
The Flower of Lagrange
must never be allowed to blossom again.
I'll never forget that the soul in my chest would never yield
Don't cry
Promise me, okay
Promise me you'll never cry alone
We will always be together, you know
If we do get sad, we will share our sadness
and be stronger through it
Yay yay yay!
I'll laugh soon, my friend
My friend!
This isn't for just anyone, you're special
I am sure of my own emotions
With an upright voice, I say
Hello!
Sing the song that you always sing
and put a little bit of courage into my heart
Yay
I'm Michi.
I'm Sachi.
And I'm Kojiro!
Dad...
It's the preview,
so can't you sound a little more optimistic?
No one's going to watch the next episode if you sound like that.
I'm Kojiro!
You still sound tense.
By the way, I didn't know your name was Kojiro, sir.
Departing Katsuura, Heading to Kamogawa
I'm Kojiro!