Hey, have you heard the phrase "a sea of flames"?
It's saying that the fire is like the sea, right?
I want to see this "sea of flames."
Like, if we set fire to this whole area, all the way to the horizon...
Would that make a "sea of flames"?
Forget it.
You might be able to set the fire, but I doubt you could quell it.
Do not play with fire when you cannot control it, Akura-oh.
If you want to see a sea of flames,
I will show you an ocean of foxfire that devours crimson flames.
Someday.
I wonder what's happening on this world
I fly through the sky into space
and circle the world
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday
With my periodic biorhythm
I'm like a washing machine
Just kidding
Yes, I'm spinning around
Around, around the world
Because there's no limit to my love
Spinning around, around, around the world
I want to tell you that I love you, even if it confuses me
Bam, bam, bam
You're not paying attention
Sometimes love keeps being one-sided
It's gotten so hopelessly complex
But I'll make it all true with a miracle
Hey, God,
I'm your god
I think
Kirihito, are you awake?
How are you feeling?
Do you mind if I come in?
You haven't eaten since morning, right?
You have to eat something.
Oh, good. Your complexion looks great today.
It's your favorite: sautéed liver with garlic chives.
Boys need to eat a lot to build their strength.
If you don't eat, you won't heal as quickly, okay?
Oh, dear, your hand is so cold.
Did you forget to turn on the heat?
I told you, didn't I? I'm busy right now.
You don't need to prepare my meals for me.
Leave me alone, Mother.
Y-You're right. I'm sorry for interrupting your studies.
But...
Meals are a different matter.
Make sure you eat it all.
Once you're done, leave the
plates out in the hallway for me.
The God Goes Back to Being a Child
Damn. I never know how to deal with that woman.
Oh-ho! Are these organ meats, Master Kirihito?
Liver and chives! Liver and chives!
They sealed off Yomotsu Hirasaka, but there are other entrances to the Netherworld.
I made this stone mirror with soil I
brought back from the Netherworld.
When it resonates at the frequency of the Netherworld,
the entrance should be complete.
And soon enough...
the door will open!
I'll enter the Netherworld once more,
and this time, I will regain my old body.
The two of you can stay here.
Daemons and spirits turn to dust when they come in contact with the air of the Netherworld.
But will you be all right going alone?
Yeah.
That woman's hair...
That is the key.
Heading out to do battle, Master Kirihito?
How incredibly brave of you.
I would absolutely love it if you took me to the Netherworld with you.
You! You're that rude bastard from before!
Whoa-oh.
What are you doing here?!
Well, I am so ashamed about
what happened with Kurama.
I really dropped the ball there.
You're pathetic.
You talk such a big game, and then you come back
here with nothing to show for it. That's gutsy, Yatori.
I'm so flattered! You actually remember who I am!
Trickle
Master Kirihito!
Of course.
Do I look so stupid that I can't even remember your name?
Master Kirihito!
The stone mirror is about to open!
It's finally opening...
Master Kirihito, I would like to accompany you as well.
No way!
Fine.
What?
Have it your way.
If you can keep up.
The underground world of stench and defilement.
Those who cannot withstand the
poisonous atmosphere turn to dust.
Slumbering somewhere down here is my body.
And I will get it back.
It's massive.
So this is the Netherworld.
I never imagined that it was so hot down here.
Good grief. I wonder where
Master Kirihito ended up landing.
Master Kirihito!
Thank goodness! I wouldn't
know what to do if I was lost!
How unexpected.
You're still alive.
Huh?
Weak spirits turn to dust when
they touch the Netherworld's air.
I thought that you might turn to dust like Tekkimaru did.
Who are you really?
And what's your interest in Akura-oh?
I...
used to serve Master Akura-oh long ago, you see.
Grrrrr
Smack
I don't know this guy.
Grrrrr
Smack
Don't lie. Someone like you...
It is true.
Although, Master Akura-oh is unlikely to remember me.
Because I was shy and always off in some corner, crying to myself.
You seem young, Master Kirihito, so I doubt you
ever had the pleasure of knowing Master Akura-oh.
He possesses a spirit of pure wickedness.
He is also true to his own desires and cares naught for others.
But even so, many underlings wanted to
follow his lead, and I, too, was one of them.
Are you listening, Master Kirihito?
It's hot.
drip
However, there was one man he kept
by his side, and that was the fox spirit.
drip
Wherever the two went, none could stand before them.
Before their great might, even the
heavenly gods stood by and did nothing.
However...
At one point, Master Akura-oh and the fox grew apart.
And it was all downhill from there.
The fox disappeared, and Master Akura-oh's body went to the Netherworld.
Do you know what their disagreement was—
It was because the fox got stupid.
That volpine fool became
infatuated with some human girl
and got this crazy idea that he
was going to become human too!
Oh!
I will make Nanami's favorite Salisbury steak today.
Do you actually know how to make something that fancy?
Yes, I looked into it, and it is actually rather simple.
And the flavor will disguise the shiitake that are going in.
That's so mean! Nanami hates shiitake mushrooms!
Then let me add something.
I'll put in a lizard's tail.
I want Nanami to have more energy.
Gecko! Softshell turtle! Salamander!
Hey!
You're slacking off again!
Did you even finish cleaning the storehouse, Mizuki?!
Oh, Nanami!
The new year is just around the corner, you know.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, we're having Salisbury steak tonight?
I can't wait!
I see.
So the fox has actually gotten soft.
But seriously, it is so hot here!
Where do you suppose we are?
It feels like we've walked an awfully long way.
Is Master Akura-oh's body still far away?
Maybe I am imagining it, but it seems to be getting hotter and hotter.
Well, Master Kirihito?
I found it.
I found my body.
I can hardly believe it was discarded in such a wretched place.
Wh-What is that mountain of fire?!
No question about it.
My body is at the top of that mountain.
I guess this is the Netherworld's de facto dumping ground.
The gods must use this place to incinerate undesirable entities that are too much for them to handle.
Master Kirihito?
But those flames can't burn my body to ash.
Self-regenerating over and over, for all eternity...
What is the matter, Master Kirihito?
Continually burning in hellfire...
My body...
Master Kirihito!
Now that we know what the situation is,
let us turn back for today.
If we stay here, I am afraid that you will dry up into a husk.
Don't be ridiculous! It's right in front of my eyes!
Unfortunately, we are not immortal.
We cannot climb a mountain like that.
Unless...
If you had some way to extinguish
the flames, that would be different.
Dammit! Dammit!
He put me through this, and I hate him from the depths of my soul,
but I can't retrieve my body without his help?
Whew, we have returned.
Master Kirihito!
Please hang in there, Master Kirihito!
Bastard! What did you do to Master Kirihito?!
Oh, please. I did nothing.
Help, from that bastard?
I can't believe I almost considered that a possibility.
Whatever it is, if it's useful, I'll use it. End of story!
If I can retrieve the body, nothing else matters!
Yes, sir!
Master Kirihito, there's black smoke coming out of the stone mirror!
Poison from the Netherworld.
It's leaking out from the stone mirror?
Monjirou!
Master Kirihito, we must close the hole to the Netherworld!
No!
The connecting aperture can't be sealed without shattering the stone mirror.
I finally got this entrance to the Netherworld opened. I can't destroy it now.
Nothing will stop me from getting
my body back from the Netherworld.
And if I must expose this place to
the Netherworld's poison, so be it.
Not to me...
Kirihito.
Kirihito, are you studies going well?
We received some peaches,
so would you like a late-night snack?
Look, I told you.
I'm busy right now...
Mother.
Next part coming
right up
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
A wedding, huh?
What was that?
Do you want to have one too?
Yeah, I've actually received a proposal already.
What?!
As long as Tomoe's okay with it,
I'm thinking of accepting the offer.
Ever since we descended from Mount Kurama,
I have felt a sharp pain in my chest for some reason.
Master Tomoe, you must go to the Lord Year God's place before the new year arrives.
We need to receive a new talisman and soon.
Oh, is it time for that already?
Tomoe!
Wham
A lowly familiar proposing to his lady and
mistress is deserving of ten thousand deaths!
Outside! Now!
I do not know what you are talking about, but...
That is just fantastic, snake!
I will have your hide and leave you out to dry!
Stop that!
Freeze
Honestly!
What made you think that I'm the one getting married?
You're not, Nanami?
No, I'm not!
I only received a proposal asking to hold a wedding at the shrine.
Oh-ho. From whom?
Himemiko of the Swamp!
Himemiko of the Swamp
Like hell a catfish can marry a human!
Y-You can't know that unless you give it a try!
Himemiko said that when she and Kotarou are ready,
they'd love to hold the ceremony here!
Getting to be there from when they met up to when they get married would be so amazing!
They are playing house, but this is marriage we're talking about.
An interspecies one at that.
And you are not qualified for this task.
I can do it, and I will!
I'm making really good progress
as a god in case you hadn't noticed!
Yeah, I have faith that you can totally pull it off!
And even if Tomoe won't cooperate, you can always count on me.
Thank you, Mizuki.
Damn snake!
Whew. I'm so relieved.
I totally thought that you were going to relinquish your position to get married.
Oh.
I'm not getting married.
Ever.
Master Tomoe, you must get ready soon.
If you do not hurry to the Lord Year God's shrine, the gates will close.
Ah, yes, that is right.
The Year God?
That god that comes to your house every year on New Year's Day?
Yes, the god that visits to bring fruitfulness to the new year.
There was originally one god
who visited every house, but...
My back
hurts
Being overworked took its toll, and he hurt his back.
Now, twelve different gods take turns each year to serve as the Year God.
Therefore, it has become customary to go to the Year God's shrine each year
to receive a talisman from the next Year God.
And so, the two of us will now go to the Year God's shrine.
Oh? When you say "the two of us," are you referring to you and me?
How sharp you are.
That's right.
What do you say we tend to unfinished business with some rare privacy?
Just a couple of old familiars.
You guys are going alone?
When will you be back?
Gee, there is a chance that Mizuki may not be able to return, and I do mean forever.
No, no, it's Tomoe who...
I-I'm coming too.
No!
You'll only make things worse.
I'm coming too!
Sounds good.
Good grief.
It is always like this with her.
Oblivious to her limits, she wants to stick her nose in everything.
Wow...
This is the Year God's shrine?
Well, the entrance at least.
There are so many torii gates.
We just have to pass through these, right?
Nanami
Huh? It has my name written on it.
Why?
These are the Torii Gates of Twelve.
It has been twelve years for this Year God,
and to show your last twelve years to the god,
those who go to the Year God's shrine must pass through these to look back upon their twelve years.
I hate this part, you know.
It makes my head spin.
Makes your head spin?
Call it the twelve-year hangover.
You wait here, Nanami.
The snake and I will go, finish our business, and come right back.
An abrupt shift of the consciousness is not safe for humans.
I'll be fine! It sounds kinda fun anyway!
You just have to go through the torii gate with your name on it, right?
Not again...
And off she goes...
Twelve years...
I envy Nanami for her unburdened soul.
I'm scared of reliving the years after I had
lost Lady Yonomori and shut myself away.
Nanami does define "devil-may-care."
That's not entirely true.
She may say she loves you, but she knows full well that you're not someone she can marry.
Smart girl.
Unfortunately, she is not nearly as conniving as you are.
You're amazing, Tomoe! You know Nanami so well!
The vibe here is getting toxic, so I'm going too.
Of course.
I know Nanami better than anyone.
Her habits. Her mannerisms.
Even her sweet smell...
Yes...
Tomoe...
Nanami went in first, but she still hasn't come out.
Even if some trouble were to crop up, it would not be entirely unexpected.
Don't yell at her, okay?
In all likelihood, her consciousness is probably hung up somewhere.
You do know it's forbidden to pass
through someone else's gate, right?
That doesn't matter now.
Where is Nanami's consciousness?
I couldn't even begin to guess.
Tomoe!
What're you just standing there for?! That was Nanami!
Huh?
Nanami's consciousness has gone back twelve years in time!
What?
That... is Nanami?
Nanami.
On your way home from preschool?
Dad.
What's that?
I got bread crusts!
I'm giving them to Mom!
I'll give you something way better.
Look.
Wow! Chocolate!
Yay!
A prize from the slots.
I won today, you know.
Later.
I've got my war chest now, so let Mom know that I won't be back for a while.
Nanami.
I found you!
The little version of you is cute too.
Let's go. Come on home with me.
Kidnapper!
Wha...
That is definitely her.
I told you that she was, didn't I?! You idiot!
She acts beyond her limits, and she is still just as reckless and crazy.
Not only that, but she has this way of scurrying about, and that is adorable in its own way.
Whatever the case, I must work
quickly to get Nanami back home.
You have my deepest apologies!
Come on! Are you gonna pay up or what?!
I saw your husband lined up at the slots this morning.
If you've got money to play slots, you can pay back your debts!
And you're two whole months behind on rent now too!
I am so sorry.
I promise. I'll have my husband pay you by Monday for sure.
Like I believe that!
If you've got no interest in paying up, either...
You don't have money to begin with, and you...
Renting a place from someone...
We have to make a living too.
It makes things awkward for me here...
I'll leave for today, but make sure you have it next time.
I'll have the money by Monday.
Yes, of course.
I swear!
You have my deepest apologies.
Oh...
Nanami, welcome back.
Mom!
Nanami has barely ever spoken about her parents at all.
Now it makes sense.
Makes sense, my tail. Get going already.
Her mother is suffering from an illness.
She is not long for this world.
So one crept away into the night.
And the other stayed just to die.
Hey, can you hear me?
Come on, Tomoe.
Wait, just a little longer.
That is a Nanami I do not know.
That night, I was looking
at the fleeting remnants of the day
The milky way spread across my vision
It was very beautiful
Hey, can you hear me?
I don't think I can talk to other people about this
I'll call up God, I think
If a new day hadn't begun
then yesterday's tomorrow would be today
and yesterday would be the day before
I'm waiting for you
I'll stay here
The boat is stopped here
If today weren't today
and were that day instead, oh, that'd be nice
Preview
Tomoe and Mizuki take a peek into Nanami's childhood.
Oh, such a stormy life for one so young!
Can't watch! But can't look away!
What thoughts cross Tomoe's mind as he gets close to this tiny Nanami?
That'd be nice, that's what I think
Next time, "The God Receives a Marriage Proposal."
The God Receives a Marriage Proposal
It will be the final episode! Get excited!