We just have to pass through these, right?
Yay!
Tomoe! That was Nanami!
Mom!
Her mother is suffering from an illness.
She is not long for this world.
I wonder what's happening on this world
I fly through the sky into space
and circle the world
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday
With my periodic biorhythm
I'm like a washing machine
Just kidding
Yes, I'm spinning around
Around, around the world
Because there's no limit to my love
Spinning around, around, around the world
I want to tell you that I love you, even if it confuses me
Bam, bam, bam
You're not paying attention
Sometimes love keeps being one-sided
It's gotten so hopelessly complex
But I'll make it all true with a miracle
Hey, God,
I'm your god
I think
The Nanami from twelve years ago is someone I do not recognize.
The God Receives a Marriage Proposal
This bamboo-leaf rice cake is yummy!
I made plenty more.
I'll put the rest in the freezer.
The money I hid in the freezer for this month's electric bill...
is gone!
Curse you...
That was the best hiding spot I could come up with.
Dad
Lucky me!
Ooh! Lucky me!
Mom! Hang in there!
I'm okay. I'm okay.
I'm sorry, Nanami.
Mommy won't be able to stay with you forever,
so if Mommy ever goes away,
you be strong all by yourself, okay?
Locking up and taking care of the house... Everything.
All by myself? What about Dad?
You mustn't count on your dad!
And don't tell him where the money is hidden!
Even if he begs and cries, you keep it to yourself, okay?
Okay.
It would've been nice if I could've
given you a little brother or sister.
Our family line has been entirely female, and for some reason, only one girl is born to each generation.
It was like that for your grandma, your great-grandma, and so on.
Why? I wanted a big brother!
Boo!
Really? But it's quite the romantic story, you know.
They say that once upon a time,
our ancestor received a potion from the gods to become beautiful, and she drank it.
Ever since then, each generation of our family has been blessed with just one healthy, adorable girl.
That's why... Look.
Look at how beautiful I got you to turn out.
But unfortunately, every generation of our family...
has bad luck with men for some reason!
Our family has the worst trouble with men!
So please listen to me, Nanami.
You mustn't count on men, okay?
That way, you won't ruin your health like Mommy did.
You can live big and live long,
even if you have to stay single!
Okay!
I won't count on men!
I'll stay single and get big!
Good!
I see.
So Nanami's nerves of steel come from her late mother.
Interesting.
Human children all grow up by watching their parents.
Nanami is no different. Her parents set the example of who she could become.
Why do you like look you've
gotten settled in here, Tomoe?
I can understand wanting to get your fill of the adorable Nanami, but this is the world of Nanami's memories.
There's nothing we can do here.
Let's hurry up and lead her out of this nightmare.
Yes, you are right.
But even so, just a little longer...
I want to see this side of her that I do not know.
A little longer...
Hey, Emii, what did you ask Santa for this year?
Last year, I got a new Barbar doll, so this year, I'm asking for a matching dream house.
You're so lucky!
I asked for a bicycle.
What about you, Nanami?
I'll be okay.
I lock all the doors every night at home,
so no strange man can just enter in the middle of the night.
You should all lock up before you go to sleep too.
You're weird, Nanami!
Santa comes in through the chimney!
He's not a strange man!
Nanami! I can't watch anymore!
This is like some soap opera!
Who is this Santa?
Santa
I can't leave this to you anymore!
I'm going!
You can continue being lackadaisical if you want.
A powerless child with no guardian.
No wonder she developed such spirit.
It is how she survived.
Life would have been overwhelming otherwise.
Nanami?
Nanami.
Long time no see!
Don't look at me like that!
I'm here to help you!
It's me. Me!
Mizuki, your primary familiar!
But I guess there's no way you'd remember me.
I remember.
What?
Stranger danger!
I should've known.
You've got it all wrong. I'm...
Oh, Tomoe!
Quickly. Come with me.
We have to run.
Hm?
The stranger is closing in.
Okay!
Hey!
Serves you right, you lousy snake!
Tomoe...
When we get home, you are so dead!
I swear...
Your ears!
They're so funny!
Kinda like a cat's!
Can you hear a lot?
Hey! Hey! Hey! Lemme touch your ears!
Why did I get caught up in this mess?
Come on! I wanna touch your ears! I wanna touch your ears!
Well, I suppose we should head for the exit.
The scenery is rather odd.
I thought it was blurry,
but some parts are exceedingly detailed.
I see.
This is the world of her memories.
The more she paid attention to something, the more clearly it is reflected here.
You want ice cream, do you not?
Eep
D-Do not!
Here.
Wow!
Thank you, mister!
Mister?
If there is anything else you desire, let me know.
I am happy to fetch it for you.
In this world, the things that
you long for are as plain as day.
For me, satisfying those needs is a simple matter.
Wow! I can eat this?
Yes.
Really?
So smile.
Like you always do.
I will...
stay by your side.
There is no need to be sad.
I guess the sun's going down now.
The sunset is massive.
Once the sun sets, everyone will go home.
I don't wanna go home.
Back there, no one is waiting for me.
There's only me.
I see.
What you want is...
Only for the time being.
In a few years, when you are older, you will become the head of a household more rowdy than you can imagine.
Are you telling me that I'm gonna get married when I get bigger?
And that I'm gonna make a new family to replace my old one?
Oh, well, no...
That's good 'cause I'm not getting married!
And why is that?
Because my family has really bad luck with deadbeat men!
I can't count on a husband!
I'm gonna stay healthy and single!
It is not that you have bad luck.
You are a poor judge of character.
For example, I would be able to make you happy.
Your wish is my command.
There is surely no man more reliable than I.
You can't use yummy foods to
trick me into a loveless marriage!
So do you really love me?! I need to know!
When asked in such a direct and adorable way...
Yes.
...how could I not tell you the truth?
I do love you.
Well, will you marry me, Nanami?
Know this...
I will ensure you always have
that carefree smile on your face.
Okay!
I will always stay by your side.
Next part coming
right up
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Oh, what in the world am I saying?!
Why did I get caught up in the moment and propose to her?!
How am I going to explain this later?!
Knowing her...
Tomoe, you asked me to marry you, right?
She is bound to press the issue!
How can I possibly get out of this mess?
What's wrong, Tomoe?
You seem awfully fidgety.
Don't you worry about a thing. I can keep a secret.
Nanami will never know what you did to her as a child.
Wait. Seriously?
So you did do something?
Stop that!
Honestly! Why do you guys fight
every time I turn my back on you?
Where are we? What about the Torii Gates of Twelve?
We passed through them already.
Huh? When did we go through?
I can't believe I missed that. I must've fallen asleep.
It does feel like I woke up from a really long dream.
Really? What kind of dream?
It would appear I was worried for nothing.
Even if she did remember what happened,
she would believe the proposal was merely a fantasy.
Nothing more.
I don't know.
I can't remember anything, so it
must not have been that important.
Really? Are you sure?
Nothing about a sweet, handsome stranger?
Did you just say a "stranger"?
Doesn't ring any bells.
She...
She really does not remember?!
Come on! Let's hurry to the Year God's shrine, grab the new talisman, and go home!
If we don't hurry, the sun's gonna set!
The entrance should be around here somewhere.
I wonder what next year's Lord Year God is like.
What do you think, Tomoe?
Tomoe?
Is it true? Does she really not recall?
Would you like some ice cream?
Wow, that was amazing. What'd you make this from?
Wow! Ice cream!
Mizuki, you know what ice cream is?
Yeah! I love it!
Then you have it. Here.
You don't mind, right, Tomoe?
Can I? Thank you! Yay!
You're just like a little kid sometimes, Mizuki.
Until just earlier, you were a child too.
That reminds me. I never knew how much you take after your mother.
You think I'm like my mom?
I dunno. I always thought I took after my dad.
I was really young when she passed away, so I hardly knew her. I can barely remember what she looked like.
We lost all the photos of her in the fire.
It would've been nice if one had survived, but oh well...
It seems twelve years is enough time for a human to change.
Little Nanami and the present one...
are the same person, and yet they are so different.
If that is so...
where did that child disappear to?
Tomoe!
Wh-What is this?!
Floooof
Hi there!
Hey!
Ah! Are you the human god of the Mikage Shrine?
Oh, Lord Year God!
What? Him?
Goodness! Sorry that you had to see me like this.
I have to shear off all this wool before the new year.
If I don't, we're gonna have problems.
Wool?
Floof.
Huh? What?
He is the zodiac sheep.
So this thing is a sheep.
Yay! So fluffy!
Huh? I thought it'd be softer.
This guy says that floof will be in next year, so he does not want to be sheared.
If I can't get him trimmed down,
there's no way he'll fit in the shrine.
Then why did you wait until the last minute to handle this?
Lord Year God, we came to receive next year's talisman.
Oh, right, the talisman.
It is in there!
Floof...
What?!
That's the shrine?!
Just a bit of the sheep's wool is inside there!
He hasn't budged since this morning, so I told him it was time for a haircut, much to his dismay.
Floof!
No, stop! You're crushing the shrine!
Too bad it's not softer.
Shall I put him down?
All that fluff must be really heavy.
Floof...
This coming year is gonna be all about you,
so you should try to look your best for the occasion.
Floof...
You have such wonderful floof.
Instead of staying put here, wouldn't you rather show it off to everybody?
Floof!
Oh?! I can shear off your wool?!
Nanami, you're incredible!
I know, right?
Yep! Incredible! Incredible!
The child I saw twelve years ago has long since vanished.
Is this a slight sense of loss...
that I feel?
Floof!
Thank you, land god. You have my gratitude.
How did it get so small?
Here is next year's talisman.
Wakatoshikami
Otoshimioyanokami
Mitoshinokami
Wakatoshikami
Otoshimioyanokami
Mitoshinokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Consecrated Gods
Wakatoshikami
Mitoshinokami
Otoshimioyanokami
Thank you very much, Lord Year God.
One more thing.
A present. My way of saying thanks.
I heard you say that after the fire,
you didn't have any left.
With the memories I saw while you were in the Torii Gates of Twelve...
I can make you a print.
What is the matter, Nanami?
Mom...
I see.
They have not vanished after all.
Neither the child nor the mother.
Even the emotions she felt back then...
All of these things live on inside her.
Even though...
she may not remember.
Heave-ho!
Oh! Wait! Wait!
Please take these ones too!
Sure thing.
Whew!
It's the first New Year since I became a god.
So much has happened. It's hard to believe.
Traffic
Safety
Marital
Happiness
Good
Business
Safety
of
Family
Fruition
of
Love
Long
Life
As a god...
I stayed up late and made talismans for the first shrine visits of the year!
...I feel that maybe I've begun
to grow into my role somewhat.
That's the Nanami I know! You're so thoughtful.
Slip
Let me see.
What did you do that for?!
Because any worshiper who is sorry enough to ask for your blessing
should not be further punished by your orange-scented chicken scratches.
The more I think about it, the more I
realize how much we've gone through.
Yes, yes. I know, Grandmother Izanami.
But I'm extremely busy preparing for New Year's Eve right now.
Yes, but of course!
I've made the arrangements for your favorite dishes.
Lord Ookuninushi, please look over these as well.
Hey, Kotarou.
For our New Year's shrine visit, what dost thou say to going to Mikage Shrine?
Was that the shrine that Momozono works at?
I wish to go with thee!
And to see where we will hold our ceremony.
Oh!
Look, Himemiko! I set a new personal record!
Kota!
Surely, next year... Surely, next year...
Let us pledge ourselves to one another!
I thought I told you...
Don't book any work for me
until after the 20th this month.
Bam
Good grief, what a badly-fitted door.
Master Shinjurou!
B-Brothers and Botanmaru!
It has been so long since I've seen you!
So how may I help you, Brother?
We've come in the service of Soujoubou the Third.
He sends a resolution.
You are to spend the New Year in training and refrain from all further immersion in the mundane world.
As your senior, I've come to oversee your progress.
What?!
That is not our only reason for coming.
We were concerned for our brother with whom we have been reunited by fate.
So we came to check in on you as representatives of the mountain.
And we thought you might take us to the shrine of the lady land god who did so much for us.
So that's why you tagged along, Brother Jirou.
The old year will end,
and a new year will come for each of us.
All year long,
we've laughed, and we've cried.
It's been a crazy year, but...
it's also been a lot of fun.
Another year comes to an end.
It has been a long year, and yet it really flew by.
Yeah...
Oh, Nanami, snow!
What?
You're right!
Wow! It's already piling up!
Only for the time being.
In a few years, when you are older, you will become the head of a household more rowdy than you can imagine.
Hey, let go of me!
Knock it off!
Strange. I can't remember who told me that.
Nanami.
What?
Peel this mandarin for me.
I can't get it right.
Okay, sure.
You can do that yourself, you stinking brat!
That's right! Nanami isn't your mom, so stop acting like a baby!
Oh, I don't really mind if Mamoru thinks of me as his mom for now.
Say, "Ah!"
Ah!
What? No fair!
Nanami, don't leave us to get
married like a mom would, okay?
I want you to stay my lady and mistress forever and ever!
I'm not sure I like that either.
Don't worry. I'm not getting married.
Probably.
Probably?