Lan, Muginami...
Wait for me!
Lan, isn't this...?
I wonder if something happened to Madoka.
Lag-Rin, Lag-Rin
That girl wearing sweats is somehow special
When she takes it off, she can be anything
In search of things she treasures, she'd go to the bottom of the ocean
She's brash to a fault and difficult for those around her
Lag-rin, Lag-rin
I'll come meet you right away
when I hear you call for help
Perfect!
Live life!
Rewrite fate and fly,
Fly away
On a brighter day
If sticking your tongue out and walking proudly gets you in trouble
burn and fly away
Try unite tonight
Lag-rin, Lag-rin
Kamogawa's Last Line of Defense
Why is Aura starting up?
I'm not sure!
We haven't detected any interference from the outside.
Send the investigation team to the hangar immediately.
Have them find out what's making Aura start up.
Mr. Tadokoro, did something happen to Madoka?
What makes you think that?
Well...
Madoka's Memoria symbol was flickering inside our cockpit.
Flickering?
We can't confirm that on our side.
What?
Madoka is saying something...
She must be on a different frequency.
We're not picking up anything.
I can hear Madoka's voice.
We made a promise!
The Sweats Club always sticks together... The three of us!
How could you two go without me? That's horrible!
Why are we hearing Madoka's voice?
I'm heading over to you!
Madoka, can you hear me?
I don't care if Asteria says no.
No one's going to stop me from flying Midori!
Madoka?
I don't think Madoka can hear us.
Still nothing, sir.
I'm not picking up any transmissions from Kyono Madoka.
Her voice is definitely being transmitted through Aura,
but we don't know how.
What's going on?
Cap, look at this!
Kyono?!
She's coming this way.
What the hell is she doing?
Maybe Aura is channeling Madoka's thoughts to them?
That doesn't explain how Aura started up,
or how the Memoria symbol just appeared,
but it does explain why this is happening.
Aura is evolving nicely...
Mr. Tadokoro, can Madoka be allowed to pilot Aura again?
I tried not to think about it,
but now that I know how Madoka feels...
I can't ignore it.
This isn't something I can authorize on my own.
We need Asteria to change her mind, right?
Please try to convince her one more time.
Enemy Ovid dispatch confirmed.
They're coming!
Laffinty, Muginami, forget about Kyono right now.
But...
Let us worry about the rest.
We're also aware of the difference Kyono's presence
would make in terms of our strategic strength.
I understand.
Roger that!
Approximately 30 minutes until we encounter the enemy.
Continue to launch the Ovids!
An old tale, from ancient times.
The giant green demon will sunder the heavens...
The giant blue demon will devour the stars...
The giant orange demon will spew out darkness...
Through countless sacrifices, they will rule the land...
Feeding off a tainted heart, they awaken from within the mind.
And the demons shall rise.
Do not let them loose...
Never let them...
Hey, do you guys think a giant demon would cease to be
if it didn't have a tainted heart to feed off of?
Or maybe there's no such thing as a pure heart to begin with.
Why are you bringing this up now?
Or maybe this counts as a tainted heart as well.
It's beginning.
Enemy Ovid down, in one blow!
As one would expect of Novumundus' anti-Ovid weaponry.
Jonon, destroyed!
H-Help!
The Russell sustained damage to its legs and has exploded during atmospheric entry!
Our first wave of attack forces have successfully entered the atmosphere!
Are you all right, Lan?
Yes, thank you.
Let's split up.
Good idea. The enemy is after our Vox...
We'll make them split their strength into two groups.
Exactly!
Vox Lympha and Vox Ignis have separated into two different directions.
Just as Lord Villagiulio predicted.
Cap, Madoka has entered Pharos.
She's headed toward the hangar.
We don't know how Aura will respond, so instruct all personnel that they are not to intimidate Kyono.
James...
Get me the Chairman.
Roger!
The enemy force isn't splitting off.
They're focusing their attack on Lympha!
What?!
Push her down beneath gravity.
Light the surface of the earth with the flames of war.
Lan!
Hold on!
Bro—
Villagiulio!
What? You're not going to call me "Brother" anymore?
Absolutely not!
Ignis is engaging with the enemy.
It's enemy unit four. It's Villagiulio, sir!
They're planning to take them down one by one.
Sir, incoming message from our number four fleet ship!
A segment of the enemy force is headed for Pharos!
We've lost Gargo!
We should have known about their anti-Ovid artillery.
Subspace Field deployment confirmed.
I hope it holds.
They've adapted Le Garite's technology well and made their own weapons in such a short time.
No matter.
All units! Prepare to fire at once!
Our target is Pharos!
Block Two has been damaged!
The Subspace Generator's power output is dropping!
Switch to auxiliary power!
We need damage control, stat!
It'll take five minutes to reach maximum power.
If we're hit once more before then, it's all over.
The fleet will be ready to volley in five minutes.
I'm about to settle things on my end too.
It was fun, wasn't it Muginami?
But this time, it's really...
Goodbye!
I'm tired of your nagging, Tadokoro.
I will not authorize Kyono Madoka to fly.
It's time.
There's no turning back, you know.
Depending on how it goes, we might have to go up against the entire world.
Are you scared?
If we're going to die, we'll die together!
Don't even joke about that.
Not gonna happen on my watch.
What?
You too. Put your fist out.
Come on.
Let's go!
Ignis is getting overpowered by Villagiulio's craft.
What about Lympha?!
She's pinned down by the enemy fleet.
The enemy fleet is going into battle formation.
They've got Ignis and Lympha cornered
and they plan to destroy Pharos.
What's the status on the generator?
It's charging at top speed. Three more minutes!
We're at a stalemate.
Tadokoro...
Please ask the Chairman again.
But depending on her answer...
Yes, I know. Where's Kyono?
She's been prepped and is receiving instructions on the new weaponry.
If they find out what we're doing right now, I'll be stripped of my command.
I've got nothing to lose anyway.
It took a while, but I went through the historical data that was left behind on Pharos.
They all contain evidence which defies our current archaeological
understanding of this planet's history from 20,000 years ago.
Even as we speak, my assistant is ignoring the evacuation orders
to learn more about this.
Must you tell me this now?
This is the only time.
Continue.
The people who left Earth 20,000 years ago and those who remained
understand the Vox in different ways.
Those who left feared the Vox as a "giant demon",
but I couldn't find any evidence
of similar legends or data among those who remained.
Perhaps they all died off without leaving stories behind.
Civilization may have sunk to the bottom of the ocean,
but people still left stone tablets.
What are you trying to say?
Maybe the Vox didn't go out of control.
You're wrong.
It happened.
It did go out of control.
How do you know that Madoka will do the same?
You also witnessed it, didn't you?
You saw Aura making the Rin-ne blossom.
Yes, flowers came raining down.
I cannot allow Madoka to pilot it.
Madoka's not the only Vox pilot.
There are three of them.
The number three appears in myths throughout this world.
The Trinity is just one example.
There are countless myths and legends surrounding gods of three.
It's the smallest, yet most stable number.
One is not enough to sustain.
Two would split apart.
With three, there is finally stability.
Madoka is not alone.
The three of them together are the Sweats Club.
Will you please put your faith in them?
The entire fleet is in position.
We are standing by.
Begin the countdown.
Roger!
The Subspace Field will be operational in 30 seconds.
Lympha is unable to counterattack.
Ignis is also cornered.
I will take full responsibility!
I'm not willing to go down in defeat without utilizing our full capabilities.
Aura is...
...authorized for battle.
What?!
I said I'm authorizing Aura to battle.
Roger!
Kyono Madoka is authorized for takeoff!
All right!
Midori, let's go and join up with everyone!
Commencing Vox Aura A.I. Remote System check.
Pilot's heart rate, blood pressure, respiratory rate, all normal.
A.I. Remote Systems are normal. Vox System is operational.
Lan! Muginami!
Madoka!
You're late!
Well, who left me behind?
We can talk later. It's time to strike back!
Perfect!
Now that I have some distance...
It makes sense that the Vox's power level
increases in proportion to the pilot's Bio Telepathic Wave.
So that's Kyono and the girls?
Yes.
And we're just going to sit back and watch
and make our Sweats Club juniors do all the work?
Well, I can't say that I'm enjoying it.
But we can send our thoughts to them.
Ready whenever you are.
Madoka! Look over towards Kamogawa!
What?
That's...
You can do it,
Sweats Club
You can do it, Sweats Club
Everyone!
Fire!
Kamogawa!
That's...
You're late.
I'm sorry.
I knew right from the start that this would happen.
There's no need to pursue him.
Coordinate your attacks between Kyono and Laffinty.
Roger that.
Amazing...
The Bio Telepathic Waves from each pilot far exceed normal levels, yet they continue to remain stable.
They can do this!
Force them back!
Do you think we'll be okay?
Huh?
Madoka will protect us!
You're right.
Sachi?
It is the Jersey Club, after all.
Michi?
Where are you?
Array, here they come!
I know! Thanks anyway!
Hey, you've become more appreciative!
Yurikano would be proud of you!
Yurikano?
Of all places to...!
Run for it!
Big Sis?
It hurts! It hurts!
Someone, help!
Ms. Machiko! Over here! Hurry!
It's Miss Yoko! Miss Yoko's been...!
Big Sis?
Madoka?!
What's wrong, Madoka? What happened?
Big Sis!
Big Sis...
No...
No!
Big Sis...
Don't go...
No, don't pull me...
Madoka, you're making me feel sick!
I'll never forget that the soul in my chest would never yield
Don't cry
Promise me, okay
Promise me you'll never cry alone
We will always be together, you know
If we do get sad, we will share our sadness
and be stronger through it
Yay yay yay!
I'll laugh soon, my friend
My friend!
This isn't for just anyone, you're special
I am sure of my own emotions
With an upright voice, I say
Hello!
Sing the song that you always sing
and put a little bit of courage into my heart
Yay
That's right, I totally forgot!
I still haven't shown you two
all the things that make Kamogawa great, have I?
There are so many places nearby with great views.
And there are still tons of great foods I want you both to try.
That's why...
Let's meet again, okay?
Until We Meet Again, In Kamogawa.