Hang in there!
Reach out your hand!
Trouble in the Netherworld.
You tell me your name too!
What's a human doing in the world of the dead?
I'm Kirihito.
Cool name.
We have been waiting for you.
Our lady and mistress, the presiding goddess of the Netherworld, Lady Izanami...
...awaits the two of you at the shrine.
I got a bad feeling about this.
I wonder what's happening on this world
I fly through the sky into space
and circle the world
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday
With my periodic biorhythm
I'm like a washing machine
Just kidding
Yes, I'm spinning around
Around, around the world
Because there's no limit to my love
Spinning around, around, around the world
I want to tell you that I love you, even if it confuses me
Bam, bam, bam
You're not paying attention
Sometimes love keeps being one-sided
It's gotten so hopelessly complex
But I'll make it all true with a miracle
Hey, God,
I'm your god
I think
Hey, I know we're in the Netherworld and all,
but getting here was totally an accident,
so if you wouldn't mind just telling us how to get to the surface...
Please watch your step, human god.
The residents within this corridor are not what you would consider polite.
Is there a problem?
Skulls! Skulls!
What's the deal with this guy?
We're practically in Hell, and he isn't fazed one bit.
I came here to save him, yet I'm the one freaking out.
It is just beyond these doors.
The God Races Across the Netherworld
Well met, maiden god.
I am the Goddess of the Netherworld.
I welcome thee.
So she's the god of the Netherworld.
Pardon our intrusion.
My name is Momozono Nanami.
This is the human Kirihito.
We want to return to the surface, but we got lost.
So, uh, if it pleases you, can you please tell us how to get there?
Growl
Clap
A token of my welcome.
I doubt thou can partake as it is of the Netherworld, but thou may still enjoy the sight.
This is only making it worse.
If indulgence is thy wish, thou art free to do so.
And the exit to the surface, was it?
If thou wishes to know, I do not mind guiding thee.
However, I am afraid thy companion shall not make the trip. He is forbidden to leave my kingdom henceforth.
Kirihito!
Wh-Why?
Because he possesses the body of a dead man.
What?
He is human, and yet he is no longer human.
A spiritual being resides within that dead man's body.
Did thou truly not notice, human god?
Even if that's true,
I can't leave him behind without hearing his side.
Please return him to me.
I'm sure he has his reasons.
His reasons are of no consequence.
I cannot allow the dead to leave the Netherworld.
My word is final.
This is a matter of what is just. It is not a matter of feelings.
He is not one who should be unleashed upon the surface.
Surely, thou must understand as well.
I see.
Return to the surface.
It seems that thou art still not a full-fledged god.
Her reasoning is sound.
I can't argue with her.
Even so... I must...
There's no way I'm going to back down without getting to the bottom of this.
Izanami.
Oh, my word...
Now I'm a denizen of the Netherworld too.
Please allow me to remain here as well, Izanami.
Very well then.
I will welcome thee.
It actually worked.
I really made it taste like a sweet potato donut.
I knew it.
Are you not confident in your power?
I'm starting to think that I can save you, after all, Kirihito.
Kirihito
Please, white talisman, work with me to find Kirihito.
I was trapped in a cold darkness.
How many decades had it been since I had stopped thinking about how much time had passed?
How many centuries had it been since I had last seen light?
I was very nearly in danger of
even forgetting just who I was.
Excuse me.
Is there someone there?
Who are you?
Nice to meet you. My name is Mori Kirihito.
About halfway up this mountain,
I got caught in an avalanche and ended up trapped in the snow.
I hung in there for a couple days,
but it seems my body is giving out now...
I mean, this was my first time dying, after all.
I completely lost it and used up a lot of energy.
A disembodied human spirit, huh?
When was the last time I even saw a human?
It seems they are still as frail as I recall.
I'll cut to the chase.
It's high time that I passed on.
But I have one regret I have trouble letting go of.
As I was leaving the house, I got in an argument with my mom.
It was a really stupid argument.
If I had known that was gonna be the last time I'd ever talk with her, I wouldn't've been so mean.
I'm sure my mom must think the same thing, and I don't want her to blame herself.
I can't let things end that way.
If you wouldn't mind doing me a favor, would you please let my mother know that I was sorry?
What is he going on about? He's not making any sense.
He's dead already. What's he got to gain from passing on that message?
I mean, I thought about writing a farewell note,
but my hands wouldn't move.
But that's right.
Humans are stupid and incomprehensible like that. I remember now.
You ask the impossible.
What?
I am bound to this spot.
My body has been stolen by scoundrels.
Thanks to that, here I am, just my soul
clinging to some rocks in these mountains.
In that case, take my body.
It's buried in the snow and won't move,
but maybe you can use it.
Would you grant me my request then?
Sure.
I only agreed on a whim.
I didn't give a damn about his situation.
Chances were I was going to die right along with his body.
If it had any potential, there was no harm in trying.
Anything to escape from that nightmare.
Even if I met my end, I no longer cared.
Because if this worked...
there'd be no more darkness.
I was irritable that day, and...
Who're they?
What're they talking about?
My... hand?
Kirihito!
I can feel...
I can move...
How many centuries had it been since I'd seen light?
Kirihito, you're okay now.
I can't imagine what it was like for you to be trapped in the snow for so long.
You did good hanging in there by yourself.
How many years had it been since I'd felt warm?
Mother...
I'd like to apologize for the fight we had the other day.
You don't have to worry about that.
Okay, Kirihito?
Bit by bit, I started to remember my past.
And then...
I have to get myself back to normal.
This weak body is inconvenient.
I must sleep once a day, or this form doesn't sustain itself.
And on top of that, daemons are about all I can use.
It takes seven freakin' days to make one?
But I've got time.
I'll conceal my true nature.
I cannot arouse unwanted suspicion.
As my senses return, so does my desire to strike back.
Those damn gods...
Damn them for sending my body to the Netherworld.
It seems they found it too much to handle.
What shall we do, Master Akura-oh?
Don't call me by that name.
There's no chance the Netherworld's poison could dispose of my body.
I just have to find someone to fetch it for me.
I'm being shut away in darkness.
Don't tell me.
Was all of that until now a dream?
A figment of my imagination seen in this long time of darkness...
No more!
I don't want to be in darkness anymore!
There you are! Kirihito, I came to save you!
Wh-Where am I?
What happened?
You're in the dungeon of Izanami's shrine!
Izanami totally jumped you and locked you away in here!
You don't remember?
It was a real pain finding this place, you know.
Want to know how I found it?
You want to know, right? Right?
Believe it or not, it was the great Nanami's specially made white talisman...
Ahem
So warm...
Aaah!
What are you doing, blindsiding me like that?!
My heart belongs to Tomoe, the most beautiful fox ever!
Tomoe?
What's wrong?
You look kind of pale.
Ow!
You should've hightailed it out of here by yourself.
Why did you go through the trouble of saving me?
What?
You could've gone back to the surface by yourself, right?
I don't particularly have a reason for saving you.
We're going to sneak out so they don't find us.
Because if they do, they might turn us into skulls.
Skulls?
I swear, humans are incomprehensible.
They're idiotic creatures.
Goodness! The Lucky Mallet is not
considered a divine tool for nothing!
We can grow bigger or grow smaller,
whatever we please!
Gold, silver, and other treasures flow in abundance as if from a spring!
But I had no idea it was still at the shrine.
Lady Narukami entrusted us with it to return to Lord Daikokuten,
but it would be a shame to return it so soon.
Right. After all, no one is watching.
Perhaps we can pretend to have forgotten...
Master Tomoe!
Terrible news!
Revert back! You look hideous!
I hate to tell you this, but we just got word from Lord Otohiko!
Lady Nanami has gone missing in the Netherworld!
Where...
No one has any idea where she is in there.
Mi...
Master Mizuki was acting
independently of Lady Nanami.
That idiot.
I sent her off to the Divine Assembly,
so what is she doing in the Netherworld?
Even the gods of the surface rarely travel there.
One false move, and it becomes the kind of place from which you never return.
Ever.
We leave at once!
Make the preparations, Kotetsu!
Are you going to the Netherworld?
Obviously.
I am bringing that idiot back.
I swear it.
Next part coming
right up
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Sorry to keep you waiting, meow, Lady Izanami!
Tonight we welcome the human goddess!
I, Hiou, will also be purr-viding entertainment!
Lady Izanami?! What is the matter, meow?!
Nanami duped me and fled with the man.
Meow?
Seize her for me.
She is my new playmate.
Do not let her escape.
Meow-ger!
Nanami, art thou truly capable of saving a person?
We should be safe this far out.
We need to hurry up and return to the surface.
I'm starting to feel better about my divine power,
so let's have this white talisman show us the way to the exit.
And so...
Kirihito! Hey, what's wrong?
I just felt dizzy.
Could it be that you're not feeling well?
Otohiko said the air in the Netherworld causes the human body to rot and stuff.
That won't be a problem.
As long as I'm touching some part of a god's body,
the poison of the Netherworld won't affect me.
I took a lock of your hair while you were sleeping.
Oh, that's a relief.
Wait, my hair?!
Hair?!
Thanks to that, I'm spared from having to walk while holding hands with you.
Okay, but if you need to take a break, just let me know.
Kirihito, someone's come after us.
Ah! Ah! Testing, testing!
Human god and man!
I know that you are hiding, meow!
You have five meow-nites to reveal yourselves.
If not, I, Hiou, Lady Izanami's familiar, will burn you two to ashes along with the forest, meow!
If she's going to burn us along with the forest,
then she probably hasn't pinpointed our actual location.
We gotta get out of here.
To the exit
Talisman, please show us the way out of here.
Softly... Quietly...
Hurry!
Tomoe, what should I do?
Tomoe!
Their time's me-out! Set the fire!
Oh, no!
Max headwind!
Meow! The direction of the wind!
That should buy us some time.
Let's hurry, Kirihito.
There's no one here to tell me what I should do.
There's only the two of us here.
So it's up to me to handle it!
What's wrong, Kirihito?
The white talisman has stopped here.
My divine power wasn't strong enough?!
No, this scenery looks familiar.
It's where we started.
We're near the Yomotsu Hirasaka entrance.
What? Was it this dark?
Before, there was light from the
surface shining through the hole.
Looks like someone went and plugged the damn thing up.
Seal
Meanwhile, back on the surface...
Hey, you.
Move aside.
I have business below.
Long time no see, fox.
I have no interest in you.
So you wished to go to the Netherworld?
Too bad for you.
I sealed this hole with a new barrier boulder.
Move the rock aside.
My lady and mistress is still inside.
If that maiden is truly a god, she can free herself.
If she were not a god...
If she were simply a human being, she is sure to be long dead.
Going to her rescue would be a waste of time.
Move aside!
You think a familiar can win against a god, fox?
In all likelihood, you are using that maiden to do as you please, just as you have done in the past.
I will do away with you here once more, as befits a fox.
Please wait one moment, Lord War God!
As a familiar, Master Tomoe is a most excellent fox.
I beg of you... I beg of you...
Kotetsu.
He speaks the truth.
I cannot possibly win as a familiar.
That is the way of things.
Tomoe, from now on, you should
live here at this shrine as a familiar.
I'm certain the spirits of the shrine will welcome you too.
I am a spirit.
I cannot live in such a stifling place.
You'll be fine.
Once we seal the familiar contract,
you'll be able to live here with ease.
However, becoming a familiar means that
even what is dark will be overcome with light.
It means that you will be under the constraint of gods.
I understand, Master Tomoe.
If you long for your mistress, I will send you to her!
Return to being a spirit!
Though he may dissolve the contract,
Master Tomoe is still a loyal familiar of the shrine.
Curse you, damnable fox!
Netherworld gate, open!
It didn't work?!
What do I do?
Meow!
Kirihito, run as far away as you can.
I'll draw their attention.
How?
It'll be okay.
I have one white talisman left.
We'll be getting back to the surface real soon.
Just hang in there.
What can she do with one single talisman?
Dammit! My head is spinning.
What is wrong with this body?
It kills me to back down, but right now,
I need to get back to the surface and regroup.
With her hair, I can return as I please. She's of no use to me now.
We'll be getting back to the surface real soon.
Just hang in there.
I'll get as far away as possible and buy time for Kirihito to escape.
I have to be the one to handle this.
I have to.
Found you, meow!
Too bright!
Light?
Nanami!
Tomoe!
I missed you.
Are you well?
Yeah.
Thank goodness.
I was worried.
Tomoe. Tomoe!
Now, Nanami,
mind telling me why you missed the Divine Assembly to play around with a cat in the Netherworld?
What do you have to say for yourself?
His hair's so long.
What's that about?
Oh, how I've missed you.
It's been a while, Tomoe.
The sun will be setting soon.
I wonder if Master Tomoe was able to find his way safely to Lady Nanami.
Kotetsu!
Lady Nanami!
I am so glad you are safe!
Same to you, Kotetsu. Thank you for coming.
I'm finally back.
And Kirihito too.
H-H-Hey! What are you doing, Tomoe?!
I brought him with us because he was there, but I have no idea who this man is.
He appears to be human, but he is lifeless.
It is as though he is dead.
If necessary, I could always
return him to the Netherworld.
Nanami, what is wrong?!
Lady Nanami!
She is asleep?
What is this woman to you?
Master Tomoe!
So...
This is the thanks I get for saving you?
By no means.
This is hardly enough to repay you in full.
But I have grown tired as well.
This will be as far as we go today.
So long!
Daemons, huh?
Master Tomoe, who in the world was that man?
A paltry matter. Ignore him.
We are going to the Grand Shrine.
I shall carry Nanami there.
Yes, sir.
What is this woman to you?
Hey, can you hear me?
Master Tomoe? What is the matter?
Oh...
It is nothing.
Hey, can you hear me?
That night, I was looking
at the fleeting remnants of the day
The milky way spread across my vision
It was very beautiful
Hey, can you hear me?
I don't think I can talk to other people about this
I'll call up God, I think
If a new day hadn't begun
then yesterday's tomorrow would be today
and yesterday would be the day before
I'm waiting for you
I'll stay here
The boat is stopped here
Preview
Nanami has returned!
Tomoe is back to being a spirit.
Oh, an invisible wall stands between them.
If today weren't today
Though it may divide them,
and were that day instead, oh, that'd be nice
this feeling is the one thing it cannot stop.
Next time, "The God Makes Her Second Romantic Confession."
The God Makes Her Second Romantic Confession
I'll say it as many times as it takes.