Wow!
The ocean looks so pretty!
Lord Dizelmine! I want to go too!
I wish I could take you there too, Yuriyuri.
Really?
Then let's go!
I can't. Today, I have an important meeting to attend.
We can visit some other day.
Huh?
That's no fun.
Boo!
You might get sick like last time if you push yourself too hard.
Right now, the most important thing for you to do is rest.
Understood?
Okay!
I realize this is part of your duties,
but still, I applaud you.
She's our trump card.
Assign her more chaperones
so that she doesn't go off on her own.
As you wish.
I'm counting on you.
Back then we tried to fly with propellers that couldn't do it
We ran with bare feet, and now we see different skies
We always live
full of conviction
that we are misunderstood
You're precious to me
but lost at the same time
I'll get over it
Spin the wheel of fate
Inside the dew, like magic,
are tears and sunny days
I feel lonely now
I'm sure my dream will come true
and we will be together forever
A Reunion in Kamogawa
What on earth was that thing yesterday?
You mean with the experiment?
Yeah.
There's this thing with Midori...
And a girl appeared in my cockpit.
What was she trying to tell me?
Lan.
What is it?
Are you afraid of your brother?
He would never forgive me for seeking asylum.
Don't worry.
I'm sure Asteria will make things work out.
I hope so.
Are you serious?!
I don't mess around when it comes to that sort of thing.
All right.
Ms. Watabe?
Yes, sir. I'll begin preparations right away.
This is going to be fun...
We have word that shuttles have departed
both the Le Garite and De Metrio mother ships
with their respective kings aboard.
I hope this ends without incident.
It would certainly be better at least
if they got into a fist fight, rather than an intergalactic war near Earth.
It's been a while.
You haven't changed.
Glad to see you're in good health too, Captain Tadokoro.
The look on your face says you're still having problems with the ladies.
That's enough.
His Majesty, the King of Le Garite.
This way, please.
When did you install this?
Huh?
Yo.
You came alone?
Nah, I'm here with friends.
How about you?
My constituents.
Regal, as always. You haven't changed a bit.
Same for you.
As always.
It appears the information we have of the two of you
being best friends since your Academy days is true.
We've prepared a quiet location suited for your historical conference.
Please follow me.
Is my younger sister aboard this vessel?
Yes.
She and her two friends are engaging in girl talk.
What d'you say?
First one to find them can revoke their asylum status?
Looks like becoming king
has given you a better sense of humor.
So we're starting this already?
What's this for?
Huh?
My brother?
Looks like it worked.
Asteria, what are you doing here?
What're you planning?
You'll see.
Okay, it's show time.
Lights, camera!
Action!
I see...
So this is the quiet place suited for our historic conference, huh?
Did you put her up to this?
You think that girl's the type who'd listen to a guy like me?
She wants to hear what the boys have to say.
About our childhood?
Uh, that's not exactly what I meant...
But come to think of it,
weren't we locked up together like this once before?
It was when our shuttle reactor went critical
after failing on a Subspace trip.
That was the year I went to study abroad at your Academy, so...
We were both in our first year.
Second year.
We should've just waited for help,
but thanks to your meddling,
it took them two extra weeks to find us.
Except if I hadn't, the ship would've been completely destroyed.
I'd have saved it if I was alone.
So they both went to the same school?
No wonder they seem to get along.
Are you watching the same thing I am?
Well, well, looks like we're all here.
Moid?!
And why are you here?
That's what we'd like to—
Lord Villagiulio?!
What exactly are you scheming here?!
Silence.
They're in the middle of a conference.
You call that a conference?
I made these special arrangements for those two shy little boys.
You should thank me.
Nothing you say will change the Chairman's mind.
Let's just watch and see how it goes.
Did you sleep well last night?
What kind of question is that?
Well, wasn't yesterday the first time you witnessed
the power of the Vox?
Even when you used your own sister,
word on the street is that you couldn't open the Rinne.
So I thought the legend might've scared you into insomnia.
Just like when you were a kid.
My brother was scared?
Aren't you glad?
Being a wuss runs in the family, Lan.
Yes.
You're right, I got very little sleep.
I was too excited.
Oh?
With that power, I can solve the thousand year problem.
Shut up!
Guess the rumors about you wanting to use the Vox
to destroy our planet are true, then.
I only wish to avert impending doom.
You've lost family.
You, more than anyone, should know the danger of the Vox.
But rest assured,
under our research and care,
we can expand upon Vox Aura's potential.
We can avoid further tragedy.
After all, Aura's pilot is special.
Me?
Special?
Looks like he's finally sharing his true feelings.
I see...
If you're really that into Madoka,
I'm gonna have to change my plans.
Hell, why don't we just fight over her as warring nations?
Well?
That's fine by me.
An unregistered craft has left the Le Garite mother ship
and is headed right for us.
Jim?
No response from the Occupational Forces, Ma'am.
They're letting it through.
Connect me to Cap.
Tadokoro here.
From Le Garite?
Hey, look!
An Ovid?!
Care to explain, Moid?
Looks like pretty terrible piloting, to me.
It's one of your pilots.
No complaints if we take care of it, right?
Be my guest. Go easy, though.
Wow...
It's all over the place.
Must be a newbie.
Not that I'm any better, but still.
Oh no!
Look where it's going! It's headed for Kamogawa!
What?!
Can I get a Kamopaccio, please?
Sure. One order of Kamopaccio!
Hey Izo! It's burning.
Oh, no!
Hot!
You still thinking about that thing from yesterday?
Hell yeah.
If what happened on Militia happens here,
think how many people would die!
The king of Le Garite and Villagiulio
are in talks to avoid just that.
Yurikano paved the way for this.
Let's have faith.
How many more of these Sangayaki Lunch Specials do we need?
Three more.
An Ovid!
A Le Garite production model!
This is bad! It's coming right at us!
Everybody, run!
It's down!
Lan.
Brother!
Bro!
You sure look busy!
Uh, yeah. Gotta get to Kamogawa...
Sorry! We'll catch up later!
Forgive me.
What the hell is the Le Garite thinking?!
Aren't they here for the conference?
Doesn't matter, this is crazy!
Hey you!
Le Garite pilot!
You can hear me, right?!
Are you out of your mind?!
This is Kamogawa,
a designated neutral zone of both De Metrio and Le Garite!
That hurt... What a landing!
Yurikano?
Heya!
Damn it!
Take your hands off of me!
I have to speak to her!
Let me go, dammit!
Yurikano!
It's me! Array!
Why don't you recognize me?!
Yurikano...
Yurikano!
I'm so sorry, Lord Dizelmine.
I broke your promise and came here anyway!
You're a very bad girl, Yuriyuri.
Yuriyuri?!
The Princess of De Metrio?!
That's her?!
Yes...
She's Villagiulio's real sister.
Oh, but I know that deep down,
he considers you his little sister, Muginami.
So you shouldn't worry about whom he loves more.
Look, Lan, that's not really important right now.
I see. His real sister, huh?
We get it, Madoka!
But Lan, what was Yurikano doing on Le Garite?
I don't know.
Didn't you come on the same ship?
No...
Lan?
I met Lady Yurikano several times when I was little.
But I never saw her on the ship.
I didn't even know that we were on board together.
My brother didn't say a word about it during our trip.
So it was a secret.
Explain yourself!
Aren't you glad your little sister is alive?
I'm asking why the hell she was with Le Garite!
I rescued her from the tragedy that was Militia Zodia.
All while you were busy playing rebel and calling yourselves Kiss.
Don't fuck with me!
For a while, I feared she wouldn't make it,
but we finally managed to heal her up to this point.
As her older brother, shouldn't you be happy for her?
Older brother?
That's right.
This man is your real older brother, Yuriyuri.
Um... I...
She doesn't remember anything?
No. Not even about her being the princess of De Metrio.
Lord Villagiulio.
Biotelemetry numbers are normal.
Her DNA pattern is a perfect match with Lady Yurikano.
She is not a clone.
But she's changed so much...
It's hard to believe!
It's her, all right.
No doubt about it.
I can tell.
She's acting exactly like she did when she was a little kid.
Right down to calling herself Yuriyuri.
We're going home!
Huh?
Do you plan on stopping them?
No!
I'm not leaving without Lord Dizelmine!
I see you've tamed her well.
Don't be ridiculous.
More importantly, what about our conference?
Although we're at fault,
I think continuing talks might be difficult.
We've got no choice then.
We'll meet again at the Intergalactic Conference.
If you'll excuse us, then.
Lord Villagiulio!
Are you just going to let them leave?!
Enough!
Please, leave me alone right now.
She's terrible!
Calm down, Muginami!
But! But I feel so sorry for him!
I'm sorry.
You have nothing to apologize for, Lan!
I know, but...
Okay! Let's go and see them.
Huh? Right now?
We should act now while it's still fresh on our minds!
Huh? But—
Let's go!
Can I ask you one question?
Was all this commotion part of your plan?
Well...
Just a minute!
I'd like to speak with Miss Yurikano.
Yesterday, it was you who appeared in my cockpit, wasn't it?
Cockpit?
Mind telling me what this is about, Miss Kyono Madoka?
Yesterday, during our experiment,
she appeared in Aura's cockpit.
That's quite strange.
She was with me the entire time.
But it was definitely Miss Yurikano.
Well, Yuriyuri?
Do you recall meeting with Miss Madoka?
You are...
Uh-huh. Do you remember me?
Nope, sure don't!
What?!
Even after you grabbed me and choked me like that?!
Oh yeah! What about before that?!
We also met another time!
Stop right there.
Hold on, Asteria.
I've heard enough.
Now's not the time.
Let's go.
For now, I guess we'll do as she says.
Right.
How'd it go?
She's definitely that girl.
I'm positive!
But if she's the real Miss Yurikano,
wouldn't she act more unwilling?
That's why we need to have a real talk with her!
Otherwise, Big Brother Giuvi and Lan's brother will—
Then let's sneak in!
Huh?
Sneak in where?
If we stay here, you'll never get a chance to talk!
Don't worry. Just leave it to me.
Lady Yurikano is on board.
We'll continue negotiations regarding Lady Lan.
Moid.
Yes?
I thought I told you to assign
more chaperones to Yurikano, did I not?
I'm terribly sorry!
Although it did allow us to gather some unexpected information.
Yes.
Brother!
Please wait!
Lan?
Brother...
I'd like to return to Le Garite...
But I want to bring my friends.
'Scuse us, comin' through.
Oh my.
Never even been to Tokyo, but outer space is friggin' cool.
I've been begging Laffy to take me there with her...
Oh, you can call me Perfect.
And this here is...
Suzuki Namie.
Do you mind?
Of course not.
Thanks a bunch, man.
Thanks so much!
Is it all right to let them go?
No, of course not.
Come on! We're in a huge hurry!
I know!
But I'm not just gonna manhandle my nets!
To a fisherman, they're more important than life itself.
You guys should know that by now
after being in Kamogawa for so long!
Oh yeah...
So Izo, when are you gonna ask Sachi out to the movies?
I never made such promise!
Come on! How tangled can these nets get?!
Oh, no! The Le Garite shuttle's taking off!
Damn! This can't be happening!
Yurikano!
Oh! Super amazing, yeah?
So this is outer space!
Perfect says "wow!"
"Just leave it to me," she says.
Totally amazing, yeah?
"After all, I'm a member of Kiss," she says...
Totally crazy, yeah?!
I think she's having too much fun.
Friggin' super amazing, yeah ?
Fun?! This is embarrassing.
You can take off those disguises now,
Miss Madoka. Miss Muginami.
Sure thing...
What do we do now?
It seems Dizelmine is hellbent on going to war with me.
On the water's surface I see a light reflected that stirs my heart
When we realized our bond,
we were already deeply connected under the blue sky
We had so much fun, as in a daze, that time seemed forgotten
I prayed that there would be no end to the way we lived
I won't forget our days together, although time goes by,
and you are far from me now,
because you left behind a wonderful world
for me to wait in
Oh, wow! This spaceship is huge!
There are even sections of it that I'm not familiar with.
Maybe that's where Miss Yurikano is.
What? No, she wouldn't be there.
Do you know of such a place?
No, it's just my imagination.
After all, that place is an eel farm.
Eel?
This spaceship really is huge...
Orbiting Above the Summer Skies of Kamogawa