What?
A pincer attack!
So that's the Ovid prophesied in the ancient legend....
The Vox.
It's beautiful.
The Ovid that's entered the airspace above Kamogawa has been confirmed as a new enemy combatant.
We'll refer to it as unit three.
Issue an order to the pilot!
Tell her to vacate the premises immediately!
Hey, you in the black robot over there!
Watch what you're doing!
That's the town where Uncle Hiroshi and Ms. Machiko, Sachi, Michi,
Erika, and everyone else lives!
Lovely, lovely
The girl in the training suit is somehow special
When she takes it off, she can be anything
To look for something she treasures, she'd go to the bottom of the ocean
The surge of her emotions can turn her opposition into mist
I come to meet you as fast as I can
when your visions call to me
Perfect!
Live your life!
Rewrite fate and fly
Fly away
Oh and fly today
If it's dangerous to laugh at your foes as you advance
burn brighter and fly away
Try, unite, unite
Lovely, lovely
I'm coming to save you right now,
Kamogawa!
Let's see how good the pilot
who is pledged to the legendary Ovid really is.
Vox Aura is now engaged in close-range combat with enemy unit three.
Lan Blooms in Kamogawa
The Municipal Fire and Disaster Management Department has issued
an evacuation order for all Kamogawa residents.
Can you do it, my lady?
You're afraid of the legend.
Can you really handle the Vox in your current state?
It's impossible, isn't it?
You were unable to activate the Vox System despite trying countless times.
You couldn't transform Lympha into Warrior Mode.
My lady, you weren't able to overcome your fear.
Madoka doesn't know the legend.
That's why she can pilot Aura so well.
That's right.
She doesn't know.
Enemy unit two has fallen out of range.
Two enemy Ovid units remain within the battle zone.
So the first one is underwater.
Do you think it's an attempt to rescue the detained unit one and its pilot?
Expand the sea gauge sensors in the surrounding area to full scale!
And force Vox back into Piercer Mode!
Get her out of the area by using the AI remote.
It's no use, sir!
Our signals are being overridden by the pilot's telepathic control waves.
Great... If only a certain princess were a little more useful,
then we wouldn't have to rely on a complete amateur to handle everything on her own!
Whoa!
I'm not done yet!
Is this the power of the Vox?
She's been hit.
Ouch! I should have asked Erika to let me practice that move.
Oh no!
Grandpa Nagase's peanut farm!
I'm so sorry, Grandpa Nagase.
I'll treat you to some seaweed with sesame next time!
You are indeed worthy to be the pilot of the Vox.
You instantly reacted to my Non-Lethal Mode Strike and boldly took action. I'm impressed.
Huh?
I've never seen such a move.
Are you, by any chance, a pilot of this planet?
So what if I am?
This is a warning.
I don't know what you were told by the ones from Le Garite,
but we have no wish to harm you people.
All we want is for you to come to our planet.
How about an "I'm sorry"?
First, to Grandpa Nagase and his peanut farm.
Second, to everyone in Kamogawa. You owe them an apology!
Never mind that.
"Never mind that"?
You drop out of the sky suddenly and scare everyone half to death.
How can you be like that? Huh?
You think the crisis on your planet is more important?!
What's that supposed to mean?
Why can't we hear the enemy transmission?
It must be a secure line.
What do you mean "big and small"?
The love people have for this town is just as strong as yours!
So you're saying you won't listen to my request?
You're in for a big surprise if you think the Sweats Club blindly listens to every request!
Sweats Club?
So I have no choice but to turn you down.
That's unfortunate.
I have no choice...
but to let you have it!
If I remember correctly, the Ayanokoji family on 7th Street demolished their old house and are rebuilding it
so their lot should be vacant now.
I've got to hand it to them!
This is a really nice and large empty lot!
Vox Aura has resumed close-range combat with enemy unit three!
If I didn't know
about the fate that awaits those who fight alongside the Vox,
then I could be like Madoka.
Aura is unable to escape the enemy's assault!
The pilot's respiratory and circulatory readings will reach dangerous levels shortly.
No, that's not it.
She is...
There's a warning on the Catapult Conveyor!
What?!
Vox Lympha has entered into T.O. sequence!
What are you trying to do, my lady?
I already told you.
Even if you go, there is nothing you can do.
Perhaps there's nothing I can do, but there's something I must do.
Because Madoka can't even be scared.
I was the one who made her like that.
I can't get Lympha out of its self-select launch mode!
Fin E Ld Si Laffinty, taking off!
Enemy unit two has reappeared from underwater.
Another Vox. Sorry, Array.
You'll have to wait a bit longer!
Damage to the ventral stabilizer!
Drag is increasing.
Her speed is dropping.
Don't try anything stupid.
Kirius is busy playing with your friend over there!
Thank goodness!
There's no need to worry about the customers since this shop went out of business last week.
I don't get it.
Why would she do something so reckless twice in a row?
Is this some kind of ritual required of a pilot
who has made a vow to a Vox?
I thought it would work this time.
Let me borrow this for a bit!
How's this?
Choking an Ovid that doesn't even breathe?
They didn't teach this at the academy in De Metrio.
Is it a finishing technique unique to this planet?
Tanpopo Children's Park has been destroyed!
Why isn't this one transforming?
Could it be?
I would think it's easier to fight in humanoid form.
Why doesn't she—?
That is because the pilot cannot transform Lympha into Warrior Mode.
You are Madoka Kyono's cousin,
correct?
Yoko!
And what if I am?
I have a question.
How did you convince Madoka to get back on her feet?
I just reminded her of something that should come naturally.
"Something that should come naturally"?
To finish whatever you start.
I guess you could call it the Sweats Club spirit.
Sweats Club?
When I hear a voice that moves my heart,
I'll put on my sweats and give it my all.
The end result alone isn't enough to inspire me.
I leave it up to my heart to decide,
on whether or not to take something on.
Move forward!
Run!
That's the Sweats Club spirit!
When the voice that moves your heart reaches you,
Put on your sweats and get ready!
Duty and justice alone aren't enough to convince me.
Thank you...
Perfect!
What?!
I leave it up to my heart to decide,
on whether or not to take on a request.
Madoka?
Don't run away.
Are you serious?
Keep moving forward.
That's the Sweats Club spirit!
I want you to hear that voice too.
It's a voice that has a passionate spirit...
I'm sorry, Madoka!
Lan?
I've done such a terrible thing to you.
Just because I can't do anything,
I've pushed everything onto you.
I'm sorry, Madoka!
I'm so sorry.
Lan, you're totally full of the Sweats Club spirit!
I mean, you came all the way out here just to tell me that, right?
But you're wrong.
I'm not doing this for your sake.
I agreed to take this job on, so I'm just seeing it through!
You haven't done anything wrong.
So...
Put on a smile, comrade!
Uh-oh!
Madoka!
Dammit!
I completely forgot.
I was so focused on reaching you that I forgot my fears.
I'm okay now,
comrade.
Lympha's Vox System has been activated!
What?!
All joint form systematics are in active mode!
CSR Border Line at 70, 80, exceeding 90 percent!
Link with pilot's Bio Telepathic Control Waves is a success!
Huh? What? What?
Excuse me!
Fox seems to be slowing down!
It's because of the damage received during close-range combat.
If she keeps sustaining direct blows...
Did you think my attacks were random?
The Non-Lethal Mode Strike is quite a technique too.
It's not flashy, but it's very effective.
Let's put an end to this, shall we?!
Welcome, Lan!
Woof!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
That's...
the second legendary weapon!
Kirius!
It's risky to fight against two Vox robots.
We'll withdraw for now and wait for another opportunity.
Damn it!
Ovid units two and three are retreating!
No other enemy unit presence has been detected in the vicinity!
It seems...
You and Madoka
have saved us.
I didn't do anything.
Don't be modest.
Let's see, how can we thank you?
These are gate passes for this vessel!
Say, Lan...
Hm?
If I didn't agree to pilot Fox, I might've gone crazy.
Standing helpless on the sidelines,
watching Kamogawa being destroyed.
Thanks to this robot,
I was able to save my dear city.
Thank you, Lan.
I should be saying that to you.
Thanks to you, I was able to overcome it.
Overcome what?
Come on, tell me, Lan.
You have it wrong, Madoka.
The robot's name isn't Fox.
Yeah, I know.
From today, her name is Midori!
Huh? Midori? Why?
We went through hell together!
That makes her my comrade, just like you!
So she deserves a proper name.
But why Midori?
Midori as in the color green, isn't that obvious?
Anyway, I'm counting on you, Midori!
I'm counting on you... Orca.
Huh? Why Orca?
Does it sound weird?
Yeah, it does.
Weirder than Midori?
What? Is Midori weird?
A little...
Huh? You think so?
I think Orca sounds weirder.
It's an old tale,
from ancient times.
The giant green demon will rip through the heavens...
The giant blue demon will swallow the stars...
The giant orange demon will spew out darkness...
Through countless sacrifices, they will rule the land.
Feeding off tainted hearts,
they awaken from within the mind.
And the demons shall rise.
Do not let them loose.
Do not let them, ever.
I'll never forget that the soul in my chest would never yield
Don't cry
Promise me, okay
Promise me you'll never cry alone
We will always be together, you know
If we do get sad, we will share our sadness
and be stronger through it
Yay yay yay!
I'll laugh soon, my friend
My friend!
This isn't for just anyone, you're special
I am sure of my own emotions
With an upright voice, I say
Hello!
Sing the song that you always sing
and put a little bit of courage into my heart
Yay
Who are you?
Oh, don't mind me. I was just passing by.
What's going on? Is it something fun?
Actually, I heard a little bit of news about Miss Laffinty, that she...
Hold it!
Ouch, ouch!
And actually, there's more.
Madoka, don't listen to her.
They're lies. All lies. This girl is...
The Swimmers of Kamogawa