Don't you dare start a fight without me!
Aura is moving?!
The Vox System has been activated!
And its CSR Border Line has already exceeded 100%.
It's not responding to the A.I. Remote System, Sir!
Going full throttle from the get-go, huh?
Mr. Tadokoro!
I'm going to stop them!
Hold on a minute!
You haven't piloted that thing in almost a year!
The distance between Lympha and Ignis is zero!
Lympha has sustained damage to its cockpit!
Lan!
The pilot has lost consciousness!
The craft is losing altitude!
Quick, Midori!
Back then we tried to fly with propellers that couldn't do it
We ran with bare feet, and now we see different skies
We always live
full of conviction
that we are misunderstood
You're precious to me
but lost at the same time
I'll get over it
Spin the wheel of fate
Inside the dew, like magic,
are tears and sunny days
I feel lonely now
I'm sure my dream will come true
and we will be together forever
Mayhem on Komogawa Beach
Lympha, respond!
Laffinty!
Lan...
Lympha...
Please respond! Lympha...
Lympha!
Lan...
Lan!
That voice just now...
Madoka!
Aura is approaching the battle zone!
Madoka?!
You two need to
stop fighting
right n—
She flew right past them.
Huh?
What?
Lympha and Ignis have resumed battle!
Wait...
Hey, what're you doing?!
How should I know?!
Hey, Midori! Snap out of it!
The three of us are finally together again, so why...?
I was hoping to see you two, just like old times.
What?
What was that?
Why do I have to fight you, Muginami?!
I really love you Lan!
Are these their thoughts?
Why won't you understand?!
Stay away from Madoka!
You're one to talk!
Your people tried to destroy De Metrio!
Do you plan on being your brother's puppet forever?!
Look who's talking!
I don't know who started all this, but...
Madoka?
I said...
Stop fighting!
What's going on with you two?!
You're crazy! What're you two fighting for?!
Answer me!
What?
It's the Le Garite Occupation Forces.
Switch to an open channel.
But Ignis will be able to hear the transmiss—
That's fine.
Kyono!
A Le Garite platoon is closing in towards your position.
They plan to shoot down the enemy unit, Ignis.
Reinforcements are sure to follow.
Back off so that you don't get mixed up in it.
Huh? What do you mean shoot down Muginami?!
Did you hear me?
Thank you...
Muginami?!
Lan, let's go!
I'm sorry, Madoka.
Lan?!
I'm sorry!
Sorry?
Hey wait, Lan!
What's going on here?
I don't get it.
Huh?
Hey... Hey, hey!
Midori?!
I keep telling you, I can't authorize that.
Please let me go search for them!
That's what you get for trying to swim after them.
We're also searching for Lympha and Ignis.
And even if you were to go look for those two on Aura,
you have no idea where they both went.
Besides, their fight is part of an interplanetary dispute between two planets.
Earth shouldn't interfere so recklessly.
But both of them were acting strange.
Lan and Muginami seemed like
they were being forced to do something they didn't want to do.
I mean, why are they fighting to begin with?
Have you heard a single thing I've said?
They finally came back to Kamogawa. So why?
No. No she wasn't...
W-What is it this time?!
That's it.
It's Kamogawa.
I'm sure of it!
Thanks much!
Hey, Kyono? Kyono?!
She already left.
What?
Lan!
Muginami?
Huh?
They're not here.
Oh, welcome home.
They're back!
Man, I'm starving.
Another busy day, wasn't it?
Hey, what the hell?
Are they back?!
Oh, hey... Welcome back.
Where are Lan and Muginami?!
Huh?
Are you expecting them?
That's odd... It wasn't Kamogawa then?
I was so sure they'd be here.
Maybe they went home.
If they're not here, they went home?
Hey, do you know where they live?
Do you?
Do you know?
I don't!
I understand Laffinty and Muginami went at it.
I'm sure this is the motive.
You mean the Polyhedron Millennium Problem?
It's the phenomenon in which the planetary orbits of
Le Garite and De Metrio will collide and result in the destruction of both star systems.
But I understood that a plan of action would be discussed
at the upcoming intergalactic conference. Or no?
Do you plan on being your brother's puppet forever?!
Look who's talking!
Judging from this recording, Laffinty was trying to get Madoka
to pilot Aura under her brother's orders.
By all accounts, he is willing to destroy De Metrio
in order to correct the orbit.
They believe that Aura has the power to destroy a planet?
According to what Izo and others have said, it's possible.
Apparently, the princess of De Metrio
destroyed a natural satellite named Militia Zodia
during a Vox Core experiment.
What is a Vox Core?
It's the prototype of the Vox cockpit.
At any rate, Dizelmine is planning something
outside the intergalactic conference
and intends to use both Madoka and Aura.
Depending on Madoka's actions,
a war could break out in space.
It's no use. I can't detect Ignis' signal.
Well, Muginami has always been good at hiding...
Is this it?
Are we connected to them now?
As long as they still haven't changed their identification signal.
State your ship's affiliation and I.D. number.
This ship belongs to the De Metrio Army—
Hold it, Grania...
Oh, hello?
Uh... This is Madoka Kyono from Kamogawa!
Repairs will be expedited and should take about one week.
We should make it before the intergalactic conference starts.
Thank you.
Are you relieved to see that Aura is operational again?
It only adds to the list of my problems.
Say, Cap...
What is it?
Look...
Hey, Brother Giuvi...
Is Muginami over there?
I saw her once this afternoon.
But she took off somewhere and now I can't find her.
Brother Giuvi?!
Who do you think you're talking to—
Kyono! What the hell are you doing?!
Oh, Mr. Tadokoro...
I'm on the phone.
That's not what I meant!
Uehara!
Intercept her call from the bridge and end it!
W-Wait!
What complete imbeciles!
Are you insane?!
Didn't I tell you to not be reckless?!
Right now De Metrio is considered an enemy!
Did you seriously think you could make contact with them
without clearing it with the Le Garite Occupation Forces first?!
Why do we have to be here too?
And as for you guys!
You work for the Chairman! You must know the situation here!
Nope, sure don't.
We've been out of the loop for six months.
Longer, actually.
Aren't you worried about those two, Mr. Tadokoro?
Listen, this has nothing to do with worrying or not!
What is it then?
Stop!
In any case, those two have not gone back to their brothers.
If they had left this planet,
our surveillance satellites would have seen them.
Where are they then?
They haven't left Earth.
They haven't left Earth?
Hey, Kyono!
I'm going back to Kamogawa.
If they haven't gone back to their brothers,
then the only other place they could be is Kamogawa!
Are you going to just let her go?
There are shuttles left to take her back to land.
There's no way she can leave Pharos.
Lan... Muginami...
Madoka hasn't changed at all.
Lord Villagiulio, over half a day has passed
since we lost Muginami's signal.
Even if she's on the run from the Le Garite forces,
isn't it a bit odd?
You allowed her to act on her own
under the assumption that if Aura fell into Le Garite's hands,
Muginami would personally deal with Kyono Madoka, right?
But if she's having second thoughts,
then maybe you should give out the order to—
I won't give such an order.
Are you deaf?
I won't do what Dizel would do.
However—
He plans to sacrifice our planet in order for his to survive.
And I'm fighting him to prevent that.
So how can I tell Muginami to just sacrifice her feelings?
If I do that, I lose the very reason for taking up the throne in the first place.
She'll show up in time...
Along with whatever fruit her feelings have wrought.
Lan?
Why?
This place hasn't changed at all.
My locker... It's still here.
Madoka would never throw it out.
You're right.
Say, Lan...
What is it?
Are you going to involve Madoka in this no matter what?
What about you? You're the one trying to kill her.
I'll never allow it!
I will protect Madoka!
You've got a lot of nerve.
You're the one trying to take advantage of her!
What the hell do you know?!
At this rate, Le Garite will use Madoka by force!
That's why I'm trying to get in between them.
See? You're just being your brother's pawn!
Y'know what, Lan?
I came here because I wanted to be sure...
This place where the three of us went together...
When the three of us were the Sweats Club...
I wanted to make sure I was doing the right thing.
Me? Kill Madoka?
I could never bring myself to.
I mean, I like Madoka.
I love her!
That's why I won't allow her to become tangled up in this!
Please leave.
And never come near Madoka again!
I refuse.
Lan!
I told you.
I'm the one who's going to protect Madoka!
Madoka?
I knew it.
You two were here, after all!
M-Madoka?
Madoka?
You two...
You don't really want to fight, do you?
I heard your voices.
It wasn't very clear.
But I could feel the pain you two were experiencing.
And it hurt me too.
I felt so sad.
How could this happen?
Please tell me.
I'll do anything I can. Anything.
I'm sorry, Madoka.
Lan?
It's too late.
Our planets...
Our brothers are beyond coming to an understanding.
Muginami?
There's nothing we can do anymore.
Wha—
If that's all it is, then don't worry!
We can make your brothers become friends again.
I'll make them.
Like I did just now!
Then you two won't have to fight.
Let's try it!
Giving up without even trying
and being forced to fight against your will
isn't the way the Sweats Club works!
The three of us together can do it!
Madoka...
Listen, Madoka. The problem isn't that simple.
W-What are you doing?!
I've made up my mind!
Muginami will rejoin the Sweats Club!
Muginami!
I haven't got a clue as to what we could do.
But the three of us...
With the three of us, I feel like we can pull it off.
Didn't you just say you didn't want Madoka to get involved?
But now I think it's worth a shot.
Lan, you should do it too.
Okay...
No, I can't! There's no plan!
It's impossible.
You're starting to think it's going to work out, aren't you?
You're feeling like it's going to work out.
Don't come near.
You're feeling like it's going to work out...
Come on!
Oww!
I-I'm sorry!
How could you, Lan?!
Haven't I always told you to keep a sharp eye on Madoka?
How did you let this happen?
We've been so busy every day.
We were careless.
Asteria, please don't scold them so much.
I'm sure they've learned their lesson.
Whose fault do you think this is?
Well...
I had a bad feeling about this when I heard
that Laffinty and Muginami had started fighting above Kamogawa.
I'm sorry.
We're being swamped with government inquires from both nations.
So I'll just get right to the point.
Both of you, seek asylum on Earth.
That's the only way to avoid war.
Yes, ma'am.
Please help us.
All right, you two! We're going to get busy!
You're back.
It sounded awfully noisy out here.
Your dear cousin has done it again.
I'm glad nothing has changed.
So?
The results of the measurements showed Vox particles.
And from the flower too.
As we predicted,
the Vox may possess the potential to be more than a weapon.
If we can show that,
it could be the trump card to end this deadlock.
Provided I can make things run smoothly, of course.
It's not like you to sound so uncertain.
That's because I can't risk repeating
the same tragedy from 20,000 years ago...
The Sweats Club spirit! The Sweats Club spirit!
I won't leave you alone, hello and let's be cheery!
Who knows if it's fun?
We're still trying to work that out
This is the youth of us three!
Our destined meeting happened in a split second
We're together when we walk ahead
We're together with each of the breaths we take
Look
We're together when we laugh from the bottom of our hearts
Is this friendship?
We'll be fine!
I won't press the issue!
I won't delve into it too deep!
We don't really have to know that
Why can we trust each other so much, you ask?
That's obvious!
We're comrades!
The Sweats Club spirit! The Sweats Club spirit!
I want to help you, hello and let's be cheery!
Are you telling me to have my first summer experience?!
No, that's "experience."
We're asking you to do an "experiment."
I'll do it if I have to, but it's my first time, y'know.
I told you, you're talking about experience!
Okay, I've made up my mind. Bring it on!
How brave of you.
Well, I'll make sure you enjoy this.
The Kamogawa Experiment
She's scary...