I won!
Perfect!
Did I get too carried away?
The color changed.
This looks much better!
Excellent work.
What? Uh, thanks.
You fought brilliantly by pushing Vox Aura's abilities to the limit.
I'm Moid, and you have made a lasting impression on me.
Fox...?
Vox Aura.
It is the name of that Ovid.
Oh, so that's its name?
Lan!
Were you watching?
Yes...
This robot is amazing!
I didn't think it would be that easy to pilot.
Easy?
Yup!
It moves just the way I want it to move.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's red.
I hit my head.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
I am Tadokoro, the Fleet Captain here.
I would like to brief you before your next mission.
Next? There's going to be more?
Woof.
Can I... go to the restroom first?
Lovely, lovely
The girl in the training suit is somehow special
When she takes it off, she can be anything
To look for something she treasures, she'd go to the bottom of the ocean
The surge of her emotions can turn her opposition into mist
I come to meet you as fast as I can
when your visions call to me
Perfect!
Live your life!
Rewrite fate and fly
Fly away
Oh and fly today
If it's dangerous to laugh at your foes as you advance
burn brighter and fly away
Try, unite, unite
Lovely, lovely
Kamogawa Spirit
Wait, Izo.
I said, wait!
I can't wait. Array's Ovid isn't responding.
Which means one of us has to go and rescue him.
The enemy Ovid signal was like nothing we've ever seen.
Are you saying that they brought out the Vox?
We can't rule that out.
If they already had the Vox,
it's possible "Memoria" has been achieved as well.
So they've found a pilot.
All the more the reason for me to head out.
I'm the best Ovid pilot in De Metrio.
Izo!
Using the power of the Vox to crush Le Garite is our destiny!
No time like now to check out the power
of the legendary weapon which we'll ultimately possess.
And if I don't come back, get out and save yourself.
I was tricked.
I was totally tricked!
No one told me that there was going to be a second time!
Did she pretend to be my comrade just to get close to me,
to make me pilot that "Fox"?
Were those memories false too?
No, that was real... I think.
Or was it?
Which is it? I'm so confused!
Missed calls: Nakaizumi Yoko
Yikes! They're all from Yoko!
I wonder what's up?
No service
No service.
Yes, a single bar!
It's gone.
Oh wait!
Does this...
Does this mean your cousin beat that thing?
Seeing that it's not moving, I guess it does.
What does this mean?
Did your cousin actually manage to pilot that thing?
I thought she could only ride a bicycle.
Maybe she actually got a scooter license.
That's not enough to pilot a robot!
It must be the people here.
They're hiding something!
We've spent five years trying to figure out the Ooparts with no success.
But the guys here built a robot out of it in six months!
There's got to be some secret to—!
U-Um...
Shh!
You stay here.
Wait, please don't leave me alone here!
What were you planning to do if Kyono Madoka
was unable to activate Vox Aura today?
Those who've achieved Memoria with the Vox
become its one and only pilot.
Even if Vox Aura falls into enemy hands,
as long as we safeguard Miss Kyono Madoka,
we have an even chance of winning.
And the same could be said if their positions were reversed.
We could have accelerated her organic response with the Vox,
but it was risky, so I wanted to avoid doing that if at all possible.
In any case, we really weren't prepared to take considerable steps.
So I'm glad to see that everything worked out.
And as a result, I also learned quite a bit.
You don't give a damn about protecting this planet, inside that head of yours.
Protecting the Vox is the same thing as protecting Earth.
And whose idea was it to make the Vox fight on the front line?
Weapons from Earth are useless against them.
Then why don't you take the Vox and get off of this planet?
Then Earth would fall under their sphere of control.
Such a future would be bleak.
Fine.
So what now, then?
Will taking our chances against them work a second time?
Judging only from the performance of the craft,
it has power that surpasses the enemy's.
The rest depends on her.
So we'll have to take our chances after all.
You could say that.
Can I ask you one last question?
Ask me anything.
Is this main force of your's really coming?
Immediately. After the war on their side is over.
Captain.
What is it?
The pilot has run away.
It's no good. I'm completely lost.
Ouch!
Oww...
Come on!
It looks similar...
But I guess it's a little different.
Who's there?!
Please wait!
Wait!
Excuse me! I'm...
Lost!
You too?!                               You too?!
Excuse me, but who are you?
The pilot... or... rather...
I'm Kyono Madoka. And you?
I'm Muginami.
Say Miss Muginami...
Roger that!
Then I'm going to look over that way.
And you go that way.
Oh, okay.
Wait now...
So what do I do?
Found you.
I told you, I wasn't trying to run away.
It's all right. I understand how you feel.
You do?
To be honest, I wish I could help more
instead of forcing everything onto you.
But all I can do is fly.
Uh... What are you talking about?
I'm sorry, I...
There's no way I'm going to be able to put this on by myself.
Help me out.
Can you do it?
Not sure. I'll have to take my chances.
Good answer.
Now listen calmly.
An enemy has appeared.
Presently, its location is 100 km southeast of Oshima.
It's heading this way at Mach 2.
At this rate, the confrontation will be in three minutes.
Th-Three minutes?!
We will control the craft during Piercer Mode.
All you have to do is sit tight, like the last time.
I have a question.
Was that last jolt an accident?
Jolt?
I believe she's referring to what triggered the Form Change.
Oh...
It wasn't an accident. It was planned.
So we're going to do that again?
Correct.
Okay, I understand.
Kyono.
Yes?
The future of our planet rests in your hands.
We're counting on you.
What?! Wait a minute!
I can't handle that kind of pressure right now!
The whole planet? But I've never even been to Tokyo!
Commencing Vox Aura A.I. Remote System check.
Codes 1 through 11 are clear.
Pilot's heart rate, blood pressure, respiratory rate... all normal.
Opening barrier walls one and two.
Enemy unit two is approaching quickly.
Vox Aura will engage the enemy
in approximately 100 seconds.
A.I. Remote Systems are normal.
Vox System is operational.
Shuttle locks are open.
Check complete. All systems go.
I'm starting to get really nervous.
The Vox System is silent like the last time.
Let's just hope for the best.
Vox Aura, take off!
An Ovid signal...
It's not Array's, so that means...
The Vox!
You should see the enemy straight ahead.
I see it... a black one.
We're going in head-on!
What?!
The hell with it... charge!
So you wanna fight?
Bring it on!
What happened?!
We don't know, sir!
The Vox System suddenly started up
and is overriding the A.I. Remote!
What's going on?!
Are you telling me she's now in control of the Piercer Mode as well?!
It appears the girl really is a perfect match for Vox Aura, isn't she?
Can't you take this more seriously?
All stations, prepare for attack!
This isn't it either! This place is too big!
Let's go back inside.
That's...
What's it doing?
It's running away?
What's going on?!
If you're the real deal, then let's see how you'll handle this!
Vox Aura's power grid is failing.
At this rate...
What is the status of the pilot?
Her vital signs are normal,
but the craft has shut down completely!
Where are you going?
Can you do it, milady?
You fear the legend.
Can you really accept the Vox in your current state?
This is what Array lost to?
It's no good! I can't see a thing!
Who am I kidding?
It was a crazy idea to begin with.
Me, being a pilot...
Yoko...
Hello?
Where are you now?
Inside a robot...
I see...
Putting her on speaker.
Wait... You're not surprised?
Cell phones work in there?!
Where's that call coming from!
Within Pharos premises, sir.
Why are you piloting a robot?
Well, a lot of stuff happened, and...
Oh, yeah. I wanted to ask you...
Did something happen to me
when I almost drowned ten years ago?
Do you even remember it?
Yeah, I remember.
It seems like I met this robot back then.
Where is the enemy unit?
Distance from Vox Aura, 200.
It's inside that black smoke.
Who is that?
Damn... of all the places.
She's a marine archaeologist.
She's been snooping around ever since
our foundation confiscated her research regarding Vox Aura.
Then she's...
The pilot's cousin.
The one opposed to Kyono Madoka piloting the Vox Aura.
This robot is amazing.
It moves according to my thoughts.
I was scared at first, but I got the hang of it quickly.
It was quite fun, to be honest.
But it's not anymore?
Well, after giving it some thought...
Enemy unit two, distance from Vox Aura, 130!
It seems a lot of people are placing their hopes on me to pilot this robot.
I want to live up to their expectations as much as I can.
I don't want to disappoint anyone, but...
When I started thinking about that, it stopped moving.
You've got some nerve!
Just who the hell do you think you are?!
That thing's not moving because you're acting like you're doing them a favor!
Not that I'm saying you have to feel grateful to them for letting you pilot that thing.
But if you decided to do it,
then take responsibility for that decision!
And if that bothers you, then quit...
the Sweats Club!
You're so irritating!
Yeah, you're right. You are absolutely right, but...
It pisses me off hearing that coming from you!
It drives me nuts!
Distance from enemy unit, 20.
At a distance of ten, nine,
What are you doing? Move!
eight, seven,
six, five, four,
Vox System online!
What's the distance with the Enemy Unit?!
Zero...!
All right!
What? What happened?!
An unknown craft has broken through the atmosphere!
Where's it heading?
Right here!
What?
A pincer attack?
Kirius, what are you—?
I can't sit and watch this anymore.
If we're going to die, we'll die together!
I'll never forget that the soul in my chest would never yield
Don't cry
Promise me, okay
Promise me you'll never cry alone
We will always be together, you know
If we do get sad, we will share our sadness
and be stronger through it
Yay yay yay!
I'll laugh soon, my friend
My friend!
This isn't for just anyone, you're special
I am sure of my own emotions
With an upright voice, I say
Hello!
Sing the song that you always sing
and put a little bit of courage into my heart
Yay
I'm going to do it!
Do what?
I'm going to do it and I mean it!
You're going to do what?
Once I make up my mind to do it, I go all out. That's my style!
I'm asking you, what are you going to do?
I'm in.
Oh, you're in?
What about you, Array?
Me? Well, I've been captured.
That's lame.
Did you say something?
Izo said that you look bad.
Lan Blooms
Don't be so blunt!