What's happening?!
Princess!
What're you waiting for, Madoka?!
Where am I?
We have to get out of here!
Is that me?
Is that
me?
How?!
Back then we tried to fly with propellers that couldn't do it
We ran with bare feet, and now we see different skies
We always live
full of conviction
that we are misunderstood
You're precious to me
but lost at the same time
I'll get over it
Spin the wheel of fate
Inside the dew, like magic,
are tears and sunny days
I feel lonely now
I'm sure my dream will come true
and we will be together forever
May This Voice Reach Kamogawa
Something unexpected must have interfered during the fusion
of Lady Yurikano and Kyono Madoka's personalities,
which might be the cause of this anomaly—
I'll hear your explanation later.
Get Yurikano off the ship to safety.
Huh? No way.
Are you Miss Yurikano?
Does this mean we're...?
Madoka, come on!
Wait, I'm not—
I'm—
Miss Yurikano can wait!
Right now, we have to run!
No, listen to me!
Stop, you two!
H-Hey, wait!
I'm over here, Muginami!
It's too dangerous to remain on board!
You must head to the escape pod immediately!
Huh? Escape?!
King Dizelmine's orders!
We will escort you, Lady Yurikano.
Just a minute! You have the wrong person.
I'm not Miss Yurikano...
No, wait!
There's something I have to tell you!
We need to hurry.
Oh, come on, listen!
You, and you, all of you...
You all need to stop right this instant!
The surrounding energy field is in flux.
Could that be what's causing the anomaly on Dizelmine's ship?
Doesn't matter.
We came here to get Yurikano back.
What happens to the Le Garite vessel is none of our concern—
How many?
Three!
The Eques are about to intercept them.
This anomaly on the ship...
Perhaps they're using a new type of weapon against us.
Send out every Ovid we have available to attack!
Yes, Sir!
Have you secured Princess Laffinty?
Negative!
Where could Madoka and Muginami be?
Currently unable to guarantee that the launch systems will function properly.
All Ovids are to launch using manual launch protocols.
Repeat: Currently...
Our sensors have picked up multiple Ovid launches
from Dizelmine's ship.
Are you still going to tell me
that this war is just between
you and Dizelmine, Sir?
Do as you wish...
Don't mind if I do.
Scramble all squadrons!
Protect King Villagiulio!
Roger!
Just don't get in my way!
Wait! I have to return to the lab!
Are you crazy?!
The anomaly is assuredly because I've returned to this world!
I need to use the Vox Core and return beyond the Rinne immediately!
What's gotten into you, Madoka?!
Was it something you ate?!
I keep telling you, I'm not—
Oh! At the reception,
they must've spiked your drink with something nasty!
Damn you, Le Garite!
Madoka?!
Listen to me!
I'm not Miss Yurikano...
Hold on, this is my chance!
That's right, my name is Yurikano.
I may not look it, but I am indeed the princess of De Metrio.
I, the most regal one, hereby command you.
I request an audience with Lan's brother immediately!
Sorry! King Dizelmine's orders have priority!
What?!
Another one from Le Garite?
No! The readings are different!
Is it Villagiulio?!
It's not him, either.
Hey, those are...!
I need to stop this fighting already...
Orca!
Madoka! Where are you?!
Thank you, Hupo!
First, we detect a powerful energy field...
Next, the Vox just flies off by themselves.
What the hell's going on up there?
Dizelmine must have done something.
The anomaly was seen originating from the Le Garite flagship.
We've confirmed link-ups with Lympha and Ignis.
Which means Lan and Muginami are safe.
What about Aura?!
Well, the signal indicates it's made contact with the pilot.
But it's almost like...
What is it?
Aura appears to be confused.
What's that mean?
I see, so you're hers...
Listen, I need your help!
Take me to the laboratory division of this ship.
Huh?!
Hey, come back!
Should've known...
The Vox won't respond unless both mind and body are united as one.
That's...!
I said...
I need to tell Lan's brother something really important!
Wait! Hold on!
There's just too many! We'll never get through.
Quit whining!
If we survive this, we can make it to Dizelmine's ship!
But that anomaly...
If we don't hurry, Yurikano's life will be in danger.
Six o'clock, Kirius!
Why did that Le Garite Ovid save me?!
Show some guts, Kirius!
Didn't I teach you that it's not the enemy,
but your own carelessness that trips you up?
Is that you, Kyono?
You guys know her?
Madoka, why are you here?
I'm Yurikano!
It's a long story, but I'm stuck in her body.
Hey, that's a pretty lame joke if you ask me!
I'm not joking! Trust me!
Indeed, that advice just now
was something Yurikano's said to me countless times.
And Madoka wouldn't know our tactical radio frequency.
You really expect me to believe that?!
What about that time during the Academy's drill camp?!
I was bathing and I saw a mouse,
a-and clung to you stark naked, remember?!
It's really her.
But how on earth?!
I'll explain later!
Let's take out those guys first!
Don't go on the defensive!
Drive a wedge into their formation before you're surrounded!
Maintain your attack!
Follow me!
Roger!
Outta the way!
Yahoo!
Is that our Ovid? Who's piloting it?
We don't know.
What we do know is that the pilot is extremely skilled.
Our standard squadron is no match.
It took me an entire minute just to deal with those amateurs.
Did I get rusty while stuck inside the Rinne all that time?
Time for the elite squad now, eh?
I'll cover you, Yurikano!
Stay back, Array!
Wipe them out!
Brother!
Huh?! Madoka—
No!
You believed that even royalty should know how to cook for themselves.
I could make all sorts of dishes just by guessing the ingredients
and every time you ate my cooking you'd tell me
how important measuring and following the recipe was!
I'm your younger sister!
Yurikano?!
I wonder if this thing is carrying any food.
I could go for some fish-flavored crackers.
Crackers and a bottle of Kamogawa Energy would be perfect...
Found it!
Huh? Is this all?!
I'm gonna die of hunger before I even get to Le Garite.
But before that happens,
I wish there was some way for me
to tell Lan's brother and Giuvi
that Miss Yurikano is suffering.
Oh!
But I wonder why she doesn't want to tell them herself?
I totally don't get it... Ow!
Ow...
Where's that bastard Dizel?
If his ship's so messed up that he can't come out,
I'll go and meet him from the inside!
No!
I won't let you!
Muginami...
I, Fin E Ld Si Laffinty, Princess of Le Garite, command you!
Stand down immediately,
and lock down your armament
and battle control systems!
You too, Brother!
Don't be ridiculous.
What's with this "Brother" stuff?
Madoka?! What're you doing here?
I keep telling you, I'm not her! I'm Yurikano!
Brother, what have you done to Makoka?
Don't look at me with such a sad face!
What can I do to make you people believe me?!
S-Sweet and sour pork... E-Edible hot chili oil... Y-Y...
Is that the emergency frequency?
I really don't get why Miss Yurikano doesn't want to tell
Lan's brother and Big Brother Giuvi how she feels.
If she tells them, they might even understand....
Huh?
F-Fried wheat pasta?
T-Tuna salad...
Huh?
Madoka?!
I mean, it sounds pretty simple enough to me.
But no...
She has to take her sweet time
like a girl hesitating to confess to some guy she loves.
L-L-Love...
B-B-Bouillabaisse...
I-I love you.
I-I'm in love with you...
Wait a second.
No way!
Yurikano loves Lan's brother?!
I see... Yurikano just couldn't stand it.
Seeing her brother and the man she loved
trying to duke it out all the time.
Sacrificing herself probably didn't hurt as much.
That's why...
Well, that's the last of the rations.
If some day, I could meet Lan's brother again...
I want to tell him how you feel.
Doesn't look like that day will ever come.
Good bye, Lan...
Good bye, Muginami...
Good bye, Kamogawa...
Good bye, Earth...
Everybody! I'm back!
You saved me, Midori!
Huh?
Why won't you respond to my commands?
Is it because I'm not in my own body?
Hey! Midori!
Ow...
Yurikano... No. Right now you're Miss Madoka, aren't you?
I heard everything you said
through the escape pod's communications.
What?!
Being able to fly Aura implies
that you did indeed swap places with her.
I'm back in my own body.
Lan? Muginami?
Madoka?
Madoka, I thought you were in the escape pod.
Then she must be back there now?!
When I see the flowers of Lagrange in full bloom like this,
it brings back memories
of the day when Yurikano and I became engaged.
We were so little that we hardly knew the meaning of that word.
But we were entrusted to become the guidepost
for Le Garite and De Metrio to work together and move forward.
As time passed, our two planets parted ways,
and in a similar manner, the ties that bound us were severed.
Even then, the love I felt for her never faded.
To this day, I still love Yurikano.
That's why my heart aches.
This chaos is necessary for the billions of citizens in the Polyhedron.
It's hard to imagine that the person you love wouldn't understand.
Villagiulio!
Go to them!
I don't want to hate Yurikano.
I want her to share my feelings.
If she really does love me...
Why don't you ask her directly?
Miss Madoka?
Make her understand. Tell her how you feel.
Then... You're the real...
Liar...
Huh?
I think you're absolutely
despicable!
Ah... That felt good!
Miss Yurikano?
Don't get the wrong idea!
I would never love a man like him!
So go right ahead and hate me.
If that means that this world won't be buried in grief...
If that's what it takes...
Then I...
I'll have to let you go.
Be honest, don't you think all men are fools?
Dizelmine included.
Yurikano!
My brother, too.
If we ever meet again...
If by some miracle we get the chance...
Let's have a nice, long talk. Okay, Madoka?
We'll meet again. Definitely!
Yes...
We should definitely meet again.
I'll come to see you, Yurikano.
All right, you two...
Time for some answers!
On the water's surface I see a light reflected that stirs my heart
When we realized our bond,
we were already deeply connected under the blue sky
We had so much fun, as in a daze, that time seemed forgotten
I prayed that there would be no end to the way we lived
I won't forget our days together, although time goes by,
and you are far from me now,
because you left behind a wonderful world
for me to wait in
I wanted you more than anyone to understand these feelings.
I didn't want you, of all people, to know about them.
I've been wavering back and forth between these feelings...
Is that what it means to love someone?
Thinking about someone else's feelings,
and wanting them to understand yours...
But if you can't understand that,
A Vow to Kamogawa
I'll have to teach you the hard way!