You know, the universe is so large that we can't even begin to fathom it.
And time has been spinning for an eternity...
Even still, we were able to meet.
Do you think it's a miracle?
I don't think it is.
I mean...
Our encounter had to be destined.
Destined?
Yes, like one single bee out of a swarm,
and a single flower out of a meadow...
They come together and the flower produces fruit.
Single droplets of night mist that fall from the leaves
fill the springs that become the foundation of a great river.
I'm sure that us meeting has meaning.
Meaning? Like what?
Well, for example...
To make me fall in love?
I've been feeling this way since we first met.
I love you!
You can't...
Huh?
I wanted to say it first.
We'll always be together.
Yes.
Forever and ever.
Cut!
That's a wrap for The Lily and the Spaceship!
Thank you, everyone!
Thank you!
You did it!
It's over.
Uh-huh.
That was a little embarrassing, wasn't it?
Yeah.
That was the last job for the Sweats Club.
Good job, Lan.
Good job, Madoka.
I'll never forget that the soul in my chest would never yield
Don't cry
Promise me, okay
Promise me you'll never cry alone
We will always be together, you know
If we do get sad, we will share our sadness
and be stronger through it
Yay yay yay!
I'll laugh soon, my friend
My friend!
This isn't for just anyone, you're special
I am sure of my own emotions
With an upright voice, I say
Hello!
Sing the song that you always sing
and put a little bit of courage into my heart
Yay
Until We Meet Again, In Kamogawa
It has been two weeks since the delegation
from Le Garite came to Earth.
Today, their representative and the U.N. delegate met in a conference for the twelfth time
Hey, look up there!
at the Kamogawa Municipal Auditorium in Kamogawa City in Chiba Prefecture.
Also participating in the meetings were the Prime Minister, the Foreign Minister,
the governor of Chiba Prefecture, and the mayor of Kamogawa City.
The talks were conducted cordially and interspersed with occasional planetary
Sorry
Reserved for the day
and regional jokes.
A princess from a distant planet!
How romantic!
But I still can't believe it.
Are you seriously an alien?
Can I touch you?
Huh?
S-Sure...
Hey, come on. Stop slapping her like a sumo wrestler.
Here you go!
I'll keep bringing out food, so eat up.
Besides, Uncle's cooking, not me!
Here you go!
I'll help too.
What are you saying?!
Lan!
And the wrap party for "The Lily and the Spaceship"
Have a safe journey
back to your home planet!
You're the guest of honor, so sit back and enjoy yourself!
It'll be lonely around the shop again.
How many times do I have to repeat myself? No gloomy talk!
She's right, Mr. Hiroshi!
You're coming right back to Earth, aren't you?
I'm not sure about that.
What?
Huh?
Intergalactic travel isn't that easy.
Are you saying this is really goodbye?
Lan...
Lan!
Lan should just play along and say she's coming right back.
Take good care of yourself.
We'll never forget you, Lan!
She's just too honest.
So please don't forget about us either!
All right, that's enough!
How can Lan go back to her planet feeling happy with a send-off like that?!
Princess Lan, will you say a few parting words to us plebeians?
What?
Ahem!
We are gathered here today in such wonderful weather...
Not like that...
No one is surprised anymore
by the fact that you're an alien.
Uh-huh.
It's been two weeks since that incident.
You're right.
Wow!
How beautiful!
Isn't it?
I should've brought you here to the Hill of Vows earlier.
But it totally slipped my mind.
The Hill of Vows?
We vow...
that we will meet again in Kamogawa someday.
You too, Lan!
All right.
I vow too.
Good.
As long as this lock remains here,
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
we must honor our vow, no matter what.
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
Until we meet again
in Kamogawa!
Madoka & Lan & Muginami
I wish Muginami were here too...
Do you think we'll all meet again?
Yes, absolutely.
After all,
the view before us is still here.
That's right.
Yes.
It's because you protected it.
Flowers?
Why did it have to be Big Sis...
and everyone else?
If you wanted to hurt someone,
Madoka!
you should've just done it to me.
I've been ready to risk my life for a long time.
I was prepared...
Madoka...
Why does it always have to be the ones I love?
If I try to go in for close-range combat, my craft will mutate.
Damage report!
But long-range attacks are also ineffective.
Ovids Garua, Baizand, and Nekusan are out of commission due to the effects of the anomaly!
So what are my options now?
Detecting a massive energy field!
What's that?
What's gonna happen?
What's the situation with the energy field?!
It's growing even larger!
Phochville ships 1 and 2 are going to be swallowed up!
All ships within effective range are to activate overdrive if necessary!
Get out of there!
Aura, Lympha and Ignis...
The telemetry from each one is off the grid!
Just what is happening, Moid?
Shut the hell up!
Don't talk to me now!
This is the best part, and I'm trying to enjoy it.
Uehara!
Yes sir!
Can we communicate with the pilots?
We can't.
We're disconnected from all three.
No, wait...
It's Aura...
What is this static?
There are lots of people I want to protect.
There's Big Sis,
Uncle,
everyone at school...
The people of Kamogawa...
and...
also... also...
Hey,
was I really the right choice?
Can I really do it?
If I say you can't, are you going to give up?
But if it's impossible, it's impossible.
You don't know that until you try.
It's a fact that you were chosen.
But whether or not you can do it, no one knows.
In other words...
It's all up to you.
All up to me?
Before I came here,
there was someone else here.
She went back to her own world, almost like she was switching places with me.
She said she was going to try one more time.
But I didn't ask what she was going to do.
Do you want to leave this place?
I'm staying here because...
that's the path I've chosen.
I see...
So... who are you?
"That's the path I've chosen," huh.
That's so cool!
Let's try this...
my way!
Lan!
Muginami!
Let's go
together!
What?
The only thing I can do...
is to fly with everything I've got, just like this!
A-Aura!
It's beautiful...
Well?
Does my kid sister have potential?
Yes.
She's an outrageous girl,
that Kyono Madoka.
Big Sis?
She's alive!
Midori, Big Sis is okay!
What happened?
What? What? What?
What's wrong, Madoka?
Midori stopped moving!
Why?
I don't know! Maybe she fell asleep?
Hey, wake up! Come on, Midori!
Bravo!
That was a brilliant illusion.
But...
there is no doubt that the Vox hides a frightening power.
In fact, we just saw the proof.
Villagiulio!
It appears that for the people of De Metrio to sleep safely at night...
you must be put to sleep!
You! The leader of the giant demons!
Brother...
Brother!
It can't be...
Brother Dizelmine...
Eliminate all resistant forces within Earth's domain.
There is no need to pursue anyone who flees.
Yes, my lord.
Muginami!
Let her go!
If she stays, my brother will definitely kill them...
Both Villagiulio,
and Muginami for trying to save him.
If I knew earlier that my brother's ship was coming to get me,
I wouldn't have let Muginami go into battle.
I'm sorry, Madoka.
It's not your fault, Lan.
I hope she's doing okay.
I wonder what planet she's on?
I'll find her.
Huh?
I'll find her, and we'll return together.
To this town where the three of us first met.
I promise.
And when that day comes,
will you let us be your comrades again?
Yes!
Well...
I'll be going, okay?
Yeah.
See you!
Bye-bye!
See you again!
Per—
And so, Muginami left,
Lan returned to her home planet,
and time passed.
And autumn in Kamogawa is slowly coming to an end.
We're counting on you, Madoka!
You got it!
Stop! Stop!
Safe!
You did it!
Madoka, help!
Okay!
At dawn's break,
as though lit by the morning moon...
Got it!
Huh?
Madoka!
Bring it on!
Hey, Kyono!
Oh, just a minute!
The next opening I have in the Sweats Club schedule is...
Nothing like that. You received a letter.
Huh?
It's addressed to the Sweats Club.
Midori hasn't moved since that day.
Even the people on Pharos don't seem to know why.
So many things happened that I think she just wants to rest.
Yeah, I'm sure that's it.
Mr. Moid returned to Le Garite with Lan and her brother.
Since that happened, the wind's really been taken out of Mr. Tadokoro's sails.
H-Hot!
My Big Sister Yoko recovered completely from her injuries.
Just what I'd expect from her.
The scar doesn't bother her one bit.
She seems to have gotten close to Asteria lately.
Madoka said that during the last battle, she realized she was on a beach.
A beach?
And she got some advice from a girl she didn't know.
I see.
So she saw her too.
Isn't it about time you shared your story with me too?
If I did, what would you do?
Nothing.
I'm just curious.
They say girls who are too curious miss their chance at marriage.
I am the witch who pulled this universe into an eternal loop
comprised of peace and calamity.
But don't worry,
I promise I'll disappear.
Once Madoka severs this...
The Rin-ne.
Come on!
I was looking forward to the roasted pollock roe inside!
Isn't this the...?
The Chairman of Novumundus is your personal reference, huh?
I saw Lan recently.
We talked about so many things.
About each other, about our future, and about you, Madoka.
We ended up arguing again,
but we made up
just like when we were a trio.
We argued a lot and made up a lot.
And now, I love you two even more.
Even if I squint really hard,
I still can't see the Earth from here.
But,
I promise I'll return to Kamogawa someday.
When I do, let's argue lots and lots!
To my dearest Madoka...
Perfect!
Didn't I tell you to hold on to it since the wind is blowing?
You didn't listen to your mother!
Just a minute!
I'll get it for you in a jiffy!
On my way!
Special announcement!
When did you get back, Muginami?
Madoka, all you said was "Ehhh."
Oh, you're back too, Lan?