I am Botanmaru!
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Have you any knowledge of Master Soujoubou the Third's son and heir, Master Shinjurou?
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Master Shinjurou
Conceptual Future
Portrait
Wait! There he is! Master Shinjurou!
No way!
No way, no way, no way! No way!
Shadow... Die...
I wonder what's happening on this world
I fly through the sky into space
and circle the world
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday
With my periodic biorhythm
I'm like a washing machine
Just kidding
Yes, I'm spinning around
Around, around the world
Because there's no limit to my love
Spinning around, around, around the world
I want to tell you that I love you, even if it confuses me
Bam, bam, bam
You're not paying attention
Sometimes love keeps being one-sided
It's gotten so hopelessly complex
But I'll make it all true with a miracle
Hey, God,
I'm your god
I think
What's up? Your call was very unexpected.
Unfortunately, my evening is already spoken for.
I'm not the one who needs to talk to you.
I brought someone who wants to meet you.
Huh?
Botanmaru.
Master Shinjurou!
Who the hell is that brat?!
The God Goes to Mount Kurama
I am Botanmaru of Mount Kurama.
I've been wanting to meet you for so long,
and now... Well, now that I have... I wanted...
Save it. I don't know what you want, but you need to get back home before they know you're gone.
Descending the mountain is
forbidden for the half-fledged.
You didn't tell the others, didn't you?
I don't have time to look after a runaway if that's what you were expecting.
Go home.
What?!
That is not it. I came to take you back, Master Shinjurou.
Right now, the mountain is in a state of crisis.
Ever since Master Soujoubou collapsed,
the mountain has been shrouded in a cloud of miasma.
Master Jirou was hastily chosen to be the fourth successor,
but many oppose his appointment.
On the mountain, our days pass with much uncertainty.
Master Shinjurou, if you would return...
And what exactly do you want me to do about it?
Botanmaru. Come on, man.
You already know.
I descended from the mountain over 17 years ago.
I'm a failure.
I'm all about the mundane world scene now.
And besides, there are tons of cute girls down here.
N-No!
You are no failure, Master Shinjurou!
You are actually...
my role model!
It's because you are just like me.
That's why you have to be the one to fix it.
Botanmaru, what's wrong?
This is what he gets for descending as a kid.
Crow children get their strength from the mountain.
The young mustn't descend into the lower world where the mountain can't protect them.
He's inhaled too much of this toxic air.
Where did he get these wounds?
Scars from lashings.
Oh, man...
It was never my plan to go back home so soon...
What's this, Shinjurou?
Still can't fly on your own?
You're already five, yet you still can't fly without help.
You may be the master's son,
but you're absolutely beneath us.
The master's child was the target of the elder brothers' envy.
Shinjurou, why will you not change?
Do you mean to attend the great worship dressed like that?
I'm fine as I am.
I'll wear what everyone else wears.
I'm no better than the others, so it makes no
sense for only my clothes to be of a higher rank.
I'd look like a clown.
This is tradition!
To me, it was nothing but a burden.
Starting today, I'm sleeping here!
Brothers, I look forward to getting along with all of you.
I've never had a proper conversation with my father.
Just met him a couple times.
He was shaggy. Is that what I'm going to look like?
Looking back, I didn't even realize how lonely I was.
My bed is gone!
Oh, was that yours?
It reeked of old milk, so we tossed it.
Dammit.
Come here, Shinjurou.
You can sleep with me.
Until I met Brother Suirou,
I never knew the warmth of another.
Here's the deal.
I'm only taking Botanmaru back and going to see how my sire is doing.
You can come with, but nothing interesting is going to happen.
I didn't come for fun and games.
I came to support you.
You're going to go help the house you ran away from, right?
I brought tons of white talismans, so you can count on me!
I never dreamed that you were the master's son.
Your act as a common crow was most convincing.
So why is the fox here too? I didn't even invite you!
Watching drama unfold from
the sidelines is a hobby of mine.
Oh, is that so? Here's what I think.
You didn't want me to be alone with Nanami, and that's why you rushed to join us.
What?!
Can't you two hold off on fighting until we get there?
Botanmaru's still sleeping, you know.
Where am I?
Are you awake?
You collapsed from exhaustion.
We gave you a Peach Pill, so you'll be fine.
Your arm should be healed too.
You speak the truth! How?!
Peach Pills are the miracle cure of the gods.
A panacea that works on everything from injuries to illnesses.
I do not know what illness Soujoubou has succumbed to,
but he may recover if he takes these.
Is that true, fox?!
Who do you think you're calling "fox," brat?!
You sure traveled a long way for not being able to fly.
I-I rode a crow on the way here.
When I spoke of my desire to bring you back,
Brother Suirou lent me a crow.
Mount Kurama in the human world is a facade.
The crows live on a mountain hidden behind it.
The entrance to it is through Soujougadani.
Ah! The air's so clean out here!
Take care, land god.
Between these two branching cedars is the entrance to the hidden side.
Beyond this point, we will be on our mountain.
You weren't kidding. The air is really different here.
It's morning, but it's totally dark.
There is a fog setting in.
Do not get separated, Nanami.
The miasma here has been known to cause dimensions to contort.
If you lose your way, you can never return.
The miasma is terrible.
Indeed. Ever since the master's presence faded, tainted beings have taken residence here.
However, once he regains his health, things will surely return to normal.
B-But...
Someday, it is my hope...
that you will become the fourth successor, Master Shinjurou.
Brother Suirou!
I want you to become the fourth successor, Brother Suirou.
My sire is shaggy and stern-looking,
but you're beautiful,
so even the crows of Atago and Takao will all be envious!
Me, the fourth successor?
You say such odd things, Shinjurou.
I'm serious!
You've got the fastest wings on the mountain, and you're great with the flute too!
Will you please play it again?
My favorite one about our cherry blossoms!
Wait just a moment.
This is a terrible bruise.
Did Jirou beat you again?
He is always raising his hand against you when my back is turned.
Well, that's not the issue.
The real problem is being a weakling.
Brother Jirou just... doesn't realize how strong he is.
Fine.
I shall play for you.
Your favorite song about our beloved cherry blossoms.
Brother Suirou...
You were my favorite part of life on the mountain.
But because of me...
Brother Suirou!
Master Shinjurou?
What is the matter? Are you not feeling well?
I'm okay.
The fog has grown even thicker.
Are you all right, Nana...
Wait, Botanmaru.
Nanami and Tomoe are gone.
What?
Oh, no...
It's the fog.
Master Shinjurou!
What is this?
Are we inside a fog barrier?
It's likely an attempt to prevent us from entering.
Well, I know I'm not exactly welcome here.
But I still have to return him to the village.
Botanmaru, we're turning back! This fog is...
You've grown, Shinjurou.
You can even fly now, I see.
One might even think you're a respectable crow.
B-Brother Suirou...
Nothing like me. I mean, look at my wings.
I can no longer fly.
I lost them because I helped you.
Shinjurou!
You're twelve already. The reason you can't fly is because you're not tough enough!
Quit clinging to Suirou!
Come, Shinjurou!
I'll get you retrained!
Stop, Brother Jirou!
If you don't quickly use these wings to fly out,
the thunderbolt beasts inside will destroy you!
Now do it!
You couldn't fly.
I heard what happened and entered the cave of thunderbolt beasts to save you.
Then I was struck by lightning
and reduced to this sorry state.
While you swiftly fled the mountain
as soon as your wounds were healed.
Forgive me, Brother Suirou. I—
You don't have to apologize, Shinjurou.
Just die for me.
It will clear a small measure of the fog shrouding my heart.
I should've left you behind.
I never should've even bothered with you.
I never should've reached out to you that day.
Don't say that, Brother!
I do not have the will to defy you.
I hated everything about the mountain.
The one exception was you.
The song of our cherry blossoms!
What of it?!
It means you're an impostor.
The real Brother Suirou is at the top of the mountain
playing my favorite song for me.
Master Shinjurou!
Look where I found them!
Well, how insulting! We were definitely not lost!
How shall I face you?
Not that I really care, but are we still not there yet, crow?
I realized then that while I harbored doubts,
Nanami is carrying on about
needing to go to the bathroom.
I was no longer hesitant to move forward.
Hey! Tomoe!
Next part coming
right up
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
This is it.
This is the crow village of Kurama.
The fog has dissipated, but the miasma is thick.
I know we just got here, but I have to pee so frickin' bad!
This place is closest to the cloud, after all.
Why stand around yapping?
Let's cut to the chase and say hi.
Oh! W-Wait, Nanami!
I don't feel ready yet!
What a beautiful person.
Welcome home, Shinjurou.
Brother!
You've done well to return home safely, Botanmaru.
Come on. You too, Shinjurou.
I am sorry for failing to stay in touch, Brother.
The proud Kurama is offering the deepest bow of respect...
Look up.
Let me get a good look at your face.
Nuzzle, nuzzle.
Nuzzle, nuzzle, nuzzle...
Uh...
I'm Momozono Nanami, and I serve as a land god.
This is my familiar, Tomoe.
I'm so sorry for dropping in on you without warning.
The mountain path must have been tiring for your companions as well.
Come to my home.
What was that about?
The mountain has grown desolate, hasn't it?
Because of this miasma, new plants will not grow.
Even the eternal cherry blossom tree at the heart of our mountain has wilted away.
Gotta pee... Need a bathroom...
But still... Why are you living in a dilapidated house so far away from the compound?
I would've thought you'd have
a home on the temple grounds.
It can be a little drafty, but it's not bad.
I would've liked to make you feel at home at the main hall, but I doubt Jirou would let you in.
It's my fault that you're not
welcome in the hall anymore.
Because I...
Because... I...
Nuzzle, nuzzle, nuzzle...
Fidget
Uh, Suirou...
Master Suirou, forgive me, but it seems nature is calling fiercely to my lady and mistress.
Oh, is that so, Master Familiar?
Then I shall direct you to the outhouse.
What with this house being so shabby, you'll have to walk rather far.
In that case, I shall accompany her.
Y-Y-You...
You don't have to come with me!
The main hall of the hidden Mount Kurama.
Brother Chiyomaru!
I found a wild boar piglet!
Daidaimaru, don't bring things like that back with you.
You'll get yelled at.
His mother will be looking for him.
She was dead.
This guy was alone near her body.
An evil spirit must have gotten her!
If I left him, he would've died too!
That would be sad!
All right. Do as you like.
But keep it a secret from the elders, okay?
They will discard him if he's found.
Okay!
If alone it would die, then that was its fate.
Weakness must perish.
If you don't want to die, grow stronger.
If you can't live on your own strength, that's your time to die.
Ooh, scary.
You are more menacing today than ever, Master Jirou.
It's you, Yatori.
The eternal cherry blossom tree, was it?
Ever since that tree wilted away, everyone on the mountain has completely lost their spirit.
Why not replace it with a new tree and be done with it?
If you take care of that towering tree all by yourself, everyone is sure to sense the advent of a new era!
What do you think, Master Jirou?
Your manners are sorely lacking!
Who the hell just casually snacks away in front of their superior?!
The eternal cherry blossom is sacred!
I will not have that foul mouth of yours speak of supplanting it!
But Master Shinjurou's come back.
What will you do if some folks start talking of making him the fourth successor?
By the looks of things, you don't seem very popular.
Right now, I'm the strongest one on the mountain.
Therefore, I'm the one most
worthy of becoming the Fourth.
I ran farther and flew higher than anyone.
I've been training day and night, never idling,
and working to harden myself,
all to become stronger.
I must succeed the Third's powers before he breathes his last.
Only a few more days until the rite of succession.
None shall stand in my way!
Finally, it will not be Suirou nor Shinjurou,
but I who will truly be the strongest man!
Oh, honestly!
It makes no sense for the bathroom to be this far away!
I've walked like a million miles already!
Suirou didn't seem to like me very much.
Maybe he doesn't trust me.
I am not letting you use my bathroom!
The crow village...
It's true. All the trees are dead here.
It's because of the cloud of miasma.
This is a huge tree. Is it a cherry blossom tree?
It's rotten.
Do not touch it, human!
That hurt! What was that for?!
You're so cute! Are you crow kids from around here?
Uh...
It's coming this way!
This is the mountain's eternal cherry blossom tree!
Outsiders who casually touch it suffer divine retribution!
Eternal cherry blossom tree...
So it is a cherry blossom tree.
It's rotten, though.
Hey! Don't touch it!
This is the sacred tree at the heart of the mountain!
It blooms four times a year,
and it's really, really beautiful!
Th-That swelling of the chest...
That can only mean one thing.
A woman!
She's a woman!
Wh-What of it?
We spoke to a woman! The elder brothers will yell at us!
Oh, we're done for!
What's wrong with talking to me? How insulting!
We're not allowed to speak with women or look them in the eye!
Especially with young beautiful women, they say
you'll fall to the mundane world if you touch one!
Beauty
I-I don't know if I'd go that far, but...
Huh? Wait.
Is she beautiful?
Brother Suirou's more beautiful.
Then I guess it's okay.
Brothers...
Dig a hole at the base of the eternal cherry blossom tree.
I want to lay this wild boar piglet to rest soon.
Ever since Master Soujoubou collapsed,
we've had this cloud of miasma hanging over us.
Evil spirits now appear on the mountain,
and the animals are growing scarcer too.
And in the end, even the eternal cherry blossom wilted away.
I wonder what's going to happen to the village.
It'll be okay.
Master Soujoubou will be well again soon,
and the mountain will go back to the way it was too.
Really?
Yeah.
You're lying.
Brother Jirou said that Master Soujoubou didn't have long to live.
So Brother Jirou will become the Fourth, right?
But will Brother Jirou becoming the Fourth really make things better here?
Will this eternal cherry blossom tree flower again?
With my powers,
I can't dispel the cloud of miasma over the mountain...
But at the very least, I can dispel
the cloud hanging over these boys.
Please...
They bloomed!
The flowers bloomed!
Are we dreaming?
It's just like you guys said.
I'm glad I got to see the beautiful cherry blossoms.
The evening bell!
We have to get back to the hall to prepare the evening meal.
All right! When we get back, let's tell everyone about the eternal cherry blossom!
Hey, are you...
a celestial nymph from the heavens who's
showed up to put an end to our suffering at last?
You've got some game for a kid!
Hurry on home now.
Thank you, miss.
I'm glad. Really glad.
What?
The petals are blowing away.
It's no use.
My powers really aren't enough to make it last.
We need Master Soujoubou to regain his health quickly.
Hey, can you hear me?
And thus, the man...
met a celestial nymph.
That night, I was looking
at the fleeting remnants of the day
The milky way spread across my vision
It was very beautiful
Hey, can you hear me?
I don't think I can talk to other people about this
I'll call up God, I think
If a new day hadn't begun
then yesterday's tomorrow would be today
and yesterday would be the day before
I'm waiting for you
I'll stay here
The boat is stopped here
If today weren't today
and were that day instead, oh, that'd be nice
Preview
Oh, dear! What a violent man!
Will they be able to slip past Jirou to go see Master Soujoubou?
That'd be nice, that's what I think
Will they be okay with Nanami's plan?
T-Tomoe, wh-wh-wh-what's gotten into you?
Next time, "The God Sneaks In."
The God Sneaks In
Stealthily, sneakily, off on a mad dash!