Hey, Kyono...
What're you planning to do?
Well... What should I do?
Unbelievable. It's your last summer in high school.
Most students have their career plans figured out by now,
but you haven't even decided
whether you want to go to college or get a job.
When you put it that way... I guess you're right.
You guess? Y'know...
This is your future we're talking about here.
I know that.
In fact, I've been giving it a lot of thought.
Stupid. It's obvious you haven't thought about it at all.
Uh-oh...
Well...
After that huge stunt you pulled off,
I can't blame you if you feel a little burned out.
Oh, not at all.
The Sweats Club is always full of energy!
Seniors are supposed to retire from their club activities.
Once a Kamo Girls' Sweats Club member,
always a Sweats Club member!
One, two, three!
Two, two three!
Three, two three!
My career plans, huh?
Back then we tried to fly with propellers that couldn't do it
We ran with bare feet, and now we see different skies
We always live
full of conviction
that we are misunderstood
You're precious to me
but lost at the same time
I'll get over it
Spin the wheel of fate
Inside the dew, like magic,
are tears and sunny days
I feel lonely now
I'm sure my dream will come true
and we will be together forever
Welcome Back to Kamogawa!
Are you ready, Milady?
Yes.
We will now begin the third Vox Particle Control Experiment.
Stage One.
Connecting the Nerve Cutter to the Consciousness Strata.
Stage Two. Activating Mind Probe.
Penetrating straight into
the Fourth Layer of the Consciousness Strata.
Bio telepathic wave pulse is in sync.
Beta to theta range biometrics pattern is orange.
What's the Vox particle concentration?
It's stalling around 200.
Far from the breaking point.
Let's move on to Stage Three.
Commencing Stage Three.
Mind probe now penetrating the Sixth Layer.
into the Ego Borderline Layer.
The cell structure in her Consciousness Bubble is becoming unstable.
Any further stimulation could cause severe damage to her personality.
Pull back the probe to the Fifth Layer—
No, keep going.
King Dizelmine?
This could cause severe damage to Lady Lan's psyche...
We don't have enough data yet.
As you wish, my lord.
Control, report.
It's an enemy attack!
Armored Forces from the De Metrio Army are approaching!
The enemy crafts have activated their weapons systems.
They're attacking!
Lympha, standing by for takeoff.
Lan, we're abandoning this station.
Brother?!
We're ready for takeoff.
Start up all the jammers and deploy them!
This facility is useless to us
now that Villagiulio has discovered it.
I understand.
Then I'll cover your escape.
Dizelmine!
Thanks for waiting!
Here's your Oraga Bowl lunch special!
Please enjoy!
Madoka, I can handle the rest.
Can you go help out the guys at the Seaside Cafe?
It's gonna get busy there soon.
Sure thing, Uncle.
I'll be going then.
I really should start thinking about what's best for her future.
Welcome.
What a babe...
Izo!
Our lunches are the best in town!
Here's your Offshore lunch special. Thanks for waiting!
Array, you're so cute!
Did you notice the customers out on the deck?
Yeah, they're from Le Garite.
Just leave 'em alone.
It's not uncommon to see them around here lately.
You guys seem pretty busy.
Kyono.
My uncle asked me to come help.
We can definitely use the help, Kyono!
The guys only come around when you're here.
Array here only attracts the weirdos.
We have regulars who come all the way from Tokyo to see Array.
It's not like I choose the customers.
Everyone's welcome here.
Y'know, you three are really starting to fit in around here.
Someone's drowning!
Oh, no!
I'm coming!
She's okay now.
Perfect!
Madoka!
Madoka, you're on the ball, as always.
One never retires from the Sweats Club.
More like the School Swimsuit Club.
Either way, it's pretty weird.
Weird?
Anyway, I'm still surprised that your uncle opened up a beach cafe.
There was some talk about it a while ago.
But until last year, it would've been impossible
with just my uncle and me running the place.
He should stick to easy dishes like curry and ramen noodles here.
My uncle takes pride in his cooking.
Did things change this year then?
Yup. He found a great chef to work part-time.
You mean Izocchi? But he's an alien.
Not the sort of skill you'd expect from him.
We decided to let those three run this place,
and it's become a huge hit.
Well, Kirikiri and Array sure aren't bad looking...
Not Kirikiri. It's Kirius.
Whatever.
A lot of the other students come here all the time.
See?
Damn, this isn't a host club.
It makes sense that this place is so popular.
The three of them are from outer space, after all.
Michi, is it that important?
Of course.
I mean, it's sort of romantic.
Dunno, they don't seem all that romantic to me.
And lately, we've seen people from Le Garite around here.
Isn't that why you changed which college was your first choice?
Oh, you did?
You've always wanted to study astronomy, right?
Now I'm more interested in diplomacy!
Diplomacy?
Yes. From now on, we'll be dealing with people from Earth,
Le Garite, and even other planets.
So maybe if I become a diplomat,
I'll be able to visit all kinds of places.
Wow... That sounds pretty awesome.
It's still just a dream though...
Compared to that, my career plan is really plain.
You're planning on finding a job in Tokyo, right?
No, no...
I'm looking to join the Kamogawa Fisheries Cooperative now.
The Cooperative?
Are you gonna use Kojiro's personal connections?
I probably will.
But the place is perfect for surfing.
Plus, Kamogawa's become the center of the world lately.
Tokyo doesn't even hold a candle to this place.
Madoka...
Will Lan and Muginami ever return to Kamogawa?
I guess that subject is still off limits, huh?
They're both busy.
They'll probably just show up unannounced one day.
You're right.
It hasn't even been a year. I'm sure they'll come back.
I wonder if Lan learned how to swim?
Hey, Muginami!
Hey, Lan!
I wonder if they're doing okay...
No, no! I have too much to do tomorrow.
I need to sleep!
All sections, confirm anchor stabilization,
and then turn in your checklists to the bridge.
Jim, please let Headquarters know that we've reached Kamogawa.
Roger.
We will hold an Intergalactic Conference on Pharos.
And it will take place in Kamogawa!
I want you to head there immediately.
So here we are once more...
Morning! Let's make this another great day, guys!
What's wrong?
Pharos?
They must have arrived late last night.
So you didn't know about this, Kyono?
No, I didn't.
What about you? Didn't you hear anything from Asteria?
That girl has totally forgotten about us.
Maybe something happened?
Maybe they're on summer vacation.
Madoka...
Lan?
Woof.
Lan!
Welcome back!
You look great. Has your hair grown out?
My aide evens it out for me every day.
Spoken like a true princess!
You haven't changed at all, Madoka.
Actually, she wasn't quite herself until you arrived.
It's been a long time, Mr. Hiroshi.
Is this for me?
Of course! Eat up.
Thank you.
Is it good?
Yes, it's great.
What's wrong?
Did you put wasabi in it, Uncle?
Huh? Why would I?
I'm sorry. It's nothing.
How has everyone in Kamogawa been doing?
Huh?
Oh yeah, they've been fine.
And Miss Yoko?
She went to Madagascar.
Madagascar?
It's slight, but I'm getting Vox particle readings.
There's no mistaking it.
It's a Flower of Lagrange fossil.
I see... So she's there to investigate the Vox.
What about you? Is your brother doing well?
Yes.
Yeah? That's great!
We'll have to throw you a welcome back party!
Madoka...
Huh?
Will you hear me out?
Lan?
I want you to do something.
What is it?
Damn it! I can't hear them.
What are they talking about?
What would the princess from Le Garite be doing here now?
Izo!
Vox Lympha?!
Let's go!
Can you please take my order?
Water please!
Right away!
Damn it! Kirius and Izo had better hurry and get back here!
I wish I could say it's good to have you both back on board,
but arriving unannounced on your Vox like this is just...
I'm here on a special assignment from King Dizelmine of Le Garite.
This is an unofficial visit, but one with utmost importance.
Then you came fully aware that Pharos was heading back to Kamogawa.
Lan?
Madoka, please pilot Aura one more time.
Huh?
But...
Aura shut itself down after its last battle.
You know that already.
Yes, I understand. But...
This is absolutely necessary.
Lan...
In order to maintain our military power, we tried to reboot Aura.
We conducted many tests with Madoka's help,
but nothing worked.
Well, even if it had, there was nothing for me to do.
You're wrong!
Lan?
The connection shared between you and Vox Aura is very powerful.
It's a bond that can't be broken that easily!
You think so?
She'll move if you get on, Madoka. I know it!
I've already tried several times.
But if you say so, I'll try it again.
So what should I do... Comrade?
Comrade...
Tadokoro here.
What?
We have a lot of guests today.
The unidentified craft will soon enter
our air defense identification zone.
Does it belong to the Le Garite?
We made an inquiry, but the reply we got back said that there was no match.
Order all ships to Defcon 2 status.
The unidentified craft is quickly approaching.
No!
Could this be...?
What's going on?
Snap out of it and report!
E-Excuse me!
According to our IFF systems,
the unidentified craft is Vox Ignis.
It's Muginami!
Muginami?!
Lan, Muginami came back too!
She intends to interfere again...
Wait, Lan!
Hey, Lan!
What's going on?!
Lan?
Don't worry. I'll protect you, Madoka.
Huh?
That girl...
Muginami is planning to kill you.
Let's go, Orca.
Muginami is planning to do what?
Orca... So Lan is here, after all.
Muginami!
So you intend to have Madoka pilot the Vox, no matter what?
Fine!
I'll destroy you first, Lan!
Lord Villagiulio, Muginami has left the force
and has headed for Earth on Vox Ignis.
What?
I believe she intends to go after Kyono Madoka by herself.
Oh, brother...
I guess she's not cut out for De Metrio's regular army, after all.
How should we proceed, Sir?
She's chosen to carry out the dirty work, for my sake.
What should I do? Have her court-martialed and executed?
Well, we can't just ignore her...
Let her be.
Otherwise, I'd be no different than Dizelmine.
Tell everyone that Muginami went to Earth under my orders.
Yes, Sir.
Damn it...
They're way too gentle. Each and every one of them.
Move! Please, Midori!
Lympha and Ignis are still engaged in battle.
Lan... Muginami...
I don't get it. Why?
What happened between you two?
This is crazy!
Midori...
We've had more than enough rest, right?
It's time to get up.
It's already a new semester!
Time to wake up!
You sleepyhead!
Ow!
Midori!
Aura has been activated!
What?!
Don't you dare start a fight without me!
The Jersey Club spirit! The Jersey Club spirit!
I won't leave you alone, hello and let's be cheery!
Who cares what's correct right now
First things first
Here in front of me is someone
who carries around a billion issues
I won't just shut up and leave you be
Lie down a while and you're fine again
Let's just stretch
I'm tired
Here, have some Kamogawa Energy
I'm back!
It's good to drink it all
It's good to drink two
Don't worry how much I drink
You ask me why I do so much for you
Isn't that obvious?
I do it because your dreams are wonderful!
The Jersey Club spirit! The Jersey Club spirit!
I want to help you, hello and let's be cheery!
Hey, why are you two fighting? This isn't right!
Wait, I got it! Are you fighting over a killer whale plushie?
No.
It's not? Wait, I got it!
Is it about Muginami's gorgeous cape?
No!
It's not? Then what?!
What else could possibly be worth fighting over?
Oh wait, I got it!
That's not it, either!
Mayhem on Kamogawa Beach