So it exists... it exists...
No, it doesn't...
Y-You...
Dirty dog!
Louise!
Chibi-Louise!
E-Eléonore-oneesama!
Aren't you up early?
That's convenient for me. Pack up already.
Get moving!
You're coming home.
Please hold on, Eléonore-oneesama.
You there. Come with me.
I'll have you be my personal maid until we get home.
Hey! Let go!
What rowdy people.
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君のそばにいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai ga bokura wo tameshitatte
どんな未来が僕らを試したって
No matter how the future tests us
kitto…
きっと…
I’m sure…
aa futari no unmei
ああ 二人の運命
Ah, it’s our destiny
meguriaeta no wa
巡り合えたのは
I was able to meet you
kimi no koe kikoeta kara
君の声 聞こえたから
Because I heard your voice
sou pinchi na dekigoto
そう ピンチな出来事
Yeah, even if crisis events
oshiyosete kite mo
押し寄せてきても
Press on at me
kimi to ireba norikoerareru
君といれば乗り越えられる
If I'm with you, then I can overcome them
tokimeki to makenki to
ときめきと負けん気と
Palpitations and competitive spirit
urahara de haraharasuru kedo
裏腹でハラハラするけど
Excite me on the contrary, but-
Stay with me
tada kimi o mamoritai yo
ただ 君を守りたいよ
I only want to protect you
tooi sekai de umareta futari da kedo
遠い世界で生まれた二人だけど
We were born in distant worlds
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君の側にいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai mo kibou ni kaeyou
どんな未来も希望に変えよう
Let’s change any future into hope
Forever
The Vallière Sisters
It's a little tight in here.
Are you all right?
Ah, yes.
There he goes, closing in on her again!
Chibi-Louise! I'm not done talking yet!
I'm sorry, Nee-sama.
You keep looking away, too. Settle down a little.
Because my familiar is...
Geez, this military training and whatnot...
The Magic Academy has degraded.
I can't leave you in a place like that any longer.
Come back home and commit to bridal training instead.
B-But...
"But"?!
"Yes", you mean!
You Chibi!
Chibi-Louise!
Siesta, is something wrong?
You don't seem well these days.
I have... realised Saito-san's true feelings.
You have chosen Miss Vallière...
So, I no longer...
That perverted dog!
This is...
...Louise's house?
Welcome home, Eléonore-sama and Louise-sama.
Louise.
Welcome home, little Louise.
Chii-neesama!
She's a hot one...
Also...
It's been a long time, Chii-neesama!
Louise, let me have a good look of your face.
My, you've become beautiful.
Chii-neesama...
Anyway, how have you been?
Thank you for worrying.
Nothing has changed.
Don't worry. It's the usual.
Cattleya.
Where's Mother?
Damn it, I'm hungry, too...
U-Um, Mother...
Mother! Tell Louise for me!
She should stay home from now on!
I bet she's an outcast at school, too.
I-I'm not the same as I used to be!
The Princess...
I'm helping out Her Highness!
She says that she needs my strength.
Your strength?
What could you possibly do when you have zero talent?
Well...
Mother, let's get a groom for Louise already.
How about the second-born son of the Albert family?
Groom?
Why does it turn out that way?
If you're talking about marriage, shouldn't you get married first?
Your engagement with Count Burgundy.
Louise, that topic is...
Chibi-Louise...
To talk back to me with sarcasm...
It sure looks like you attitude has grown bigger!
The engagement has been dissolved!
It's been dissolved!
You got a problem?!
Why?
I don't know. Something like "I can't take it anymore".
I wonder why...
Eléonore.
Louise.
We're having dinner right now.
But, Mother!
We shall speak of Louise when Father comes home tomorrow.
So Louise really is a lady from a rich family.
Her world is different from mine.
Besides... besides...
Are they serious about getting her a groom?!
If Saito-san loves Miss Vallière,
I was thinking of giving up on him and stepping out.
However, they don't seem to have made any progress.
As a woman, I'm in an equal position.
Either way, I'm clearly better than her in some categories.
Why is Eléonore-oneesama always mean to me?
She's been like that forever.
She always bullies me.
It's because you're cute.
Because you're cute, she's worried about you.
Because she loves you, she can't stop pestering you.
That's not true.
The same goes for me as well.
Because I love you, I can understand everything about you.
You're at an age of falling in love, right?
I-I'm not in love!
You can't hide it from me.
R-Really, I'm not in love with anyone!
Saito-san. Saito-san.
What's wrong?
Can't get to sleep?
Were you thinking of someone?
Could it be that boy you brought with you?
N-No!
He's only my familiar.
I don't love him at all.
Oh... I never asked if you loved him or not.
Chii-neesama, I hate you.
Oops, she hates me now.
Off you go.
To where you belong.
I-It's not... because I want to meet him.
I'm a mage.
I'm an aristocrat.
It's natural to keep your familiar around you at all times.
I'm going to him since I bet he's worried...
...not having his master around.
T-That's really all there is to this!
Saito-san...
W-Why are you here?!
Miss Vallière...
Why are you in Saito's...
...my familiar's bed?
S-Saito-san...
Saito-san called me.
Yes, he told me... to come to his room tonight.
I came because Saito-san asked me to!
Louise's room is...
Is it this?
Louise?
Louise, right?
About the groom thing you guys were talking about earlier...
I've always wanted to meet you.
I regret having dissolved our engagement.
My dear Count!
Please! Don't say anything and make love to me!
Out of the blue?
Moreover, at your home?
Wait, did she have this much?
You're...!
What's a plebeian doing in my room?
Uh, I went into the wrong room...
I mean, I'm sorry.
Hold it!
Plebeians without manners must be punished.
I-I'm sorry! I won't do it again!
Forgive me!
I won't come close to you ever again!
I wouldn't want to, even if asked to...
What did you just say?
No! My tongue slipped...
Um... ah...
I'm sorry!
Stop!
Louise?
Has Louise returned?
You're late in returning.
Did the military meeting run overtime?
Yes. I must soon leave again.
Military life really is pathetic,
dispatching troops and inflaming the citizens with war.
What a problematic Queen we have.
F-Father! Queen Henrietta isn't aggravating the war at all!
What do you possibly understand?!
Listen, Louise. You do not have to force yourself to learn magic.
Return home and get yourself a groom.
That is the end of this conversation.
Father!
Looks like it's settled.
We should quickly arrange Louise's engagement.
That's the best way to get her settled.
Why? If you're talking about marriage, shouldn't you get married first?
Didn't I tell you that my engagement got dissolved?
I'm sorry!
But I'm not ready to get married yet...
Mother, Nee-sama, you're troubling Louise with this sudden marriage talk.
Louise. Is there someone you're currently in a relationship with?
No! No, I don't! There's no such person!
But it looks like you do have someone on your mind.
No, I don't!
Whom?
Which aristocrat is this?
A count? Or a baron?
Don't tell me he's a baronet or something even lower.
You're joking...
Are you serious?
You've fallen in love with someone of a lower status?
This girl keeps worrying me no matter how old she gets.
I'm not in love with anyone!
Louise!
Damn it, it hurts!
She's so brutal.
I wonder what Louise is doing...
It's open.
May I please come in?
Y-Yes, please.
She looks mature, kind and so soft.
I wonder if Louise will look like this when she grows up...
If so...
Louise will grow to be more attractive than myself.
You see, at this rate, Louise will have to get a groom.
You wouldn't want that, would you?
Louise getting married...
She's in the courtyard, so go to her.
Ever since she was little, she would hide in the boat in the courtyard any time something happens.
If you find Louise, go outside of the mansion.
A horse carriage is waiting for you.
May primogenitor's blessings be upon both you and Louise.
Note: Primogenitor: One's earliest male ancestor.
Please take care of my cute little sister, Knight-dono.
Knight... You mean me?
I'm not in love with anyone, since Saito likes the maid...
He likes her more than me...
Let's go, Louise.
Saito.
Your sister prepared a carriage for us.
Don't bother. I don't care about you anymore.
What are you talking about?
Because... I can't tell my family... about my Void magic.
Nobody gives me credit, no matter how much I try.
I've had it.
Man...
I'll give you credit, then.
I'll assent to everything about you.
So stand up already.
Don't lie to me... when you were the one who called the maid.
Huh?
You prefer her, don't you?
Are you an idiot?
Who are you calling an idiot?!
Who would willingly please a selfish girl like you?
Who would willingly be a familiar for a flat-chested master?
H-How dare you say that!
Yeah, I'll say it as many times as you want.
I don't give a damn about all this war, mission and groom stuff!
Do whatever you want, then!
I love you!
I love you.
Looking at your face makes my heart race.
Isn't that what being in love is?
And yet you blab about maids and whatnot...
Why do you think I risk my life by fighting?
It's because I love you!
I'll kill you if you're lying.
I'm not lying.
W-Wait!
Um... um... um... you see...
Well, anyway, ah...
S-Since you've sworn your loyalty to me by saying that you love your master,
I-I guess you do deserve a reward...
J-Just one spot, okay?
Y-You can touch anywhere you want on your master's body, just one spot.
I'm going to die...
Hey, Saito.
I love you.
No, Saito...
Hey, I said no.
I love you. I really love you.
I seriously love you.
Do you really?
Yeah.
Really? Seriously?
No, you can't...
No, don't rush like that...
Don't be so full of yourself...
I love you, Louise.
I really love you.
Saito.
What are you doing?
Decapitate him.
You were so close, Partner.
Only a step away.
Shut up. We can talk later.
They're handsome guys.
Here I go.
What is he?
He can't be a human.
Please don't worry about Louise, Father!
Don't give me that crap!
Damn, what do I do?
Onee-san...
Saito-san! Hurry!
Siesta!
Let's go.
I can trust what you said earlier, right?
Of course.
Hey, Saito.
Where were you last night?
Um... well...
Is it true that you called her to your room?
Of course not!
Then where were you?
Well, your older sister was...
What?!
You touched Eléonore-oneesama, of all people?
N-No, I had no intention of doing so.
Your sister was the one who jumped me.
Oh, so you did sneak into her room!
Because I mistook her room for yours...
I won't forgive you!
I was a fool for believing you.
You lying dog!
Dirty dog!
Perverted dog!
I-I'm sorry!
I'm the only one who can make Saito-san happy.
Unforgivable. I won't forgive you!
With my womanly charm, I'll beat Miss Vallière.
Hey, are you listening to me?
You stupid dog!
Y-You stupid dog!
chanto koko ni ite watashi no chikaku de
ちゃんとココにいて! 私の近くで
Be right here! close to me
zutto watashi o itsumo itsumo mitsumete nasai
ずっと私をいつもいつも見つめてなさい
Always, always look at me at all times
yosomishiteta desho hoka no onna no ko
よそ見してたでしょっ 他の女の子
You looked away, didn’t you? At other girls
o-shiokisuru wa furari furari furachi na yatsu wa
お仕置きするわ　フラリフラリ不埒なヤツは
I’ll punish those who are wavering and insolent
Don't touch! kikanai kara ne iiwake wa
Don't touch! 聞かないからね　言い訳は
Don’t touch! Because I won’t listen to excuses
Touch me... tsukareta kara nee kata o kashite yo
Touch me… 疲れたから… ねぇ肩を貸してよ
Touch me… because I'm tired… Hey, lend me your shoulder
suki yo nante uso yo
スキよ　なんて嘘よ
I love you, it’s a lie
kirai sore mo uso da wa
キライ　それも嘘だわ
I hate you, that’s a lie, too
nai nai nai dame yo kanchigai
ないないない　ダメよ勘違い
Nay nay nay, it’s useless, it’s a misunderstanding
dakara suki yo nante iwanai
だから「スキよ」なんて言わない
So I won’t say, “I love you”
Non non non dokka e ittara
Non non non　どっかへ行ったら
Non non non, because I absolutely won’t forgive you
zettai ni yurusanai kara ne
絶対に　許さないからね!
If you go to somewhere else
datte
だって
But
honto wa dare yori soba ni itai no
ホントは誰より傍にいたいの
The truth is, I want to be by your side more than anyone else
ai no kusari de sanposhimasho
愛の鎖で　散歩しましょ!
Let’s go take a walk in chains of love!
I... to be honest...
...might love you...
Next Time
You dog!
What are you investigating so stealthily?
My sister would never steal.
Zero no Tsukaima. Futatsuki no Kishi.
The Spy's Seal.
If you want to meet me again next week, then sit tightly and wait!
The Spy's Seal