Twice-Cooked Pork
Sorry for the wait.
I can only make this.
Here.
Wow, awesome!
It's twice-cooked pork.
I'm really hungry, so this is perfect.
I put something in for a hidden taste.
I wonder if you can tell.
Having a hidden taste makes it sound like the real thing.
I'm digging in!
It only has the miso flavour, or rather,
the hidden taste is not so hidden, or rather...
No, instead, the more you chew it,
the hidden taste gets worse, or rather...
I'm really against this hidden taste!
tatta ima hajimete kizuita
たった今 初めて気づいた
I just realised it for the first time
koi ni ochita no dana
恋に落ちたのだな～
That I had fallen in love~
nijyuuyo jikan kimi kimi kimi
24h キミ☆ キミ☆ キミ☆
Twenty-four hours a day thinking of you, you and nothing more than you!
ishiki sezaru o emasen
意識せざるをえません!
It's something I wasn't consciously aware of
nanka (nanka) itsumo to chigau
なんか (なんか) いつもと違う
Somehow (somehow) I'm feeling different from the usual
kimi to (futari) gikochinai kaiwa
キミと (二人) ぎこちない会話
With you (the two of us) and our dull chatter
masaka (ryouomoi) iya kataomoi
まさか (両思い) いや 片思い
Don't tell me (mutual love?) Nope, it's a one-sided crush
yabai shisen acchatta
やばい! 視線合っちゃった!
This is bad! Our gazes met!
nani nani kono doki doki
なになに?! このドキドキ?!
What, what? Why is my heart pounding like this?
shikoukairo guccha guccha konsen
思考回路 ぐっちゃぐっちゃ 混線・・・
Did a short circuit just make a mess out of my mind?
konna koto hajimete dayo
こんなこと 初めてだよ
This is my first time... feeling like this...
netsu demo aru no kana
熱でもあるのかな～
I wonder if I have a fever~
kyuutenchokka irasshatta koigokoro
急転直下 いらっしゃった 恋心
Suddenly and precipitately, love has arrived.
acchuuma kao hakka de makkakka
あっちゅうま 顔 発火で まっかっか
Instantly igniting my face into a bright red
ba ba baka na te ga furueruzo
バ・バ・バカな?! 手が震えるぞ
T-That's stupid?! My hands are shaking
kore ga zoku ni iu koi nano
これが 俗に言う 「恋」 なの?!
Is this really what they call "love"?
yayayacchatta kaiwa kami makuri
やややっちゃった 会話 噛みまくり
I-I did it! A conversation filled with stutters
kimazui chinmoku mamimumemo
気まずい沈黙 マミムメモ
This awkward silence... *mumble mumble*
kimi no (kimi no) kimochi shiritai yo
キミの (キミの) 気持ち 知りたいよ
Your... (Your...) I want to know your feelings.
kakakata kataomoi
カカカタ☆カタオモイ
O-One-sided love
hatsukoi itsumo no tsuugakuro
初恋! いつもの通学路
First love! The usual way to school
pika pika hikaru I do fall in love
ピカピカ光る I do fall in love!
The shining light. I do fall in love!
sora mo tobesou sa
空も飛べそうさ
I feel I could fly towards the sky
kakakata kataomoi
カカカタ☆カタオモイ
O-One-sided love
Nichijou 23
This is actually pretty good...
Mio-chan, Mio-chan!
TL note: Kappa, literally meaning "river-child", is a water sprite found in Japanese folklore.
is cool, isn't it?
What the hell is this?
Kappa?
is cool, isn't it?
Why a kappa all of the sudden?
Moreover, what does she mean by "is cool, isn't it?"...
But...
Next time, I might want to draw something in fantasy that's interesting and strong.
Something like a Daidarabotchi and a kappa.
TL note: Daidarabotchi is a gigantic demon in Japanese mythology.
Kappa... Heh, I guess he will be the "uke".
TL note: In yaoi, "uke" refers to the more feminine partner.
Kappa, kappa, huh?
Kappa...
Kappapaa... pa... pa...
Parasite.
With this, maybe we can just play picture shiritori.
Yukko.
Thanks.
Parashite?
TL note: In Japanese, parasite is read as "parasaito", but Yukko read it as "parashite".
This is what a parashite's meant to be like?
Having this arrow means...
I see. She's inviting me to a game of picture shiritori.
I'll accept it.
Hmm... Parashite...
"Te"... "Te"... Okay.
So big!
I didn't have time!
Moreover, a "tengu"...
She read parasite's "to" as "te".
Oh, well.
A "tengu," huh?
"Tengu"... "gu"... "gu"... "gu"...
"Gu-"!
N-No way!
Tengo!
What the hell is a "tengo"?!
What's a "tengo"?!
No! Wait a minute!
There's no way a high school student would make such a childish mistake.
I mean, she already drew a picture of a
tengu and still wrote down what it was.
I don't get it.
I don't really understand, but...
I guess I'll go with "go" here.
Here.
Draw smaller!
What's with this Goku drawn out of boredom?
TL note: Goku is a character from a classical Chinese novel "Journey To The West".
Huh... Wait... Goku?
I'm pretty sure I drew a tengu just now...
Well, I can understand how she could mistake "gu" for "go".
I'll get juice from her later for this.
Now, it's "u"... "u"... "u"... Okay!
Draw smaller!
I can't draw very well!
A sea urchin?
TL note: Sea urchin is "uni", and rabbit is "usagi", or "usa" for short, in Japanese.
Draw smaller!
I can't draw very well!
cow
No, a rabbit.
I can't draw very well!
cow
It's a cow?!
TL note: Cow is "ushi" in Japanese.
I can't draw very well!
cow
This cow is beyond terrible...
Here.
Tongue! She came at me with the tongue!
TL note: In Japanese, tongue is "shita".
Then, it's "ta".
"Ta"... "ta"...
Taxi... Ta...
W-Why are you doing this?!
If you write it like this, it isn't a taxi.
It's a taxy!
I'm just going to write down whatever works.
Oh, seafood has started to come up!
shisu
She's really up for it.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, no!
uperman
I'll lose like this!
TL note: There is no word in Japanese beginning with the sound "n", so you lose if you use a word ending with the kana "n" in a game of shiritori.
uperman
No, this... I just have to do this...
Here.
X
Go Soccer Club
Go Soccer Club 3
Ah, there's nothing to do.
There's nothing to do, Sekiguchi.
Okay, Sekiguchi, let's have an "Isse no se" match!
TL note: "Isse no se" is a Japanese numbers game played using both hands.
I'll start!
Isse no two!
Sekiguchi...
There's nothing to do, anyway. Can't you play with me sometimes?
President.
Sekiguchi...
Nichijou 24
I forgot my homework and was made to stand in the hallway, Mogami river. By Yukko.
I can't believe I have to stand in the hallway just because I forgot my homework today...
How should I spend this time, Mogami river. By Yukko.
Wai-
E-Everyone! It's a deer... It's a deer...
W-Why is the principal is trying to catch the deer...?
W-Wai- Principal... D-Deer...
Principal!
W-Wait, everyone... The principal's... dying...
That's a... shika senbei?!
TL note: Shika senbei are rice crackers specially made to feed deer.
W-Wai- Everyone, the principal is d-dyin-
He got up.
He climbed up!
He jumped!
And falls down just like that!
He climbed up again!
He climbed down!
H-He's in a deadlock!
Principal!
Principal...
Wai- Everyone... Death... Principal... Death...
Uh... Wai- Um... Uh...
Wai- Everyone, listen!
Uh... Um... P-Prin...
Um... Prin...
Nothing new to report from the hallway!
Those were the true words that came from the bottom of her heart.
They were by no means to cover up for the principal,
nor because explaining it would be too troublesome.
Nothing like that.
Maybe she just wanted to show respect to the
heroes who had just performed a fight to the death.
It's too early to gather the early-summer rain, Mogami river.
No idea what it means.
10 Yen Soccer
Okay, then. Mio-chan will be the referee.
You don't need a referee for ten yen soccer.
You don't understand, do you?
It's all about the feeling, the feeling.
Now, kick off!
I guess it can't be helped.
Come at me from any angle!
Okay...
First comes rock, next comes paper. Rockscispaper doesn't count,
rock, paper, scissors!
I-
Chomp.
I love you.
Shinonome Institute
Nichijou 25
What should I do?
I caught a cockroach...
C-Carefully...
Anyway, I'll have to do it carefully...
I have to make sure this disgusting root of evil doesn't spread in the house again.
A plan... I have to go with the most perfect plan...
Ah, pesticide spray!
No, I can't.
It's not a one-hit-kill, so there's a chance that it will just run away.
Most of all...
I don't want to see it squirm!
Ah, that's right!
What about detergent?
I'll cover the tea table with detergent to seal its movement, and then pinpoint it directly!
I-It will fly!
With nowhere to run, it'll definitely fly!
When it flies, it's over.
It'll blindly aim somewhere and hit people!
If it were to hit my body... or hit my face...!
No, wait...
I-If this was to get inside... get inside my mouth...
It's a one-shot rock and roll!
This is the worst kind of uneasiness.
I don't have any other choice.
The choice of lifting this bowl up might kill me!
Death or die!
There's...
Trash
There's no choice but to do that...
What are you doing?
S-Sakamoto-san!
Please save me!
I-Inside this, there is a r-roach... a roach.
What?
Could it be a cockroach?
I guess it can't be helped.
All right.
Leave it to me.
That'll save me.
Hey.
Yes?
What are you doing?
I'll get it, so lift the bowl.
Yes?
No, I'm saying lift the bowl.
Otherwise, I can't get it.
Hey!
W-What are you saying?!
How could I lift the seal on the root of evil?!
This is Pandora's box!
The moment I lift it up, it's death or die!
No, no, no.
How am I supposed to get it without lifting up the bowl?!
Lift it up yourself!
As if I can!
W-What should I do?
Sakamoto-san has gone somewhere...
Nano!
What's today's snack?
Ah, good timing!
The professor is not bothered by bugs either, so surely she can...
Professor, i-it'd be nice if you could get rid of t-this cockroach inside this bowl!
Sure.
R-Rock and roll!
Sorry, then I shall leave it to you.
It's okay.
I'll do it in one shot!
Men!
TL note: "Men" is what you say after successfully hitting your opponent's head in kendo.
Oh, I hit the wrong one.
I-I'm... I'm seriously worried here, but this person is... this person is...
Seriously, I hate you, professor!
You're going to cry?
It's just a joke!
Geez, there's no way I would hate you.
Professor, I love you.
Nano!
Geez, professor.
Now, it's time to rock and roll!
If You Count To 10
Hey, it's hot, so can I get out?
Huh?
We just got in.
But it's become hot...
Then let's get out after a count to ten.
Twenty log root ten!
Huh?
You said we can get out once we count to ten.
Uh... Um...
You have to say "One, two"...
Go Soccer Club 4
What's with everyone?
Just because they have cram school, they all leave.
Sekiguchi, you're bored as well, right?
Huh?
Come to think of it, didn't you go to cram school, too?
You've got to be kidding!
Nichijou 26
Delicious!
Yukko, how's the curry?
Yeah, it's almost done.
I'm quite hungry.
Yeah, me, too!
Mai-chan, how are things over there?
I foresee a big one.
This will be a feast.
All right! It seems like it's ready.
Thanks for waiting.
The extremely delicious super-curry is complete.
I think it will take a little longer over here.
We should have started these before the curry.
Well, they say,
"Even if a baby is crying from hunger, don't remove the lid".
Ah, we should have brought mayonnaise.
You really need mayonnaise for curry.
M-Mayo-
Yukko, what do you like with curry?
Just kidding.
No... It's not like that...
T-This is... not what you think...
I still have- Look, I still have tokoroten!
TL note: Tokoroten are strips of gelidium jelly (agar).
T-Tokoroten... Just kidding.
What is your...
M-Mio-chan...
What is the colour of your blood?!
Sorry, Mai-chan!
We've lost the curry and rice we were having for lunch.
Mai-chan...
There's still tokoroten, if you want...
Mai-chan!
Release.
Well, then. There's one tokoroten here.
Only one?!
I think we should take turns eating it.
However, as we are to blame, Mai-chan, you should start.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Just make sure you don't eat all of it in one bite!
That's upsetting to me... I'm not a demon, you know.
I'll dig in first.
I choked.
That's right! Let's play cards!
Let's not!
If things continue this way,
this'll end as a disappointing camping trip!
Let's play cards at the very last moment and give it a happy ending!
That's right!
Oh, what's up?
I totally forgot!
Adults drink alcohol at times like these, right?
T-That's right.
Hey, Mai-chan, don't you agree?
Actually, I brought some!
T-That can't be, Mio-chan.
That's right.
A delinquent.
There's a delinquent here!
Tada!
Vinegar
A-Any bottle is fine!
Mio-chan stop it! You'll die!
We still have Mai-chan's left!
This is cider.
Sign: サイダー Cider
asa okite hao migai te
朝起きて 歯を磨いて
Woke up in the morning, brushed my teeth
attoiuma gogo juu ji
あっという間 午後10時
In the blink of an eye, it's 10pm
kyou mo takusan waratta naa
今日も たくさん 笑ったなぁ
Today, we laughed a whole lot
takusan tokimeita naa
たくさん ときめいたなぁ
We had a great time
tomodachi to baka mitai ni sawai deru toki ni mo
友達と バカみたいに騒いでる 時にも
At times, with my friends, acting like fools, being noisy
chirachiratte me ga au
チラチラって 目が合う
Fluttering, our eyes met.
guuzen dayo ne
…偶然、だよね。
It's a coincidence, right?
hatsukoi nante ie nai
初恋なんて言えない
I wouldn't call this my first love
kyara janai n da mon
キャラじゃないんだもんっ!
It's not my character.
nee ashita mo aeru yo ne
ねえ あしたも会えるよね?
Say, will we be able to meet again tomorrow?
mabuta o tojiru to
まぶたを 閉じると
As my eyelids close
kirakira kimi darake
キラキラ キミだらけ
I see you sparkling all over the place
kyou mo tanoshikatta ne
今日も 楽しかったね
Today was fun, too, wasn't it?
aa koi shite n da naa
あー 恋 してんだなぁ
I'm in love~
ureshii na ureshii na
うれしいな うれしいな
So happy, so happy
hajimemashite koi gokoro
はじめまして こいごころ
It is my pleasure to meet you, my new-found love.
ashita mata aeru ne
あした また あえるね
Surely, we'll meet again tomorrow~
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
Have a good night
yume de sugu aeru ne
ゆめで すぐ あえるね
We'll meet immediately in our dreams
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
So have a good night
Word Of The Day
MILK
Exit the bath, drink milk, act drunk.
I'm a peso!
I'm ten yen!
I'm wadoukaichin!
TL note: Wadoukaichin is Japan's first circulated coinage, minted in 708 CE.
No, no.
A person's value is not measured by money!
The next Nichijou is the seventh!
Narration:     Koyama Rikiya
Look forward to it!