Shinonome Institute
I'm hungry.
It's the kid.
Doing this kind of thing again...
Well, if the traps are of this level, I don't mind getting trapped.
At least it's food.
You got caught!
I literally got the stick.
Hey!
This was going to be the side dish for today's lunch.
We don't have one now.
Sakamoto.
You're the criminal, too.
No, Sakamoto said he wanted to eat it.
No, I did not!
Why do you start saying things like this?
Well, you did eat it.
Hey! Let's go eat ice cream from in front of the station!
Hm?
Hey, kid.
Don't you think she wants to go to school?
I don't want you to go!
What's with this, all of a sudden?
Nano is going to go somewhere...
Eh?
Who said that?
Sakamoto.
That's not what I meant!
Nano, are you going somewhere?
I am thinking of going shopping in the morning...
...since we don't have a side dish for our lunch any more.
Professor will come along with you, too!
I won't buy you anything.
I want to buy Chocolate Sharks!
I won't buy that.
Buy some!
Chocolate Sharks!
I said that I won't buy them.
Buy some! Buy some!
I won't buy them.
Sakamoto said to buy some!
I did not!
tatta ima hajimete kizuita
たった今 初めて気づいた
I just realised it for the first time
koi ni ochita no dana
恋に落ちたのだな～
That I had fallen in love~
nijyuuyo jikan kimi kimi kimi
24h キミ☆ キミ☆ キミ☆
Twenty-four hours a day thinking of you, you and nothing more than you!
ishiki sezaru o emasen
意識せざるをえません!
It's something I wasn't consciously aware of
nanka (nanka) itsumo to chigau
なんか (なんか) いつもと違う
Somehow (somehow) I'm feeling different from the usual
kimi to (futari) gikochinai kaiwa
キミと (二人) ぎこちない会話
With you (the two of us) and our dull chatter
masaka (ryouomoi) iya kataomoi
まさか (両思い) いや 片思い
Don't tell me (mutual love?) Nope, it's a one-sided crush
yabai shisen acchatta
やばい! 視線合っちゃった!
This is bad! Our gazes met!
nani nani kono doki doki
なになに?! このドキドキ?!
What, what? Why is my heart pounding like this?
shikoukairo guccha guccha konsen
思考回路 ぐっちゃぐっちゃ 混線・・・
Did a short circuit just make a mess out of my mind?
konna koto hajimete dayo
こんなこと 初めてだよ
This is my first time... feeling like this...
netsu demo aru no kana
熱でもあるのかな～
I wonder if I have a fever~
kyuutenchokka irasshatta koigokoro
急転直下 いらっしゃった 恋心
Suddenly and precipitately, love has arrived.
acchuuma kao hakka de makkakka
あっちゅうま 顔 発火で まっかっか
Instantly igniting my face into a bright red
ba ba baka na te ga furueruzo
バ・バ・バカな?! 手が震えるぞ
T-That's stupid?! My hands are shaking
kore ga zoku ni iu koi nano
これが 俗に言う 「恋」 なの?!
Is this really what they call "love"?
yayayacchatta kaiwa kami makuri
やややっちゃった 会話 噛みまくり
I-I did it! A conversation filled with stutters
kimazui chinmoku mamimumemo
気まずい沈黙 マミムメモ
This awkward silence... *mumble mumble*
kimi no (kimi no) kimochi shiritai yo
キミの (キミの) 気持ち 知りたいよ
Your... (Your...) I want to know your feelings.
kakakata kataomoi
カカカタ☆カタオモイ
O-One-sided love
hatsukoi itsumo no tsuugakuro
初恋! いつもの通学路
First love! The usual way to school
pika pika hikaru I do fall in love
ピカピカ光る I do fall in love!
The shining light. I do fall in love!
sora mo tobesou sa
空も飛べそうさ
I feel I could fly towards the sky
kakakata kataomoi
カカカタ☆カタオモイ
O-One-sided love
Mio-chan.
Good morning.
Whoa. What's wrong, Yukko?
You're all unsteady!
People have been telling me that since this morning.
The balance of your speech is having a Gestalt Breakdown!
Seems like you have a fever, too.
Why did you come to school in that state?
Well, you see...
I was thinking that I'd show you that
magic show I've been telling you about.
Nichijou 53
What are you talking about?
I haven't heard anything about that.
You're in no state to be talking about magic.
I even practised, so you'll be surprised when you see my magic!
I can't wait.
The truth is that I'm already surprised.
First of all, take your sea-
What!?
Yukko...
I can already...
...see what you're going to do!
I'll just pretend that I didn't see that.
She did come all this way in that state.
But Yukko was going bring out a big trick-
I-It already came out!
It already came out!
Ah.
It escaped!
Tissues...
All right.
Let's begin.
Okay.
Why am I hiding this?
Well, let's see...
First off...
I wonder how weakened she is that she didn't notice the dove and the wand.
I'll pass a cigarette through a one hundred-yen coin.
The hole is already open!
They're all Ace of Hearts!
Just now,
something came flying out of her mouth.
What kind of trick were you planning?
Yukko!
Yukko.
You should just sleep right now.
Shinonome Institute
Nichijou 54
Well, I'm off to the supermarket.
Professor shall come with you!
Since you weren't behaving, I wont buy you anything!
I feel bad for you, Sakamoto.
It's you!
Well, let's go.
What are you buying today, Nano?
More fish, I guess.
What should Professor get?
Professor can't buy anything today!
But they're not snacks, though...
You can't buy anything, even if they're not snacks.
Then I'm not too sure what I can buy.
You really do want to buy something.
Shark Castella
Nano, it's a shark castella!
It looks like there's a stand.
Since it looks delicious, shall we have some?
Geez.
Have you forgotten already?
I'm not buying anything for you today.
Eh?
But it's a gift for Sakamoto.
Sakamoto did some bad things, too, so no.
I was going to give it to Nano, actually.
I made a mistake.
If I say no, it's a no!
If I treat her here, she'll do the same thing again.
All right, Professor.
We're going.
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
I need to clear my mind.
But maybe...
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
But right now...
Or maybe...
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
No!
Maybe just a bit...
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
No way!
But...
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
No, no!
Maybe...
It's delicious!
So in the end, you bought it for her.
I'm sorry.
I lost.
This kid is really selfish,
always throwing tantrums for some reason or another.
I think I'll teach her a lesson.
Hey, kid.
Hurry up and learn about self-restraint.
I understand.
No, you don't!
The Shinonome household was at peace again today.
80 Point Mongolian
Whoa! You got eighty points! Amazing!
You can do it if you try!
What's the secret behind that good mark?
No, no, no. There really is no secret.
Come on!
Tell me your secret!
Stop!
Ow...
Tricks
Should I teach you the secret to getting eighty points?
You don't have to tell me.
Besides, I got ninety-six points.
Eighty points.
It's all about effort...
...and your heart.
Crude.
A Small Miracle
Aioi.
Uh...
Eh?
Yeah!
Reality
Dad, I've come to make food for you!
Mum's still on her trip, right?
Oh, thanks.
Hello!
Hello, Mii-chan.
Well, I'll play with my grandson all day today...
...and forget about the sad reality.
Mii-chan, what do you want to do today?
You see, you see!
Instead of that, where is your registered seal?
TL note: An official stamp that can be used in place of a signature. Someone else could forge legal documents in your name with it.
Eh?
Hey, hey!
Where is your seal?
Where are you hiding it?
Hey, hey!
Tell me!
Is it in this bookshelf?
Hey, hey!
Where is your seal?
This is worse than reality.
Hey, hey! Where is it?
Where? Where?
Come out right no-
You're slow!
What did you think the time to meet up was?
I'm sorry.
I meant to get on the bus...
I was on a wave known as time.
Let's just go to town like this!
Nichijou 55
Nano.
Ah!
Hey, Nano?
Nano?
What is it, Professor?
I kinda need to go pee a little bit.
Nano, come with me.
Hey, lets go.
Hey...
Lets go.
Hey, Nano.
Hey...
Professor, you're wrong...
Eh? What is?
Borscht is a type of food.
TL note: Borscht is a type of Eastern European soup.
That's not it.
I want to go pee.
Hey, Nano.
Nano!
Just go!
Did you possibly...
It's okay, only a little.
Anyway, just hurry up and go to the washroom.
I'll sleep.
Just go!
Sakamoto was being careful not to speak too loudly.
Geez.
It can't be helped.
This is why I hate kids.
I guess she can't go to the bathroom alone this late at night when a storm like this is raging...
...because she's just a kid.
For now,
I'll go with her and make her feel grateful to me again.
Hey, kid.
It can't be helped, so I'll go with you.
Sakamoto is small and looks weak, so it's fine.
Don't you think she wants to go to school?
Oh, Professor, you came over here?
Nano, come go pee with me.
Well, I don't really need to, but...
I'm just a tiny bit scared, so come with me.
Ah.
You should have just woken me up.
I tried to, a lot!
It's making a lot of noise.
Maybe someone's here.
It's probably the chimney banging around.
But it's raining really hard.
Nano, what's wrong?
Ah!
Hey, Nano?
Professor, Professor...
It's the thunder...
It's all right. The professor is here.
Let's just get this over with and go back to our futons.
It might be scary alone, but I think it's okay if we're together.
I guess that's true.
Nano, do you want to go to school?
Eh?
No, I'll stay at home forever.
But Sakamoto said that Nano wants to go to school!
I guess that's true.
Things you think are cool!
Eighty points!
Annoying.
Word Of The Day
A month goes by so quickly, yet Sundays always seem so far away.
Really Into It
Next stop is the eightieth one.
Eightieth stop.
The exit is to the right.
Annoying.
I'll sing you a song about 80s, since it's 80 points.
Eighty points, hooray!
Eighty points, hoo-
Fall in to Eden!
Eden
All right. Listen up!
I'll announce the average score for this test.
The average was ninety-two points.
Yukko.
Stop!
Just stop already.
Great Luck
Great
Luck
Hey, kid. What the heck are you doing so suddenly?!
What are you doing?
Stop playing around and help me fold up the laundry.
You can go to school starting tomorrow.
Eh?
Are you serious?
Yes.
What's with this, all of a sudden?
It's the Professor's wise decision.
Yay!
Now I can eat lots of snacks in the afternoon and not get in trouble.
But Professor, I won't be able to wear a backpack like this.
TL note: In Japan, backpacks are only worn by elementary school students.
You're going to high school.
But Professor, you'll have to take off this key, or else-
It's Nano's school uniform.
I love you so much, Professor!
Nano! Nano! Nano! Nano! Nano! Nano!
Professor! Professor! Professor! Professor! Professor! Professor!
Nano! Nano! Nano...
Professor! Professor! Professor...
asa okite hao migai te
朝起きて 歯を磨いて
Woke up in the morning, brushed my teeth
attoiuma gogo juu ji
あっという間 午後10時
In the blink of an eye, it's 10pm
kyou mo takusan waratta naa
今日も たくさん 笑ったなぁ
Today, we laughed a whole lot
takusan tokimeita naa
たくさん ときめいたなぁ
We had a great time
tomodachi to baka mitai ni sawai deru toki ni mo
友達と バカみたいに騒いでる 時にも
At times, with my friends, acting like fools, being noisy
chirachiratte me ga au
チラチラって 目が合う
Fluttering, our eyes met.
guuzen dayo ne
…偶然、だよね。
It's a coincidence, right?
hatsukoi nante ie nai
初恋なんて言えない
I wouldn't call this my first love
kyara janai n da mon
キャラじゃないんだもんっ!
It's not my character.
nee ashita mo aeru yo ne
ねえ あしたも会えるよね?
Say, will we be able to meet again tomorrow?
mabuta o tojiru to
まぶたを 閉じると
As my eyelids close
kirakira kimi darake
キラキラ キミだらけ
I see you sparkling all over the place
kyou mo tanoshikatta ne
今日も 楽しかったね
Today was fun, too, wasn't it?
aa koi shite n da naa
あー 恋 してんだなぁ
I'm in love~
ureshii na ureshii na
うれしいな うれしいな
So happy, so happy
hajimemashite koi gokoro
はじめまして こいごころ
It is my pleasure to meet you, my new-found love.
ashita mata aeru ne
あした また あえるね
Surely, we'll meet again tomorrow~
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
Have a good night
yume de sugu aeru ne
ゆめで すぐ あえるね
We'll meet immediately in our dreams
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
So have a good night
I'm the flags of the world.
You often hear it pronounced both
"bankokki" and "bankokuki" in Japanese,
but both are correct.
"Don't sweat the small stuff!"
Those were father's last words.
Narration:     Ogata Megumi
Next time on Nichijou: Episode 14.
Look forward to it!