En garde!
Strike!
Stop!
As you've all requested, we shall have you practice practical magic.
For that, we brought a special teacher from the National Magic Academy.
That's-
Onee-sama!
I am Eléonore de la Vallière.
It'll only be for a short while,
but let us all have an enjoyable training session.
Okay?
Is she your sister?
She seems like a kind person.
How so...?
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君のそばにいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai ga bokura wo tameshitatte
どんな未来が僕らを試したって
No matter how the future tests us
kitto…
きっと…
I’m sure…
aa futari no unmei
ああ 二人の運命
Ah, it’s our destiny
meguriaeta no wa
巡り合えたのは
I was able to meet you
kimi no koe kikoeta kara
君の声 聞こえたから
Because I heard your voice
sou pinchi na dekigoto
そう ピンチな出来事
Yeah, even if crisis events
oshiyosete kite mo
押し寄せてきても
Press on at me
kimi to ireba norikoerareru
君といれば乗り越えられる
If I'm with you, then I can overcome them
tokimeki to makenki to
ときめきと負けん気と
Palpitations and competitive spirit
urahara de haraharasuru kedo
裏腹でハラハラするけど
Excite me on the contrary, but-
Stay with me
tada kimi o mamoritai yo
ただ 君を守りたいよ
I only want to protect you
tooi sekai de umareta futari da kedo
遠い世界で生まれた二人だけど
We were born in distant worlds
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君の側にいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai mo kibou ni kaeyou
どんな未来も希望に変えよう
Let’s change any future into hope
Forever
The Spy's Seal
Like I said...
Queen Henrietta personally requested
my assistance and sent me to this school.
She did?
Apparently, someone told the Queen that Duke Vallière's family...
...tried to lock up their youngest outcast.
I wonder who was the one that said such a thing.
I really wonder who it was.
It wasn't me.
Huh?
The Princess came and personally asked me to help you.
In person!
I've been told that you're doing something under the Princess' secret orders.
What can you possibly be doing when you can't even use average magic?
Well...
Forget it. I bet it's nothing special, right?
Anyway, it's a great opportunity, so I will watch over you from today onwards.
So that strange things won't latch onto you.
Got it?
Hey, this is...
Louise.
Chii-neesama!
You're here, too?
Yes, as Eléonore-neesama's assistant.
She's got a weak body, so she'd be better off staying home.
"I want to be by Louise's side no matter what", she says.
I'm delighted!
It'll be reassuring to have you around.
You mean, "to have both of you around", right?
Both of us!
Yes, you're right.
Man...
Do all of the Duke's daughters really wear ones like these?
Oh, Saito-san.
Siesta!
No! This is...
L-Louise's sister told me to unpack her luggage.
I thought I spotted a lingerie burglar.
You're kidding, right...?
Please leave this kind of thing to me.
But...
Wow, they're so pretty!
I wish I could wear something like these, even if it's only once,
but they probably wouldn't suit me, right?
N-No, that's not true!
I'm sure you'd look fine in them.
Then,
may I try them on?
Yeah, yeah. Please go ahead.
If I were to wear ones like these,
I wouldn't be inferior to Miss Vallière.
What, you're changing here?
How long is Saito going to take?
L-Louise, y-you got it all wrong!
Siesta's only helping me organise the clothes.
Yes, I only wanted to please Saito-san.
W-What are you saying?
Saito-san, you don't have to play dumb.
I-I won't forgive you.
You swore to me...
You even kissed me...
Wait, you got it all wrong!
Shut up!
You...
...lying dog!
W-What was that?
Could it have been from the Principal's office?
All right, let's go take a look.
Hey!
Wait!
I told you to wait...
Colbert-sensei, what happened?
Oh... I just got here myself.
It appears that a ruffian broke into the Principal's office.
Don't worry, everybody.
It was only a minor incident.
Everybody, return to your rooms.
But, Old Osmond!
Did you not hear me?
I ordered you all to leave.
The Musketeer Force will investigate the cause of the explosion.
You're all dismissed.
Saito, come with me.
I'll have you give me a good explanation of what happened before.
Wait, Saito. We must talk.
What?
It's related to our mission. I want to borrow Saito's strength.
I'm sorry, but I'd like you to stand by in your room.
But...!
You stand by in your room, Louise.
Don't give me that!
Ow!
The ruffian broke in while I was gone and destroyed this safe.
However, my familiar was watching as the events unfolded, so it came to get me.
Right, Motsognir?
Who's there?!
They're huge!
She was very nimble, so she got away in no time.
What was inside the safe?
The Wind Ruby and the Water Ruby.
Queen Henrietta told me to hold onto them the other day.
She said that they were precious items to her, but were too much of a pain to keep them close by.
Fortunately, the ones stolen were imitations.
Imitations?
The real ones aren't kept here.
I forwarded them to my friend in Romalia.
Is it all right to give Her Highness' precious items to a foreigner?
It's safer than keeping them at the palace or at this academy.
There were no signs of anybody
escaping from or entering the campus.
In other words, the ruffian is...
...an insider.
Exactly.
Therefore, I'd like Chesaré-dono and Saito to help find the criminal.
I don't mind that, but what about Louise?
Why's she on standby?
The culprit used Earth magic.
In other words, all of the mages are suspects.
Louise, too.
That's ridiculous!
Louise can't use such advanced magic!
We are not suspecting Miss Vallière.
However, the two who arrived recently are a different story.
I hear that Duke Vallière is against the Queen's doctrine.
He might be trying to use the Wind Ruby and Water Ruby...
...as proof of a scandal, and employ that as an excuse to overthrow the Queen.
What?
Are you really suspecting Louise's sisters?
All mages are suspects.
We'll make a list of the ones who can use Earth magic and investigate thoroughly.
Chesaré-dono and I shall handle the females.
Michel and Saito, you two handle the teachers.
But... how do we check?
This seal is a magic item only I can use.
Once applied, even a Triangle Mage cannot erase its effects.
Saito.
The seal is pressed here on the ruffian's body.
Look for that.
Hey, how are we doing this?
Are we going to tell them to show us their chest?
I'll leave the Vallière sisters to you.
I'll handle the other teachers.
What? Aren't we working together?
Work with you?
Say that again after you improve your swordsmanship.
You'll only be dragging me down.
Stay out of my way.
She's so uncute.
I guess I'll sneak in.
Hello. Good evening.
You're asleep...
...right?
She's wearing some pretty cute pyjamas.
And now, excuse me for a second.
If I'm right, the seal was pressed right at the cleavage.
I don't see one at all.
Besides, I don't see any cleavage to begin with.
Wow. You are pretty bold.
No, this is nothing!
It's... right, a physical examination!
Since the flu's been spreading recently...
If you need to say anything, say it now.
No!
I need to check Cattleya, too.
Hey, be quiet.
Who is it?
Oh, um...
Saito!
Louise? You're still awake?
I-I've been searching for my familiar, since he hasn't returned yet,
and he's trying to sneak into Chii-neesama's room, of all people?!
You got it wrong, I was only trying to sneak a peek at her chest...
N-No, that's not what I meant.
I'm sorry, Chii-neesama.
I'll be sure to kill this dog.
Louise?
I'm pissed at myself for believing you at all.
You'd say "I love you" to anyone, wouldn't you?
To maids, to dogs, to cats, and even to goats, too!
You've got it all wrong, I said!
I was right to have bought a new whip.
Take your shirt off.
B-But...
Take it off!
Y-Yes!
What's wrong, Saito? Your body's covered in scars.
Ah, well...
Don't tell me...
You went to Eléonore-oneesama's...
No, no, no...
I wouldn't dare...
So, you did.
You did sneak into Eléonore-oneesama's room.
Don't tell me you can read people's minds with magic...
Listen.
Even without using magic, I could easily read your mind.
By the way, can you read my mind... right now?
Let's see...
"I'll forgive you, Saito"?
Nope.
"Saito, let's go to bed"?
You're thinking of... killing me?
Save me!
What was that?
Chii-neesama!
Louise.
I'm fine.
Let us through.
Excuse me.
It's a burn.
It's not really that bad.
Can anyone heal it?
I can.
Please.
Michel, send the onlookers away.
Y-Yes.
So, the ruffian appeared out of nowhere?
Yes, the animals made noises, so I asked who it was.
How did you get the burn on your chest?
She melted part of the candle stand and threw a silver liquid at me.
Alchemy... an Earth magic, right?
You are also able to use that type of magic, am I right?
Huh? Yes.
So, it could've been planned and enacted.
Huh? What's that supposed to mean?
The one who stood against the Principal had a seal pressed upon her chest.
We were searching for suspects in the academy with that as the hint.
Saito, what about her?
Well, I came to check, but I got caught by Louise.
In other words, Miss Cattleya figured that it'd only be a
matter of time until she's checked, so she faked the assault...
...to make us think that the ruffian is somebody else.
And also, to erase the seal by wounding herself.
That's how it is, isn't it?
I can't believe this!
You guys seriously think that Chii-neesama is the one who assaulted the Principal?!
Saito, don't tell me you do, too!
No, I'm only cooperating with Agnes' search.
Why would you keep it a secret from me, then?
You're my familiar, aren't you?
Search or whatever, it's strange for you to do it behind my back!
You were suspecting Chii-neesama, weren't you?
N-No, I wasn't.
Julio, did you check the other suspects?
I have checked all of the girls who can use Earth magic.
All?
How?
Every time either Agnes or I asked,
they all happily showed us their chest.
Would you like to hear the details?
No, I wouldn't.
Either way, Chii-neesama would never do such a thing.
Besides, why would she?
Captain.
I found these inside the hay.
That's...!
The Wind Ruby and Water Ruby imitations.
What's this about?
Captain!
Miss Cattleya, do you admit to the charge?
No.
We have the proof in our hand!
It must be some kind of a mistake.
Yes, it has to be!
Louise!
You stay out of this.
Onee-sama!
But Chii-neesama is...
This is the part of the candle stand that melted and then hardened, right?
It's either Cattleya's or the ruffian's hair.
The hair is not Cattleya's.
How can you be so sure?
Here, I have a potion made by my friend at the academy.
This hair shall now return to its owner.
This is stupid.
You dare try to force your sister's crime onto me with your foolish magic?
Captain, she's a part of this, too!
Let's arrest both of them!
All right.
However, I do not want them to think that we forced the charge on them.
I'm sorry, vice-captain.
Show your chest and prove to them that you don't have the seal.
You're kidding...
It's for the sake of the mission.
It's an order.
You're kidding...
I can't comply with such a humiliating order.
Michel. In case the ruffian was at the site,
the Principal told a lie in order to trick her.
These are not imitations.
They're genuine!
Why are you so surprised?
Because...
You used that lie to force the charge onto Miss Cattleya,
because you thought you failed despite the trouble you went through, right?
It was a foolish thing you tried.
Captain! I am not the ruffian!
I will... show you the proof!
Too slow!
Saito!
Step aside!
Michel! Stop the futile resistance!
Captain, were you suspecting me from the beginning?
I respected your hard work.
There was much mystery in your background,
but I trusted you as a swordswoman.
But if the culprit behind the incidents at the castle and today's case were the same individual,
I realised that it had to be someone close to me.
What?! You could've told me, then!
You need to use a real sword, right?
Don't get in my way.
I won't be a loser forever!
He did it!
Damn you!
That's far enough!
Looks like the case is closed.
Cattleya, I'm sure you can't sleep here, so come to my room.
Thank you, Onee-sama.
Louise, you should go to bed, too.
It's no time for a child to be awake.
Child?
Geez, Onee-sama...
I'm the one who was betrayed!
Ten years ago, my father was a Legal Affairs Committee counsellor.
He was accused of being the leader of the graft...
...and had his aristocratic title taken away.
He said he was betrayed by his country and then committed suicide.
Mother followed him afterwards.
I was left alone, without a place to call home, wandering about the country.
I understand that.
You understand?
My home town was razed, and I, too, was the sole survivor.
But I never held undue resentment against Her Highness!
What did she ever do for us?
Even if it means borrowing Albion's power,
unless we destroy the royal family, this country will remain rotten!
No!
The ones we must fight are the ones who monopolise this country's authority and deceive the Queen!
Spill it! Whose orders were you following?!
An old friend of my father's.
I can't say any more than that.
Friend?
Yes. He believed in my father's innocence,
and took me in when I was left alone.
Lishman, the Chair President of Legal Affairs.
That case ten years ago.
I don't have solid proof, but the true leader of the graft was probably Lishman.
What?
The one who cornered your father into death was Lishman.
You're lying!
Stop making things up!
I'm not lying.
I've searched everything concerning him.
Why?
Because Lishman is my foe!
It's already morning.
Let's go to bed already.
Saito.
Haven't you forgotten three important things?
Huh? Three?
How you were doing something with that maid.
How you were helping with Agnes'
search without telling me anything.
How you snuck into Eléonore-oneesama's bedroom.
How you even stepped into Chii-neesama's room.
That makes four, not three.
I'll give you extra punishment to compensate, then!
Mercy!
Y-You stupid dog!
chanto koko ni ite watashi no chikaku de
ちゃんとココにいて! 私の近くで
Be right here! close to me
zutto watashi o itsumo itsumo mitsumete nasai
ずっと私をいつもいつも見つめてなさい
Always, always look at me at all times
yosomishiteta desho hoka no onna no ko
よそ見してたでしょっ 他の女の子
You looked away, didn’t you? At other girls
o-shiokisuru wa furari furari furachi na yatsu wa
お仕置きするわ　フラリフラリ不埒なヤツは
I’ll punish those who are wavering and insolent
Don't touch! kikanai kara ne iiwake wa
Don't touch! 聞かないからね　言い訳は
Don’t touch! Because I won’t listen to excuses
Touch me... tsukareta kara nee kata o kashite yo
Touch me… 疲れたから… ねぇ肩を貸してよ
Touch me… because I'm tired… Hey, lend me your shoulder
suki yo nante uso yo
スキよ　なんて嘘よ
I love you, it’s a lie
kirai sore mo uso da wa
キライ　それも嘘だわ
I hate you, that’s a lie, too
nai nai nai dame yo kanchigai
ないないない　ダメよ勘違い
Nay nay nay, it’s useless, it’s a misunderstanding
dakara suki yo nante iwanai
だから「スキよ」なんて言わない
So I won’t say, “I love you”
Non non non dokka e ittara
Non non non　どっかへ行ったら
Non non non, because I absolutely won’t forgive you
zettai ni yurusanai kara ne
絶対に　許さないからね!
If you go to somewhere else
datte
だって
But
honto wa dare yori soba ni itai no
ホントは誰より傍にいたいの
The truth is, I want to be by your side more than anyone else
ai no kusari de sanposhimasho
愛の鎖で　散歩しましょ!
Let’s go take a walk in chains of love!
I... to be honest...
...might love you...
Next Time
You dog!
I'll behead you if you try to take advantage of
being alone with Her Highness and... k-kiss her!
Zero no Tsukaima. Futatsuki no Kishi.
The Queen's Holiday.
If you want to meet me again next week, then sit tightly and wait!
The Queen's Holiday