Hey, Sie-Sie!
Don't say you'll just be his second choice!
Yes, yes, that's right.
Smooch.
But Saito-san has Miss Vallière.
You don't lose to her charm at all.
With your breasts and all!
Oh yeah, I'll give this to you.
A love potion I confiscated from a customer.
He tried to use it on me of all people.
These things are illegal!
Apparently it lasts only for one day.
So don't worry, no one will find out about it.
More importantly, you shouldn't be so negative!
Even you're saying that, Uncle?
But...
You can't say it's fair against an
aristocrat unless you use a love potion!
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
mejirushi no nai michi mo heiki sa futari nara
メジルシのない道も平気さ　ふたりなら
Even on a road without signs, I'll be fine, if we're together
saki no mienai tabi mayoinagara mitsuketa yo
先の見えない旅　迷いながら見つけたよ
On a journey that I can't see ahead of, while I was lost, I found it
boku no iru basho kimi no tonari
僕の居る場所　君のとなり
That my place to be is next to you
kenkashite nando mo hanashita sono te
喧嘩して　何度も離したその手
When we quarrelled, I let go of your hand again and again
hikiyose dakitai ima
引き寄せ抱きたい　今
I want to pull close and hold it now
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
namida no ame ni utaretara
涙の雨に打たれたら
If I'm beaten down by the rain of tears
I wanna hold you sugu yobi na yo boku no namae
I wanna hold you　すぐ呼びなよ　僕の名前
I wanna hold you, call my name immediately
dakishime ni yuku wa
抱きしめに行くわ
I'll go embrace you
kanashimi mo tsuyogari mo kono te ni uketomeru
悲しみも強がりもこの手に　受け止める
I'll accept sadness and bluffing in my hands
The Taboo Magic Potion
What a charming glow.
If I use this...
I love you, Siesta!
I can't control myself anymore!
We mustn't, Master.
No, not that!
No! I can't control people's hearts with magic.
But...
Maybe if it's just for a while, I can enjoy a dream, can't I?
Miss Vallière, did you not go to class?
I was taking this water flea on probation for a little walk.
It hurts...
Oh my god, look at him.
You're being too harsh on Saito-san.
You dare intervene in a matter between a familiar and his master?
It's because I am Saito-san's personal maid.
A maid is obliged to be concerned
about her master's health.
Aren't you thinking much of yourself.
I think that if you can't trust your familiar, you don't love him enough.
If I were his master, I would take better care of him!
What? Are you saying I'm doing it wrong?
Yes, basically.
You've said it.
Do it if you can. I'll watch you.
May I really?
How about for one month, then?
Huh?
Is that too long?
So how about one week?
Hey, now...
Can't be helped, then. I'll settle for one day.
Gosh, make it one hour.
Feel what it's like to be his owner.
Take him wherever you want.
Thank you very much, Miss Vallière!
I'll start right away, then.
Let's go, Master.
Well, ah...
Hurry now, or else we'll run out of time.
Oh boy...
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Just a moment ago Louise was dragging him around, and now it's Siesta.
We were fortunate, in a way, to get our parole with just weeding.
I'm hungry! I'm thirsty!
My delicate body isn't made for manual labour like this!
I'm sorry.
Tiffania! You can't give them any leeway!
They're the Order of Pervert Knights who peeped at the girls' bath.
That was because my desire for ultimate beauty led me to the forbidden land.
You there! Stop talking and keep working!
Yes! Pardon me!
They called us, the noble Order of Undine Knights, the Order of Pervert Knights.
Ow!
Owie...
Are you all right?
Y-Yeah...
I'm... not really fine, but thanks anyway.
You're welcome.
So, um, what should we do next?
"What", as in...
We're short on time! We must make progress!
D-Don't mind me.
S-Saito-san, are you thirsty?
Not really.
Please don't hesitate. Since today, erm...
...we're playing newlyweds.
N-Newlyweds?!
Yes, since I want you to have some quality time.
So today...
...we're a newlywed couple!
Siesta...
So, what do newlyweds do?
Well... How should I put it...
What am I doing?
Maybe you were thirsty?
No, that's not what I meant.
Excuse me for a moment.
Jessica! And Uncle Scarron, too?
Siesta, is someone there?
N-No, there isn't.
What are you two doing here?
We came since we're worried about you.
So did you use it already?
Please, stop it!
I'm sorry for the commotion.
So, about what I was saying before...
Yes.
I'm the bride, and you're the husband.
So it's basically like playing house?
M-More or less.
So to start out...
Welcome home, Dear.
I'm... home...
What's wrong?
I wasn't breathing for a moment there.
S-She's so cute...
U-Um...
Would you like dinner?
Or maybe a bath?
Or...
Wait! No! Hold!
Food! I'll have dinner!
Why did I say that?
Where did that stupid maid and water flea disappear to?
We're finally alone, Siesta.
I'm happy, Saito-san.
Geez!
After this, we're going to the front gate.
Tiffania, keep an eye on them.
Beatrice and I go check the premises.
Okay.
Now, get working.
Don't try to dodge your task just because I'm not around.
We won't.
Wow, Jessica, you're so aggressive.
I can't do that.
But aren't you two newlyweds?
Then this is the most basic of basics.
But it's pushing it too much.
Tres bien! Maybe I'll put it into practice at our store!
You'll scare the customers away.
Then I guess I can't!
It's too much!
You don't have the time, right?!
Come on now. Your precious time is ticking away.
Are you doing it or are you not?
Fine, okay.
You made your point!
That's right, looking good.
Don't stare at me like that!
I'm starving...
S-Siesta?!
What in the world are you doing?
I never imagined I'd get to see the
legendary naked apron with my own eyes!
I don't care if I die from divine retribution right now!
Are you all right, Saito-san?
Please enjoy.
Enjoy what?
The food, of course.
Before that...
"Get any closer"...
..."and you're dead"?
What's the matter?
Oh, nothing.
Is this torture?
Or a trial?
Oh no, what am I doing?
Sorry, going to toilet.
Maybe the stimulation was too intense?
She should just use the love potion.
This is impossible.
I feel bad for Siesta, but I have to
apologise to her and return to my room.
Should I really return?
I might never get this kind of chance ever again.
What's holding you back, Siesta?
Hurry and put this in.
Then Saito-san will...
I love you, Siesta!
I can't control myself anymore!
We mustn't, Master.
Oh, so that's what your "good care" is?
Yes, so what?!
Things like this are first come, first served!
Whoever takes the step wins!
I win in bust size, too!
What is it about busts, anyway?
I'm sorry!
Gosh...
Ow.
What is this?
A love potion?!
Who did that?!
Sorry, Montmorency. Are you all right?
Thanks to you, I breathed in the potion.
Crap.
G-Go away.
Why?
Louise...
What? You're creeping me out.
Louise, you're amazingly cute.
You're making my heart throb.
Let go of me! I said you're creeping me out.
Your heartless words are so great.
Listen, you're a girl and so am I!
I don't care about that.
If you don't stay still, I'll rip your clothes off.
Tabitha! Help me! Please!
I'll help with scouting.
Other matters are not my concern.
Don't say that, help me!
No, don't touch there!
Seriously! You really can't touch there!
N-No...
Where did it go?
Jessica...
Isn't it Jessica?
It's been a while.
You remember me, right?
Look at how much you've grown since we last met.
Unforgivable! Absolutely unforgivable!
Don't tell me you...
Tell you what?
That love potion is starting a big mess.
This is... about that, right?
The thing I gave to Siesta, right?
I've got to do something before this gets any worse.
Hey you, maid!
Wow, you're cute.
Are you new here?
Let me touch your fine bosom.
I do it first!
No, me!
Hey, wait! Let go of me!
If we're done, I'm leaving.
Tabitha... When I take a good look at you, your small and thin body's really cute.
Let me see how small yours are.
I won't let you say no.
Air Hammer.
Does it taste good, Dear?
Y-Yeah...
It's kind of noisy outside.
Let's not worry about the outside.
Rather than that, please look at me.
I'll go check outside!
Saito-san!
Ouch.
What are you doing?
Do you know that I'm Princess Guldenhorf?
You're as tough as always.
But that's what I like about you.
Montmorency-neesama...
I'll do anything you say.
It spreads through kisses?
I've finally caught you.
S-Stop it, Louise!
This strange feeling...
Is this what love is?
Saito-san!
Shh! Something looks strange.
Um, how long should I keep an eye on them?
Hey, it's Tiffania.
What beautiful white skin...
Why did you come?
I shouldn't have?
Why are they so big?
You'll suffocate others with them.
I've got to punish you for that.
No fair! Don't take her all for yourself!
I want to touch them, too! I want to kiss her, too!
Please stop!
No!
What's wrong with you all?
Please don't look at me like that.
You're scaring me.
Wait!
Hold it!
We're not letting you get away!
Tiffa-chan!
Stop following me!
That's Scarron.
What a manly maid...
Wait!
You're so different from a skinny stuck-up I know.
I don't know who you are, but you flatter me.
Look at those muscles.
I wonder what it feels like to be hugged by those arms.
Louise! What are you doing?!
Long time no see, Saito-kun!
You're so my type!
What is this all of a sudden?
No, you can't!
Call me "Mi mademoiselle".
Hey, stop! I said you're making me...
...sick!
Ouch!
My crotch... My crotch...
My balls...
Rest in peace.
Saito-san, help me.
What's wrong, Tiffa?
Something's wrong with everyone.
They're coming after my breasts and hugging me.
I bet it's a magic that makes people lose their senses.
Please get out of here, Saito-san.
Magic?
Tiffa. So that's where you were.
You won't get away from us.
The quarrel between us started the moment we met.
Today, we'll end it using our bodies!
Using your bodies?!
You'll make love just like us.
Love is great.
What a sight.
What should I do?
I never imagined the effects of the
love potion would spread this much.
Now, Tiffa!
I didn't want to use it at a place like this, but...
But, if it's magic...
Nau cid yisa waysarel.
Hagaraz yul beog.
Need is algees.
Bel kana man lagoo!
What was I doing?
Who are you?
I think I was having a great dream.
Eek! Who are you?!
Crap!
We shouldn't be here! Let's go home!
Wait for me!
Tiffa, what was that magic you just used?
I'm sorry, Saito-san.
Everyone, I think the love potion I had caused this.
Love potion?
You mean this?
It's a real low quality one, but it was yours?
I'm sorry. I'm very sorry.
Forget it. I don't remember anything, and I don't want to.
You'd better not play a prank like this anymore.
Yes.
Magic for oblivion?
Yes. It's the only spell I can use.
It erases memories.
I've never heard of such magic before.
Nature magic?
Or...
I'm not sure.
Nice to meet you,
Chevalier de Norfatul, Tabitha-dono.
Why?
Why am I here and not in Gallia?
My master wants a dragon, of which only four exist in this world.
You know what I'm talking about, right?
Someone you're very familiar with.
Listen. This could be a chance for you to regain your mother's heart.
Succeed in your mission.
Sigh...
It's impossible.
But...
kyuu ni senaka wo mukete kakedashita wa (Just love me)
急に背中を向けて 駆け出したわ
I suddenly turned my back on you and ran away
hoka no ko ni yasashiku shiteta kara yo
ほかの子に優しくしてたからよ
Because you've been so gentle to many other girls
Boy onegai oikakete yo
Boyお願い 追いかけてよ
Boy, please chase after me
ato ni wa hikenai kara
あとには引けないから
Because it won't be over after this
pun pun pun
I am so sorry
gomen to ienakute gomen ne
ゴメンと言えなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't say "I'm sorry", sorry ♥
shinjite iru no ni kuchibiru ga togaru
信じているのに くちびるが尖る
Even though I believe you, my lips are pouting
kawaiku narenakute gomen ne
可愛くなれなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't be cute, sorry ♥
kosame no furu machi tsukamaete
小雨の降る街 つかまえて
Catch me in the town where a drizzle is falling
furimuku kara nakanaori no chu o shite
振り向くから 仲直りのCHU～をして
Because I'll turn around and give you a make-up kiss
atsui ryouude no naka de
熱い両腕の中で
In your warm arms
Next Time
Mirror, oh mirror, tell me! Who do I want to be the most?
I'm sure it'll be someone unlikely.
Zero no Tsukaima. Princess no Rondo.
The Sleipnir Ball.
The Sleipnir Ball
Saito, come find me quick!
I won't forgive you if you look away.