Red light...
Green light.
Red Light
Green Light
tatta ima hajimete kizuita
たった今 初めて気づいた
I just realised it for the first time
koi ni ochita no dana
恋に落ちたのだな～
That I had fallen in love~
nijyuuyo jikan kimi kimi kimi
24h キミ☆ キミ☆ キミ☆
Twenty-four hours a day thinking of you, you and nothing more than you!
ishiki sezaru o emasen
意識せざるをえません!
It's something I wasn't consciously aware of
nanka (nanka) itsumo to chigau
なんか (なんか) いつもと違う
Somehow (somehow) I'm feeling different from the usual
kimi to (futari) gikochinai kaiwa
キミと (二人) ぎこちない会話
With you (the two of us) and our dull chatter
masaka (ryouomoi) iya kataomoi
まさか (両思い) いや 片思い
Don't tell me (mutual love?) Nope, it's a one-sided crush
yabai shisen acchatta
やばい! 視線合っちゃった!
This is bad! Our gazes met!
nani nani kono doki doki
なになに?! このドキドキ?!
What, what? Why is my heart pounding like this?
shikoukairo guccha guccha konsen
思考回路 ぐっちゃぐっちゃ 混線・・・
Did a short circuit just make a mess out of my mind?
konna koto hajimete dayo
こんなこと 初めてだよ
This is my first time... feeling like this...
netsu demo aru no kana
熱でもあるのかな～
I wonder if I have a fever~
kyuutenchokka irasshatta koigokoro
急転直下 いらっしゃった 恋心
Suddenly and precipitately, love has arrived.
acchuuma kao hakka de makkakka
あっちゅうま 顔 発火で まっかっか
Instantly igniting my face into a bright red
ba ba baka na te ga furueruzo
バ・バ・バカな?! 手が震えるぞ
T-That's stupid?! My hands are shaking
kore ga zoku ni iu koi nano
これが 俗に言う 「恋」 なの?!
Is this really what they call "love"?
yayayacchatta kaiwa kami makuri
やややっちゃった 会話 噛みまくり
I-I did it! A conversation filled with stutters
kimazui chinmoku mamimumemo
気まずい沈黙 マミムメモ
This awkward silence... *mumble mumble*
kimi no (kimi no) kimochi shiritai yo
キミの (キミの) 気持ち 知りたいよ
Your... (Your...) I want to know your feelings.
kakakata kataomoi
カカカタ☆カタオモイ
O-One-sided love
hatsukoi itsumo no tsuugakuro
初恋! いつもの通学路
First love! The usual way to school
pika pika hikaru I do fall in love
ピカピカ光る I do fall in love!
The shining light. I do fall in love!
sora mo tobesou sa
空も飛べそうさ
I feel I could fly towards the sky
kakakata kataomoi
カカカタ☆カタオモイ
O-One-sided love
This is bad.
This is really bad!
Homeroom's already starting!
I was helping an old lady!
I already used that excuse last week.
"Mum wasn't around"... isn't a good reason.
What should I do?
I need an excuse!
At least one car should go by!
How did I get stuck at a red light four times?
First period already started a while ago-
Nichijou 40
That's such an obvious trap.
There's no way I'd fall for such an old tra-
At both sides?!
What?
Is this my punishment for being late?
What did I do wrong?
Even if I'm late.
Well, I can just sneak in through the back.
Yeah, there's no reason to get scolded.
It's...
...locked, after all!
I know!
I can sneak in through the lower door!
That's it. I'll creep in like I'm air and go into class like I'm invisible.
Why?!
Although, I already have an idea!
The only person that would do this kind of thing is the queen!
If I'm discovered sneaking in through the bottom,
I feel like I'll get in even more trouble.
If I'm gonna be discovered,
I might as well go in through the top window!
Stained glass has been put up!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Why am I running?
Nothing will be solved if I run away from the classroom.
I might as well go back.
Yes, the question is where it would be best to enter from.
If I'm going to get in trouble no matter what,
brazenly charging through the front is...
...cooler!
Yes, the best way is...
...the eraser at the front!
Appearing with a huge smile while getting hit by the eraser!
Good morning!
And the whole class breaks out in smiles!
What time do you think it is?
Man, you sure are helpless.
Hurry up and take your seat.
It'll work!
That's right, Yukko!
Be a bright, energetic clown!
Now!
Into battle!
Good morning so early in the morning!
Just kidding!
First Period is in the Language Lab.
Bubble
Oh ho ho. I'm an Invincible Alien!
Invincible Alien
What sort of stupid thing are you doing?
It's not like you're still an elementary schooler.
The Invincible Alien is unharmed by your verbal attacks!
Sorry about that!
Are you all right?
Blue Note
Shut up!
Miles must be spinning in his grave!
Oh, I'm sorry.
We just got a little carried away.
Were you listening, Sakamoto?
Of course I was listening!
Are you trying to torture me!?
My ears are going to fall off!
We're going to do it again, so can you listen to us?
Listen to what I have to say!
Nagashi soumen at Tokisada Park.
Around lunchtime.
I decided to go to the nagashi soumen at a nearby park.
I've only seen a nagashi soumen on TV before, so I'm really excited!
I wonder... If I don't stand near the top,
I won't be able to get any noodles.
I haven't eaten anything all day, so I'll sit at the front and eat a lot!
Slide
Nichijou 41
Here it comes!
What are you doing?!
This is the first time I've seen that!
Next one's coming.
Uh, excuse me...
What is it?!
Are you going to leave without even having a single bite?!
Even if the law allows that...
I won't!
But... um, I don't have chopsticks.
What an impudent child!
Here.
The next is coming right up!
All right.
Excuse me, but these chopsticks have been used...
It's eco.
Here's the next!
Time waits for no one!
No helping it... I'll just use them upside down.
A small bit of humour.
The next won't be like that!
I'll show you the true meaning of hell!
It's foolish to think there will be water forever!
Come take it by force!
Um...
You're a lady, aren't you?!
Why not try enjoying the raw flavour?!
Don't just stand around!
The war isn't going to wait!
You haven't changed at all.
Nagashi Soumen Researcher - Egi Masaharu (51)
Masaharu-san.
Masaharu-san!
I heard there was a nagashi soumen at the park, so I stopped by.
I've been doing nagashi soumen,
thinking that you would appear someday!
It's been 30 years since you left on a journey in search of the ultimate nagashi soumen.
Have you found it?
After eating every kind of soumen, I can no longer tell.
Using our savings to travel... That money has run out.
I'm sorry.
Let's wash away the nagashi soumen with water.
Yes!
What are you looking at?!
This isn't a show!
TL note: Some restaurants offer nagashi-soumen "flowing noodles".
I'm sorry, but could you make like nagashi soumen and flow away?
Word Of The Day
First years, are you all here?
Listen up.
There's the type that grows with praise and the type that grows with criticism.
I'll decide that with my instincts as a teacher.
Got that?
Even though I grow from praise, I don't get praised at all.
NASA
Launch when I say that!
What?!
Nano!
Look at this!
I thought I'd try tying it up.
Does it look cool?
Professor, you look a little bit like an older sister.
Nichijou 42
Hey, hey, just how much like an older sister do I look?
Um... You look pretty older sister-like.
Then what about you, Nano?
How much do you?
Well, I might not look very older sister-like.
What a mistake!
I see.
That might be true.
Then, there's no helping it, so I'll clean up.
Clean up, clean up.
Honestly, Nano.
I was still reading that.
Come on, Nano.
Honestly, there's no helping Sakamoto, either.
Hey, what are you doing?
You'll catch a cold.
What's with all this so suddenly?
What are you up to?
Honestly, Sakamoto.
What?
You'll catch a cold.
I won't!
And if you're gonna cover me, use a towel!
Why are you using a book?
Honestly, Sakamoto, you always try to contradict me.
I'm asking what you're doing!
I'm going to go do laundry.
I'll do it!
It's all right, Professor.
All that's left is to turn the dial.
There's no helping it.
Then, I'll turn it.
No, that's all right. All I have to do is turn it.
I told you I am going to turn it, so I am going to turn it!
Um...
Then, go ahead.
If you need help, call me.
Okay.
Oh, my.
You're helpless, Nano, so I'll do the cooking.
Well, I'm making it right now.
Mine will taste better.
Hey, come on.
Hey, hey, I'll do it.
That's dangerous!
Don't worry.
What am I not supposed to worry about?
Professor, wai-
Hot!
Hot! Hot! Hot!
Are you all right, Sakamoto-san?
What the heck are you guys doing?!
I'm sorry!
You're so helpless, Sakamoto, walking around there.
There's nothing helpless about that!
Stop messing around!
Come on, Sakamoto.
It's nothing to get mad at.
I don't understand what you're trying to imply!
Well, I guess I'll start over.
Oh, then I'll make it.
Well, the other dishes will get cold, so I have to do it quickly.
Honestly, Nano.
I'll do it.
Hey, Professor! That's dangerous!
The eggs will fall!
It's all right.
Hey, watch out!
You're so helpless.
No, you are!
Hey, Girl, what's up with the kid today?
I think she wants to act like an older sister.
Since I am an older sister.
Damn.
Hey, kid.
What?
Did you know that older sisters don't eat snacks?
Tada!
I was actually the Professor!
Liar.
No way!
River Fishing
Hey, this is pretty large.
Whoa!
It was a boot.
This time, I really got something!
What!?
It's a kettle!
In a way, isn't this better than fish?
If I knew these kinds of things were going to happen,
I would have brought someone along.
Oh, well.
Trendy things.
Eating sushi with your hands.
Crap!
I don't want to do my homework!
Nichijou 43
Why do we even have to do homework in the first place?
Well, since my marks aren't good, I have to do it.
But I'm equipped with enough skill to avoid failing marks,
so I won't be held back.
I think.
And after I graduate, I don't want to go to university to study more.
Should I work?
But I heard on TV that it's difficult to find employment.
Without a degree, it might be difficult.
High School
College.
Employment.
You can't get through without a university entrance exam.
But right now, I don't want to study!
Anyway, how will what I'm studying now help me in the future?!
Wait a minute.
What's my dream for the future?
My Dream for the Future, by Aioi Yukko.
My dream for the future is to be a frill-necked lizard.
Frill-necked.
I don't want to study!
I don't want to study, and I don't want to be a frill-necked lizard!
No, wait a minute.
If I become a frill-necked lizard, I might be released from this burden.
But I might as well become a living national treasure and be spoiled.
Some
Clay-like
Thing
Some
Clay-like
Thing
By the way, I wonder how much a living national treasure gets paid a month.
Payment
And how do you become a living national treasure in the first place?
And more importantly, what is a living national treasure?
No, no, no.
I should think more realistically.
What I want to be... want to be... want to be...
It's no good.
I can't come up with anything.
Well, I'm still a first year high schooler.
I have three years to think about it.
If I can't figure it out by then...
University!
Exams!
In other words...
I don't want to study!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Getting depressed about it won't help.
I should worry after I think of what I want to be!
I'll try thinking of something I'd like to do!
Something I'd like to do... like to do, huh?
Mum!
Your pounding is obnoxious!
What time do you think it is?!
Well, I don't really understand hard things.
For now, how about I do my homework?
asa okite hao migai te
朝起きて 歯を磨いて
Woke up in the morning, brushed my teeth
attoiuma gogo juu ji
あっという間 午後10時
In the blink of an eye, it's 10pm
kyou mo takusan waratta naa
今日も たくさん 笑ったなぁ
Today, we laughed a whole lot
takusan tokimeita naa
たくさん ときめいたなぁ
We had a great time
tomodachi to baka mitai ni sawai deru toki ni mo
友達と バカみたいに騒いでる 時にも
At times, with my friends, acting like fools, being noisy
chirachiratte me ga au
チラチラって 目が合う
Fluttering, our eyes met.
guuzen dayo ne
…偶然、だよね。
It's a coincidence, right?
hatsukoi nante ie nai
初恋なんて言えない
I wouldn't call this my first love
kyara janai n da mon
キャラじゃないんだもんっ!
It's not my character.
nee ashita mo aeru yo ne
ねえ あしたも会えるよね?
Say, will we be able to meet again tomorrow?
mabuta o tojiru to
まぶたを 閉じると
As my eyelids close
kirakira kimi darake
キラキラ キミだらけ
I see you sparkling all over the place
kyou mo tanoshikatta ne
今日も 楽しかったね
Today was fun, too, wasn't it?
aa koi shite n da naa
あー 恋 してんだなぁ
I'm in love~
ureshii na ureshii na
うれしいな うれしいな
So happy, so happy
hajimemashite koi gokoro
はじめまして こいごころ
It is my pleasure to meet you, my new-found love.
ashita mata aeru ne
あした また あえるね
Surely, we'll meet again tomorrow~
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
Have a good night
yume de sugu aeru ne
ゆめで すぐ あえるね
We'll meet immediately in our dreams
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
So have a good night
Crap!
I don't want to do my homework!
Yo! It's me, the origami frill-necked lizard!
It's really difficult to make me in origami!
To make me, you're going to need two pieces of paper!
Next time, Nichijou 11.
Narration:     Nozawa Masako
Be prepared for it!