Louise!
Your Highness.
I'm sorry for calling you all the way to Albion.
Saito-san, too.
Sorry to ask this of you upon your arrival, Miss Vallière,
but I would like you to wield your magic for the sake of your country.
This is where we are, the Lowscythe Military Port,
and this is our final destination, Albion's capital, Londinium.
Currently, the enemy's line of defence is located
between these two places, at the city of South Gotha.
We predict a large resistance against our invasion into this city.
Therefore, I would like you to eradicate the soldiers in the city of South Gotha with your Void magic,
like you did against the force that marched into Tristain.
If the battle were to break out within the city, civilians would get dragged into the war.
I would like to avoid that.
Understood.
I will do my best to meet your expectations.
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君のそばにいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai ga bokura wo tameshitatte
どんな未来が僕らを試したって
No matter how the future tests us
kitto…
きっと…
I’m sure…
aa futari no unmei
ああ 二人の運命
Ah, it’s our destiny
meguriaeta no wa
巡り合えたのは
I was able to meet you
kimi no koe kikoeta kara
君の声 聞こえたから
Because I heard your voice
sou pinchi na dekigoto
そう ピンチな出来事
Yeah, even if crisis events
oshiyosete kite mo
押し寄せてきても
Press on at me
kimi to ireba norikoerareru
君といれば乗り越えられる
If I'm with you, then I can overcome them
tokimeki to makenki to
ときめきと負けん気と
Palpitations and competitive spirit
urahara de haraharasuru kedo
裏腹でハラハラするけど
Excite me on the contrary, but-
Stay with me
tada kimi o mamoritai yo
ただ 君を守りたいよ
I only want to protect you
tooi sekai de umareta futari da kedo
遠い世界で生まれた二人だけど
We were born in distant worlds
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君の側にいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai mo kibou ni kaeyou
どんな未来も希望に変えよう
Let’s change any future into hope
Forever
The Enemy at the Snowy Mountain
We came all the way to Albion because Her Highness summoned us,
but, in the end, we're being used for war.
I've said this many times. I don't want to kill nor be killed, okay?
Seriously, "I will do my best to meet your expectations" my ass.
Shut your mouth!
All you need to do is fly this thing!
Hey, I can't if you do that!
Her Highness is seeking help from me.
From me, someone who's been ridiculed for
being unable to use magic since her childhood.
I can't possibly tell her I can't do it.
We're nearing the place we were told to go to.
Are you able to control your Void magic?
Yeah...
Leave it to me!
I see it!
Rol'n Suny, Feely, Jalunsa, Kusa...
Os, Sumy, Rodde,
Lyn, Rade, Beozzs...
Yul.
Louise?
Louise!
What's wrong?
I figured.
What did you figure?
Last time, she released all of the energy she had charged throughout her life during the critical moment.
It isn't magic that can be used freely to begin with.
You should've said that earlier!
Louise!
What happened to me?
Are you awake?
Turn around! I'll do it again!
Are you sure?
Turn around now. That's an order!
No, I don't think you should.
Why not?
They've spotted us!
Louise, you're in my way!
What do you mean I'm in your way?
Just stay down!
Saito!
You did it!
What's going on?
Damn it, they took out the engine!
What are we going to do?
Hang on tight!
What happened to Louise?
She has yet to return.
There do not appear to be changes in the enemy lines either.
The tactic of utilising Void seems to have failed.
It can't be...
It was a mistake to have depended on unreliable magic.
The only remaining choice is to charge into them head on.
Give us the order to march into the city of South Gotha!
Very well.
Proceed.
Yes, Ma'am.
Your Highness!
What about Louise and Saito?
Saito, you idiot.
You hesitated in shooting the enemy, didn't you?
Look at what happened because of that.
Of course I'd hesitate.
The enemies are human, too.
Colbert-sensei's letter told me to not get used to killing...
How should I apologise to Her Highness for this failure?
Our tactic failed because you couldn't use your magic.
What'd you say, you stupid dog?!
Stupid!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Yuck, you're so disgusting. Stay away from me.
If we don't stick together, we'll freeze to death.
Here. You're not a child, so blow your nose.
I could die at any moment for having to make a shelter in the snow.
F-Fine.
Maybe it'd be better if we both strip and use our body heat to warm each other up...
You perverted dog!
Saito...
Saito! Saito!
Wake up!
Saito!
Well, I bet Partner had a good life.
He was killed by none other than the girl he loves.
Stop saying strange things!
Saito...
Saito, don't die.
You said you loved me and all, but I never gave you a reply,
so you can't die on me like this.
Please don't die!
Man! That was a good sleep!
Louise, you okay?
Let's go.
Saito, how are you feeling?
Feeling?
Partner, you don't remember anything?
This aristocratic girl was naked all night-
If you say any more...
I'll kill you!
Okay.
Magistrate Sheffield.
Our enemy has sent its forces to the city of South Gotha.
We need to send reinforcements.
There's no need.
Tell the troops stationed there to retreat.
And while doing so, have them take as much of the city's food supply as possible.
The food supply?
Even if they occupy the city, being unable to
replenish their food supply would be a disadvantage.
We'll be able to stop them there for a while.
However, what will happen to the citizens?
I don't care what happens to them.
Begin the retreat.
Yes, Ma'am.
An iron dragon?
It seems to have crash-landed in the
mountains around the city of South Gotha.
It's probably the one that appeared when we marched into Tristain.
I see. That's interesting.
Find this iron dragon.
Make haste.
The retreat is in progress.
I don't mind the pilot dying.
This is...
...a dragon.
Saito!
You!
Is he unconscious?
It looks like his leg's been wounded.
Saito, carry him.
He'll freeze to death at this rate.
Hurry!
Hey, he's our enemy.
Yesterday, you bit my head off for hesitating to shoot.
If I were to forsake a wounded person,
my reputation as an aristocrat would be tarnished.
Yeah... aristocrat...
I'll protect my honour even at the cost of my life.
That's what aristocrats do!
Louise!
Give me Del!
Kill me.
Kill me!
I refuse.
Is it because I'm wounded,
or because you'd tarnish your name?
I... wouldn't call this a wound... if I were you.
I'm not an aristocrat!
I don't like the war nor killing people.
Right now, I only care about protecting Louise and making it home safely!
If we argue here, we'll both die.
If you must fight, do so after we get off the mountain.
Is this yours?
Give it back!
I picked it up for you.
Shouldn't you be saying words of gratitude?
Hey, you don't have to be so spiteful.
Spiteful?
Here.
What do you mean by spiteful?
Hey, are you trying to warn your master?
Since when did you become so almighty?
You're only a dog!
You dog!
You dog! You dog! You dog! You dog!
Louise! Stop it, stop it!
Hey, Saito.
Well...
What?
Need to go to the bathroom?
No!
I was wondering... how I should report our failure to Her Highness.
Simply tell her exactly what you just said.
"I failed."
I'm troubled over it because that won't cut it!
Her Highness... gave me this mission because she had faith in me.
I couldn't meet her expectations.
But what else can you do?
Or will you commit seppuku as atonement?
Seppuku?
It means cutting open your stomach. Your stomach.
Where I come from, that's what they used to do.
Are you telling me to die?
Hey, I was only joking around. Don't take it seriously...
But... it's more presentable than simply returning home.
Hey! Her Highness is at war with thousands of soldiers.
Your one success or failure won't make much difference.
Yeah, like you say, my duty might not be anything meaningful,
but I'm an aristocrat!
As a full-fledged mage, I have to be of use to Her Highness!
If I can't do that, then it's better to die!
Wonderful spirit.
I heard that the aristocrats from Tristain were wusses,
but I never imagined a girl like you
would have such an admirable attitude.
You're young, too.
You're probably about the same age as us, right?
My name's Louise.
Louise de La Vallière.
I'm Saito.
Hiraga Saito.
I'm the legendary sword, Delflinger.
Can't you at least tell us your name?
Henry.
Henry Stanford of the Albion Air Force.
Nice to meet you, Henry.
It should be around here.
Hurry!
Sir!
So that's not a dragon, but a new magic weapon?
Yeah.
It's a military secret, so I can't tell you any more than that.
I see.
So that's why it was faster than Winzar...
Winzar?
My dragon.
Thanks to you, it died in action.
It was your treasured partner, right?
Yeah, it was an important friend.
It was alive until this morning.
It was the only reason I didn't freeze to death.
I'm sorry.
Why apologise?
If you don't kill, you get killed.
I...
Even in the midst of war, I don't want to become a murderer.
What?
Regardless of whether or not it's for the sake of the country, I do not wish to die,
nor do I want to kill others.
You're a strange one.
You're the one who rode right into the middle of the enemy's base on the new weapon.
What do you fight for, then?
I don't know.
But if it's to protect the person I love...
I guess I can fight if that's the situation.
Protecting the person you love?
In other words, Louise?
Well, not only for Louise.
Like, everyone at the school.
Even the Princess of Tristain.
If she's in danger, I would want to protect her.
However, I would refuse to kill anyone for the sake of politics.
Don't let it bother you, Henry.
He's not an aristocrat, so he doesn't
understand the concept of pride and honour.
Yeah, I don't!
I don't even want to!
There's no point in dying or killing others for those things.
There's no point, you say?!
Honour is the most important thing for an aristocrat!
Right, Henry?
Yeah.
But...
"Fighting for your loved ones", eh?
I'd... like to say that one day.
It'd be nice to live solely for the sake of love.
But aristocrats wouldn't hesitate to break up with the one they love if it's for the sake of honour.
The person in your picture...
Did you... say goodbye to her?
You saw it?
W-What? Person in the picture?
Yeah.
I applied to the military after dissolving the engagement with my fiancée.
Why?
I managed to live through this time,
but if the war continues, I'll eventually die.
If I can't return alive, I have no choice but to break up.
That's...
You're the worst man alive.
What?!
I said that you're the worst man ever!
You dare mock an aristocrat?
So what if you're an aristocrat?!
Dying for the sake of honour is something an idiot does!
Why you...!
I won't take insults from you!
You bastard! Do you want to die that badly?!
Henry, you're a human before being an aristocrat, aren't you?
You're a man, aren't you?
Living through it no matter what and returning to her side... doesn't that thought cross your mind?
Stop acting cool by saying "die" all the time!
But...
When an aristocrat goes off to war, he must prepare for death.
You...
However, it's strange to have a death wish from the outset.
Death... comes at the very end, doesn't it?
Until that time comes, do your best at living!
Yeah! That's exactly it, Louise!
Henry, live and make it back home...
...and marry her!
Marriage...
Even if the engagement was dissolved, I'm sure she's still waiting.
Waiting for you to return.
A rabbit...
That was gunfire.
Enemy?
In search for me...
Or rather, they must be here to capture you two.
Henry?
Don't shoot. I'm on your side.
You are?
A dragon knight of the Albion Air Force.
I ended up in a fight with the enemy and dropped here.
Oh, they were alive?
And where is the enemy?
It seems they fell on the other side of the mountain.
Other side, huh?
That won't be easy.
All right, let's go!
We saved his life.
Paying back debts is what aristocrats do.
Louise! Saito!
That's...!
Is it the enemy's dragon?
Fire!
That idiot!
There they are.
Louise! Saito!
That way!
Sparkle!
Sorry for the delay.
Forget the sparkle and get moving!
What are you doing? Go after them!
Saito, Louise.
Let's meet again somewhere.
Until then, let us all live.
Thank you, Julio.
But why did you come?
Agnes asked me to search for you two.
After all, my mission is to help Her Highness.
Louise! Louise!
Saito-san, too.
I'm glad you two are safe.
Yes.
Your Highness...
I'm sorry I couldn't be of any help to you.
Louise?
The enemy has abandoned the city of South Gotha, and we were able to seize it without any trouble.
There is nothing for you to worry about.
No, I must atone for this.
Louise, you're not thinking-
Saito, you stay out of this!
Please, give me any mission regardless of its danger.
Louise...
To fight and to die for Your Highness is the greatest honour for us aristocrats.
Damn it.
You encouraged him to live, didn't you?
Is honour that important to you, Louise?
chanto koko ni ite watashi no chikaku de
ちゃんとココにいて! 私の近くで
Be right here! close to me
zutto watashi o itsumo itsumo mitsumete nasai
ずっと私をいつもいつも見つめてなさい
Always, always look at me at all times
yosomishiteta desho hoka no onna no ko
よそ見してたでしょっ 他の女の子
You looked away, didn’t you? At other girls
o-shiokisuru wa furari furari furachi na yatsu wa
お仕置きするわ　フラリフラリ不埒なヤツは
I’ll punish those who are wavering and insolent
Don't touch! kikanai kara ne iiwake wa
Don't touch! 聞かないからね　言い訳は
Don’t touch! Because I won’t listen to excuses
Touch me... tsukareta kara nee kata o kashite yo
Touch me… 疲れたから… ねぇ肩を貸してよ
Touch me… because I'm tired… Hey, lend me your shoulder
suki yo nante uso yo
スキよ　なんて嘘よ
I love you, it’s a lie
kirai sore mo uso da wa
キライ　それも嘘だわ
I hate you, that’s a lie, too
nai nai nai dame yo kanchigai
ないないない　ダメよ勘違い
Nay nay nay, it’s useless, it’s a misunderstanding
dakara suki yo nante iwanai
だから「スキよ」なんて言わない
So I won’t say, “I love you”
Non non non dokka e ittara
Non non non　どっかへ行ったら
Non non non, because I absolutely won’t forgive you
zettai ni yurusanai kara ne
絶対に　許さないからね!
If you go to somewhere else
datte
だって
But
honto wa dare yori soba ni itai no
ホントは誰より傍にいたいの
The truth is, I want to be by your side more than anyone else
ai no kusari de sanposhimasho
愛の鎖で　散歩しましょ!
Let’s go take a walk in chains of love!
Next Time
You dog!
Today's special.
I'll become a cat for you, meow.
Zero no Tsukaima. Futatsuki no Kishi.
The Silver Advent Festival.
If you want to meet me again next week, then sit tightly and wait!
The Silver Advent Festival