Three years earlier
Henrietta.
Wales-sama.
The Ruby of Wind, passed down through the Albion Kingdom, and...
...the Ruby of Water, passed down through the Tristain Kingdom.
Water and wind create a rainbow.
A rainbow between the two royal families.
Let there be a rainbow between us,
those who are in the midst of forbidden love.
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君のそばにいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai ga bokura wo tameshitatte
どんな未来が僕らを試したって
No matter how the future tests us
kitto…
きっと…
I’m sure…
aa futari no unmei
ああ 二人の運命
Ah, it’s our destiny
meguriaeta no wa
巡り合えたのは
I was able to meet you
kimi no koe kikoeta kara
君の声 聞こえたから
Because I heard your voice
sou pinchi na dekigoto
そう ピンチな出来事
Yeah, even if crisis events
oshiyosete kite mo
押し寄せてきても
Press on at me
kimi to ireba norikoerareru
君といれば乗り越えられる
If I'm with you, then I can overcome them
tokimeki to makenki to
ときめきと負けん気と
Palpitations and competitive spirit
urahara de haraharasuru kedo
裏腹でハラハラするけど
Excite me on the contrary, but-
Stay with me
tada kimi o mamoritai yo
ただ 君を守りたいよ
I only want to protect you
tooi sekai de umareta futari da kedo
遠い世界で生まれた二人だけど
We were born in distant worlds
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君の側にいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai mo kibou ni kaeyou
どんな未来も希望に変えよう
Let’s change any future into hope
Forever
The Oath of Wind and Water
Wales-sama.
The spirit that lives in Lagdorian Lake is also called the Spirit of Oath.
I have been told that an oath made here cannot be torn apart.
That is a fairy tale, Henrietta.
I believe it.
I, Henrietta of the Tristain Kingdom, hereby make an oath to the Spirit of Water.
I will love Prince Wales for all eternity.
Henrietta...
Well, will you please swear your love, too?
I, Prince Wales of the Albion Kingdom,
hereby make an oath to the Spirit of Water.
To walk along the side of this Lagdorian Lake while holding Princess Henrietta of Tristain's hand...
...under the bright sun without worrying the eyes of others.
Wales-sama...
You are no longer in this world...
I cannot believe that...
How could I live in a world where you don't exist?
A rainbow can only exist in the sky in the presence of both water and wind.
What is happening?
Henrietta.
W-Who is this?
You insolent man, coming to the Queen's room after dark.
It is me, Henrietta.
It is Wales.
Wales?
Open the window for me, my dear Henrietta.
Wales-sama?
That cannot be.
How?
You should be dead...
I am not dead, for I am alive before you.
The one who died was my double.
It cannot be...
Then I shall show you the proof that I am really me.
On that windy night...
The oath between the water...
Wales-sama...
You were alive...
You are alive.
I have come for you, Henrietta.
I want you to come with me.
Go with you?
To Albion!
You cannot go.
If you go to Albion now, they will definitely kill you.
Still, I must return.
It is my duty as a prince.
Please do not go.
Please stay in this kingdom with me.
I love you, Henrietta.
So, please come with me.
I love you.
What's the story behind this?
The Princess got kidnapped?
It is my fault.
So, where's the Princess?
My subordinates are currently on the chase.
The ruffian who kidnapped Her Highness is headed towards Lagdorian Lake.
Lagdorian Lake?
At any rate, we cannot publicise this event.
We must save Her Highness with only my Musketeer Force and you two.
You will cooperate, won't you?
Of course.
The crisis involved the Princess, so we can't overlook this.
Thank you for your assistance.
It's still under repair, do you hear?!
All I need it to do is fly!
Oh yeah, Colbert-sensei.
What about the thing I asked you before?
If you mean the acceleration unit that uses gunpowder, I had it installed.
This should let you take off even with a short runway.
However...
Geez, it's no time for chitchat!
The Princess is in danger!
We need to catch up with Agnes fast!
We'll head out now.
But...
We'll crash!
There they go.
Will they really be all right?
With all these parts left behind...
Geez, what's with the racket so early in the morning?
Emergency?
What? What?
What's the emergency?
So, Princess got kidnapped from the castle?
Speaking of that, she said that she
thought there was a spy in the castle.
Could it be that person?
I heard that, too.
The Ring of Andvari was also stolen.
What?
That was supposed to be returned to the Spirit of Water.
Yes...
But before doing that the castle was holding on to it temporarily.
If I remember correctly, Montmo said it's a magical item that gives the dead a false life, right?
What's the use for such a thing?
Obviously, it's for controlling the dead.
S-So, what for?
How would I know?
Rather than that, we need to catch up with them fast.
Hey, can't this go any faster?
It's not working very well...
What are you doing?
I-I don't know!
Princess...
I hope she's safe.
Who's there?
I am sorry to surprise you.
I thought that the Spirit of Water was...
...drawn up to the surface by the moonlight.
You flatter me...
You have become beautiful, Henrietta.
You are more beautiful than the Spirit of Water herself.
Wales-sama.
We are almost at the place of our first meeting.
Lagdorian Lake.
Lagdorian...
I have a ship hidden by the lakeside.
We will fly to the Albion using that.
Albion...
I love you, Henrietta.
I will not let anyone interfere with us.
Faster!
We must catch up and save Her Highness as soon as possible!
Yes, Sir!
Captain, I see Her Highness!
Spread out, Michel!
Aim at the horse!
Do not hit Her Highness!
Watch out, Captain!
Wales-sama...
How horrible...
That was my Musketeer Force.
I am sorry.
I did not want anyone to interfere with us.
What?
Trust me.
I will explain everything to you later.
You should just be quiet and follow me.
But...
All you have to do is act according to those words you said when you made the oath.
I, Henrietta of the Tristain Kingdom,
hereby make an oath to the Spirit of Water.
I will love Wales-sama for all eternity.
I love you, Henrietta.
Let us speak our oath by the lakeside again.
I, Prince Wales of Albion, will love Henrietta for all eternity.
Wales-sama...
Crap, this might crash.
What do you mean, crash?!
In other words...
This is what I mean.
You idiot!
Saito, you stupid, stupid idiot!
What are you going to do?
We need to save the Princess!
Ow, don't hit me!
I'll make it land somehow!
Idiot!
This is...
Tabitha!
Kirche!
Hi, Darling.
Your Kirche's here for you.
What did you two come here for?
Hey, I don't think we deserve that after saving you.
Thanks, you saved us.
Hey, this is a secret mission.
Don't follow us!
Hearing that makes me want to follow you even more.
Hey!
Below.
Princess!
That's...
Prince Wales?!
No way...
It can't be...
That Prince should be dead.
Could it be...
The Ring of Andvari?
Are you all right?
Yes.
Let us go. The ship is up ahead.
Okay.
Princess!
Are you all right?
Inescapable.
Excuse us.
Hold on, is that Queen Henrietta?
Return the Princess to us!
What a foolish thing to say.
Henrietta came with me under her own free will.
What?
Princess!
Wales, don't tell me that you...
were revived with the Ring of Andvari?
What did you say?
Ring of Andvari, eh?
I have heard of it.
It is a magic item that gives false lives to the dead, right?
If that were true... it would be a frightening thing.
Princess! Your Highness!
Please come to us!
He is not Wales-sama.
It is a phantom of the Prince!
Louise, do not speak such nonsense!
The one who died was Wales-sama's double!
This is Wales-sama himself!
Now, you shall let us through here.
Princess!
I don't really get it, but...
Conversation is futile.
Lavis fortal is hetha wind.
It is meaningless.
Your attacks cannot wound me.
Wales-sama.
How about this, then?
I said that it is meaningless!
Kirche, Tabitha!
Princess, you saw that, did you not?
He's a phantom with a false life!
No.
No!
That cannot be true.
He said that he would love me for all eternity!
You must not be fooled!
Louise.
Have you ever loved anyone from the bottom of your heart?
If you truly loved someone...
You would want to follow that person, even if you had to cast away everything you have.
So please, let me go, Louise!
No, Princess.
Please open your eyes!
This is an order from the Queen.
Louise Françoise.
This is...
...my last order to you.
Open the way!
Save the sleep talking for when you're in bed.
That... isn't love or anything.
Please move, Saito-san.
I have already made my decision.
I will follow Wales-sama.
Princess.
If you insist on going,
I shall stop you!
Don't come!
Saito!
I will not let you lay even a finger on Wales-sama.
Please.
Do not get in my way!
Princess...
Louise, I beg you, please move aside.
Yes.
That is for the best.
We only wish to pass on by.
Unite the Water Triangle and the Wind Triangle.
I can't stop all of this...
Yo, why not use the Book of Invocation?
Huh, Book of Invocation?
But, nothing's written in it.
"Dispel magic"?
That's the one. Undo the magic.
The privilege of the selected royal family, Hexagon Magic.
Nobody can stop us.
Louise.
Ful blisars ansul ken.
Louise, aren't you done yet?
It's rough here, you know?
It's your job to protect your master until the spell's done, Gandalfr.
My job?
Gyofu need nousis.
You're right.
I'm Zero's familiar.
Heilos iala.
Damn it...
Damn it!
Is this the best I can do?
Elpeo Y's!
Wales-sama.
Henrietta.
Do not cry.
Even though I was being controlled,
I want you to forgive me for what I have done.
And...
...promise me, Henrietta.
I will promise you anything.
What must I promise?
That you will forget me.
Promise me to forget me and love another man.
I want to hear those words from you.
By this Lagdorian Lake...
To the Spirit of Water.
I cannot possibly promise such a thing!
Please, Henrietta.
No, I cannot.
I cannot make a false promise!
I cannot!
I no longer have time left in me...
Then, please promise with me.
That you'll love me...
That you'll love me forever!
If you were Wales-sama...
The real Wales-sama would swear, and then the oath would be made!
I would like to, if I could,
but the deceased cannot promise an eternity, Henrietta.
Forgive me, Henrietta.
I could not say those words three years ago either.
Because our fate was never bound to be...
Wales-sama!
I am glad that I met you,
Henrietta.
I loved you.
Wales-sama.
Wales-sama!
Please open your eyes!
Wales-sama.
Wales-sama!
On that windy night.
The oath between the water...
chanto koko ni ite watashi no chikaku de
ちゃんとココにいて! 私の近くで
Be right here! close to me
zutto watashi o itsumo itsumo mitsumete nasai
ずっと私をいつもいつも見つめてなさい
Always, always look at me at all times
yosomishiteta desho hoka no onna no ko
よそ見してたでしょっ 他の女の子
You looked away, didn’t you? At other girls
o-shiokisuru wa furari furari furachi na yatsu wa
お仕置きするわ　フラリフラリ不埒なヤツは
I’ll punish those who are wavering and insolent
Don't touch! kikanai kara ne iiwake wa
Don't touch! 聞かないからね　言い訳は
Don’t touch! Because I won’t listen to excuses
Touch me... tsukareta kara nee kata o kashite yo
Touch me… 疲れたから… ねぇ肩を貸してよ
Touch me… because I'm tired… Hey, lend me your shoulder
suki yo nante uso yo
スキよ　なんて嘘よ
I love you, it’s a lie
kirai sore mo uso da wa
キライ　それも嘘だわ
I hate you, that’s a lie, too
nai nai nai dame yo kanchigai
ないないない　ダメよ勘違い
Nay nay nay, it’s useless, it’s a misunderstanding
dakara suki yo nante iwanai
だから「スキよ」なんて言わない
So I won’t say, “I love you”
Non non non dokka e ittara
Non non non　どっかへ行ったら
Non non non, because I absolutely won’t forgive you
zettai ni yurusanai kara ne
絶対に　許さないからね!
If you go to somewhere else
datte
だって
But
honto wa dare yori soba ni itai no
ホントは誰より傍にいたいの
The truth is, I want to be by your side more than anyone else
ai no kusari de sanposhimasho
愛の鎖で　散歩しましょ!
Let’s go take a walk in chains of love!
Next Time
You dog!
What do you think you're doing accepting a sword battle?
He's a flamen from Romalia,
and a real handsome man, too!
You'd never win with your face
Zero no Tsukaima. Futatsuki no Kishi.
Sword of the Holy Man.
Sword of the Holy Man
If you want to meet me again next week, then sit tightly and wait!