So the Silver Advent Festival is your New Year's festival.
We're in the middle of war.
Do the people in the city of South Goth not have any pride,
welcoming their enemy and all?
Not only did the Albion forces not protect their people, but they also ran away with the town's food supply, right?
The Tristain forces gave food to the people in their stead,
so it's only natural for them to be welcomed.
Why are you only capable of thinking like that?
Plebeians are plebeians, after all.
What's that supposed to mean?
Well yeah, I'm different from aristocrats.
I prefer festivals to war.
Fine, then go enjoy yourself!
I'll go see the Princess by myself!
Hey, wait!
I don't need a dog following me!
Louise!
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君のそばにいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai ga bokura wo tameshitatte
どんな未来が僕らを試したって
No matter how the future tests us
kitto…
きっと…
I’m sure…
aa futari no unmei
ああ 二人の運命
Ah, it’s our destiny
meguriaeta no wa
巡り合えたのは
I was able to meet you
kimi no koe kikoeta kara
君の声 聞こえたから
Because I heard your voice
sou pinchi na dekigoto
そう ピンチな出来事
Yeah, even if crisis events
oshiyosete kite mo
押し寄せてきても
Press on at me
kimi to ireba norikoerareru
君といれば乗り越えられる
If I'm with you, then I can overcome them
tokimeki to makenki to
ときめきと負けん気と
Palpitations and competitive spirit
urahara de haraharasuru kedo
裏腹でハラハラするけど
Excite me on the contrary, but-
Stay with me
tada kimi o mamoritai yo
ただ 君を守りたいよ
I only want to protect you
tooi sekai de umareta futari da kedo
遠い世界で生まれた二人だけど
We were born in distant worlds
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君の側にいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai mo kibou ni kaeyou
どんな未来も希望に変えよう
Let’s change any future into hope
Forever
The Silver Advent Festival
Louise, where's Saito-san?
Saito is...
I've given him a task, so I'll hear the mission in his stead.
I see.
There was something that I wanted to ask Saito-san, but...
The other day, we recovered Saito-san's vehicle from the mountain...
"Zero", was it?
Can it be operated right now?
U-Um...
If it's an order, we'll do something about it.
As you know, per Albion's proposal, we'll be in a truce during the Silver Advent Festival.
But you never know. They might attempt a surprise attack.
Therefore, we'd like you to fly to the
capital, Londinium, and spy on them.
Understood.
We will be the ones breaking the truce if we use a dragon from our Air Force.
On the other hand, you two can say that you're
students if you were to get caught by any chance.
The results from the last mission were pitiful,
but I'm sure you two can do fine if it's just scouting.
We will not fail you.
Please don't be rash.
Yes.
This is hard without Colbert-sensei.
Julio, I have a favour to ask of you.
You got it.
I didn't ask anything yet.
If it's a favour for my beautiful Louise, I'll fulfil it no matter what.
So?
I heard that you are a dragon knight in the Musketeer Force but haven't joined Tristain's military, right?
I haven't since I'm a flamen from Romalia.
What's he doing?
Ready?
Louise, what are you doing?!
Going on a date, of course.
Would you not bother us?
Date?!
It's a mission!
We're off on a secret mission by order of the Princess!
In that case, get on my Zero!
That can't fly right now.
W-Well, I can fix it in a rush.
Besides, you don't want to help out with the war effort, right?
I don't need a familiar who only complains!
Go wherever you want!
Goodbye!
Well, let's go.
Excuse us, Saito-kun.
Louise!
Are you okay with that?
With what?
Saito-kun.
He was hurt.
I don't care about him.
He won't understand me at all.
Damn her.
Damn her!
Damn Louise.
Why won't she understand me?
Saito... san?
Huh? Siesta?
Saito-san!
I never imagined I'd see you here!
I'm so happy!
Why are you here in Albion?
The school's closed for a while,
and I have an uncle who's starting a business here,
so I had him bring me with him.
Oh, your uncle.
Oh, no!
Saito-chan!
Don't tell me M-Master Scarron is your uncle...
T-That's him.
Who are you calling an uncle, huh?
I'm sorry, young lady.
And what's this? Saito and Siesta were friends?
Yes, well, we know each other from the Magic Academy...
What? Then the boy Siesta said she wanted to look for in Albion,
the great person whom she loves unrequitedly, but wants to get no matter what,
is Saito?!
Hey, hey, hey,
hey-hey-hey-hey-hey!
Hey!
Saito, you playboy!
Two-tim-ing Louise-chan?
A love triangle?!
No...
Come to think of it, Miss Vallière isn't with you?
She's...
Doesn't look like they're preparing to march out or anything.
Yeah...
Surrender, you say?
Do you guys intend to betray your country?
N-No, we're only saying that we should consider it a possibility.
If we focus on defence, we should be able to withstand them for a while.
However, we lack sufficient force to attack with.
It's no matter how much force we have.
I was able to get some results, but there is no
longer any merit in using this country further.
You asked me to take part in this
mission for Saito-kun's sake, didn't you?
For Saito's sake?
You can't force a pacifist to go to war
and put him in a dangerous situation, right?
I don't care about that dog.
You don't have to blush.
You want Saito-kun to be safe even if you were to die in war.
You care about him so much, but he just doesn't understand.
That's why you're angry.
I'm...
Oops, looks like chatting time is over.
Azuro.
Hey, what do you plan on doing?
You'll bite your tongue if you talk.
Breath!
End of mission.
Let's go back, shall we?
You didn't kill them.
How kind of you to worry about their well-being.
I wonder if it's Saito-kun's influence.
It's nothing like that!
Cheers!
But what a surprise that you are the boy that Siesta loves!
Well...
I feel bad for Louise, but I think I have to root for my cousin.
Cousin?
Oh, yeah.
They're alike, I guess.
Everyone in our family has big breasts.
See? Me, too.
Isn't that muscle?
Saito! Isn't that Saito?
Guiche!
Y-You're...
What is it?
Oh, this?
This is a White Spirit Medal.
It's not much, but I was distinguished on the battlefield.
General Poitier gave it to me in person.
Wow...
To an aristocrat, there is no greater honour!
I'm back.
Saito?
Gosh, even when your master's back and all...
Hey!
Woah, what?
Where's Saito?
Huh? Wasn't he with you?
I see. You acted coldly to him again, didn't you?
And then Partner went away with a bitter face.
I wasn't being cold to him.
So I was right.
I don't care about him!
He shouldn't talk back to me.
He should just follow the orders I give him.
Yes...
He says he loves you.
That's got nothing to do with it!
Oh, really?
Partner gave up on going home and joined the war to follow you.
Though he doesn't want to get involved in it.
Why do you think that is?
Because he's my familiar...
Because he loves you.
Have you ever responded to his feelings, even once?
While he devotes himself to you,
isn't whipping the only thing you do to him?
Oh, where's Louise?
She's not with you?
I don't care.
Oh, and I thought I'd show her the medal.
Why don't you go call her, then?
You know... Deep down, I'm really grateful to him.
But he's my familiar and a man.
Without my having to tell him so every time,
he should understand how I feel.
You're asking for the impossible.
He seems to be lacking in relationship experience.
And if the war continues, and if I were to die in it, he would never understand.
That's why. Instead of keeping it inside, why don't you tell him exactly how you feel?
And make a solid bond with him while you're alive.
Bond?
How do I do that?
This is what you say.
"I love you! I love you, Saito!"
"Please! Marry me!"
M-Marry?!
"Make me your bride, make love to me!"
"Pamper me!"
You're scary.
You think an aristocrat could say "l-love" and "m-marry me" and "m-make love to me"...
...to a familiar?!
That is the problem.
Partner says that in the world he comes from, there are no plebeians nor aristocrats.
That's why he doesn't understand your standpoint.
I know! Why don't you two swap positions for a day?
Swap positions?
You'll become Saito's familiar.
What?!
Yup, that's a great idea.
You will be able to come to a good understanding if you do.
Understanding?
A-ha. It's that room, isn't it?
Will Saito really be happy with this outfit?
Definitely!
Partner's simple-minded, so he'll be emotionally touched to know how much you love him.
Hey, he's back.
You're... y-you're my master tonight! Meow, meow!
What are you doing?
Ah, Louise, you were adorable.
Yup, yup, really.
If you're on the floor in that outfit, you'll get lots of customers.
I won't lose!
Siesta?
Geez... I wondered what you were doing while I was gone.
To tell you the truth, Partner,
she was...
S-So you know, it wasn't for you, okay?!
Then who was it for?
U-Um...
J-Julio!
Stupid Delflinger said that if I wear the cat outfit and say,
"You're my master for the night, meow",
I could make Julio fall for me.
Right?
Well...
Right?!
Yes!
Are you serious about that?
Of course I'm serious!
He's superior to you in looks, brains and swordsmanship.
His dragon-controlling ability was godly.
Compared to him, you're a pinworm to his lion,
fly to his phoenix,
water flea to his swan!
I get it!
Then enjoy your time with Julio!
Hey, looks like everyone's here.
Julio...
I-I'm going back!
Hold.
What's wrong?
No, let me go!
Saito-kun, did something happen?
Like I'd know!
Saito-pyon!
S-Siesta?
Hey, who's cuter, Miss Vallière or me?
Who is it?
W-Who, you ask...
What is this outfit?! Trying to mock me?!
A maid dares to make fun of me?!
No, I only want Saito-san to be happy.
Ah, stop it, both of you.
Keep it up, Siesta!
Damn this!
Magistrate Sheffield, can we really use
the secret measure for repelling the enemy here?
A third of South Gotha's water supply comes from here.
That is...!
The ring of Andvari.
It controls both the living and the dead.
I must have the war continue.
Who exactly are you?
General. Do the rest as we planned.
I leave Albion in your hands.
Magistrate!
Fairy, you say?!
Does that mean a cute girl like me?
No! A real fairy!
Yeah, a fairy...
I really saw one!
It happened when we encountered an
enemy while marching from Lowscythe.
When I noticed, I was surrounded by enemies in the mountain.
I was killed.
I was surely inflicted a fatal wound.
However...
When I woke up again,
my body didn't have a single scar.
Thank you, fairy-san!
Maybe you had a dream.
Humans are likely to see strange dreams when they're faced with death.
It wasn't a dream!
Either way, I'm glad you're alive.
It's frightening to die in war, in an unknown land.
No, no, I'm an aristocrat.
I'm not afraid of dying.
I can die any time I'm asked to for the sake of honour.
But if possible, I'd like to be more recognised, so I can die with another medal on me.
Are you an idiot?!
W-What did you call me?
I don't get it, but you came back after nearly dying, right?
Then cherish that life!
Dying for the sake of honour? That's garbage!
Saito! Apologise to Guiche!
Why?
Honour is more important than life to aristocrats!
How many times do I have to tell you until you understand that?
You, too! Why won't you understand me?!
Everything ends when you die no matter how many medals you get!
I don't need medals.
What's important is loyalty to the Princess.
I don't need anyone to recognise me.
I only need the Princess to understand me.
That is my honour.
I would gladly give my life if it's for her!
Suit yourself, then!
Saito-san...
Listen, Partner.
About the cat outfit...
It wasn't for Julio, but...
I don't care about Julio!
What?
I get it now.
My true rival for Louise is... the Princess!
Saito-san!
Please wait!
Siesta?
A-Are you angry at me?
I'm troubling you, following you all the way to Albion, right?
No, not at all...
I'm cold.
I'm freezing.
Are you all right?
Man, I drank too much.
Henrietta's men are your enemies.
Kill your enemies.
Kill your enemies!
So, do you feel warmer?
I'm hot.
I told a lie.
I wasn't cold at all to begin with.
It's just that... I wanted to feel your warmth.
Siesta...
I love you!
Stupid Saito.
When will he understand me?
I want a stronger bond, not just one between master and familiar.
What was that?
Your Highness, there's a revolt!
Some of our own men are assaulting our soldiers!
What ridiculous things are you saying?
Watch out!
General Poitier!
Something strange is happening outside.
Saito-san...
You'll return to Miss Vallière's side, won't you?
W-Well...
Please take this with you, then.
It's a sleeping potion.
If Miss Vallière tries to make you do something dangerous,
make her take this, and run away while she's asleep.
Siesta...
It may be natural for aristocrats to die for the Princess,
but I can't stand having you get caught up in it!
What? What's going on?
Saito!
Where's Saito?
chanto koko ni ite watashi no chikaku de
ちゃんとココにいて! 私の近くで
Be right here! close to me
zutto watashi o itsumo itsumo mitsumete nasai
ずっと私をいつもいつも見つめてなさい
Always, always look at me at all times
yosomishiteta desho hoka no onna no ko
よそ見してたでしょっ 他の女の子
You looked away, didn’t you? At other girls
o-shiokisuru wa furari furari furachi na yatsu wa
お仕置きするわ　フラリフラリ不埒なヤツは
I’ll punish those who are wavering and insolent
Don't touch! kikanai kara ne iiwake wa
Don't touch! 聞かないからね　言い訳は
Don’t touch! Because I won’t listen to excuses
Touch me... tsukareta kara nee kata o kashite yo
Touch me… 疲れたから… ねぇ肩を貸してよ
Touch me… because I'm tired… Hey, lend me your shoulder
suki yo nante uso yo
スキよ　なんて嘘よ
I love you, it’s a lie
kirai sore mo uso da wa
キライ　それも嘘だわ
I hate you, that’s a lie, too
nai nai nai dame yo kanchigai
ないないない　ダメよ勘違い
Nay nay nay, it’s useless, it’s a misunderstanding
dakara suki yo nante iwanai
だから「スキよ」なんて言わない
So I won’t say, “I love you”
Non non non dokka e ittara
Non non non　どっかへ行ったら
Non non non, because I absolutely won’t forgive you
zettai ni yurusanai kara ne
絶対に　許さないからね!
If you go to somewhere else
datte
だって
But
honto wa dare yori soba ni itai no
ホントは誰より傍にいたいの
The truth is, I want to be by your side more than anyone else
ai no kusari de sanposhimasho
愛の鎖で　散歩しましょ!
Let’s go take a walk in chains of love!
Next Time
You dog!
This is goodbye,
so... I'll marry you!
Zero no Tsukaima. Futatsuki no Kishi.
The Farewell Wedding Ceremony.
If you want to meet me again next week, then sit tightly and wait!
The Farewell Wedding Ceremony