It is time to depart.
Okay.
Do not worry. I will protect you during the journey.
Come on, let's go.
Thank you.
Are you all right? Do you have motion sickness?
No, it's just...
I...
This is the first time I'm venturing far away from home.
So I'm a bit anxious.
I see.
We'll travel much farther. Will you be okay?
To the Kingdom of Tristain, right?
Yes.
What about your family?
Were you living alone in that lonely place?
My mother...
...has passed away.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
It's okay.
I'm sure this is the work of fate, too.
I wanted to see the vast world.
Fate?
Speaking of which, the other Void wielder...
Don't tell me...
Rejected! Completely and utterly rejected!
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
mejirushi no nai michi mo heiki sa futari nara
メジルシのない道も平気さ　ふたりなら
Even on a road without signs, I'll be fine, if we're together
saki no mienai tabi mayoinagara mitsuketa yo
先の見えない旅　迷いながら見つけたよ
On a journey that I can't see ahead of, while I was lost, I found it
boku no iru basho kimi no tonari
僕の居る場所　君のとなり
That my place to be is next to you
kenkashite nando mo hanashita sono te
喧嘩して　何度も離したその手
When we quarrelled, I let go of your hand again and again
hikiyose dakitai ima
引き寄せ抱きたい　今
I want to pull close and hold it now
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
namida no ame ni utaretara
涙の雨に打たれたら
If I'm beaten down by the rain of tears
I wanna hold you sugu yobi na yo boku no namae
I wanna hold you　すぐ呼びなよ　僕の名前
I wanna hold you, call my name immediately
dakishime ni yuku wa
抱きしめに行くわ
I'll go embrace you
kanashimi mo tsuyogari mo kono te ni uketomeru
悲しみも強がりもこの手に　受け止める
I'll accept sadness and bluffing in my hands
Return of the Hero
Several days later
Wow!
Oh, this is your first time here, right?
This is where Henrietta...
I mean, the Queen lives.
I see.
Reporting back, Ma'am!
I am glad you have returned safely.
I have been worried.
Princess...
Your words are too kind for me.
I'm delighted that you are well too, Saito-san.
The mark of Gandalfr...
So you have returned to being Louise's familiar.
Well, a lot happened...
Yes. It's pretty inconvenient when you don't have a familiar.
You don't have to say that!
Saito-san, will you accept the title of chevalier this time?
More importantly, Princess,
this is Tiffania, who we have been looking for.
Come on, present yourself.
O-Okay.
My name is Tiffania.
I am honoured to meet you.
Welcome to my country, Tristain.
You must be weary from your long journey.
I cannot see your face clearly.
The hat?
It's rude to wear one in front of Her Majesty.
T-There's a reason for it...
What reason?
It's been bothering me all the time...
Do you have something on your head or what?
I do not mind.
I-I'm sorry, I am...
An elf?
An elf!
So you were an elf!
U-Um... I wasn't planning to hide it...
It's scary, isn't it?
You are disgusted by an elf, aren't you?
It appears you have your own story to tell.
Would you mind telling us?
Okay.
I am... actually... a half-elf.
My deceased mother was an elf and the mistress of the Archduke of Albion.
The reason I lived secretly without being seen by anyone is because of my mother.
The Archduke of Albion?
I will not hate you for being an elf, Tiffania.
You saved Saito-san's life.
Please be at peace.
Here in Tristain, I shall be your support.
Your Majesty, thank you so much!
I don't know how I can show my gratitude.
You do not have to be so formal.
Now, shall we have some tea over there?
Good work, Agnes.
Did anything occur during the journey?
I did not wish to make you worry unnecessarily, so I did not report it,
but there was some trouble again.
What happened?
I'll tell her.
Actually, the woman from before...
The one called Sheffield who attacked you before?
Yes.
She threatened me and asked about
the whereabouts of a second Void wielder.
A second one?
We believe the enemy knows something we don't.
That woman, Sheffield, is quite skilled.
It's too dangerous to just ignore her.
If she's that skilled, her name must be known.
It could also become a rumour among the royalty.
Agnes, be cautious from now on.
I shall also look into this.
Please tread carefully.
Thank you, Agnes.
By the way, Saito-san.
Yes?
You will accept the title of chevalier, will you not?
Yes!
Myoz...
Myozunitonirun, I want to see your face.
Yet another wielder, huh?
The pawns have begun to gather.
Did I make you wait?
No, I do not dislike waiting.
The incompetent king has no choice but to wait.
Such a joke...
I am terribly sorry.
I was unable to find the other wielder.
Do not rush it.
We will find them soon.
I'll leave it to you.
Such kind words...
Stand up, Myozunitonirun.
Yes, sir.
Now it is time for me to play a little game.
I must attend a conference.
Tristain, Gallia and Germania will try to acquire Albion.
Oh well.
I'll show to that avaricious bunch.
After all, I'm incompetent, so I shall just sleep and pass time.
Please summon me any time you need something.
I shall do my best to serve you.
Very well.
I've grown tired of Albion already.
You are certain that Sheffield said there is another wielder, right?
Yes. But I have no clue who she was talking about.
If it's as you said, there must be other wielders of the Void.
Tiffania, do you have any ideas?
Tiffania?
Y-Yes?
I don't know.
I don't really know much about the world...
What were you looking at?
A ring?
It has no stone set in it.
It's a memento from my mother.
When I saved Saito-san, the stone dissolved and vanished.
Awaken.
The power enshrined in this ring shall bring the lost life back to this world.
So huge!
Tiffania, I have no memory of what happened after I was surrounded by the enemy.
Why was I in the forest?
I shall tell you.
Saito, at that time your heart had stopped beating...
Oh no! I'll get embarrassed if you all listen so closely.
It wasn't really that big a deal.
Louise!
I transported my unconscious partner to Westwood.
I see.
I had no idea.
Well, yeah.
More importantly, thank the half-elf girl.
She was the one who used that magic ring without any regrets.
Is that so?
So you are pretty special,
having such a ring...
N-No, I just did the natural thing.
My deceased mother used to say that one should help people in need.
That's why...
Only nature magic can bring the dead back to life.
That power is a part of elf magic, isn't it?
Yes.
The fact that the blood of elves flows in your veins means you can use magic, right?
Something similar to Void magic...
We won't put up any resistance.
We elves do not desire conflict.
I can't.
It's very important.
I'm sorry.
Please let me rest a little.
Tiffania!
Wait, partner.
She's gone through a lot, too.
Leaving her alone is the best you can do at a time like this.
Wealth is such a futile thing in this world.
Extravagant banquets...
Gardens that please the eyes...
Music that pleases the ears...
They are all unnecessary in this world.
The music box of the Primogenitor.
The other Void wielder must have heard your melody.
Just like this.
kamino hidari te Gandalfr
Gandalfr, God's left hand...
神の左手ガンダールヴ
yuumou kakanna kamino tate
The valiant shield of God.
勇猛果敢な神の匿
kamino migi te ga Windalfr
Windalfr, God's right hand...
神の右手がヴィンダールヴ
kokoro yasashiki kamino fue
O God's gentle flute.
心優しき神の笛
That's a strange song.
Sorry, did I wake you up?
It's okay. I couldn't sleep anyway.
Can I sit next to you?
Sure.
Say, Tiffania.
It's hard to pronounce, isn't it?
Just call me Tiffa.
I see.
It's strange.
The moon I saw from the forest is the
same as the one I see from this balcony.
Tiffa, um...
Did I drag you into something troublesome?
I've been alone since I started living in that little house in the forest four years ago.
I thought that I'd live alone like that forever.
Do you regret this?
Um... It was as if we forcefully dragged you out of there...
And I feel bad about that.
Sorry, Tiffa.
It's not your fault.
Besides, I wanted to see the world.
Really?
Yes.
I want to walk freely on this vast world.
I want to meet many people.
But I'm scared.
I don't know anything.
The truth is, I can use magic.
I found that out when my mother passed away
and I was about to be taken away by the military.
That's why even remembering it is painful for me.
Is that so?
I have the magic power I inherited from my mother...
But I don't know if it's something good or bad.
I don't know that either, but it can't be something bad.
There must be some reason that you were
born a half-elf and possess magical powers.
Just like how I came here from a distant world.
Another world?
Yes.
That's why I can understand how you feel.
Ask me if you need help.
You're the one who saved my life, after all.
Thank you, Saito-san. I'm glad to be friends with you.
T-Tiffa.
S-Saito!
A-Ah... er... sorry! Good night!
Does he hate me now?
Lower your head.
I, the Queen of Tristain, Henrietta,
bestow the title of knight upon you.
Do you pledge loyalty?
I do.
In the name of the Primogenitor, Brimir,
I name you chevalier.
You are now my knight.
Saito Chevalier de Hiraga-dono,
please support me.
Yes!
Do it.
Master, please excuse me.
Master?
W-Wait! Why is Saito your master now?
This is an order from Her Majesty the Queen.
N-No way!
Your Majesty!
Oh, I thought Siesta-san was appropriate for the position since they get along well.
T-That's okay, but...
No, thank you for being so considerate.
I'm very grateful as well!
With this, the formal ceremony is over.
I shall prepare dragons to transport you to the academy.
I must prepare for the conference...
Tiffania will stay here in the meantime.
She is my cousin, after all.
Cousin?
Cousin, you said?!
Right, Tiffania?
Yes...
I just found out.
I still can't believe it.
Her father is my uncle.
As the Archduke of Albion, he governs South Gotha.
The fact that we crossed paths must surely be because of Primogenitor Brimir's guidance.
But Tiffa...
Won't you be lonely in such a big place?
Why don't you come with us to the academy?
No thanks. Her Majesty offered that, too, but...
I declined her offer.
Why?
I'm a half-elf.
I still don't have the resolve to walk among the crowd of strangers.
Actually, I want to be with you, Saito-san...
But I'd definitely be a burden to you.
Don't worry about that, Tiffa.
I'll protect you with everything I've got!
Saito, you sure seem to care about her a lot.
I hope you remember that you're my familiar.
But protecting fragile maidens is the job of a knight.
A chevalier's duty is to assist Her Majesty the Queen.
Please don't fight because of me.
If he can really protect me, then I'll come to the acade-
No, you don't have to come.
Saito, we're going back to the academy.
Tiffa, cheer up!
Come to the academy as soon as you can.
We'll be waiting for you.
Please come soon.
Saito-san, Siesta-san, thank you so much.
I'm happy you made such good friends.
I think Louise will realize that sooner or later as well.
Do you think I'm mean?
That's not true!
I'll warn you since you saved Saito's life.
What can you do by marching into the academy with such feelings?
Are you planning to stay in the shadows?
You can't go on like that!
Louise-san.
There might be many hardships waiting for you,
but fate will not continue like that forever.
You have to stand up with your own power.
You got it?!
Yes.
If you got it, stop crying all the time.
And regarding Saito...
Thank you.
If you hadn't been there, Saito would...
I'm sorry for saying harsh things.
I-It's okay.
Saito Chevalier de Hiraga-dono.
When you return to the academy, you will be surprised.
Oh? What is it?
It is a secret.
Have a good day, Saito Chevalier de Hiraga-dono.
Um, Princess...
This makes me kind of nervous. Please call me Saito.
I don't know what to do if you treat me courteously like that.
Today is an exception.
I see...
Saito-san, everyone, please take care of yourselves.
Oh, I can see the academy.
It looks fun.
Hurrah! Saito Chevalier de Hiraga!
Hurrah!
What's this all about?
They're celebrating your elevation to chevalier.
The emergency call from the royal palace came early in the morning.
It said to celebrate in as lively a manner as possible.
Her Majesty insisted on it personally.
Celebrate?
So you don't know about the Order of Undine Knights?
Though we didn't know about it before this morning either.
Order of Undine Knights?
Congratulations, Saito!
That's the way to go!
I'm Reinard.
I'll take care of the knightly practices.
And I'm the captain.
Otherwise it'd be a lot of trouble.
H-Hey hold on.
I'm blanking out.
I've got no idea what's going on.
Oh, come on.
Just leave the complicated details alone for now, Saito.
Becoming a chevalier changed my opinion of you.
Well, I guess it's all right for me to praise you.
Her Majesty is bad at choosing people...
Indeed.
Well then, gentlemen of the Order of Undine Knights,
let's lift Vice-captain Saito on our
shoulders for becoming a chevalier!
Saito! Saito!
You guys! Stop messing around!
Are you all right?
Hey!
What do you think you are doing to
Her Highness, Princess Guldenhorf?!
Hurrah! The Queen!
Hurrah! The Undine!
Oh, and also... Hurrah! Vice-captain Saito!
"Oh, and also"? And... vice-captain?!
Sigh...
It's impossible.
But...
kyuu ni senaka wo mukete kakedashita wa (Just love me)
急に背中を向けて 駆け出したわ
I suddenly turned my back on you and ran away
hoka no ko ni yasashiku shiteta kara yo
ほかの子に優しくしてたからよ
Because you've been so gentle to many other girls
Boy onegai oikakete yo
Boyお願い 追いかけてよ
Boy, please chase after me
ato ni wa hikenai kara
あとには引けないから
Because it won't be over after this
pun pun pun
I am so sorry
gomen to ienakute gomen ne
ゴメンと言えなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't say "I'm sorry", sorry ♥
shinjite iru no ni kuchibiru ga togaru
信じているのに くちびるが尖る
Even though I believe you, my lips are pouting
kawaiku narenakute gomen ne
可愛くなれなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't be cute, sorry ♥
kosame no furu machi tsukamaete
小雨の降る街 つかまえて
Catch me in the town where a drizzle is falling
furimuku kara nakanaori no chu o shite
振り向くから 仲直りのCHU～をして
Because I'll turn around and give you a make-up kiss
atsui ryouude no naka de
熱い両腕の中で
In your warm arms
Next Time
Practicing and practicing every damn day!
And ignoring your master and saying you want to protect that half-elf?!
Zero no Tsukaima. Princess no Rondo.
The Rumoured Accepted Student.
The Rumoured Accepted Student
Just a little more and...
I won't forgive you if you look away.