Louise-san!
Louise! Wake up!
Let's hurry.
It's all right now.
Saito...
You had a relationship like that?!
Explosion!
I can't use any magic...
A dream?
I...
Could I really be?!
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
mejirushi no nai michi mo heiki sa futari nara
メジルシのない道も平気さ　ふたりなら
Even on a road without signs, I'll be fine, if we're together
saki no mienai tabi mayoinagara mitsuketa yo
先の見えない旅　迷いながら見つけたよ
On a journey that I can't see ahead of, while I was lost, I found it
boku no iru basho kimi no tonari
僕の居る場所　君のとなり
That my place to be is next to you
kenkashite nando mo hanashita sono te
喧嘩して　何度も離したその手
When we quarrelled, I let go of your hand again and again
hikiyose dakitai ima
引き寄せ抱きたい　今
I want to pull close and hold it now
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
namida no ame ni utaretara
涙の雨に打たれたら
If I'm beaten down by the rain of tears
I wanna hold you sugu yobi na yo boku no namae
I wanna hold you　すぐ呼びなよ　僕の名前
I wanna hold you, call my name immediately
dakishime ni yuku wa
抱きしめに行くわ
I'll go embrace you
kanashimi mo tsuyogari mo kono te ni uketomeru
悲しみも強がりもこの手に　受け止める
I'll accept sadness and bluffing in my hands
Wings of Freedom
Jella isa undzu hagal beoque il!
Explosion!
Tabitha.
Have you been up all this time?
No. Just for a while.
What are you reading?
The Hero, Ivaldi.
A book full of memories.
I see.
I wish I could read the words.
I can teach you.
You saved my life.
What's the big deal?
Friends are supposed to help each other.
To show my gratitude.
Ivaldi.
It's the name of the hero.
What's this?
Lu. The name of the girl who was saved.
I see...
My mother used to read it to me when I was young.
Saito.
Louise?
What's wrong?
I... I...
I can't use any magic.
What should I do if I can't use it ever again?
I bet you're just tired.
Get some rest and I'm sure it'll come back.
Don't say such an irresponsible thing!
It's empty! I don't feel anything in me!
Louise?
If you can't use magic, I'll protect him.
Tabitha?
W-What are you saying?
Saito saved me.
So this time, I will protect Saito.
It is what I want to do for him.
Hey, you girls.
What's the ruckus so late at night?
Enemies?
No. No one is after us.
A-Are you sure?
Thank goodness.
A Square-class golem...
This puppet really is like a devilish monster.
I like it, my beloved Myoz.
It's my honour.
What's Charlotte and her party doing?
They passed through the forest of Alden and are approaching the border.
I see.
Let the totem bell ring!
The wind that blows through the
Carillon Canyon shall cry at your death!
My dear Charlotte...
Daughter of my brother, Charles, who left her behind.
If I see you lie bleeding on the ground, will my heart cry out in pain?
Similar to when I killed Charles?
Saito-san...
Please be safe.
I don't see anything in the distance.
Okay. Continue to keep your eyes open.
Roger!
I received a notice saying there's something suspicious going on at San Maron, near the border of Gallia.
The King of Gallia wouldn't just let them go.
However, invading through another's border is...
It's merely for support.
It is time to make use of the Great Spear.
The Great Spear?
I'm sure this too came originally from the eastern land.
It's one of the artefacts we cannot tie to anything else.
So this is?
Mr. Colbert.
Please go save everyone.
I understand.
I will save them even at the cost of my own life.
What do you intend to do with just the four of you?
If you're going to load that on the Ostland,
I'll lend you the Musketeer Force's strength.
Thank you.
The Great Spear...
I just hope we don't have to use it.
Having slain the dragon, Ivaldi made his way deeper into the c... c-
Cave.
...deeper into the cave where the room was.
What do you think, Louise?
I'm starting to be able to read a lot.
Hey, Louise.
But it's strange.
When you're teaching me, I can pick up reading really fast.
It's part of Gandalfr's power.
I heard you'll change, body and soul,
when you are completely overtaken by Gandalfr's power.
Is that true?
You become a different person when you become Gandalfr?
You should know that best.
What? So Saito's with me because he's Gandalfr?
So once I'm no longer a Void mage, it's over between us?
If I can't use my magic anymore,
then someone else will become the Void mage and...
Saito!
What did it feel like when you got out of your Gandalfr state?
What did it feel like? Nothing special.
Don't lie to me! You should have felt a change in your heart!
I'm not sure...
So why did you form a contract with me again?!
Are you an idiot?
You're the one that summoned me.
Don't call me an idiot!
I'm being serious here!
Everyone! Look!
What's it?
Hey-
Saito...
What?
Look ahead.
It's the border!
Once we're over the bridge, we're in Tristain.
Go right over it!
Watch out!
You're joking...
You've got to be kidding me...
What is this thing?
Long time no see, Gandalfr.
Sheffield!
You didn't think you would be able to get away that easily, did you?
Sylphid.
You got it.
Ow.
They're after me.
Find an opportunity to cross the bridge.
Don't go, Tabitha!
Dages forter lis.
Hello, Princess. I'm glad to see you're safe.
You're very brave to fight against this Jormungand.
Jormungand?
Iisan Hagaras.
Javelin!
Sorry, but aren't here for you.
Get lost!
In that case, allow us to entertain you.
Valkyrie! Take it down!
Fire!
We did it!
Not yet.
Gandalfr.
Isn't it about time for the trump card to come out?
Trump card?
Fine. If you don't understand what I'm talking about...
...then all I have to do is crush that carriage.
I won't let you!
Saito!
Don't come out! She's after you!
No! I'll fight with you!
You can't, Louise-san!
No, let go of me!
Malicorn! Hurry and get us moving!
O-Okay!
Let go of me!
Louise-san!
Saito...
Spirits of fire!
Spirits of earth!
Did we do it?
Looks like it's not working after all.
I'll stop it!
It's useless!
Let go of me!
I said let go!
Louise!
You idiot! Why did you come back?!
Void mage.
Show me your strength.
Show me the true power of a Void mage!
She doesn't know yet that I can't use magic.
Let go of me, you coward!
You have no right to order me around!
Looks like you don't know your place.
Louise!
I already told you it's useless!
What?
Tabitha!
Reinforcements.
That's...
The Ostland!
Louise!
Saito?
Don't come!
Louise...
Saito saved me.
So this time, I'll protect Saito.
Sheffield!
I'm the one you want, right?!
So let everyone else go!
Ful blisars ansul ken.
Gyofu need-
Louise, what are you doing?!
Shut up!
But your magic's...
I don't have time to babysit you!
Don't come near me!
How could I do that?!
Why did you come save me?
You ruined my plan to buy time.
Don't be ridiculous. That's my role!
Why don't you get it?
I'm back to being the Zero Louise.
I'm not worth being protected.
What nonsense are you speaking?
Hey, you weren't thinking about sacrificing yourself, were you?
You idiot.
Colbert-sensei!
What's this?
It's the Great Spear.
Why is this thing here?
We don't have time! I'll explain later!
Reinard! Turn the handle and set the bearing!
Okay!
Guiche, you set the elevation!
Gimli and Malicorn, prepare the shell!
Okay.
What's "elevation"?
Get a move on!
I-It's heavy...
I'll help.
Does this go here?
Yeah, that's it.
Reinard! Set the bearing to 45 degrees!
Guiche! Elevation twenty degrees!
Roger!
Everyone, plug your ears!
Fire!
We did it!
No...
Hurry with the next round!
It has Counter on its armour.
What do we do?
Cast Dispel on the shell.
That's the only way to pierce it.
Dispel?
Louise...
Saito!
Spirit of fire!
Colbert-sensei!
I'll help, too!
Wind!
Damn mages!
Louise!
I can't do it...
I can't do it!
I just can't do it!
My heart's empty!
You're Gandalfr, and you're with me only because I'm a void mage.
Louise...
What's the contract good for?
When the master can't use magic, the bond is practically gone!
Don't be ridiculous!
It's not the time for that!
Just say what's on your mind!
Or can't Gandalfr say what's he's really thinking?!
Louise!
Listen to me!
I'm...
I'm just Louise...
I'm not an aristocrat...
I'm not worth anything...
Then I'll take him.
Saito.
My Ivaldi.
I will protect you with everything I have.
Tabitha will become your knight.
No...
I won't allow that!
Saito...
Don't go...
Don't go!
Don't leave me alone.
Stay with me!
Now!
Cast Dispel!
Ful blisars.
Set the target!
Roger!
Ansul ken.
Gyofu need nousis.
Heilos iala.
Elpeo.
Y's!
Fire!
Charlotte...
What an amazing power...
That Void mage...
Saito...
I...
Was it for the best?
You idiot.
Why are you thinking all this by yourself?
All this master and familiar crap.
You're thinking too much.
I've been telling you that I love you from long ago.
Saito.
Do you really mean it?
Not because you're Gandalfr?
Of course not.
So let me ask. What was that about earlier?
That was Tabitha being witty...
You're a really pitiful dog.
You're so scared of getting yelled at
by your favourite master, aren't you?
What? Speaking of you, you can't control the fact you love me so much, can you?
I'm just conditioned to love my familiar.
I knew you were all jealous and all!
I pity myself for how I developed feelings for my familiar,
getting controlled by the power of the Void.
Why you...
So... I'm doing this against my will.
Dog...
You'd better be grateful.
Your Highness. We have disobeyed your orders.
We are all ready to accept any kind of punishment.
Stand up, Louise.
I will now give you your punishment for trespassing into Gallia.
That's...
A royal mantle...
You are now my sister.
Second in line for the throne.
As a Void mage, work hard for Tristain.
Princess...
Louise!
Saito-san.
I'll return to you the mantle of a chevalier.
Don't let go of it again.
Y-Yes.
Tabitha-dono.
Yes.
Rather, Princess Charlotte.
Allow me to say, welcome to Tristain!
Snuggle.
Sa-i-to!
C-Come down here right now!
You stupid dog!
The End
kyuu ni senaka wo mukete kakedashita wa (Just love me)
急に背中を向けて 駆け出したわ
I suddenly turned my back on you and ran away
hoka no ko ni yasashiku shiteta kara yo
ほかの子に優しくしてたからよ
Because you've been so gentle to many other girls
Boy onegai oikakete yo
Boyお願い 追いかけてよ
Boy, please chase after me
ato ni wa hikenai kara
あとには引けないから
Because it won't be over after this
pun pun pun
I am so sorry
gomen to ienakute gomen ne
ゴメンと言えなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't say "I'm sorry", sorry ♥
shinjite iru no ni kuchibiru ga togaru
信じているのに くちびるが尖る
Even though I believe you, my lips are pouting
kawaiku narenakute gomen ne
可愛くなれなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't be cute, sorry ♥
kosame no furu machi tsukamaete
小雨の降る街 つかまえて
Catch me in the town where a drizzle is falling
furimuku kara nakanaori no chu o shite
振り向くから 仲直りのCHU～をして
Because I'll turn around and give you a make-up kiss
atsui ryouude no naka de
熱い両腕の中で
In your warm arms