I heard that Saito-san is no longer Louise-san's familiar.
Which means he doesn't belong to anyone, right?
He's a free plebeian, right?
It's all right for me to make a move on him, right?
Wait! Louise!
Give me a break!
I beg you!
No! Until you repent your actions, I won't let you on!
Agnes, go faster.
You can leave him for all I care.
Louise!
Shut up, you stupid dog!
Stop!
Please stop!
Woah!
Woah, woah.
Wait...
Ow.
Saito-san.
Siesta?
Thank goodness I caught up.
Saito-san, if you're going away, take me with you.
Hey, how do you know we're going away?
I have many friends.
What are all those suitcases for?
These are...
...cooking materials!
Without me, you won't be able to eat, will you?
Fine, get on.
Yes.
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
mejirushi no nai michi mo heiki sa futari nara
メジルシのない道も平気さ　ふたりなら
Even on a road without signs, I'll be fine, if we're together
saki no mienai tabi mayoinagara mitsuketa yo
先の見えない旅　迷いながら見つけたよ
On a journey that I can't see ahead of, while I was lost, I found it
boku no iru basho kimi no tonari
僕の居る場所　君のとなり
That my place to be is next to you
kenkashite nando mo hanashita sono te
喧嘩して　何度も離したその手
When we quarrelled, I let go of your hand again and again
hikiyose dakitai ima
引き寄せ抱きたい　今
I want to pull close and hold it now
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
namida no ame ni utaretara
涙の雨に打たれたら
If I'm beaten down by the rain of tears
I wanna hold you sugu yobi na yo boku no namae
I wanna hold you　すぐ呼びなよ　僕の名前
I wanna hold you, call my name immediately
dakishime ni yuku wa
抱きしめに行くわ
I'll go embrace you
kanashimi mo tsuyogari mo kono te ni uketomeru
悲しみも強がりもこの手に　受け止める
I'll accept sadness and bluffing in my hands
Fairy in the Forest
Man, I'm exhausted.
You're sweating so much.
Thank you, Siesta.
Doing this makes it feel like it's just the two of us on a trip, doesn't it?
Nah...
I'm in a tight spot.
If you pamper him, he'll take advantage of you.
He's done something very rude.
He's worse than a dog; he's a water flea.
We didn't need to let him on the carriage.
Why does any of that matter when he's no longer your familiar?
How do you know that?
No, who cares about that?
Make some room between you and the water flea.
I don't want to!
If he's no longer your familiar,
then he doesn't belong to anyone, right?
W-Well...
So we should let him decide for himself.
Saito-san.
Would you not like to sit next to me?
Next to you? How could I...
Saito...
You water flea!
Anyway, I was thinking, Saito-san.
How long do you intend to live with Miss Vallière?
If you're going to start living alone, I'll take care of you.
Ah, even if you say that all of a sudden,
I still don't have any idea about that.
But thank you for your concern, Siesta.
It's my pleasure, Saito-san.
You two are really happy, aren't you?
We're in the middle of an important
secret mission given to us by the Queen.
We're not here to have fun.
Really? What is this secret mission?
A secret mission is a secret mission, so it's a secret.
How could I tell you?
We're off to find a fairy, Siesta.
A fairy?
What is that? A fairy tale?
It's not a fairy tale!
It's a secret mission, do you understand?!
Here, Saito-san. Your seconds.
Thanks, Siesta.
What's wrong, Louise?
You won't grow if you don't eat properly.
Quiet. Leave me alone.
Hey, Louise.
I'm going to sleep in the carriage.
I'll go do the dishes.
Y-Yeah.
What's with her?
She's uncertain.
Because your rune disappeared.
Just resummon me.
She's having a dilemma because she's not certain if it will work or not.
How troublesome.
You're just unique.
If you hadn't come back to life, I'm sure she would have given up and summoned a new familiar.
Are you saying it's my fault?
What a dense guy!
You don't understand her feelings?
She wants you to be her familiar again.
But there is no such precedent.
Can't even guess what'll happen.
Like what?
It's said that the same familiar won't appear in your second summoning.
Basically, renewing the contract is just impossible.
Even if you say that...
Take this.
It's crudely made, but it should be sufficient for training.
Um...
What?!
What are you brooding over?
Didn't you decide to protect Miss Vallière?
Or do you not have the confidence?
That's not it!
Pick up the sword, Saito.
I'll see how much weaker you are.
Saito-san.
You never know when and where an enemy will come.
Mind the terrain. If you don't have the skill, make up for it with your brain.
You've gone through real battles.
Sharpen all your five senses.
Don't think anything unnecessary!
Looks like it's come back to you a little.
I guess.
We'll continue tomorrow.
Looks like someone's worried.
Louise...
Saito... What am I supposed to do?
If I perform Summon Servant again, will you come to me?
Saito...
Watch out, Saito-san...
She's amazing in her own way.
We're almost at the village of Westwood.
Does the scenery around here look familiar to you, Saito?
I honestly don't remember much.
Tiffania's house is surrounded by the forest.
She lives in a small hut.
That...
Stop!
What?
Saito!
Hey!
It's me! Hiraga Saito!
Tiffania?
Saito... san?
I knew it. It is you!
Saito-san!
Tiffania!
W-Wh...
W-What are those?
Probably... her breasts...
I didn't imagine I'd get to see you again.
T-This indeed is...
Bust Revolution!
You sit right there!
Let's have you give a clear explanation.
I don't know who exactly she is, but Saito!
You're so intimate with her that you hugged her back?
Louise, you've got it wrong.
What exactly?!
Are you telling me you hugged someone you don't know?!
I don't believe this!
You are that low?!
Like I said, she's the one who saved my life.
She's Tiffania.
Tiffania?
So you're Tiffania, the fairy of the forest?
Fairy?
O-Okay, I understand.
Everything makes sense now.
Why Saito wanted to come here so much...
It was all for those breasts.
N-No, you got it wrong.
I'm wrong again, you say?
You're telling me nothing happened between you two after showing me that embrace?
You were pressing those malicious objects against him!
I didn't do any such thing...
Yes, you did!
Or what? Are you saying that what I saw was just imagination?
Are those malicious things empty inside?!
If you're going to persist, I'll check them myself!
No! Please stop!
Ever heard of common sense?! Ever heard of moderation?!
It's not "the bigger, the better"!
These can't be breasts.
They must be things that transform into breasts!
Aren't you ashamed of dangling such things?!
Quit it! I told you she saved my life!
What do you think you're doing?! You've teased her enough!
But!
What...
Fine! Enjoy your time with the person who saved your life!
There is another one somewhere in Westwood?
Yes, Master.
That stupid Saito.
Smirking without caring what's around him.
I've never seen such a happy face on him before.
What's the big deal?!
The bigger, the better?! Don't joke with me!
But... Saito fought alone to protect me...
What exactly did happen?
I didn't even ask him.
I'm the worst.
She might really be the person who saved his life,
yet I yelled at her without even hearing her story.
I hardly spoke with him during the journey here, either.
Because...
I don't know what to say...
Miss Vallière.
Everyone's worried about you.
Let's go back.
Siesta...
Tiffania-san's cute, don't you think?
Her breasts are foul play, don't you agree?
What do you think, Miss Vallière?
Can you forgive her?
Yeah, I'm not the bad one.
It's those monster breasts that are bad.
Looks like we share the sentiment, Miss Vallière.
Yeah.
Let's beat Tiffania!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Do you hear something?
Fenrir!
Miss Vallière...
Why are they in a place like this?
Void mage.
It'd be faster to call help with your cute voice.
That voice...
Sheffield!
Yes, very astute of you.
Now, call for help.
There should be another Void mage here.
Another?
Louise-san!
Louise!
Saito?
Take care of Tiffania!
Saito-san?
Where is the other one?
What are you talking about?
It's for your own sake to speak up.
Or would you rather be shred to pieces by Fenrir?
I don't have a clue what you're talking about!
Is that your answer?
Go!
No!
How is it?
Feel like screaming for help now?
I told you. We don't know what you're talking about.
Isn't there a way out with your magic?
I can't cast anything without my wand.
It got knocked away somewhere.
Over there! I'll go get it!
Siesta!
Fenrir!
Louise-san!
Siesta!
Explosion!
Hey, are you all right?
You shouldn't, Saito-san...
Impressive.
But can you defeat all of them with magic only?
Louise!
Where are you, Louise?!
You're no longer Gandalfr.
You're just a human now.
Will you be all right?
It doesn't matter even if I'm not.
Louise is calling for me.
I can tell!
Your life is really covered with trouble.
Well, those who believe shall be rewarded, right?
Keep your mouth shut.
I'm counting on you in the case of emergency, buddy.
Explosion!
Saito, help me.
You're my familiar, aren't you?
Are you done with your magic?
Then hurry and call the other Void mage.
My name is Louise Françoise Le Blanc de La Vallière.
Pentagon that governs the five powers...
Open the summon gate before me and my yet to be seen familiar.
Stop.
Trying to resummon, eh?
Interesting. Let's see what she gets.
Saito... Saito...
You'll come to me, won't you?
You're my familiar, right?
My familiar is...
...only you!
If Saito doesn't come...
No, I have faith! Saito will come!
Saito... Saito... Saito! Saito!
Saito...
Come!
Ow...
Saito!
Saito! Saito! It's you, right, Saito?
You're not anyone else, right?
Of course not.
I knew you would come.
Impossible. How could the same familiar appear twice?
Sheffield. I'm your opponent from here on.
Looks like there's something special about you.
We'll meet again...
...Void mage's familiar.
What's with her?
I don't know.
She demanded that I call another Void mage.
Void mage?
Wow, look at your outfit.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it like that.
It's fine.
If you don't look at me, I can't do it.
C-Can't do, as in, uh...
Contract Servant!
Why are you making me say it?!
S-Sorry.
Don't apologise!
I'm sorr-
You're not regretting this?
You're going to be my familiar again, you know?
I came for that purpose.
You know that, don't you?
Yeah.
Pentagon that governs the five powers.
Give this person your blessing and make him my familiar.
Saito?
Saito!
I really didn't need the pain of getting this back...
Saito-san!
Hey, you! What do you think you're doing?
You came to save me, Saito-san?
You're so wonderful.
Hey, you stupid maid!
Keep sleeping!
Yes, Joseph-sama.
I'm very sorry.
I couldn't find the other Void mage.
But instead, I confirmed that Gandalfr is back.
That boy who claims to have come from a parallel world.
That's fine.
Don't rush, Sheffield.
You're a good girl.
Observe for a while longer.
I'm glad to see that you're all right, Saito-san.
We were worried since you dashed out.
Well...
So Saito-san's back to being a familiar again?
How disappointing.
It's just how things turned out.
Sorry about "how things turned out".
Louise.
It's fine. I'll forgive you for today.
But you're still a dog.
You only became a dog again.
We still have problems to deal with!
Do you really understand, you dog?!
Sigh...
It's impossible.
But...
kyuu ni senaka wo mukete kakedashita wa (Just love me)
急に背中を向けて 駆け出したわ
I suddenly turned my back on you and ran away
hoka no ko ni yasashiku shiteta kara yo
ほかの子に優しくしてたからよ
Because you've been so gentle to many other girls
Boy onegai oikakete yo
Boyお願い 追いかけてよ
Boy, please chase after me
ato ni wa hikenai kara
あとには引けないから
Because it won't be over after this
pun pun pun
I am so sorry
gomen to ienakute gomen ne
ゴメンと言えなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't say "I'm sorry", sorry ♥
shinjite iru no ni kuchibiru ga togaru
信じているのに くちびるが尖る
Even though I believe you, my lips are pouting
kawaiku narenakute gomen ne
可愛くなれなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't be cute, sorry ♥
kosame no furu machi tsukamaete
小雨の降る街 つかまえて
Catch me in the town where a drizzle is falling
furimuku kara nakanaori no chu o shite
振り向くから 仲直りのCHU～をして
Because I'll turn around and give you a make-up kiss
atsui ryouude no naka de
熱い両腕の中で
In your warm arms
Next Time
To get a status directly from the Princess, you're really something.
But you're still a dog, do you hear?
Zero no Tsukaima. Princess no Rondo.
Return of the Hero.
What are you staring at?!
Return of the Hero
I won't forgive you if you look away!