All right!
Here goes!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Best of Three
Okay!
I'll be starting, then.
P-i-ne-app-le-s!
Rock, paper, scissors!
All right!
Here I go!
You can't do that!
The rule is to go up one step at a time.
I know!
Gu... ri... co... bonus!
H-Hey!
Heh?
What is it?
Why are you putting that at the end?
Eh?
You don't normally put "bonus" after it?
What do you say, Mai-chan?
Fifty-fifty.
I get it.
It's fine like that.
But if you're going to do that,
then I'll put my own rules into effect, okay?
Rock, paper, scissors!
You're next, then, Mai-chan.
chi-yo-ta ni-ke-ra ha-to-ho ra-su-te no-ha-te ki-ra-to na-ri-ha shi-te-to
It's the spell for revival.
tatta ima hajimete kizuita
たった今 初めて気づいた
I just realised it for the first time
koi ni ochita no dana
恋に落ちたのだな～
That I had fallen in love~
nijyuuyo jikan kimi kimi kimi
24h キミ☆ キミ☆ キミ☆
Twenty-four hours a day thinking of you, you and nothing more than you!
ishiki sezaru o emasen
意識せざるをえません!
It's something I wasn't consciously aware of
nanka (nanka) itsumo to chigau
なんか (なんか) いつもと違う
Somehow (somehow) I'm feeling different from the usual
kimi to (futari) gikochinai kaiwa
キミと (二人) ぎこちない会話
With you (the two of us) and our dull chatter
masaka (ryouomoi) iya kataomoi
まさか (両思い) いや 片思い
Don't tell me (mutual love?) Nope, it's a one-sided crush
yabai shisen acchatta
やばい! 視線合っちゃった!
This is bad! Our gazes met!
nani nani kono doki doki
なになに?! このドキドキ?!
What, what? Why is my heart pounding like this?
shikoukairo guccha guccha konsen
思考回路 ぐっちゃぐっちゃ 混線・・・
Did a short circuit just make a mess out of my mind?
konna koto hajimete dayo
こんなこと 初めてだよ
This is my first time... feeling like this...
netsu demo aru no kana
熱でもあるのかな～
I wonder if I have a fever~
kyuutenchokka irasshatta koigokoro
急転直下 いらっしゃった 恋心
Suddenly and precipitately, love has arrived.
acchuuma kao hakka de makkakka
あっちゅうま 顔 発火で まっかっか
Instantly igniting my face into a bright red
ba ba baka na te ga furueruzo
バ・バ・バカな?! 手が震えるぞ
T-That's stupid?! My hands are shaking
kore ga zoku ni iu koi nano
これが 俗に言う 「恋」 なの?!
Is this really what they call "love"?
yayayacchatta kaiwa kami makuri
やややっちゃった 会話 噛みまくり
I-I did it! A conversation filled with stutters
kimazui chinmoku mamimumemo
気まずい沈黙 マミムメモ
This awkward silence... *mumble mumble*
kimi no (kimi no) kimochi shiritai yo
キミの (キミの) 気持ち 知りたいよ
Your... (Your...) I want to know your feelings.
kakakata kataomoi
カカカタ☆カタオモイ
O-One-sided love
hatsukoi itsumo no tsuugakuro
初恋! いつもの通学路
First love! The usual way to school
pika pika hikaru I do fall in love
ピカピカ光る I do fall in love!
The shining light. I do fall in love!
sora mo tobesou sa
空も飛べそうさ
I feel I could fly towards the sky
kakakata kataomoi
カカカタ☆カタオモイ
O-One-sided love
It stopped.
Argh, Mum, I told you to wake me up at seven!
Mum!
TL note: sepak takraw = kick ball
Dear Mio,
I'm off to to the sepak takraw game with the
people from the neighbourhood association.
.                                             From, Your Mother
Sepak...
...Sepak takraw.
Nichijou 05
Argh.
Even though I'm on day duty today.
Setting the alarm clock aside,
why did they have to cut the power today, of all days?
Really, I wish they'd warn us in advance if they're going to cut the power!
This sucks!
I'll just have to hammer out the fastest lap that I can.
That should be enough to...
I mean, just now...
There was something freaky there!
Above that...
It's coming!
What what what what!?
This sprinter!
Why... is it... following me!?
Impossible!
Um... Excuse me...
Did you drop a wooden mask?
Or maybe a golden one?
It'll get me.
If I don't do it,
it'll get me.
I'm sorry!
Sometimes, I'm a bear.
And sometimes...
...I'm a b-ea-r...
Whose identity is...!
S-Sorry, sorry.
Tada!
The answer was your sister!
You didn't realise I was wearing the
same school uniform as you, did you?
Ah, that was fun-
Oh, that is a fine corkscrew this early in the morning.
Yes.
It is indeed splendid!
It was a lot of work, you know, to stop your alarm clock as well.
You were the culprit?!
No, no, no.
Don't be so mad.
Here, I'll treat you to some ramen with this.
That was my pocket money!
chi-yo-ta ni-ke-ra ha-to-ho ra-su-te no-ha-te ki-ra-to na-ri-ha shi-te-to
Spell
Please enter your revival spell:
Chiyota
Nikera
Hatoho
Rasute
Nohate
Kirato
Nariha
Shite
The spell is wrong.
Nichijou 06
A shark...
A shark!
I'm home!
Hm?
Professor, what are you up to?
Nano!
That cloud looks shark-ish!
Heh, which one?
Ah, it really does!
It looks cool.
Indeed it does.
Ah, yeah.
I brought it with me, Professor.
Milk.
Is it the 4.5?
The 4.5?
The 4.5 milk?
Yes, it's the special one.
The 4.5 milk~
But what happened?
For you to want to drink milk so suddenly...
That is...
Because there's cake roll!
Why are you remodelling me without asking!?
Because it's a cake roll.
I don't understand!
Nano, the 4.5 is milk!
It's not 4.5!
Why do I have to live with a cake roll in my arm!?
It's cold and delicious!
I'm not talking about that!
What if someone outside saw this?
Professor...
What is it?
Um... Can I have some, too?
Okay.
Just a minute.
Here, go ahead.
Thank you very much.
Um...
Hm?
A little of that cake roll, too?
Ah, yeah!
I'll give the sweet bun to you, then, Nano.
Eh!?
Go ahead.
It went back in!
Sorry, I pressed the wrong one by mistake.
So, why are you doing these things?!
What would I do if it happened outside,
because of a bump of some sort?
What will happen?
I'm sure...
Commander Sunborn Master is the greatest!
Right!
I'll also make it so you can play music!
That's not the point!
How did this become about remodelling me even more?
Listen to me properly, please!
This much!
What is it?
Sweet bun!
You can't have it, since you already ate the cake roll.
Eh?
Professor?
It's okay,
since I still have some Baumkuchen left!
Eh, eh?
N-No way.
Where will it come out this time?!
Above?
Below?
P-Put them all in the refrigerator the first time, please!
No!
Eh?
Shinonome Institute
Eh...
First comes rock, next comes paper, rockscispaper doesn't count,
rock paper scissors!
I'm so sleepy...
Mio-san.
What's that smile for?
Show me your notes!
Don't tell me you forgot your homework, again?
It's pretty embarrassing...
Geez.
If you keep that up, you're in for a
painful experience on your exams again.
I get it.
But this time, only for this time...
I'll make this the last time, so please.
How about it?
Yukko.
That's what you said last time, too, isn't it?
There's no "last time" in ignorance!
No, I told you before...
Eh...
I-Is that so?
Oh, well... I guess there's nothing we can do.
Just this once, okay?
I mean it.
I get it.
One should always treasure their Mio-chan.
Yukko!
The one I told you about has appeared!
I'll give it back as soon as I've copied it.
Sure.
Really?
Show me, show me!
Huh?
Am I forgetting something?
Last night, I did my homework...
I did my homework...
I drew...
I drew a picture in there...
...and forgot about it by this morning!
I won't
let you
do it.
I won't
let you.
I won't let you do it!
I forgot!
Nichijou 07
Right? Right?
Yeah!
Yukko!
Sorry, sorry.
Come to think of it, I forgot to do my homework.
It beat me!
So that means, I'm taking my notebook back.
Sorry.
Eh?
What?
See, there's no point in looking...
Again?
Don't say that.
You said you'd lend it to me.
I'm off.
Sorry, I'm back now.
This is bad.
This is very bad.
If she sees that, she'll definitely think I'm weird.
Not to mention, if she sees that...
Especially if it's Yukko, she'll definitely tell...
...everyone!
Yukko!
T-That's my Japanese notebook.
This one's my maths notebook.
But this one's got "Maths" written on it.
You're wrong!
It hurt... my stomach hurt!
Okay.
Oh no.
I'll copy it right away.
Hold on for a bit.
Oh no.
If she sees it now...
...it's over.
My high school life will be...
...over.
Yukko.
That notebook... I'll buy it from you for 1000 yen!
Why are you running away?!
Yukko!
You've got it all wrong.
That notebook is... That notebook is...
...going to explode!
It's useless.
There's no way I can chase down the running Yukko.
It's over.
My life is...
Thank you, my life.
Up until now it has been fun.
There were a few bad things, but it was a happy life.
But now it's over.
My life is over...
...along with my banquet of men.
It's over.
Like. Hell. I'd. Let. It. Be. Over!
My life is blazing!
Coconut
Milk
Even so, I still can't reach her.
Yukko!
Don't... run in the hallway!
Are... Are you all ri-
Here.
Okay, hand your notes in from the back.
After that, those who didn't do their homework, own up quickly.
An hour ago, I was wondering how I'd go on,
but it looks like I managed to survive just fine.
With this, my everyday life has returned...
Ah!
I didn't erase it!
What is it, Naganohara?
Our Goal: Sweat Buckets And Enjoy Youth Together
Sensei!
I forgot to do my homework!
...and like this.
Tidying Up
Professor, can you help me clean up some of the mess in this room?
It might be a bit soon for the Professor.
I'm going to go play.
Um...
Student Guidance
I said to that guy...
Um, excuse me.
Annaka-san, can I have a moment?
Yes?
It's just for a moment.
That ribbon, I wonder if it's a bit too big...
Pyon~
Sweet Buns
Sweet buns are delicious, aren't they?
Indeed they are.
TickMart
Welcome!
Sold Out
Home-Style
Sweet Bun
55 Count
Super
Full of
vigor
Super
Manager's Choice
Adult Flavor
Super
Delicious
Cheap Sweet Bun
55 Count
Nichijou 08
Sasahara, do you have any sense of responsibility as a Cultural Festival Executive Committee member?
You need to think seriously about it.
I am utterly diligent.
I'm the President of the Drama Club, so I'm always like that.
Do you not even understand that, Tachibana Misato?
No, I don't understand it!
Sweet.
Listen to me!
Besides, we're here to decide on the program for the cultural festival.
Your Drama Club has nothing to do with it!
The brand has changed?
Why did I end up paired together with this guy?
It's delicious.
Even I've got a tournament coming up in the Kendo Club...
Geez.
I shouldn't have joined the Cultural Festival Executive Committee.
Hey, you!
Why are you reading manga?
If we don't come up with something quickly,
we wont be able to return home.
Sorry.
It's a new release.
Don't you even have one idea?
Was the wine tasting championship idea I gave you earlier really not any good?
Obviously, it wasn't any good.
Rejected. Rejected! Absolutely rejected!
Hey, Sasahara?
You!
What have you been doing since earlier?
Sorry, had some piled up stuff.
Analog signal...
Sasahara, running away, huh?
I'm going to make a brief trip to the toilet.
Honestly...
It looks like she's in a really bad mood today.
As far as it concerns me,
the wine tasting championship would have been more than enough.
Male Restroom
Nevertheless, she didn't bring up any ideas of her own.
If I tell her that, this time she may even take my life.
In other words,
if I don't come up with something it seems I won't be able to go home.
However, can my way of thinking drop to the level of a commoner?
Maybe I should try thinking seriously about it.
I-It's not like I have feelings towards you.
asa okite hao migai te
朝起きて 歯を磨いて
Woke up in the morning, brushed my teeth
attoiuma gogo juu ji
あっという間 午後10時
In the blink of an eye, it's 10pm
kyou mo takusan waratta naa
今日も たくさん 笑ったなぁ
Today, we laughed a whole lot
takusan tokimeita naa
たくさん ときめいたなぁ
We had a great time
tomodachi to baka mitai ni sawai deru toki ni mo
友達と バカみたいに騒いでる 時にも
At times, with my friends, acting like fools, being noisy
chirachiratte me ga au
チラチラって 目が合う
Fluttering, our eyes met.
guuzen dayo ne
…偶然、だよね。
It's a coincidence, right?
hatsukoi nante ie nai
初恋なんて言えない
I wouldn't call this my first love
kyara janai n da mon
キャラじゃないんだもんっ!
It's not my character.
nee ashita mo aeru yo ne
ねえ あしたも会えるよね?
Say, will we be able to meet again tomorrow?
mabuta o tojiru to
まぶたを 閉じると
As my eyelids close
kirakira kimi darake
キラキラ キミだらけ
I see you sparkling all over the place
kyou mo tanoshikatta ne
今日も 楽しかったね
Today was fun, too, wasn't it?
aa koi shite n da naa
あー 恋 してんだなぁ
I'm in love~
ureshii na ureshii na
うれしいな うれしいな
So happy, so happy
hajimemashite koi gokoro
はじめまして こいごころ
It is my pleasure to meet you, my new-found love.
ashita mata aeru ne
あした また あえるね
Surely, we'll meet again tomorrow~
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
Have a good night
yume de sugu aeru ne
ゆめで すぐ あえるね
We'll meet immediately in our dreams
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
So have a good night
Word of
Asian innocence.
the Day
This is a sweet bun.
In Kansai, there seem to be many people who don't
know whether to read it as "Amashoku" or "Kamshoku"
Next week's Nichijou is the third one.
Narration:     Ikeda Masako
Look forward to it.