No, I really did get a 32.
Then show me.
Didn't we say we'd show our scores at the same time?
I showed you mine.
I told you, I got a 32...
Come on, show me.
No, really...
When you think about it, it's a 32.
Why would I lie about such a real score?
About a 32...
Thirty-twelve.
Thirty-two, you mean?
Anyway, yeah...
Let's leave it at that.
All right, I guess I can't do anything about whether you'll show me or not.
My score was bad this time too.
It's a bit shameless, but...
I'll be taking a look!
An Everyday
Compliment
I couldn't even...
Um... um... this is... um...
Yukko, as expected!
No, no, no, no, no... What I meant to say was, it's unexpected.
Look, you forgot about your homework the day before yesterday, right?
No, no, that's not right... You did your homework, but left it at home, right?
Yeah...
That's your attitude towards it.
You don't do your homework often, but you did this time, right?
You're just not very good at it.
Dreams and ambitions are like that too...
The first step is the hardest.
That's what you've done, Yukko.
You've cleared the first barrier!
Ba... rrier?
That's right, the barrier!
The first barrier!
I...
...cleared it?
You're amazing, so you may not have realised that.
Especially for an ordinary person, that's a very difficult thing to do.
I...
...guess I did.
You did, you did!
In all seriousness, that's something worthy of respect!
But Mio-chan is even more amazing...
You always do your homework through force of habit.
It's just a habit of mine to always do it.
I do it by force of habit...
By comparison, you never do it.
This is-
With this...
I've got her!
Well, you know...
I know, Yukko.
Cars and even trains first need energy to start running.
If you think of it like that, you might be hiding an incredible power!
I...
...understand!
I mustn't rush it.
Little by little... little by little.
But you know, Mio-chan...
You're overestimating me.
I'm just an ordinary human.
I fail plenty of times.
I can get pretty depressed too...
No, no, you don't have to be so modest.
No, it's not modesty...
Everyone already knows you're amazing.
No, well...
Is that what they call the will to challenge oneself?
I guess it's not a total lie...
Right?
I'm absolutely no good.
The manga I drew recently...
...I started thinking that nobody would appreciate it.
So I got scared and couldn't submit it.
You get nervous a lot, don't you Mio-chan?
You only got one point, so don't you say that!
Yukko, come with me.
Read it!
Exam information.
One: Give it your best effort.
Yes, that's it! That's exactly it!
That's the most important thing.
You always give it your best effort.
You've grasped the most important aspect!
But... I got one point.
N-No... good.
Yukko, I'm sorry.
I forgot the most important thing and got caught up in our scores.
Since you've already grasped that, I might have been jealous of you.
Eh? But...
Since I'm already doing my homework through habit,
I don't know whether or not I can give it my best in exams.
It's the same for my manga.
But you're different, Yukko.
You always give it your best.
You're a breath of fresh air.
I'd really love to have your positive attitude, Yukko.
Eh, but that's all I have.
But that's the most important thing, like I told you.
Well, if you say so, I guess it's true.
How'd you work up the courage to take that first step?
It's simple.
I might say something bad though.
Anyway, you just have to avoid thinking negative thoughts.
You need to have the will to always look ahead.
Things that you can believe in are very important, and knowing that, you can't lose.
Something like that.
Always look ahead...
Well, as for me, I guess it came to me subconsciously.
Or rather, that's what's natural for me.
Or maybe... um...
A talent.
That's your talent, Yukko.
No, it's not a talent.
But... maybe...
I guess... that could be it.
If it comes to you subconsciously, then it's something born into you.
You can't gain it just through trying!
I'm envious of that talent.
Natural Talent
Genius
Mio-chan!
Are you really Mio-chan?
I'll give you 100 yen. Or not.
What are you doing?
I thought I could at least get a little of that blessing.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I couldn't possibly give such a blessing.
That's not true.
You're probably spreading the blessing around already, Yukko.
Is that so?
Well, I suppose.
They say you should try everything out.
I don't really understand it, but...
Maybe I got a little of it.
The courage to move forward!
Come on, you're not going to achieve anything by praising me so much!
Did you get some of my motivation?
Yukko, your motivation is the best!
All right!
I can't be discouraged by only getting one point.
I got away with it!
As expected, hers was only a lukewarm Heavenly Rock Cave.
Note: In Japanese mythology, this is a reference to the cave where Amaterasu hid when angered.
If you set it up, she'll bite soon enough.
Well, all I did was randomly compliment her.
I just hope she studies a bit more after this.
Mio-chan!
I turned the source of all of this into a paper plane.
If I just send this flying...
I'll also fly to even greater heights.
She's in denial.
Well then, here goes.
Farewell, light of youth!
Ouch.
Shinonome Institute
Nano.
What should we play?
An Everyday
Cold
Blow your nose.
Professor, you should have some medicine now.
What should we play?
Please take your medicine.
Sakamoto, what should we play?
Hm, I wonder.
Sakamoto-san!
Me?!
Geez, you've had a runny nose since yesterday.
I told you to hurry up and go to bed, but you didn't.
You won't eat properly either.
Oh, here it is.
I'm going to go over there and play.
No.
I'm going to get the water now, so make sure you take it.
But he said that I don't have that bad of a cold, so I don't need to take medicine.
Who said that?
Sakamoto.
I didn't say that!
Sakamoto-san!
I told you, I didn't say that!
He also said he loves medicine, so he wants to drink my medicine too.
When did I say that?
Sakamoto-san!
You believe that?!
And after that, he said that no matter what you say, he likes medicine so much that he'll-
Blow.
Anyway, please take your medicine.
If you don't, you're the one who'll suffer.
But the medicine's a little bitter and I don't like it.
It's fine.
It'll be over soon, right?
You're lying.
I'm not lying.
You are lying!
Last time, it wasn't over quickly.
All right, if you take this you'll feel better in no time.
Is it tasty?
I wrapped it in a wafer, so there's no taste at all.
You just need to swallow it.
I don't believe you...
Here you go. Say "Ah".
All right, swallow it.
No, swallow it with water!
Ah, if you don't hurry, the wafer will melt and-
Nano, you're a liar.
That happened because you didn't swallow it right away.
I guess it can't be helped.
Leave this to me.
Are you sure?
Watch this.
Hey, brat.
You like sharks, right?
Sharks? Yeah.
Did you know? Sharks hardly ever get sick.
Is that so?
Yeah.
When they're only hurt a little bit, they heal very quickly.
However, humans are different.
That's because we're not as cool as sharks, right?
Yeah.
For that reason, humans have to eat many things.
When they get sick, they have to-
Gotcha!
Sakamoto-san!
Well, I'll take some as well.
So please take your medicine, Professor.
It's fine if we both do it, right?
Since I can't drink it and Nano can, I think Nano should drink it all.
That won't do!
Then Sakamoto should take it.
Why would I take it?
If you keep this up, your cold won't get any better.
I don't care if my cold doesn't get any better.
Sakamoto-san, please get me a tissue.
Sure.
Sakamoto-san!
Damn! I can't stop!
If you wipe it there, it'll get dirty, won't it?
It's not really dirty... and I'm not taking the medicine!
Fine.
If you're not going to take your medicine, we'll go without snacks today.
I even made pudding.
Pudding...
He said it was okay for me to eat snacks!
Who said that?!
You're going to blame me again?!
Shinonome Institute
Damn it.
She's not even eating?
No.
She's hopeless.
Girl. Follow me.
You're the one at fault here.
Even if you force her...
...that brat won't take her medicine.
So it seems.
But... what should I do?
Persuading her now will be difficult.
There is only one way.
There's a way?
Mix it in with her snack.
I see!
Dock it with her favourite food and camouflage it as a ride-on.
Call it "Operation Snack Mash-up".
Amazing, Sakamoto-san! You're an incredible strategist.
You're hopeless.
I'll go and make that right away.
Hold on.
Yes?
You'll only have one chance.
If you're found out, you won't get another.
Got it?
Yes.
Shark.... Shark...
Professor!
Here she comes.
It's time for a snack.
Do you want some pudding?
Really?!
Yes.
Eat up.
Pudding!
It's not even hidden!
Girl, follow me!
That was a shock.
Are you an idiot?!
Do you want that brat to see the medicine?!
Did I do it wrong?
Didn't I say you only had one chance?
Anyone would have doubts about that!
You have to mix, mix and sprinkle it inside.
Sorry, I'll mix it in right away.
Geez, you guys can't do anything without me.
Really, it's a good thing I'm here-
Sakamoto-san!
Delicious!
What the-
This pudding's delicious!
It's crunchy at first, but then it becomes more like pudding. It's delicious!
R-Really?
That's great!
Please eat it all!
We did it, Sakamoto-san.
Well...
I guess it sometimes happens like this too.
Shinonome Institute
Nano, can I have another one?
Crunchy pudding!
Yes, okay.
The next one's not going to be crunchy, though.
Aw, Sakamoto-san said that the crunchy pudding was better!
Me again?
Shinonome Institute had another peaceful day today.
Sakamoto-san!
An Everyday
Reservation
Huh?
The train's due to come soon, right?
Yeah, about a minute left.
There's absolutely nobody here!
I guess not.
There aren't as many people around in the afternoon, I suppose.
Could it be that we're alone here?
In that case...
...even if I do this, nobody will get mad!
Amazing, Yukko!
You do it too, Mio-chan!
Nobody's looking anyway.
I-Is that right?
Okay then.
Here I go!
How'd I do?
Mio-chan, that's not quite right.
It's here.
Mai-chan, do you like trains?
A bit.
There's nobody here. It's like we've reserved it!
The tension's rising!
Mio-chan, Mio-chan!
Let's play, let's play!
Here we go.
One, two!
Mai-chan, you're the referee.
Watch us...
Bunk bed.
Triple-decker bunk.
Somehow, I feel as if I'm the only one losing out.
Nichijou
Episode 0