Being in the boonies like this bores me to death.
The mission I went on the other day was simply
carrying a sick woman out of the Orléans house!
Really?
What a waste of such a fine man like you.
I'm attracted to such strong men.
I'd like to hear more of your story.
Please.
Sure.
Really? Oh, I'm so happy!
Anyone can think of gathering information near Tabitha's house,
but Kirche's about the only person who can actually pull it off.
She completely understands how men's minds work.
It's a talent of hers at that level.
Al Hambra Castle.
That's where Tabitha's mother was taken.
Tabitha's probably there, too.
Al Hambra... It's on the eastern edge of Gallia, isn't it?
Goodness. Looks like we'll have to go over mountains again.
We'll go over however many mountains we need to.
Let's go save Tabitha!
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
mejirushi no nai michi mo heiki sa futari nara
メジルシのない道も平気さ　ふたりなら
Even on a road without signs, I'll be fine, if we're together
saki no mienai tabi mayoinagara mitsuketa yo
先の見えない旅　迷いながら見つけたよ
On a journey that I can't see ahead of, while I was lost, I found it
boku no iru basho kimi no tonari
僕の居る場所　君のとなり
That my place to be is next to you
kenkashite nando mo hanashita sono te
喧嘩して　何度も離したその手
When we quarrelled, I let go of your hand again and again
hikiyose dakitai ima
引き寄せ抱きたい　今
I want to pull close and hold it now
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
namida no ame ni utaretara
涙の雨に打たれたら
If I'm beaten down by the rain of tears
I wanna hold you sugu yobi na yo boku no namae
I wanna hold you　すぐ呼びなよ　僕の名前
I wanna hold you, call my name immediately
dakishime ni yuku wa
抱きしめに行くわ
I'll go embrace you
kanashimi mo tsuyogari mo kono te ni uketomeru
悲しみも強がりもこの手に　受け止める
I'll accept sadness and bluffing in my hands
Captive in Al Hambra
Based on Malicorn's telegnosis spell,
there are about a hundred soldiers at Al Hambra Castle.
If we consider the safety of Tabitha and her mother first,
I think this is the only way to do it.
So I have to make as many sleeping potions as possible, right?
And I go buy loads of alcohol and spike it with the potion.
But how do we make a hundred people drink at once?
I have a secret weapon for that.
Come on in.
We'll dance in these, charm everyone and have them drink.
What do you think?
Great! Magnificent!
So we're going to do this tonight.
Malicorn, you keep scouting the castle.
Tiffa and Illococoo, you two help Montmorency.
Got it!
Yes!
Hey! Isn't there anything for me?!
You want to dance with us?
We do have a costume for you, if you'd like.
I don't mean that.
You and Saito should rest.
You're being nasty to me even at a time like this?
I know you don't like me, but...
I'm not hating you. I'm recognising you.
I didn't want to say this in front of everyone,
but in reality, we have no clue what we're up against.
I'm counting on you.
Counting on your legendary skill.
You knew about the Void?
I'll apologise for all the discourtesy my ancestors have done.
Please lend this weak one your holy power.
S-Stop this ancestor thing and whatnot.
I'm no longer an aristocrat.
Right now, I'm just the Zero Louise.
Louise, you're such a...
H-Hey!
Hey, when this issue is resolved, come visit Germania.
I'll hire you as my maid.
Don't joke with me!
Oh, and I thought you'd be perfect as one.
What are you talking about, stupid Kirche?!
"No clue what we're up against", eh?
Are you worried about her?
Then why not give her some gentle words?
Void magic completely depends on mental state.
I guess.
See, I'm so cute.
I lose nothing to the dragon, the boob monster or the cow maid.
Hey, Louise.
W-Why don't you knock first?!
I'm sorry!
I-Is that costume...
I-I decided to dance with everyone else.
I don't want to be treated specially.
I see. So you'll be dancing, too.
I-In that outfit?
G-Gosh. Look at him snorting. Pervert.
But, I wonder why...
This sort of feels good.
Hey Saito. Does this look good on me?
I think it's good.
You can't tell without actually looking, can you?
Turn around.
What? Well...
You don't want to see?
N-No, I didn't mean that.
So look then.
I didn't come for that.
Gosh, he's so indecisive.
Fine then.
I-I wonder what will happen if I move the bra off a little.
I-I'm invincible, you know.
I can easily take my familiar out with the added sexiness.
Hey, Louise?
L-Look. I'm moving it.
I'm moving it aside.
I'm moving it!
See? See? See? See?
H-Hey! Saito!
I tried to hold myself back, but I can't!
S-Stop it!
We don't know what will happen to us if we end up fighting tonight!
So...
Saito...
Hey, Saito, can you give me a ha-
We were just practising dancing!
Get out.
I heard you were playing dead with your student's magic.
Yes. But I don't want you to blame my students for that.
I take full responsibility.
I probably owe them thanks.
Colbert-sensei!
So you've been released!
Thank goodness.
I can never forgive you, who burned my home town to the ground.
Even after knowing that it was you who saved my life,
I still want to kill you.
But if I kill you in anger, your students will hate me.
And the chain of hatred continues.
I have the opportunity to end that chain.
You'll eventually receive an audience with the Queen.
Until then, remain on the ship.
Very well.
So Baron, don't you think your men need some fun once in a while?
We're here to provide you with that fun today.
Drink and dance, eh?
Why not.
Enter.
Thank you very much.
We'll begin right away-
But...
Y-Your attention please...
Get it started already!
We don't need to see a guy on the stage!
W-What you're about to see is a dance of
beautiful flowers that bloom in the desert.
Dansez, s'il vous plait!
Are you ready?!
How do you dance like that?
I don't know.
I can't do it well!
Who's short on drink?!
Keep drinking.
I'm starting to get the hang of it.
To save Lu, Ivaldi entered the dragon's den.
Meanwhile, Lu was trapped inside a dark room in despair.
I heard a travelling circus has come to put a show on.
If you want to go watch it, I'll give you special permission to go.
I do not need to.
The drug that erases emotions will be ready before sunrise.
Tonight's the last day you can remain yourself.
I do not need to be pitied.
Face! Hands! Body!
It's boring! Bring the girls out!
Get lost!
After the break, I'll dance, too!
Dancing is hard.
It's not that bad for you.
All you have to do is move and they'll shake.
Oh yeah, I'll learn the trick now.
What? Louise?!
Keep your voice down!
I'm sorry.
Louise can't do that.
But that Baron Miscor took a liking in
Louise and wants her as his drinking partner.
You know what a humiliation that is.
Besides, leaving them alone is too dangerous.
You're right...
Maybe I'll go after all and try to...
I'll do it.
Just chatting with him and pouring him drinks, right?
It's easy.
What nonsense are you saying, Louise?
I've got to live on my own from now on.
This is nothing!
Louise...
Okay. I'll leave it to you then.
It's a sleeping potion with immediate effect.
Deal with him a little, and slip him this when you have a chance.
I-I'll be going now.
Will she be all right?
Let's have faith in her.
Enter.
I've been waiting for you.
Come close.
What's the matter?
I-It's such an honour to be chosen by you, so I'm a little nervous.
Is that so? How very cute of you.
Allow me to pour the wine for you.
You have a very dignified look.
It's a waste to leave you as a dancer.
You flatter me.
And to add to that,
those wonderful breasts!
That flatness turns me into a beast.
F-Fla-
I love flat boobs! I love them!
F-F-
Let me have a better look!
Please, don't stare at them like that.
Resist. I must resist.
All I have to do is drop the potion into the drink.
No way!
I-I'll be going now.
I don't have it!
Exactly! You don't have any, but that's what's good!
What is this?
So heavy...
What's the matter, Tiffa?
Illococoo-san fell asleep on the stage all of a sudden.
What? What's wrong with her?
I heard it is tiring for nature dragons to stay in human form.
She must be tired.
Onee-sama, you dance, too.
Let's let her sleep for a while.
Yes.
Saito-san, what's that bottle?
This?
I found it there.
Could that be...!
Come on. What's wrong with touching a
breast that you could hardly even call a breast?
Stop it, you pervert baron!
I can't have enough of this flat chest!
Let go of Louise!
Saito!
It looks like you guys are no ordinary travelling circus.
Don't even try.
Take another step and her head will be blown off.
Nau cid yisa waysarel.
Hagaraz yul beog.
Need is algees.
Bel kana man lagoo!
Saito!
Louise.
Saito.
Thank you, Tiffa.
It was nothing. You're welcome.
Don't go without your wand.
Well, I wanted to be of some use...
You're foolish to hide something in your breasts when you don't even have any cleavage to hide it in.
What?
What was I doing here?
Those are breasts to my liking!
I know! Mine are so flat that it's almost foolish!
I'm so sorry!
Having slain the dragon, Ivaldi made his way deeper into the cave where the room was.
There, Lu was shaking, clutching her knees.
Ivaldi reached out to Lu.
No hero will come for me.
No one will come...
Ivaldi...
Are these really all the soldiers?
Don't worry. Even if there are some around, I will-
What are you doing?
We have a guest!
Don't!
Kirche!
It's futile.
He's an elf!
He's the one that took Onee-sama away.
Give Onee-sama back to us!
You're that nature dragon.
You came all the way here to save her?
But I cannot let you have your way.
Spirits that live in the stones.
Here, I command you in the name of the ancient contract.
Strike those who stand in my way!
Don't underestimate us!
Get blown away!
All right!
Stop it!
Saito!
Saito-san!
Begone, warrior!
You stand no chance against me.
Saito, what was that?
I don't know.
It's like there's an invisible wall.
That was Counter.
A dirty nature magic that reflects all sorts of physical and magic attacks.
So there's nothing that works against him?
That's not true. You already know how to nullify nature magic.
Dispel, right?
Chant it, Louise.
I'll buy you the time!
Yeah.
Ful blisars ansul ken.
Gyofu need nousis.
Heilos iala
Damn it.
Elpeo Y's.
Cast the Dispel on me!
The devil's power?!
Wait, Saito-san!
Please, no more...
But he took Tabitha and attacked everyone!
Why is my kind with the devil's child?
My mother taught me.
Elves do not fight by choice.
I'm sure he has his reasons, too.
Even so...
Saito...
Louise.
We're here to save Tabitha.
If he's no longer in our way, there's no need for us to hurt him...
Louise-san!
Louise!
Damn it...
That girl is in the north tower.
The door is locked with the power of the spirits,
but I'll have it unlocked.
Louise!
Let me warn you of one thing.
Joseph, the King of Gallia, is a heartless man.
This won't end it.
Keep that in mind.
Tabitha.
Onee-sama!
Tabitha!
Everything's okay now.
Looks like Vitartial failed.
That was too easy for them.
But who cares. It was only the first act.
So you'll finally use it?
Yeah.
Let's play with this new toy a little.
Sigh...
It's impossible.
But...
kyuu ni senaka wo mukete kakedashita wa (Just love me)
急に背中を向けて 駆け出したわ
I suddenly turned my back on you and ran away
hoka no ko ni yasashiku shiteta kara yo
ほかの子に優しくしてたからよ
Because you've been so gentle to many other girls
Boy onegai oikakete yo
Boyお願い 追いかけてよ
Boy, please chase after me
ato ni wa hikenai kara
あとには引けないから
Because it won't be over after this
pun pun pun
I am so sorry
gomen to ienakute gomen ne
ゴメンと言えなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't say "I'm sorry", sorry ♥
shinjite iru no ni kuchibiru ga togaru
信じているのに くちびるが尖る
Even though I believe you, my lips are pouting
kawaiku narenakute gomen ne
可愛くなれなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't be cute, sorry ♥
kosame no furu machi tsukamaete
小雨の降る街 つかまえて
Catch me in the town where a drizzle is falling
furimuku kara nakanaori no chu o shite
振り向くから 仲直りのCHU～をして
Because I'll turn around and give you a make-up kiss
atsui ryouude no naka de
熱い両腕の中で
In your warm arms
Next Time
I feel so bad for myself.
I want to blow off all my worries and anxiety,
and yet I can't use any magic now!
Zero no Tsukaima. Princess no Rondo.
Wings of Freedom
Final episode: Wings of Freedom.
Keep your eyes only on me!
I won't forgive you if you look away.