You'll go no matter what?
Yeah.
Montmorency, I'm headed off to join the army now.
I want you to see me off with a smile.
A smile?
Even if you might die when you go off to war?
To die protecting one's country...
Is this not the most honourable death for an aristocrat?
Who cares about honour?!
If you die, we'll never see each other again!
Do you... care that much about me?
Of course.
Montmorency.
Guiche.
It looks like the army really is going to march into Albion.
They drafted all the boys in the academy.
It's rough being an aristocrat, eh?
Hold on...
If all the boys were drafted,
that leaves me as the sole remaining young male in the academy.
What are you imagining?
Hey, what's that?
A dragon?
He's so handsome!
Oh, my.
Montmorency?
Oh, you're still here?
D-Don't give me that...
My name is Julio Chesaré.
I am a transfer student from Romalia.
Pleased to meet you.
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君のそばにいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai ga bokura wo tameshitatte
どんな未来が僕らを試したって
No matter how the future tests us
kitto…
きっと…
I’m sure…
aa futari no unmei
ああ 二人の運命
Ah, it’s our destiny
meguriaeta no wa
巡り合えたのは
I was able to meet you
kimi no koe kikoeta kara
君の声 聞こえたから
Because I heard your voice
sou pinchi na dekigoto
そう ピンチな出来事
Yeah, even if crisis events
oshiyosete kite mo
押し寄せてきても
Press on at me
kimi to ireba norikoerareru
君といれば乗り越えられる
If I'm with you, then I can overcome them
tokimeki to makenki to
ときめきと負けん気と
Palpitations and competitive spirit
urahara de haraharasuru kedo
裏腹でハラハラするけど
Excite me on the contrary, but-
Stay with me
tada kimi o mamoritai yo
ただ 君を守りたいよ
I only want to protect you
tooi sekai de umareta futari da kedo
遠い世界で生まれた二人だけど
We were born in distant worlds
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君の側にいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai mo kibou ni kaeyou
どんな未来も希望に変えよう
Let’s change any future into hope
Forever
Sword of the Holy Man
As you can see,
the colour of a flame becomes fainter as its temperature rises.
Do you see?
There are several metals that cannot be processed without a hot flame.
They say he's a flamen from Romalia, so he isn't joining the military
Flamen?
Why come to a magic academy?
I don't know.
Who cares as long as he's handsome.
Damn it.
All the girls are looking at him.
Is the blondie that good?
Better than a dog I know.
Do you want to be popular that badly?
N-Not really.
How about you? Aren't you interested in him?
W-Why me?
Agnes?
Everyone, out to the field, now.
W-Who are you people?
Her Highness' Musketeer Force.
We have been stationed at this school in order to provide you with military drills.
Class is cancelled.
Cancelled?
Assemble in the field.
Everyone, please take your seats.
We are continuing the class.
Teacher, we are in the midst of war.
It is not a time to be holding classes.
It is because we are in a war that we must learn how foolish it is.
All the boys have joined the military,
but I would like you to not bring war onto this campus!
Silence!
I hate mages...
especially those who use fire.
Hate mages?
Do not interfere with my duties.
Out to the field!
Saito.
To attention!
We will now begin the training.
Hold on!
We're mages!
We don't need this kind of thing.
Let's practice practical magic, whether offensive or defensive.
Magic, eh?
Go ahead.
Defeat me using magic.
What is wrong?
Y-You're hurting me!
Can't you do anything once you get your wand taken away?
If I were an enemy, you would be dead.
L-Let go of me!
You never know what might happen in a real battle.
Even with a wand in your hand, you may not have enough time to cast your spell.
Listen.
These are the very basics.
Skills with which to protect yourself.
Begin!
Practice with us.
Hey, how about a private lesson with me?
I am sorry, but my partner has already been chosen.
So, who's your partner?
No way!
Miss Vallière.
Actually, may I call you Louise?
Well, come at me.
Come on.
Okay.
No, no, not like that.
O-Okay.
What, why Louise?
T-That snobby son of a...
Don't get so close to her!
What?!
Show me what you've got.
But I'm not a student at this school...
If the enemy were to come right now, would you not be fighting as well?
I can only use practical weapons well...
You can also defeat an enemy with a wooden sword.
Wait! Give me a sec!
Stop running away!
Boring fight.
Saito!
Saito.
Hey!
What do you think you're doing to my familiar?
Miss Vallière.
I saw him fight the other day, but...
...his level was beyond mine.
That's because he was holding Delflinger.
Delflinger?
My... sword.
Without a real sword or a practical weapon,
I can't use my skill as a familiar.
Oh, so your skill wasn't sharpened as a swordsman.
That's interesting.
Saito-kun.
May I ask you to fight with me?
You can use your Delf... whatever.
Why do I have to fight against you?
I am merely curious.
Curious?
I know.
What if the winner of the fight gets to kiss Louise?
What?
Wait, kiss? Stop making stuff up!
Aren't you a flamen?
Truth be told, in order to come to Tristain, I have temporarily returned to secular life,
so I am allowed to wield a sword as well.
Not to mention relations.
Back off! Don't touch Louise!
Saito.
I don't care if you're a flamen or whatever.
You're so snobby it bothers me.
If you want to fight or whatever, you got it.
Hey, hold on.
No, I'm doing it.
What are you getting all worked up for?
If you get serious, he'll die.
What? You're worried about him and not me?
That's not what I meant.
Now isn't the time to be creating trivial problems.
If you insist on fighting, use the wooden sword.
I won't allow you to use a real sword.
Fine.
We'll fight tomorrow morning using wooden swords.
Saito!
I am looking forward to it.
What do you want, calling me out here?
If it's a ridiculous request...
Please! Teach me how to fight with swords.
I've... never seriously learnt swordsmanship.
If it's a real weapon, I can use it the moment it's in my hands.
When I hold a sword, my body moves on its own.
It's the power of Gandalfr, the legendary familiar.
Gandalfr?
However...
I don't think that I should rely solely on that power.
If I were suddenly attacked like how the vice-captain did...
...and caught without a weapon,
that'd be the end of me.
With this war... there could be lots of danger ahead.
So, I can't protect Louise unless I become strong.
Louise?
So, you want me to teach you swordsmanship for the sake of protecting Miss Vallière?
Of course, I want to win tomorrow's fight, too.
I just can't bring myself to like that guy.
I don't like flashy guys, either.
But Saito, can you keep up with my training?
Saito-san?
I haven't seen him.
Don't lie to me! He isn't in our room, either.
You're hiding him, aren't you?
Where is he? Where did you hide him?
Don't tell me...
I am not hiding him!
Stand! There is no time to rest.
Ow!
At least you have the form.
By experiencing real battle, you must have picked up the basics.
Y-Yeah?
But form alone will not help you win.
Strike at the opponent's opening!
Your familiar?
If you're looking for Saito, I saw him in the backyard.
He was with the captain of the Musketeer Force.
By Captain, do you mean Agnes?
They were breathing hard and drenched in sweat together.
W-What's that supposed to mean?
Damn it...
Strike at the opening, she says...
But, where do I even find an opening?
Come to think of it, you said that you don't like mages who use fire...
You got something against them?
K-Keep your mouth shut.
There's my chance!
Good. That's the way.
O-Okay.
So it was true...
Huh? Louise?
It's your fault.
Not at all...
You stupid dog!
No!
Dirty dog!
Pervert dog!
What's wrong?
You look as though you were beaten all night long by a dragon in a jealous rage.
Well... that's actually what happened.
I do not mind calling off the fight.
I don't intend to run away.
Shall we get started, then?
Louise, is that kiss ready?
You bastard!
Go, go!
Good luck!
Saito! Don't lose!
Oh, you're rooting for Saito?
It's because whoever wins gets to kiss Louise.
I see. You can't bear to see Julio-sama kiss Louise.
I understand.
Hey, my partner's doing pretty well.
Can he win?
Nope, he'll lose.
The opponent's too strong.
He's quite a master.
Saito.
Are you really a flamen?
Do you want to kiss Louise that much?
You said you returned to secular life,
but didn't you really get kicked out for being a womaniser?
Now!
A plan to aggravate me, then striking during the opening?
What an amateur trick.
Saito-kun, not only do I want to kiss Louise,
I want to kiss you, too.
An opening!
I lost.
Sir Julio!
Saito, you jerk!
You did it. Are you hurt at all?
Nothing more than the wounds you gave me.
What kind of response was that?
Anyway, my partner wins.
Let him kiss you.
Do it, partner!
A chance to do so with permission!
W-What are you saying?!
But...
I don't want it.
Hey! What do you mean by that?
You want... to.. kiss me, right?
That's why you beat Julio, right?
I didn't win.
He lost on purpose.
With partner's current skill, there was no chance of winning.
That bastard...
He's fooling around with me!
Even then, you didn't have to refuse me in front of everyone.
That looked as if I... I was rejected.
Code name Zero.
Emergency call.
Come in.
Good job. Step outside.
Julio!
You bastard! What was the meaning of that battle?
I am interested in neither win nor loss.
I just wanted to know the strength of my team-mate.
Team-mate?
Exactly.
He is your team-mate.
Are you...
Princess!
Louise. Saito-san.
Thank you very much for the other day.
No, it was nothing.
Sorry for my familiar's rudeness.
Absolutely not.
Thanks to you two, I was saved.
And I'm sure he was, too.
I heard what happened to Prince Wales as well.
It was Albion's conspiracy after all, was it not?
Princess! Why is he here?
Like I said, I am your team-mate.
What's that supposed to mean?
Romalia's pope senses danger from Albion as well,
so he sent me to lend my hand to the Princess.
Both he and I wish to avoid the war.
But the situation is profound.
Louise, Saito-san, Julio-san.
And Agnes.
You are those upon whom I rely.
Yes, Your Highness!
So, in other words, you concentrated your force to this school.
What? You have something to say about that?
No, I'm just bothered by what Colbert-sensei said.
The "don't bring war onto the campus" thing?
Saito-san.
I have no intention of subjecting the school to the dangers of war.
I honestly want to borrow your strength for the sake of peace.
Will you cooperate?
I will.
I hope we'll get along well, Louise.
Hey! Stay away from Louise!
Louise! What are you blushing for?
I-I'm not blushing!
You are.
You're bright red.
Bright, bright red.
What? You're a dog, and you dare make fun of your master?
Stop calling me a dog!
Dog!
Everyone, I must start with an unfortunate piece of news.
Tristain's Queen, Henrietta, on her day of coronation,
has executed our King, Lord Cromwell.
What?!
Unforgivable!
Furthermore, in thirst for more blood, Henrietta is increasing her military forces in order to invade our country!
Sheffield... She was Lord Cromwell's secretary...
Now she's acting like the new King rather than a magistrate.
It is now time to show the true power of Albion.
We shall repel all the enemies that come,
However, when she stands before us,
we cannot object against her authority.
and execute the detestable Henrietta with our hands!
Who is she exactly?
Magistrate Sheffield!
Hurray!
Y-You stupid dog!
chanto koko ni ite watashi no chikaku de
ちゃんとココにいて! 私の近くで
Be right here! close to me
zutto watashi o itsumo itsumo mitsumete nasai
ずっと私をいつもいつも見つめてなさい
Always, always look at me at all times
yosomishiteta desho hoka no onna no ko
よそ見してたでしょっ 他の女の子
You looked away, didn’t you? At other girls
o-shiokisuru wa furari furari furachi na yatsu wa
お仕置きするわ　フラリフラリ不埒なヤツは
I’ll punish those who are wavering and insolent
Don't touch! kikanai kara ne iiwake wa
Don't touch! 聞かないからね　言い訳は
Don’t touch! Because I won’t listen to excuses
Touch me... tsukareta kara nee kata o kashite yo
Touch me… 疲れたから… ねぇ肩を貸してよ
Touch me… because I'm tired… Hey, lend me your shoulder
suki yo nante uso yo
スキよ　なんて嘘よ
I love you, it’s a lie
kirai sore mo uso da wa
キライ　それも嘘だわ
I hate you, that’s a lie, too
nai nai nai dame yo kanchigai
ないないない　ダメよ勘違い
Nay nay nay, it’s useless, it’s a misunderstanding
dakara suki yo nante iwanai
だから「スキよ」なんて言わない
So I won’t say, “I love you”
Non non non dokka e ittara
Non non non　どっかへ行ったら
Non non non, because I absolutely won’t forgive you
zettai ni yurusanai kara ne
絶対に　許さないからね!
If you go to somewhere else
datte
だって
But
honto wa dare yori soba ni itai no
ホントは誰より傍にいたいの
The truth is, I want to be by your side more than anyone else
ai no kusari de sanposhimasho
愛の鎖で　散歩しましょ!
Let’s go take a walk in chains of love!
I... to be honest...
...might love you...
Next Time
You dog!
If you do anything to Eléonore-oneesama or Cattleya-neesama, you won't stay alive.
Zero no Tsukaima. Futatsuki no Kishi.
The Vallière Sisters.
If you want to meet me again next week, then sit tightly and wait!
The Vallière Sisters