The battlefield is great.
I love the smell of humans burning.
I can only enjoy this during war.
Thank you for coming, Menville-dono.
I'd like to borrow your strength.
My unit is filled with wild ones.
What do you want us to do?
You heard how Tristain and Germania captured our port, right?
And you're telling me to repel them?
No, I don't expect you to burn five hundred ships.
I don't like the roundabout conversations.
Tell me the place I get to burn.
The Magic Academy.
The Magic Academy?
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君のそばにいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai ga bokura wo tameshitatte
どんな未来が僕らを試したって
No matter how the future tests us
kitto…
きっと…
I’m sure…
aa futari no unmei
ああ 二人の運命
Ah, it’s our destiny
meguriaeta no wa
巡り合えたのは
I was able to meet you
kimi no koe kikoeta kara
君の声 聞こえたから
Because I heard your voice
sou pinchi na dekigoto
そう ピンチな出来事
Yeah, even if crisis events
oshiyosete kite mo
押し寄せてきても
Press on at me
kimi to ireba norikoerareru
君といれば乗り越えられる
If I'm with you, then I can overcome them
tokimeki to makenki to
ときめきと負けん気と
Palpitations and competitive spirit
urahara de haraharasuru kedo
裏腹でハラハラするけど
Excite me on the contrary, but-
Stay with me
tada kimi o mamoritai yo
ただ 君を守りたいよ
I only want to protect you
tooi sekai de umareta futari da kedo
遠い世界で生まれた二人だけど
We were born in distant worlds
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君の側にいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai mo kibou ni kaeyou
どんな未来も希望に変えよう
Let’s change any future into hope
Forever
The Magic Academy's Crisis
It's so huge...
What's this?!
What? No!
Keep it down, will you?
Saito!
Let me out, now!
Who is this?!
Who do you think I am?!
Eléonore-oneesama!
And Saito?
Louise. I'll have you stay in here for a while.
Why, Onee-sama?
"Why"?
Because of what you had said.
Take aim!
Fire!
Focus on the target!
In a real battle, your target moves!
Yes, Sir!
They're so into it.
I can't imagine this is only training.
Everyone, stop!
Five minute break.
Agnes, did something happen?
You're quick to notice.
I'll soon be gone from here.
Our Queen will be heading to the front line.
She will leave in seven days.
We, the Musketeer Force, will be going to Albion to protect Her Highness.
We'll say farewell to this academy, too.
It's a shame I couldn't uncover the name of the person who razed Dungletale...
I'll go to the front line, too.
Front line?! What are you...?
I have to help the Princess.
I heard everything from this plebeian.
Saito!
Louise!
I cannot allow a daughter of the La Vallière family to go to war.
Besides, what good would come out of
your going when you can't use any magic?
It's okay! I'd definitely be of help!
Listen, Louise.
War isn't as simple as you think.
That's why I'm going.
I'm the only one who can protect the Princess.
Silence!
Until you change your mind, I will not let you out of here.
You can't do that!
I'll hold onto this.
You're being tyrannical, Onee-sama!
W-What?
L-Let me down!
Louise!
Saito!
Onee-sama!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Cool your head in here for a while.
Keep your eyes on Louise here.
Okay...
Saito, you're going to take Eléonore-oneesama's side?
I'm sorry, but I agree with your sister this time.
It's ridiculous for you to go to war.
Saito!
Miss Vallière.
Saito-kun's right.
Sensei...
Colbert-sensei. Please provide this impudent girl with guidance.
Excuse me.
You blockhead!
Your sister is worried about you.
Though I'm not good with magic, if it's for Her Highness, I could do anything.
I'll defeat the enemy forces, too!
Defeat the enemy?
In other words, you'll go and kill the enemy?
I didn't mean that...
"To fight for her Highness' sake."
"To defeat the enemy for the country's sake."
No matter how you phrase it, it's still murder!
Colbert-sensei...
I don't want my students to go through that experience.
Please don't say you'll go to war.
Sensei...
It isn't fun to assault a school if there are only kids there.
No, I heard there are only girls at the school right now.
Girls? That's great!
Let's capture them alive.
You're all so filthy.
It doesn't matter if they're women.
We'll bring death to them all.
What's wrong?
Nothing, I just thought I saw something move.
That was easy.
No way...
All right. Get moving as we planned.
Sir!
What do you want, Tabitha?
Outside...
It's not even light out yet...
...strange.
Sounds like it...
Captain!
Are you safe?
I'm fine.
Two came to our rooms, too.
We took care of them.
Looks like they're dogs from Albion.
Most likely.
Okay, armour up and follow me!
Sensei!
What's this?
I'll go check.
Saito-kun, you stay here and protect Miss Vallière.
Okay.
What... happened?
Captain! They have occupied the dormitory wing!
And the students?
They're assembling in the cafeteria...
...along with the faculty and staff.
Damn it, they have hostages in their hands...
Something isn't right.
What's going on outside?
Don't worry about it, go to bed.
I'll wake you up if something happens.
To come to the academy instead of the front line...
It looks like Albion's cornered.
Trying to be cynical, brat?
It all means nothing to me.
It's what my employer wants.
I see, you're only a mercenary who's moved by money.
Julio-kun, it's dangerous. Stop provoking him.
Let me say this.
As long as you don't do anything to hinder us,
we will not take your lives.
Rest assured.
Shut up!
Do you want to turn into ashes?
Then, shut it.
Hey, you guys.
What?
You want a hostage, right?
Can you make due with only myself?
I want you to release the students.
I'm sorry, but you won't do.
The country won't move for you.
How about me, then?
I'm the first-born daughter of the La Vallière family.
My father is an aristocrat with influence in this country.
There shouldn't be any problems.
I shall become a hostage as well,
so please release the students.
I like your spirit, but two isn't enough.
I need all of the students.
With the lives of all the aristocrats' daughters in danger,
Queen Henrietta will have to give us a thought.
Those inside the cafeteria, listen!
We are Her Highness' Musketeer Force!
We have you surrounded with my unit!
Release the hostages!
If you surrender, we won't kill you!
Musketeer Force, eh?
We have hostages in hand, though.
Those in the cafeteria!
No... Albionians!
What is it that you want?!
This isn't a political target, nor are there any weapons stored here.
This is only an academy of magic.
It exploded before the signal?
You guys stay on watch here!
Sir!
What was that?
An explosion?
Let's go, Saito!
No, Colbert-sensei told us to stay here.
I'm worried because he isn't coming back!
Give me back my wand.
Fine.
Here.
Let's see, Unlock was...
Whatever.
Blowing up the door, eh?
It opened, so what's the big deal?
Let's go.
Okay, okay, Master.
What a cheap tactic.
Henrietta's Musketeer Force!
Stop this futile resistance!
Only an academy of magic?!
Then why is your Musketeer Force stationed here?
To Tristain, this is a treasure chest filled with people of Tristain's future.
Right?
Maybe I'll kill one person to test that.
Who should it be?
You first.
I'll show them that we're serious.
Stop it!
Agnes!
So she's the captain?
How foolish.
You think you can beat me?
I will not lose to a coward who takes hostages!
Personally, I don't like taking hostages.
Rather than going through the trouble, I'd burn everything.
What?
I burned an entire village once before.
The sight of the fire engulfing everything was breathtaking!
That's what's great about war.
You're...
You're the...
You're the one who...
...burned...
...Dungletale...
It was you!
They must be from Albion.
Damn it, they took hostages.
Those cowards!
Yup, cowardly and unmerciful guys.
You guys sure took your time to show up, Vallière and Saito.
Kirche, Tabitha...
Oh, you're a survivor of that village?
You're one person I'll never forgive!
Die!
Looks like you're more skilled with swords than myself.
However...
You're only a plebeian in the end!
Now you're unarmed!
Take this!
Kirche, do you know how many of them there are?
I don't think there are too many of them.
However...
They're skilled.
Doesn't look too good...
We need to hurry and save them.
Shh... someone's here.
Everyone.
Colbert-sensei.
So you came here...
I looked all over for you.
Sensei, everyone's been taken hostage.
I know.
I just sent for reinforcements.
You guys get out of here now.
Reinforcements? They have to come all the way from the palace, don't they?
We've got to handle this.
We're up against professionals.
You won't be a match for them!
But what about everyone else?
We need to wait until the reinforcements arrive.
You all get out of here.
I don't need a coward.
If you want to run, then please do.
You can go.
So you're...
You were the captain!
Unfortunately, no.
What?
Unfortunately, I was not.
I was only the vice-captain at the time.
Flame Snake was the captain.
He was referred to as Enjya.
He's more cruel than myself,
and possessed a flame that burned everything.
What?
I'm in search of that man myself!
That man who inflicted a wound upon me...
...the Flame Snake!
I want to burn that man...!
That's all I wish for!
chanto koko ni ite watashi no chikaku de
ちゃんとココにいて! 私の近くで
Be right here! close to me
zutto watashi o itsumo itsumo mitsumete nasai
ずっと私をいつもいつも見つめてなさい
Always, always look at me at all times
yosomishiteta desho hoka no onna no ko
よそ見してたでしょっ 他の女の子
You looked away, didn’t you? At other girls
o-shiokisuru wa furari furari furachi na yatsu wa
お仕置きするわ　フラリフラリ不埒なヤツは
I’ll punish those who are wavering and insolent
Don't touch! kikanai kara ne iiwake wa
Don't touch! 聞かないからね　言い訳は
Don’t touch! Because I won’t listen to excuses
Touch me... tsukareta kara nee kata o kashite yo
Touch me… 疲れたから… ねぇ肩を貸してよ
Touch me… because I'm tired… Hey, lend me your shoulder
suki yo nante uso yo
スキよ　なんて嘘よ
I love you, it’s a lie
kirai sore mo uso da wa
キライ　それも嘘だわ
I hate you, that’s a lie, too
nai nai nai dame yo kanchigai
ないないない　ダメよ勘違い
Nay nay nay, it’s useless, it’s a misunderstanding
dakara suki yo nante iwanai
だから「スキよ」なんて言わない
So I won’t say, “I love you”
Non non non dokka e ittara
Non non non　どっかへ行ったら
Non non non, because I absolutely won’t forgive you
zettai ni yurusanai kara ne
絶対に　許さないからね!
If you go to somewhere else
datte
だって
But
honto wa dare yori soba ni itai no
ホントは誰より傍にいたいの
The truth is, I want to be by your side more than anyone else
ai no kusari de sanposhimasho
愛の鎖で　散歩しましょ!
Let’s go take a walk in chains of love!
Next Time
You dog!
We need to save everyone, fast!
What? Colbert-sensei is...?
He can't be!
Zero no Tsukaima. Futatsuki no Kishi.
The Flame of Atonement.
The Flame of Atonement
If you want to meet me again next week, then sit tightly and wait!