Hey, you guys!
How long will you keep hoarding the rent?
With this month, you owe 60,000 yen!
I'm sorry!
Don't apologise! Pay your rent!
Last time I came by,
you said you'd pay it this month for sure, didn't you?
Come on.
Out with it.
It's no good pretending you're asleep!
I won't leave until you pay it!
Um...
Even though this may not be too much,
please, accept the humble tears of this bird...
tatta ima hajimete kizuita
たった今 初めて気づいた
I just realised it for the first time
koi ni ochita no dana
恋に落ちたのだな～
That I had fallen in love~
nijyuuyo jikan kimi kimi kimi
24h キミ☆ キミ☆ キミ☆
Twenty-four hours a day thinking of you, you and nothing more than you!
ishiki sezaru o emasen
意識せざるをえません!
It's something I wasn't consciously aware of
nanka (nanka) itsumo to chigau
なんか (なんか) いつもと違う
Somehow (somehow) I'm feeling different from the usual
kimi to (futari) gikochinai kaiwa
キミと (二人) ぎこちない会話
With you (the two of us) and our dull chatter
masaka (ryouomoi) iya kataomoi
まさか (両思い) いや 片思い
Don't tell me (mutual love?) Nope, it's a one-sided crush
yabai shisen acchatta
やばい! 視線合っちゃった!
This is bad! Our gazes met!
nani nani kono doki doki
なになに?! このドキドキ?!
What, what? Why is my heart pounding like this?
shikoukairo guccha guccha konsen
思考回路 ぐっちゃぐっちゃ 混線・・・
Did a short circuit just make a mess out of my mind?
konna koto hajimete dayo
こんなこと 初めてだよ
This is my first time... feeling like this...
netsu demo aru no kana
熱でもあるのかな～
I wonder if I have a fever~
kyuutenchokka irasshatta koigokoro
急転直下 いらっしゃった 恋心
Suddenly and precipitately, love has arrived.
acchuuma kao hakka de makkakka
あっちゅうま 顔 発火で まっかっか
Instantly igniting my face into a bright red
ba ba baka na te ga furueruzo
バ・バ・バカな?! 手が震えるぞ
T-That's stupid?! My hands are shaking
kore ga zoku ni iu koi nano
これが 俗に言う 「恋」 なの?!
Is this really what they call "love"?
yayayacchatta kaiwa kami makuri
やややっちゃった 会話 噛みまくり
I-I did it! A conversation filled with stutters
kimazui chinmoku mamimumemo
気まずい沈黙 マミムメモ
This awkward silence... *mumble mumble*
kimi no (kimi no) kimochi shiritai yo
キミの (キミの) 気持ち 知りたいよ
Your... (Your...) I want to know your feelings.
kakakata kataomoi
カカカタ☆カタオモイ
O-One-sided love
hatsukoi itsumo no tsuugakuro
初恋! いつもの通学路
First love! The usual way to school
pika pika hikaru I do fall in love
ピカピカ光る I do fall in love!
The shining light. I do fall in love!
sora mo tobesou sa
空も飛べそうさ
I feel I could fly towards the sky
kakakata kataomoi
カカカタ☆カタオモイ
O-One-sided love
Number 1, Honduras Slider Turtle.
Number 2, Modern Ornate Box Turtle.
Number 3, Worrell's Neck-folding Turtle.
Number 2.
The answer is...
Number 3. Everyone is correct.
Shut up.
Oh, you're still awake?
Are you over your cold?
Then go back to school tomorrow.
You've got a test coming up, don't you?
All right.
You've been out for three days, so be sure to ask your
friends what you missed and what will be on the test.
You know, you didn't even get a good mark on the last test.
Are you listening?!
Man, you're annoying, Mum.
Besides, finals are-
Tomorrow!?
Not A Winner
Nichijou 44
Hey, it's too late!
Your warning is too late!
But you've been stuck in bed and unable to study, haven't you?
I studied!
I studied while I was asleep!
You studied?
I didn't study!
Which is it?!
You warned me too late, so I didn't!
Would you have studied If I warned you earlier?
I wouldn't!
If you get a failing grade, I'll kill you.
That's too radical!
This is super-ultra-great-delicious-wonderful bad.
Anyway, I've got no choice but to do it!
I have approximately ten hours left until school.
Finals Day Schedule
Day 1
English
Music
Day 2
Health & P.E.
Day 3
Language Arts
Maths
Science
History
Luckily, tomorrow's tests are in English and Music!
That means I can focus on English.
What I need to do is say goodbye to the degenerate person I was up to now and concentrate.
So that I make it through today without regrets,
and make it through tomorrow laughing.
Even if there were tears shed yesterday.
Even if I'm knocked flat many times.
I will not give up,
because I always want to have a smile...
...I will aim the boat floating on the distant sea...
...towards the distant light, and keep running.
Simply straight ahead, simply straight ahead,
and break free from the chains.
By Yukko.
All right.
I'm finished...
...with a poem.
Things you think are cool!
It's nothing special.
A shop worker's embarrassed smile!
I'll take a risk.
Since I don't know what will be on the English test,
I have no choice but to take a gamble!
I will do this by studying only English vocabulary words!
Attempt: to try.
Love: my feelings have.
Always: always been apart.
Confirmation: your love will.
Teleportation: leap through time.
And so...
Cosmos: pass through the sky.
Midnight submarine: I want to be with you.
Forever: for eternity.
Forever: with you.
Forever: always.
I'm finished...
...with a poem!
I understand, I understand!
It's impossible to study at this point!
Ah, it's no good. I'll be killed by mum.
Why did I have to get over my cold today?
If I'm gonna die anyway, I'd prefer it to be from a cold!
At least for three more days...
And then...
This is my perfect mission.
Yes.
If I don't want to take the test, I'll just get sick again!
This is painful.
But still, if I get in an ice-cold bathtub after just getting better from a cold,
I'll definitely catch it again!
Come on, come on!
That's perfect!
I can't give up here!
I must endure!
The path will be opened!
This is how you get a fever.
Eating shaved ice after getting out of the bath.
Turning the room's air condition up to max.
Saying goodnight without getting under the covers.
I am completely healthy!
Yukko!
Wake up!
It's come to this.
Thermometer! Plus match! Equals temperature!
Are you up?
It's time to go to school, isn't it?
Good heavens!
Yukko.
Hot! Hot! Hot!
What are you doing?
I got a f-fever!
I caught the cold again!
How high is it?
E-Eighty-eight point eight degrees.
What have you broken?!
No!
It's a cold!
You seem lively and healthy enough.
Daiku Power
Thanks.
I didn't realise today was the deadline for club applications.
We were close to getting disbanded.
But even though you turned in the application, at this rate,
you're going to get disbanded for having too few members.
That's not a worry.
Anyway, I'll treat you to some juice tomorrow as thanks.
You don't need to do that.
Don't hold back.
See you.
We need to stop and buy a mixer and an apple orchard on the way home.
All right.
So that's the power of the Daiku Corporation?
Nichijou 45
I don't have any string.
I can't make a voodoo doll to put in the principal's shoebox like this.
Wait.
I don't even have the always important straw,
and I don't have any money to go buy some,
Wife Away At School Reunion
and my wife's not here to give me money.
I'm hungry, but I don't have any rice left.
At times like this, I want to drown myself in brandy.
But...
Liver
Duodenum
Pancreas
Hepatic Portal
Gall Bladder
Common
Bile Duct
Bile
Duct
I've already screwed up my liver.
Hanshin lost.
I don't really know why, but when I bought a cheeseburger, there wasn't any cheese on it.
I got the special visitor number on my own website.
Huge Chat Meeting Tonight At 19:00
And nobody came to the huge chat meeting I held last night.
Chat Participants
People
Nobody coming reminds me...
When I got on the bus yesterday, everyone got off.
Everyone getting off reminds me...
School Trip Photo Album
Tour of Kamakura Houses
Name: Oora Kousuke
When I went on a school trip in high school...
Two minutes after the lights were out, I asked,
"Are you guys awake?".
But everyone was asleep.
Then, being asleep reminds me...
I've been having insomnia lately.
I eat just before I try to force myself to sleep,
but then I get heartburn.
Food reminds me...
The present I got for my birthday last month...
...was...
...a butter roll.
Stop, stop!
I have to get over these pessimistic thoughts!
I should think about something more fun.
Who is it?
Yes?
Oh!
Kimiko, huh?
Mum's on vacation, isn't she?
I thought I'd come make you a meal.
Oh, that would be great.
Hello.
Yes, hello.
You've gotten big, haven't you, Mii-chan?
That's it.
I should spend all day just playing with my
grandson without worrying about anything else.
Also, also...
Earlier, I made a dumpling in the park.
You can eat it.
This is...
You're hungry, so you can eat it.
Mii-chan...
It's made entirely of chocolate, so go ahead and eat it.
I see. I see.
Thank you.
What are you crying for?
You're moved to tears too easily, Father.
Well, I'll be in the kitchen.
All right.
That's right.
Life isn't full of only bad things.
There are also good things like this.
It's all chocolate, so hurry up and eat it.
Come on. Come on.
Hurry up and eat it.
It's delicious, so hurry!
But, this is...
Hurry!
Come on. Hurry!
Right this minute! It's delicious!
I'm sure...
...that happiness tastes like mud.
Mum, gramps collapsed.
Word Of The Day
Here. Sorry for the wait.
It's always best to deal with things peacefully.
Nichijou 46
Are you trying to kill me?
It's complete!
What?
Super Glue!
It's... really big.
Because it's super!
If I spread this on the floor,
Nano and Sakamoto will be unable to move!
You're doing something strange again.
Who would fall for such an obvious trap?
I got you!
You didn't get me yet!
Hey, hurry and get me out of here!
I have plans after this!
You can get out if you put water on it.
Then hurry and get some water!
It's time for snacks.
Listen to me!
Well, the professor is going to go eat snacks.
Excuse me.
Hey.
What are you going to do about this?
This is terrible.
You look like you're stuck in a cockroach trap.
Don't laugh!
You're in the same situation!
Take a look!
That's divine punishment!
That's strange...
You're always playing pran-
Sakamoto, what should we do?
Huh, Sakamoto's gone.
Sakamoto?
Sakamoto!
We can't get out without water.
I won't be able to eat snacks like this.
I might get hungry while I'm here.
I won't be able to eat, so I might die!
I might die!
I might die.
I'm home!
It's Nano!
It's really hot, isn't it?
I heard it's 35 degrees outsi-
What are you doing?
You see, I was spreading glue and got stuck!
You need to put water on it.
I got all stuck, and you need to put water on it, Nano! Nano!
Huh? Water?
Yes!
Before that, get up, please.
If you lie around in the hallway, your clothes will get dirt-
Hey, what is this?!
Hey, my hand!
What the heck is this?!
My hand, my hand!
Participating
in the
Prefectural
Tournament
Aim for
#1 in Japan!
Congrats!
Go Soccer Club Participa
Money
President.
This is the power of the Daiku Corporation.
A Small Miracle
Next one is Sakamoto
Guess who!
Is...
Is it the Professor?
Correct!
Did you know?
No, it was kind of obvious.
You're the only one here.
Then, it's your turn, Nano.
Guess who!
It's Nano!
The Shinonome household was at peace again today.
Hey, Nano, was I right?
Yes, you were.
Then, then, next, it's my turn.
Nichijou 47
This is bad.
This is bad!
I'm completely lost from the very first question!
Write the English vocabulary word
that each picture represents.
What the heck is this thing that looks like it'd vanish pretty easily, anyway?
What kind of vocabulary word would describe that?
Wait.
This question...
I've done it before.
What was it?
I asked Sakurai-sensei about it.
I'm sure...
What is this?
Did you draw this thing that looks like it'd vanish pretty easily, Sensei?
This thing that looks like it'd vanish pretty easily...
That's it!
Something that looks like it'd vanish pretty easily!
Wait! That's not it!
Just calm down!
Calm down, Yukko!
If you get too worked up, even things that you know will confuse you!
Anyway, it's flying, so...
Was it "fly"?
The impact of the character is too strong, though.
What is this monster?
Monster?
This is no longer an English test...
It's Logic!
But this all I can do for now!
Anyway, next question.
The same monster is holding a tennis racket!
Meaning the first question wasn't "monster"!
What is this strange trap?!
I'll erase the first answer and re-think it.
My eraser!
Nothing human life!
What am I supposed to do?!
I've got no other choice but to rub it out with spit!
M-Mai-chan.
In the end, you can truly depend on your friends!
Of course! It's a pen eraser!
It'll rip!
If I use this, the paper will rip!
Wait. Now is not the time to panic!
Mai-chan! Give me a normal era-
Oh! She's asleep!
Ten minutes left!
Time!
I'm running out of time!
Anyway, calm down.
Yes, calm down.
And clear...
...your mind.
Clear.
All right, the test is over.
Good heavens!
It's raining.
In my heart.
asa okite hao migai te
朝起きて 歯を磨いて
Woke up in the morning, brushed my teeth
attoiuma gogo juu ji
あっという間 午後10時
In the blink of an eye, it's 10pm
kyou mo takusan waratta naa
今日も たくさん 笑ったなぁ
Today, we laughed a whole lot
takusan tokimeita naa
たくさん ときめいたなぁ
We had a great time
tomodachi to baka mitai ni sawai deru toki ni mo
友達と バカみたいに騒いでる 時にも
At times, with my friends, acting like fools, being noisy
chirachiratte me ga au
チラチラって 目が合う
Fluttering, our eyes met.
guuzen dayo ne
…偶然、だよね。
It's a coincidence, right?
hatsukoi nante ie nai
初恋なんて言えない
I wouldn't call this my first love
kyara janai n da mon
キャラじゃないんだもんっ!
It's not my character.
nee ashita mo aeru yo ne
ねえ あしたも会えるよね?
Say, will we be able to meet again tomorrow?
mabuta o tojiru to
まぶたを 閉じると
As my eyelids close
kirakira kimi darake
キラキラ キミだらけ
I see you sparkling all over the place
kyou mo tanoshikatta ne
今日も 楽しかったね
Today was fun, too, wasn't it?
aa koi shite n da naa
あー 恋 してんだなぁ
I'm in love~
ureshii na ureshii na
うれしいな うれしいな
So happy, so happy
hajimemashite koi gokoro
はじめまして こいごころ
It is my pleasure to meet you, my new-found love.
ashita mata aeru ne
あした また あえるね
Surely, we'll meet again tomorrow~
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
Have a good night
yume de sugu aeru ne
ゆめで すぐ あえるね
We'll meet immediately in our dreams
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
So have a good night
Open
Good morning!
Good morning.
No way!
There was a love letter!
Who's it from?!
It says Tanaka from class Q!
All right, let's go take a look!
I'm mud.
I'm a metal sphere!
I sleep like mud.
I get hit while heated up.
Narration:     Shiraishi Fuyumi
Next time on Nichijou is episode 12.
Look forward to it!