Wasn't Sasahara-kun sleeping?
He definitely was!
He was crossing his arms and not moving an inch!
Misato, go wake him up!
Sasahara-kun probably forgot that it's time to change classes.
Well, so what?
Just let him be.
That's not right.
You guys are childhood friends.
You should go wake him up!
And I think Sasahara-kun is alone in the room right now.
Wha...
Well, I'm going ahead.
Good luck!
Hey!
Geez!
Why do I have to do something like this?
Just because we're childhood friends...
Why don't you confess to Sasahara-san?
jou jou yuu jou banjin maji kaichou
じょーじょーゆーじょー万事マジ快調
Amazing friendship, the absolute best!
na na na na na na na
ななななななな
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
hai! icchaimashou!
ハイ!言っちゃいましょう!
All right! I'll say it!
kimi wa best best friend
キミはベストベスト フレンド
You are my best, best friend!
(furai!) chotto fuzakete mitara
(フライ!) ちょっとふざけてみたら
(Fly!) When I joke around a bit,
(shain!) motto fuzake kaeshite kuru
(シャイン!) もっとふざけ帰してくる
(Shine!) You joke around more in response.
(La La La) ikogochi ii ttara arya shinai
(ラーラーラー)居心地良いったらありゃしない
(La La La) Nothing is better than this!
(wai!) iya na koto attatte
(ワイ!) 嫌なことあったって
(Why!) Even if something bad happens,
(fain!) sokkou wasurechaunda
(ファイン!) 即効忘れちゃうんだー
(Fine!) I immediately forget about it!
(La La La)
(ラーラーラー)
itsudatte jan jan yarimasho
いつだって、じゃんじゃんやりましょ♪
Always keep it going!
24 jikan issho demo mondai nai
２４時間一緒でも問題ない
Being together 24 hours a day isn't a problem.
marude futago ka oyako ka clone saibou
まるで双子か親子かクローン細胞
Just like twins, or a parent and child, or clone cyborgs.
kore ja me ga sumu hitsuyou wa nakunakunai!?
これじゃ目が澄む必要はなくなくない!？
Then isn't there no reason to clear your eyes?
sore to kore to wa mattaku mattaku betsumondai
それとこれとは まったくまったく 別問題
Those are completely, completely different issues.
(faito!) kenka shichatta toki mo
(ファイト!)喧嘩しちゃった時も
(Fight!) Even when I get in a fight with you,
(daoun!) kanari hekonda toki mo
(ダウン!)かなり凹んだ時も
(Down!) even when I get really down,
(shai!) hitori de itai you na toki mo
(シャイ!)一人で居たいような時も
(Shy!) even when I feel like I want to be alone,
futokizukeba chikaku ni iru shinaba morotomo
ふと気付けば 近くに居る 死なば諸共
before I realise it, you're right there; we'll be together even in death!
nande daro
なんでだろ
I wonder why it is.
soba ni itainda
そばに居たいんだ
I want to be with you.
kimi to issho nara
君と一緒なら
When I'm with you,
tokei hyakubai soku
時計百倍速
time goes 100 times faster!
tanoshii na
楽しいな
It's fun, isn't it?
tanoshisugirunda
楽しすぎるんだ
It's way too fun!
sasuga saikou friend
流石 最高 friend
As expected of my best friend!
Hey! na na na na na na na
Hey! ななななななな
Hey! Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
nannanoyo
なんなのよー
What is it?
yabai synchro
ヤバいシンクロー
The synchro is amazing!
itsumo oosawagi
いつも大騒ぎ
Always making an uproar,
kanari gokinjo meiwaku
かなりご近所迷惑
bothering the neighbours a lot.
ima nanji
今何時
What time is it now?
ato ne yorereihifu
あとねヨレレイヒーフ
And then yo de le hi hoo!
wake wakannainai
訳分かんないない!
I don't get it at all!
soredoshira
ソレドシラ
So re doh si la!
souzou ijou nante iu ka saiko
想像以上なんて言うか最高
It's better than I imagined, the absolute best!
aa da kou da ittetemo tomodachi (wasshoi!)
あーだこーだ言ってても友達 (わっしょい!)
Even if I say this and that, we're still friends. (Hooray!)
jou jou yuu jou banjin maji kaichou
じょーじょーゆーじょー万事マジ快調
Amazing friendship, the absolute best!
cha cha la cha la cha cha
ちゃちゃらちゃらちゃちゃー
Cha Cha La Cha La Cha Cha!
Sasahara!
Why are you sleeping when there's a classroom change?
Tachibana Misato?
Just get your textbooks ready!
That's right, I was just planning to rest my eyes.
It seems I went too far.
Hurry up already!
People might get weird ideas if we're late together!
Weird ideas?
About what?
Shut up!
Nichijou 106
I didn't mean to!
I mean, I didn't realise they were there!
It's because you weren't hurrying up!
Tachibana Misato.
Your hand is bleeding.
What's with you being a nice guy?
You should be angry at the fact that I broke your glasses.
No worries.
It doesn't hurt when my glasses are broken.
A hand injury does hurt, though.
What do you mean?
Of course it hurts!
You think you said something clever?
Besides, the other lens is still there.
It's just like a warrior with a long history of service.
That warrior is pretty frail.
Pretty frail.
Let's go.
Tachibana.
I know!
I already know that I'm at fault!
Walk or Don't
Actually, I don't think it's working out so well...
That's right!
And then...
They're looking at me!
I'm gonna die!
I'm gonna die from embarrassment!
But I broke his glasses,
so I need to become Sasahara's eyes.
It's all right!
If we just say he broke his glasses,
it'll look like I'm just helping out!
Yeah!
I'm getting in the volunteer spirit...
...and becoming your eyes for the day!
Tachibana Misato.
Yes?
Before we arrive at the classroom,
I would like to go to the restroom.
Restroom?
You mean the men's restroom?
That very one.
A sudden roadblock...
But since it's my fault,
I need to get over this block...
Got it!
I'll go in with you!
Why?
Well, that's because your glasses are broken!
And?
Geez. You're so thick-headed!
Since you can't see anything, I'm becoming your eyes for the day!
These are just fakes.
What are you mistaking?!
I was just shooing off the bug that was pestering your arm!
Today is a beautiful day.
I-I know of a restaurant in Kamakura that has really hot curry!
Curry
I see!
How much spice can you tolerate when it comes to curry?
Um, well...
Zero tolerance.
Same here!
Nichijou 107
Um, Naganohara-san...
Class is about to...
Hey, Mio-chan!
Our next class isn't that way!
Our next class...
And besides,
you never know what's going to happen in baseball!
That's what makes it fun!
You never know what's going to happen in baseball.
Besides, you don't even know for sure that she's his girlfriend!
Hey, Nano-chan!
What?
Yes!
Of course!
Sasahara-senpai was...
Senpai was...
Senpai...
Anyway, let's just go back!
Mio-chan!
Naganohara-san!
Nano-chan,
get to the next class and somehow explain to the teacher!
Got it!
Mio-chan, wait!
Mio-chan!
You're going to crash!
M-Mio-chan!
Mio-chan!
Mio-chan...
This is my stop.
Mio-chan!
M-Mio-chan...
M-Mio-chan!
Mio-chan!
Damn it!
Chan-mio!
T-Thanks...
Mio-chan!
Mio-chan, are you all right?
I'm kinda...
...tired.
Mio-chan.
Where is he?
Over here!
Maa-chan!
Osamu...
Thank god you're okay!
Are you okay?
Somehow...
This person saved me...
You guys!
You're from that time...
You know, that's known as obstruction of justice,
and it's a serious crime!
Me, too?
I would normally have to call the school...
Considering what just happened, I'll let it go.
Really?
Finally!
I finally found you, pig-tailed girl.
I was surprised at your shadow boxing earlier.
Would you like to take on the world with boxing?
Don't think badly of me!
Well, I'm off now!
Make sure to come to me later!
We need to fill out some stuff!
Onee-chan, I want you to have this.
O-Okay.
Osamu, it's okay, right?
Of course!
Anyway, after you calm down, drop by our gym.
We'll continue talking about it there.
I just noticed, but your English textbook is missing!
Mio-chan?
Being rejected before even asking him out,
saving a child while on a full-out rampage,
getting awards and medals,
and getting scouted as a boxer.
You really don't know what's going to happen.
It's exactly like you said, Yukko.
Huh?
You really never know what's going to happen.
That's why it's interesting!
That's what baseball is, right?
What do you mean?
See?
Word Of The Day
I've realised that...
...fantasising is free.
Damn, I completely lost sight of her.
Nichijou 108
I was watching her ever since she left school,
but as soon as I took my eyes off her,
she completely vanished...
What an amazing feature.
It makes me want to find out your secrets even more.
Shinonome Nano.
Well, since I've come this far,
should I see if I can find a house that looks like it might be hers?
But that might be dangerous...
I guess I'll call it a day...
...and retreat for now.
Shinonome Institute
It's completely obvious!
I found it so suddenly!
Ever since project "Acquire Shinonome Nano" started,
this could be the luckiest breakthrough.
I can't describe this with just "lucky".
It's more like...
Uh...
Well...
Um...
Whatever.
This really fires me up.
I just want to go in and see the laboratory.
I want to see the person who made Shinonome.
I want to steal the blueprints!
With this climax, my heart is having a stampede!
Calm down, my cowboy!
Bill Watt!
Since it's the person who created Shinonome,
I don't know what kind of traps there'll be.
I shouldn't get too courageous.
I'll just end with peeking today.
Is there something you need?
What?!
Crap, a patrol robot already found me!
It looks pretty cheap,
but it was probably made by the same skilled person that made Shinonome.
I have no idea what might happen if something goes wrong.
For now, I need to raise a white flag.
Nakamura-sensei.
Apparently you carried an injured lady, on your goat, all the way to the hospital.
Just as you say.
Could it be that you attend our school on your goat thinking ahead in the case something like this happened?
Don't tell me such a bad joke.
Now you were supposed to say "well said".
Here you go.
I was caught by surprise.
Because of that, I was able to gain entry,
but I shouldn't forget about my objective.
I think it's best to assume that there's a trap.
For example, this tea.
It's perfectly sane to think that there's a drug in it that erases your memories.
There's probably a camera watching me from somewhere in this roo-
W-What is that?!
There has to be something wrong with that.
It feels like I'm in danger with that thing in my sight...
If I make one wrong move,
I'll be taken out!
Is there something wrong?
Oh sorry, there's nothing wrong!
I drank it.
What have I done?
Was it too hot?
If I'm going to be taken out...
I shall say it directly.
Oh, yes!
I came here to get to know you much more deeply!
If I can, I want to see the real you.
Can I?
Well, it's completely up to personal preference,
but I don't think it's normal for two girls to have that kind of relationship,
and I think it's best to be normal for that!
Stupid, no!
Completely wrong!
What are you thinking about?
You're so embarrassing!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
What I want to know more deeply is...
Nano...
Professor.
Nano, we ran out of snacks.
Did she just say "Professor"?
No way. I must have misheard it!
Just leave it until tomorrow.
I can't imagine this kid making Shinonome.
Who is this person?
Is this person a relative of Shinonome?
This is Nakamura-sensei from our school.
Possibly a younger sister?
Does that mean this kid is also a robot?
Hello, I'm the professor.
I made Nano.
Shoulder Block!
Professor!
Made?
Why did you say that?!
This kid made Shinonome?
It's just a greeting.
Hey!
Do something about this!
The kid did something again!
A homunculus?!
The patrol robot outside,
the creepy doll thing,
the child professor,
Shinonome Nano...
...and now a homunculus?
I'll admit that it was a mistake to come here unprepared,
but this is just insane.
Professor, what kind of knot did you use?
I need to escape and rethink my plan!
The impossible knot.
It isn't coming off yet?
But...
I'm terrified that thing is going to come attack me,
so I can't move recklessly...
If I politely ask to leave...
Then...
So it comes to this...
May I go to the washroom?
Oh sure.
Well, I-
Wait.
If you just tell me the location, I can go there alone.
So in the end, you fell for it, Shinonome Nano.
My escape was a success.
I knew you would believe what I told you.
That's right.
Your weakness is your kindness towards people.
Next time we meet, I'll be the one putting up attacks.
As long as that weakness doesn't go away,
I'll be back as many times as it takes!
Are you on your way home?
Crap!
N-No, I was just asked to trim the lawn.
Wha?!
Oh, hold on for a moment!
Oh no, I was caught!
They completely saw through the fact that I was trying to escape.
Geez.
What is this?
The freedom of my body!
Over here.
Wasn't she going to the toilet?
Huh?!
What is this?!
Professor!
This glue comes off with water, right?
If I get caught now, everything will be finished.
What?
Water!
My hopes, my dreams!
What?
Crap, I need to do something about this situation...
I can't hear you...
Curse you, Shinonome Institute!
Water, water!
First of all, someone...
...someone, help me!
Oh, I have that!
Really?
Could I borrow it, then?
Sure.
I'll bring it next time.
You really never know what's going to happen.
That's what baseball is.
Is that it?
She started laughing and became cheerful.
Maybe she's just forcing herself to act cheerful.
She was denied by her long-admired senpai.
It's certainly possible to see it that way.
Are you sure?
Yukko, did you forget your homework again?
No, that's not it!
But the part about forgetting homework is true.
Geez. Make up your mind...
The answer will be given after the commercial break!
Huh?
That's hilarious, Aioi-san!
Right, Minakami-san?
Flemming?
Rap?
Naganohara-san,
I actually have another favour...
What is it?
Aioi-san, isn't there anything?
A way to cheer up Naganohara-san...
I wonder why they went home...
I was going to go eat something with them...
What are you doing?!
Congratulations!
Go ahead and give it a spin!
What are you doing? You're Yukko, aren't you?
Huh? Who is that?
It's as clear as glass...
I can see Nano-chan's key, too...
This is nothing related to robots!
Either way, it's a rule that people who pass here must do this!
Come on!
What?
Geez.
I don't get it...
I just have to spin it?
Congratulations!
Geez. That's loud.
Here, a special prize!
What is this?
Just accept it!
I always say that these things you do aren't very fun...
Well, now that you've received it, off you go!
Thank you!
Bonus prize.
Thanks.
I remember Sasahara-senpai saying something like this...
The daily life that we live is possibly...
...a string of miracles.
I think... No, I'm sure it must be like that.
Voucher to stay
friends for all eternity
Aioi
Shinonome
Minakami
All right!
I'll go home and draw some manga!
明日を探そう　この広い世界で
ashita wo sagasou, kono hiroi sekai de
Let's search for tomorrow within this vast world
今こそその時　さあ　みんなで旅立とう
ima koso sono toki, saa, minna de tabi datou
Right now is the time, so let's all set out on a journey
明日への　限りない期待ふくらませて
ashita e no kagirinai kitai fukuramasete
The expectations for tomorrow swell infinitely
僕たちのすばらしい希望と夢を
bokutachi no subarashii kibou to yume wo
To hold our amazing hopes and dreams
Let's search for tomorrow,
Search for tomorrow,
この広い世界で
kono hiroi sekai de
Within this vast world
この広い世界で
kono hiroi sekai de
Within this vast world
Love-Like
Damn it...
Thanks to you, we got lost!
Sorry about that.
Let's find our way with my mobile telephone.
What's with that?
Just call it a cellphone!
Hey, why are you watching 1seg?!
TL Note: 1seg = Mobile TV
Don't you watch 1seg, too, Tachibana Misato?
Mine is a NoSeg!
I'm Nano-chan's key!
Sometimes I turn!
Sometimes I don't!
Sometimes I come off!
Those are my days!
The next episode of Nichijou is the last one!
Narration:     Yokozawa Keiko
Look forward to it!