I'm sorry for the blunder I've committed.
It's all right.
You're not responsible for anything, Agnes.
Everything was my...
Your Highness.
The ship has been seized, and we are currently searching for the crew throughout the city.
We will find them in no time.
Excuse me.
Agnes.
Yes?
Do not hurt them.
Ma'am!
Have you found them?! Keep searching!
Nothing over here!
Looks like quite the commotion.
Has there been a break-in or something?
I'm so scared.
Um.
No! Don't hurt me! If you must, do it gently!
Hey, wait. Scarron-san!
Hello.
Oh, it's you guys.
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
mejirushi no nai michi mo heiki sa futari nara
メジルシのない道も平気さ　ふたりなら
Even on a road without signs, I'll be fine, if we're together
saki no mienai tabi mayoinagara mitsuketa yo
先の見えない旅　迷いながら見つけたよ
On a journey that I can't see ahead of, while I was lost, I found it
boku no iru basho kimi no tonari
僕の居る場所　君のとなり
That my place to be is next to you
kenkashite nando mo hanashita sono te
喧嘩して　何度も離したその手
When we quarrelled, I let go of your hand again and again
hikiyose dakitai ima
引き寄せ抱きたい　今
I want to pull close and hold it now
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
namida no ame ni utaretara
涙の雨に打たれたら
If I'm beaten down by the rain of tears
I wanna hold you sugu yobi na yo boku no namae
I wanna hold you　すぐ呼びなよ　僕の名前
I wanna hold you, call my name immediately
dakishime ni yuku wa
抱きしめに行くわ
I'll go embrace you
kanashimi mo tsuyogari mo kono te ni uketomeru
悲しみも強がりもこの手に　受け止める
I'll accept sadness and bluffing in my hands
The Path to the Border
Don't worry. You weren't followed.
I had no idea that you were all being held in the castle.
To give up the status of an aristocrat just to help a friend?
It's so idiotic that I could expect it only from you guys.
We managed to get out, but what's our plan from here on?
Yeah. The city's crawling with guards.
It won't be easy getting out of here.
We'll walk to Gallia.
Colbert-sensei?
Everyone, take a look at this map.
I'll first fly the Ostland to Germania, in the opposite direction of Gallia.
The military will think we're going to enter Gallia via Germania, so they'll come after me.
And that's when we take the chance to walk into Gallia.
Yes. Head over to the former territory of Orléans.
That is where Miss Tabitha's residence is.
We might find some clues there, is that the idea?
I'm sure we'll find something.
Yes.
Hold on!
Are you guys thinking of going all the way to Gallian Kingdom?
If you disobey the Queen that much, that will be a serious felony.
Not only will they take your titles away,
but you might experience something even worse.
I-I wouldn't want that.
Even so...
We still have to go!
Yeah. Since Tabitha's our friend.
She's my dear sister!
She's my best friend.
You can never find a cure for idiots.
Oh fine.
Jessica, give me a hand.
But Sensei, to use the Ostland as a distraction,
we need to go back to the castle.
Yeah. By the timing of the escape,
it's obvious the Ostland assisted in it.
I'm sure guards have been stationed on it.
Then what do we do?
Leave the Ostland to me. You should all make haste to Gallia.
Jean! Are you serious about that?
I can't put you in such danger alone!
He's right. We can't do that!
Use your heads.
The one in greatest danger now is Miss Tabitha.
We don't have time to lose by arguing.
Okay.
Sensei!
I'm coming with you!
I think we can help with manoeuvring the Ostland.
I'm sure we'll be of use.
Thank you.
I'll go anywhere with you, Saito-san.
After all, I am your personal maid.
Siesta...
Hey! Saito is no longer a chevalier,
so he doesn't need a personal maid!
Being a chevalier has nothing to do with this!
You're no longer an aristocrat either.
So I don't want to hear a plebeian boss me around.
Hey, both of you. Calm down.
It's not the time to argue over thing like this.
Shut up!
First of all, what are you thinking?!
Um...
Yes! You make the choice!
I'm amazed how they can keep going with that.
I'm so jealous of him.
Hey, where did Jessica and Scarron go?
Everyone.
Sorry for the wait.
What's all that?
Some time ago, a really poor travelling
carnival left these for the food they ate here.
They'll catch you in no time with the clothes you're wearing now.
So...
Disguise yourselves in these and go to Gallia or wherever you need to go!
But promise to save your friend.
Thank you very much, both of you.
Thank you. I won't forget this.
It's a wonderful idea.
I can now save Onee-sama!
Hey, where's mine?
No fair!
Guiche.
Yeah.
Ready, go!
Let go!
Très bien!
He feels so good!
So nice. What's your name?
May I ask one thing?
Saito?
What is it?
Why are you doing all of this for us?
Miss Tabitha is my student.
She even saved me by making me appear dead.
I have an obligation to help her.
Jean! You really are wonderful!
Stop it, Miss Zerbst.
Guys on the first floor and girls on the second floor. Get a move on and get changed!
Okay!
Why?! Why are you laughing at me?!
You look perfect in it!
Yes. Those clothes! Those boots! That nose!
You're so mean!
Sorry for the wait.
Everyone looks absolutely lovely.
I cannot imagine exposing my belly in front of others.
It's so vulgar.
It's not so bad once in a while. You look good.
Since there's a poor one who can't even get a gram of attention.
What's that?
Are you talking about me?
Did it sound like I was talking about someone else?
Aren't you really carefree?
We're going to save your best friend,
and what's with your messed up clothes?
So the mission will succeed if I furrow my
brow and have a complicated look on like you?
If it does, then I would, too.
What did you say?!
Stop fighting, I said!
If you don't work together, even things that are supposed to work won't work.
Saito-san.
Siesta?
I gave up on going with you.
I don't have any strength like you all do,
so I'll probably only be in your way.
I'll be on the Ostland.
Siesta...
You're right. I can't take a frail girl like you on a dangerous journey.
You'll have to give up on this one.
Saito-san.
But my heart will be with you no matter where you go!
Saito-san?
Sorry for not being frail!
You're such a cocky dog!
Like I've been saying... Why are we fighting here?
Now, we shall head to the Ostland to recover it.
Saito-kun's party will go rescue Miss Tabitha.
Depart!
Yeah!
The girl captured by the dragon withheld her tears...
...because she was the daughter of the people who
mistreated l'Ivaldi, and she thought she had no right to cry.
"This is a punishment for me."
Punishment...
Punishment for betraying my friend...
Myoz!
My dear Myoz.
I've been expecting you, Joseph-sama.
I heard the requested item would be ready soon,
so I came rushing down.
On another note, this place is really hot.
To not allow any air or sound to escape, this place is sealed.
And we also have multiple furnaces and smelts.
I don't care. I'm more interested in the item.
Right here.
So this is Jormungand...
It's chained down.
As we expected, there are guards.
What should we do, Colbert-sensei?
Siesta-kun.
Yes?
Strip.
Str... Eh?!
That...
What?
They figured we'd head for the border, so they've set a checkpoint.
What should we do?
They'll find out who we are.
Then I bet they'll throw us into the jail and...
Shh! Calm down.
We're disguised right now.
They won't see through us that easily.
Act normally as much as possible.
All right, you guys. Stop.
A travelling circus, eh?
That's right!
Fine. Go on.
Thank you very much.
Hey fatty! Stop!
We're done for...
What do we do?
If I have to...
Fatty.
Y-Yes?
You dropped your nose.
Thank you very much...
Be careful on your way!
Thank you very much!
I was really worried there for a second.
Seriously.
Yeah, scaring us like that.
But...
All that's left now is to go over the mountains.
Just a little more until we get to Onee-sama!
I hope Colbert-sensei will get the Ostland back without problems.
Louise?
Louise!
What's with the troubled look?
N-Nothing.
Huh? Weirdo.
You're no longer an aristocrat either.
So I don't want to hear a plebeian boss me around.
She's right. I'm no longer a Vallière, so I'm a plebeian.
I'm not related to Father, Mother, or my sisters.
I only have Saito from now on.
Only Saito...
Um...
Who's there?!
Good work, both of you.
This place is off limits. Go home.
Um...
I actually have something even better to show you.
Something better?
I gotta see that.
We did it!
That was easy.
Now, we must hurry.
Who's there?!
So many people are coming.
Dana tel winde!
Oltal sleip cloudy!
Now's our chance.
Quickly, get aboard the Ostland.
Siesta-kun, you come to the bridge with me.
Gimli-kun and Reinard-kun, you two head to the engine room.
Yes.
It's moving.
Or not.
Throw more coal in!
Right away!
Hurry! The soldiers are coming!
Mister...
All right!
Mr. Colbert! If we don't hurry, the pursuit force will come right away!
That's what we want.
We're the bait.
We have to lure them away until
Saito-kun's party crosses the border.
What are you standing around for?
They're going to cross the border into Germania and to Gallia!
Intercept them!
Yes Ma'am!
We'll go after them, too!
Louise...
That looked pretty good.
With this, I will dismiss all your past failures.
In fact, you've made quite the achievement.
Thank you very much.
It's too great an honour for me.
However, there is one thing that worries me.
What is it? You don't look happy enough for the occasion.
Well...
They're being chased as traitors?
That void mage is?
Yes. I presume their intent is to rescue Charlotte-sama.
Interesting.
I'll face them before they enter Gallia.
No.
Vitartial is at Al Hambra.
It will be entertaining.
Before my niece falls into her eternal sleep,
I'm sure she would like to see her friends once more.
Lu kept thinking.
But only the fact that she betrayed her friend remained.
"So it's only natural for me to go through this."
Lu's last wish was...
...to be forgiven by the friend she betrayed.
But that was a wish that was not to be.
"Since... there's no way..."
"...he'd forgive me..."
We have a large number after us.
If we don't hurry, they'll catch up!
If it's come down to this...
We should attack them, too!
We can't do that!
I don't want to see anyone get injured.
Do we have to climb much further?
Stop whining. Everyone's tired.
Louise!
Are you all right?
I'm all right.
I've got to live alone from this point on.
This is nothing.
Louise.
I only sprained my ankle.
It doesn't hurt at all.
Stop lying.
Come on.
Rely on me at times like this, at least.
You might think of me as unreliable, but...
D-Don't get me wrong.
It's not that my ankle hurts.
I have to reward my familiar once in a while,
so I'm just letting you do as you wish.
Yes, yes.
Saito's been alone in this world all this time.
How can he still be so courageous?
How does he not get lost?
Why am I filled with so much anxiety?
Sensei! The Dragon Knights are right behind us!
Any more than this will be dangerous.
We surrender!
Just the four of you?
Where are the others?
They should have crossed the border by now.
It's been a while, Agnes-kun.
I-Impossible...
You... were alive?
I can't believe I was fooled by you thrice.
Come! If I don't take you guys back, I cannot face the Queen!
So this is Gallian Kingdom...
Onee-sama...
Tabitha... We're coming for you.
Sigh...
It's impossible.
But...
kyuu ni senaka wo mukete kakedashita wa (Just love me)
急に背中を向けて 駆け出したわ
I suddenly turned my back on you and ran away
hoka no ko ni yasashiku shiteta kara yo
ほかの子に優しくしてたからよ
Because you've been so gentle to many other girls
Boy onegai oikakete yo
Boyお願い 追いかけてよ
Boy, please chase after me
ato ni wa hikenai kara
あとには引けないから
Because it won't be over after this
pun pun pun
I am so sorry
gomen to ienakute gomen ne
ゴメンと言えなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't say "I'm sorry", sorry ♥
shinjite iru no ni kuchibiru ga togaru
信じているのに くちびるが尖る
Even though I believe you, my lips are pouting
kawaiku narenakute gomen ne
可愛くなれなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't be cute, sorry ♥
kosame no furu machi tsukamaete
小雨の降る街 つかまえて
Catch me in the town where a drizzle is falling
furimuku kara nakanaori no chu o shite
振り向くから 仲直りのCHU～をして
Because I'll turn around and give you a make-up kiss
atsui ryouude no naka de
熱い両腕の中で
In your warm arms
Next Time
My body's shaking!
This is a mission only someone as cute as I can do!
Zero no Tsukaima. Princess no Rondo.
Captive in Al Hambra.
You better watch closely!
Captive in Al Hambra
I won't forgive you if you look away.