Louise...
Saito...
S-Stop... staring so much.
You idiot!
Y-You dog!
Sorry.
Don't apologise.
You finally come back, and what's this?
It's wrong to look at your master with that kind of eyes.
I'm sorry! I can't hold it in anymore!
I-It's still light!
Th-
When it gets dark, then?
A-After asking the primogenitor, Brimir, and Mother.
Louise...
Saito...
Good morning!
How long do you two intend to sleep?
H-Hi! Good morning, Siesta!
I wasn't doing anything.
I didn't ask anything.
What?
You... Your hand...
My hand?
The rune is fading!
No way.
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
mejirushi no nai michi mo heiki sa futari nara
メジルシのない道も平気さ　ふたりなら
Even on a road without signs, I'll be fine, if we're together
saki no mienai tabi mayoinagara mitsuketa yo
先の見えない旅　迷いながら見つけたよ
On a journey that I can't see ahead of, while I was lost, I found it
boku no iru basho kimi no tonari
僕の居る場所　君のとなり
That my place to be is next to you
kenkashite nando mo hanashita sono te
喧嘩して　何度も離したその手
When we quarrelled, I let go of your hand again and again
hikiyose dakitai ima
引き寄せ抱きたい　今
I want to pull close and hold it now
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
namida no ame ni utaretara
涙の雨に打たれたら
If I'm beaten down by the rain of tears
I wanna hold you sugu yobi na yo boku no namae
I wanna hold you　すぐ呼びなよ　僕の名前
I wanna hold you, call my name immediately
dakishime ni yuku wa
抱きしめに行くわ
I'll go embrace you
kanashimi mo tsuyogari mo kono te ni uketomeru
悲しみも強がりもこの手に　受け止める
I'll accept sadness and bluffing in my hands
The Familiar's Mark
As you all know, after the Gallian Kingdom joined the fight,
the Albion army surrendered and the eight-month war ended.
Students. The peace we have now is a result of countless sacrifices.
Let us give prayer to those who have given their lives for this country.
Why? Why?
A moment of silence.
For the rune to be gone... Does that mean he's not my familiar anymore?
What's wrong? Did you eat something to upset your stomach?
Be quiet. Leave me alone.
What's with that attitude when I'm actually worried about you?
Okay.
Next, regarding our plan for classes,
first-years will go through basic spell...
It's really gone.
Hey, Del. Will it ever come back?
I'm not sure.
But Partner, doesn't this take a load off your shoulders?
You don't have to get yelled at by that aristocrat girl anymore.
You're a free man.
Oh, yeah.
You're right.
I should be happy, right?
Yeah. There's nothing to be sad about.
Saito-san.
I am glad to see you are well.
It's been a while, um...
I'm glad to see you're doing well too, Cattleya-san.
You too, Eléonore-san.
Forget it!
We're here just to get Louise.
What?!
The rune's gone?!
Hey, not so loud.
Seriously?
It disappeared?
See? Everyone heard.
But why? Why did it disappear?
So Saito is a mere plebeian now.
But isn't it strange? There must be a reason.
Don't know. Unheard of.
Could such a thing happen?
Isn't a contract with a familiar a lifelong thing?
Is it something that can disappear that easily?
Louise.
We're going home.
The war's over, so you need a respite.
Eléonore-oneesama.
If you need a familiar, just summon
another one that is more suitable for a Vallière.
Onee-sama!
First of all, I hate that plebeian's dog-like vulgar face!
But he is my dog.
I like him.
You're attached to this familiar that much?
T-That's none of your concern.
What did you just say to me?
I'm sorry.
Eléonore-neesama...
Does my opinion matter?
I'm sorry when you're occupied.
I, captain of the Musketeer Force, Agnes,
am here to convey the words of the Queen.
Louise Françoise Le Blanc de La Vallière.
Her familiar, Hiraga Saito.
Report to the castle at once.
The Princess?
Hey, Louise.
Make up your mind.
If you don't want to be with me, just say so.
I won't stop you.
You're free.
What is this all of a sudden?
Well, you are!
If the rune's gone, it means your contract as my familiar is over!
So there's nothing that ties us together!
You don't like being bossed around by a master like me, do you?
What are you saying?
Do as you like.
You belong to a different world to begin with.
You don't have to be with me.
I'm asking you, where is this talk coming from?!
What do you think I went through to come back to you?
And now you tell me to do whatever I like?
Aristocrats really are cold, eh?
I never said that!
The same goes for you!
You don't understand a thing about how I feel!
I was just being considerate for you!
Let's take a short break.
Louise.
Don't wander off too far.
Hey, Louise.
What? Do you need something?
Not really, but...
If you don't, then don't talk to me.
I want to be alone!
Fine! Suit yourself!
What am I doing?
Why am I so worked up over one familiar?
So what if he's not my familiar anymore?
I just have to summon another one.
Like Nee-sama said, summon another one more appropriate for a Vallière.
Even if he's not my familiar, would he choose to be with me?
Or...
This is frustrating!
Why do I have to go through all of this?
Thanks.
Alby? What is it doing here?
Nice to meet you, Miss Vallière.
You, who wields the great Void magic.
Who are you?!
Coward! Identify yourself!
I suppose. Call me Sheffield.
Don't play with me!
I wouldn't.
My doll stabbing you would be faster than you chanting a spell.
I'm here to fetch you.
My master is seeking a cute mage.
Will you come with me?
Don't mess around with me!
Please, notice this, Saito.
Louise!
Too bad. I have the ability to control every magic item in existence.
It's useless.
I know you very well.
Why are you after me?!
What do you want from me?!
First, you're not the only Void mage.
The same applies to the familiar.
Do you want to know more?
I'm Myozunitonirun.
T-That's...
I'm called the Mind of God.
As you've guessed, I'm a Void mage's familiar.
The familiar of a very noble man.
Where is your familiar?
Taking a nap somewhere, perhaps?
Or maybe he left you?
How do you...
Guess.
That's enough talk.
Saito!
I'll buy you time.
You start chanting the Void magic.
B-But you're no longer...
No longer your familiar nor Gandalfr, you want to say?
So what?
It's only natural for a man to protect the girl he likes.
Just leave your life in my hands!
Hey, Del. I just said all that, but I'm-
Duck!
I'm just an ordinary human!
Lift your left leg!
Have some confidence!
You've stalled an army of seventy thousand!
But back then, I was-
Right! Parry!
Who's the one who said to leave a life in his hands?
Ul Slis Ans.
Louise...
So what about some contract.
I said I would protect Louise!
I'm here to assist!
That boy shouldn't be her familiar anymore.
Yet why?
Myozunitonirun.
Retreat for now.
Joseph-sama?
We don't have all the pieces we need yet.
To enjoy the game, we need all the necessary pieces.
I trust you will do this correctly.
Nousis Heilos Iala.
As you wish.
Elpeo Eol.
Your words are law.
Y's!
Good job, Louise!
You stupid dog!
You have to stay right by me!
You can't go wandering off...
I'm sorry.
B-But...
Thank you for saving me.
Reporting back, Ma'am!
There's nothing here.
Louise. Saito-san.
Princess, what happened here?
The war caused my room to empty.
I sold all the furniture to support the war even a little.
Even you went through such a sacrifice?
This is nothing. I was about to lose you instead.
Not only did I try to take advantage of your strength, but I was also about to kill you.
I do not know how to apologise.
Princess, please don't mind it.
Thank you, Louise.
Saito-san.
No matter how many times I thank you,
it wouldn't be enough to express my appreciation.
W-Well, it's just how things went.
You're the hero who saved this Tristain.
A piece of paper?
That admits you to be a Chevalier.
A letter of appointment to be my knight.
A letter of appointment?
A hero deserves an honour befitting the deed.
You will accept it, won't you, Saito-san?
To be honest, I have no clue what this means.
It means you'll become an aristocrat!
A-Aristocrat?
I can't accept it.
Right now, I'm an ordinary human without any power.
I'm not even sure if I can protect Louise alone.
I don't think I can take the role of Chevalier.
What do you mean?
The rune's gone, right?
It completely disappeared.
Along with Gandalfr's power.
His heart stopped once in the war.
I'm guessing the contract was nullified then.
Then how did you come back to life?
Well... I was saved by a fairy.
She had a magic ring on her finger.
That ring resurrected him.
That's what happened in a nutshell.
Could resurrection really exist?
What is the fairy's name?
Where does she live?
In Albion Kingdom, South Gotha province, village of Westwood.
Tifania!
Tifania? That is a new name.
Agnes.
Go to the village and find Tifania-san.
Ma'am!
Wait.
It'd be easier if I went.
What's the point of you going when you no longer have the power of the rune.
Yeah. What do you plan on doing if you get attacked again?
Attacked?
Explain this to me!
Well...
Another Void mage and his familiar, eh?
Since I'm no longer a familiar, this all might mean nothing to me now.
He's leaving...
No...
Saito!
Saito?
Louise? What's wrong?
Saito...
Stupid.
Huh? Did you say something?
You'll catch a cold like that!
Come on, let's go inside.
Shut up. Leave me alone.
Don't be so stubborn.
You're shivering.
Who cares. You're the one who left me alone.
Come on now, let's go.
Louise?
I...
"I"?
I... I...
"Aye aye"?
I thought I couldn't see you again!
I have so many things I want to tell you, but you keep disappearing!
You weren't there when I woke up on the ship...
You weren't there when I woke up in bed at school...
I can't forgive you...
I can't forgive you at all.
You're so mean.
I thought you had left without telling me again.
Louise...
Don't cry.
Don't go anywhere.
I won't.
Really?
Yeah.
I won't go anywhere anymore.
S-Stay by me.
Yeah.
I don't care if you're not my familiar...
I don't care if you don't have Gandalfr's power...
Saito?
I'm confused.
I wonder if that's really all right.
What good am I if I can't protect you in an emergency?
Saito?
Hey, Louise. Is it possible to bind the contract again?
That whatever ceremony.
You mean Summon Servant?
I've never heard of it being done before.
I don't have a clue what may happen.
What... What if another familiar shows up?
What if you get sent to an unknown place?
I couldn't handle that!
We'll deal with it when it happens.
In fact, that won't even happen.
I came to this world to be your familiar, didn't I?
Oh, I get it. The contract is important on its own, but something is even more important...
What?
Simply a man and a woman is enough, right?
You love me, and I love you.
What do we need more than that?
W-Wait! I never said I love you!
We promised this morning, didn't we?
When night falls...
T-That's...
Let's go to bed.
I-I said wait!
No, I won't.
Wait! T-The sun is about to rise, too!
But it's still night.
I haven't done my prayers yet.
It can wait.
I-I said...
Wait , you stupid dog!
Why are you like that?
Stay there and cool your head until morning.
We promised though...
Dog! I mean, lowly creature!
Water flea!
Hurry up or we're leaving you behind!
Yes, coming!
Wait, water flea?
You... You suffice as a water flea!
Also, I'll have you keep up by running.
Y-You've got to be kidding me! Let me on!
I mean, please let me on!
I beg you!
Sigh...
It's impossible.
But...
kyuu ni senaka wo mukete kakedashita wa (Just love me)
急に背中を向けて 駆け出したわ
I suddenly turned my back on you and ran away
hoka no ko ni yasashiku shiteta kara yo
ほかの子に優しくしてたからよ
Because you've been so gentle to many other girls
Boy onegai oikakete yo
Boyお願い 追いかけてよ
Boy, please chase after me
ato ni wa hikenai kara
あとには引けないから
Because it won't be over after this
pun pun pun
I am so sorry
gomen to ienakute gomen ne
ゴメンと言えなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't say "I'm sorry", sorry ♥
shinjite iru no ni kuchibiru ga togaru
信じているのに くちびるが尖る
Even though I believe you, my lips are pouting
kawaiku narenakute gomen ne
可愛くなれなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't be cute, sorry ♥
kosame no furu machi tsukamaete
小雨の降る街 つかまえて
Catch me in the town where a drizzle is falling
furimuku kara nakanaori no chu o shite
振り向くから 仲直りのCHU～をして
Because I'll turn around and give you a make-up kiss
atsui ryouude no naka de
熱い両腕の中で
In your warm arms
Next Time
You! Tell me what exactly you were doing behind my back!
Zero no Tsukaima. Princess no Rondo. Fairy in the Forest.
What? Even water fleas have souls?
Fairy in the Forest
I won't forgive you if you look away.