I've brought him.
Enter.
Well, well, if it isn't King Albert.
Dolph!
Just what on earth do you intend by doing this?!
I thought we could enjoy a tasty meal together.
How unfortunate.
It appears nothing was prepared for you.
Keep him restrained.
So that's what you're after?!
Now, then, I suppose it is about time to end the game of hide-and-seek with the cute princess.
King Albert.
Or should I simply call you Albert?
Have you found her?
No, no luck.
I'll look over there.
Listen up, men!
Our objective is the Wood Cube!
Do not kill the princess yet!
Do you think you'll be able to get away with this, Dolph?!
"Get away with this"?
Who will pass their judgement on me?
You have no allies left here, Albert.
This trip around the world that you planned...
It was the perfect opportunity for me.
With the exception of you and the princess, everyone here is my subordinate.
But why?
Why did you betray me, Dolph?!
That's a mean thing to say, Albert.
I am thankful to you.
You raised me, an orphan,
and even made me the general of the kingdom!
Then why?!
Do you think I've been supporting you without any ambitions of my own?
This is justified by the will of God, Albert.
Dolph-sama!
We've found the princess!
Okay!
I'll be right there!
So, it's about time for you to think about your last words, King Albert.
Traitor!
What's wrong with you?!
Don't you know your place?!
Well, well, if it isn't Princess Starla.
Good evening.
Dolph, you bastard!
Do you have any idea what you're doing?!
Your words are always less refined than your looks.
Of course I know what I am doing.
After acquiring this Wood Cube from King Albert and that Wood Cube from you, Princess...
...I shall reactivate the ancient weapon.
Yes... So that I may become the new king of Fay!
You have no allies here.
You can no longer escape.
Now, be a good girl and hand it over-
He... He's dead!
Princess! Hurray! Princess! Hurray!
You scum!
I'll have you pay me back with interest!
All right.
Lead me to my father.
A Wood Cube?
The Princess should be holding onto it tightly.
But what if...
Ehh-
Super-eeeh!
This... Can't I become king with this?!
No.
Wait.
Calm down.
Take a minute to think about this.
After twelve years as a soldier,
I've always thought I would just die a grunt.
I can't believe I would have this kind of chance...
I should give up.
It's not like I have any plans after becoming king.
Despite having gathered both,
I have no idea how to call the ancient weapon.
Hot!
Nichijou 27
Good morning.
Super
Jumbo
Country-wide
Drawing
Lottery
I did it! I did it! I did it! I did it! I did it!
Mio-chan!
I won the third prize in the lottery for 100,000 yen!
No way!
Really?
Get me something.
Ah, what should I do?
What should I buy?
Maybe a house or something?
Just kidding.
Yukko.
This is from last year.
Well, well, it's not like lottery tickets win that often.
Present
It's okay, don't try to console me.
Besides, it's your birthday today, isn't it?
Here.
Eh? No way!
A present? Thanks!
Can I open it?
Go ahead.
It's nothing special.
Just something I had around the house.
That's fine.
It's the thought that counts.
Octopus
Wasabi
Teacher's Lounge
Sakurai-sensei.
Ah, Takasaki-sensei.
Good morning.
Sensei, can you do anything about that Aioi girl?
That
Aioi
Girl
She's never handed in any homework.
Ah, I-I'm sorry.
I'd be thankful if you could really take charge
and do something, as her homeroom teacher.
Ah, sorry.
I'll talk to Aioi-san about it.
W-Well, I had better get going for first period.
I'll leave it to you.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry!
Are you all right?
Did I get any tea on you?
Nichijou 28
I want to protect her!
For me, who has not had any luck with women for the past 26 years,
Sakurai-sensei is like a bamboo shoot suddenly sprouting in the garden.
Ah, no, no!
As a teacher, bringing feelings of love into the workplace is unacceptable!
Get it together, Takasaki Manabu!
Oh, she forgot something.
Sakurai-sensei!
You forgot your notebook.
Ah, thank you, Takasaki-sensei.
But this is my notebook.
Takasaki-sensei!
Where are you taking my notebook to?
I-I'm sorry.
Well, excuse me.
I want to invite her to hunt shiitake mushrooms!
I wonder if Sakurai-sensei has a boyfriend at the moment.
She doesn't wear a ring, so it's hard to imagine she's married.
So I might actually have a chance?
I wonder what kind of music she likes? Animals? Sports? Edible wild plants?
What am I thinking about?!
How impure.
How impure, Takasaki Manabu!
There is no way I can fulfil my responsibility of being a role model for the students like this!
Oh, Takasaki-sensei.
Are you worrying over your students?
But wouldn't it be all right to at least ask what kind of food she likes?
What kind of food do you like, Sakurai-sensei?
Um, I eat anything.
Ha ha ha, is that so?
How about shiitake mushrooms?
You can fry them, or even boil them.
Let's see.
Is it all right to deep-fry them?
Of course.
It's also all right to deep-fry them.
Then, it's all right to deep-fry them?
All right! This can work!
Naturally.
Do it naturally, Takasaki Manabu.
Talk to her naturally, like you're talking to an eggplant at home.
Sakurai-sensei.
Yes, what is it?
I'm sorry that I keep stopping you.
Do you have a boyfriend that you're going out with at the moment?
What am I saying?!
Am I an idiot?!
A moron?!
No, I don't.
I don't.
Yahoo!
U-Um, Takasaki-sensei.
Ah, sorry.
I asked something impolite.
It turned out all right.
Sakurai-sensei, do your best in first period.
Okay.
You do your best, too, Takasaki-sensei.
Well, excuse me.
I'll be off.
You do your best, too, Takasaki-sensei.
Ah, I see you're working hard.
Wait!
Um... Please give back my scythe!
I need to pawn this scythe in order to buy food, or else I'm going to die!
Oh, no! It's a river!
I did it.
Please give it back!
First comes rock, next comes paper, rockscispaper doesn't count,
rock, paper, scissors!
Yay, I won!
Thanks!
This isn't all of it!
I hear a voice in-
Tomorrow's weather is going to be-
Miraculous Beach!
This is where it all begins!
Mind
Right now, I'm gonna try to say something that isn't going through your head at all, Mio-chan.
What, what?
An Inconsistent Office Lady's Journey Diary.
It was, a little bit.
Jumping onto a train at the last
second is dangerous.
Mio-chan, Mai-chan, the train's already here!
Hurry up!
Wait up!
I made it! I'm safe!
You're the only one that made it.
Selemat tinggal!
TL note: Indonesian for "Farewell".
What should we have?
Well, bring on the orders.
I'll take one pitoro.
TL note: Pitoro is an exquisite part of the pig which is usually rich with fat.
I'll take an Amberjack, no, a Hamachi!
Well, bring on the orders.
Can I have some tuna and some halibut, please?
One sea urchin, please.
Let's see.
One pitoro and...
I forgot.
He forgot!
Nichijou 29
Ah, hello.
Uh, hello.
Um, do you need something?
Well...
Hey! What are you trying to do?
Well, I thought it was strange and interesting.
I-It's not strange!
It's normal!
A key can be an accessory!
Hey, hey, how did you do that?
Hey, hey, tell me about it.
Please give it back!
Come on. Just tell me how you did that.
All right, then. Let's do this.
Bye.
Why?!
Sorry, sorry.
It was just a joke.
Don't joke!
Please give it back!
Which hand is it?
It's in the bag!
Wow, correct!
Now, question two.
Kenta-kun's mother bought ten apples.
Of those, his mother ate three.
She gave four of the remaining apples to Yumiko, the neighbour.
Where is your hand?
In your bag!
Amazing!
You got it correct again!
Then please hurry up and give it back!
Now, then. The final question.
If you get this correct, you win a hand!
But it was mine to begin with!
Do you not want the hand?
I want it!
Then, here is the question.
Say "kaban" ten times.
TL note: "Kaban" means bag.
Bag Bag Bag Bag Bag Bag Bag Bag Bag Bag.
What do you draw on?
Ba- I mean a drawing board!
TL note: "Gaban" is a drawing board.
The correct answer was paper.
TL note: "Kami" is paper.
No way!
That's not fair!
I'm just joking.
Please don't hang around me!
All right, all right.
I'm sorry.
Oh, it came off.
It came off!
Mio!
Let's go home together.
Huh?
Onee, are you on the way home from university?
Man, I met a really interesting person earlier.
What kind of person?
Her arm came off.
What?
Also, she had a key attached.
What's with that?
There was a person like that.
Really?
That's strange.
Word Of The Day
I want to act in a way that makes people think,
"Oh, that's pretty cool."
Nano, here I go!
Nichijou 30
All right!
Magic ball.
Well, she's only a child, after all.
About what you'd expect.
I won!
I lost!
What's up with these two?
They aren't even doing it properly...
Sakamoto, how many points did I just get?
What!?
All right!
Here it comes, Professor!
She hasn't even thrown it yet!
I-Is she trying to kill me?!
Sakamoto-san, how many points did I just get?
You, too?!
She swung again?!
You're next.
Here, Sakamoto.
Why me?
More importantly, how can I even hold a bat with hands like these?
Honestly... I mean, what do you think my hands are?
You even thoroughly examined the pads when I first arrived.
This is why I can't stand kids...
Moe~
Well, you know.
Just the two of you alone are kind of dangerous, so I'm watching.
I have no intention of participating.
Why don't you just play catch?
All right.
All right, Coach.
Coach?
Coach, we only have one glove!
You should be fine with your bare hands.
Coach, the glove doesn't fit very well.
It was perfectly fine on your other hand!
Coach!
You guys are helpless.
Professor!
Here it comes!
Bring it on!
Ah, man.
Where did it go?
And then the teacher got mad at me.
Well, of course he would, you know.
I agree.
You think so, too, Mai-chan?
But he didn't have to get that mad.
I guess, but you'd better watch out from now on.
Yeah, you never know what will happen.
Ah, thank you.
Oh! Gentleman!
So yeah, Mai-chan, can you lend me again?
All right.
Hooray! You really do gotta have friends, after all.
I wonder if that's the person sis was talking about.
Man, you're a saviour.
Birthday Present
asa okite hao migai te
朝起きて 歯を磨いて
Woke up in the morning, brushed my teeth
attoiuma gogo juu ji
あっという間 午後10時
In the blink of an eye, it's 10pm
kyou mo takusan waratta naa
今日も たくさん 笑ったなぁ
Today, we laughed a whole lot
takusan tokimeita naa
たくさん ときめいたなぁ
We had a great time
tomodachi to baka mitai ni sawai deru toki ni mo
友達と バカみたいに騒いでる 時にも
At times, with my friends, acting like fools, being noisy
chirachiratte me ga au
チラチラって 目が合う
Fluttering, our eyes met.
guuzen dayo ne
…偶然、だよね。
It's a coincidence, right?
hatsukoi nante ie nai
初恋なんて言えない
I wouldn't call this my first love
kyara janai n da mon
キャラじゃないんだもんっ!
It's not my character.
nee ashita mo aeru yo ne
ねえ あしたも会えるよね?
Say, will we be able to meet again tomorrow?
mabuta o tojiru to
まぶたを 閉じると
As my eyelids close
kirakira kimi darake
キラキラ キミだらけ
I see you sparkling all over the place
kyou mo tanoshikatta ne
今日も 楽しかったね
Today was fun, too, wasn't it?
aa koi shite n da naa
あー 恋 してんだなぁ
I'm in love~
ureshii na ureshii na
うれしいな うれしいな
So happy, so happy
hajimemashite koi gokoro
はじめまして こいごころ
It is my pleasure to meet you, my new-found love.
ashita mata aeru ne
あした また あえるね
Surely, we'll meet again tomorrow~
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
Have a good night
yume de sugu aeru ne
ゆめで すぐ あえるね
We'll meet immediately in our dreams
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
So have a good night
I am the Wood Cube.
Whoever possesses me can acquire the ancient weapon.
Well, then, the next episode of Nichijou is episode 8.
Narration:    Wakamoto Norio
Look forward to it!