Nichijou 72
It's true!
The Daiku Café had a renovation!
Here it is.
Oh, wow.
They turned it into a café.
Welcome!
I've been here before, so you can go ahead and order first, Mio-chan.
Oh, really?
Well then...
I'll take a grande white chocolate mocha Frappuccino.
Eh?
Also, I'd like a shot of espresso with caramel syrup,
hazelnut syrup, chocolate chips and extra whipped cream.
Die!
Wait! Yukko, where are you going!?
jou jou yuu jou banjin maji kaichou
じょーじょーゆーじょー万事マジ快調
Amazing friendship, the absolute best!
na na na na na na na
ななななななな
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
hai! icchaimashou!
ハイ!言っちゃいましょう!
All right! I'll say it!
kimi wa best best friend
キミはベストベスト フレンド
You are my best, best friend!
(furai!) chotto fuzakete mitara
(フライ!) ちょっとふざけてみたら
(Fly!) When I joke around a bit,
(shain!) motto fuzake kaeshite kuru
(シャイン!) もっとふざけ帰してくる
(Shine!) You joke around more in response.
(La La La) ikogochi ii ttara arya shinai
(ラーラーラー)居心地良いったらありゃしない
(La La La) Nothing is better than this!
(wai!) iya na koto attatte
(ワイ!) 嫌なことあったって
(Why!) Even if something bad happens,
(fain!) sokkou wasurechaunda
(ファイン!) 即効忘れちゃうんだー
(Fine!) I immediately forget about it!
(La La La)
(ラーラーラー)
itsudatte jan jan yarimasho
いつだって、じゃんじゃんやりましょ♪
Always keep it going!
24 jikan issho demo mondai nai
２４時間一緒でも問題ない
Being together 24 hours a day isn't a problem.
marude futago ka oyako ka clone saibou
まるで双子か親子かクローン細胞
Just like twins, or a parent and child, or clone cyborgs.
kore ja me ga sumu hitsuyou wa nakunakunai!?
これじゃ目が澄む必要はなくなくない!？
Then isn't there no reason to clear your eyes?
sore to kore to wa mattaku mattaku betsumondai
それとこれとは まったくまったく 別問題
Those are completely, completely different issues.
(faito!) kenka shichatta toki mo
(ファイト!)喧嘩しちゃった時も
(Fight!) Even when I get in a fight with you,
(daoun!) kanari hekonda toki mo
(ダウン!)かなり凹んだ時も
(Down!) even when I get really down,
(shai!) hitori de itai you na toki mo
(シャイ!)一人で居たいような時も
(Shy!) even when I feel like I want to be alone,
futokizukeba chikaku ni iru shinaba morotomo
ふと気付けば 近くに居る 死なば諸共
before I realise it, you're right there; we'll be together even in death!
nande daro
なんでだろ
I wonder why it is.
soba ni itainda
そばに居たいんだ
I want to be with you.
kimi to issho nara
君と一緒なら
When I'm with you,
tokei hyakubai soku
時計百倍速
time goes 100 times faster!
tanoshii na
楽しいな
It's fun, isn't it?
tanoshisugirunda
楽しすぎるんだ
It's way too fun!
sasuga saikou friend
流石 最高 friend
As expected of my best friend!
Hey! na na na na na na na
Hey! ななななななな
Hey! Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
nannanoyo
なんなのよー
What is it?
yabai synchro
ヤバいシンクロー
The synchro is amazing!
itsumo oosawagi
いつも大騒ぎ
Always making an uproar,
kanari gokinjo meiwaku
かなりご近所迷惑
bothering the neighbours a lot.
ima nanji
今何時
What time is it now?
ato ne yorereihifu
あとねヨレレイヒーフ
And then yo de le hi hoo!
wake wakannainai
訳分かんないない!
I don't get it at all!
soredoshira
ソレドシラ
So re doh si la!
souzou ijou nante iu ka saiko
想像以上なんて言うか最高
It's better than I imagined, the absolute best!
aa da kou da ittetemo tomodachi (wasshoi!)
あーだこーだ言ってても友達 (わっしょい!)
Even if I say this and that, we're still friends. (Hooray!)
jou jou yuu jou banjin maji kaichou
じょーじょーゆーじょー万事マジ快調
Amazing friendship, the absolute best!
cha cha la cha la cha cha
ちゃちゃらちゃらちゃちゃー
Cha Cha La Cha La Cha Cha!
Nakamura-sensei
The sleeping medicine didn't work on Shinonome.
That's where this comes in!
A mixture that increases the rate of oxidation,
Mr. Rust+!
and as added insurance, it also numbs the senses.
If I get Shinonome to drink this,
I'll easily capture and have my way with her.
What will I do after I capture her?
Well, this and that...
2nd Science Room
Magnets: How do they work?
What should I do?
Huh, we're using compasses today.
Nano-chan, did you get a compass too?
Yes!
Everyone.
Today's class is now a free-study session.
Oh! Yay!
Nakamura-sensei collapsed again?
Nakamura sure collapses a lot.
Nichijou 73
Sasahara, why are you skipping clean-up duty again?
I cleaned up my own area.
You left behind a lot of dust!
I see.
Hurry up and get back there.
By the way, how did you know I was on the roof?
Are you stupid!?
I just came up here because the weather was so nice!
I see.
Thanks for going through the trouble of checking my area, too.
Don't get the wrong idea!
It's not like I'm doing it for you or anything!
Wow.
Crane Game
Tokisadame
Nichijou 74
It's the weekend.
I'm supposed to meet up with Mai-chan in the next town over.
Apparently I'll get free candy, so I'll bite!
Would you like some bread?
Oh no, it's fine.
I ate on my way out!
Aren't dogs, like, against the rules or something?
It's fine.
I need to stand up because my stop is coming up soon!
Coming up next is Tokisadame Wholesale Town.
Tokisadame Wholesale Town.
Nice timing, announcer!
All right.
The exit is to your right.
Let's just get off!
To everyone on the train...
Farewell!
Well, well, well, I'll just say farewell from this side, then.
Endure it!
There's no reason to get embarrassed over such a little thing!
Oh, pardon me!
I was in a bit of a hurry!
Oh, I give up!
I'll never see her again.
This is the next town over.
Nobody here knows me.
Don't worry about it!
Wait...
Is she following me?
It must be my imagination.
I'm just thinking too much today.
She said there'd be a Daiku Burger as soon as I left the station...
Where is it?
The map Mai-chan gave me...
Daiku
Burger
Here
...is a bit twisted.
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
It'd be quicker just to ask.
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
All right!
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Daiku
Burger
Here
Excuse me, where can I find the Daiku Bur-
Hey!
Why have you been following me!?
There'll be copyright issues if you do that!
Daiku Burger is right over there.
I'm meeting up with someone there, too.
If you want, I can show you the way.
Welcome!
Sorry, Nee-chan.
I was held up in club.
You're late!
She really was meeting someone?
Sorry for the wait.
I guess Mai-chan isn't here yet.
But seriously...
...today is just not my day!
It's been extremely embarrassing!
Whatever.
I'm in a different town.
That's right!
If you think positively about it,
it's good practise for life.
That's right!
I'll overcome this embarrassment!
Now, I'll be able to overcome anything!
Yukko.
Sorry for the wait.
Mai-chan!
Could that possibly be...
Trick or Treat.
If it's come to this, then there's no helping it.
I'll get my  treat.
Trick or Treat.
Are they dressing up for Halloween?
Crows are like this!
When you absolutely must pass by a menacing crow,
it is extremely important not to lose eye contact.
Shinonome Institute
Sleep
I really can't fall asleep.
They say if you count sheep jumping over a fence,
you can fall asleep.
All right, I'll try it.
One sheep...
She fell asleep with one sheep!
Professor, that's amazing!
I'll try, too!
One shee-
The sheep... didn't even make it over.
Volunteer Spirit
It's finished.
Thanks.
As expected of Nee-chan!
Does Sasahara-san teach you this kind of thing?
Why does he have to teach me everything?
But don't you guys get along really well?
Not at all! Not at all.
I mean, not at all!
Nee-chan, calm down.
Still, you ironed his handkerchief earlier.
That was just garbage I found on the street.
Eh?
It was Sasahara-san's, wasn't it?
I'm telling you, that's not what happened.
I was just exercising my arms,
and there happened to be an iron there.
Also, there happened to be a handkerchief under it.
Something like that...
Something like that!
She's so easy to read...
But Nee-chan, you looked so happy when you were ironing it.
That's stupid!
At that moment...
At that moment, the Earth was just passing through the Photon Belt!
So, listen to this!
What?
I talked to Ono-kun yesterday!
You're so lucky!
On a train for two hours.
On a bus for one.
From the tough city,
I have come to this remote S-town.
Even though I didn't believe I would ever find it again,
I couldn't give up, and I've continued to search for that book.
That book, which is said to be a myth,
gave colour to my grey childhood days.
It is in this library.
I will be able to read that book in this age.
I am thankful that I happened to meet the donor.
Because of that, I got my hands on it.
Tones of a
Clear Autumn
With my heart beating fast,
I...
...slowly opened my prize.
Love-Like
All right, time's almost up.
Everyone, make sure you wrote your name.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Sev-
-en.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Zero.
All right, pass them forward.
Nichijou 75
Halloween was a while back.
This coffee isn't very coffee-like.
Huh? It's not "coffee-like"?
What does that mean?
I don't really know how to explain it,
but it's not really... coffee-like.
Just take a sip.
Come on.
Really, what does it mean to be not coffee-like?
It's not coffee-like.
Shinonome Institute
Nichijou 76
Everyone!
It's finally finished!
Meet Biscuit #2.
I'm Biscuit #2.
Oh, I remember him.
Such a bland reaction!
Hey, take a closer look!
But I already saw him before.
#1 and #2 are different!
He's much more amazing!
My name is Biscuit #2.
I'm a biscuit robot created by Professor Shinonome.
As the name implies,
my power source is biscuits.
I operate on the power of biscuits.
Professor, it's about time for a biscuit.
Eh?
But this is the last one...
Biscuit #2's special skill is speed-reading.
Go ahead.
Finished!
There!
Why aren't you amazed?
Well, I can read fast, too.
Then why do you always read so slowly?
I think that this way...
...makes me more like a normal person.
What's wrong, Biscuit #2?
I get sleepy when I read a lot of words in a book.
That's pretty normal.
Why won't you say it's amazing?
I'm really amazing!
What?
You're mad about something small like that?
It's not something small!
But you were already amazing.
Is that so?
Maybe I made a bit of a mistake.
I don't really think you made a mistake.
Hey, hey.
How amazing am I?
Um, how about as much as the Chichibu Mountain Range?
I don't know how much that is!
Um, then how about the Nullarbor Plain?
Eh? Why not something bigger?
Then, how about a whale?
Oh, that might be good.
Whales are big, aren't they?
Yeah, they are!
Word Of The Day
It's not that it's fine like that,
and it's not that it's fine like this,
it's fine like that.
What are you doing?
I'm doing sugoroku.
TL Note: Japanese backgammon.
What are you doing?
I have a quiz.
A quiz is peaceful and fun!
Winning money by making the princess happy...
...seems like an interesting form of recreation.
You gotta have something fun like this every now and then.
Right?
The ball was in this one, right?
It's actually in here.
Nice going, number 66.
I can't believe you had that kind of skill.
I'm actually aiming to be an official magician for the empire.
If that happens, you'll have a nice job.
Yeah.
I'm fired up now, too!
I'll definitely win the prize money!
Hey, it's time.
Nichijou 77
Be quiet.
Attendant
Now then,
proceed in the order of the number you received.
Number one, please step forward.
I'm first.
Oh, number 66 is first?
The money will be won right away.
An imperial magician, huh?
Seize your dream, number 66.
Now, where is the ball?
I want to be an imperial magician!
Next.
Number two, step forward!
It's time.
Time for my name to be known by the world!
I'll turn this into a chance.
That's...
Number 4, the comedian.
He can do it.
I, number 4, shall be going.
Next.
No way. Number 4, too?
Hey, are you okay?
It's me.
But you said...
...you had a quiz.
I can't believe it turned out like this.
But my only skill is with quizzes.
I must assure that the princess gets it correct.
It's okay.
I won't let myself fail.
I should probably make it a simple one.
I, number 6, will give a quiz!
What kind of bread can you not eat?
Oh, it's multiple choice!
A) Frying pan.
B) Melon bread.
Now, which is the answer?!
What?
I don't know.
That is correct!
I regret everything!
It's over.
Even the quiz master was expelled.
Next.
I, number 7, will recite all the cities that have hosted the Olympics!
I will never forget your courage, number 7.
What's wrong?
Is there no one who can please the princess?
What should I do?
I intended to do a cheer...
You fool!
I was going to break chopsticks with my ass!
I was going to play a bamboo screen!
I was going to chop up a cabbage!
We're all going to be erased.
Hey, hey.
I hope you're not forgetting about me.
You're...
From that comedic stance,
it's the comedian that no one in the comic world can surpass:
Comedian 13!
I'm gonna go visit the brink of death...
...and change the atmosphere.
Wait, 13!
That's far too dangerous!
Do you think I'm simply going to do the "swan lake" dance?
Well, watch closely.
I'll teach you about true comed-
Watch me!
Comedian 13!
Why me, too?!
Next. Number five.
How long are you going to make us wait?
Hurry up!
Who is it?
Who the heck is number five?
Is it you?
No!
That's the number on my hat!
Hey...
Number five is you-
He's finished!
Hey, number five!
Get out here!
What's wrong?
And still!
Next.
I don't care who.
Someone go.
No matter what we do, it's...
...hopeless!
No matter how many lives you have, it's not enough for that!
I won't participate in such a selfish kind of recreation!
I'll go stand in the hall!
aru hi
ある日
One day,
papa to futari de katari atta sa
パパとふたりで語り合ったさ
I had a talk with my father.
kono yo ni ikiru yorokobi
この世に生きる喜び
It was about the various happy...
soshite kanashimi no koto wo
そして悲しみのことを
...and sad things that live in this world.
green green
グリーン　グリーン
Green Green
aozora ni wa kotori ga utai
青空には小鳥が歌い
Birds are singing in the blue sky.
green green
グリーン　グリーン
Green Green
oka no ue ni wa lala midori ga moeru
丘の上には　ララ　緑がもえる
Up on the hill, la la, green is sprouting.
sono toki
その時
At that time,
papa ga itta sa boku wo mune ni daki
パパが言ったさ　ぼくを胸に抱き
my father said, while holding me to his chest,
tsuraku kanashii toki ni mo lalala nakun ja nai to
つらく悲しいときにも　ラララ　泣くんじゃないと
not to cry, la la la, even at painful and sad times.
green green
グリーン　グリーン
Green Green
aozora ni wa soyokaze fuite
青空にはそよ風吹いて
A gentle breeze is blowing in the blue sky.
green green
グリーン　グリーン
Green Green
oka no ue ni wa lala midori ga yureru
丘の上には　ララ　緑がゆれる
Up on the hill, la la, green is swaying.
midori ga hirogaru
緑がひろがる
Green is spread out.
midori ga hirogaru
緑がひろがる
Green is spread out.
midori ga hirogaru
緑がひろがる
Green is spread out.
I'm a sweet grande white chocolate mocha Frappuccino...
...with a shot of espresso and caramel syrup, hazelnut syrup,
chocolate chips and extra whipped cream.
Next time on Nichijou: Episode 19.
Narration:     Aikawa Rikako
Look forward to it!