Language Arts
All right.
The test is now over.
Wow, they're really happy.
Everyone must have really given their all on this test.
That makes me happy.
The test is over; rock, paper,scissors!
That's not rock, paper, scissors!
It's like a dream!
It's over now.
It's all over now!
My parents are each going to give me a bag of rice!
Way to go, rice seller!
The two of us are getting married!
All right!
You guys, help out! One, two...
What... the... heck?!
tatta ima hajimete kizuita
たった今 初めて気づいた
I just realised it for the first time
koi ni ochita no dana
恋に落ちたのだな～
That I had fallen in love~
nijyuuyo jikan kimi kimi kimi
24h キミ☆ キミ☆ キミ☆
Twenty-four hours a day thinking of you, you and nothing more than you!
ishiki sezaru o emasen
意識せざるをえません!
It's something I wasn't consciously aware of
nanka (nanka) itsumo to chigau
なんか (なんか) いつもと違う
Somehow (somehow) I'm feeling different from the usual
kimi to (futari) gikochinai kaiwa
キミと (二人) ぎこちない会話
With you (the two of us) and our dull chatter
masaka (ryouomoi) iya kataomoi
まさか (両思い) いや 片思い
Don't tell me (mutual love?) Nope, it's a one-sided crush
yabai shisen acchatta
やばい! 視線合っちゃった!
This is bad! Our gazes met!
nani nani kono doki doki
なになに?! このドキドキ?!
What, what? Why is my heart pounding like this?
shikoukairo guccha guccha konsen
思考回路 ぐっちゃぐっちゃ 混線・・・
Did a short circuit just make a mess out of my mind?
konna koto hajimete dayo
こんなこと 初めてだよ
This is my first time... feeling like this...
netsu demo aru no kana
熱でもあるのかな～
I wonder if I have a fever~
kyuutenchokka irasshatta koigokoro
急転直下 いらっしゃった 恋心
Suddenly and precipitately, love has arrived.
acchuuma kao hakka de makkakka
あっちゅうま 顔 発火で まっかっか
Instantly igniting my face into a bright red
ba ba baka na te ga furueruzo
バ・バ・バカな?! 手が震えるぞ
T-That's stupid?! My hands are shaking
kore ga zoku ni iu koi nano
これが 俗に言う 「恋」 なの?!
Is this really what they call "love"?
yayayacchatta kaiwa kami makuri
やややっちゃった 会話 噛みまくり
I-I did it! A conversation filled with stutters
kimazui chinmoku mamimumemo
気まずい沈黙 マミムメモ
This awkward silence... *mumble mumble*
kimi no (kimi no) kimochi shiritai yo
キミの (キミの) 気持ち 知りたいよ
Your... (Your...) I want to know your feelings.
kakakata kataomoi
カカカタ☆カタオモイ
O-One-sided love
hatsukoi itsumo no tsuugakuro
初恋! いつもの通学路
First love! The usual way to school
pika pika hikaru I do fall in love
ピカピカ光る I do fall in love!
The shining light. I do fall in love!
sora mo tobesou sa
空も飛べそうさ
I feel I could fly towards the sky
kakakata kataomoi
カカカタ☆カタオモイ
O-One-sided love
Oh, Mio.
Good morning.
Nichijou 35
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Where's your "Eh?! Why are you wearing that?!" reaction?
Aw, you're still mad, aren't you?
About what I did to your Mont Blanc yesterday...
Sticking a knight piece in it...
Well, it's not like it became inedible, so it's all right.
Of course it's not all right.
I was looking forward to that Mont Blanc!
What, what, what?! I don't get it!
Why would you stick a knight piece in it?!
Well...
I thought it would look cool.
Head!
She always takes jokes so badly.
Honestly, stupid Nee.
They only make ten of those Mont Blanc a day.
Without even knowing it, she's always messing with things.
She's a college student now.
She should pay attention to other people's pain.
But today, I have the capacity to forgive her actions.
Because I've hidden a shortcake that's limited to five a day...
King
Checkmate!
The strawberry!
The strawberry that I've been looking forward to since last night, which is limited to five a day!
My...
Strawberry!
Where's the strawberry?!
Where's the sweet that goes in this position?!
Torso!
Come on, you idiot Nee!
A cake without a strawberry is no better than bread!
Nothing more than sweet bread!
Happy birthday to me.
Happy birthday dear Watashi.
Onee...
Mio.
It's not your birthday!
Teachers' Lounge
Quiz
TL note: In Japan, a check means the answer is wrong, and a circle means it is correct.
Nichijou 36
I've always wanted to come here at least once.
You said it was mentioned in a magazine?
Yeah!
Look, I have a coupon and everything!
You don't need to go pulling that out yet.
I'll have nishin soba.
TL note: Nishin soba is soba with boiled herring on top.
Oh, even though it's so hot out, huh?
Without the herring.
That'd just be regular soba!
What are you gonna get, Mio-chan?
I'm probably just going to get zaru soba.
TL note: Zaru soba is a variety of chilled soba.
How unexciting.
That's really an amateur kind of thing to get.
There's nothing wrong with it.
What about you, Yukko?
I'm gonna go with the tendon with summer vegetables.
It's pretty daring going for a rice dish at a noodle place, huh?
So cool!
I know, right?
And it's a seasonal special, too.
Who knows when we'll have the chance to eat it again?
A year from now.
Man.
You have no dreams, Mio-chan.
The present is what's important. Now.
Oh, I see.
Well, you may be a bit too young for it, though, Mio-chan.
Sure, whatever.
Excuse me.
I'll be taking your order.
Nishin soba, zaru soba...
And also... tendon... with summer vegetables.
Nishin soba, zaru soba and summer vegetable tendon.
I will go put the order in.
It says right here that this store makes all their noodles by hand.
They're really serious about it, huh?
I wonder what this sobagaki is.
TL note: Sobagaki is a paste made from buckwheat, which is also used to make soba noodles.
It's those squishy balls of buckwheat.
Huh, is that right?
Thank you for waiting.
That's one nishin soba and one zaru soba.
Oh, you can go ahead and eat before me.
Sorry.
Before it gets cold.
Mine's already cold.
It must be because mine is a special menu item.
They take their time and make it carefully.
Yours sure is taking a while, Yukko.
I wonder if it's taking a long time to fry the tempura for it.
Maybe they went out to gather summer vegetables.
Ah, ha, so that's why it's so slow.
They apparently have a lot of a-la-carte dishes here, too.
Is that so?
Yes!
We were wrong.
Too bad.
Goddamn!
Hey, Yukko, calm down!
How can I?! It's so slow! It's too slow!
No matter how far they go to preserve the taste,
they aren't preserving the heart!
You're not making sense!
I'll definitely submit a complaint!
Sorry for the wait.
Wasn't that a bit too slo-
Thank you.
Oh, read a magazine or something.
I'll finish right away.
Things you think are cool!
Child Shogi Pros!
Nichijou 37
My mosquito coil and repellent are in place.
I figured I could just wait and it'd go away.
But it never fades, like the Mogami River in the dead of night.
They say that even a tiny mosquito has half a soul.
Just accept it and sleep peacefully.
You will!
Yes!
Chest!
Such a worthless death.
I'll kill you!
I hit.
And I hit.
But there's no effect.
I don't know what's what any more!
Mum!
This house is no good any more!
We have no choice but to move!
Do you have any idea what time it is?!
Be quiet and go to sleep!
Chirashizushi.
TL note: Chirashizushi is a kind of sushi.
Now you.
No. Chi Ra Shi Zu Shi.
Non, non.
Chi.
Ra.
Shi.
Zu.
Yes!
Chirashizushi.
Now you.
Endurance
Sign: No talking.
Shinonome Institute
Nichijou 38
Sakamoto!
Look, look!
I got a winner on the bottom of the popsicle!
Why aren't you excited?!
You shouldn't be eating that kind of thing.
What do you mean by "that kind of thing"?!
You won't be able to finish your dinner.
Omelette rice.
You're such a kid, getting excited over something like a winning popsicle.
It's not just a winner!
It's on the bottom! It's super-rare!
Top or bottom, it's still just a winner.
Of course there are times when the winner is on that side.
Man, you're such a blissful kid.
You're getting way too happy over a winner.
A crab!
This is something super-rare!
I'll save this one for last-
Thanks for the meal.
Huh? You haven't eaten at all, Professor.
Were you eating lots of snacks this afternoon?
I'm sorry.
Come on. How much of the snacks did you eat from the pantry?
All of them.
All of them?!
You ate all of this month's?!
I'm not praising you!
Honestly, now.
But Sakamoto told me to eat them!
Sakamoto-san?!
Shinonome Institute
But Sakamoto said that food rots more quickly in the summer!
That's not related!
They say that snacks go in a different stomach!
Are you an office lady in the afternoon?!
Sakamoto-san!
Why are you going along with this?
I am completely innocent!
It's black and white! Or rather, it's white!
You're completely black, Sakamoto.
She's right.
That's how I was born!
That's enough.
You won't listen to anything I say, anyway.
And so, I am taking your strawberry juice, Professor.
I won't eat snacks any more!
Too bad.
I'll give you my winning popsicle!
I don't want it.
I'll eat all my vegetables!
Of course you will.
I'll remove the key!
I'll forgive you just this once.
If it happens again, you're going a month without snacks.
Okay!
Well, then.
It feels like if I give it to her now, she won't do it in the end.
You can have the juice after you've removed the key.
Then turn around.
Okay!
Your right hand is a loser.
Why did you install something like that?!
I'm not praising you!
You're too impulsive, Professor.
You should think more about your actions.
She's not listening!
A Small Miracle
Rock!
Paper!
Scissors!
Word Of The Day
If you look, you really can find anything...
Oh, Mio.
Perfect timing.
What's up, Onee?
I had some urgent business come up.
Could you help out at the neighbourhood association's stall in my place?
What?
You should ask mum for something like that.
Mom's out playing sepak takraw with her friends.
Besides, you'll get paid 10,000 yen.
Well, thanks.
Neighbourhood Association
Daihuku Fair
I'm happy to get paid 10,000 yen.
I had nothing else to do, anyway. Maybe I'll check it out.
Nichijou 39
I've been tricked!
This is awful.
What the heck is this?
How did I get fooled into this?
Daihuku Fair
And for a neighbourhood association stall,
it's just the two of us selling daihuku on the street!
It's embarrassing!
Daihuku Fair
Everyone is looking at me with pity.
Am I supposed to draw in customers?
As the mascot character, Daihuku-kun?
There are no eyes or even a mouth.
It's just a white mask.
This isn't Daihuku-kun...
It's a daihuku!
Wait a minute... This Daihuku Fair...
It's not a fair!
I'm sor-
There's no way this will work.
Oh, what's that?
It looks gross!
Take that!
Stop that!
It's starting to hurt, so stop!
Hey, stop!
There's no protection at the bottom!
It got angry.
Run away!
What now...
Yukko!
Please, don't destroy the image of the Daihuku.
I can't watch this.
Hurry, take it off.
This is why I can't stand part-timers.
Don't just stand there and stare. Go manage the stand.
It's for 10,000 yen pay.
I have to endure.
I want leave.
I miss my home.
But will these sell?
They're pretty neatly placed.
Excuse me.
How much for one?
It's a customer.
Wait, how much are they?
Excuse me, how much are-
So my daring enterprise ends in ruin?!
I won't run away. I'm not going to run away after one little setback like this!
Just take it for free.
How lucky.
asa okite hao migai te
朝起きて 歯を磨いて
Woke up in the morning, brushed my teeth
attoiuma gogo juu ji
あっという間 午後10時
In the blink of an eye, it's 10pm
kyou mo takusan waratta naa
今日も たくさん 笑ったなぁ
Today, we laughed a whole lot
takusan tokimeita naa
たくさん ときめいたなぁ
We had a great time
tomodachi to baka mitai ni sawai deru toki ni mo
友達と バカみたいに騒いでる 時にも
At times, with my friends, acting like fools, being noisy
chirachiratte me ga au
チラチラって 目が合う
Fluttering, our eyes met.
guuzen dayo ne
…偶然、だよね。
It's a coincidence, right?
hatsukoi nante ie nai
初恋なんて言えない
I wouldn't call this my first love
kyara janai n da mon
キャラじゃないんだもんっ!
It's not my character.
nee ashita mo aeru yo ne
ねえ あしたも会えるよね?
Say, will we be able to meet again tomorrow?
mabuta o tojiru to
まぶたを 閉じると
As my eyelids close
kirakira kimi darake
キラキラ キミだらけ
I see you sparkling all over the place
kyou mo tanoshikatta ne
今日も 楽しかったね
Today was fun, too, wasn't it?
aa koi shite n da naa
あー 恋 してんだなぁ
I'm in love~
ureshii na ureshii na
うれしいな うれしいな
So happy, so happy
hajimemashite koi gokoro
はじめまして こいごころ
It is my pleasure to meet you, my new-found love.
ashita mata aeru ne
あした また あえるね
Surely, we'll meet again tomorrow~
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
Have a good night
yume de sugu aeru ne
ゆめで すぐ あえるね
We'll meet immediately in our dreams
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
So have a good night
Mosquito
Take that!
The Shinonome household was peaceful again today.
Hello! I'm the King!
When you think of shogi, you think of Habu-san!
TL note: Habu Yoshiharu is a famous shogi player.
Habu is also a breed of snake which hunt mongooses.
When you think of Habu-san, you think of mongooses!
Now I want to go on a trip to Okinawa!
Nankuranaisa!
TL note: Okinawan speech. Its meaning is akin to "Don't worry".
Narration:     Hirano Aya
Next time on Nichijou is episode 10!
Look forward to it!