Glasses, Glasses, Glasses, Glasses.
Glasses, Glasses, Glasses.
Glasses, Glasses...
Glasses!
Glasses, Glasses, Glasses, Glasses!
jou jou yuu jou banjin maji kaichou
じょーじょーゆーじょー万事マジ快調
Amazing friendship, the absolute best!
na na na na na na na
ななななななな
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
hai! icchaimashou!
ハイ!言っちゃいましょう!
All right! I'll say it!
kimi wa best best friend
キミはベストベスト フレンド
You are my best, best friend!
(furai!) chotto fuzakete mitara
(フライ!) ちょっとふざけてみたら
(Fly!) When I joke around a bit,
(shain!) motto fuzake kaeshite kuru
(シャイン!) もっとふざけ帰してくる
(Shine!) You joke around more in response.
(La La La) ikogochi ii ttara arya shinai
(ラーラーラー)居心地良いったらありゃしない
(La La La) Nothing is better than this!
(wai!) iya na koto attatte
(ワイ!) 嫌なことあったって
(Why!) Even if something bad happens,
(fain!) sokkou wasurechaunda
(ファイン!) 即効忘れちゃうんだー
(Fine!) I immediately forget about it!
(La La La)
(ラーラーラー)
itsudatte jan jan yarimasho
いつだって、じゃんじゃんやりましょ♪
Always keep it going!
24 jikan issho demo mondai nai
２４時間一緒でも問題ない
Being together 24 hours a day isn't a problem.
marude futago ka oyako ka clone saibou
まるで双子か親子かクローン細胞
Just like twins, or a parent and child, or clone cyborgs.
kore ja me ga sumu hitsuyou wa nakunakunai!?
これじゃ目が澄む必要はなくなくない!？
Then isn't there no reason to clear your eyes?
sore to kore to wa mattaku mattaku betsumondai
それとこれとは まったくまったく 別問題
Those are completely, completely different issues.
(faito!) kenka shichatta toki mo
(ファイト!)喧嘩しちゃった時も
(Fight!) Even when I get in a fight with you,
(daoun!) kanari hekonda toki mo
(ダウン!)かなり凹んだ時も
(Down!) even when I get really down,
(shai!) hitori de itai you na toki mo
(シャイ!)一人で居たいような時も
(Shy!) even when I feel like I want to be alone,
futokizukeba chikaku ni iru shinaba morotomo
ふと気付けば 近くに居る 死なば諸共
before I realise it, you're right there; we'll be together even in death!
nande daro
なんでだろ
I wonder why it is.
soba ni itainda
そばに居たいんだ
I want to be with you.
kimi to issho nara
君と一緒なら
When I'm with you,
tokei hyakubai soku
時計百倍速
time goes 100 times faster!
tanoshii na
楽しいな
It's fun, isn't it?
tanoshisugirunda
楽しすぎるんだ
It's way too fun!
sasuga saikou friend
流石 最高 friend
As expected of my best friend!
Hey! na na na na na na na
Hey! ななななななな
Hey! Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
nannanoyo
なんなのよー
What is it?
yabai synchro
ヤバいシンクロー
The synchro is amazing!
itsumo oosawagi
いつも大騒ぎ
Always making an uproar,
kanari gokinjo meiwaku
かなりご近所迷惑
bothering the neighbours a lot.
ima nanji
今何時
What time is it now?
ato ne yorereihifu
あとねヨレレイヒーフ
And then yo de le hi hoo!
wake wakannainai
訳分かんないない!
I don't get it at all!
soredoshira
ソレドシラ
So re doh si la!
souzou ijou nante iu ka saiko
想像以上なんて言うか最高
It's better than I imagined, the absolute best!
aa da kou da ittetemo tomodachi (wasshoi!)
あーだこーだ言ってても友達 (わっしょい!)
Even if I say this and that, we're still friends. (Hooray!)
jou jou yuu jou banjin maji kaichou
じょーじょーゆーじょー万事マジ快調
Amazing friendship, the absolute best!
cha cha la cha la cha cha
ちゃちゃらちゃらちゃちゃー
Cha Cha La Cha La Cha Cha!
Nichijou 78
I will now do something that has never been done before and will never be done again.
Domestic Violence.
What did you think?
Even if you ask us that...
That was very like you, Fecchan.
That was definitely very like you, Fecchan.
Yeah, that was very like you, Fecchan.
Next I'm going to try something that's not like me.
I fell!
That was very like Fecchan.
Oh.
That's definitely very like Fecchan.
Newcomer 1
Hey! We've got daihuku! How about one?
I'm sorry, but can you wear this instead?
Hey!
We've got daihuku!
How about one?
I'm sorry, but...
...could you not talk?
Newcomer 2
Could you possibly put on some clothes?
Are you mad at me?!
Newcomer 3
You aren't mad at me?
What is it, then?
Hey...
It's all right if you talk right now!
Love-Like
I hope I pass the test to get into Tokisadame High School.
I hope the person above me passes.
I hope the person to my right passes.
I hope the person below me passes.
Good Luck!
I hope the person to my right passes.
I hope the person below me passes.
Good Luck!
Nichijou 79
Here I go!
Yes!
You didn't jump it!
But the bar is-
To be more precise, you didn't go over it!
Just what should I do for you to properly learn how to jump?
The sun's going down!
I'm sorry.
I'll try harder next time.
I'm going to lower the bar this time,
so just take it slow and jump as I taught you.
I got it.
Anyway, I need to get better before the next examination.
I need to be able to jump, even if it's just a bit.
Or else everyone...
...will laugh at me!
How was it?!
You stupid pumpkin!
Why don't you jump with the form I taught you?!
Are you messing with me?!
Well, in my head, it's an elegant backward jump...
An elegant backward jump?
Your form is more like...
...a torpedo!
A human... torpedo.
I didn't say that!
Wait...
I did say that...
No way! You're joking, right?
You don't even realise it?!
Sorry.
Well, I'll stick around until you can do it, Mio-chan.
You always let me copy your homework.
It's my turn today!
Let's keep going until you get it!
Anyway, just take it slow!
First, try to jump like you're just stepping over it.
Mio-chan, just calm down.
It's all right!
katari tsugu hito mo naku
Even if the names of the stars scattered
This isn't the first time I've been bad at sports.
fuki susabu kaze no naka e
within the fierce winds
Hey, Mio-chan.
This is soccer!
My physical strength is about average.
magire chirabaru hoshi no na wa
and are completely forgotten
But when rules are thrown in, I forget what I'm doing.
Sympathetic Heart
Fall!
wasureraretemo
and not remembered by anyone,
On your mark...
Start!
Mio-chan, falling is the other way around!
But if I don't do anything about it, nothing will change!
Headlight, Taillight   tabi wa mada owaranai
Headlight, Taillight. The journey isn't over yet.
I'll just stay the same!
Here we go.
Mio-chan, we're not trying to be propellers!
We're doing somersaults!
I don't care if the effort is wasted.
Headlight, Taillight   tabi wa mada owaranai
Headlight, Taillight. The journey isn't over yet.
I don't care if there are no results!
ashiato wa furuame to
Your footsteps vanish into time
However, there is one thing!
There's one thing that I can do for myself!
One, two, three!
furu toki no naka e kiete
along with the falling rain.
Let's try once more.
I'm doing it for Yukko.
tataeru uta wa
Even if songs of praise
I'm going to rest for a while.
Oh, all right.
eiyuu no tame ni sugitemo
are no longer for heroes,
And I'm doing it for myself!
Headlight, Taillight   tabi wa mada owaranai
Headlight, Taillight. The journey isn't over yet.
I won't give up!
If I'm going to give up,
I'll give up after I do everything I can!
Effort will always open up a door.
Headlight, Taillight   tabi wa mada owaranai
Headlight, Taillight. The journey isn't over yet.
It later became known as the "Torpedo Jump".
White tigers are like this!
They're kinda...
...all sleeping.
That one even has its butt pointed at us.
I guess.
Also, they're pretty far away, so we can't see them well.
We came all the way to see this, but it's so boring!
At least we got to see them.
I guess so.
Yay!
Nichijou 80
It's raining!
I need to bring in the laundry!
Hey, where are you going?
It's too late.
Just bring it in!
It's raining!
Professor, Sakamoto-san, I'm home!
It's raining pretty hard outside.
Did you bring in the laundry?
It's because Sakamoto told me to bring it in!
It's the truth.
It's really because Sakamoto said that.
Sakamoto-san said to bring it in, so it fell to the ground?
That's not it.
Sakamoto said to bring it in,
and then he said to drop it.
I didn't say that!
Geez, that startled me.
What are you saying all of a sudden?!
It's because you said that.
I never told you to drop it.
You did.
I didn't.
You did!
I didn't!
Just leave me alone!
Nano.
I'll go sacrifice Sakamoto.
Is that okay?
What do you mean?
It's all right.
If you wash the dirt, the clothes will come back to being clean.
That's right.
That's right!
However, today won't come back.
Neither of you are getting any dinner tonight.
Why am I always the victim?
But it was Sakamoto who did it!
Which is why I'll go sacrifice him. Is that okay?
All right.
I'll take Sakamoto-san,
and only you won't get dinner.
Wait, no!
I'll be the sacrifice!
I was the one who dropped them,
and I was the one who got them all wet!
Tonight's dinner is omelette rice!
Eggs were on sale!
Wait, I can eat tonight?
Oh right, I completely forgot!
Um, well...
I'll just let you eat today.
Yay!
You won't get anything tomorrow, though!
Swim, swim.
Sharky, sharky, chomp!
If that happens, do this!
Mio-chan, Mai-chan!
Selamat pagi!
Wasn't it a pain to make a self portrait out of clay?
Oh, that was due today?
What's this?
Did Mio-sensei forget to do her homework?
I totally thought it was due tomorrow.
Mai-chan, did you do it?
Crap.
Mai-chan, you, too?
Maybe it'll start raining today.
Not just a bit of rain,
it's going to be a deluge.
A deluge.
Nichijou 81
It actually...
...started raining.
Y-You guys...
What are you doing to my temple?!
You donation thieves!
T-That was close!
You're cursed...
Plague bringers!
Get out...
Get out of my temple!
"Just go with it"...
...is what the girls thought as they were hit by the late autumn rain.
Nichijou 82
Please, President!
I'm going to have a match against Takasaki-sensei.
Could you be the referee?
Referee? For Go Soccer?
That's correct.
If I win this match, he'll have no choice but to become our advisor.
I'm going to win this!
But how do I do it?
Don't worry.
The beginner's guide to Go Soccer that I lent you earlier:
If you take a look at that, you'll be fine.
It might be my fault for not reading the book,
but I have no clue what these two are doing!
Is this really Go Soccer?!
Even if you had read it, you wouldn't understand.
Ogi!
Because they both started off with prohibited techniques,
they're in a high-level stand-off that ignores reason.
For example, that arm raised straight up.
If you consider that a leg on a Go board,
then the opposition's stance is like the Go stones.
It's like they're in perfect unison.
The way he's holding the ball is deceptive.
Based on my judgement, these two are...
...becoming the sun.
I have no clue what he's saying!
They started moving!
Oh no!
Be loved!
Ogi, what is that supposed-
Be quiet.
Don't you get it?
The grave atmosphere around them.
If they make a single mistake,
someone could die.
What in the world is going on?
It's been a while since I've seen such a high-level battle!
Of course, the wind is rustling.
Oh no!
That stance!
Could he be planning to do that in a field match?!
Is he insane?!
But I can't just stand by and watch in this situation.
Father, I am going to use it.
It's all for the sake of justice!
Shine a light...
...and become a path!
Ogi forbidden style.
Super Ogi!
Ogi Star!
This is it!
Oh, Final Loved!
Nice going!
You too!
Good heavens.
I started this club just to play around.
This is...
...becoming something outrageous!
yasei no uma wa
野生の馬は
A wild horse
yasei no uma wa
野生の馬は
A wild horse
naze kakete yuku
なぜ駆けてゆく
Why does he run around?
kubi motage
首もたげ
With his head raised
o wo nabikasete
尾をなびかせて
and his tail fluttering
kinniku no yakudou mune ni
筋肉の躍動胸に
his muscles throbbing in his chest
doko made mo
どこまでも
Endlessly
doko made mo
どこまでも
Endlessly
kakete yuku
駆けてゆく
Running around
natsu no arashi no naka wo
夏の嵐の中を
In a summer storm
itazuma ni mukatte
稲妻に向かって
Toward the thunder
itazuma ni mukatte
稲妻に向かって
Toward the thunder
oh-oh oh-oh
オ　オー　オ　オー
yasei no uma wa
野生の馬は
A wild horse
doko made mo kakete yuku
どこまでも　駆けてゆく
Running around endlessly
kakete yuku
駆けてゆく
Endlessly
Word Of The Day
Get down when nobody's looking.
Free for
employees
No matter how much I get stepped on, like a phoenix, I shall come back.
That's me: Clay!
Scramble here!
Today, I'll be changing into many different forms in order to fight with the kids!
Next time on Nichijou: Episode 20.
Narration:    Mitsuya Yuuji
Very well, then! Kids, come at me!