What is this about?
What's going on?
Kill Henrietta...
Louise!
Saito!
You idiot! Idiot! Where were you all this time?
Sorry, Louise. It's all right now.
Albion troops?
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君のそばにいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai ga bokura wo tameshitatte
どんな未来が僕らを試したって
No matter how the future tests us
kitto…
きっと…
I’m sure…
aa futari no unmei
ああ 二人の運命
Ah, it’s our destiny
meguriaeta no wa
巡り合えたのは
I was able to meet you
kimi no koe kikoeta kara
君の声 聞こえたから
Because I heard your voice
sou pinchi na dekigoto
そう ピンチな出来事
Yeah, even if crisis events
oshiyosete kite mo
押し寄せてきても
Press on at me
kimi to ireba norikoerareru
君といれば乗り越えられる
If I'm with you, then I can overcome them
tokimeki to makenki to
ときめきと負けん気と
Palpitations and competitive spirit
urahara de haraharasuru kedo
裏腹でハラハラするけど
Excite me on the contrary, but-
Stay with me
tada kimi o mamoritai yo
ただ 君を守りたいよ
I only want to protect you
tooi sekai de umareta futari da kedo
遠い世界で生まれた二人だけど
We were born in distant worlds
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君の側にいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai mo kibou ni kaeyou
どんな未来も希望に変えよう
Let’s change any future into hope
Forever
The Farewell Wedding Ceremony
Lowscythe military port (occupied by Tristain)
Don't push!
Please don't worry! Everyone will be able to get on!
Your Highness.
I'm glad you're safe.
Cardinal Masarini.
What happened in the city of South Gotha?
I heard our men started a rebellion.
It seems that they enemy had placed
some kind of a magic item in our wells.
So, they're under an enemy spell?
Most likely.
Since Albion marched in during the chaos,
I didn't have time to investigate.
All I could do was retreat here with Her Highness.
Not only did they recapture the city of South Gotha,
but they're also approaching our
position with seventy thousand men.
Your Highness, there's no time to waste.
Please board the escape ship.
No. I shall board the last ship.
Your Highness!
I am the Queen of Tristain.
Until everyone escapes safely, I have no intention of moving from here.
Your Highness...
Wait! We finally made it back to Lowscythe!
Why do you want to take care of the rearguard?
Let go of me.
The rearguard, you know, is the last line of defence.
You basically have to resist the enemy force while everybody else escapes.
I know that!
Is that an order from the Princess?
The Princess isn't aware of this.
Miss Vallière, we need your strength in order to save the Queen's life.
I beg of you.
What? Cardinal, please, raise your head.
If it is to save Her Highness' life, I'll do anything.
Miss Vallière...
This is not an order.
And... you... accepted it?
Are you insane?!
They're coming here with seventy thousand men!
I have my Void magic.
Void?
You couldn't use it last time.
But this time I might be able to!
If it means saving the Princess' life,
I will make it happen.
If I can save the Princess with my Void magic,
there would be no greater honour.
Screw honour.
Fuck that!
Do you understand?
They're telling you to be a bait!
They're asking you to die!
I'm going to turn down that mission!
Stop it!
Louise...
This is something that only I can do.
Therefore, I have to do it.
Hey, Louise-
Our men don't have the strength to hold back seventy thousand men.
But why do you have to-
It's not just for the Princess!
The maid and everyone else at the Fairy Inn might be killed.
They may get shamed.
I don't want to die either.
But I'm an aristocrat.
It's an honour to die for one's people.
You make fun of it,
but is it that insignificant to die for everyone else?
I don't get it...
I don't get it.
Yeah, I also want to protect everyone.
But... the one I want to protect more than anyone else is-
Saito.
Louise.
You get out of here, Saito.
You don't have to die staying with me.
What did you say? Hey, Louise?
Please, just get out of here.
After all, you aren't from this world.
Are... you saying that seriously?
Louise...
Fine. Okay. I won't stop you anymore.
Saito?
Let's have a toast.
In my world, we have a toast and say goodbye at times like this.
Just a second.
It's a farewell.
Farewell?
Here we are. Since it's this kind of a situation, no one will blame us for stealing one.
Damn it, it won't open.
What's going on?
Hey, Saito?
It's really tight...
I have one request upon our farewell.
What? This is the last one after all, so I'll listen to you.
I want to get...
You want to what?
I said...
I said I want to get married!
Married?!
D-Don't get me wrong!
I-I don't want to die unwed!
It's unsatisfactory to get married to you, but I won't complain.
A-Anyway, as a proof that I existed, I want to at least get married!
Come on, hurry.
Excuse me, could we buy this flower?
I'll give it to you. Take it.
I'm closing the store anyway.
Thank you.
What is that?
They're Éclair D'amour.
"Éclair D'amour"?
What does it mean?
I-It doesn't matter what it means!
Here!
Louise? Ah...
I'm sure that after this, a definite bond will form between Saito and me.
Not one between master and familiar.
You better work.
Louise.
It's ready.
Well, cheers.
Cheers.
So, how do you do weddings here?
Um, I don't really know, but...
Kiss of oath?
Why are you like that?
You've got no sense of delicacy to the very end!
But-
We take each other's hands and say our vows.
Louise.
I love you.
I'm glad I met you.
M-Me, too.
You were such a strange familiar and made me doubt you,
but now, I'm glad it was you.
Louise.
Thank you so much for all you've done.
I... I also...
Louise...
Hey, Saito-kun.
Julio!
What are you doing here?
I'd like to know what's going on.
I heard she accepted the rearguard mission,
so I was searching for you two.
To ensure that she won't run away?
No. To tell her to run away.
The Princess is important, but I'm more interested in the cute Louise.
I see.
Perfect timing, then.
Take care of Louise.
Sure, you got it.
And what about you?
I'm going... to meet the enemy of seventy thousand.
May I ask one question?
Didn't you think that dying for honour is a stupid thing to do?
It isn't for honour.
It's because I said "I love you" to Louise.
If I didn't go now, I have a feeling that
those words would lose their meaning.
You've made me want to say "I love you" to you, too.
Hearing that from you won't make me happy at all.
See ya.
Take care of Louise for me.
The enemy is outside of Lowcythe!
Hurry!
The ships will depart soon!
I won't let you guys reach the port!
What?
You...
Cancel the departure!
I'll go get Louise back!
Your Highness!
Let me go!
If you go now, you'll lose your life!
But I can't make Louise take my place!
Let me go!
Please let me go!
I beg you, Your Highness.
If you die here, the matter will not end as a simple failure in tactics.
Our country will fall into chaos.
Cardinal Masarini...
If you were to jump out now,
Miss Vallière's noble act would have been in vain!
But...
Are you awake, Sleeping Beauty?
Julio?
What am I...
Where am I?
On a ship?
I need to stop the enemy!
Miss Vallière!
Where's Saito-san?
Saito?
Where's Saito?
He isn't here.
Saito-kun went to face Albion's troops alone.
What did you just say?
He went to fight Albion by himself.
While you were sleeping from the effects of a potion.
No way... Saito...
So... he used that potion?
But... I gave it to Saito-san because I wanted him to live.
Siesta!
Saito...
In order to save me...
Louise-chan!
Saito!
Louise-chan! It's too late!
No, stop it!
Let me off! It isn't too late at all!
I can't let Saito die alone!
You can't!
Let go of me!
Let me go! Please!
Saito!
Why'd I have to turn into that?
For your beloved, right?
Hey, Del.
What?
Will I... die?
Probably.
Well, if you're going to die anyway, then do your best to act like a hero.
I guess you have point.
All right.
Enemy!
Partner! Up front!
Are you all right, Partner?
Damn it, I regret not being able to do what comes after the wedding.
Damn you all!
Louise...
Man, I don't want to die.
Partner!
Éclair D'amour...
A magic flower that informs one of the condition of one's significant other even when they're far apart.
No...
Saito!
Louise!
Who would have thought that Saito-kun would...
We were saved because of him.
I'm sorry...
It's all my responsibility.
Your Highness...
Louise...
Saito...
How long do you intend on doing that,
Crybaby Louise!
You let your familiar die because you went to the battlefield...
...ignoring Father's word against doing so.
Onee-sama!
My fault...
Saito died because of me...
Stand firm!
Why the big deal over some familiar's death?
Louise!
What do you mean by "some familiar"?!
He was special to me!
Saito was a special person to me!
Louise...
Get out!
Leave me alone...
Let me be alone!
Let's go, Onee-sama.
Was it a mistake to go to the battlefield?
Why did you have to go and die for the sake of my honour?
Saito...
I love you...
I can say it without hesitation now.
So, please!
Saito!
Louise!
Saito! Saito!
It's really you, Saito!
You're not a ghost, are you?
You're alive, right?
Yeah.
I'm home, Louise.
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
I thought you died!
You idiot!
You know,
I was saved by a fairy.
Fairy?
Wake up, Gandalfr.
Gandalfr, the God's left hand.
Go home.
To where you should return.
So huge!
And she took care of me for a while.
But man, her breasts were so huge, they surprised me.
They were bigger than both Siesta's and Jessica's.
I see. I'm happy for you.
I see... S-So you met a big-breasted fairy.
Louise-san?
You do like big breasts, don't you?
You love huge breasts, don't you?
Wait, Louise!
Then keep living with the fairy!
What was that?
Look!
Wow.
Saito-san!
I can't forgive you for making me drink a sleeping potion!
Calm down, Louise!
Saito!
Welcome back!
Darling! You were alive!
Tough.
Partner, don't you think the enemy of seventy thousand was easier than this?
I think so, too.
Saito-san?
Siesta!
Saito-san.
I kept believing... that you were still alive.
Saito...
You pervert dog!
I'm sorry!
Y-You stupid dog!
chanto koko ni ite watashi no chikaku de
ちゃんとココにいて! 私の近くで
Be right here! close to me
zutto watashi o itsumo itsumo mitsumete nasai
ずっと私をいつもいつも見つめてなさい
Always, always look at me at all times
yosomishiteta desho hoka no onna no ko
よそ見してたでしょっ 他の女の子
You looked away, didn’t you? At other girls
o-shiokisuru wa furari furari furachi na yatsu wa
お仕置きするわ　フラリフラリ不埒なヤツは
I’ll punish those who are wavering and insolent
Don't touch! kikanai kara ne iiwake wa
Don't touch! 聞かないからね　言い訳は
Don’t touch! Because I won’t listen to excuses
Touch me... tsukareta kara nee kata o kashite yo
Touch me… 疲れたから… ねぇ肩を貸してよ
Touch me… because I'm tired… Hey, lend me your shoulder
suki yo nante uso yo
スキよ　なんて嘘よ
I love you, it’s a lie
kirai sore mo uso da wa
キライ　それも嘘だわ
I hate you, that’s a lie, too
nai nai nai dame yo kanchigai
ないないない　ダメよ勘違い
Nay nay nay, it’s useless, it’s a misunderstanding
dakara suki yo nante iwanai
だから「スキよ」なんて言わない
So I won’t say, “I love you”
Non non non dokka e ittara
Non non non　どっかへ行ったら
Non non non, because I absolutely won’t forgive you
zettai ni yurusanai kara ne
絶対に　許さないからね!
If you go to somewhere else
datte
だって
But
honto wa dare yori soba ni itai no
ホントは誰より傍にいたいの
The truth is, I want to be by your side more than anyone else
ai no kusari de sanposhimasho
愛の鎖で　散歩しましょ!
Let’s go take a walk in chains of love!
I... to be honest...
...might love you...
The End