It is true I touched Miss Tiffania's breasts in the infirmary.
I couldn't help but touch her indecent breasts,
so I pinned Miss Tiffania down,
despite her resistance, to fulfil my desire.
The more Miss Tiffania resisted, the more it excited me...
Who said you could stop? There's more to read, isn't there?
"The more Miss Tiffania resisted, the more it excited me,
and I kept f-fondling her b-breasts", right?!
I can't read this junk!
Forget this pledge.
It's not junk!
I saw it with my own eyes!
R-Right when you were touching her breasts.
I told you that Tiffa asked me to touch them!
How am I supposed to believe such a lie?!
Continue reading now.
Fine.
Eh... I, Saito Chevalier de Hiraga, have deeply reflected upon my act.
Additionally...
Say it.
Or do you want to live the rest of your life dressed like that?
I do not prefer large breasts!
I swear I will never touch anyone else's breasts!
Sign it.
I feel bad for Saito-san.
This matter is between the familiar and his master!
You stay out of this!
But...
It's fine, Siesta.
Saito-san...
What? Sign it already.
I can't take this anymore.
I can't sign that thing!
Hey, I won't allow you to go off like that!
What's the point of being with a master who can't trust her familiar?
See ya.
After seeing that...
...what do you expect me to trust?!
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
mejirushi no nai michi mo heiki sa futari nara
メジルシのない道も平気さ　ふたりなら
Even on a road without signs, I'll be fine, if we're together
saki no mienai tabi mayoinagara mitsuketa yo
先の見えない旅　迷いながら見つけたよ
On a journey that I can't see ahead of, while I was lost, I found it
boku no iru basho kimi no tonari
僕の居る場所　君のとなり
That my place to be is next to you
kenkashite nando mo hanashita sono te
喧嘩して　何度も離したその手
When we quarrelled, I let go of your hand again and again
hikiyose dakitai ima
引き寄せ抱きたい　今
I want to pull close and hold it now
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
namida no ame ni utaretara
涙の雨に打たれたら
If I'm beaten down by the rain of tears
I wanna hold you sugu yobi na yo boku no namae
I wanna hold you　すぐ呼びなよ　僕の名前
I wanna hold you, call my name immediately
dakishime ni yuku wa
抱きしめに行くわ
I'll go embrace you
kanashimi mo tsuyogari mo kono te ni uketomeru
悲しみも強がりもこの手に　受け止める
I'll accept sadness and bluffing in my hands
The Captivating Girl's Bath
Why can't she believe what I say?
Look at it from her point of view, too.
Before I do that, she should listen to my story.
Colbert-sensei...
Sensei, I became a chevalier.
I was really happy. It felt like I was accepted.
I want to see that world.
Take me there one day.
You were the only person who believed what I said.
I wanted to talk much more with you.
Tiffa asked you to? Yeah, right?!
You touched them yourself!
There is a limit to how much he can make a fool out of me!
The only ones you're allowed to touch are mine...
Ow...
What? When did I fall asleep?
Um, would you give this to Guiche-sama?
Would you give this to Reinard-sama?
Form a queue, please. A queue, please.
What's that?
What is this about?
It increased after the Luft Panzer Ritter incident.
Reinard-san. You have a first-year girl calling you.
Okay.
Who's he?
A new member, Gimli.
He joined because he wanted to become popular among the girls.
Geez, everyone's hooking up.
I never knew I'd have trouble with being too popular.
Guiche.
M-Montmorency!
Who gave you those?
Y-You've got it wrong, Montmorency.
I prepared these for you. Believe me.
I want to believe that.
But I'm worried.
The girls won't leave you alone nowadays.
Montmorency...
Totally different from someone we know.
Yup, totally.
Hey there, Saito.
Hey, Maricor-
What do you think? Doesn't it look good?
Brigitta insisted on me wearing it.
Please, Maricorn-sama.
It's hard being so popular.
Spring has come to him, too...
Owowow... What are you doing, Guiche?
Just come with me.
Looks like you're the only one who
doesn't have things working out right.
What, Saito, you had another fight with Louise?
Want me to teach you how to treat girls?
Are you not going to come back?
Are you that mad?
Where have you been, Sai-
I-I'm sorry to not be Saito-san.
No one said that stupid dog's name!
I don't think Saito-san will come back here tonight.
What's that?
You talk like I'm waiting for him to come back.
Who cares about that stupid dog?
It feels great to not have him around.
Why do I deserve this?
What's the reason behind the fight?
He touched breasts that weren't hers.
I'm surprised that he's still alive.
There.
Eat up. You're hungry, right?
I don't have much of an appetite.
I envy how you don't have anything to worry about.
Saito's totally depressed.
Poor him.
I want to see him cheer up soon.
There's nothing we really can do.
Captain Guiche!
What is it, Gimli?
I have a great idea!
Sure, I regret what I did a little.
I think I said too much.
But...
I just can't forgive him!
We should turn back!
Don't you want to find out the truth?!
We're aristocrats!
Who knows when we'll have to die for our country.
And yet, you say you can die before discovering the truth?!
Our friend Verdandi has reached the holy land!
Let's get Saito immediately!
Yes, Sir!
Is bigger better after all?
Um...
May I join you?
I-
It's your choice where you soak.
I guess.
T-There has to be a limit!
Il Earth Del...
I've brought Saito-san.
So what are you guys showing me?
Perfect timing! The hole is through!
Hey, Saito. You go first.
Me?
Take a look and cheer up.
What is this about?
What is this?
Fog?
C-Could this be...
The girls' bath?
You guys made a hole to the girls' bath?
It's a present from us.
This won't cheer me up.
What are you guys thinking?
Louise.
Tiffa!
M-Miss Tiffania?
Get out of the way, Saito!
As the captain, I deserve the view.
Let me have a peek, too!
Damn it. I can't see well with the fog.
Please switch off already.
Um, thank you.
For saving me the other day.
Oh, that. It was nothing.
I wanted to thank you sooner,
but it felt like you were avoiding me, so I couldn't find the right time to.
I-I'm not avoiding you.
It's just that...
I... I...
I can die happy now...
You don't want to be friends with someone with scary breasts like these, right?
No, it's not that.
Louise-san. May I please touch your breasts?
What? Touch my breasts?
I want to know what real breasts feel like.
Please.
E-Even if you say so...
In exchange, you touch mine, too.
And please tell me what's strange about them.
Wait, stop. I'm not mentally prepared for this yet.
Girls do that in the bath?
So this is what real breasts feel like.
I'm sorry it's flat.
I knew something was strange with mine.
That stupid Saito!
The two girls are...
Change already.
Move! You're in the way, Louise!
Right. Tiffa's not the only person they can see.
At this rate, everyone will see Louise naked.
D-Don't worry about it. They're just a little bigger than others.
Thank goodness.
I had Saito-san touch and check them too,
but it looked like he didn't have a good idea.
W-Wait, what did you just say?
You had Saito touch them for you?
Yes.
I told you that Tiffa asked me to touch them!
So Saito was telling the truth.
Yet I once more didn't believe him.
I didn't try to believe him at all.
Louise-san?
What should I do?
If Saito doesn't return...
I-I'm sorry! I asked a really strange thing of Saito-san.
He's supposed to be your lover...
He is not my lover!
He's only my familiar!
You guys...
Don't look!
A man's voice.
Look! There's a hole here!
Crap!
We must retreat.
I told you we shouldn't do this.
You'd better get moving, Reinard.
Wait!
Don't get caught, everyone.
Wai- You guys!
I'm stuck!
Reinard...
I never imagined you of all people would do this.
I-I was against it.
T-The Captain proposed the idea!
The one who says that is the most suspicious one.
Be a man and...
...accept the wrath you deserve!
Damn it! Just a little more to go...
There he is!
So you got in through that hole.
Please, spare my life.
Would there still be someone in there?
Stop hiding and come out, peeping tom!
Ow...
Looks like it's best you surrender.
What's this?
Tiffa!
What the heck is this?!
I'm gonna crash! I'm gonna crash!
Ow...
Who is it?
Quiet.
That voice...
Tabitha?
You got me out of there?
Sylphid's dinner.
For something like that?
Knights never maintain a debt.
I see...
Anyway, you saved me. Thanks.
Shh.
Guiche! Where are you hiding?!
Geez...
Come out!
Guiche!
Reinard already told me that you were part of the peeping!
W-Why isn't Tabitha wearing anything?
P-Please, don't hold me any closer.
We found Guiche!
Where?!
Saved...
What?
Ghost...
Ghost?
What? You're scared of ghosts?
Don't worry, I'm with you.
Hey, Tabitha.
Shoot, this is turning me on.
F-Forgive me, Montmorency.
It was on impulse. Just a whim!
This time around, I really know what kind of person you are.
Goodbye.
A ball for dolls?
I could dance with you if you want.
I've been working hard to this day, wishing to see her smile,
yet why doesn't it ever work out?
I'll believe you.
Obviously, I'm at fault.
Even if it was Tiffa's request, I did something to betray Louise.
Yet I say I haven't done anything wrong, but I've hurt Louise.
I'm the worst.
The dolls dance here every night.
I heard you were in that hole, too.
You're not going to deny it?
No.
You're scum.
But I didn't know that I was being taken to peep on the girls' bath.
I tagged along since they said there was something good to see.
But of course, you don't believe what I say, right?
I'll believe you.
W-Well, you're not smart enough to lie.
I know you well.
Then, even about Tiffa?
I'll believe you.
Thank you, Louise.
I-I'm sorry, too.
But even if you were asked, it's your fault for actually doing it.
Yeah. I'm sorry, Louise.
I promise never to touch any other girl's breasts.
You mean it?
E-Even though you like big ones?
I prefer small ones like yours.
Hey, stop throwing me off.
If you're so honest...
Let go of me.
I don't want to.
I've always wanted to do this.
Saito...
You have to kiss me to make up for it.
Most certainly, Master.
Ghost.
I see...
It... It looks like you really do like small ones.
Calm down, Louise.
There's a reason for this!
I don't like girls smaller than Louise either!
I hereby pledge not to touch the breasts of others!
Sign it.
Yes!
Saito-san...
You can touch mine, okay?
Y-You know what happens i-if you break the pledge, right?
Wait, Louise!
Sigh...
It's impossible.
But...
kyuu ni senaka wo mukete kakedashita wa (Just love me)
急に背中を向けて 駆け出したわ
I suddenly turned my back on you and ran away
hoka no ko ni yasashiku shiteta kara yo
ほかの子に優しくしてたからよ
Because you've been so gentle to many other girls
Boy onegai oikakete yo
Boyお願い 追いかけてよ
Boy, please chase after me
ato ni wa hikenai kara
あとには引けないから
Because it won't be over after this
pun pun pun
I am so sorry
gomen to ienakute gomen ne
ゴメンと言えなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't say "I'm sorry", sorry ♥
shinjite iru no ni kuchibiru ga togaru
信じているのに くちびるが尖る
Even though I believe you, my lips are pouting
kawaiku narenakute gomen ne
可愛くなれなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't be cute, sorry ♥
kosame no furu machi tsukamaete
小雨の降る街 つかまえて
Catch me in the town where a drizzle is falling
furimuku kara nakanaori no chu o shite
振り向くから 仲直りのCHU～をして
Because I'll turn around and give you a make-up kiss
atsui ryouude no naka de
熱い両腕の中で
In your warm arms
Next Time
Something's wrong with me.
My chest is aching. My body is trembling.
Is this what love is?
Zero no Tsukaima. Princess no Rondo.
The Taboo Magic Potion.
Saito, look at me!
The Taboo Magic Potion
I won't forgive you if you look away.