Shinonome Nano.
Paralysing drugs, Mr. Short Circuit and a trap hole.
To perfectly evade all the traps I've set for her so far...
She's much better than I had expected.
I want her!
So far I've tried not to arouse suspicion by trying to capture her at school,
Nakamura Sensei 2
but now that it's come to this...
Could that possibly be...
Wait, wait!
Wait, hold on!
Thanks for the food!
Go get your dad.
Why?
Onee-chan, where's the remote?
It was under the kettle yesterday.
It wasn't him.
Hey, who are you?!
What are you doing?
A robber?!
Crap!
What, a girl?
jou jou yuu jou banjin maji kaichou
じょーじょーゆーじょー万事マジ快調
Amazing friendship, the absolute best!
na na na na na na na
ななななななな
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
hai! icchaimashou!
ハイ!言っちゃいましょう!
All right! I'll say it!
kimi wa best best friend
キミはベストベスト フレンド
You are my best, best friend!
(furai!) chotto fuzakete mitara
(フライ!) ちょっとふざけてみたら
(Fly!) When I joke around a bit,
(shain!) motto fuzake kaeshite kuru
(シャイン!) もっとふざけ帰してくる
(Shine!) You joke around more in response.
(La La La) ikogochi ii ttara arya shinai
(ラーラーラー)居心地良いったらありゃしない
(La La La) Nothing is better than this!
(wai!) iya na koto attatte
(ワイ!) 嫌なことあったって
(Why!) Even if something bad happens,
(fain!) sokkou wasurechaunda
(ファイン!) 即効忘れちゃうんだー
(Fine!) I immediately forget about it!
(La La La)
(ラーラーラー)
itsudatte jan jan yarimasho
いつだって、じゃんじゃんやりましょ♪
Always keep it going!
24 jikan issho demo mondai nai
２４時間一緒でも問題ない
Being together 24 hours a day isn't a problem.
marude futago ka oyako ka clone saibou
まるで双子か親子かクローン細胞
Just like twins, or a parent and child, or clone cyborgs.
kore ja me ga sumu hitsuyou wa nakunakunai!?
これじゃ目が澄む必要はなくなくない!？
Then isn't there no reason to clear your eyes?
sore to kore to wa mattaku mattaku betsumondai
それとこれとは まったくまったく 別問題
Those are completely, completely different issues.
(faito!) kenka shichatta toki mo
(ファイト!)喧嘩しちゃった時も
(Fight!) Even when I get in a fight with you,
(daoun!) kanari hekonda toki mo
(ダウン!)かなり凹んだ時も
(Down!) even when I get really down,
(shai!) hitori de itai you na toki mo
(シャイ!)一人で居たいような時も
(Shy!) even when I feel like I want to be alone,
futokizukeba chikaku ni iru shinaba morotomo
ふと気付けば 近くに居る 死なば諸共
before I realise it, you're right there; we'll be together even in death!
nande daro
なんでだろ
I wonder why it is.
soba ni itainda
そばに居たいんだ
I want to be with you.
kimi to issho nara
君と一緒なら
When I'm with you,
tokei hyakubai soku
時計百倍速
time goes 100 times faster!
tanoshii na
楽しいな
It's fun, isn't it?
tanoshisugirunda
楽しすぎるんだ
It's way too fun!
sasuga saikou friend
流石 最高 friend
As expected of my best friend!
Hey! na na na na na na na
Hey! ななななななな
Hey! Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
nannanoyo
なんなのよー
What is it?
yabai synchro
ヤバいシンクロー
The synchro is amazing!
itsumo oosawagi
いつも大騒ぎ
Always making an uproar,
kanari gokinjo meiwaku
かなりご近所迷惑
bothering the neighbours a lot.
ima nanji
今何時
What time is it now?
ato ne yorereihifu
あとねヨレレイヒーフ
And then yo de le hi hoo!
wake wakannainai
訳分かんないない!
I don't get it at all!
soredoshira
ソレドシラ
So re doh si la!
souzou ijou nante iu ka saiko
想像以上なんて言うか最高
It's better than I imagined, the absolute best!
aa da kou da ittetemo tomodachi (wasshoi!)
あーだこーだ言ってても友達 (わっしょい!)
Even if I say this and that, we're still friends. (Hooray!)
jou jou yuu jou banjin maji kaichou
じょーじょーゆーじょー万事マジ快調
Amazing friendship, the absolute best!
cha cha la cha la cha cha
ちゃちゃらちゃらちゃちゃー
Cha Cha La Cha La Cha Cha!
Oh, it's Nano-chan.
T-Thank you.
That seems heavy.
Not at all.
Thank you very much.
Are you sure that you can carry them by yourself?
Nichijou 102
Mio-chan, Mio-chan!
Big news!
I'm writing a report, so tell me later.
It's not the time for that!
I saw it!
What did you see?
Sasahara-senpai and Nano-chan were walking together!
Huh?
Well, I was expecting a bigger reaction.
And?
So, yeah...
They seemed to be having a casual conversation.
I see.
That's not very out of the ordinary, is it?
Eh?
They're human.
Of course they'll talk.
Well?
Is that it?
Yeah, that's it.
I need to finish this report by next period,
so I need to concentrate.
Right, sorry.
That was lame...
And?
Huh?
So what happened?
What do you mean?
I'm asking what they were casually talking about.
Hello?
Yukko-san?
Well, um...
Sasahara-senpai was saying how her books looked heavy.
And?
That's it.
Yukko, are you just stupid?
I've always thought you were stupid,
but to think you were this stupid...
Saying there's "big news"...
Your idiocy itself is amazing, don't you think?
An amazing idiot?
Just kidding.
Well, Nano-chan and Sasahara-senpai were kissing, too.
Come on, now...
After having a greeting kiss,
they went to go buy bread together.
And after they talked a bit about the bread they bought,
Sasahara-senpai...
Sasahara-senpai?!
...slowly began to take off his clothes.
Take off his clothes!
Then, using Sasahara-senpai's statement of "delicious!" as an opportunity...
The two of them...
The two of them!
...in the courtyard...
In the courtyard!
I totally forgot!
I need to do that report, too!
Oh, no!
We have to think of our own topic, too!
In the courtyard... in the courtyard... in the courtyard!
Oh, you bought some yakisoba bread.
Well, I like it!
You always get yakisoba bread.
I suppose that makes you the Yakisoba Princess?
Well, what did you get, then, Koujirou?
Me?
I bought a red bean bun.
So that makes Koujirou...
Hm?
What is it?
It's nothing!
I suppose that makes Koujirou...
...the Red Bean Prince!
Delicious!
That makes Koujirou...
What is it?
It's nothing!
I suppose that makes Koujirou...
I suppose that makes Koujirou a fair-skinned beauty!
Let's eat in the courtyard.
I'm up for that!
And then the teacher ate a wild whale.
Are you sure?
It's true!
If that's true, it would have to be outside the 200-mile international boundary.
That's not a problem!
That teacher's an Eskimo.
Nano...
You have yakisoba bread on your face.
...and that moment was delicately carried in the spring breeze.
The gentle time together...
[Sign: Courtyard, Courtyard, Courtyard...]
Rendezvous
Rendezvous!
I can't progress! I can't progress!
I can't work on a report in a situation like this!
I can't finish like this!
Yukko!
I just had a good idea!
Tell me what they did in the courtyard!
Just shut up already!
Well... um...
Addis!
Ababa!
Since it's come to this...
I need to go to the courtyard myself!
I need to enter that indecent Garden of Eden!
Thank you.
It was nothing.
Farewell.
Huh?
What's wrong, Naganohara-san?
Nano-chan...
Yes?
I heard you ate yakisoba bread in the courtyard with Sasahara-senpai...
Sasahara-senpai?
Oh, the person just now?
All he did was help me carry my books.
That's it?
Yup.
That's it.
Really?
How about the yakisoba bread?
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Helvetica Standard
Come on!
Just tell me whom you like, Yumi!
What should I do?
I promise I won't tell anyone!
If I do, I'll pay you one million yen!
Really?
You better.
Okay!
Takashi-kun.
Hey, listen up: Yumi likes Takashi-kun!
Taking Off
I see.
Nichijou 103
Head!
Thank you very much.
Here.
That damn genius.
How odd to find you at the dojo.
The tournament's soon,
so it's better to practise with the Master than at school.
Besides, Naganohara-san was here, so I'm relieved.
She actually hasn't been coming in lately.
What?
Really?
She says that practising makes her weaker.
She's a monster.
Whom do you usually practise with, then?
The Master, usually...
Oh, but lately Sasahara-san has been coming in a lot.
Sasahara?!
Why is he coming?!
What do you mean, "why"?
He's been coming to our dojo since middle school,
so why wouldn't he come?
I know that, but...
Why didn't you already know?
Don't you talk to him at school?
Aren't you in the same club?
We aren't!
He's been in the Acting Club from day one!
Acting Club?
Why isn't he in the Kendo Club?
How would I know?
Because if you take away kendo from Sasahara-san,
he's nothing more than a funny guy.
You say that because you've only seen Sasahara at the dojo!
What do you mean?
Listen, the Sasahara that joined the Acting Club...
...is completely out of his mind!
It's just grape juice.
I can see that...
Okay?
But why didn't you invite him to the Kendo Club?
What a waste.
Huh?
Why do I have to invite him?
He can do whatever he wants.
I bet Sasahara-san can make it to the nationals!
How would I know?
Besides, he joined the Acting Club without even telling me.
He's just an idiot, a big idiot!
Well, then again...
If you care that much, Mihoshi...
I guess I can invite him...
This person...
...is so easy to read.
Well?
When does Sasahara usually come?
He's been dropping by once every three days,
so he'll probably be there tomorrow.
Well, it doesn't really matter. I don't really care.
Hey, Nee-chan.
What?
Why don't you confess to Sasahara-san?
A middle-schooler shouldn't say such things!
I'm going to go ahead now.
Nee-chan...
You're too pure-hearted...
Love-Like
It's so cold.
Cold attack!
Later.
Jumping
I see.
Nichijou 104
That was delicious.
Thank you for the food.
Professor.
You have to eat your onions, too.
I think I'm too young for onions.
What's that supposed to mean?
Regardless, you need to completely finish off your food.
Well, green onions are bitter, and I just don't understand.
If you don't eat everything, there'll be no snacks for you starting tomorrow.
You should look at Sakamoto-san.
He never leaves anything-
Sorry, I can't help you.
Sakamoto-san, what's wrong?
Are you okay?
No problem.
It's just a cold.
A little rest will cure-
But you haven't eaten anything.
You should try to have a little.
No, I'm fine.
Would you like some milk?
Not really...
This is a problem.
What do you think you'll be able to eat?
Really, I don't want anything right now.
But...
Sakamoto wants to eat green onions.
Are you trying to kill me?
Is there anything you want?
No.
Anyway, I'll leave some milk out for you.
If you need anything, please tell me.
I'll go buy it for you.
All right...
I seem to be sick, too, so I want some chocolate.
Please eat your green onions, Professor.
Why does Sakamoto get everything while I get nothing?!
Because Sakamoto-san has a cold.
I was coughing too!
You're full of energy.
I'm sick, so I want chocolate!
I have a cold, too, you know!
If you have a cold, you need to take some medicine!
Do you want some medicine?
I give up!
Hey, Professor!
Professor...
Go away!
You give me onions to bully me because you hate me, Nano!
You like Sakamoto more, so you don't force him to eat them.
That's not it.
Cats can't eat green onions.
I've never heard that before!
You're hopeless...
I like you more, Professor.
Really?
Yup.
Can I have some chocolate, then?
Let's see... Only if you finish your green onions.
Why?!
You said that you liked me more!
I like Sakamoto more, then.
What? Make up your mind!
I love you both!
What's that supposed to mean?!
Sakamoto, what's the meaning of this?!
Hypnosis
Word Of The Day
What floor?
Oh, the seventh floor, if you would be so kind.
Thanks.
Now that I think about it, I haven't been shy this year.
Guidance Counselling
Um...
Naganohara-san, your dream for the future...
...is to become a manga artist?
Y-Yes.
You're pretty good at drawing, Naganohara-san.
No, not really.
I think it's good to go after your dreams.
Please do your best.
Let's see, Yukko wants melon juice...
What should I choose?
Well, I'm tight on money this month,
so I won't get anything special and settle for banana juice.
Sorry about that.
Nichijou 105
Sa... Sa... Sa... Sa... Sa...
Sasahara-senpai!
What's wrong?
Your expression resembles a dove that has been shot.
Oh, s-sorry!
Um, what am I supposed to do?
I should say something.
Um...
The weather's nice today...
What am I saying?!
It's completely cloudy!
How deep.
Yes.
Does this coin belong to you?
Oh, yes!
I see.
Sorry for the trouble.
Yes.
What a surprise for a thing like this to happen.
I seem to have forgotten to bring my wallet today.
I came to this vending machine in hopes of quenching my thirst,
and there, I found a coin.
I must be loved by God.
The beverage I'm about to consume...
...is like holy water from the heavens.
Um...
This vending machine...
It's definitely a prankster!
Y-Yes!
Still, for this vending machine to play me like this...
It's a rare sight for a device to make such a play in this age.
I like you!
You can keep the coin.
Senpai...
I have no proof,
but it feels like I've become closer to Senpai.
Mio-chan, melon juice!
Was she trying to tell me something?
Naganohara-san is so strong that people call her invincible.
Knight.
A knight...
Speaking of knights...
Why don't you confess to Sasahara-san?
Nee-chan, the bath's ready.
I wonder if Sasahara-senpai gazes at the moon, too.
You've got pretty good muscles, Sasahara-kun.
Let's practise again soon!
All right!
I'll teach you my secret move next time!
Onee!
Look, look, look, look!
Sisters.
Geez, don't just come into my room like that!
What were you thinking about?
Shut up.
Who cares what I was thinking about?
Don't be shy, don't be shy!
I'm not being shy!
Just leave me alone!
mukashi girisha no ikarosu wa
むかしギリシャの　イカロスは
In ancient Greece, Icarus
rou de katameta tori no hane
ろうで固めた　鳥の羽根
Made bird wings out of wax
ryoute ni motte, tobitatta
両手に持って　飛び立った
He put them on each arm and flew off
kumo yori takaku, mada tooku
雲より高く　まだ遠く
Higher than the clouds, far away
yuuki hitotsu wo tomo ni shite
勇気一つを友にして
Keeping a bit of courage with him
oka wa gungun toozakari
おかはぐんぐん　遠ざかり
The land steadily grew far away
shita ni hirogaru aoi umi
下に広がる　青い海
The blue sea spread beneath him
ryoute no hane wo habatakase
両手の羽根を　はばたかせ
Flapping the wings on his arms
taiyou mezashi tonde yuku
太陽目指し　飛んでゆく
Flying toward the sun
yuuki hitotsu wo tomo ni shite
勇気一つを友にして
Keeping a bit of courage with him
bokura wa tsuyoku ikite yuku
ぼくらは強く　生きて行く
We all live boldly
yuuki hitotsu wo tomo ni shite
勇気一つを友にして
Keeping a bit of courage with us
It's always when you don't have any ten yen coins...
...that you need exact change.
That is the law of me, the vending machine.
Next time on Nichijou: Episode 25.
Narration:    Nagai Ichirou
Look forward to it!