Everything in this world can be proven by science.
In the world there are talks about the so-called "spiritual phenomena"...
There's no way those kinds of sleep-inducing things could be real!
It'd be bad if they were.
In other words...
I don't believe in spirits!
Nichijou 93
jou jou yuu jou banjin maji kaichou
じょーじょーゆーじょー万事マジ快調
Amazing friendship, the absolute best!
na na na na na na na
ななななななな
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
hai! icchaimashou!
ハイ!言っちゃいましょう!
All right! I'll say it!
kimi wa best best friend
キミはベストベスト フレンド
You are my best, best friend!
(furai!) chotto fuzakete mitara
(フライ!) ちょっとふざけてみたら
(Fly!) When I joke around a bit,
(shain!) motto fuzake kaeshite kuru
(シャイン!) もっとふざけ帰してくる
(Shine!) You joke around more in response.
(La La La) ikogochi ii ttara arya shinai
(ラーラーラー)居心地良いったらありゃしない
(La La La) Nothing is better than this!
(wai!) iya na koto attatte
(ワイ!) 嫌なことあったって
(Why!) Even if something bad happens,
(fain!) sokkou wasurechaunda
(ファイン!) 即効忘れちゃうんだー
(Fine!) I immediately forget about it!
(La La La)
(ラーラーラー)
itsudatte jan jan yarimasho
いつだって、じゃんじゃんやりましょ♪
Always keep it going!
24 jikan issho demo mondai nai
２４時間一緒でも問題ない
Being together 24 hours a day isn't a problem.
marude futago ka oyako ka clone saibou
まるで双子か親子かクローン細胞
Just like twins, or a parent and child, or clone cyborgs.
kore ja me ga sumu hitsuyou wa nakunakunai!?
これじゃ目が澄む必要はなくなくない!？
Then isn't there no reason to clear your eyes?
sore to kore to wa mattaku mattaku betsumondai
それとこれとは まったくまったく 別問題
Those are completely, completely different issues.
(faito!) kenka shichatta toki mo
(ファイト!)喧嘩しちゃった時も
(Fight!) Even when I get in a fight with you,
(daoun!) kanari hekonda toki mo
(ダウン!)かなり凹んだ時も
(Down!) even when I get really down,
(shai!) hitori de itai you na toki mo
(シャイ!)一人で居たいような時も
(Shy!) even when I feel like I want to be alone,
futokizukeba chikaku ni iru shinaba morotomo
ふと気付けば 近くに居る 死なば諸共
before I realise it, you're right there; we'll be together even in death!
nande daro
なんでだろ
I wonder why it is.
soba ni itainda
そばに居たいんだ
I want to be with you.
kimi to issho nara
君と一緒なら
When I'm with you,
tokei hyakubai soku
時計百倍速
time goes 100 times faster!
tanoshii na
楽しいな
It's fun, isn't it?
tanoshisugirunda
楽しすぎるんだ
It's way too fun!
sasuga saikou friend
流石 最高 friend
As expected of my best friend!
Hey! na na na na na na na
Hey! ななななななな
Hey! Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
nannanoyo
なんなのよー
What is it?
yabai synchro
ヤバいシンクロー
The synchro is amazing!
itsumo oosawagi
いつも大騒ぎ
Always making an uproar,
kanari gokinjo meiwaku
かなりご近所迷惑
bothering the neighbours a lot.
ima nanji
今何時
What time is it now?
ato ne yorereihifu
あとねヨレレイヒーフ
And then yo de le hi hoo!
wake wakannainai
訳分かんないない!
I don't get it at all!
soredoshira
ソレドシラ
So re doh si la!
souzou ijou nante iu ka saiko
想像以上なんて言うか最高
It's better than I imagined, the absolute best!
aa da kou da ittetemo tomodachi (wasshoi!)
あーだこーだ言ってても友達 (わっしょい!)
Even if I say this and that, we're still friends. (Hooray!)
jou jou yuu jou banjin maji kaichou
じょーじょーゆーじょー万事マジ快調
Amazing friendship, the absolute best!
cha cha la cha la cha cha
ちゃちゃらちゃらちゃちゃー
Cha Cha La Cha La Cha Cha!
I heard that exorcisms were being performed at a local temple, so I went to check it out.
So, what brings you here?
First, I'll pretend I'm possessed by a demon,
then I'll look for contradictions.
Lately, I've been having the feeling of
something tightening around my throat.
Oh my!
Here.
Use this.
Here it comes!
The offering of useless exorcism goods!
Lozenge
It should work really well on your throat.
He's being awfully reasonable.
Is there not enough reality in my story?
Well, then I'll need to get him to believe me.
You see,
it's not just that my throat is sore...
It feels like I'm being strangled by someone,
and I think I heard a strange voice.
I'm possessed by something!
Well, isn't it that...
...you're just reading too many strange books?
You shouldn't...
...do that too much...
I never would have thought that someone in the business would tell me that.
More importantly, does this priest even believe in spirits?
But I came all this way to the temple.
There's no way I'm just going to back down!
I'm being strangled by some sort of monster!
Excuse me!
He saw through me!
Of course he did.
I was wrong for trying to fool someone in the business with a half-assed performance!
I have to do it seriously.
To get him to believe,
I need to go mad!
W-What?!
W-What are you doing?!
What the heck are you doing?!
What in the world is this?!
Japanese Martial Arts
Why you...
What are you doing...
What are you doing to my temple?!
My dream is to become a scientist.
Crap.
I seem to have lost myself.
To explain everything in this world with science...
...and to help many people understand it.
And when that time comes, there is one thing I want to express.
Are you okay?
Get...
Get out, you demon!
A person can become a demon at any time.
Nichijou 94
Gotcha!
Who is it?!
Mihoshi, it's been a while.
Oh, it's Naganohara-san!
I haven't seen you for a while.
You're already a middle schooler, huh?
Well, lately, you haven't been coming to the dojo at all.
I haven't gone to practise at my university lately, either.
I've been skipping!
And yet you still won the National Tournament?
This darn genius type!
Are you going to the dojo now?
Yeah.
Clubs just ended, so I'm going now.
Naganohara-san, are you coming?
I'm the type that gets weaker when I practise a lot.
What is she saying?
This darn genius type!
Although I can accept that she's strong,
I can't accept that she's strong despite never practising.
It's been rumoured that when Naganohara-san was in middle school, she scored a point against the Master!
That legendary master!
I'm a middle schooler now, too, but I can't seem to do anything.
I go to the dojo after club,
and I spend my entire weekend practising.
The Master says that effort will always open up a door!
Oh, a black cat!
Hey, kitty!
When I look at her, I start to feel uneasy.
You're so cute!
I'll take a swing.
Just one.
In this situation, even I can...
This is the most I can do right now,
but someday I'll do it in a match.
I'll do it against the Master someday, too!
This darn genius type!
Oh, sorry!
Master!
Love-Like
It's cold.
Daihuku Fair
Got it?
Be sure to do it right.
Reign
Dad intends to pass the business on to me.
Also, take this balloon.
If a kid comes around, hand it to him.
I won't stand for this.
As soon as I see a chance, I'm running for it!
But you know...
This thing...
Daihuku
It isn't floating!
Word Of The Day
In the very end, I just want a little bit of a happy ending.
Shinonome Institute
A Certain Christmas One-shot
What are you going to ask Santa for, Professor?
Well, I want some chocolate,
some coloured pencils,
a cake-shaped eraser and...
Wow!
Having that many isn't fair!
Well, what I would like is...
Two packs of eggs, 500 grams of beef, a book and...
I've already asked for a lot, so you only get one thing, Nano!
Nano, if it's only a little more, then I guess it's okay.
I'll let you borrow this, too.
Bobon!
Yay, it's Santa!
Merry Christma-
Delicious Melon Bread
Daihuku
Trap
I'm not sticking around for this!
I need to hurry up and get this off!
Ow! It hurts!
Are you going to run away, Tsuyoshi?
Dad!
I made some modifications to the mask.
Modifications?
The inside of that mask...
...is freshly coated with glue!
Hot!
Damn, I dropped my meat bun!
I didn't even get to take a bite out of it...
It's fine, Websey!
If there had been poison in that meat bun, you would have died,
so it's actually a good thing!
No, it isn't!
It's what I look forward to the most on the way home from school...
You need to always look forward. Your luck will come back.
Be thankful to the fallen meat bun.
Nichijou 95
What's with your extremely positive attitude?
I've decided to always be positive, even in tough times!
Look, if you take off the dirty parts, you can still eat it.
The poison is already gone?
See? You do it like this-
Hot!
The popsicle is safe!
See?
Good things happen when you're positive.
It's positive magic!
My meat bun isn't safe, though...
It's times like this you need to be positive!
If there had been poison in the meat bun,
you would have died, Websey.
You don't have much variation.
Even if I remove the parts that got dirty,
I can't accept the fact that some popsicle juice got on it.
Come on! Positive thinking-
Oh, god!
The heat from the meat bun must have made it a bit loose.
If I imagine that there was poison in the popsicle, I can handle this...
You were eating so much of it, though.
What is it?
Loser
Your positiveness just had its combo broken!
No, this is a message from God that I shouldn't eat two because I might get a stomach ache!
That's some Fecchan-like perseverance!
Also, if this had been soft serve, it would be completely out.
I can just wash off this popsicle.
I'm thankful for that!
You're still going to eat that?
Wait!
What's it like?
It's like it's wet.
Come on, Fecchan!
Positive, positive!
Oh, I give up!
Dash for Freedom
If you refuse to inherit my legacy,
just wait for my second and third traps!
Dad...
This...
You...
...is my...
Could it be?!
...answer!
Guidance Counselling
Tachibana, what are you going to do in the future?
I'm deciding between going to a university or getting into cooking.
Cooking, huh?
Marry him?!
Calm down, Tachibana.
Shinonome Institute
Tie it like this,
and it's done.
I'm back!
Oh, Nano, I'm going to take Sakamoto out for a walk.
I'm going to have some friends over to study, is that all right?
Nichijou 96
Okay.
I want to play, too, so I'll be right back.
Well then, I'm off!
Hey! What are you doing, kid?!
I'm going to die!
Okay, I get it.
I'll listen to you!
What do you want?
A shark.
Don't screw around!
...while crying...
I'm the one that wants to cry here!
Okay. A shark.
Piece of cake!
I'll go get one!
Let me off!
Dogs...
They're dogs, so they might bite.
Sakamoto, there are dogs.
They might bite us.
W-What? A-Are you afraid of dogs?
T-They're on leads, so there's no way we'll get bitten.
Our only choice is to run!
All right, run away!
Sakamoto, we can't escape!
Don't give up!
If you give up, it's over!
Ask the owner to hurry up and put their leads on!
It's...
...over!
It's no good!
Use your brain!
Isn't there anything?
I found a gummy in my pocket.
That's it!
While they're busy eating it, we'll make our escape!
I know!
Make a tool to help us escape.
Oh, right!
I forgot!
Sakamoto!
What is it?
I don't have any tools to make a tool!
Damn!
Fine then, just do whatever you want!
TL Note: This is a common Japanese phrase: "Boil me or burn me or do whatever you want to me".
Boil... burn... whatever you want...
Dinner.
We're going to be eaten.
If we're going to be eaten, we might be eaten.
Huh, Professor?
Why are you crying?
Are you lost?
It's Yukko!
Oh, this is the Professor you were talking about.
Oh, Sakamoto is with you?
Let me pet him!
No, Yukko!
Go take care of the dogs!
He's a lot softer than I expected!
Me next!
Don't screw around!
Hurry up and fend the dogs off!
I get it!
You want revenge because they bit you!
No, they're about to bite us!
What's that?
Let me guess: you're scared of dogs? Who are you, Oba-Q?
TL Note: Oba-Q, from the manga Obake no Q-tarou, is deathly afraid of dogs.
That's not it!
It's a dog, so it's going to bite!
Look how friendly he is.
There's no way he'll bite.
It'll bite.
It won't bite.
It'll bite!
Bite some gum?
Just kidding.
It'll bite!
Well then, look.
Here, shake.
Hey, Yukko, are you okay?
It won't bite if you don't get near it, so don't worry.
Yukko was... Yukko was...
It's okay.
Yukko's just stupid.
I got it.
All right, let's get Yukko up and go to Nano-chan's house.
Oh, you know Nano?
Of course I kn-
Where were you?!
You have to keep them on a lead!
Did you play with them?
What are you talking about?!
They almost bit us!
Here.
Chocolate sharks!
Thank you very much.
There were dogs, and we got chocolate.
Isn't that great, Sakamoto?
Being afraid of dogs. You're still just a kid.
More importantly, take this rope off of me.
All right, since I got chocolate.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Sakamoto, take it off.
It's stuck.
It'd be off already if I could!
Let's get Yukko to take it off.
Hey, Yukko, take this off.
Hey, Yukko.
Hey!
H-Hey, isn't that...
Shinonome Institute
I'm back.
There were so many dogs.
Wow, you're sweating a lot!
Oh, right!
There was chocolate!
Chocolate, chocolate, chocolate, chocolate, chocolate...
...sharks, chocolate, chocolate, chocolate, sharkie, sharkie, sharks...
That being said, Aioi-san and Naganohara-san sure are late.
I'm sure they came in this direction...
W-What is this?
Buddy.
Little Buddy.
What exactly are they doing?!
Grandpa!
People live by helping each other out, Takashi.
The same is true about animals' hearts, Takashi.
Don't take the bond between an
animal and a human lightly, Takashi.
Grandpa...
I'm Kiyoshi.
aogeba toutoshi waga shi no on
仰げば尊し　我が師の恩
I respect and owe a great deal to my teachers
oshie no niwa ni mo haya ikutose
教えの庭にも　はや幾年
Many years have passed in this garden of learning
omoeba itotoshi kono toshitsuki
思えばいと疾し　この年月
These months and years have gone by quickly
imakoso wakareme izasaraba
今こそ別れめ　いざさらば
Now is the time to part, farewell
I'm Melon Bread.
Humans, do you prefer it with the taste of melon or without?
Continue the debate over this for eternity.
Next time on Nichijou: Episode 23.
Narration:     Shibata Hidekatsu
Look forward to it!