Birthday
Hey, hey!
Let's throw Nano-chan a birthday party!
Sounds good.
When should we do it?
Today.
Today?!
You have to tell me these things earlier!
Sorry.
Well...
What should we do?
We haven't prepared anything...
Well, it's not like today is her birthday.
You didn't ask?!
Exactly.
What?!
It's going to be a surprise!
Let's also...
Let's also throw a birthday party for the professor.
Good idea!
Two birds with one stone!
Let's do this!
Well, I guess a happy surprise is fun for both sides.
All right.
On our way home, let's buy some cake!
All right!
Are you okay with that, Mai-chan?
I forgot my wallet.
T-That's too bad.
Well then, Yukko and I will...
I also forgot my wallet!
I'm begging you, Mio-chan!
Well, I never paid you back the money I lost at the amusement park,
so I guess I'll pay for today.
Well, I'll go tell Nano-chan we're having a birthday party!
What happened to the surprise?!
Geez.
Yukko, you're an idiot.
Wha...
Yet you got dumped by Sasahara-senpai...
I wasn't dumped!
You ran away crying.
That was...
Just because they were holding hands...
...doesn't mean they were going out!
I never actually asked him about it,
so it's not like I got dumped or anything!
It's not like I gave up!
I still like him!
Let's leave it at that!
Shinonome Institute
All right!
Nothing forgotten...
Nichijou 110
Professor, I'm heading out now!
Nano!
What's with you, Professor?
I made a small one, so I'm taking this one off.
Professor, what do you mean by "a small one"?
By small... uh...
Will that make my back smooth?
It will.
But even on top of the small one...
Nano.
Yes!
I lost it.
Nano!
Are you okay?
Why are you guys yelling in the morning?
It's so loud...
Kid, why did you set up a trap?!
Sakamoto broke the small thing!
W-What? No!
Well...
Sakamoto made Nano cry.
No way!
It's your fault for leaving it on the ground!
I'm heading off to school.
Nano...
You forgot this.
I'll make another one real quick.
Will it be made before I get back?
Well, I can make it really quick.
Professor!
I'm heading off to school!
All right!
I'm going!
Shinonome Institute
Have a safe trip!
Have a safe trip...
Principal
Well, that's odd...
Principal & Vice Principal
Vice Principal...
This statue is from when I was the principal...
That's odd.
Where's the statue of you, Principal Shinonome?
Geez.
Kids these days with their sophisticated pranks...
Or is it something else?
Could I possibly have an admirer?
Mister Vice Principal!
We've finished moving it!
The statue is fine here, correct?
I didn't say anything...
Vice Principal, this is...
Well, the pranks these youngsters do...
They're well plotted out.
Sorry, can you take this statue as well?
You want to take away this cheap statue, too?
Cheap...
Got it!
I'll take away this pathetic one as well!
Pathetic...
We're taking this stupid one, too!
Now, now, Vice Principal, don't be so gloomy.
Well, we're taking it with the stinky one!
What?!
Go Soccer Club 8
Huh?
It's unlocked.
Oh, you were here, Sekiguchi?
I wanted to be first,
so I even went through the effort of flying a Blackbird here.
What is it?
Sekiguchi, are you going to do morning practice, too?
Um...
Well...
Yes.
Seriously?
Nichijou 111
To think that I'll have to pay for both of your lunches...
Sorry!
Well, since you don't have your wallets, it can't be helped.
Of course Mio-chan understands!
So generous!
Are you okay?
Geez.
Yukko, you hit me too hard.
Sorry.
Sorry, Mai-chan.
I'm fine.
Oh yeah, Yukko.
Did you ask Nano-chan if we could come over today?
Crap!
I completely forgot!
All right!
I'll tell her about the birthday party.
No, you can't!
Just ask her if we can come over!
I understand!
No, you don't!
Geez.
I'll go myself!
I told you I'll go!
No, I'll go!
I'll go!
I will...
I'll go.
Wait... Mai-chan, Mai-chan!
Moment, please!
Just a moment, please!
Well, I'm going to see Nano-chan now.
I must hurry!
I'm sorry!
Don't worry about it.
Go forth!
I'm truly sorry!
I'm sorry...
I accidentally pressed black coffee.
I'm sorry!
Don't worry.
It's partly my fault, too.
I'm sorry...
If it says "Winner"
you get one more!!
Winner
A-Aioi-san,
please be quiet in the halls!
Rainbow...
I found it!
Ouch...
Aioi-san!
Are you all right?
Nano-chan!
I was looking for you!
Oh, really?
Yeah!
Actually...
That's, uh...
Are you okay?
Didn't it hurt?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I see.
Thank goodness.
Anyway, this isn't what it looks like.
How should I explain this?
That's great and all, but is it all right if I come over today?
Y-Yeah.
That's righ-
That's a surprise, so I can't tell you.
Eh? Uh...
Well, see you later!
O-Okay.
Well, I guess I'll have to buy some for Aioi-san, too.
First comes rock,
next comes paper.
Rockscispaper doesn't count,
rock, paper, scissors!
What the heck?
Nichijou 112
This pumpkin!
It's rock-hard!
O        ni    gi        ri
Geez.
Why does the kid always-
Taisho!
Is that you, Taisho?
Nakamura!
I've been looking for you, Taisho!
Thank god you're saf-
Why are you running away?
Have you forgotten me?
I'm running away because I haven't forgotten!
Taisho, time for food.
Here.
What's wrong, Taisho?
You're not going to eat?
It's time for a bath.
Taisho!
Robotic Studies
Raising Cats
Damn.
If I don't hurry, I'll be late.
Well, Taisho, I'm off.
Damn.
Taisho!
Come out, Taisho!
Hurry up and go, please!
Oh, Nakamura-sensei?
Hello!
Shinonome!
Girl, do something!
Is there something wrong?
Are you looking for something?
So this is what they mean by "like a robot to the flame."
Then again, I can talk to Shinonome any time at school.
Right now, Taisho is the priority.
Sorry, Shinonome, have you seen a black cat?
You have a black cat, too?
Well, kinda.
It escaped from me.
We have a black cat, too.
I see.
Do you mind if I help you find it?
Sure, sorry for the hassle, Shinonome.
No problem.
Are you stupid?!
Oh, that's right, Nakamura-sensei.
Could you tell me the name of your cat?
It's Taisho.
What an interesting name.
The cat at our house is Sakamoto-san.
That's a strange name.
I know.
Isn't it such a strange name?
Is he cute?
Is Taisho cute?
What are you talking about?
You...
Well, it's not like Nakamura had bad intentions.
Then again...
If that kind of crap starts again, my body won't hold.
Memories of
Nakamura's
Mess-ups
Memories of
Nakamura's
Mess-ups
Memories of
Nakamura's
Mess-ups
Memories of
Nakamura's
Mess-ups
Memories of
Nakamura's
Mess-ups
Memories of
Nakamura's
Mess-ups
Memories of
Nakamura's
Mess-ups
Memories of
Nakamura's
Mess-ups
Memories of
Nakamura's
Mess-ups
Memories of
Nakamura's
Mess-ups
Memories of
Nakamura's
Mess-ups
Memories of
Nakamura's
Mess-ups
Memories of
Nakamura's
Mess-ups
Memories of
Nakamura's
Mess-ups
Memories of
Nakamura's
Mess-ups
Memories of
Nakamura's
Mess-ups
Memories of
Nakamura's
Mess-ups
Wait. Hold on...
Memories of
the Kids'
Pranks
Memories of
the Kids'
Pranks
Memories of
the Kids'
Pranks
Memories of
the Kids'
Pranks
Memories of
the Kids'
Pranks
Memories of
the Kids'
Pranks
It hasn't changed that much now, either...
Memories of
the Kids'
Pranks
Memories of
the Kids'
Pranks
Memories of
the Kids'
Pranks
Memories of
the Kids'
Pranks
Memories of
the Kids'
Pranks
Memories of
the Kids'
Pranks
Memories of
the Kids'
Pranks
Memories of
the Kids'
Pranks
Memories of
the Kids'
Pranks
Memories of
the Kids'
Pranks
Memories of
the Kids'
Pranks
The scales aren't even tipping!
Oh, look at the time.
Sorry, Nakamura-sensei, but if I don't go home soon,
my food will...
I see.
If you find him, could I come see him?
Yes, come!
Come any time!
Come tomorrow!
Well, I'm heading off now.
Okay!
Damn it!
Either way, I'm screwed!
Nichijou 113
Professor, Sakamoto, I'm back!
Nano!
The small thing!
Professor, you made it?!
Sakamoto stepped on it again.
Sakamoto-san...
Is it okay for you to take it off again?
I'll make another one right now.
Professor!
But it came off so easily.
When I tried to take it off, it wouldn't budge!
Well, that's because Nano can't take it off, but other people can!
I see...
But even you can put it back in!
What kind of feature is that?
By the way, Professor,
what kind of features does the small one have?
If I make this, your thumb won't come off any more.
Yeah, I remember that feature...
I wonder if that's Aioi-san and her friends.
Yukko?
It's Yukko!
Oh, right. I need to put this key away.
I'll finally look like a normal person.
I wonder if I'll get along better with everyone now.
Going out with friends...
and enjoying things more normally...
That kind of daily life is waiting for me!
That's great and all, but is it all right if I come over today?
That's because it's cute!
You're Nano-chan.
Isn't that enough?
I came over to say that.
I'd forgotten.
Nano-chan!
Nano!
Girl.
Be quiet!
This is the important part.
I got it.
Nano-chan!
Happy birthday!
I brought some cake over.
Oh, Aioi-san!
Birthday... How did you...?
It's because it's a surprise!
It's cake!
Cake, cake, cake!
Geez, Professor.
Oh, Professor!
Come on, Professor.
Look what happened!
The cake...
What should we do...?
I have one more...
Mai-chan!
What is that?!
Yeah!
But I wonder how everyone knew...
...that today was my birthday.
Nano's
Birthday
Nano!
I made the small thing!
Professor.
This key has been a bother to me,
and I really wanted to take it off,
but I want to stay like this!
What this small thing does is: when Nano is happy,
it turns the key a little.
What is that supposed to be?
Oh, right!
Professor, can you take this cake over there?
It's another cake!
I'll be taking the tea over.
Roger that!
Cake, cake, cake, cake...
Professor!
Cake...
Geez. What are you two doing?
Aioi-san, are you all right?
Nano-chan, get something to clean this up!
Yes!
Here's the candle.
I want to do it, too!
Mai-chan, we need to do something about this first...
Something to clean... something to clean...
Mai-chan!
Here's another one.
As I said, something else!
Mai-chan, stop, stop!
shiroi hikari no naka ni yamanami wa moete
白い光の中に　山並みは萌えて
The mountain range springs up in the white light
haruka na sora no hate mademo kimi wa tobidatsu
はるかな空の果てまでも　君は飛び立つ
And you set off on a journey into the distant sky
kagirinaku aoizora ni kokoro furuwase
限りなく青い空に　心ふるわせ
My heart trembles at the boundless blue sky
jiyuu wo kakeru tori yo furikaeru koto mo sezu
自由をかける鳥よ　振り返ることもせず
Be free, little bird, and never look back
yuuki wo tsubasa ni komete kibou no kaze ni nori
勇気を翼に込めて　希望の風に乗り
Gather courage into your wings and ride the winds of hope
kono hiroi oozora ni yume wo takushite
この広い大空に　夢を託して
Entrust your dreams into this vast sky
Motivation
What's wrong, Mio-chan?
I can't stop sneezing...
What are you talking about?
You can stop sneezing with willpower!
So until I gather enough willpower,
what should I do about the sneezing?
You just have to stop it!
It's impossible.
There's a simple idiot here.