These are...
They were found in an aristocrat's manor.
Are they perhaps from your world?
They are.
But I've never seen so many of them in one place at once.
It's amazing.
I knew it.
Now, as for their use...
Judging by their shape...
Nononononono.
Yes, they may look like that, but they are...
In the water?! With these?!
So hot...
This summer's hotter than usual...
Hey, did you hear about the summer vacation?
What vacation?
Group trip.
They cancelled the trip to the Great Cathedral in Romalia, and we're going to the ocean instead.
The ocean?
I've always wanted to see it.
Tiffa, you've never seen the ocean?
No, since I've always lived in the forest.
The ocean's really nice.
Especially the beach at night! It's so mysterious and romantic.
Montmorency.
Would you like to walk the beach with me at night to gaze at the stars?
Not with the Order of Perverts.
Why don't you forgive him already?
He'll only get full of himself if I forgive him now.
Couldn't agree more.
Hey, come on.
The vacation's the perfect opportunity to fix relationships.
Just do this!
Gosh! What are you doing, Kirche?!
I'd... I'd never let him go further.
But... a night time stroll along the beach, huh?
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
mejirushi no nai michi mo heiki sa futari nara
メジルシのない道も平気さ　ふたりなら
Even on a road without signs, I'll be fine, if we're together
saki no mienai tabi mayoinagara mitsuketa yo
先の見えない旅　迷いながら見つけたよ
On a journey that I can't see ahead of, while I was lost, I found it
boku no iru basho kimi no tonari
僕の居る場所　君のとなり
That my place to be is next to you
kenkashite nando mo hanashita sono te
喧嘩して　何度も離したその手
When we quarrelled, I let go of your hand again and again
hikiyose dakitai ima
引き寄せ抱きたい　今
I want to pull close and hold it now
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
namida no ame ni utaretara
涙の雨に打たれたら
If I'm beaten down by the rain of tears
I wanna hold you sugu yobi na yo boku no namae
I wanna hold you　すぐ呼びなよ　僕の名前
I wanna hold you, call my name immediately
dakishime ni yuku wa
抱きしめに行くわ
I'll go embrace you
kanashimi mo tsuyogari mo kono te ni uketomeru
悲しみも強がりもこの手に　受け止める
I'll accept sadness and bluffing in my hands
Seductive Beach
So, Tiffa, what do you think of the ocean?
The ocean...
It's so blue... and big.
And salty, too.
It is.
You've got to go to a beach during the summer.
Siesta?! Why are you here, too?
You're even wearing a swimsuit.
I was told to take care of Saito-san.
Saito-san!
He's right. Those are not  swimsuits.
"Those"? What do you mean?
A real swimsuit should be more like this...
And like this down here.
And this!
And this has to be more like this!
A real swimsuit?
What?!
Before we enter the ocean, the Queen has a word to say.
The Queen does?
Everyone, thanks to Principal Osmond,
I am here to join the Tristain Magic
Academy's annual summer vacation.
I would like to get along with everyone here without consideration of status...
...and let us enjoy the vacation together.
Now, to start things off,
all girls, change into what's in there.
What's this?!
That's what a real swimsuit looks like.
What? That's not underwear?
In this area, one must give prayer to the Spirit of Water before entering.
As it is a tradition, there are special uniforms for the priestesses.
I've never heard of such a thing.
Is there a Spirit of Water in the ocean, too?
Anyway, we can't get in the ocean unless you change into those!
The belly is totally exposed!
I can't wear something indecent like this.
If you were to wear one, Your Highness,
then the students shall surely follow suit.
I insist.
Very well.
When in Romalia, do as Romalians do.
If it is to give prayer to the Spirit of Water, I will gladly change into it.
If the Princess is going to wear one...
She'll be wearing one?
We'll now begin the purification ritual for the Spirit of Water.
First splash each other with water to cleanse one another.
Like this!
I'm all wet.
But that felt good.
Everyone, start splashing each other!
Siesta!
Ignoring status, right?
Stop being so cheeky! Stop!
I've never been happier to be alive than today.
This brings back memories.
Saito. You come from a wonderful country.
There are more extreme ones than those, too.
Even more?!
Then lets have them wear those.
Of course.
They'll call us the Order of Perverts, again.
So you don't want to see it, Reinard?
This is an important ritual to offer prayer to the Spirit of Water.
Let us burn the sights of beautiful, innocent,
pure girls offering their prayers to the Spirit onto our eyes together!
Yeah!
Yeah...
We're changing again?
It's for the sake of the Spirit of Water.
Siesta... Aren't you getting full of yourself recently?
This keeps falling off.
This time, it's an offering ritual.
So close!
Amazing!
This view is glorious.
Is it over here?
No! Stop! It's me!
A bit more to the right, Tiffa!
Right?
Right there!
So close!
What was that?
I can only imagine a lecherous intent.
Agreed.
Hey. Why did you make Tiffa wear that of all things?
Louise...
W-What?
Well, ah... I thought you looked good in that swimsuit.
W-What are you saying all of a sudden?
Y-You know, Saito.
I-If it's okay...
W-Would you want to go out for a stroll tonight?
Y-Yeah...
Really?
That's great.
So I'll catch you later.
What? Louise, what did you just say?
Oh, well.
The next ritual makes use of a ball.
Now, everyone.
The team that wins this ritual will don the true priestess' garments,
allowed only to the chosen maidens.
It's all for the Spirit of Water's prayer, so take it seriously.
The chosen maidens...
We've got to see Tiffa in it.
We'll set things up so that she wins.
I don't see the whole picture,
but if I can see Tiffa in an amazing swimsuit, then I'm your man.
If I'm chosen as a true maiden, then I'm sure Saito would...
I guess this is a match, Miss Vallière.
The first match is Team Queen and Agnes vs. Team Tiffania and Siesta!
Here goes!
There!
Your Highness!
Okay!
That was amazing, Your Highness!
Out!
What did you say?!
Are your eyes knotholes?
How was that out?
That was definitely in!
No, it was out.
The word of the referees is final.
There!
Take this!
They'll crash!
Out.
Stop that nonsense!
That was definitely in!
What's going on?
10-7! Team Tiffania and Siesta wins!
We lost due to your crappy judgement!
Calm down.
Next up, Team Louise and Montmorency vs. Team Kirche and Tabitha!
Ready?
Yay!
Out.
You guys are doing it again!
I can't get enough of that!
I want to be the swimsuit!
10-9. Team Louise and Montmorency wins.
Yay!
We wanted to see...
...Team Kirche vs. Team Tiffania in tomorrow's final.
I wish you would understand the mood more.
What does that mean?
Is there a problem if we win?
N-No, nothing like that.
S-Saito. L-Let's go for the walk, shall we?
What? I'm kind of busy right now, so later, okay?
What was that?!
I even asked him, too!
I'll never let him pick up where we left off last time!
Everything's going as planned.
Though it was a shame that Kirche's team lost.
It'll finally be time for this tomorrow.
Y-You mean that that's...
...the true maiden garment?
Yes. Hard to believe, right?
I never imagined this would be a swimsuit, either.
Even I've only seen this one in magazines.
I can't wait for tomorrow.
What is it?
Let's go take a look.
I knew something was strange.
This is beyond perversion.
They're sickos!
Just you watch.
You'll get what you deserve.
They're late! What are they doing?
I'll go check.
Montmorency. What took you so long?
Where's everyone else?
Well...
My leg's cramped up from using it too much yesterday.
My sunburn hurts.
My shoulder's stiff from wearing something I'm not used to.
And I'm busy healing everyone with my Water magic.
I can't take part in the ritual.
S-So all four finalists are taking a break?
Is there a problem?
No, um...
Oh, and a message from Louise.
From Louise?
I actually wanted to be alone with you.
So come to the rocky stretch alone.
Make sure no one sees you.
To set up "alone time" by lying means...
I guess people in this world become more open at the beach.
Louise!
W-What the?!
Sorry to scare you, Darling.
I'll apologize beforehand.
Sorry, Saito-san.
"Sorry"? About what?
Miss Zerbst. What is it that you want,
calling me out to a place like this?
I can make a guess, but we are teacher and student.
Is that all right?
Yes, of course, Principal Osmond.
Does this suit your tastes?
This is the place, right?
But still, I can't believe that Tiffa gave me a letter.
Who knew Tiffa loved me?
Tiffa!
Not in your lifetime!
What are you doing to me?!
How dare you guys trick us?!
W-What are you guys talking about?!
Don't play dumb with us.
Looks like we've been found out.
W-What are you doing?!
How is it? Do you feel like giving prayers to the Spirit of Water?
Although this is a vacation, you guys went too far.
You all look nice.
Especially you, Malicorn.
I do?
Yes, since you have more breasts than someone.
Hey-
Who are you talking about?
We're sorry! We really are!
We swear we won't do it again, so forgive us!
Please! Louise!
Let's go, everyone.
Wait, Louise!
Princess!
I left my wand at the inn, so there's nothing we can do.
Rather than that, everyone, look at our feet.
Isn't the tide rising?
Yes, that's it.
You're getting better at it, Tiffa.
Really?
What's the matter, Miss Vallière?
I think I bumped into something.
That tickles!
What are you doing to me, Siesta?!
It's not me.
So who is it?
W-What is that?
That is the Spirit of Water that appears once every thirty years.
The legendary giant octopus!
It is blinded with rage since you all neglected the ritual!
Just a joke. A joke.
Tiffa! Montmorency!
You idiot! Don't do it, Louise!
Damn it...
You! Let go of those two!
Louise!
Your Highness, it's dangerous!
Please wait!
No!
Your Highness!
No, not there!
What an envi... I mean, horrible thing!
Need is ha nowsis.
Tabitha's the only one with her wand!
Can't you cast something stronger?
No. Anything stronger would hurt the others.
I got it off!
Hang on, Louise!
Saito! Untie us, too!
Partner, look at the water!
You can run along its leg.
All right.
Stop it!
Don't worry! I'll save you right now!
Hurry and get away.
Yes.
Got you.
Louise, are you hurt?
Saito...
Thank goodness you're all right.
Come save me sooner.
You're such a useless familiar.
Where I come from, this is how you eat octopus.
I bet you'll all love this.
Hey, Louise.
What? Hey.
We can't let those lechers see...
...But we wanted to try these on.
But Tiffa's by far the best one in these.
P-Please don't stare at me so much.
Isn't that one too big for Miss Vallière?
What did you say?!
Too loose.
I'm satisfied.
I didn't expect to get to see them in the true maiden garment.
I don't mind dying right now.
Hey, help me...
Did anyone else just hear something?
I think it's your imagination.
Hey, Louise. The octopus balls are ready.
Sigh...
It's impossible.
But...
kyuu ni senaka wo mukete kakedashita wa (Just love me)
急に背中を向けて 駆け出したわ
I suddenly turned my back on you and ran away
hoka no ko ni yasashiku shiteta kara yo
ほかの子に優しくしてたからよ
Because you've been so gentle to many other girls
Boy onegai oikakete yo
Boyお願い 追いかけてよ
Boy, please chase after me
ato ni wa hikenai kara
あとには引けないから
Because it won't be over after this
pun pun pun
I am so sorry
gomen to ienakute gomen ne
ゴメンと言えなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't say "I'm sorry", sorry ♥
shinjite iru no ni kuchibiru ga togaru
信じているのに くちびるが尖る
Even though I believe you, my lips are pouting
kawaiku narenakute gomen ne
可愛くなれなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't be cute, sorry ♥
kosame no furu machi tsukamaete
小雨の降る街 つかまえて
Catch me in the town where a drizzle is falling
furimuku kara nakanaori no chu o shite
振り向くから 仲直りのCHU～をして
Because I'll turn around and give you a make-up kiss
atsui ryouude no naka de
熱い両腕の中で
In your warm arms