I'll go home.
I'll...
...return to Japan!
This is...
Tokyo's...
Akihabara!
It's a sailor uniform!
A real sailor uniform!
Check it out, Louise. This is Japan's Akiba-
Louise?
Where are you, Louise?
Come out.
That's right... I came back to Japan by myself.
I was summoned as a familiar to a strange world by an incompetent mage, Louise,
and was dragged into a war.
I found this Zero and finally managed to come back, but...
There's...
There's no point in coming back to Japan without Louise!
Louise...
Louise!
Huh?
Where am I?
What's wrong, Saito?
Louise?
Louise!
Thank goodness.
Thank goodness, I thought you went away somewhere...
Saito...
Hey!
Ow...
Stop making a ruckus out of your dream, would you?
Haven't you been a little full of yourself lately?
No, I'm...
Yes, you did give up on returning to your world and chose to stay as my familiar.
I'm really grateful for that.
I'm not lying.
That's why I won't call you a dog anymore,
make you sleep on the floor or whip you.
So...
You better take your eyes off the maid
and the other girls and look only at me!
Do you hear me?!
Huh?
You're a familiar, so it's only natural for you to look only at your master.
Right, okay.
If you get it, then go back to sleep already.
Yo, partner.
No matter what you guys say to each other, you're getting along well.
But I wonder how long that'll last.
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君のそばにいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai ga bokura wo tameshitatte
どんな未来が僕らを試したって
No matter how the future tests us
kitto…
きっと…
I’m sure…
aa futari no unmei
ああ 二人の運命
Ah, it’s our destiny
meguriaeta no wa
巡り合えたのは
I was able to meet you
kimi no koe kikoeta kara
君の声 聞こえたから
Because I heard your voice
sou pinchi na dekigoto
そう ピンチな出来事
Yeah, even if crisis events
oshiyosete kite mo
押し寄せてきても
Press on at me
kimi to ireba norikoerareru
君といれば乗り越えられる
If I'm with you, then I can overcome them
tokimeki to makenki to
ときめきと負けん気と
Palpitations and competitive spirit
urahara de haraharasuru kedo
裏腹でハラハラするけど
Excite me on the contrary, but-
Stay with me
tada kimi o mamoritai yo
ただ 君を守りたいよ
I only want to protect you
tooi sekai de umareta futari da kedo
遠い世界で生まれた二人だけど
We were born in distant worlds
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君の側にいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai mo kibou ni kaeyou
どんな未来も希望に変えよう
Let’s change any future into hope
Forever
Her Highness's Zero
I shall now explain the procedure for leaving the ceremony.
Cardinal Masarini...
I do not need a crown.
And here you are being selfish again.
We are in the middle of a war.
Although we have halted Albion's
march, we cannot let our guard down.
The citizens are wishing for you to become the true Queen...
...and defeat the enemy.
Praise Princess Henrietta!
Praise Tristain!
Time for food?
Today's the coronation ceremony, so I bet even a captive like myself would be served a special meal.
Unfortunately, there's no Last Supper for you.
You are...!
Cromwell,
how foolish of you to become a captive after going through...
...the trouble of killing the prince of Albion to gain authority.
Luckily, in the midst of the coronation ceremony, I was able to retrieve the Ring of Andvari.
Please, give me another chance!
They used a magic I've never seen before!
A huge light appeared all of a sudden and annihilated my troops!
That might have been...
Void?
Y-Yes, that was completely unexpected.
It was not my responsibility!
Don't worry. You'll never have to take responsibility again.
Wait! Wait!
S-Stop it...
Stop it!
Hey, let's get going.
The Princess' parade is going to end.
Saito, I have a present for you.
Here, take it.
Is this a pair of glasses?
I have fine eyesight if you ask me.
It isn't an ordinary pair of glasses.
I asked my elder sister to send one of our family treasures.
Louise, you have an elder sister?
Just put them on already.
Okay...
Oh yeah, I remember you saying that you're the youngest...
I can't take it off!
Let's get going.
Siesta!
S-Saito!
Saito-san!
Saito-san, what's that?
Are you working today, too?
Do you want to go check out the parade with us?
No, I'm...
What's wrong?
I know...
...that you have given up returning to your home for Miss Vallière's sake.
That's...!
So...
This is...
I...!
U-Um... What's with those glasses?
Huh? What's this?
They won't come off.
Those Medusa's Glasses are a magical item.
Any time you look at a girl other than myself, the one who gave them to you, with lascivious eyes,
the gems around them glow.
W-What's with that?
I didn't hear about that!
You need only look at your master.
To stare at other girls when you're a familiar...
With lustrous eyes...
With dilated eyes...
With bloodshot eyes!
No, I wasn't...
Where exactly were you looking?
That maid's face, perhaps?
Or...
...her breasts?!
I see...
L-Louise-san?
I see. You were looking at her boobs.
So, you like big ones that much?
So you like big boobs.
Louise! Hold on!
So, the bigger ones are better for you!
Ah, it's Miss Vallière and Saito-kun again.
Hey, Louise.
Montmorency.
Are you two off to watch the parade as well?
You two get along well as always.
Just like us, Montmorency.
Look, Louise.
Since today's a day to celebrate, I'm wearing an outgoing dress.
Ow...
Isn't it a little short?
This is nothing.
Saito.
Oh, it's those two again.
Kirche!
Tabitha.
I can't believe you.
I can understand Kirche, but who
knew you were eyeing Tabitha, too.
Is "female" the only trait that you need?
Pretty much...
No, that's not true!
I won't look.
I won't look at anyone else anymore...
Fine.
You keep your eyes shut until we go back to our room.
Okay...
Princess!
Look, Saito!
What are you doing closing your eyes?
She looks so majestic.
S-Saito.
How dare you eye the Princess... no, the Queen...
Wait, Louise! Not here!
You're...
You're the worst!
We have a ruffian!
Protect Our Highness!
Captain. I assume it was them.
Arrest them!
Sir!
Saito...
I am Her Highness' court lady, Louise de La Vallière.
I need to talk with Her Highness!
Let me through here!
You cannot!
We have been ordered to not let anybody through.
Just let me through!
La Vallière-dono.
Drop your wand!
A gun is faster than spell casting.
Her Highness is in a meeting with Principal Osmond.
I shall hear what you need to say in her stead.
Principal Osmond?
And you are...?
Agnes Chevalier de Milan.
Captain of the Musketeer Force.
Musketeer Force?
You're the one that arrested Saito, aren't you?
Release Saito!
Saito?
The culprit.
Saito isn't the culprit!
I caused the explosion.
The idiot was eyeing the Princess...
A-Anyway, give me back Saito!
To hell with this present!
I guess I'm treated like this, after all.
Then, in the future...
Louise will get married with some stupid aristocrat.
I'll praise the two from afar,
and end my life as a familiar.
Damn it, I should have returned to Japan.
If I can't return home, then I'd rather pick a different girl.
The Queen was beautiful.
Saito-san.
Y-Your Highness!
Why are you here?
I came to see you.
See me?
You don't say...
Saito-san...
She can't be...
No! That's way too much!
Saito-san.
I have a favour to ask of you.
If you desire so much...
You insolent fool!
How dare you touch the hands of the Queen!
I'll shoot you right this moment!
Agnes, please stand back.
I want to talk to him alone.
But...!
It is fine.
It's fine.
You keep quiet!
Agnes!
Next time I will shoot you regardless of what Her Highness says!
Saito-san, are you hurt?
We're finally alone.
Yes.
Then...
From the information gathered by Intelligence and from what Principal Osmond said,
it was you and Louise who defeated the Albion force.
We are certain that it was done by the void mage and her familiar, Gandalfr.
T-That's...
Could you...
Could you lend us your power?
Right now, the entire country is at war.
The military in particular is saying we should take the opportunity and march into Albion.
Cardinal Masarini and the senior statesmen seem to agree with the military.
But I want to avoid war, if possible.
Saito-san.
So, this is the Gandalfr's insignia?
Yes.
Please, along with Louise, help me with your power.
Well, Louise said that she'd do anything if it's for you, so...
I am asking you personally.
Please become one of my few allies.
One of the few?
Being a Queen is inconvenient.
There are only a handful of people who can truly understand and help me.
Will you accept my request?
All right...
What a relief.
Thank you very much.
But for now, please stay at the Magic Academy with Louise.
I want to keep you two undercover.
Enemies exist within the Kingdom, too.
Spies, you mean?
A few hours ago, inside the jail for aristocrats,
Lord Cromwell was assassinated.
A multi-layered Lock spell had been cast there.
Someone who could dispel a Lock must have led the culprit through.
Could that really happen?
Saito-san.
If there is anything you want as a reward for your cooperation, please say it.
Anything?
Yes, anything.
As long as it is within my capabilities.
Then...
Agnes.
Please bring Miss Vallière over.
Ma'am!
L-Louise?!
Saito.
Wait! You got it wrong! You got it all wrong!
S-Saito!
Idiot...
You idiot...
Saito, you idiot...
How dare you make me worry.
Louise.
Hey, what's that?
Heresiarch's Book of Invocation.
Princess gave it to me.
She said that it'd be better for me to hold onto it.
Apparently, it's passed down through the Tristain's royal family.
What's this?
According to Principal Osmond's research,
void spells should be written in it.
Should be? But there's nothing there.
A misprint?
Or it could be...
What, did you figure something out?
White paper. In other words, nothingness.
"Fight with an empty mind", perhaps?
Sparkle~
Don't you often see that kind of line in manga?
Manga?
Oh yeah, I haven't read manga in a while.
Saito, do you feel that you should have returned home?
Well, a little.
But...
I can't leave you alone in a dangerous place like this.
Saito.
From now on, Miss Vallière, the Queen's words shall be
passed down to you via a member of the Musketeer Force.
The code name for you two is Zero.
Is that understood?
Y-Yes!
And Hiraga Saito.
I shall overlook today, but if you act in a perverse manner towards the Queen in the future, be prepared.
Saito...
Yes!
What's this "perverse manner"?
You dog!
Pervert dog!
Dog in heat!
Hentai Dog!
Liar, you said that you'd never call me a dog or whip me!
You dare talk back to me, perverted dog?!
It's your own fault!
It's because you wag your tail at every girl!
And to... the... the... P-Pri...
Priceless Joumon artefact?
Acting lecherously towards the Queen...
I won't forgive you.
Hold it, Louise! Calm down!
I knew that this was going to happen.
Die!
Vallière-dono!
Pardon me.
Actually, it is an emergency, so forgive me!
The Queen has been kidnapped by somebody!
Y-You stupid dog!
chanto koko ni ite watashi no chikaku de
ちゃんとココにいて! 私の近くで
Be right here! close to me
zutto watashi o itsumo itsumo mitsumete nasai
ずっと私をいつもいつも見つめてなさい
Always, always look at me at all times
yosomishiteta desho hoka no onna no ko
よそ見してたでしょっ 他の女の子
You looked away, didn’t you? At other girls
o-shiokisuru wa furari furari furachi na yatsu wa
お仕置きするわ　フラリフラリ不埒なヤツは
I’ll punish those who are wavering and insolent
Don't touch! kikanai kara ne iiwake wa
Don't touch! 聞かないからね　言い訳は
Don’t touch! Because I won’t listen to excuses
Touch me... tsukareta kara nee kata o kashite yo
Touch me… 疲れたから… ねぇ肩を貸してよ
Touch me… because I'm tired… Hey, lend me your shoulder
suki yo nante uso yo
スキよ　なんて嘘よ
I love you, it’s a lie
kirai sore mo uso da wa
キライ　それも嘘だわ
I hate you, that’s a lie, too
nai nai nai dame yo kanchigai
ないないない　ダメよ勘違い
Nay nay nay, it’s useless, it’s a misunderstanding
dakara suki yo nante iwanai
だから「スキよ」なんて言わない
So I won’t say, “I love you”
Non non non dokka e ittara
Non non non　どっかへ行ったら
Non non non, because I absolutely won’t forgive you
zettai ni yurusanai kara ne
絶対に　許さないからね!
If you go to somewhere else
datte
だって
But
honto wa dare yori soba ni itai no
ホントは誰より傍にいたいの
The truth is, I want to be by your side more than anyone else
ai no kusari de sanposhimasho
愛の鎖で　散歩しましょ!
Let’s go take a walk in chains of love!
I... to be honest...
...might love you...
Next Time
You dog, get a move on!
The Princess got taken away by Prince Wales, who's supposed to have passed away.
Zero no Tsukaima. Futatsuki no Kishi.
The Vow of Wind and Water.
If you want to meet me again next week, then sit tightly and wait!
The Vow of Wind and Water