Geez, I don't see it anywhere.
Strange... It should be around here...
Order of Undine Knights!
Search the premises thoroughly!
Yeah!
"Ah"?
I-It's your fault for dangling such a malicious object!
But it's still hard to believe that Tabitha attacked
Louise and Saito on the orders of the Gallian Kingdom.
We need proof to support that claim.
If Gallia really is behind this,
will you be going to Gallia, as well?
You're worried about me, Montmorency?
I'm worried you'd have an affair with a Gallian girl!
What's this?
What are you doing?!
Malicorn?!
You have man boobs.
What's wrong with a guy having boobs?
Fondle them more!
I'm just joking with you.
I want to touch a girl's, too.
I want a girlfriend!
S-She's so cute.
We finally meet!
Why is it always Saito?
Help Onee-sama.
Onee-sama?
I can't believe you. One after another.
You pervert dog!
First of all, why are you naked?!
I have a name, and it's Illococoo.
Illococoo? What a cute name!
It means "swift as the wind".
I don't care about your name.
Clothes!
What do I do now?
I can't go save Onee-sama like this.
Pardon me. You've said "Onee-sama" a few times,
but who might you be referring to?
Tabitha-oneesama, of course!
You're Tabitha's younger sister?
Please save Onee-sama.
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
mejirushi no nai michi mo heiki sa futari nara
メジルシのない道も平気さ　ふたりなら
Even on a road without signs, I'll be fine, if we're together
saki no mienai tabi mayoinagara mitsuketa yo
先の見えない旅　迷いながら見つけたよ
On a journey that I can't see ahead of, while I was lost, I found it
boku no iru basho kimi no tonari
僕の居る場所　君のとなり
That my place to be is next to you
kenkashite nando mo hanashita sono te
喧嘩して　何度も離したその手
When we quarrelled, I let go of your hand again and again
hikiyose dakitai ima
引き寄せ抱きたい　今
I want to pull close and hold it now
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
namida no ame ni utaretara
涙の雨に打たれたら
If I'm beaten down by the rain of tears
I wanna hold you sugu yobi na yo boku no namae
I wanna hold you　すぐ呼びなよ　僕の名前
I wanna hold you, call my name immediately
dakishime ni yuku wa
抱きしめに行くわ
I'll go embrace you
kanashimi mo tsuyogari mo kono te ni uketomeru
悲しみも強がりもこの手に　受け止める
I'll accept sadness and bluffing in my hands
Tabitha's Younger Sister
So Tabitha's charged with treason for letting Saito go and was stripped of her status as a chevalier?
That's not all.
Even Onee-sama's mother was arrested.
What?
And what's Tabitha doing now?
She went to save Mother.
But...
For that Tabitha to lose...
We must be facing a Square-class mage.
If I had known this, I would have chased after her!
So you've come to ask us for help?
Please.
Sure.
We'll be glad to!
Won't you all go help?
You guys aren't...
Are you all doubting her?
Where's the proof that she's not a Gallian spy?
It could be a trap to lure Louise in.
Besides, she's tall and has big breasts.
It's hard to believe that she's Tabitha's younger sister.
I am her sister!
Believe me!
Where's the proof?
The proof...
The proof is...
Hey, you're all being rude to her!
How could a cute girl like her lie?!
Ah ha.
Love at first sight, eh, Malicorn?
I-It's nothing like that!
Yes, her visuals aren't bad.
I'll bring a witness!
Now?
Wait!
Illococoo?
Sylphid?
Have you seen a girl around?
A girl with long blue hair.
You have?
So you're the witness?
I see.
Hey, we want to ask something!
Does your master have a sister called Illococoo?
So it was true.
Look! You all better apologise to her!
Sylphid, there's one more thing I want to ask you.
Did your master get captured?
I see.
If Tabitha's familiar says so, we'll have to believe it.
Okay.
You just wait.
We'll definitely save your master.
The Order of Undine Knights cannot ignore this matter.
We will go to Gallia to save Tabitha!
What's wrong, Reinard?
Are you scared?
No, that is not it.
We are the Queen's private knights, right?
Can we do this without her orders?
So are you saying we should forget about Tabitha?
I didn't say that.
Because Tabitha let us go, Louise is here with us.
Knights are not knights if they don't go save their friends.
However, as Reinard says, it is wrong to take action without her orders.
We must receive permission.
I can't see her letting us.
No, the Princess will understand the situation.
You sound really confident.
I guess it comes from the trust she places in you.
So Saito and the Princess are...
Louise.
Could you help persuade the Princess, too?
O-Okay.
Good. Saito, Louise and Malicorn.
We'll go persuade the Queen.
Until then, you all stay here on standby.
You're quite skilled to capture my niece without any trouble.
Looks like nature magic is quite useful.
I've fulfilled the condition of capturing the traitor as you requested.
Now it's your time to do what we ask.
Sure, say it.
Recently, the Gate of Shytarn, which we guard, has seemed quite busy.
Gate of Shytarn? You mean the holy land?
To us, it's the gate to all evil.
It brought the calamity 6,000 years ago.
And that's starting to move?
A sign of things to come?
There is a prophecy amongst our kind.
When four devils come, the true devil will awaken.
The power of the true devil will bring the calamity back.
Power of devils?
It's what you refer to as Void magic.
Really? The Void...
At this rate, we cannot protect our peace.
What exactly do you want me to do?
I want you to stop anyone who approaches the Gate of Shytarn.
That sounds like a large task.
I hope there is merit in doing that.
The right to mine Wind Stone in Sahara for the next hundred years and the means needed to do so.
That's not enough.
What?
Serve me as long as I live.
What?!
If you don't like that, this conversation ends here.
Fine.
You're a smart man, Vitartial.
Let me ask you one thing.
What?
What's in your mind?
What are you trying to accomplish?
I'm just bored.
I see.
I have the greatest gift prepared for you, Charlotte.
As punishment for standing against your master,
I will have you take the same path your mother took.
Until the drug's ready, spend the last few moments with your family.
That's how I make up for not being much of an uncle, Charlotte.
I cannot permit you to go to Gallia.
How come, Princess?
If you go, it might start a war.
A war?
You are my private knights.
No matter what the intent is, what you do will be considered done by the Kingdom of Tristain.
From what I heard,
Tabitha-dono is currently under arrest as a criminal.
If you tried to rescue such a person,
it would be considered an act of aggression.
Do you understand?
Saito-san?
I'm returning this to you.
Saito?
Now I won't cause any trouble to Tristain, right?
Both Malicorn and I share the thought with the vice-captain.
Thank you very much for your care.
You are so...
Agnes?
Arrest these people.
Big trouble! Big trouble!
They're arrested!
You mean Guiche?!
Even Saito-san?
Didn't I tell you?! Her Highness wouldn't accept it!
Damn it!
But how do you know that they got arrested?
I've got pointed ears.
You mean sharp ears.
Hi. Jean won't pay attention to me, so I came for a visit.
Is something going on?
We should have been on our way to Gallia by now...
Sorry it turned out like this because of me.
Don't worry.
We simply kept things straight as aristocrats.
In fact, I want to thank you.
Thank me?
Why?
By staying true to my heart as a knight,
I got imprisoned at the castle!
You can't have this kind of experience every day.
I can already imagine the faces of the girls who hear this story.
I'm such a sinful man.
What nonsense are you talking about?!
If I stay at a place like this, I can't see Illococoo!
I'm sure Louise will do something.
Remember? She's a childhood friend,
so I bet things are going well and she's calming the Princess down right now.
Why is he wilfully going into danger?
Why are you wilfully going into danger?
Everyone wants to help her even now.
I don't want to lose any more dear people.
So you are...
I have a question I must ask you, Princess.
What is it, Louise?
What do you think... of...
...Saito?
What do I think?
He's doing great as a chevalier.
Not as the Queen, but as a friend!
Answer me as a woman!
Louise?
Are you not thinking of Saito as a man?
That's why during the ball, you and Saito...
I've been lonely. I've had no one to rely on.
Perhaps I wanted to lean on someone.
It could have been anyone?
I'm not entirely sure myself.
Not sure?
That's fine. Your feelings belong to you.
They're nothing I can comment on.
Louise?
However, Saito is my familiar.
If you lay your hand on him,
please be ready for the consequences.
You're right.
Saito-san is important to you.
I'm envious of you...
...for having a person to talk like that about.
Since I don't have one anymore.
I'm sorry, Louise.
But if so, we need to convince him to not go to Gallia.
I can't do that.
Why? Can you sit by and watch your dearest go to war?
Tabitha always helped us.
So this time, we want to help her.
Louise...
Why even you?
With this, I'm no longer an aristocrat.
I'm just Louise.
Treat me as a traitor who has stood against you.
Then nothing will befall you or Tristain.
Gallia is after your Void magic, too!
I know.
But doing this is for an aristocrat,
or rather,
for a human being, the right thing to do.
If you're doing what you think is right,
then I will have to do what I think is right.
I'm hungry.
I'm gonna die.
What's taking Louise so long?
What could she be doing?
Is that Louise?
Louise!
See? Just like I said, right?
You sure took your time, Louise!
We got tired waiting for you.
Huh?
Where's your...
I returned it to the Princess.
Huh? Returned?
Why?
What do you mean, Louise?
You didn't persuade the Princess?
Can't you tell by looking?
I disobeyed the Princess as well and got arrested.
Arrested?
I had no other choice.
To avoid causing any problems for her, this was the only way.
You might be sad to know that you're now a familiar of a plain girl.
Louise!
For you to throw away your status as an aristocrat for Tabitha's sake!
Amazing?
Or should I say I'm touched?
Saito?
This isn't the way it's supposed to go!
What are you going to do with all four of us arrested?
You rejoiced a moment ago, saying it's an aristocrat's honour.
They are different matters entirely!
To be trapped in a place like this...
I won't see Illococoo...
What, are you giving up already?
I'm not.
I will get myself out of here.
I will come save you, Tabitha.
Are you awake now?
You're the...
Vitartial.
I have your wand.
Where am I?
This is the Al Hambra Castle.
If you're of the royal family, I'm sure you've heard the name.
Where's my mother?
Mother!
Mother?
I put her to sleep since she had fits.
Do not worry. I didn't harm her in any way.
Do not think of trying to escape.
Where's my familiar?
That nature dragon got away.
Don't think of calling for help.
You've seen my power.
What do you plan on doing, shutting us in a place like this?
A drug is being made right now.
When it's done, we're having you take it.
A drug?
The same one your mother drank.
The drug that erases the heart.
That drug?
Only we can make it.
If the time before it's completed passes slowly, read a book.
It's a heroic epic of a man named l'Ivaldi who goes to save a girl captured by a dragon.
You said you will get out of here no matter what,
so I thought you had some idea...
And why is it only us working?
If you have the time to move your mouth, move your hands!
If only I had my wand, I could easily get out of this place.
If I had Delf here, then same goes for me.
But Malicorn, I'm surprised that you had spoons on you.
More than one, not to mention.
I always have them with me.
This way I can eat anything, anywhere.
No wonder his breasts grow.
Everyone in Tristain!
What was that?
That voice!
We have news.
Germania's von Zerbst family has come to show you the latest piece of technology that uses the water vapour engine, the Ostland.
Those in the city and those in the castle.
Come closer and take a look.
Those guys...
What are they thinking, waving hands?
Kirche!
Colbert-sensei!
We'll talk later.
Yes!
Saito-san!
Over here!
Siesta!
Tiffa!
You guys shortened our lives.
Montmorency!
How did you know that we were captured?
That's because...
Hey, Illococoo.
I'm guessing your master told you not to reveal the secret,
but isn't it enough?
If you won't say it, I will.
Darn it! I promised Onee-sama that I wouldn't tell anyone!
Wind that coats me.
Transform me.
Sylphid!
This Sylphid here is a nature dragon.
What's a nature dragon?
A legendary ancient dragon.
Intelligent, knowledgeable in languages and able to control nature magic.
So they aren't extinct.
The one I fell in love with isn't a human girl,
but a legendary nature dragon?
Sigh...
It's impossible.
But...
kyuu ni senaka wo mukete kakedashita wa (Just love me)
急に背中を向けて 駆け出したわ
I suddenly turned my back on you and ran away
hoka no ko ni yasashiku shiteta kara yo
ほかの子に優しくしてたからよ
Because you've been so gentle to many other girls
Boy onegai oikakete yo
Boyお願い 追いかけてよ
Boy, please chase after me
ato ni wa hikenai kara
あとには引けないから
Because it won't be over after this
pun pun pun
I am so sorry
gomen to ienakute gomen ne
ゴメンと言えなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't say "I'm sorry", sorry ♥
shinjite iru no ni kuchibiru ga togaru
信じているのに くちびるが尖る
Even though I believe you, my lips are pouting
kawaiku narenakute gomen ne
可愛くなれなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't be cute, sorry ♥
kosame no furu machi tsukamaete
小雨の降る街 つかまえて
Catch me in the town where a drizzle is falling
furimuku kara nakanaori no chu o shite
振り向くから 仲直りのCHU～をして
Because I'll turn around and give you a make-up kiss
atsui ryouude no naka de
熱い両腕の中で
In your warm arms
Next Time
I can't turn back anymore.
I have made up my mind.
From now on, I will live without relying on anyone.
Zero no Tsukaima. Princess no Rondo.
The Path to the Border.
But I'm actually very unsure.
The Path to the Border
I won't forgive you if you look away.