Motivation
What's wrong, Yukko?
I can't summon the motivation to do anything.
What are you talking about?
We're high school students, you know.
It's the start of a new term.
Motivation is something that comes out naturally once you start doing it.
The motivation to do something before actually doing it won't come out.
How do I get motivated to do
something before I actually start doing it?
The motivation to do something before actually doing it?
Hm...
Anyway, just do it!
All right!
I just want to stay as a simple-minded idiot.
Shinonome Institute
Professor! It's about time you woke up.
Nichijou 01
And... there!
Good morning...
What are you doing?
Today's breakfast will be fried fish.
Eh?!
I want omelette-rice!
Didn't you have that yesterday?
Fish contain lots of nutrients, you know!
Stop being picky and eat everything,
otherwise you won't grow bigger- Ah!
Um, that's our important breakfast, so...
Ah, no, it's not like that!
This isn't anything robotic at all!
Um, this is...
Ah, it ran away.
Wait up!
Have a safe trip.
Perhaps that cat is also having a hard time?
Ah, I'm gonna crash!
tatta ima hajimete kizuita
たった今 初めて気づいた
I just realised it for the first time
koi ni ochita no dana
恋に落ちたのだな～
That I had fallen in love~
nijyuuyo jikan kimi kimi kimi
24h キミ☆ キミ☆ キミ☆
Twenty-four hours a day thinking of you, you and nothing more than you!
ishiki sezaru o emasen
意識せざるをえません!
It's something I wasn't consciously aware of
nanka (nanka) itsumo to chigau
なんか (なんか) いつもと違う
Somehow (somehow) I'm feeling different from the usual
kimi to (futari) gikochinai kaiwa
キミと (二人) ぎこちない会話
With you (the two of us) and our dull chatter
masaka (ryouomoi) iya kataomoi
まさか (両思い) いや 片思い
Don't tell me (mutual love?) Nope, it's a one-sided crush
yabai shisen acchatta
やばい! 視線合っちゃった!
This is bad! Our gazes met!
nani nani kono doki doki
なになに?! このドキドキ?!
What, what? Why is my heart pounding like this?
shikoukairo guccha guccha konsen
思考回路 ぐっちゃぐっちゃ 混線・・・
Did a short circuit just make a mess out of my mind?
konna koto hajimete dayo
こんなこと 初めてだよ
This is my first time... feeling like this...
netsu demo aru no kana
熱でもあるのかな～
I wonder if I have a fever~
kyuutenchokka irasshatta koigokoro
急転直下 いらっしゃった 恋心
Suddenly and precipitately, love has arrived.
acchuuma kao hakka de makkakka
あっちゅうま 顔 発火で まっかっか
Instantly igniting my face into a bright red
ba ba baka na te ga furueruzo
バ・バ・バカな?! 手が震えるぞ
T-That's stupid?! My hands are shaking
kore ga zoku ni iu koi nano
これが 俗に言う 「恋」 なの?!
Is this really what they call "love"?
yayayacchatta kaiwa kami makuri
やややっちゃった 会話 噛みまくり
I-I did it! A conversation filled with stutters
kimazui chinmoku mamimumemo
気まずい沈黙 マミムメモ
This awkward silence... *mumble mumble*
kimi no (kimi no) kimochi shiritai yo
キミの (キミの) 気持ち 知りたいよ
Your... (Your...) I want to know your feelings.
kakakata kataomoi
カカカタ☆カタオモイ
O-One-sided love
hatsukoi itsumo no tsuugakuro
初恋! いつもの通学路
First love! The usual way to school
pika pika hikaru I do fall in love
ピカピカ光る I do fall in love!
The shining light. I do fall in love!
sora mo tobesou sa
空も飛べそうさ
I feel I could fly towards the sky
kakakata kataomoi
カカカタ☆カタオモイ
O-One-sided love
Kokeshi
Akabeko
Salmon
Mio-chan, selamat pagi!
TL note: Indonesian for "good morning".
Ah Yukko, good morning!
What should I do, I forgot to bring my student ID...
Huh?
She ignored my selamat pagi?
I won't be called upon by the seniors, right?
If that happens,
saying "I'm a third year student!" should be enough, don't you think?
That won't solve anything.
What?
Thunder?
Even though the weather's clear?
It might suddenly start pouring down, you know!
A shower or a hailstorm...
A kokeshi came down.
A-Are you all right, Yukko?
Who would've thought that a kokeshi would come down?
What a surprise!
I wonder where it fell from...
I don't know...
But it's extremely unlikely that you'd get hit by a kokeshi in your lifetime!
Those people are rare, you know.
I don't think they exist.
It might actually mean that luck is with me!
Luck is not with me...
Yukko, are you okay?
An Akabeko of all things...
Akabeko...
I'm wrong, it's not that luck is not with me.
We should just think of it this way, Mio-chan...
I should be happy that I wasn't hit by raw food.
Thinking like that, the small mercy amongst the misfortune-
It's a salmon!
Tokisada Prefectural High School
Morning!
Good morning.
Ah, Mai-chan, good morning.
Selamat pagi!
Morning.
What are you reading, Mai-chan?
A real estate information magazine.
Eh?
You're moving, Mai-chan?
Undecided.
Do you even say selamat pagi?
It can't be helped, I guess I'll let the phrase rest for today.
Yukko.
Selamat malam.
TL note: Indonesian for "good evening".
Mai-chan, you should say selamat pagi there!
What language is that?
H-Homeroom will begin.
Um, when I came to school this morning, this was in the shoe rack...
Did anyone put this in there?
U-Um... If there is anyone who knows about it, please tell me, okay?
Mio-chan, I wonder who did that?
Maybe it's a prank?
It might be something unexpected
like a student who likes the teacher...
I don't think they would leave a Maitreya statue though.
But, well, it's not like I don't understand
people who have unachievable aspirations.
Yeah, it's that, right?
Like the way you feel about Sasahara-senpai.
Y-You idiot!
Where am I?
I have to get home!
I'm sure the professor is worried,
and leaving her with the charcoal stove is dangerous.
Eh?
I can't get off!
My chopsticks are gone!
One of my shoes is gone as well!
What should I do?!
My hand's gone!
Now it'll be exposed that I am a robot!
Here it goes.
Wonderful
Thank you for the food.
If you don't finish up quick, the bell for fifth period will ring.
Huh?
You didn't like sausages?
Saving the most delicious food for last in a lunch box is fundamental.
Then, I can finish by saying: "It's delicious".
Well then, here goes... I'm going to eat it!
Nichijou 02
It came out!
Not yet!
It's over!
Not just yet!
One...
...two...
...three.
Safe!
You're out!
No way, Mio-chan!
It's the three-second rule, the three-second rule.
No, you were already out way before that!
It's delicious!
Yukko really is an idiot.
First comes rock, next comes paper, rockscispaper doesn't count,
rock paper scissors!
Yes!
Good morning, everyone.
Spring has come and a new year has started,
but the cold days are still continuing.
In my case, I have it twice as cold as everyone else.
Nichijou 03
Anyway, make sure you don't catch a cold...
This is a promise with your principal, okay?
If you don't listen, then I'll be...
...transferred to a different school, on principle!
Mio-chan, Mio-chan.
What?
He'll get mad if you talk.
Say, doesn't the principal notice that his jokes are way too old?
He must know best of all that his jokes aren't received very well.
I wonder about that...
Could it be that he knows his jokes aren't received well,
and is putting on a show of even more
effort to the young people nowadays?!
If that's true, then this principal...
...is pretty skilful!
Mai-chan?!
Mai-chan is...?!
Could it be because of that old geezer gag?
Above that, this is the first time I've ever seen her laughing so hard!
All right!
This should do it!
Mai-chan!
Why is it?
If I said it here now, I feel like I'll lose everything.
Yukko.
Sorry.
Never mind, actually.
I guess, until she notices...
...I won't grab it.
Squid
Well then, next is a talk about student guidance from Sakurai-sensei.
Sakurai-sensei, please.
Um, Sakurai-sensei?
Yes!
I'm sorry, I'm Sakurai from student counselling...
I'm sorry... Eh, ah...
I get really nervous when there's so many people.
No good, this is no good!
I can't always stand and look like a helpless teacher...
I have to say what I need to say properly!
I know!
Do you often see a goat on the school grounds lately?
Let's not take goats with us to the school grounds!
What's wrong...
What's wrong with goats?!
Going to school on a goat isn't prohibited by the school rules,
am I right?!
Eh, ah... that is...
Mio-chan, isn't that Sasahara-senpai?
Eh, really?
No... I'll permit goats!
It's rejected, rejected!
Absolutely rejected!
There's no way it's okay to bring a goat to school!
You can say that, but Tachibana Misato...
Why must I rush about on my own two legs?
First of all, the heir of the Sasahara family...
What's that about the heir of the Sasahara family?
You guys are just normal farmers!
So?
What's wrong with the heir saying he's the heir?
Heh, so Sasahara-kun's family are farmers.
I feel like I've been deceived.
So that goat at the bike rack was Sasahara-senpai's.
Riding a white goat, Sasahara-senpai will come and pick me up!
A happy new year!
M-Me too!
Mio-chan!
Using a cellphone while riding a bicycle is very dangerous,
let's stop doing that!
And also, one last thing...
This morning, a Maitreya statue was in my shoe locker!
I don't think these kind of pranks are good.
Excuse us, passing through...
A Maitreya statue.
Mai-chan!
Don't stop suddenly!
Ah, this thing again?
It might be déjà vu.
Who did it?!
I won't get mad, so raise your hand!
You'll all stay here until he comes forth!
Who was it?
You go forth.
I'm sorry, I heard it was Sakurai-sensei's birthday, so...
I see, a Maitreya statue is no good, eh?
With good intentions on your birthday, a present.
I'll imagine that you don't need a Maitreya statue.
The principal.
With this, the morning assembly is finished.
Thank you very much for your work up until today, Principal.
Deputy principal?!
Fire Alarm
Push Hard
Button
This fire hydrant button has a really strong magical pull that makes you want to press it, doesn't it?
Indeed.
What if you try pressing it?
The alarm didn't go off last time I pressed it.
Eh?
Really?
Fire?
No way!
What should we do?
Are we going to run?
Everyone!
For now, let's go to the court!
What the hell are you pushing me aside for?!
You're the one pushing me!
What're you saying?
Besides, I've always hated you!
Stop it!
We might end up dying here!
Let's get out of here first!
Leave the arguing for later!
Um...
I'm sorry, but what is "KY"?
TL Note: "KY" is short for "Kuuki Yomenai" meaning "unable to read the atmosphere".
Um...
What could "KY" be?
I'm sorry, please tell me about "KY"!
Help me, someone!
Hey!
Oh, Captain... What could "KY" be?
It's referring to you.
Second grade Class B, Sasahara Koujirou.
Important Matters and Things to be done
Please come to the staff room immediately to Tomioka.
It's true, it's not violating the school rules... But a goat?
Can't you do something about it?
If you don't like to walk,
you could come by bicycle... Just as long as it's not a goat.
Sir.
It's Tomioka.
Tomioka.
Add sensei to it.
Sensei.
Can you call him Sasahara Kojirou, and not goat?
He is a goat for now.
Nichijou 04
My name is Shinonome Nano.
I'm a robot created by Professor, whom I live with.
Professor seems to be doing some kind of research,
and is at home all day.
I spend my days while also helping out the professor.
Professor!
I warmed up the milk-
I don't have any special features, but it seems like I can still feel pain.
Nano, what's wrong?
Professor!
My little toe...!
My little toe was...!
Y-Your l-little toe was...!
With this, you should be fine for now.
Eh?!
I don't have any special features,
but it seems like you can take off my little toe.
Professor, what's this key for?
I didn't turn it?
Ah yes, it turns sometimes.
You turn it like this.
Ah, what's going on?!
I'm sorry, I'm full of special features.
See, it's something interesting, isn't it?
Could it be that you made the key just for this?
Yup.
Could it be that you made the key just for this?!
Yup!
Take it off, please!
No way!
Eh?!
Because it's cute.
Remove it from my back, please!
Eh... But it's cute...
I want to be more normal.
I want to sit on a chair like a normal person,
and turn over when I sleep.
With this, I can't even go to school.
I would've been okay with not being a human-type robot at all.
Nano...
I-It's just a lie!
A lie!
Don't take it seriously, Professor!
Then take it...
Eh?
Go and win the Akutagawa Award for Literature!
Why?!
Shinonome Institute
Win the Akutagawa Award!
Every day is like that.
Where am I?
asa okite hao migai te
朝起きて 歯を磨いて
Woke up in the morning, brushed my teeth
attoiuma gogo juu ji
あっという間 午後10時
In the blink of an eye, it's 10pm
kyou mo takusan waratta naa
今日も たくさん 笑ったなぁ
Today, we laughed a whole lot
takusan tokimeita naa
たくさん ときめいたなぁ
We had a great time
tomodachi to baka mitai ni sawai deru toki ni mo
友達と バカみたいに騒いでる 時にも
At times, with my friends, acting like fools, being noisy
chirachiratte me ga au
チラチラって 目が合う
Fluttering, our eyes met.
guuzen dayo ne
…偶然、だよね。
It's a coincidence, right?
hatsukoi nante ie nai
初恋なんて言えない
I wouldn't call this my first love
kyara janai n da mon
キャラじゃないんだもんっ!
It's not my character.
nee ashita mo aeru yo ne
ねえ あしたも会えるよね?
Say, will we be able to meet again tomorrow?
mabuta o tojiru to
まぶたを 閉じると
As my eyelids close
kirakira kimi darake
キラキラ キミだらけ
I see you sparkling all over the place
kyou mo tanoshikatta ne
今日も 楽しかったね
Today was fun, too, wasn't it?
aa koi shite n da naa
あー 恋 してんだなぁ
I'm in love~
ureshii na ureshii na
うれしいな うれしいな
So happy, so happy
hajimemashite koi gokoro
はじめまして こいごころ
It is my pleasure to meet you, my new-found love.
ashita mata aeru ne
あした また あえるね
Surely, we'll meet again tomorrow~
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
Have a good night
yume de sugu aeru ne
ゆめで すぐ あえるね
We'll meet immediately in our dreams
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
So have a good night
Hello!
This is Nano-chan's big toe!
My capacity is one gigabyte.
I would've preferred to be a bit bigger...
The next episode of Nichijou is episode two.
Narration   Katsura Reiko
Please look forward to it!