Shinonome Institute
Nano!
Nano?
Naaaaaano!
Nano!
Yes?
Nano, Nano!
Nano!
Yes, yes.
It's Nyan~
Nano!
Look, look!
It's Professor nyan~!
Nyan.
You too, Sakamoto... Look, look!
It's Professor nyan~!
Professor.
That's probably... moe!
Nyan~?
Nyan~!
It's Professor nyan~!
It's moe!
It's Professor nyan nyan~!
It's Professor nyan~!
It's moe!
It's Professor nyan nyan~!
The Shinonome household was at peace again today.
tatta ima hajimete kidzuita koi ni ochita no da no
I just realized for the first time that I had fallen in love
nijyuuyo jikan kimi, kimi kimi ishiki sezaru wo emasen
All day long, it's only you, you, you; I just couldn't avoid it
nanka nanka itsumo to chigau kimi to futari
Somehow, somehow I'm different from usual when I'm with you
dojina kaiwa masaka ryouomoi
Do we converse awkwardly? mutual love?
iya kataomoi yabai shisen acchatta
Nope, it's an unrequited love, whoops, we made eye contact
nani ga niko hottoki doki sha ba da ba de bee doo wa ba dee ay
Something's making my heart beat faster sha ba da ba de bee doo wa ba dee ay
shikoukai wa gucha gucha konran shaaba deebee doobee, yeah!
My train of thought derails with a *splat* *splat* shaaba deebee doobee, yeah!
konna... koto... hajimete da yo
This... is the... very first time for me
netsu demo aru no kana?
Do I have a fever, I wonder?
kimi sasotterasha na koigokoro hajimankan datte de nakatta
The awakening of love that you induced it was without pride
ba-ba-baka no te ga furueru zo kore kazuku ni yuku yaranai
T-T-These stupid hands are shaking and from here, we'll proceed
ya-ya-ya chotto kaiwa kamimakuri kimadzui chinmoku no ninmu na no
No no no, I've messed up my words a bit and so there's an awkward silence
kimi no kimi no kimochi shiritai yo ka-kata-ka-kataomoi
About your about your feelings I really want to know, it's an u-u-un-unrequited love
hatsukoi itsumo no tsuugakuro
First love always in the school zone
pikapika hikaru I will fall in love
A glittering light I will fall in love
sora mo tobesou sa
I'm flying through the sky
ka-ka-ka-ka-kataomoi!
U-U-U-U-Unrequited love!
Why is the Earth round?
Why do rockets fly?
Why do magnets pull against each other?
Everything in this world can be proven by science.
Grave
There are things that may be eliminated...
Spiritual phenomena such as a world after death, ghosts and ghost stories.
There's no way those kinds of sleep-inducing things could be real!
Grave
Because... they can't be.
Mt. Osore
In other words...
I don't believe in spiritualists!
Nichijou 19
Using my day off, I spent 8 hours going one-way to Mt. Osore.
Getting closer to the summit, the beating of my heart increases.
I wonder if a spiritualist really exists here.
If so, where?
I wonder if she would live alone here.
Or...
There she is!
Spiritualist
A-All right!
Let's have her summon something already.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Um... Please summon some soap!
Ah, OK.
Bubble, it's Soap!
What's this sensation of helplessness?
Could it be there's someone called Soap...?
I-It's S-S-Soap.
No, there can't be.
What... if I keep asking, then eventually a contradiction point will appear.
I have a question.
What's the blood type of Soap?
Who knows?
Let's try a simpler person.
Excuse me.
Nobunaga... please summon Oda Nobunaga!
Please give me a break.
Rejecting me before even trying to summon him?
No, she's old after all.
She has to look after her health.
I shouldn't scold her here.
Excuse me.
Let's go home.
Scolding people is not for me.
Just by knowing that, I should reap what I've sown.
Oh, Onii-san?
That'll be 5000 yen.
Daruma Otoshi
100 Points
Nichijou 20
2nd Period
Self Study
Ok here goes.
Rock Paper Scissors.
W-W-Whoa!
That's not how you do it Mai-chan, didn't I just explain it?
You have to hit me if you win!
It's amazing, you've got incredible concentration. In a way, it's even more cruel than hitting me.
Listen. As I've just explained, when you lose you defend, when you win you hit, OK?
Not now! Why did you hit me now!
No, it's because I won just then.
It wasn't now was it, it was just then!
It's the moment! Live for the moment! We're that kind of living thing you know!
OK then, let's do it again.
Rock paper scissors.
You have zero motivation to play!?
You are a clown!
How much of a clown can you be?!
In my mind... something is coming.
Ah, hold on Mai-chan.
There it is.
Mai-chan, w-what's with that?
I carved it.
Thank god! I thought it had been reincarnated!
I will put this here.
Somehow, she looks really happy.
Ah well that doesn't matter, let's start.
OK, rock paper scissors.
Ma-Mai-chan. That's...
...rockscispaper...!
No way, such a brutal...
Seriously, Mai-chan, that doesn't count, that doesn't count. Rockscispaper doesn't count.
Also, hitting with the Buddha doesn't count either.
OK, let's do it again.
First comes rock-
Rock paper scissors.
Mai-chan...
That, that! That's it Mai-chan.
See, you can do it if you try!
Ok, let's do the next one.
First comes rock-
God is dead!
God has died.
Hey, why did you hit me?! You did it properly just now!
How do I say it, because I don't want to play.
Can I take a look at your Maitreya?
Sure.
Shinonome Institute
Then, I'll be going to the library to return the books!
Make sure you look after the house, OK?
Yes!
Nichijou 21
You can't have too much
ice cream and juice!
I wonder why Nano's daruma only has one eye...
That's it! If I give it another eye I might get praised!
She might say 'it's OK to eat as many snacks as you like'!
I might've made a mistake...
It's Nano's, so what do I do...
Oh! She might get mad at me!
You won't get any snacks for a long time!
Um... here... and here...
What are you doing?
S-Sakamoto, what should I do? This...
What's this? What were you doing!?
This is hers, right?
You see, it didn't have an eye...
It can't be helped, try doing what I say.
I'm home!
Stay in good health.
Ah, Sakamoto!
Ah, Sakamoto-san, you're going out?
Professor, I'm home.
I'm late because it took me some time to choose some new books to borrow.
What are you doing?
Eh, what's with that stomach of yours?
It's not 'ehehe'!
I-It'll be born!
No no no, that's not possible.
It'll be born! It'll be born! It'll be born!
Um, is this some kind of game?
No it's not! Your little brother is about to be born!
It's your little brother.
T-This isn't good.
Kokkuri-san
Mio-chan, Mio-chan!
What is it?
Let's play Kokkuri-san!
Hm? What's that?
Oh, you don't know it?
I don't.
OK, I'll briefly explain it then.
First you need to prepare a piece of paper by drawing a gate in the middle like this,
then you write 'yes', 'no' and the 50 Japanese syllabary on the page.
Mmm.
Although in some regions, you're supposed to draw a fried tofu on the paper instead...
For now, let's just keep it simple.
Mmm.
Then, for Kokkuri-san to be able to come in, you open the north-facing window.
Then you set this 10-yen coin on the gate.
We put both of our fingers on it and ask a question that you want to know about,
such as a person's secret, or who someone likes, or something that's bothering you.
Mmm.
If you do that, all by itself, the 10-yen coin will move and Kokkuri-san will answer your question.
Isn't it amazing?
There are some taboos though...
First, don't do it by yourself... second, don't mess around when doing it...
or else you will be haunted by spirits...
Also, if you stop halfway through, you will be haunted, so be wary.
I see.
It's something like that.
It's a pretty dangerous game, don't you think?
Anyway, why don't you give it a try?
It's OK.
Whaaaaaat?
Nichijou 22
Um... well that's all for today.
Tomorrow we have a mini-test, so everyone please study for it.
Eh? Postpone it, postpone it!
Wouldn't the outcome be exactly the same for you no matter how long it's postponed?
Mini-test
English
Probably.
Sakurai-sensei.
What is it, Aioi-san?
There's something I want to ask you.
Yes?
Um... about the test we had before.
What is this?
Um... That's a fly.
No, not the answer. I'm talking about this thing that looks like it'd vanish pretty easily... did you draw it, Sensei?
Yes. I thought that if I included some pictures, the test might be a little easier...
You draw very interesting pictures, Sensei.
I'm sorry. I'm bad at drawing pictures, so it was hard to understand wasn't it?
Ah! That's right.
Could you include a picture that I've drawn next time?
I'll draw something really cool!
OK.
Ah, Mio-chan!
Listen, listen. My picture's going to be in the test.
Eh? Why?
Sensei said she'll put them in.
If you draw something right now, she'll definitely put yours in, maybe.
It's 'definitely', but it's still 'maybe'?
Uh... you're not going to draw something?
No, I'm fine. I'll pass on that.
Besides, I have to return this.
Oh, really?
All right! One cool guy-
Something like this?
Uwah! He's so cool!
Aioi-san, you're so good at drawing. You have my respect.
No, I'm not that good... I'm awesome at it!
Just kidding.
Incidentally, his name is Samidare George.
That's even cooler.
Cool?!
Hold on a second you two.
Normally, what you'd call cool is...
Piss off!
something like this, right?
Uwah! Amazing! It's just like a manga.
Naganohara-san, do you draw manga or something?
No, well, only a little.
Amazing! Please show me next time.
That is, well...
Eh? You can't?
I want to see it. Please show it to me.
Eh... ah... but...
Give that back to me!
Mine are much cooler.
You just ripped off mine!
I didn't rip it off.
Yes, you did.
This kind of rip-off is known as homage.
You just admitted it!
Uwah! So cool!
Anything works for you?!
Well, how about this?
Glasses!
An intelligent and cool look that appeals to all women of any era!
Glasses, huh?
Is his eyesight bad?
He should just wear contacts.
These two just don't get it!!
Then I'll do... this!
They're underneath his ears!
Anyhow, this is a rip-off too!
Tsk, tsk, tsk... they're sunglasses.
Uwah! So cool.
You're OK with it?!
Then... how about this? A butler!
From picking you up to serving you tea... you'll feel like a real lady.
Feel the magic of Darjeeling!
Glasses again? I'm sorry, I don't really get it.
She didn't listen to my advice about contacts...
Mio-chan, you don't get it, do you?
You see, what's really cool is...
...this!
It's floating!
No, hold on... this... it's running?!
Uwah! It looks so fast and cool!
I can't believe this!!!
What cool is...
Normally...
If you think about it in a normal way...
What cool is...
this, right?
Oh no...
Just kidding!
In front of the
1-Q lectern
Naganohara Mio:
Sunk
Word Of The Day
I drew this while I was listening to jazz music.
The Next Day
Morning!
Ah! Sensei, good morning!
Who are you calling Sensei?!
Well then, I'll hand out this morning's mini-test, so please pass them around.
I'm done for...
I wanted to keep secret the fact that I draw.
I can't believe I drew a picture like that...
English
Anyway, even though I lost control, only going to that level was a blessing amongst all the misfortune.
It was pretty close.
Yukko's going to tease me for two or three days though...
No, no! I have to keep my chin up and move forward.
Mio-sensei, hurry up.
Um... begin!
Mio-sensei!
asa okite, ha wo migaite, attoyuuma, go-gojyuu ji
Wake up in the morning, brush my teeth and in the blink of an eye, it's 10pm.
kyou mo takusan, waratta na, takusan tokimeita na
Today also, we laughed a whole lot; we had a great time.
tomodachi to, baka mitai ni, sawaideru toki ni mo
With my friends, I played the fool, and we all played around.
chi ga chiratte, negau, guuzen da yo ne
And when the blood began to run, we wished it was a coincidence.
hatsukoro nante ienai, kyara ja nain da mon
I can't talk about the first time, it wouldn't be in-character.
ne, ashita mo aeru yo ne
Hey, we can meet again tomorrow, right?
mabuta wo tojiru to kirakira kimi datte
As my eyelids close, I see you glittering.
kyou mo tanoshikatta ne, atashittara ne
Today was fun too, wasn't it? Silly me.
DREAMS COME TRUE
ureshii na, ureshii na, hajimemashite koigokoro
So happy, so happy, how do you do? It's an unrequited love.
ashita mata aeru na, oyasuminasai
We'll meet again tomorrow, goodnight!
yume ga sugu aeru na, oyasuminasai
I'll soon be dreaming, goodnight!
Pleased to meet you, I'm onomatopoeia!
You can't help but say 'Cock-a-doodle-do' in Japanese even though it's not Japanese.
Narration          Koyama Rikiya
The next Nichijou is the sixth. Look forward to it.