Excuse me.
Agnes Chevalier de Milan at your service.
Have you completed your research?
Yes.
Here is the report.
This is a prime example of how it's dark at the base of a lighthouse.
Will you arrest and prosecute him immediately?
No.
The testimony of the Musketeer Force's former vice-captain is not enough to incriminate the Chair President of Legal Affairs.
Let us proceed with the plan.
But would that not endanger you?
Don't worry.
I have a reliable bodyguard.
Thank you very much, Your Highness.
Not only have you given rank and a title to a plebeian like myself,
you even gave me a chance to take revenge upon my foe.
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君のそばにいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai ga bokura wo tameshitatte
どんな未来が僕らを試したって
No matter how the future tests us
kitto…
きっと…
I’m sure…
aa futari no unmei
ああ 二人の運命
Ah, it’s our destiny
meguriaeta no wa
巡り合えたのは
I was able to meet you
kimi no koe kikoeta kara
君の声 聞こえたから
Because I heard your voice
sou pinchi na dekigoto
そう ピンチな出来事
Yeah, even if crisis events
oshiyosete kite mo
押し寄せてきても
Press on at me
kimi to ireba norikoerareru
君といれば乗り越えられる
If I'm with you, then I can overcome them
tokimeki to makenki to
ときめきと負けん気と
Palpitations and competitive spirit
urahara de haraharasuru kedo
裏腹でハラハラするけど
Excite me on the contrary, but-
Stay with me
tada kimi o mamoritai yo
ただ 君を守りたいよ
I only want to protect you
tooi sekai de umareta futari da kedo
遠い世界で生まれた二人だけど
We were born in distant worlds
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君の側にいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai mo kibou ni kaeyou
どんな未来も希望に変えよう
Let’s change any future into hope
Forever
The Queen's Holiday
We're here again.
I don't really get along with that owner.
What are you saying?
We came because Agnes told us to stand by at the shop.
It must be an important mission from Her Highness.
Come on, let's go.
Ow ow!
I said that hurts!
Yes! Yes!
You all look wonderful, my dear fairies!
U-Um...
H-Hello...
I-It has been a while, Master Scarron.
No, that's wrong.
Everyone, together!
One, two!
Ma mademoiselle!
Tres bien!
Hey, what brings you two here all of a sudden?
We're waiting for someone.
And what's with your costume?
Oh, this?
Tonight, we're going to be in the Taniariji Royal Theatre.
My beauty has finally been accepted by the world!
"Vacances en Tristania"?
Oh yeah!
Why don't you two join in?
We're a little short on staff, too.
Okay, okay, my dear fairies, time to open the shop.
Get ready.
Yes, ma mademoiselle.
Um-
Hey, why are you two spacing out over there?
You'll help out, right?
We have an important mission.
Stop blabbing.
Saito, you go to the kitchen.
Louise, you go change with the girls.
Off you go, get moving.
Yes!
H-Hey.
Stay still already!
Oh well...
I guess I look more natural in this than in my uniform.
She's so cute!
Number one is definitely Jessica!
Number two's Marlene,
and number three's Jane.
Last place is definitely Louise.
What kind of ranking was that just now?
What? It's breast-
You pervert dog!
You mere dog!
Act like a dog and bark!
Hey, Louise-chan, you got a nomination.
Come on out already.
Yes.
Hurry up.
Sorry to make you wait.
You!
Hi, Louise.
J-Julio?
You look cute in that outfit, too.
H-Hey.
Don't get so close to me.
I was told by Agnes to stand by at this shop, too.
Damn it...
What the heck is he talking about?
Cheers!
Hey, how many times do we have to toast before you're satisfied?
It's fun no matter how many times you do it.
Cheers!
This really is a great shop.
There we go.
Did he come all the way here just to meddle with Louise?
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
Um, is there a shop called "Charming Fairy Inn" around here?
Eh? That'd be here.
That voice!
Search that side!
She might have gone to the Kurdone alley.
Make haste!
This way, Your Highness.
I don't know what happened, but let me go get Louise.
Please wait, Saito-san.
I'm here to borrow your strength.
M-Mine?
Please be my bodyguard for several hours.
Why me?
You're the Queen, so shouldn't you have
bodyguards who are more suitable than myself.
I must act while undercover.
So this was why you told us to be here on standby?
Okay. Since it's a request from none other than the Queen, I'll accept it.
It isn't anything dangerous, is it?
If I were to put you in danger, who knows what Louise would do to me later...
D-Don't worry about that.
Well, okay.
Well then, let's make our way out.
The security guards will be here soon.
We can't stay here for too long.
Saito-san, could you lend me some clothes that would make me look like a plebeian?
Y-Yes...
Louise's skirt is about the only thing we have here.
That'll do.
Thank you very much.
Can I have those clothes?
H-Here.
Can she even fit into Louise's clothes?
The shirt's a little small.
I knew it.
Cheers!
Where's Agnes?
My dear fairies!
The show's tonight, so let's close the shop early.
Yes!
What? It's closing already?
Let's toast some more!
We're closing.
What, she never showed up.
Saito!
Saito?
Identify yourselves and indicate your destination.
Take off your hood and show us your face.
Looks like they formed a security line.
A search order has been issued to
the soldiers for a missing aristocrat.
So, in other words, they're looking for you?
What should we do?
They'll suspect us even more if we were to hide our faces.
Saito-san, please put your arm around my shoulder.
You can go now.
Um... I think we're really standing out.
Keep playing with me.
But-
I'm in heaven.
Search the other street!
Yeah!
Tell Lishman-dono that Agnes of Her
Highness' Musketeer Force has arrived.
It's urgent news.
Please send me through.
Urgent news, you say?
It must be an absolute emergency for the captain to come all the way to the Chair President of Legal Affair's house.
Her Highness has disappeared.
What?
Was she kidnapped?
We're investigating.
We just had a similar kidnapping case the other day.
Was your unit made to display incompetence?
We are searching for her in order to not present ourselves as such.
We would like your permission to block off major roads and ports.
Search for Her Highness with everything you've got.
If you can't find her, by the name of Legal Affairs, I'll have you all.
Yes, Sir!
Sir?
What?
I'm researching the case regarding the Protestants.
I heard that you were involved in that case twenty years ago.
You were the one who proposed the Massacre of Dungletale.
Massacre?
Don't make me the villain here.
The people in the village were planning to overturn the country.
It was a justified mission of suppression.
Suppression. I see.
I'm searching for records of that instance, but I can't find them.
You would know who the captain of that mission was, wouldn't you?
I don't remember such a thing.
Rather than what happened twenty years ago,
shouldn't you be prioritising the search for Her Highness?
Sorry to bother you.
Where did Saito go?
Is this room really acceptable for you?
Yes.
But really, what horrible rain...
Maybe it'll rain all night long at this rate...
Your Highness?
What's wrong?
I'm cold.
Would you... hold my shoulders?
She feels like ice...
Open up! We're from the castle!
Your Highness!
It's an emergency! We'll force it open if we must!
We have no choice!
Your Highness...
Open up!
Damn it, let's go.
Agnes?
It is you!
What are you doing here?
There are so many soldiers out in the street, too.
What's going on?
I don't have time to explain right now.
Come with me.
Hey!
Let's go!
Hey, what's going on?
Give me an explanation!
Be quiet.
Master is waiting at the usual theatre.
Looks like the Queen has been kidnapped by someone.
What?!
What was that for?!
It's part of the mission!
What mission?
Princess... what are we doing this for?
In order to lure out the traitor, we issued a
false emergency stating that I went missing.
However, they're unlikely to fall for misinformation so easily.
So I seriously ran as hard as I could.
As hard as you could? But what if something were to happen to you?
That's why I asked you to be my bodyguard.
I wanted you to protect me...
...like you would Louise.
So I was fooled by you as well?
I'm sorry.
Isn't there a saying about deceiving the ally before you deceive the enemy?
I get it now.
It's time. Let us go again.
Huh, where?
To the theatre.
Saito's with Her Highness?
Yes. We needed Saito to be Her Highness' bodyguard.
What? Was I just an extra, then?
Well, that's...
Anyway, until everything is done, be on standby at that shop.
Wait, where are you going?
The theatre.
Bye.
Hey!
Agnes...
Hey, Louise-chan.
What are you doing? The show's going to start.
Ladies and gentlemen.
This is a tear-jerking play performed by the Scarron family.
Make a move, everyone!
Saito!
Louise!
Weren't you with Her Highness?
Yeah, until a while ago.
She's with Agnes right now.
Agnes?
God, what are you two doing?!
All right,
it's show time!
Hey, what is this?
This is called the Liar's Mouth.
When a liar puts their hand inside, they won't be able to remove it.
Oh, no! What should I do?
Why don't you try and put your hand inside?
No! No! It's too scary!
I'm a dog even in the play...
So Her Highness has yet to be found?
Yes, she's still missing.
So, now's our chance.
Who knows where she is right now?
I am right here.
I overheard everything.
Lishman-dono!
Your Highness!
I figured that you'd hurry and make
contact with the spy if I went missing.
The more you rush, the less careful you become.
Even a cautious rat will show its tail.
I see. So your going missing was a trick to lure me out.
Exactly.
Lishman, Chair President of Legal Affairs,
You are under arrest for treason.
Your Highness!
The curtain has dropped, Lishman-dono.
Are you sure about that?
You're still naive, Henrietta.
Protect Her Highness!
Yes, Sir!
Kill Henrietta!
You must be from Albion.
You're under arrest for spying.
Your Highness!
Prepare to die!
Are you safe?
Saito-san!
Your Highness!
Out of the way!
Louise!
Stop, Lishman!
Farewell, Henrietta.
The theatre is under my jurisdiction.
I have my ways around.
Halt.
Where do you think you're going, Lishman?
Ah, it's you.
I won't be caught by an ex-plebeian.
I have no intention of catching you.
I'll be killing you.
What?
Dungletale...
My home vanished without being guilty of any crime.
I see. So you're a survivor from that village.
Now is the time I take my revenge.
I can kill you in an instant.
Listen. The record from Dungletale you're
looking for is kept underneath the Magic Academy.
Got you!
That was easy.
What?
I-Impossible.
Taste the fang we plebeians sharpened to use against you aristocrats.
Die from the bite of the fang.
Lishman!
Hurry!
So, what were you doing with Her Highness?
Hey, what are you doing?
I smell Her Highness' perfume.
You can't be her bodyguard unless you're so
close to her that her perfume sticks onto you.
You didn't do something to Her Highness by any chance, did you?
I-I wouldn't do anything...
Speaking of that, what were you doing?
N-Nothing.
What? Did something happen?
Nothing, of course!
Y-You dare doubt your master, dog?
Unforgivable!
Hey! Wait! That's not fair!
You dog!
You better tell the truth!
You pervert dog!
Stupid dog!
I'm sorry!
Y-You stupid dog!
chanto koko ni ite watashi no chikaku de
ちゃんとココにいて! 私の近くで
Be right here! close to me
zutto watashi o itsumo itsumo mitsumete nasai
ずっと私をいつもいつも見つめてなさい
Always, always look at me at all times
yosomishiteta desho hoka no onna no ko
よそ見してたでしょっ 他の女の子
You looked away, didn’t you? At other girls
o-shiokisuru wa furari furari furachi na yatsu wa
お仕置きするわ　フラリフラリ不埒なヤツは
I’ll punish those who are wavering and insolent
Don't touch! kikanai kara ne iiwake wa
Don't touch! 聞かないからね　言い訳は
Don’t touch! Because I won’t listen to excuses
Touch me... tsukareta kara nee kata o kashite yo
Touch me… 疲れたから… ねぇ肩を貸してよ
Touch me… because I'm tired… Hey, lend me your shoulder
suki yo nante uso yo
スキよ　なんて嘘よ
I love you, it’s a lie
kirai sore mo uso da wa
キライ　それも嘘だわ
I hate you, that’s a lie, too
nai nai nai dame yo kanchigai
ないないない　ダメよ勘違い
Nay nay nay, it’s useless, it’s a misunderstanding
dakara suki yo nante iwanai
だから「スキよ」なんて言わない
So I won’t say, “I love you”
Non non non dokka e ittara
Non non non　どっかへ行ったら
Non non non, because I absolutely won’t forgive you
zettai ni yurusanai kara ne
絶対に　許さないからね!
If you go to somewhere else
datte
だって
But
honto wa dare yori soba ni itai no
ホントは誰より傍にいたいの
The truth is, I want to be by your side more than anyone else
ai no kusari de sanposhimasho
愛の鎖で　散歩しましょ!
Let’s go take a walk in chains of love!
I... to be honest...
...might love you...
Next Time
You dog!
What are you doing with the maid in the school's basement?
What? Sailor uniform?
Zero no Tsukaima. Futatsuki no Kishi.
The Underground Secret Document.
If you want to meet me again next week, then sit tightly and wait!
The Underground Secret Document