Nichijou 87
It's finally lunch!
I guess odd things happen from time to time.
It must be a miracle!
I wasn't punished for forgetting the homework for Takasaki's class.
It must be my lucky day!
You should still do it.
Anyway, Mio-chan, how about you buy me juice to celebrate this miracle?
Aioi,
I need to speak to you about today's homework.
Come to the faculty lounge.
Okay.
I'll treat her from time to time.
jou jou yuu jou banjin maji kaichou
じょーじょーゆーじょー万事マジ快調
Amazing friendship, the absolute best!
na na na na na na na
ななななななな
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
hai! icchaimashou!
ハイ!言っちゃいましょう!
All right! I'll say it!
kimi wa best best friend
キミはベストベスト フレンド
You are my best, best friend!
(furai!) chotto fuzakete mitara
(フライ!) ちょっとふざけてみたら
(Fly!) When I joke around a bit,
(shain!) motto fuzake kaeshite kuru
(シャイン!) もっとふざけ帰してくる
(Shine!) You joke around more in response.
(La La La) ikogochi ii ttara arya shinai
(ラーラーラー)居心地良いったらありゃしない
(La La La) Nothing is better than this!
(wai!) iya na koto attatte
(ワイ!) 嫌なことあったって
(Why!) Even if something bad happens,
(fain!) sokkou wasurechaunda
(ファイン!) 即効忘れちゃうんだー
(Fine!) I immediately forget about it!
(La La La)
(ラーラーラー)
itsudatte jan jan yarimasho
いつだって、じゃんじゃんやりましょ♪
Always keep it going!
24 jikan issho demo mondai nai
２４時間一緒でも問題ない
Being together 24 hours a day isn't a problem.
marude futago ka oyako ka clone saibou
まるで双子か親子かクローン細胞
Just like twins, or a parent and child, or clone cyborgs.
kore ja me ga sumu hitsuyou wa nakunakunai!?
これじゃ目が澄む必要はなくなくない!？
Then isn't there no reason to clear your eyes?
sore to kore to wa mattaku mattaku betsumondai
それとこれとは まったくまったく 別問題
Those are completely, completely different issues.
(faito!) kenka shichatta toki mo
(ファイト!)喧嘩しちゃった時も
(Fight!) Even when I get in a fight with you,
(daoun!) kanari hekonda toki mo
(ダウン!)かなり凹んだ時も
(Down!) even when I get really down,
(shai!) hitori de itai you na toki mo
(シャイ!)一人で居たいような時も
(Shy!) even when I feel like I want to be alone,
futokizukeba chikaku ni iru shinaba morotomo
ふと気付けば 近くに居る 死なば諸共
before I realise it, you're right there; we'll be together even in death!
nande daro
なんでだろ
I wonder why it is.
soba ni itainda
そばに居たいんだ
I want to be with you.
kimi to issho nara
君と一緒なら
When I'm with you,
tokei hyakubai soku
時計百倍速
time goes 100 times faster!
tanoshii na
楽しいな
It's fun, isn't it?
tanoshisugirunda
楽しすぎるんだ
It's way too fun!
sasuga saikou friend
流石 最高 friend
As expected of my best friend!
Hey! na na na na na na na
Hey! ななななななな
Hey! Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
nannanoyo
なんなのよー
What is it?
yabai synchro
ヤバいシンクロー
The synchro is amazing!
itsumo oosawagi
いつも大騒ぎ
Always making an uproar,
kanari gokinjo meiwaku
かなりご近所迷惑
bothering the neighbours a lot.
ima nanji
今何時
What time is it now?
ato ne yorereihifu
あとねヨレレイヒーフ
And then yo de le hi hoo!
wake wakannainai
訳分かんないない!
I don't get it at all!
soredoshira
ソレドシラ
So re doh si la!
souzou ijou nante iu ka saiko
想像以上なんて言うか最高
It's better than I imagined, the absolute best!
aa da kou da ittetemo tomodachi (wasshoi!)
あーだこーだ言ってても友達 (わっしょい!)
Even if I say this and that, we're still friends. (Hooray!)
jou jou yuu jou banjin maji kaichou
じょーじょーゆーじょー万事マジ快調
Amazing friendship, the absolute best!
cha cha la cha la cha cha
ちゃちゃらちゃらちゃちゃー
Cha Cha La Cha La Cha Cha!
I guess Nee-chan has friends over again.
Nichijou 88
Hey...
Are you getting anywhere?
With what?
What do you mean, "with what"?
Geez.
I mean your relationship with Sasahara!
Why do I have to get married to him?!
I never said that.
What do you mean, "two children"?!
Wah, I get it!
I admire your plan for adulthood!
Adult...
How about you, Websey?
Huh, me?
I'll pass.
Come on! Tell me!
There's someone you like, isn't there?
Come on!
Tell me!
Fecchan, stop that!
Okay, I give up!
I Christian Chivu up!
I won't stop until you tell me!
Okay, I'll tell you!
If you don't tell me, I'll tickle you to death!
I said I'd tell you!
I'm sorry.
It kinda got addicting.
Well?
Who is it?
Who is it that you like, Websey?
It's more like someone that I'm interested in, however,
I don't know his name.
He has a mohawk.
Oh.
Him, huh?
Oh, you two know about him?
Of course we know about him.
He's a bit of a celebrity at our school...
...with his hairstyle and all.
Websey, why do you like him?
Well, the reason really is:
He looks like a punk.
Isn't someone who's a bit bad more attractive than an honour student?
But he's completely bad.
He has a mohawk, after all.
But I recently saw that punk speaking politely.
No way!
There's no way that's true, right?
With that mohawk!
But that punk...
He was watering the flower bed.
Wow, that's unexpected.
Oh, and also,
he was sticking some kind of bottle in.
Whoa, I like that gap.
His head is like a cut pineapple.
He's a nice guy that drips pineapple juice.
That kind of niceness is worth a lot of points.
I'd like a nice guy, too.
What about you, Fecchan?
Is there someone you like?
Who, me?
Well, I...
Sasahara...
Koujirou.
I saw Sasahara feeding his goat on a rainy day.
I get it!
That kind of niceness!
Huh?
I don't think it's particularly nice!
So how about you, Fecchan?
Huh, what?
Is there anyone you like?
Well, there's no one I'm interested in right now,
but I'm not interested in weirdos like you two are.
Start!
One point!
Love-Like
Ouch!
Hold on.
Here.
Oh, thanks!
Huh?
Give me your hand.
I finally have a day off,
but I passed it eating, sleeping and raising vegetables,
just like every other day.
Well, my days are peaceful.
I guess that's nice in its own way.
I wonder if something interesting will happen...
Hello.
Nichijou 89
Casual?
Sakurai-sensei...
Takasaki-sensei, are you out shopping, too?
It's tied up!
Also, running into each other on a day off...
It feels like I'm seeing something very private...
I feel extremely moved!
Oh, I'm sorry!
Are you hurt?
Oh, sorry!
I just felt moved.
Sakurai-sensei, are you out shopping, too?
Oh, yes.
Green onions were on sale, so I bought a lot!
Green onions, huh?
If you wanted bamboo shoots, you could have told me,
and I would have given you some.
Bamboo shoots?
Well, I have a bit of a garden at my home.
Well, what can I say...
I see!
That's amazing!
Meeting on a day off...
It feels like it's fate.
Like we're bound by fate.
Is this coincidence causing this feeling?
To be honest, I'm surprised myself.
This is the first time I've felt this way.
I wish I were a green onion.
Are you okay?
You look like you're in pain!
Would you like to go rest somewhere?
I'm sorry!
I'm completely fine!
I wasn't thinking about anythin-
Would you like to go rest somewhere?
Thinking...
That's amazingly enough...
Now! Sakurai-sensei, there's a park over that way!
Let's head that way!
Oh, yes!
Big Sale
Well...
I would never have thought this would happen.
Isn't this what you would call...
...a date?!
Aioi!
Sakurai-sensei, let's go to that empty lot, instead.
Why is Aioi here?
If she were to find out...
Oh, what are you two doing?
You idiot!
This is sort of... well... um... that!
Good day!
Geez, I didn't know that you two were dating.
You idiot!
Don't tease teachers!
But you guys seem so happy!
You...
The Next Day
Sakurai-sensei, good morning.
Sakurai-sensei
Takasaki-sensei
Way to go, you two!
Hot stuff!
You idiots!
Don't laugh at it!
Geez, those brats.
I'm, well...
I'm sorry about all this trouble.
Oh, it's fine.
I'm actually kind of happy.
Good enough!
What's wrong with me?!
There's no way it would end so nicely!
Anyway, I need to...
Wow, that surprised me.
Oh, shoot!
What are you doing, Takasaki-sensei?
Oh, what a coincidence! It's Sakurai-sensei!
And Aioi!
It's Aioi, right?!
I must not have been paying attention.
I didn't see you!
Aioi?
It's you, right, Aioi?
You sure look like Aioi.
Well, anyway,
I have to do that, so I'll be leaving.
I guess...
...I'll buy onions and go home.
Sorry for calling you out so unexpectedly.
Ah, this is
also youth
Were you able to sleep yesterday?
Yeah, but I had a weird dream.
A weird dream?
Well, I dreamt that we kissed right here.
Shall I make that dream come true?
Professor, would you like some snacks?
Do you actually love me?
The result of a month's research.
I have learned that every Saturday...
...she goes to the supermarket in this shopping district.
It's almost time for her to come out.
Nichijou 90
I will trail her when she comes out after shopping.
When we reach an area without anyone around,
I'll use this Mr. Short Circuit,
which I didn't get the chance to test before,
and then I'll take her home.
It's perfect.
I will definitely study you today,
Shinonome Nano.
Hours
Later
Huh?
Why isn't Shinonome coming?
Do you not always go to this supermarket?
No, I've waited this long!
If I leave now, there's a chance I'll miss her.
Huh?
Oh, it really is you, Nakamura-sensei.
Good day.
It's Sideburns, who teaches language!
Hello.
You weren't in your lab coat, so I didn't realise it was you at first.
Sideburns has come at a bad time.
If he doesn't need anything, I hope he'll just leave.
If Shinonome were to come at this time...
Well, Nakamura-sensei, your casual clothes are a bit boyish.
It's kind of cute.
Oh, not really...
No, it's such a difference from your regular lab coat.
It makes you look innocent...
...or cute.
I'll retreat for today!
Huh?
Nakamura-sensei?!
Have you thought about what you'd like to do...
...with your future, Minakami-san?
I have.
Would you like to get a job?
Would you like to go to school?
I understand.
Nichijou 91
The Wood Cube isn't here...
But how did it disappear from the safe?
Well, there's a reward for finding it.
So I'm fine with it.
The Advisor found one of them earlier.
There's only one left to find?
I need to get serious.
If I show my worth here, I could gain favour with the throne.
Hey, look over there.
Give back the Wood Cube.
Hey, hey.
What are you saying, young lady?
How did you get in?
Are you a stowaway?
If you are, there's a severe punishment.
It's either a minimum of 10 years in prison...
...or having a drink with me.
Just kidding-
Number 22!
Why, you! What are you doing?!
Wait!
Wait, wait, wait!
I'm all right.
I just let my guard down a bit.
Leave this to me.
You've got a pretty face, but you act a bit rough, little girl.
Hey,
playtime is over, all ri-
Is he okay?!
No, he's dead!
That bastard!
A stowaway is after the Wood Cubes?!
Move around to the rear!
Surround her!
[Hat: Advisor]
Everyone, please be quiet.
There's no need to get so excited.
Advisor!
Fay Kingdom's
Advisor to the Throne
Also known as: Persistent Negotiator
Leave this to me.
The Advisor should be able to do something in this situation.
She came aboard all alone to get the Wood Cubes.
She must be a spy from somewhere.
But that amazing strength...
If I could tame it, it would become a powerful weapon for our country.
Luckily, I also have a Wood Cube.
If this is what she wants,
I might be able to get her to change sides if I make a good offer.
This is the Wood Cube that you're after.
How about it? Why not...
...make a deal with me?
Advisor!
No!
He's dead!
This is bad!
That bastard killed the Advisor!
You bastard!
Don't think you'll get out of this alive!
Netherworld
Encyclopaedia
This is bad!
Netherworld
Encyclopaedia
This is bad!
Netherworld
Encyclopaedia
This is extremely bad!
Fay Kingdom's
Number 71
Also known as: Scholar
What's wrong, Scholar?!
What's bad?
It's very bad!
Just now, she attached a Wood Cube.
What's more, she already has another one attached by her ear.
That's another Wood Cube!
She has gathered the Wood Cubes!
But even if she's gathered them,
if she doesn't know how to summon the ancient weapon...
That's right!
We still have a chance!
Shut up!
According to this Netherworld Encyclopaedia,
a person who obtains the Wood Cubes...
...holds the power of the ancient weapon within them.
In other words,
a person who obtains the Wood Cubes...
...holds the power of the ancient weapon within them.
What was that?!
Could you explain it again?
Yeah, explain it once more!
In other words-
I shouldn't need to say it!
It's foolish to approach her!
The world could be destroyed!
It's over!
Don't despair!
[Hat & Armband: Captain]
Nothing comes from despair.
Fay Kingdom's Captain
Also known as: Nothing in Particular
Not even a bit.
Captain!
Listen. If we fight head-on, even for a bit, we're finished.
We have no chance.
However!
Even for a bit, our opponent is all alone.
While we, on the other hand, have numbers.
Therefore!
We should all try to take back the Wood Cubes together.
I'll take the lead!
After me!
Captain!
No! Leave me! Go!
B-But!
You fool!
I don't recall raising you to be so soft!
It's over.
The Advisor was killed.
The Captain can't move.
We can't do anything more.
One...
One for all...
...and all...
...for one!
Captain!
I've been in this troop for 12 years now.
These 12 years of memories...
Ending like this...
To that monster...
In a place like this...
Like I'd let that happen!
It's over!
No! I don't want to die!
I'm gonna go wash my face.
Word Of The Day
So obvious!
Surprise Box    Don't Get Surprised
Oh, boy.
Well, I've got nothing better to do,
so I guess I'll play along with the kid.
Creating free time is a skill.
Nichijou 92
Your hair is messy.
It's kind of cute.
What the heck am I doing?!
Sunday Night
I went first.
I had a very nice bath.
The
True Form
of Santa
hana no iro
花の色
The colours of the flowers
kumo no kage
雲の影
The shadows of the clouds
natsukashii
懐かしい
They're so nostalgic
ano omoide
あの思い出
Those memories
sugishi hi no
過ぎし日の
They are left behind
mado ni nokoshite
窓に残して
A window to days gone by
sudachi yuku
巣立ち行く
It's time to leave the nest
kyou no wakare
今日の別れ
Today is goodbye
izasaraba, saraba sensei
いざさらば　さらば先生
Farewell, and so long, teacher
izasaraba, saraba tomo yo
いざさらば　さらば友よ
Farewell, and so long, my friend
utsukushii asu no hi no tame
美しい　明日の日のため
For the sake of a beautiful tomorrow
Sakurai-sensei
Takasaki-sensei
I'm an Ai-Ai-Gasa.
Why don't you try drawing me once in a while?
Write your name on the right,
and on the left... You don't have any name to write?
This is for you, O lonely one:
Narration:     Shimamoto Sumi
Next time on Nichijou: Episode 22.
Look forward to it!