I'm feeling strangely cold.
Saito-san, let's get closer.
Um...
You stupid maid!
Take your hand off him!
How nonchalant of you to keep pushing yourself closer one night after another.
Saito is my familiar!
I won't move.
I have been ordered by Henrietta-sama to be his maid.
What are you saying?!
What's the matter?!
Calm down.
We're all in the same room, so there's nothing we can do.
Let's all sleep together peacefully.
Yeah? Yeah?
Shut up!
I'm sorry.
How about a challenge?
A challenge?
See whom Saito-san chooses.
I think it's pointless.
He's completely devoted to me.
I think that's just a misunderstanding.
Like how birds think whatever they see first is their mother.
That's not true!
If you're so confident, then you will not
mind having a match over him, will you?
S-Sure...
Go for it!
I already know he'll choose me.
Then how about this?
During the Sleipnir Ball tomorrow,
if Saito-san manages to find Miss Vallière, I'll give up on him.
However!
W-What?
If he can't find you...
So you're not confident after all.
Of course I am!
Don't act high and mighty just because you have big breasts!
You cow boob!
That's a loser's cry.
I can't imagine what'll come next.
Oh, and what's Sleipnir?
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
mejirushi no nai michi mo heiki sa futari nara
メジルシのない道も平気さ　ふたりなら
Even on a road without signs, I'll be fine, if we're together
saki no mienai tabi mayoinagara mitsuketa yo
先の見えない旅　迷いながら見つけたよ
On a journey that I can't see ahead of, while I was lost, I found it
boku no iru basho kimi no tonari
僕の居る場所　君のとなり
That my place to be is next to you
kenkashite nando mo hanashita sono te
喧嘩して　何度も離したその手
When we quarrelled, I let go of your hand again and again
hikiyose dakitai ima
引き寄せ抱きたい　今
I want to pull close and hold it now
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
namida no ame ni utaretara
涙の雨に打たれたら
If I'm beaten down by the rain of tears
I wanna hold you sugu yobi na yo boku no namae
I wanna hold you　すぐ呼びなよ　僕の名前
I wanna hold you, call my name immediately
dakishime ni yuku wa
抱きしめに行くわ
I'll go embrace you
kanashimi mo tsuyogari mo kono te ni uketomeru
悲しみも強がりもこの手に　受け止める
I'll accept sadness and bluffing in my hands
The Sleipnir Ball
Sleipnir is a ball held at the beginning of the new semester.
It's happening tonight.
Why a ball for the new semester?
As a welcome, of course.
It's an opportunity for me to teach the newly
admitted ladies about adult social occasions.
Have you heard about the monster bird that's been appearing near the border recently?
Yeah, I heard about it.
I heard it's incredibly huge.
My brother who is a dragon knight was talking about it.
And it's no ordinary ball!
It's a costume ball party.
Using the Mirror of Truth, you use magic to garment yourself.
You can take the form you most wish to become.
I wonder how many people will look like me.
After all, I'm the world's most handsome guy.
What do you want to become, Saito?
Saito?
Hey.
Can you give me the details of that rumour?
Sure.
It happened some nights ago.
A dragon knight on a patrol looked up into the sky and saw...
It's said that it had to be at least 150 mail long.
Maybe it's the legendary giant dragon.
No, apparently its wing shape is completely different from that of a dragon.
But by the time a squad of dragon knights had taken off after receiving the report, there was no sign of it anywhere.
It's got to be a mistake.
You're not the only Void mage.
Maybe she's up to something again.
I've got to tell Louise to watch out.
Louise, are you here?
Miss Vallière has gone out.
What are you doing on the floor?
I... actually, recently read a book called "Maid Afternoon".
Maid Afternoon?
Yes. A story of a young maid working at an aristocrat's manor...
...and the lord forces indecent things on the maid at night.
I was thinking I wouldn't mind that
happening to me if it's Saito-san.
Huh?
Slowly...
Slip.
Crash!
Huh?
Oh my gosh! I broke my master's cup!
Your turn, Saito-san.
M-My turn? What do I do?
Huh?!
Slowly...
Slip.
Crash!
Oh my gosh! I broke my master's cup!
Master.
Punish me as you please.
Peek.
Put an end to this, you guys!
We... We will...
Maid! Familiar! Listen!
Y-Yes!
The Sleipnir Ball's today.
So I heard.
So you are to find me no matter what.
This is an order.
Huh?
If you do...
If I do?
I'll let you pick up where we left off last time.
Louise!
Pick up where we left off last time?
You don't mean...
Are you serious?!
Saito-san?
That's not fair, Miss Vallière.
You can't tempt him like that!
Dear students who have gathered here.
Allow me to take you to tonight's mirage.
So that's the Mirror of Truth.
I can't wait!
Enter one at a time.
Imagine your ideal appearance.
This mirror will look into the deep part of your heart and transform you into that.
Now, imagine!
Chii-neesama.
Saito...
Please find me.
Crap, I'm late.
Could that be the giant monster bird everyone's been talking about?
Since it appeared above the academy, is it after Louise?
I've got to tell Louise about this right away!
Everyone! Today's a costume ball party.
This is to make you understand that in this academy,
family, status, nationality or rank do not matter.
Otherwise, it would be impossible to study together.
Additionally, we have Queen Henrietta as our guest.
Furthermore, to promote the purpose of the ball,
she is in disguise as well.
Trying to identify the queen is an interesting game to play, too.
Make sure all of you work hard to become the ideal person you wish to be.
Enjoy the party.
That is all from me.
Now, now, the party has started.
Everyone, start changing.
Yes! I always wanted to be a dragon knight!
I always wanted to be the Princess.
I knew I would turn into a cute girl like this.
Hi, everyone.
Captain?
What happened to getting disguised?
What are you talking about?
I am disguised.
Huh?
When it comes to an ideal form with both beauty and talent,
there isn't any other than myself.
There has to be a limit...
...to how shameless one can be.
S-She's beautiful.
You, who have taken the form of such a beautiful lady.
May I ask for your name?
I'm Osmond.
Hey, if we all disguise as Tiffania, we can't tell who's who!
Why are you taking so much time, Saito?
Come find me already.
I'm sorry.
Saito?
Hold on a minute.
What's with those breasts?
That voice. Is that you, Louise-san?
I'm sorry. I got to become Saito-san, whom I aspire to be,
but for some reason, my breasts didn't change.
T-Tiffa?
Y-Yes...
Gosh, I can't tell who's who!
I'm right here, Saito!
Where is that Louise?
But, for a costume party,
no one's wearing a costume, let alone any masks.
Louise!
Hey, that was easy.
Are you sure it was all right to make that kind of promise?
Promise?
What? You forgot already?
No, um... Who might you be?
Huh? I'm me, of course.
You're...
...really Saito-san?
Ah... Anyway!
There's a giant monster bird outside.
Well, I'm here, so it should be all right.
So, um, you know.
If the promise bothers you so much...
I don't mind picking up where we left off.
Picking up? Picking up what?
You know!
Well... It was...
I mean...
Yes?
L-Louise?
Are you really afraid of a tiny spider like that?
Saito...
Come find me already.
Who are you?
Today, I will take the void mage as a gift for Joseph-sama.
Princess?!
What are you doing here?!
The magic wore off!
The party's not over yet, though.
We have a problem! The Mirror of Truth is broken!
Magic?
Yes. Today's a ball party where you disguise yourself using magic.
Disguise using magic?
Which means-
I-I'm terribly sorry!
I completely thought you were Louise!
Please don't worry.
I was also magically disguised as the person I feel is my ideal.
It is only natural you did not recognise me.
Ideal?
Louise is?
Yes.
I am jealous of her.
How pure her heart is.
How she can stand up for her own justice.
If I had even a fraction of her courage,
I would not have had to commit a mistake.
Mistake?! You haven't done anything wrong!
No. I have...
Princess?
Saito-san...
Louise.
Louise!
Wait! You got it wrong! Louise!
Louise...
Louise! Wait!
Why? I don't get it! I don't understand him!
Louise!
No, let go of me!
Listen to me!
I hate you, Saito.
You're a big, stupid traitor.
You were with the Princess of all people.
Has this been going on for long?
Have you been sneaking behind my back?
It's not like that. That was...
How is it not? I saw it with my own eyes!
That's because I mistook her as you.
And also through a turn of events...
You liar!
Get away from me! I hate you, Saito!
Louise!
Louise.
Oh, it's Tabitha.
Hey, which way did Louise go?
Tabitha?
You're horrible. You're absolutely horrible.
I can't forgive you. I can't forgive you, no matter what.
So have your revenge on him.
Revenge?
Yes. You can do it.
Since you're a great Void mage.
Who...
Could it be...
Sheffield!
What do you want, coming all the way here?
I am not your enemy.
Yeah, right.
Listen. The only people who can truly
understand you are other Void mages.
I don't believe a word of what you say.
Then let me ask you.
Whom do you believe in this world?
That's...
Your familiar? Or the Princess?
Don't worry. I am your ally.
Really?
You won't betray me?
For sure?
That was close.
What is this?
Why did you attack me?!
It's an order.
Order? What do you mean?
What's taking you so long?
Louise!
So you were the monster bird!
Tabitha?
Out of the way, Tabitha.
Or else I'll have to beat you to save Louise.
Tabitha!
Of course she won't move.
She's Chevalier de Norfatul.
Our loyal watchdog.
Watchdog?
Partner.
It's not looking too good. She looks pretty serious.
Tabitha, stop this! Stop it!
Imotal Iisan Hagaras.
Javelin!
Why? You could have killed me.
Why didn't you?
How could I?
How could I hurt someone who has saved us numerous times.
Even if it's to protect Louise, I couldn't do such a thing.
What's wrong?
What are you taking your time for?
Move.
Tabitha?
Oh well.
I have the Void in my hands.
Louise!
Wake up, Louise!
It's useless. She's deep asleep.
Louise!
Hey! Louise!
Saito...
Saito?
W-What?
Louise.
Jump off there!
Hurry!
I won't.
Huh?
Do you understand the situation you're in?
Shut up, you jerk!
I hate you, Saito!
I hate you! I hate you! I hate you!
Stop jumping around.
Don't touch me!
I hate everyone!
Louise.
Are you all right?
Saito?
Let go of me.
I told you what happened was just how things turned out.
I hate you! Let go of me! I've had enough!
You're the only one for me, Louise!
I don't believe you!
Geez, what a trouble.
Do you believe me now?
Do you really, really mean this?
Yeah, I mean it.
The most important person in the world... Louise...
...is you.
S-Saito!
Louise.
Partner. Sorry to bother you when you're busy,
but we're surrounded.
What?
I'll take her away by force now,
Gandalfr.
W-What's this?
What is that?
The monster bird?
Hey, you guys!
Good thing I was passing by.
That voice...
It can't be.
Colbert-sensei?!
Sigh...
It's impossible.
But...
kyuu ni senaka wo mukete kakedashita wa (Just love me)
急に背中を向けて 駆け出したわ
I suddenly turned my back on you and ran away
hoka no ko ni yasashiku shiteta kara yo
ほかの子に優しくしてたからよ
Because you've been so gentle to many other girls
Boy onegai oikakete yo
Boyお願い 追いかけてよ
Boy, please chase after me
ato ni wa hikenai kara
あとには引けないから
Because it won't be over after this
pun pun pun
I am so sorry
gomen to ienakute gomen ne
ゴメンと言えなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't say "I'm sorry", sorry ♥
shinjite iru no ni kuchibiru ga togaru
信じているのに くちびるが尖る
Even though I believe you, my lips are pouting
kawaiku narenakute gomen ne
可愛くなれなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't be cute, sorry ♥
kosame no furu machi tsukamaete
小雨の降る街 つかまえて
Catch me in the town where a drizzle is falling
furimuku kara nakanaori no chu o shite
振り向くから 仲直りのCHU～をして
Because I'll turn around and give you a make-up kiss
atsui ryouude no naka de
熱い両腕の中で
In your warm arms
Next Time
Why are you always looking at the Princess?
You dog. You're hiding something from me, aren't you?
Zero no Tsukaima. Princess no Rondo.
The Eastern Pursuit.
You better tell the truth.
The Eastern Pursuit
I won't forgive you if you look away.