Is that all, Guiche?
My speciality is earth magic.
Saito-san!
They've been doing nothing but playing knight from dawn to dusk and calling it training.
They look like they're enjoying themselves, so what's wrong with it?
But it looks like someone wants to object.
What?
I can understand your feelings with Saito busy with the Order every day.
I-I don't have any problem with that!
Sure, I admit that we haven't had much time to talk despite his coming back from the war.
But so what?!
Really?
Saito-san!
Tiffa?
Oh, wow.
You're suffocating me, Tiffa...
I-I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
More importantly, you decided to come to the academy?
Yes!
Since you told me to muster the courage.
Although it's a secret that I'm a half-elf.
Don't worry. I promised that I'd protect you, didn't I?
What's the big smile on his face all about?
That dog...
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
mejirushi no nai michi mo heiki sa futari nara
メジルシのない道も平気さ　ふたりなら
Even on a road without signs, I'll be fine, if we're together
saki no mienai tabi mayoinagara mitsuketa yo
先の見えない旅　迷いながら見つけたよ
On a journey that I can't see ahead of, while I was lost, I found it
boku no iru basho kimi no tonari
僕の居る場所　君のとなり
That my place to be is next to you
kenkashite nando mo hanashita sono te
喧嘩して　何度も離したその手
When we quarrelled, I let go of your hand again and again
hikiyose dakitai ima
引き寄せ抱きたい　今
I want to pull close and hold it now
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
namida no ame ni utaretara
涙の雨に打たれたら
If I'm beaten down by the rain of tears
I wanna hold you sugu yobi na yo boku no namae
I wanna hold you　すぐ呼びなよ　僕の名前
I wanna hold you, call my name immediately
dakishime ni yuku wa
抱きしめに行くわ
I'll go embrace you
kanashimi mo tsuyogari mo kono te ni uketomeru
悲しみも強がりもこの手に　受け止める
I'll accept sadness and bluffing in my hands
The Rumoured Accepted Student
I'm off.
Just you wait, Saito!
Where do you think you're going
without saying a word to your master?!
Where else other than the Order's training?
Same as yesterday and the day before.
Let me know every day.
Yes, yes.
Master, I'm off to training.
Wait!
We're not done talking!
What are you so mad about so early in the morning?
I'm not mad!
What is it then?
Well, I want...
Want what?
I want to spend more time together like before.
Why don't you get it, you dense dog?
What?
I... I-I want you to come home earlier!
Is there something you need me for?
Basically.
Yes, Ma'am.
I'll come back early today.
See ya.
Would you like more tea?
No, I'm all right.
Please, don't hesitate.
No, I'm really fine.
What's your afternoon schedule looking like?
Um...
No, please schedule some time with me.
No, me.
Tiffa became popular in no time.
The hottest topic on campus right now is whether her great breasts are real or not.
What do you think, Saito?
How am I supposed to know?
The mystery must be solved.
If it's come down to this, I shall find out with my own hands!
Montmo will kill you, you know?
You two!
Were you listening to anything I said?
Of course I was, Reinard.
So, what was it again?
I was saying we should recruit more
people into the Order of Undine Knights.
Sure, but how do we do that?
I heard there's another chevalier on this campus other than Saito.
You mean-
This hat will suit your beauty the most!
Please!
No, this hat will look the best on you.
What are you talking about? It's got to be this!
Of course not!
Crap, if they take her hat off, they'll find out she's a half-elf.
I-I'm fine. Please excuse me!
I'm sorry!
Gosh, what a rude girl.
Unbelievable!
Insolent wench!
Oh my, it's so cute.
If he sees me like this, I bet he'll...
It's a master's duty to give presents once in a while.
Tonight, I will welcome Saito back kindly.
Louise, you're so cute!
Forgive me for leaving you unattended!
You notice that now? But just one apology isn't enough!
I'm sorry for getting caught up with playing knight.
I'm sorry for staring at Tiffania's breasts.
T-Then, demonstrate your thoughts with action!
Louise, I always wanted to hold you tight like this!
I won't ever leave you alone anymore.
Yo, Tabitha.
What?
Uh... That is...
You're a chevalier, right?
Yes.
So would you join the Order of Undine Knights?
I am a Gallian citizen.
But-
I'm not interested in playing knight.
Maybe it was too sudden.
You're being so rude!
W-What are you talking about?
Tiffa?
Who do you think she is?
Beatrice Yvonne von Guldenhorf-sama.
Guldenhorf-sama!
Princess Beatrice of the Grand Duchy of Guldenhorf.
Princess?
You get to be in the same class with the Princess,
yet you don't even come to introduce yourself to her.
Utter insolence!
Give her your apology.
Y-Yes. I'm sorry, Your Highness.
You call that an apology?
Take that dirty hat off first.
You're before an aristocrat.
It goes without saying, right?
There has to be a limit to how rude you are.
But this hat is...
When I tell you to take it off, you take it off!
Hey!
What are you guys doing to Tiffania?!
Saito-san?!
What is this all of a sudden?
Don't you know who she is?
Huh? No matter who she is, she shouldn't bully others.
Who are you?
I'm-
Oh, if it isn't Princess Guldenhorf.
Oh, hello, Mr. Gramont.
Long time no see.
This guy here is Saito.
A barbarian that was just appointed a chevalier.
If you talk with a man like this in the hallway,
you'll ruin your eminence.
But he came and-
A mature lady shouldn't show any weakness at any time.
You have a point.
It's fine. Let's go.
But-
I said it's fine, so it's fine!
Okay...
You!
I'll let you go today.
But the next time you are to take that dirty hat off in front of me.
Hey, Guiche.
Aren't you supposed to be from a really honourable family?
Why are you deferring so much to an underclassman?
She's a bad person to be on the bad side of.
Although it's just a small independent
nation, she is a princess of a country.
So what?
That's not all!
She's really rich and has her personal guards here with her.
They're called the Luft Panzer Ritter.
They're known as the strongest dragon knights in Halcheginia.
I wouldn't want to get in trouble with them.
They have deployed an entire Knight
detachment for their daughter at school?
The wealthy like to put on a display.
That's totally you.
I just want to look cool!
I don't care about their dragon knights.
If they ever come to you for anything, let me know.
Saito-san...
He's here!
Remember, Louise. Give him the best smile!
I'm back.
Welcome back, Saito! Hurry, come and sit!
I prepared dinner!
Sorry, I already ate with Guiche.
I had to discuss something with him.
Oh, and I wanted to ask you about this too, Louise.
What?
It looks like Tiffania's being bullied.
Is there anything we can do?
Tiffania?
You're related to a duke, right?
If you would talk to-
Aren't you very kind?
Maybe you should just leave her alone.
What? A word of warning won't-
Silence!
Dog!
I'm saying it's her own business!
She chose to come here of her own will, so she should take care of herself!
Is this what was on your mind all these days?
Order training? Yeah, right!
The Order's got nothing to do with this!
Shut up!
I'm going to bed now, so don't talk to me.
You're the one who said to come back early.
Fine, suit yourself!
What's with him? I've been waiting for hours,
and he gets carried away when I'm being nice to him...
All he cares about is that half-elf.
Stupid dog.
I don't care about you anymore.
What a waste.
Miss Vallière, you'll be late for your classes.
I couldn't get a wink of sleep, so I'm not feeling well.
I'll skip school today.
Stupid Saito...
I can't cause any more trouble for Saito-san and the others.
I have to take care of myself.
Miss Westwood.
Miss Westwood?
Is she absent?
In that case-
M-Miss Westwood!
What is that outfit?
What strange clothes?
She looks like a clown.
Everyone!
This robe is a memento of my mother!
What? Only nomads wear such robes!
Are you by any chance an e-e-
Yes!
An elf!
I can't forgive her.
She's an elf, and she became more popular than me?
Please calm down! I want to be friends with you all!
It's a lie! There's no way an elf won't do anything bad!
Elves have certainly been the enemies of
humans in Halcheginia for many years.
But my parents fell in love with each other and gave me both elf and human blood.
So...
Oh, so you're a half-elf?
Then let me ask. What god do you worship?
The desert's devil? Or the Primogenitor, Brimir?
I...
You wish to be friends with us,
so you believe in the same god as we do, right?
If that is necessary...
Then prove that!
My Knights!
Guldenhorf Grand Duchy, Luft Panzer Ritter.
Arrest that woman!
What's going on?
That's...
Tiffa!
Isn't it a little noisy?
Hey now...
Stupid Saito... Stupid Saito... Stupid Saito...
She's hopeless.
What is this about?
An inquisition.
I happen to be a bishop.
A bishop?
Seriously?
Prove your faith to me, a deputy of God.
What do you want me to do?
Get in there.
Don't worry. It's just the right temperature for
anyone who believes in the Primogenitor, Brimir.
Is she serious about this?
Isn't that dangerous?
Why isn't anyone stopping this?
Stop it, Saito!
Why?
Are you afraid of the dragon knights?
No, this is an inquiry.
If you side with her, they'll treat you as a heretic and send you to prison.
You can't do it?
In that case, go back to where you came from.
Then I'll treat it as though none of this happened.
No, I won't.
I have always wanted to see the outside world.
Saito-san and everyone else made that dream come true.
So I won't go back!
If I tell you to go home, then you'll go home!
I pity you...
No, I guess that's wrong.
You're still a child.
Dunk her in the pot! Now!
Wait!
You dare interrupt the inquiry?
I don't care what happens to me.
So leave Tiffa-
Stop. This isn't only about you.
This will cause an inquiry to befall your beloved, as well.
Beloved?
Louise!
Saito!
Saito...
More...
Saito-san...
W-What is this about?
Please, Your Highness.
I'm the one who brought Tiffa here.
So what?
I take full responsibility.
Please forgive Tiffa.
No.
Even with all this begging?
Can't be done!
Then...
I guess I don't have a choice!
Looks like you're a heretic, too.
What is this about, Mr. Gramont?
It's a shame on knighthood to forsake ladies and one's friends.
Knights are to decide things with wands.
I can't help acting cool when there's such an audience!
That idiot!
Follow the Captain!
Undine, draw your wands!
Tiffa, stay back!
Go, Luft Panzer Ritter!
Louise.
Saito...
Shut up!
Are you all right?
Did something happen?
What is this about?
Why...
Why did you wake me up?!
Let's go!
Louise?
Louise, you...
You're being so noisy.
You guys are being noisy.
I was having such a good dream...
I was so close, too...
What a waste!
Stop it, Louise!
Saito-san!
Y-You interrupted the inquiry!
You had better beware of the consequences!
Inquiry?
Do you even have the right?
I-If you mean the bishop's license, I have it at home.
You're lying.
I'm not!
To perform an inquiry, you need the Romalia Sectarian Head's written permission.
A bishop should know that.
What does that mean?
She didn't have the right? She uttered God's name in vain?
I can't believe her.
I-I've got nothing to do with this.
Same here.
Beatrice-san.
W-What?
Don't come any closer!
Let's become friends.
I didn't know elves were so kind.
I think I want to be her friend, too.
Back to sleep.
Sorry for the cruel treatment.
I totally fell in a state of panic. I'm sorry.
It's fine. I think I can make lots of good friends here.
That would be great.
Now, I'd like to say everything's solved,
but there's one thing I must definitely ask!
Y-Yes?
Are these genuine?
Louise isn't coming?
Saito-san.
Tiffa?
Wha- Tiffa!
Your familiar is interesting as always.
What? You're here to be cynical?
Absolutely not.
It is difficult to get down on one's knees in that situation.
If you interrupt an inquiry,
your beloved will be questioned as well.
He bowed his head after hearing that.
I wonder who he thought about.
Do these look that fake?
Everyone's talking about them,
and even the Principal asked a moment ago.
There has to be a reason why everyone is
wondering, but I can't tell what that might be.
Tiffa... What are you suggesting?
Would you...
...touch and check?
I-I can't!
You're the only person I can ask!
So... please.
I-If you want me to...
How is it, Saito-san?
Do you have any idea why they don't look real?
N-Not yet. I think I need to inspect them a little more.
I'm the one to see him first!
He's my familiar, so I should be first!
Saito!
Yes?
Hey, do you have a whip on you?
Yes. Luckily, I happen to have one right here.
Wait, Louise! Don't rush!
There's a reason for this!
Sigh...
It's impossible.
But...
kyuu ni senaka wo mukete kakedashita wa (Just love me)
急に背中を向けて 駆け出したわ
I suddenly turned my back on you and ran away
hoka no ko ni yasashiku shiteta kara yo
ほかの子に優しくしてたからよ
Because you've been so gentle to many other girls
Boy onegai oikakete yo
Boyお願い 追いかけてよ
Boy, please chase after me
ato ni wa hikenai kara
あとには引けないから
Because it won't be over after this
pun pun pun
I am so sorry
gomen to ienakute gomen ne
ゴメンと言えなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't say "I'm sorry", sorry ♥
shinjite iru no ni kuchibiru ga togaru
信じているのに くちびるが尖る
Even though I believe you, my lips are pouting
kawaiku narenakute gomen ne
可愛くなれなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't be cute, sorry ♥
kosame no furu machi tsukamaete
小雨の降る街 つかまえて
Catch me in the town where a drizzle is falling
furimuku kara nakanaori no chu o shite
振り向くから 仲直りのCHU～をして
Because I'll turn around and give you a make-up kiss
atsui ryouude no naka de
熱い両腕の中で
In your warm arms
Next Time
I'm furious right now!
And you want to shame yourself even more?!
Zero no Tsukaima. Princess no Rondo.
The Captivating Girl's Bath!
If there's a hole, you want to hide in it, you say?
The Captivating Girl's Bath
I won't forgive you if you look away.