"Declaration of war"...
Please sign the document.
The cabinet has unanimously agreed to declare war.
Our ally, Germania, has already agreed to join us and is waiting for you to make your decision.
Your Highness, preparations to march into Albion are complete!
Give us your orders.
Cardinal Masarini, do you want to go to war that badly?
No...
I can understand your love for peace.
In that case-
However, most of the citizens are seeking military action against Albion.
If you keep postponing the war, a coup d'etat shall take place!
Coup d'etat?
In the worst case, you would be put in jail,
and the authority of the royal family would plummet.
Even if that were to happen...
...I don't want to start a war!
Your Highness!
If an aggressive ruler were to come into power,
the war would only escalate.
There will be nobody to stop it.
With your presence, we can limit the bloodshed to bare minimum.
I infer that your heart must be in turmoil,
but please make a decision.
Cardinal Masarini.
General Poitier.
Ma'am!
I, Henrietta, as the Queen of Tristain, declare war upon Albion!
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君のそばにいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai ga bokura wo tameshitatte
どんな未来が僕らを試したって
No matter how the future tests us
kitto…
きっと…
I’m sure…
aa futari no unmei
ああ 二人の運命
Ah, it’s our destiny
meguriaeta no wa
巡り合えたのは
I was able to meet you
kimi no koe kikoeta kara
君の声 聞こえたから
Because I heard your voice
sou pinchi na dekigoto
そう ピンチな出来事
Yeah, even if crisis events
oshiyosete kite mo
押し寄せてきても
Press on at me
kimi to ireba norikoerareru
君といれば乗り越えられる
If I'm with you, then I can overcome them
tokimeki to makenki to
ときめきと負けん気と
Palpitations and competitive spirit
urahara de haraharasuru kedo
裏腹でハラハラするけど
Excite me on the contrary, but-
Stay with me
tada kimi o mamoritai yo
ただ 君を守りたいよ
I only want to protect you
tooi sekai de umareta futari da kedo
遠い世界で生まれた二人だけど
We were born in distant worlds
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君の側にいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai mo kibou ni kaeyou
どんな未来も希望に変えよう
Let’s change any future into hope
Forever
The Underground Secret Document
Hey! We did it!
We did it!
Our forces took the victory!
Praise Tristain!
Praise our Queen!
Hey, hey, it looks like we won the first battle!
What does it say?
Let's see...
"The war broke out a week ago."
"A large fleet of five hundred ships,
consisting of Tristain and Germanian forces,
clashed with enemy troops before entering Albion territory...
...and inflicted upon them devastating damage."
"Damage to our side was minimal."
You hear that?
What? Tristain's winning!
Aren't you happy?
Wasn't the Princess against the war?
Well, yes, she was.
But it's Albion that we're facing.
She had no choice but to do so.
I'm sure the Princess had to make a painful decision.
Is that right?
A sailor uniform!
It's a sailor uniform!
What?
Hey Mister, what's this?
Hey, you've got a good eye.
These are sailor's clothes.
The fabric's pretty tough, and-
I bought it!
That sailor uniform...
...it's mine!
I'll make Louise wear this, and...
No...
It won't be as great if Louise wore this...
What's going on?
I have the Queen's permission!
This is ridiculous.
Agnes.
Is something wrong?
Well...
"Top secret document vault"?
Yes. Beneath this academy, there is a vault for top secret documents.
I received the privilege to access these documents from the Queen.
But Principal Osmond said...
...that he never received an order to undo the Lock...
...and thus refused to open the door.
Even though the Princess gave you the privilege?
It's dangerous, apparently.
It was built over a thousand years ago, so there are handfuls of mystery within.
I also heard that a spell was cast on it as a security measure.
Entering carelessly will cost you your life.
I'm a knight!
I do not fear danger!
Agnes, what's this document you want to see so badly?
It...
...has to do with my foe.
Foe?
Since our comrade is in trouble, I want to do something about it.
That's why I also called you two.
Comrade, eh?
You and I may be better described as buddies.
Louise, you can use special kinds of magic,
so you can dispel any kind of Lock, right?
If I were to use Unlock with Void magic, then maybe...
but I can't do it without concentration.
Listen, explosions seem to be the only kind of magic Louise can use.
She uses it like it's her only trick.
Kaboom here,
kaboom there.
She can't possibly do something complicated like unlocking a door.
You're right...
I've got no better tricks!
Opening Locks, you say?
What is Saito-san thinking of doing, making me wear clothes like these?
I wonder if Saito-san will like this.
Where are you taking us?
Saito-san?
Why's he going into women's restroom...?
This is the entrance.
This is strange...
It'd be better to burn the documents instead of hiding them here.
Once documents become official, they cannot be disposed of.
It'd be troublesome for others to see them.
Government policies don't make sense now, nor did they a thousand years ago.
Three locks are used.
Each one is simple,
but they can't be unlocked without the combination.
So, have you figured out the combination?
The binding of the Lock... undo.
You did it, Onee-sama!
Thank you very much.
I'll go on alone from here.
Sorry, but we refuse.
It gets interesting from here on, doesn't it?
I unlocked the door because I'm curious to see what's inside.
I might find records of magical experiments that were conducted in secrecy.
But it's dangerous...
If it's dangerous, that's more reason not to go alone.
Thank you.
Well, let's go.
Where to?
Colbert-sensei!
Agnes-kun. I though that the Principal was against this.
I do not take orders from cowards!
A-Agnes-kun!
You two!
Stop!
A foe?
Yes.
That's what Agnes said.
When our forces take over Albion's port, the Queen will head to the front lines.
Naturally, I will go with her.
I want to take care of this case before that.
The Princess is going to the front line?
Yes.
She said that she couldn't sit by in a safe place,
having ordered hundreds of thousands of troops to go risk their lives fighting.
Princess...
Well, who is your foe?
Stop!
Someone's following us.
That's...
Saito-san!
Siesta?
I tried on the clothes you gave me!
See?
How do I look?
Oh, I thought Saito-san was alone, but he had company with him.
That's what Saito bought in town, right?
And that skirt...
Isn't that from my uniform?
Ah, well, that's...
I heard that in Saito-san's home town, all young girls wear clothes like these.
I see.
I heard you came from a distant country, right?
Y-Yeah!
So it was very nostalgic.
So he gave it to me saying, "I'm sure it'll look good on you, Siesta."
"It wouldn't look good on Louise since she's got no breasts."
Oops...
Y-You're right. I d-don't have any b-breasts, do I?
They're flat, right?
They're concave, aren't they?!
Wait, Miss Vallière, not here!
Saito, you jerk!
Saito-san!
Hey, Chibi-Louise!
You need to consider the time and place when you use magic!
You haven't even learned these basic rules yet?
I'm sure I've mentioned them numerous times...
We can't do anything about this unless there is an Earth mage nearby.
In other words, we can't turn around.
What are we going to do, then?
Sitting here and crying won't do us any good.
Let's move on.
In your home town, do young girls go to war as well?
Huh?
I mean, isn't that a military uniform?
No way.
In my country, it's a school uniform.
Neither guys nor girls go to war.
I'd like to visit your country sometime.
Did the sailor uniform catch your interest, too?
That's not what I mean. I'm jealous of a country without war.
It's not that war doesn't exist there...
I can't stand having young people become victims of war.
We're in the midst of war!
It's the teacher's job to teach students to fight for their country.
Don't be ridiculous!
You can say that because you don't know what war is really like.
If you saw the wretchedness of the battlefield even once...
You've seen one?
No, but...
I have.
The village in which I was born was razed by the military.
But it was more like a massacre than a war.
She can't be from...
Twenty years ago, insinuating acts of treason,
the government destroyed a newly-formed sect.
In reality, that "treason" was nothing more than a hoax from Lishman.
They quelled a rebellion that never took place,
then got promoted for their achievements and gained power.
And for that, my family and friends were...
Innocent people were burned to death.
I alone was saved by someone who carried me out.
In other words, your foe is...
I already killed Lishman with these hands,
but those who actually assaulted the
village must still be alive somewhere.
I want to know who they were.
And that record is here...
Hey, it's getting bright.
Is that it?
W-Watch out.
This reminds me of high school days,
though I never had good experiences like this while I was there.
Save the explosion for later.
Saito, take the rear guard.
O-Okay.
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
I'll hold back for now, but you better look forward to tonight!
Yes...
Agnes-kun.
What?
Um, what do you intend to do when you find out who your foes are?
Do you have to ask?
What will you do after you kill your foes, then?
I'll fight for the Queen, and then die.
That's all.
Even though you were able to survive...
You're going to waste your life for vengeance and war?
Have you, ah... ever fallen in love?
What's this?
Love.
You're still young.
Don't you think there are more important things than battles?
Ridiculous! I don't have time to argue with you!
This is only a rumour, but I heard that Captain Agnes likes girls.
I thought so!
What do you mean by "I thought so"?
N-Nothing.
Wait, something's written there.
"The alteration, destruction, or removal of documents,
as well as the use of magic, is forbidden."
We can't use magic?
You can't use any to begin with, so you don't have to worry.
"Those who fail to abide will encounter a catastrophe."
I bet it's just a threat.
This is something.
It's on par with Romalia's religious library.
Is there really so much stuff that needs to be hidden?
Where's the document you wanted to see, Agnes?
It's from twenty years ago.
It must be a recent file within these.
Sensei, could you be...
W-What?
Do you like Agnes, by any chance?
You were talking about love and whatnot...
D-Don't be a fool.
That isn't what I have on my mind.
"Dungletale Case"?
This isn't it...
That's it!
Hey, plebeian! Don't touch stuff when you don't know what you're dealing with!
I-I'm sorry.
Seriously...
U-Um...
What?
You just used magic...
W-What's this?
This is bad. The security magic is taking effect!
Gosh, Onee-sama! Aren't you supposed to
consider the time and place when you use magic?
Forget that, let's get out!
Wait, this is it!
"Order."
"To prevent the spread of the epidemic, burn all humans near Dungletale."
Epidemic?!
We're going to get crushed!
Agnes-kun, we need to get out!
Wait, I haven't found the captain's name yet!
Hurry up, Agnes!
Now!
Found it!
"A special force was put together to deal with the epidemic, and the captain was-"
Gone!
The section with his name has been torn away!
Why?
Let's go.
Let go of me!
The name!
The captain's name must be somewhere...!
The bridge!
It's not letting us go back.
Let's hurry.
Wait, Saito and the others are still in there!
Crap.
Agnes, get on my back.
Forget about me.
Listen to me!
Help me out, Saito.
Yes.
Let's go!
Yes!
Sensei, do you have any magic for flying?
I can levitate, but only when I'm alone.
We must run through it!
No one can go there now...
Who knows?
Maybe it'll revert back to the way it was next time we come...
Colbert, it looks like you saved my life.
Thank you.
Sensei, I've gained a new impression of you.
You're very brave in an emergency.
No, I simply got scared and ran.
All right, let's head back to the academy.
Yes!
Epidemic countermeasure?
Yes. Although they said it was rebellion, there wasn't really one,
so the massacre was ordered to remedy the epidemic.
So the troops who carried out the
mission didn't know the truth behind it.
Are you telling me to forgive them if that's the case?!
No, I'm not saying that, but...
Still, it's strange for the captain's name to be ripped out.
This place exists for the sake of holding every
document working against that individual, right?
Maybe someone came before us.
Who?
I don't know.
Maybe the captain himself.
Oh yeah...
I forgot that Chibi-Louise collapsed the entrance.
But...
Saito-kun, we give you special permission.
Go flirt with Siesta.
Huh?
I see, that's a great idea.
Yes, I think so, too.
What's so great?
You pervert dog.
Wait, Louise, wrong direction!
That way! You need to blow that way!
Shut up!
Oh, another explosion.
It's a rowdy school, isn't it?
Oh my, it's the animal chorus.
You all get along well, don't you?
Y-You stupid dog!
chanto koko ni ite watashi no chikaku de
ちゃんとココにいて! 私の近くで
Be right here! close to me
zutto watashi o itsumo itsumo mitsumete nasai
ずっと私をいつもいつも見つめてなさい
Always, always look at me at all times
yosomishiteta desho hoka no onna no ko
よそ見してたでしょっ 他の女の子
You looked away, didn’t you? At other girls
o-shiokisuru wa furari furari furachi na yatsu wa
お仕置きするわ　フラリフラリ不埒なヤツは
I’ll punish those who are wavering and insolent
Don't touch! kikanai kara ne iiwake wa
Don't touch! 聞かないからね　言い訳は
Don’t touch! Because I won’t listen to excuses
Touch me... tsukareta kara nee kata o kashite yo
Touch me… 疲れたから… ねぇ肩を貸してよ
Touch me… because I'm tired… Hey, lend me your shoulder
suki yo nante uso yo
スキよ　なんて嘘よ
I love you, it’s a lie
kirai sore mo uso da wa
キライ　それも嘘だわ
I hate you, that’s a lie, too
nai nai nai dame yo kanchigai
ないないない　ダメよ勘違い
Nay nay nay, it’s useless, it’s a misunderstanding
dakara suki yo nante iwanai
だから「スキよ」なんて言わない
So I won’t say, “I love you”
Non non non dokka e ittara
Non non non　どっかへ行ったら
Non non non, because I absolutely won’t forgive you
zettai ni yurusanai kara ne
絶対に　許さないからね!
If you go to somewhere else
datte
だって
But
honto wa dare yori soba ni itai no
ホントは誰より傍にいたいの
The truth is, I want to be by your side more than anyone else
ai no kusari de sanposhimasho
愛の鎖で　散歩しましょ!
Let’s go take a walk in chains of love!
I... to be honest...
...might love you...
Next Time
You dog!
I won't forgive you for locking me up!
The academy's under attack, you understand that?!
Zero no Tsukaima. Futatsuki no Kishi.
The Magic Academy's Crisis.
If you want to meet me again next week, then sit tightly and wait!
The Magic Academy's Crisis