Principal's Office
The discipline at this school has been lacking lately.
Nichijou 14
I'd like you to be a little more strict on keeping students to the school rules, Sakurai-sensei.
Yes!
I-I'll do my best!
tatta ima hajimete kizuita
たった今 初めて気づいた
I just realised it for the first time
koi ni ochita no dana
恋に落ちたのだな～
That I had fallen in love~
nijyuuyo jikan kimi kimi kimi
24h キミ☆ キミ☆ キミ☆
Twenty-four hours a day thinking of you, you and nothing more than you!
ishiki sezaru o emasen
意識せざるをえません!
It's something I wasn't consciously aware of
nanka (nanka) itsumo to chigau
なんか (なんか) いつもと違う
Somehow (somehow) I'm feeling different from the usual
kimi to (futari) gikochinai kaiwa
キミと (二人) ぎこちない会話
With you (the two of us) and our dull chatter
masaka (ryouomoi) iya kataomoi
まさか (両思い) いや 片思い
Don't tell me (mutual love?) Nope, it's a one-sided crush
yabai shisen acchatta
やばい! 視線合っちゃった!
This is bad! Our gazes met!
nani nani kono doki doki
なになに?! このドキドキ?!
What, what? Why is my heart pounding like this?
shikoukairo guccha guccha konsen
思考回路 ぐっちゃぐっちゃ 混線・・・
Did a short circuit just make a mess out of my mind?
konna koto hajimete dayo
こんなこと 初めてだよ
This is my first time... feeling like this...
netsu demo aru no kana
熱でもあるのかな～
I wonder if I have a fever~
kyuutenchokka irasshatta koigokoro
急転直下 いらっしゃった 恋心
Suddenly and precipitately, love has arrived.
acchuuma kao hakka de makkakka
あっちゅうま 顔 発火で まっかっか
Instantly igniting my face into a bright red
ba ba baka na te ga furueruzo
バ・バ・バカな?! 手が震えるぞ
T-That's stupid?! My hands are shaking
kore ga zoku ni iu koi nano
これが 俗に言う 「恋」 なの?!
Is this really what they call "love"?
yayayacchatta kaiwa kami makuri
やややっちゃった 会話 噛みまくり
I-I did it! A conversation filled with stutters
kimazui chinmoku mamimumemo
気まずい沈黙 マミムメモ
This awkward silence... *mumble mumble*
kimi no (kimi no) kimochi shiritai yo
キミの (キミの) 気持ち 知りたいよ
Your... (Your...) I want to know your feelings.
kakakata kataomoi
カカカタ☆カタオモイ
O-One-sided love
hatsukoi itsumo no tsuugakuro
初恋! いつもの通学路
First love! The usual way to school
pika pika hikaru I do fall in love
ピカピカ光る I do fall in love!
The shining light. I do fall in love!
sora mo tobesou sa
空も飛べそうさ
I feel I could fly towards the sky
kakakata kataomoi
カカカタ☆カタオモイ
O-One-sided love
That's right, I became a student guidance counsellor in order to change myself!
I'll have to make sure that they stick to the rules.
What's this?
What's this, all of a sudden?!
But it's not good, since it's only allowed during lunchtime.
E-Excuse me!
What seems to be the problem, Miss?
Sorry, um... I don't think it's good manners to eat while walking...
How rude of me.
My stomach wouldn't stop growling,
most likely because I didn't eat breakfast.
I'll take it off now, sorry about that.
S-Sorry.
It's okay!
As long as you understand, it's...
I'm glad that he understands it when I tell him.
Tell them...
...that it was delicious!
What do you mean, "delicious"?!
Suddenly shouting in the middle of the hallway?!
You should think about your surroundings for a bit!
U-Um, you can't take something like that to school...
Misato, let's go.
Ah, okay.
Sasahara, I have something to talk to you about during lunch, so...
...be in the classroom then!
This school might really be lacking discipline.
That was rude.
Tachibana Misato didn't mean any harm either.
Please forgive her.
Ah, yes.
Sorry about that.
E-Excuse me!
What is that?
That frilly thing around your neck...
Ah, this?
Yes.
I was thinking it's kinda cute.
The ordinary days that we have been living might actually be a chain of miracles.
As it were, it might be something like that.
Ah, hm, so in other words, what is that frilly thing...
It's ****, I say.
Well then, Miss, we shall meet again in class.
Hmm...
Thank you... very much.
Wanna try it?
Sure, it looks fun.
Student Guidance
Excuse me, Nakanojou-kun!
Yes, what is it?
Ah, nothing really. Just you know...
I was thinking that having a hairstyle like yours at school is a little...
Ah no, only a little, just a little...
...It won't...
Ah, I'm sorry.
I didn't quite hear that, can you say it once more...
From the sides...
It won't grow from the sides!
Go Soccer Club 1
Daruma-san has...
...tumbled down!
Everyone went home.
Please take another 1000 steps forward
Nichijou 15
Nano, what are these?
TL note: Ume is an Asian fruit, otherwise known as the Japanese apricot or Chinese plum.
They're unripe ume.
TL note: Umeboshi is pickled ume that's often added to onigiri (Japanese rice balls).
I've been thinking of making some umeboshi at home this year.
Umeboshi... sour.
Ume are good for your health, you know.
Besides, if you put it in your onigiri, the rice won't spoil.
Nano!
You can't!
I haven't even said anything yet.
We just bought a lot of snacks recently, haven't we?
We'll finish those first, and then we can go buy more again...
Oh geez, Professor...
You can't have those today. That cat...
Um...
Sakamoto.
Ah yeah, we also promised to buy Sakamoto-san's food,
so snacks are...
Pocky.
Ah, um...
Yes?
Can I help you with anything?
Ah, this, this is...
Ah, the snowman? It just came in today.
If you want, you're welcome to buy it.
Is it a snack?
Ah, maybe it's something like shaved ice.
It's cold.
It's cheap!
You're gonna buy it?
N-No, I'm only taking a look.
Ah, a snowman!
I want it.
Hey you.
Y-Yes?
If you're not going to buy it, can you give it to me?
I-I'm buying it!
Why can Nano buy the things Nano wants,
but Professor can't buy the things Professor wants?
No, as I said, this is just...
Since Nano is buying the things Nano wants,
it's okay for Professor to buy the things Professor wants too!
I want it, I want it, I really want it, I want it!
I got it.
Just one pack, okay?
Really?
Nano, I love you.
So that's how you ended up buying that thing?
Yes, it's cute, and since it's cold, it feels good.
Professor, it's done.
Yes!
Nano, gimme more!
Yes, yes.
Seriously, you guys...
And where's my food?
Ah!
Shaved ice?
They want me to eat... shaved ice?
First comes rock, next comes paper, rockscispaper doesn't count,
rock-paper-scissors!
It's going up~
The screw!
Nichijou 16
Midterm Test
Health
English
TL note: This is a reference to the painting "The Creation of Adam", by Michelangelo, on the ceiling of the Sistine Chapel.
No no.
Okay, the test is over.
Good heavens!
This is a wig too.
Word Of The Day
When you think of what other people are looking for,
you might not know because there are so many other people.
When you think of what you're looking for,
isn't it a little bit of love?
After that, you've just got to pray to a god somewhere.
Well then,
a god somewhere, pleased to meet you.
Go Soccer Club 2
Daruma-san...
...has tumbled down!
Maybe you should stop that already?
A Parrot
They made me stand again.
I've adapted quite well to this body.
Nichijou 17
Just by looking at them, I can't stop drooling.
What's this?
Ah, Sakamoto-san.
It's umeboshi.
You can't eat them, because they're not done yet.
I'll use this to play with Sakamoto.
Ah, a foxtail.
Sakamoto, Sakamoto.
Hey, kid, I've told you so many times to put "-san" after it!
Ah, yeah. Sorry, Sakamoto.
Are you making fun of me?
It happened unconsciously. Sorry, Sakamoto.
You're doing it on purpose, aren't you?!
Well then, I'm going shopping!
Have a safe trip!
Seriously, the people here really haven't been educated, have they?
I'm sorry, Sakamoto, I'm not doing it on purpose.
I'm telling you, it's not Sakamoto!
Here, Sakamoto, I'll give you some gum.
How many times are you going to make me say it!?
Besides, have you ever heard of someone giving gum to a cat, you dumbas- Whoa!
Cut it out already!
I'm sorry.
Listen, I've told you before that I'm older than you two.
Adding "-san" when you address people older than you is...
I mean... that...
In other words, it is...
It means that...
So it means that...
Ah!
What is it?!
Can I go wee-wee?
Ah, yeah, go ahead.
Wee-wee!
You're taking it with you, huh?
From what I can see, there are only two kids living in this house.
I see.
No wonder they're not educated.
Which means, I'm the oldest in this house.
It can't be helped.
It'll be troublesome, but I'll act as their parent.
Seriously, I've been taken in by one hell of a house.
This is bad, yet it's so fun!
Sakamoto, what are you doing?
This is bad,
if she finds out that I was playing with the eraser,
my place as parent will be...!
My place as parent will...
My place as parent will be...
I might have slept for a bit.
Cats sure do sleep a lot.
Well, that's why.
That's why?
Yeah, that's why.
There are a lot of things lying around here, so...
First off, shouldn't you start by apologising to your elders?
This is bad, but it's really fun!
Whoa, Sakamoto, do it again, do it again!
Sakamoto!
N-No you're wrong, I was just...
Sakamoto, your leg!
I mean, didn't I tell you to put "-san" after it?!
Sakamoto!
I'm home!
Home run!
Nakanojou
Mother!
Nichijou 18
Daruma-san has...
...tumbled down!
Mai-chan is doing her hard-to-get jokes again.
It can't be helped.
For now, I'll take a jab at her.
Mai-chan, isn't that "on the book"?
Yukko, don't ever try to take a jab at me like that again.
When you take such a good jab at me,
it overshadows my funny man act.
No, it's that, you know?
I'm at the age where you start to unintentionally use English,
I mean...
But you know, it was difficult to figure out if that "on the book" was serious or a joke.
Well, how do you call it, I just had to take a jab at it.
It was difficult to understand?
You're seriously saying that?
It's because it's you.
Because it's you, I thought you'd understand.
No, I'm beat.
I didn't think you thought of me like that,
but I'm happy that you have faith in me.
Faith?
Yeah...
We're not friends,
so can you stop talking about having or not having faith in you?
Eh?
You don't need words between best friends, right?
Mai... chan!
Seriously, Mai-chan, it's okay to have a few words exchanged even between best friends, isn't it?
Mai... chan?
If you're all over me like that, I'll be troubled.
U-Um... sorry.
Stop it.
If you do that, I'll fall...
I'll fall even more in love with you.
It's okay to like me more, right?
We're best friends. Yo, best friend!
That's not the problem here.
We're not of the opposite sex, but it's kinda like I see you as one...
Sorry.
I can't say it... clearly.
Ah... um...
W-What is this?!
Somehow, I thought she was a bit odd today.
You see, you see!
She's talking more than usual.
She even said we should take a detour on the way home.
Was everything she did for the purpose of saying this?
I mean... since when?
Since when did she start to feel that way?
J-Just a second, M-Mai-chan...
H-How do I put it, I-I'm not really sure about those things...
I mean, it really is a bit too soon to say something like that.
I mean, we're still high schoolers after all!
That was a joke just now.
Super ultra great delicious wonderful...
...difficult to understand!
Geez, stop putting on such weird acts.
I sorta believed you for a moment there.
I see.
Because it's you,
and you're quick on the uptake, so I thought you'd understand.
Well, I did understand a little.
That's a lie, right?
No, no, it's not a lie or anything.
It's like my head got the idea.
Like, I really did understand it.
Thinking about it, that was a weird conversation just now.
Didn't you just say you believed it?
I hate people who lie the most.
Sorry.
That was a joke too.
I can't tell if these are jokes or not any more!
You didn't notice it?
I had another one.
I don't know!
Which one is it?
When I said "you're quick on the uptake"...
...you were supposed to jab at it with "No, I'm not."
That one?!
However, that one is somehow very easy to understand.
asa okite hao migai te
朝起きて 歯を磨いて
Woke up in the morning, brushed my teeth
attoiuma gogo juu ji
あっという間 午後10時
In the blink of an eye, it's 10pm
kyou mo takusan waratta naa
今日も たくさん 笑ったなぁ
Today, we laughed a whole lot
takusan tokimeita naa
たくさん ときめいたなぁ
We had a great time
tomodachi to baka mitai ni sawai deru toki ni mo
友達と バカみたいに騒いでる 時にも
At times, with my friends, acting like fools, being noisy
chirachiratte me ga au
チラチラって 目が合う
Fluttering, our eyes met.
guuzen dayo ne
…偶然、だよね。
It's a coincidence, right?
hatsukoi nante ie nai
初恋なんて言えない
I wouldn't call this my first love
kyara janai n da mon
キャラじゃないんだもんっ!
It's not my character.
nee ashita mo aeru yo ne
ねえ あしたも会えるよね?
Say, will we be able to meet again tomorrow?
mabuta o tojiru to
まぶたを 閉じると
As my eyelids close
kirakira kimi darake
キラキラ キミだらけ
I see you sparkling all over the place
kyou mo tanoshikatta ne
今日も 楽しかったね
Today was fun, too, wasn't it?
aa koi shite n da naa
あー 恋 してんだなぁ
I'm in love~
ureshii na ureshii na
うれしいな うれしいな
So happy, so happy
hajimemashite koi gokoro
はじめまして こいごころ
It is my pleasure to meet you, my new-found love.
ashita mata aeru ne
あした また あえるね
Surely, we'll meet again tomorrow~
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
Have a good night
yume de sugu aeru ne
ゆめで すぐ あえるね
We'll meet immediately in our dreams
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
So have a good night
It's already been 40 years, this multi-unit apartment.
Try writing apartment wives.
You'll find an unbelievable degree of sexiness to it.
Next week's Nichijou is the fifth one.
Narration:      Obara Noriko
Look forward to it.