Twice-Cooked Pork
Sorry for the wait.
I can only make this.
Here.
Wow, awesome! It's twice-cooked pork.
I'm really hungry, so this is perfect.
I put something in for a hidden taste.
I wonder if you can tell.
Having a hidden taste; it sounds like the real thing.
I'm digging in!
It only has the miso flavour, or rather...
The hidden taste is not so hidden, or rather...
No, instead, the more you chew it, the hidden taste gets worse, or rather...
I'm really against this hidden taste!
tatta ima hajimete kidzuita koi ni ochita no da no
I just realised for the first time that I had fallen in love
nijyuuyo jikan kimi, kimi kimi ishiki sezaru wo emasen
All day long, it's only you, you, you; I just couldn't avoid it
nanka nanka itsumo to chigau kimi to futari
Somehow, somehow I'm different from usual when I'm with you
dojina kaiwa masaka ryouomoi
Do we converse awkwardly? mutual love?
iya kataomoi yabai shisen acchatta
Nope, it's an unrequited love, whoops, we made eye contact
nani ga niko hottoki doki sha ba da ba de bee doo wa ba dee ay
Something's making my heart beat faster sha ba da ba de bee doo wa ba dee ay
shikoukai wa gucha gucha konran shaaba deebee doobee, yeah!
My train of thought derails with a *splat* *splat* shaaba deebee doobee, yeah!
konna... koto... hajimete da yo
This... is the... very first time for me
netsu demo aru no kana?
Do I have a fever, I wonder?
kimi sasotterasha na koigokoro hajimankan datte de nakatta
The awakening of love that you induced it was without pride
ba-ba-baka no te ga furueru zo kore kazuku ni yuku yaranai
T-T-These stupid hands are shaking and from here, we'll proceed
ya-ya-ya chotto kaiwa kamimakuri kimadzui chinmoku no ninmu na no
No no no, I've messed up my words a bit and so there's an awkward silence
kimi no kimi no kimochi shiritai yo ka-kata-ka-kataomoi
About your about your feelings I really want to know, it's an u-u-un-unrequited love
hatsukoi itsumo no tsuugakuro
First love always in the school zone
pikapika hikaru I will fall in love
A glittering light I will fall in love
sora mo tobesou sa
I'm flying through the sky
ka-ka-ka-ka-kataomoi!
U-U-U-U-Unrequited love!
Nichijou 23
This is actually pretty good...
Mio-chan, Mio-chan!
TL Note: Kappa, literally meaning "river-child", is a water sprite found in Japanese folklore.
is cool, isn't it?
What the hell is this?
Kappa?
is cool, isn't it?
Why a kappa all of the sudden?
Moreover, what does she mean by "is cool, isn't it?"...
But...
Next time, I might want to draw something in fantasy that's interesting and strong.
Something like a Daidarabotchi and a kappa.
TL Note: Daidarabotchi is a gigantic demon in Japanese mythology.
Kappa... Heh, I guess he will be the "uke".
TL Note: In yaoi, "uke" refers to the more feminine partner.
Kappa, kappa, huh?
Kappa...
Kappapaa... pa... pa...
Parasite.
With this, maybe we can just play shiritori.
TL note: Shiritori is a Japanese word game in which the players are required to say a word which begins with the final kana of the previous word.
Yukko.
Thanks.
Parashite?
TL Note: In Japanese, parasite is read as "Perasaito", but Yukko read it as "Parashite".
This is what a parashite's meant to be like?
Having this arrow means...
I see. She's inviting me to a game of shiritori.
I'll accept it.
Hmm... Parashite...
"Te"... "Te"... OK.
So big!
I didn't
have time!!
Moreover, a "tengu"...
She read parasite's "to" as "te".
Oh, well. A "tengu," huh?
"Tengu"... "gu"... "gu"... "gu"...
"Gu-"!
N-No way!
Tengo!!
What the hell is a "tengo"?! What's a "tengo"?!
No! Wait a minute!
There's no way a high school student would make such a childish mistake.
I mean, she already drew a picture of tengu and still wrote down what it was.
I don't get it.
I don't really understand, but...
I guess I'll go with "go" here.
Here.
Draw smaller!!
What's with this Goku drawn out of boredom?
TL Note: Goku is a character from a classical Chinese novel "Journey To The West".
Huh... Wait... Goku? I'm pretty sure I drew a tengu just now...
Well, I can understand how she could mistake "gu" for "go".
I'll get juice from her later for this.
Now, it's "u"... "u"... "u"... OK!
A sea urchin? No, a rabbit.
TL Note: Sea urchin is "uni", and rabbit is "usagi", or "usa" for short, in Japanese.
I can't draw very well!!
It's a cow?!
TL note: Cow is "ushi" in Japanese.
This cow is beyond terrible...
Here.
Tongue! She came at me with the tongue!
TL note: In Japanese, tongue is "shita".
Then, it's "ta".
"Ta"... "ta"...
Taxi... Ta...
W-Why are you doing this?!
If you write it like this, it isn't a taxi. It's a taxy!!!
I'm just going to write down whatever works.
Oh, seafood has started to come up!
Shi-su-
She's really up for it.
OK, OK, OK.
Oh, no!
I'll lose like this!
TL Note: There is no word in Japanese beginning with the sound "n", so you lose if you use a word ending with the kana "n" in a game of shiritori.
Superman
No, this... I just have to do this...
Here.
Supermans
Superman
Go Soccer Club
Go Soccer Club 3
Ah, there's nothing to do.
There's nothing to do, Sekiguchi.
OK, Sekiguchi, let's have a "Isse no se" match!
TL Note: "Isse no se" is a Japanese numbers game played using both hands.
I'll start!
Isse no two!
Sekiguchi...
There's nothing to do, anyway. Can't you play with me sometimes?
President.
Sekiguchi...
Nichijou 24
I forgot my homework and was made to stand in the hallway, Mogami river. By Yukko.
I can't believe I have to stand in the hallway just because I forgot my homework today...
How should I spend this time, Mogami river. By Yukko.
Wai...
E-Everyone! It's a deer... It's a deer...
W-Why is the principal is trying to catch the deer...?
W-Wai- Principal... D-Deer...
Principal!
W-Wait, everyone... The principal's... dying...
That's a... shika senbei?!
TL Note: Shika senbei are rice crackers specially made to feed deer.
W-Wai- Everyone, the principal is dy-dyin-
He got up.
He climbed up!
He jumped!
And falls down just like that!
He climbed up again!
He climbed down!
H-He's in a deadlock!
Principal!
Principal...
Wai- Everyone... Death... Principal... Death...
Uh... Wai- Um... Uh...
Wai- Everyone, listen!
Uh... Um... P-Prin...
Um... Prin...
Nothing new to report from the hallway!
She said those words from the bottom of her heart.
They were by no means to cover up for the principal, nor because explaining it would be too troublesome. Nothing like that.
Maybe she just wanted to show respect to the heroes who had just performed a fight to the death.
It's too early to gather the early-summer rain, Mogami river.
No idea what it means.
10 Yen Soccer
OK, then. Mio-chan will be the judge.
You don't need a judge for ten yen soccer.
You don't understand, do you? It's all about the feeling, the feeling.
Now, kickoff!
I guess it can't be helped.
Come at me from any angle!
OK...
First comes rock, next comes paper. Go splat like a pear, rock-paper-scissors!
I-
Chomp.
I love it.
Shinonome Institute
Nichijou 25
What should I do?
I caught a cockroach...
C-Carefully...
Anyway, I'll have to do it carefully...
I have to make sure this disgusting root of evil doesn't spread in the house again.
A plan... I have to go with the most perfect plan...
Ah, pesticide spray!
No, I can't.
It's not a one-hit-kill, so there's a chance that it will just run away.
Most of all...
I don't want to see it squirm!
Ah, that's right! What about detergent?
I'll cover the tea table with detergent to seal its movement, and then pinpoint it directly!
I-It will fly!
With nowhere to run, it'll definitely fly!
When it flies, it's over.
It'll blindly aim somewhere and hit people!
If this was to hit my body... or hit my face...!
No, wait...
I-If this was to get inside... get inside my mouth...
It's a one-shot rock and roll!
This is the worst kind of uneasiness.
I don't have any other choice.
The choice of lifting this bowl up might kill me!
Death or die!
There's...
Trash
There's no choice but to do that...
What are you doing?
Sa-Sakamoto-san!
Please save me!
I-Inside this, there is a r-roach... a roach.
What?
Could it be a cockroach?
I guess it can't be helped. All right. Leave it to me.
That'll save me.
Hey.
Yes?
What are you doing? I'll get it, so lift the bowl.
No, I'm saying lift the bowl. Otherwise, I can't get it.
Hey!
W-What are you saying?! How could I lift the seal on the root of evil?! This is Pandora's box! The moment I lift it up, it's death or die!
No, no, no.
How am I supposed to get it without lifting up the bowl!?
Lift it up yourself!
As if I can!
W-What should I do?
Sakamoto-san has gone somewhere...
Nano!
What's today's snack?
Ah, good timing!
The professor is not bothered by bugs either, so surely she can...
Professor, i-it'd be nice if you could get rid of t-this cockroach inside this bowl!
Sure.
R-Rock and roll!
Sorry, then I shall leave it to you.
It's OK. I'll do it in one shot!
Men!
TL Note: "Men" is what you say after successfully hitting your opponent's head in kendo.
Oh, I hit the wrong one.
I-I'm... I'm seriously worried here, but this person is... this person is...
Seriously, I hate you, professor!
You're going to cry?
It's just a joke! Geez, there's no way I would hate you.
Professor, I love you.
Nano!
Geez, professor.
Now, it's time to rock and roll!
If You Count To 10
Hey, it's hot, so can I get out?
Huh? We just got in.
But it's gotten hot...
Then let's get out after a count to ten.
20 log root 10!
Huh?
You said we can get out once we count to ten.
Uh... Um...
You have to say "One, two"...
Go Soccer Club 4
What's with everyone? Just because they have cram school, they all leave.
Sekiguchi, you're bored as well, right?
Huh? Come to think of it, didn't you go to cram school, too?
You've got to be kidding!
Nichijou 26
Delicious!
Yukko, how's the curry?
Yeah, it's almost done.
I'm quite hungry.
Yeah, me, too!
Mai-chan, how are things over there?
I foresee a big one.
This will be a feast.
All right! It seems like it's ready.
Thanks for waiting.
The extremely delicious super-curry is complete.
I think it will take a little longer over here.
We should have started these before the curry.
Well, they say, "Even if a baby is crying from hunger, don't remove the lid".
Ah, we should have brought mayonnaise.
You really need mayonnaise for curry.
M-Mayo-Ma-
Yukko, what do you like with curry?
Just kidding.
No... It's not like that... T-This is... not what you think...
I still have- Look, I still have tokoroten!
TL Note: Tokoroten are strips of gelidium jelly (agar).
T-Tokoroten... Just kidding.
What is your...
Mi-Mio-chan...
What is the colour of your blood?!
Sorry, Mai-chan!
There's not any curry or rice for lunch!
Mai-chan...
There's still tokoroten, if you want...
Mai-chan!
Release.
Well, then There's one tokoroten here.
Only one?!
I think we should take turns eating it.
However, as we are to blame, Mai-chan, you should start.
Rock-paper-scissors!
Just make sure you don't eat all of it in one bite!
That's upsetting to me... I'm not a demon, you know.
I'll dig in first.
I choked.
That's right! Let's play cards!
Let's not!
If things continue this way, this'll end as a disappointing camping trip!
Let's play cards at the very last moment and give it a happy ending!
That's right!
Oh, what's up?
I totally forgot!
Adults drink alcohol at times like these, right?
T-That's right.
Hey, Mai-chan, don't you agree?
Actually, I brought some!
T-That can't be, Mio-chan.
That's right.
A delinquent. There's a delinquent here!
Tada!
Vinegar
A-Any bottle is fine!
Mio-chan stop it! You'll die!
We still have Mai-chan's left!
This is cider.
Cider
Word Of The Day
Milk
Exit the bath, drink milk, act drunk.
I'm a peso!
I'm ten yen!
I'm wadoukaichin!
TL Note: Wadoukaichin is Japan's first circulated coinage, minted in 708 CE.
No, no. A person's value is not measured by money!
The next Nichijou is the seventh! Look forward to it!
Narration         Koyama Rikiya