What do you think?
Isn't it a big ship?
It's called the Ostland.
It's the latest exploration ship made based on Mr. Jean Colbert's design.
Miss Zerbst invested in my research.
In other words, it's the fruit of our love!
In any case, we've been away on a test flight these past few days.
But last night, the wind pushed us off course
and we happened to be flying around here.
Then we saw you fighting.
It really surprised us.
It surprised me, too.
I mean, I saw you and heard your familiar voice...
I thought I was dreaming.
Me, too.
Since I honestly thought you...
It turns out Tabitha cast a spell to stop one's
heart temporarily to make one appear dead.
I took him out of the coffin as soon as she told me.
After that, I had him stay at my house in Germania.
Why did you keep it a secret?
Why couldn't you have told us?!
I'm sorry about that.
I meant to, but I never found the right time to.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
No... I'm glad to know that you are well.
Welcome back, Colbert-sensei.
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
mejirushi no nai michi mo heiki sa futari nara
メジルシのない道も平気さ　ふたりなら
Even on a road without signs, I'll be fine, if we're together
saki no mienai tabi mayoinagara mitsuketa yo
先の見えない旅　迷いながら見つけたよ
On a journey that I can't see ahead of, while I was lost, I found it
boku no iru basho kimi no tonari
僕の居る場所　君のとなり
That my place to be is next to you
kenkashite nando mo hanashita sono te
喧嘩して　何度も離したその手
When we quarrelled, I let go of your hand again and again
hikiyose dakitai ima
引き寄せ抱きたい　今
I want to pull close and hold it now
You are the one boku no mirai wo ageru
You are the one　僕の未来をあげる
You're the one who gives me my future
namida no ame ni utaretara
涙の雨に打たれたら
If I'm beaten down by the rain of tears
I wanna hold you sugu yobi na yo boku no namae
I wanna hold you　すぐ呼びなよ　僕の名前
I wanna hold you, call my name immediately
dakishime ni yuku wa
抱きしめに行くわ
I'll go embrace you
kanashimi mo tsuyogari mo kono te ni uketomeru
悲しみも強がりもこの手に　受け止める
I'll accept sadness and bluffing in my hands
The Eastern Pursuit
Are you sure you don't need to tell the others you fought that Gallian girl the other day?
Yeah, I should, but... I can't make sense of it yet.
Why did Tabitha do that?
He has that look again.
He's been like that since this morning.
That pervert!
I can't.
If I forgive him so easily, my dignity as his master will fade!
Saito!
What, Louise?
About last night.
What are you talking about?
Don't act dumb!
The incident with the Princess.
Oh, that.
"Oh, that"?!
Well, we already talked about it last night.
Yes, I remember.
"Just how things turned out", right?
Yeah, that's right.
If you think about it, that's not an explanation at all.
Give me a clearer story.
I-I've been a little forgetful these days...
Who do you think the master is?!
Tell me exactly what happened that led to that situation!
I-It hurts.
Hey, Saito.
I'm gathering the Order of Undine Knights.
Y-Yeah!
H-Hey, Saito!
We'll talk about it later.
Tell the whole story, she says...
But I really can't, can I?
Miss Vallière.
What?
I haven't heard the result yet.
What result?
Whether Saito-san found you at the ball last night or not.
Judging from your reaction, he didn't, did he?
T-There was an emergency yesterday.
Making excuses is what sore losers do.
Praise the Queen!
Your Highness!
Long live Her Highness!
It's Henrietta-sama!
She's always so beautiful.
Y-Yeah.
It really is a magnificent ship.
It will be spoken of in all Halcheginia.
It's an honour, Your Highness.
I heard you used this ship to repel the gargoyles that appeared near the academy last night, as well.
You have my gratitude from the bottom of my heart.
Rather than me, you should thank Saito-kun here.
Saito Chevalier de Hiraga-dono.
I give you my gratitude, as well.
Well, I am your knight, so...
What is this about?
Why is there a strange atmosphere between them?
Hey, Miss Vallière?
That dog... That dog... That dog...
What are you thinking? It's impossible.
The Dog and the Queen? How ridiculous. Damn it.
Saito-san and the Queen were h-hugging?
Shh! Not so loud!
I can't believe it.
With the Queen as a rival, there won't be any chance of winning.
Don't talk like you had a chance before.
But, I mean, it's the Queen!
She can do whatever she wants!
I bet she'll eventually make Saito-san work at the castle.
And when night falls...
What do you mean, "when night falls"?
I can't say that!
You've gone that far, so out with it!
Then let me put it this way.
In chapter two of The Glorious Day of Countess Butterfly, there's a scene that goes like this.
A noble lady invites a knight to her bedroom and says,
"My knight. Serve me the way you wish."
"Give me a delusional, sensational joy."
Wait! The Princess would never say that!
"That's right! Now... come..."
"Right to my breasts!"
"Yes! There! Right there!"
U-Um...
T-That was this stupid maid putting on an act!
Is there something on your mind?
Colbert-sensei.
Saito-kun. Do you know the origin of the name of the ship?
No.
Ostland.
In other words, the East.
I named it hoping to go to the far eastern area with you.
The reason I was able to make this ship is you.
Oh, please.
There are many things I want to show you.
Would you come with me?
Yes.
Princess?!
Why did I...
Your Highness.
The return carriage is ready.
I'm a queen.
I must return to my duties.
But...
Is there a problem, Your Highness?
Just a little...
I wish to remain here for a little while longer.
I see. Such a thing happened between Saito-san and the Queen.
You don't seem to be too surprised.
I am, but I think there must be some reason for it.
O-Of course I think so, too!
But because Saito won't say it clearly...
Louise-san.
You can use this if you want to.
What is it?
It's a magic item called Last Night Orb.
Last Night Orb?! I've heard about them!
Why do you know about them?
They're really popular among the wives in the city.
They're disposable, so the stock keeps running out.
Where did you get hold of one?
Beatrice-san gave it to me to settle things between us.
What can we do with this?
If you look at a person through this,
you can see what that person did the previous night.
I hear wives use them to check if their
husbands are cheating on them or not.
I-Is that so? But I don't need to use something like this.
I believe Saito-san, too.
But if this makes you feel better...
If I use this, will this sense of anxiety go away?
But...
I'll use it, then.
Huh?
You don't need it, right, Miss Vallière?
I never said that!
Of course I'll use it!
He's my familiar!
Those propellers provide three times the
propulsion and allow long-range flying.
Really?
I made it based on your Dragon's Plumage.
It runs on coal.
The steam pressure from boiling water
heated with the coal moves the propellers.
I decided to call it the water vapour engine.
What's wrong, Saito-kun?
Well...
You'll see Mr. Colbert's last night!
I know! It's pretty hard to aim.
What are they doing?
Could that be...
Partner, run!
Now!
Okay.
Sensei, excuse me!
O-Okay.
He ran!
Suspicious!
Let's go!
W-Why do I have to run?
What she had in her hand is a scary item that strips a man of everything.
Strips? Why?
Just keep running!
Wait, Saito!
Saito-san!
What is this about?
The usual, I say.
You won't get away, you mutt!
Saito! Stop your futile resistance!
We'll split up!
Then I'll go this way.
U-Um, what about me?
This is the water vapour engine?
It's amazing how he made this just from looking at the Zero.
It brings back memories. There were a lot of these in my world.
Saito-san!
T-Tiffa?
I-I'm sorry.
W-What is this about?
It's for Louise-san's sake.
No, you can't, Tiffa.
Saito-san's here!
Surrender, Saito.
Stop! Stop it!
Stay still!
Gotta go.
Saito!
So this is where you were.
Ah, Miss Zerbst.
I was tuning things for the next flight.
Jean.
How many times do I have to say it?
Call me Kirche.
But I'm a teacher.
It doesn't matter when there's love.
S-Stop it, Miss-
My dear Jean...
S-S-
Oh.
S-Saito-kun!
No, you see! T-This is-
S-Sorry for the disturbance!
Saito!
Thank you for all the trouble, Dog.
Stop it.
You won't run away anymore.
Last Night Orb.
Show me what Saito did last night.
What?
What's this?
Why does it show Tabitha?
Was Tabitha involved last night?
Saito! Tell me!
You're right. Tabitha got in my way when I tried to save you.
But it wasn't of her own will.
Sheffield ordered her to.
She called Tabitha a faithful watchdog or something like that.
It's getting more confusing.
Why does Tabitha listen to that woman?
I think I know.
It might be related to that.
Wait there.
I'll be back soon.
Tabitha isn't an ordinary aristocrat.
She's a member of Gallia's royal family.
Her father was the younger brother of the current King.
Her father was killed during the fight over the throne.
Tabitha was also targeted and had her food poisoned,
but her mother took the poison meant for her.
Ever since, her mother's been mentally ill,
hiding within one room.
After that the Kingdom of Gallia named Tabitha a
chevalier and gave her seemingly impossible missions.
Impossible missions?
Monster slaying, dangerous scouting and the like.
We fought you guys at the Lagdorian Lake, remember?
That was one of those.
So yesterday was as well?
I bet it was an order from the Kingdom of Gallia.
I can't forgive them!
Hey, Louise. Let's go to Gallia right now and-
Wait. I'm safe here, so Tabitha failed in her mission, right?
What will happen to her?
Even I don't know that.
But there's always the chance...
Where did you take her?
Where did you take Mother?
Oh, the woman the Gallian Military arrested this morning.
I don't know where they took her.
I'm Vitartial of Neftes.
Nice to meet you.
An elf.
Yes.
We elves do not relish needless fights.
So I ask you to comply and come with me.
To the King of Gallia, Joseph.
I need to take you there.
Nature magic...
I do not like that name.
Call it the power of spirits.
The ones who tried to take Louise away were from Gallia?!
There's no way Tabitha would attack me otherwise.
But why?
Sheffield said she wants my abilities as a void mage.
Your Highness, please let me go to Gallia!
Saito.
I can't forgive them for trying to kidnap Louise.
And to use Tabitha for that... It's too much.
I'll march in and make sure they can't do that again.
You can't do that!
Why not?!
I'll knock them all out and-
You mustn't do such a dangerous thing.
Please leave this to me.
But...
We first need to gather evidence.
If it is Gallia's doing, then I will use this Kingdom's forces...
...to protect you all.
Promise me you won't do anything rash.
Yes.
Oh dang. We never figured out what happened last night, did we?
I'm sorry I couldn't be of any help.
It's fine now.
I told Saito...
...that I believe him.
Sigh...
It's impossible.
But...
kyuu ni senaka wo mukete kakedashita wa (Just love me)
急に背中を向けて 駆け出したわ
I suddenly turned my back on you and ran away
hoka no ko ni yasashiku shiteta kara yo
ほかの子に優しくしてたからよ
Because you've been so gentle to many other girls
Boy onegai oikakete yo
Boyお願い 追いかけてよ
Boy, please chase after me
ato ni wa hikenai kara
あとには引けないから
Because it won't be over after this
pun pun pun
I am so sorry
gomen to ienakute gomen ne
ゴメンと言えなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't say "I'm sorry", sorry ♥
shinjite iru no ni kuchibiru ga togaru
信じているのに くちびるが尖る
Even though I believe you, my lips are pouting
kawaiku narenakute gomen ne
可愛くなれなくて、ゴメンネ♥
I can't be cute, sorry ♥
kosame no furu machi tsukamaete
小雨の降る街 つかまえて
Catch me in the town where a drizzle is falling
furimuku kara nakanaori no chu o shite
振り向くから 仲直りのCHU～をして
Because I'll turn around and give you a make-up kiss
atsui ryouude no naka de
熱い両腕の中で
In your warm arms
Next Time
Yet another girl?!
One after another! You pervert dog!
What? Searching for her sister?
Who are you?
Zero no Tsukaima. Princess no Rondo.
Tabitha's Younger Sister.
It's pretty tough for me, too.
Tabitha's Younger Sister
I won't forgive you if you look away.