Well, that's all for today.
The days are getting shorter,
so please try to be home before it gets dark.
Nano-chan!
Yes?!
Let's go home together.
Do you want to stop by that place near the station?
Eh?
What do you think?
Um... Uh...
Hey, Mio-chan. Do you want to come, to-
Huh?
Did she leave already?
Then, Nano-
Huh?
I ended up running away.
That wasn't very nice to Aioi-san.
If only I could've introduced myself more like a normal girl...
My name is Shinonome Nano!
And you see, this key is...
jou jou yuu jou banjin maji kaichou
じょーじょーゆーじょー万事マジ快調
Amazing friendship, the absolute best!
na na na na na na na
ななななななな
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
hai! icchaimashou!
ハイ!言っちゃいましょう!
All right! I'll say it!
kimi wa best best friend
キミはベストベスト フレンド
You are my best, best friend!
(furai!) chotto fuzakete mitara
(フライ!) ちょっとふざけてみたら
(Fly!) When I joke around a bit,
(shain!) motto fuzake kaeshite kuru
(シャイン!) もっとふざけ帰してくる
(Shine!) You joke around more in response.
(La La La) ikogochi ii ttara arya shinai
(ラーラーラー)居心地良いったらありゃしない
(La La La) Nothing is better than this!
(wai!) iya na koto attatte
(ワイ!) 嫌なことあったって
(Why!) Even if something bad happens,
(fain!) sokkou wasurechaunda
(ファイン!) 即効忘れちゃうんだー
(Fine!) I immediately forget about it!
(La La La)
(ラーラーラー)
itsudatte jan jan yarimasho
いつだって、じゃんじゃんやりましょ♪
Always keep it going!
24 jikan issho demo mondai nai
２４時間一緒でも問題ない
Being together 24 hours a day isn't a problem.
marude futago ka oyako ka clone saibou
まるで双子か親子かクローン細胞
Just like twins, or a parent and child, or clone cyborgs.
kore ja me ga sumu hitsuyou wa nakunakunai!?
これじゃ目が澄む必要はなくなくない!？
Then isn't there no reason to clear your eyes?
sore to kore to wa mattaku mattaku betsumondai
それとこれとは まったくまったく 別問題
Those are completely, completely different issues.
(faito!) kenka shichatta toki mo
(ファイト!)喧嘩しちゃった時も
(Fight!) Even when I get in a fight with you,
(daoun!) kanari hekonda toki mo
(ダウン!)かなり凹んだ時も
(Down!) even when I get really down,
(shai!) hitori de itai you na toki mo
(シャイ!)一人で居たいような時も
(Shy!) even when I feel like I want to be alone,
futokizukeba chikaku ni iru shinaba morotomo
ふと気付けば 近くに居る 死なば諸共
before I realise it, you're right there; we'll be together even in death!
nande daro
なんでだろ
I wonder why it is.
soba ni itainda
そばに居たいんだ
I want to be with you.
kimi to issho nara
君と一緒なら
When I'm with you,
tokei hyakubai soku
時計百倍速
time goes 100 times faster!
tanoshii na
楽しいな
It's fun, isn't it?
tanoshisugirunda
楽しすぎるんだ
It's way too fun!
sasuga saikou friend
流石 最高 friend
As expected of my best friend!
Hey! na na na na na na na
Hey! ななななななな
Hey! Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
nannanoyo
なんなのよー
What is it?
yabai synchro
ヤバいシンクロー
The synchro is amazing!
itsumo oosawagi
いつも大騒ぎ
Always making an uproar,
kanari gokinjo meiwaku
かなりご近所迷惑
bothering the neighbours a lot.
ima nanji
今何時
What time is it now?
ato ne yorereihifu
あとねヨレレイヒーフ
And then yo de le hi hoo!
wake wakannainai
訳分かんないない!
I don't get it at all!
soredoshira
ソレドシラ
So re doh si la!
souzou ijou nante iu ka saiko
想像以上なんて言うか最高
It's better than I imagined, the absolute best!
aa da kou da ittetemo tomodachi (wasshoi!)
あーだこーだ言ってても友達 (わっしょい!)
Even if I say this and that, we're still friends. (Hooray!)
jou jou yuu jou banjin maji kaichou
じょーじょーゆーじょー万事マジ快調
Amazing friendship, the absolute best!
cha cha la cha la cha cha
ちゃちゃらちゃらちゃちゃー
Cha Cha La Cha La Cha Cha!
A local café had been renovated, so I tried going in.
Um...
What would you like to order?
An espresso T.
Nichijou 64
So, would you like a tall espresso?
Tall?!
Tooru?!
T is for tall?!
Well, I feel like having a tall espresso.
I'll have a small-sized T. espresso, then.
Do you want a short espresso?
A small short is fine.
All right.
Okay, an espresso...
Um... Hot or iced...?
I'll have it hot.
Um, well...
For a hot...
The sizes are...
Solo or... doppio.
D-Doppio?!
Doppio?!
What the heck is doppio?! Doppio, doppio!
What the heck is doppio?! What the heck?!
[All items on the menu are foreign]
Coffee of the Day
Oh, that's right. I forgot.
I think I'll get the coffee of the day.
Um...
Today's is espresso.
All right, I'll get that.
Well, then...
Solo...
Or doppio?
Or doppio, doppio, doppio?
That makes sense...
W-Well, then...
I'll leave it up to you.
Understood.
Sorry for the wait.
Here's your espresso.
It's tiny.
And it's really bitter!
Thank you for your business!
Well, I guess...
...I'll just use vending machines from now on.
Joy
Happiness
Celebration
Fortune
I gave a baseball glove to my grandson, Mii-chan, for his birthday.
Catch
Grandpa! I'm throwing it!
Hey, Mii-chan.
If you stand that far away, you won't be able to throw it over here.
My grandson is really cute, being this delighted...
Here it comes!
All right. Throw it with all your strength.
I should act cool for him tod-
Is he a pro?
Agonising!!
Made On The Chef's Whim
Piping-Hot Chicken Bar
50 Yen
New
Tiko Mart
Um...
Yes?
I'd like one of those "Agonising!",
piping hot chicken bars made on the chef's whim.
Miss, give me a break!
What is it, Kojirou?
That's right.
I have to hurry.
They'll close-
Mio-chan!
Y-Yukko, what's up?
Well, you disappeared right after class ended.
Oh, I see.
You don't need to be in such a hurry.
Let's go home together.
Well, sorry, I have some business to attend to.
Oh? What is it?
Uh, well, you see...
What's with that pompous style of speech?
Well, how should I say it...
What's wrong with it?
Could I have a moment?
Nichijou 65
I...
I'm sorry!
Hey, Yukko!
What have you done?!
I just apologised without thinking!
Well, that surprised me, too.
You suddenly apologised to me.
I'm sorry.
So, what did you want?
Well, lately, there have been cases of counterfeit bills being used on vending machines.
I was just wondering if you'd seen anyone suspicious around.
Well, Mio-chan?
I don't visit this area often.
According to witnesses,
the culprit has a beige bag with red lines on it.
There's no way that cou-
What's that conspicuous reaction for?!
Does she have some?
Does she have counterfeit bills?
No, there's no way...
Man, stop joking around, Mi-
Why is she preparing to be handcuffed?!
Hey, do you have some counterfeit bills?
Of course not!
She's just preparing to hit a volleyball.
Right, Mio-chan?
Well, whatever.
Let me check inside your bags, just in case.
Go right ahead.
Come on, Mio-cha-
She took it out!
She took out a counterfeit bill!
It's over!
I can't believe she actually had one!
Please let me off with this.
Please let me off with this!
Is this the only counterfeit bill you have?
It's not a counterfeit!
It's a real bribe!
I don't understand what you're saying!
Just give me your bag!
Why are you resisting?!
It belongs to a relative!
It's because this bag belongs to a relative!
You're an
idiot.
Ah!
Senpai...
I...
Idiot.
One! Two! Three! Four! Five!
Six?!
Eh?!
That's
not
true...
Eh?!
It seems
that
your fever
has gone
down.
That's
not
true...
The fever...
Eh?!
It seems
that
your fever
has gone
down.
That's
not
true...
The fever...
...was
one of
passion.
Passion.
Eh?!
It seems
that
your fever
has gone
down.
That's
not
true...
The fever...
...was
one of
passion.
Eh?!
It seems
that
your fever
has gone
down.
That's
not
true...
The fever...
...was
one of
passion.
...was
one of
passion.
Eh?!
It seems
that
your fever
has gone
down.
That's
not
true...
The fever...
...was
one of
passion.
Eh?!
It seems
that
your fever
has gone
down.
That's
not
true...
The fever...
...was
one of
passion.
Fever. Stupid. Stupid. Stupid. Stupid.
What happened?! A crime?!
Oh, Kojirou. There you are.
You look like you were just born.
Mio!
Aren't you going to eat?
It'll get cold!
It's
pretty
obvious.
Stop
Idiot
Toshi, what is this?
Hey, Mio!
Hey!
Victory
Kojirou is like this
Kojirou is like this.
What are you-
Well, that's all for today.
I've put up the topics for the midterm, so please go and check them.
Goodbye!
Nano-chan always leaves really early.
Goodbye.
Word Of The Day
If I have a weakness, I think I'll pretend to know about it.
Yukko, may I borrow an eraser?
All right.
Which one?
Mai-chan, may I borrow an eraser?
Wow!
Okay.
A character eraser?!
Nichijou 66
This won't erase very well.
Yukko, let me borrow an eraser.
You don't have one either, Mai-chan?
I guess I have no choice.
All right, which one?
This one.
Wow!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
The rule is one person at a time, so that doesn't count!
When did that rule get set?
All right, Mai-chan goes first.
Go ahead, look as closely as you want.
No, no!
Damaging attacks aren't allowed!
Mai-chan, you get 1-P.
1-P?
One penalty.
Does something happen if you get one penalty?
You have to treat me to 23 juices!
She still has a grudge about that?
Here, Yukko.
Baby Star.
Kan ji zai bo sa tsu gyou jin han nya ha ra mit ta ji shou kei go...
TL Note: Yukko is reciting the first part of the Hart Sutra, a Zen Buddhist chant.
That was close!
My hand was about to open!
It's "shou ken go", not "shou kei go".
I thought it would work.
That's two penalties.
Rock, paper, scissors.
How naive.
Of course I won't open the hand I'm holding it with.
This one.
Oh, crap!
I've been played!
Well then, Yukko, give me your eraser.
All right, all right.
Here, you win.
Character erasers doing wrestling moves?!
Thank you for your business!
The character erasers didn't work after all.
Right?
It's Nano-chan.
It is.
Nano-chan must be a robot after all.
Stop that.
Nano-chan doesn't like it.
Huh?
Why doesn't she like it?
Robots are amazing!
Love-Like
Hey.
Let's run.
The Truth in the 15th Year
Father.
Hey, Father!
Do you really go out into town wearing this?
It embarrasses me!
Embarrasses you?
You cowardly child!
Nichijou 67
Um... Shinonome... Shinonome...
Oh, here it is.
Shinonome Institute...
Wow!
It's an institute?
Cool!
Excuse me!
Huh?
Are they out?
Yes, I'm coming!
Sorry for making you wai-
W-What should I do?!
Why did Aioi-san come to my house?!
If she meets the Professor, she'll definitely find out that I'm a robot!
Coming!
Oh, good day.
Huh? Where's Nano-chan?
What should I do?
But wait,
maybe she just came over to give me a printout from school.
Hooray! Come in! Come in!
If that's the case, she doesn't need to-
I'm coming in.
This way.
Thank you.
I can't help that she came inside.
I'll just have to find out what she
wants before the Professor says any-
I'm hung-
What was that voice?
That's our cat, Sakamoto.
He talks.
Professor!
Really?!
Of course not!
Sakamoto-san, say "meow"!
Why do I have to-
It's "meow", Sakamoto-san.
M-Meow.
See?
Just a regular cat.
Sakamoto-san...
...we have a guest today, so go play outside, all right?
What was that?
Scary!
Meow.
I haven't introduced myself, have I?
I'm Aioi Yuuko.
Are you Nano-chan's younger sister?
No, I'm the Professor.
I created Nano.
Created?!
Amazing!
You're so small, but amazing!
Professor is a professor, after all.
No, Aioi-san!
She's the child of a relative of mine,
and they both work and don't come home until late, so I watch over her.
Right?
Isn't that right?
What are you saying?
Stupid!
I'm sorry.
I'll go make some more tea.
Oh, wait a minute, Nano.
If you want tea...
Go ahead.
Amazing! Amazing!
This one is a gun.
Cool!
Super cool!
I'm finished!
Next, we'll have a cool line competition!
Yay!
I'll start!
You're just joking, right?
Wake up!
Wake up, I said!
Oh! Cool!
Your turn, Professor!
What a pain!
Cool!
What did Aioi-san come here for?
They're on top of each other!
I give! I give!
So small!
So big!
Well, I should go.
She had no reason?!
Thank you for today.
Sorry for staying so long.
It's fine.
Um, Aioi-san!
Hm?
I'm actually studying magic, so, um,
I'm definitely not a robot or any-
Yeah, I know.
You're not a robot, Nano-chan.
You're Nano-chan.
Isn't that enough?
I came over today to say that.
I'd forgotten.
Well, bye.
Yeah.
Aioi-san!
Um...
If you'd like...
Yeah!
I'll come back!
Really?!
Hooray!
Let's draw pictures next time!
Yeah! I'll draw sharks!
Sharks, huh? Those are cool!
They are cool!
I love them!
You like sharks, huh, Professor?
I love sharks!
They're so cool!
Professor!
Let me join, too!
minna de utaou
みんなで歌おう
Let's all sing together
kokoro wo hitotsu ni shite
心をひとつにして
Unite our hearts as one
kanashii toki mo
悲しい時も
In times of sadness,
tsurai toki mo
つらい時も
and times of pain,
minna de utaou
みんなで歌おう
Let's all sing together
ookina koe wo dashite
大きな声を出して
Let your voice out loud
hazukashigarazu
はずかしがらず
Don't be shy
utaou yo
歌おうよ
Let's sing
kokoro moeru uta ga
心燃える歌が
A song that ignites your heart
uta ga kitto kimi no moto e
歌がきっと君の元へ
A song that will surely make it to you
kirameke sekaijuu ni
きらめけ世界中に
Out across the glistening world,
boku no uta wo nosete
僕の歌をのせて
I am sending a song
kirameke sekaijuu ni
きらめけ世界中に
Out across the glistening world,
todoke ai no messeeji
とどけ愛のメッセージ
I hope my message of love reaches.
Oh, it's Sakamoto.
Bye.
Well, whatever.
"Plus screw" sounds neat, doesn't it?
TL Note: "Plus" is what Japanese call Phillips-heads.
It has a positive feeling.
It somehow makes you feel optimistic.
Next episode of Nichijou is episode 17.
Narration
Look forward to it!