Wow!
It's sparkling!
Hey, what are you doing?
Oh, Sakamoto-san.
Wait!
Don't go over there!
Sakamoto-san, your shedding has become worse these past few days.
You'll get fur on it.
What is it, girl?
Am I being a bother?
I need to change, so please step outside for a moment.
jou jou yuu jou banjin maji kaichou
じょーじょーゆーじょー万事マジ快調
Amazing friendship, the absolute best!
na na na na na na na
ななななななな
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
hai! icchaimashou!
ハイ!言っちゃいましょう!
All right! I'll say it!
kimi wa best best friend
キミはベストベスト フレンド
You are my best, best friend!
(furai!) chotto fuzakete mitara
(フライ!) ちょっとふざけてみたら
(Fly!) When I joke around a bit,
(shain!) motto fuzake kaeshite kuru
(シャイン!) もっとふざけ帰してくる
(Shine!) you joke around more in response.
(La La La) ikogochi ii ttara arya shinai
(ラーラーラー)居心地良いったらありゃしない
(La La La) Nothing is better than this!
(wai!) iya na koto attatte
(ワイ!) 嫌なことあったって
(Why!) Even if something bad happens,
(fain!) sokkou wasurechaunda
(ファイン!) 即効忘れちゃうんだー
(Fine!) I immediately forget about it!
(La La La)
(ラーラーラー)
itsudatte jan jan yarimasho
いつだって、じゃんじゃんやりましょ♪
Always keep it going!
24 jikan issho demo mondai nai
２４時間一緒でも問題ない
Being together 24 hours a day isn't a problem.
marude futago ka oyako ka clone saibou
まるで双子か親子かクローン細胞
Just like twins, or a parent and child, or clone cyborgs.
kore ja me ga sumu hitsuyou wa nakunakunai!?
これじゃ目が澄む必要はなくなくない!？
Then isn't there no reason to clear your eyes?
sore to kore to wa mattaku mattaku betsumondai
それとこれとは まったくまったく 別問題
Those are completely, completely different issues.
(faito!) kenka shichatta toki mo
(ファイト!)喧嘩しちゃった時も
(Fight!) Even when I get in a fight with you,
(daun!) kanari hekonda toki mo
(ダウン!)かなり凹んだ時も
(Down!) even when I get really down,
(shai!) hitori de itai you na toki mo
(シャイ!)一人で居たいような時も
(Shy!) even when I feel like I want to be alone,
futokizukeba chikaku ni iru shinaba morotomo
ふと気付けば 近くに居る 死なば諸共
before I realise it, you're right there; we'll be together even in death!
nande daro
なんでだろ
I wonder why it is.
soba ni itainda
そばに居たいんだ
I want to be with you.
kimi to issho nara
君と一緒なら
When I'm with you,
tokei hyakubai soku
時計百倍速
time goes a hundred times faster!
tanoshii na
楽しいな
It's fun, isn't it?
tanoshisugirunda
楽しすぎるんだ
It's way too fun!
sasuga saikou friend
流石 最高 friend
As expected of my best friend!
Hey! na na na na na na na
Hey! ななななななな
Hey! Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
nannanoyo
なんなのよー
What is it?
yabai synchro
ヤバいシンクロー
The synchro is amazing!
itsumo oosawagi
いつも大騒ぎ
Always making an uproar,
kanari gokinjo meiwaku
かなりご近所迷惑
bothering the neighbours a lot.
ima nanji
今何時
What time is it now?
ato ne yorereihifu
あとねヨレレイヒーフ
And then yo de le hi hoo!
wake wakannainai
訳分かんないない!
I don't get it at all!
soredoshira
ソレドシラ
So re doh si la!
souzou ijou nante iu ka saiko
想像以上なんて言うか最高
It's better than I imagined, the absolute best!
aa da kou da ittetemo tomodachi (wasshoi!)
あーだこーだ言ってても友達 (わっしょい!)
Even if I say this and that, we're still friends. (Hooray!)
jou jou yuu jou banjin maji kaichou
じょーじょーゆーじょー万事マジ快調
Amazing friendship, the absolute best!
cha cha la cha la cha cha
ちゃちゃらちゃらちゃちゃー
Cha Cha La Cha La Cha Cha!
Nichijou 56
Sakamoto-san, please look at this!
It's a perfect fit!
Well, of course!
It was made just for you, so of course it would fit!
How is it?
Well, it looks good.
Not like that, not like that!
Do I look...
...like a normal girl?
Well, I guess you look like any other girl.
Sakamoto-san!
Whoa!
I love you so much, Sakamoto-san!
Oh, you'll get fur on it.
What's with you?
It's school!
I might be able to make some friends!
There's no flow to this conversation!
Hey, Nano-chan, do you want to go eat ice cream on the way home?
Yes, I'll go.
Then, after that, want to go sing karaoke?
Oh, but... I've never been to one before.
I'll teach you how, so let's all go together!
Oh, well, then...
Things like that!
Good morning, Nano.
Oh, Professor!
Good morning!
Please look at this, Professor!
How does it look?
Does it look good on me?
Um...
Yeah, it looks cool!
Professor!
Those pyjamas look good on you, too, Professor!
Are they cool?
Professor, you're very cool!
Isn't it the same as every other day?
Sakamoto!
Sakamoto's cool, too!
Handkerchief, check; student card, check;
textbooks, check; notebook, check; pencil box, check;
mechanical pencils, check; pencil lead, check!
All right.
I didn't forget anything.
Professor?
You forgot something.
Huh?
What is it?
When you get hungry...
Oh!
Snickers!
Professor!
I've prepared breakfast and lunch and put them both in the kitchen,
so please eat them.
I'll also bring in the laundry when I get back,
so you don't have to do anything.
Hey, about what time does school end?
Around 3:30, I guess.
I need to do some shopping for dinner on the way back,
so I'll probably be home around five.
Five.
Huh, didn't I already tell you?
Five is already night time.
Yes, but it's because of school.
Well, I'm going no-
Um, Professor?
I changed my mind!
What?
Just a bit earlier, you said I could go!
I don't want you to go!
No way!
I'm going to be late!
Please give me back my bag!
Ah, my left hand!
Stop being unreasonable!
Professor...
Then how about this?
For dinner tonight, I'll make Professor's favourite omelette rice!
And on my way back, I'll buy some shark castella!
I'll also add some strawberry juice.
Well...
Well?
The Akutagawa Prize, too?
T-That's not possible!
I was worried how that would turn out for a bit,
but I'm glad I got Professor to cooperate.
And now, I've taken the first step towards being a regular person.
Crap!
I've completely forgot!
The key on my back!
What should I do?
Things that we think are cool!
All right.
Let's do it!
Yeah!
A motivated senpai!
What should I do?
It's not like I can come up with an answer,
no matter how much I think about it.
And now I'm here.
And now I'll introduce a transfer student.
Shinonome-san!
Yes!
I knew it!
Everyone noticed my key!
Shinonome-san, could you write your name?
My key is getting a ton of attention...
I need to say something about it!
My name is Shinonome Nano!
And you see, this key is...
The truth is...
It got stuck in me on the way here!
Oh no!
That caused even more attention!
Um, well, you see...
The truth is...
...I was kidding!
Oh no, why am I correcting myself?
What should I do?
It's not like my big toe changes into a USB drive if you turn it...
...or anything robotic like that!
It's no good!
Fortune Telling
Tell me tomorrow's weather!
Nichijou 57
Hey, Sekiguchi.
Go
Soccer
Club
Don't just sit there reading books.
Play something with me!
Go Soccer Club - Club President
Daiku Kenzaburou
2nd Year
I even bought The Game of Life...
Go Soccer Club - Club Member
Sekiguchi Yuria
1st Year
I'm so bored.
Since we're the Go Soccer Club, maybe I'll solve some Go problems.
Even if I can't play Go...
Excuse me.
Is this the Go Soccer Club?
Yeah.
I would like to join.
I'd love for you to!
What's your name?
I'm Sakurai Makoto, a first year.
I see!
I'm a second year and the president of this club, Daiku Kenzaburou!
And this is another first year, Sekiguchi-kun.
Well, sit down!
Ah, sure.
So, what do you want to do?
Want to play Life?
Um, don't you practise?
Huh?
For Go Soccer.
Actually, Go Soccer is just something that I made up.
We don't actually do that.
It's more of a recreational club where everyone can have fun.
I see...
But I was in the Go Soccer Club back in middle school.
Huh?
I didn't know there was a Go Soccer Club at this school!
You know, there were those large banners for it,
and that's how I found out.
I was actually the MVP in middle school!
Curious
Shinonome-san!
Oh, yes?!
Um, it has really been bugging me, but...
...the thing on your back...
Um, well, you see...
Nichijou 57.5
Well, what kind of things did you do in the Go Soccer Club?
It's a bit difficult to explain in words...
I'll show you my practise routine.
First, lifting.
After lifting, Go stones!
And then...
After Go stones, One-Man German!
This is it! The Avalanche Joseki!
TL note: "Avalanche Joseki" is a common starting sequence of moves in Go.
Three-Star Set!
TL note: "Three-Star Set" is a move that takes the two corners and the middle of one side of the board.
Good heavens...
Go
Soccer
Club
I half-heartedly made this club, and now...
It's become interesting!
Shoes
Hey, wait up!
What's got into you all of a sudden?
Where are you going, Buddy?
Word Of The Day
Sakamoto!
No, wait, idiot!
Stop!
What is it, you ask? It's going around in circles.
Buddy
Nichijou 58
I made such a big mistake on the first day.
I bet everyone is thinking I'm strange.
Oh, Nano-chan, you have a bento today, huh?
Y-Yeah.
That looks delicious.
Do you always bring a bento?
Yes, I do!
Because it's normal.
I'll let you see this.
It's cool,
isn't it?
Mio-chan, sorry for the wait.
You're so slow, Yukko.
Lunch break is about to end.
Sorry.
On the way,
I had to chase down a car and a dog to get my shoes back.
I don't really know the whole story, but that sounds serious.
Well, the product was safely recovered.
Huh? Where's your lunch?
I ate it on my way here.
Oh, what did you eat?
Twice-cooked pork.
Whoa!
Twice-coo- Oh well, I guess it's okay.
Hey, Nano-chan, want to come eat with us?
Huh?
Tell us more about yourself.
Okay.
I wonder if they think I'm a normal kid.
Is it possible that they want to become friends?
Hey, that thing on your back, Nano-chan...
This is definitely not anything strange...
It's like you're a robot!
No!
What kind of stupid things are you saying?
Sorry, Yukko is an idiot.
Oh, we don't have much time.
Nano-chan, sorry. I guess we have to eat quickly.
Let's see.
Hey, Yukko.
This is...
It's fried mackerel.
But what I ordered was...
Yeah, fried mackerel, right?
It was fried noodles!
Maybe I misheard you?
Please forgive me.
This isn't that cute of a problem!
It's a serious problem!
Yeah, they're pretty similar.
TL note: "Saba" = "Mackerel", and "Soba" = "Noodles"
There's only a one-letter difference.
Even so...
This will just have to do...
Where's the rice?
Hm? What do you mean?
I'm talking about white rice!
Oh, that's all there is.
How am I supposed to eat this on its own?!
But you're the one who asked for fried mackerel.
I said fried noodles!
I said...
...fried...
...noodles!
Oh, I see!
This is the kind of thing you could use as material for your blog!
I don't have a computer!
Geez!
You don't have to get so worked up.
I'll go buy it again, just give me money.
Why do I have to pay again?!
That's because I don't have any money.
Fine, just hurry up and go buy it for me.
Lunch is about to end.
Okay, okay!
Nothing but...
I have nothing but a peso!
I have nothing but a peso from Argentina that I was keeping as a souvenir.
What?
An Argentinian peso!
Argentinian peso?
Besides, Yukko, you made the mistake, so you should pay!
But I used up all my money buying my own lunch-
Then what am I supposed to do with my lunch?!
Um, well...
How about the mackerel?
Mackerel?!
Mackerel?
I've always been annoyed by you.
You're always asking me to show you my homework.
Why don't you do it on your own for once, you idiot?!
Isn't my being an idiot completely
unrelated to you not having any lunch?
It's completely related!
Then tell me how!
You misheard it because you're an idiot!
Huh?!
Hey, everyone mishears things!
You're so cold-hearted, nagging me about it!
Not having a lunch is a life or death situation!
But I guess an idiot can't understand that!
I'm not an idiot!
You admitted that you were a moron earlier!
I'll never show you my homework again!
That's fine!
But I won't let you copy my homework if you forget yours.
Who would want your crappy homework?!
Besides, you mistook my order, and you haven't even apologised!
Bow down to me!
All right.
If I bow down to you, is it all right?
I'm extremely sorry to have caused you inconvenience!
There, I apologised!
Is that all right?
That's not bowing down!
That's right.
It wasn't. I was just bending forward!
Why won't you bow down to me?
It's because I've snapped!
Besides, you're the moron, Mio-chan.
What were those strange drawings?
Oh.
Those strange drawings...
Stupid! Those were...
What were those drawings?
I don't get them!
They were weird! Very odd!
Are you an idiot?!
Are you an idiot, idiot, idiot?!
What are you saying?
You're the idiot that did those idiotic drawings, aren't you?!
Here, why don't you just hurry up and eat the fried mackerel you ordered?!
I ordered fried noodles!
Bow down to me and apologise!
Hang your head low!
I've already bought it, so I can't do anything about it!
Be a human being and apologise, you worthless person!
All right, then!
I'll show you!
A true bow!
This is a true bow!
Where is your apology for the fried mackerel?
You're supposed to apologise when you bow!
Say that you're sorry for getting me fried mackerel!
Hurry up and say it!
Say that you're sorry for being a moron!
Say it from the pits of your heart,
you scum of a human!
Come on! Hurry up!
Say it already, you moron!
Apologise already, you idiot!
Scum! Idiot! Moron!
Geez!
You're so annoying with all the "morons"!
What do you know about me after only knowing me for half a year?!
Same goes for you!
What do you understand about my drawings?!
I do understand!
You're so good at drawing,
so why don't you just become a manga artist?!
What are you saying?
Are you a moron?
Huh?
The one who says "moron" is the moron, you moron!
Didn't you yourself say "moron"?
I did not!
Yes, you did!
But I don't dislike that part of you.
What are you talking about?
Even though you're so smart...
Shut up, you... comedic genius.
What are you talking about?
Even though you're so good at drawing...
Shut up!
You're such a fast runner.
You're really smart!
You're an optimist!
You're actually pretty smart!
That's amazing!
Go Soccer Club
A Tale of Go
Stones and Balls
Adolescence
Go Soccer Club
A Tale of Go
Stones and Balls
Senpai, this is so frustrating!
Don't cry!
You still have next year.
I'll definitely win for you!
Yeah!
That was in the past.
Hey, Nano, was school fun?
Well, let's see...
A lot of things happened, but how do I say it...
Say it? Say it?
I thought that friends are really amazing!
That's awesome!
Hey, I don't get it.
Professor!
Yes?
Please remove this key on my back!
No.
Why is that?
It causes a lot of problems at school!
Today, someone thought that I was a robot!
I can't make any friends this way.
Yes, you can, because you're cute.
No, I'm not cute!
The key is cute.
Let's hurry up and eat.
Professor!
ima watashi no negai goto ga
いま 私の 願いごとが
If I could have a wish granted right now,
kanau naraba, tsubasa ga hoshii
かなうならば 翼がほしい
I would want wings.
kono senaka ni tori no you ni
この 背中に 鳥のように
I want white wings attached to my back,
shiroi tsubasa tsukete kudasai
白い翼 つけて下さい
like a bird.
kono oozora ni tsubasa wo hiroge
この大空に翼をひろげ
I want to spread my wings...
tonde yukitai yo
飛んで行きたいよ
...and fly into the open skies.
kanashimi no nai, jiyuu na sora e
悲しみのない 自由な空へ
I want to flap my wings towards...
tsubasa hatamekase yukitai
翼はためかせ 行きたい
...that free sky which doesn't know sadness.
I'm a soccer ball.
I'm always being kicked, kicked, kick-kicked around everywhere!
And then, I sleep!
The next episode is Nichijou 15.
Narration:     Chiba Shigeru
Be prepared!