Summery
Sold Out
Wow, it sure is hot.
It's hot!
Tanaka-kun, the only thing you've said so far is that it's hot.
It's already hot enough, so if you say it more, it's going to feel hotter.
I ban you from saying, "It's hot".
Okay, okay.
Well...
It sure is summery!
Summery... Summery...
Just kidding...
But it really sure is summery!
It's way too summery!
Summery!
This guy... I have no choice but to punch him.
It really is much too summery!
It is really summery!
tatta ima hajimete kizuita
たった今 初めて気づいた
I just realised it for the first time
koi ni ochita no dana
恋に落ちたのだな～
That I had fallen in love~
nijyuuyo jikan kimi kimi kimi
24h キミ☆ キミ☆ キミ☆
Twenty-four hours a day thinking of you, you and nothing more than you!
ishiki sezaru o emasen
意識せざるをえません!
It's something I wasn't consciously aware of
nanka (nanka) itsumo to chigau
なんか (なんか) いつもと違う
Somehow (somehow) I'm feeling different from the usual
kimi to (futari) gikochinai kaiwa
キミと (二人) ぎこちない会話
With you (the two of us) and our dull chatter
masaka (ryouomoi) iya kataomoi
まさか (両思い) いや 片思い
Don't tell me (mutual love?) Nope, it's a one-sided crush
yabai shisen acchatta
やばい! 視線合っちゃった!
This is bad! Our gazes met!
nani nani kono doki doki
なになに?! このドキドキ?!
What, what? Why is my heart pounding like this?
shikoukairo guccha guccha konsen
思考回路 ぐっちゃぐっちゃ 混線・・・
Did a short circuit just make a mess out of my mind?
konna koto hajimete dayo
こんなこと 初めてだよ
This is my first time... feeling like this...
netsu demo aru no kana
熱でもあるのかな～
I wonder if I have a fever~
kyuutenchokka irasshatta koigokoro
急転直下 いらっしゃった 恋心
Suddenly and precipitately, love has arrived.
acchuuma kao hakka de makkakka
あっちゅうま 顔 発火で まっかっか
Instantly igniting my face into a bright red
ba ba baka na te ga furueruzo
バ・バ・バカな?! 手が震えるぞ
T-That's stupid?! My hands are shaking
kore ga zoku ni iu koi nano
これが 俗に言う 「恋」 なの?!
Is this really what they call "love"?
yayayacchatta kaiwa kami makuri
やややっちゃった 会話 噛みまくり
I-I did it! A conversation filled with stutters
kimazui chinmoku mamimumemo
気まずい沈黙 マミムメモ
This awkward silence... *mumble mumble*
kimi no (kimi no) kimochi shiritai yo
キミの (キミの) 気持ち 知りたいよ
Your... (Your...) I want to know your feelings.
kakakata kataomoi
カカカタ☆カタオモイ
O-One-sided love
hatsukoi itsumo no tsuugakuro
初恋! いつもの通学路
First love! The usual way to school
pika pika hikaru I do fall in love
ピカピカ光る I do fall in love!
The shining light. I do fall in love!
sora mo tobesou sa
空も飛べそうさ
I feel I could fly towards the sky
kakakata kataomoi
カカカタ☆カタオモイ
O-One-sided love
Shiny!
Everything looks so very bright today!
The air, the people and even this classroom.
The reason for that is...
I did my homework today!
I'm going to show it off to Mio-chan.
Huh...
Huh?
W-What?
Nichijou 48
It's not here!
No way!
That's not possible!
I did my homework!
Why? Why? Why? Why?
Why isn't it here!?
I guess I can just copy it.
Mio-chan...
Wait...
Wait a second...
Today's homework was a worksheet!
Now I've done it.
What is it, Yukko?
You're all worked up this morning.
I forgot my homework.
I hope aliens invade.
You forgot it again?
Don't underestimate me!
I did my homework, but I lost it!
I'm not underestimating you...
You're talking about the Languages Worksheet, right?
Maybe it's stuck between something.
Look for it more carefully.
I already tried looking for it just now.
It's definitely no-
Huh?
Whoa...
Whoa!
Neighbourhood Association
Daihuku Fair
My God!
What do you mean, Daihuku Fair!?
What do you mean, a fair...?
Well, you know...
Maybe there are extra copies of the worksheet in the teacher's desk.
Ah!
You're kidding!
There were actually extra copies?
Daihuku Fair
Damn it!
You're going back to get it?
You're not going to make it back in time!
Even so I'm...
I'm still going!
Hey, class is about to start.
Go sit down.
Idiom
Spin, spin, spin...
Turn, turn, turn...
Don't be hasty, and things will turn.
Nichijou 49
I had to stand outside again...
Why am I always forgetting my homework?
And I actually did my homework this time. I just forgot it!
God is just playing with me.
Business Cards
Sakamoto.
Hm?
Here's my business card.
Professor
What is this?
What am I supposed to do with this?
Professor
What am I supposed to do?
Vending Machine
Cold~               Cold~               Cold~               Cold~
Sports Cider
-cider
Apple
Black
New Product!              New Product!
Oh, I'm sorr-
What is it, Tachibana Misato?
What?
There are some new products out,
so I was just wondering what I should get!
I see.
Then, this one is-
Why should I listen to what you have to say!?
-not very good, so you should have chosen the one next to it.
Sorry for disturbing you.
I didn't buy this because you recommended it!
I heard there were going to be stands set up in our neighbourhood,
Nichijou 50
so I decided to check them out.
My main objective is the shooting stand.
I've only seen it on TV, so I'm excited for today!
That being said, I only have 500 yen today.
I wonder if this is enough.
One try: five million yen!
Lucky!
Five hundred yen exactly.
I wanted to eat yakisoba, but I came here for this today!
There are only caramels and eggplants.
Excuse me...
Is this all you have?
What do you mean by that?
We only carry high-quality and branded products!
Well, I did already pay.
I need to bring something home.
Young lady, you can't just hit something high-tier right off the bat!
It's not going to fall that easily!
High-tier?
You're going to have to hit something easier first.
The only other option I have to hit is the caramels.
What!?
That was so close!
The caramels must be completely stuck.
You were only a few more millimetres away from knocking it over!
Young lady, you're pretty good at this.
Are you possibly some undercover gun professional?
Just kidding!
This eggplant isn't even budging!
Hey, what's with the sad face?
I bet you think I'm ripping you off.
Although this stand looks pretty shabby,
I guarantee that we are happy and fair!
No matter how you look at this, there's something wrong!
What is that?
Look at that!
I can definitely see a nail there!
A nail!
This is definitely cheating!
Hey, why are you being unresponsive!?
More importantly, these things shouldn't be allowed!
You were so happy a few moments back!
I bet you're doing something with the caramels, too!
Why are you faking sleep?
What am I supposed to hit with my last one?
Never come back.
What the heck?
Things you think are cool!
Mio-chan!
Here I go!
Whoa.
Yeah!
Nice catch!
Oh, superball!
Things you think are cool!
Crap, that was so close!
Wow!
Oh, slipstream!
Thank you.
This is fun. It's been a while since I've gone to an amusement park.
You've got to go sometime.
I want to buy some juice, so could you give me my wallet?
Oh, right.
I'm holding onto it for you.
Well, thanks.
I felt like I'd lose it if I kept it.
That's true.
What?!
What? What? What?
I'm sure it was in here.
It seems like I dropped your wallet.
Nichijou 51
I know!
Let's check the lost and found!
It might be there!
How much was in it?
4016 yen.
That's really specific.
Lost and Found
Um, I'm looking for a brown wallet that has a snake skin inside.
Oh, I've received that.
Thank goodness they had it.
I really wasn't sure what I was going to do for a bit there!
Attention: a child with denim shorts,
a denim shirt and a denim hat is looking for her mother.
If this is your child, please come to the information centre.
I'm really bad with haunted houses!
A mummy!
All right.
I'm taking it.
Coffee house
Daiku
That's three lattes to go, correct?
Um, I'd also like one of these, one of these and one of these.
Izumi
Um, I'm sorry, but could you say the name?
I'm Sakurai.
No, not that...
Oh, I see, I'm sorry.
I'm Izumi.
Sakurai Izumi.
No, I didn't mean your family name...
I've always been told that both of my names sound like family names.
No, by name I meant the product name.
What do you mean by product name?
I'm sorry.
I don't really understand.
Um, I'm sorry.
Family
Restaurant
oriental fair
Ah, that was good.
Chopstick Rest
I ate a lot.
All that's left is to wait to order dessert.
Yep.
Then I'll do it, too.
I'm done!
Me, too.
Whoa, nice.
Way to go, Mai-chan.
How about you, Yukko?
You done?
A crane?
Shinonome Institute
Nano! Look, look! Ta-da!
Nichijou 52
I put one on, too.
Now, we match!
That's true.
I'm Nano for the whole day today,
so you'd better not call me Professor.
All right, Nano-chan.
That was quick!
Professor, are you already done?
Ah, Nano, you just said Professor!
But you already took off the key.
I'm just taking a bit of a break right now.
But I'm Nano for today.
All right.
Oh, Professor-I mean Nano-chan, would you like to play together?
Okay.
Play what?
We'll play swap, where you become me and I become you.
Let's do it!
Then, Professor-I mean Nano-chan, please put on the key.
All right!
And I'm the Professor, so take off my key.
I can't do that.
Hey, hey, what are we going to play? Cards?
Oh, these snacks taste good.
I was saving those snacks!
But right now, I'm the Professor.
I don't get it!
I became Nano, so Nano became the Professor and ate the snacks!
Nano should just be Nano!
Crabs...
Then, since I've returned to being Nano, I'll go buy food for dinner.
Shinonome Institute
I'll go, too!
I'm not buying any snacks.
Buy chocolate sharks and strawberry juice!
I won't.
Buy them!
Hey, don't forget about my food.
The Shinonome household was at peace again today.
Delicious
Now hiring part-time!
Boredom Game
The next person that says something in English loses.
Okay.
Ah, Mio-chan, you just said something in English.
You didn't say "start", so I'm "safe".
Then I'll say a bunch of English before saying "start".
Do you know a lot of English?
Okay.
Word Of The Day
Carbonation is tickly, so it makes me feel awake.
Finally
Huh?
I was asleep...
Oh, Sleeping Beauty woke up without a kiss.
Why?
What do you mean, "Why"?
asa okite hao migai te
朝起きて 歯を磨いて
Woke up in the morning, brushed my teeth
attoiuma gogo juu ji
あっという間 午後10時
In the blink of an eye, it's 10pm
kyou mo takusan waratta naa
今日も たくさん 笑ったなぁ
Today, we laughed a whole lot
takusan tokimeita naa
たくさん ときめいたなぁ
We had a great time
tomodachi to baka mitai ni sawai deru toki ni mo
友達と バカみたいに騒いでる 時にも
At times, with my friends, acting like fools, being noisy
chirachiratte me ga au
チラチラって 目が合う
Fluttering, our eyes met.
guuzen dayo ne
…偶然、だよね。
It's a coincidence, right?
hatsukoi nante ie nai
初恋なんて言えない
I wouldn't call this my first love
kyara janai n da mon
キャラじゃないんだもんっ!
It's not my character.
nee ashita mo aeru yo ne
ねえ あしたも会えるよね?
Say, will we be able to meet again tomorrow?
mabuta o tojiru to
まぶたを 閉じると
As my eyelids close
kirakira kimi darake
キラキラ キミだらけ
I see you sparkling all over the place
kyou mo tanoshikatta ne
今日も 楽しかったね
Today was fun, too, wasn't it?
aa koi shite n da naa
あー 恋 してんだなぁ
I'm in love~
ureshii na ureshii na
うれしいな うれしいな
So happy, so happy
hajimemashite koi gokoro
はじめまして こいごころ
It is my pleasure to meet you, my new-found love.
ashita mata aeru ne
あした また あえるね
Surely, we'll meet again tomorrow~
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
Have a good night
yume de sugu aeru ne
ゆめで すぐ あえるね
We'll meet immediately in our dreams
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
So have a good night
Welcome back, Master.
I'm the cider.
I put a spell on these bubbles to make it taste good.
Next time on Nichijou, Episode 13.
Narration:      Satomi Koorogi
Look forward to it!