Graffiti
It's been getting colder lately.
Sakamoto...
Sakamoto-san...
Hold on!
Hold on a second!
Calm down, you two!
At least explain what's going on!
jou jou yuu jou banjin maji kaichou
じょーじょーゆーじょー万事マジ快調
Amazing friendship, the absolute best!
na na na na na na na
ななななななな
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
hai! icchaimashou!
ハイ!言っちゃいましょう!
All right! I'll say it!
kimi wa best best friend
キミはベストベスト フレンド
You are my best, best friend!
(furai!) chotto fuzakete mitara
(フライ!) ちょっとふざけてみたら
(Fly!) When I joke around a bit,
(shain!) motto fuzake kaeshite kuru
(シャイン!) もっとふざけ帰してくる
(Shine!) You joke around more in response.
(La La La) ikogochi ii ttara arya shinai
(ラーラーラー)居心地良いったらありゃしない
(La La La) Nothing is better than this!
(wai!) iya na koto attatte
(ワイ!) 嫌なことあったって
(Why!) Even if something bad happens,
(fain!) sokkou wasurechaunda
(ファイン!) 即効忘れちゃうんだー
(Fine!) I immediately forget about it!
(La La La)
(ラーラーラー)
itsudatte jan jan yarimasho
いつだって、じゃんじゃんやりましょ♪
Always keep it going!
24 jikan issho demo mondai nai
２４時間一緒でも問題ない
Being together 24 hours a day isn't a problem.
marude futago ka oyako ka clone saibou
まるで双子か親子かクローン細胞
Just like twins, or a parent and child, or clone cyborgs.
kore ja me ga sumu hitsuyou wa nakunakunai!?
これじゃ目が澄む必要はなくなくない!？
Then isn't there no reason to clear your eyes?
sore to kore to wa mattaku mattaku betsumondai
それとこれとは まったくまったく 別問題
Those are completely, completely different issues.
(faito!) kenka shichatta toki mo
(ファイト!)喧嘩しちゃった時も
(Fight!) Even when I get in a fight with you,
(daoun!) kanari hekonda toki mo
(ダウン!)かなり凹んだ時も
(Down!) even when I get really down,
(shai!) hitori de itai you na toki mo
(シャイ!)一人で居たいような時も
(Shy!) even when I feel like I want to be alone,
futokizukeba chikaku ni iru shinaba morotomo
ふと気付けば 近くに居る 死なば諸共
before I realise it, you're right there; we'll be together even in death!
nande daro
なんでだろ
I wonder why it is.
soba ni itainda
そばに居たいんだ
I want to be with you.
kimi to issho nara
君と一緒なら
When I'm with you,
tokei hyakubai soku
時計百倍速
time goes 100 times faster!
tanoshii na
楽しいな
It's fun, isn't it?
tanoshisugirunda
楽しすぎるんだ
It's way too fun!
sasuga saikou friend
流石 最高 friend
As expected of my best friend!
Hey! na na na na na na na
Hey! ななななななな
Hey! Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
nannanoyo
なんなのよー
What is it?
yabai synchro
ヤバいシンクロー
The synchro is amazing!
itsumo oosawagi
いつも大騒ぎ
Always making an uproar,
kanari gokinjo meiwaku
かなりご近所迷惑
bothering the neighbours a lot.
ima nanji
今何時
What time is it now?
ato ne yorereihifu
あとねヨレレイヒーフ
And then yo de le hi hoo!
wake wakannainai
訳分かんないない!
I don't get it at all!
soredoshira
ソレドシラ
So re doh si la!
souzou ijou nante iu ka saiko
想像以上なんて言うか最高
It's better than I imagined, the absolute best!
aa da kou da ittetemo tomodachi (wasshoi!)
あーだこーだ言ってても友達 (わっしょい!)
Even if I say this and that, we're still friends. (Hooray!)
jou jou yuu jou banjin maji kaichou
じょーじょーゆーじょー万事マジ快調
Amazing friendship, the absolute best!
cha cha la cha la cha cha
ちゃちゃらちゃらちゃちゃー
Cha Cha La Cha La Cha Cha!
Mai-chan, put tones here.
And Yukko, you write the page numbers with this pencil...
...and then colour in the hair.
Okay.
Amazing!
Naganohara-san, you draw manga?
Oh no, it's not a big deal.
She used to hide the fact that she drew from everyone.
It doesn't really matter any more.
Is that true?
Well, yeah.
Well, I submitted something a while ago,
and I got a reply saying they'll be waiting for more.
That's when I started to think it was odd to hide it.
They probably thought you had talent!
No way.
Could you let me see for a second?
Nano-chan?
Sorry about that.
You don't have to read it.
Nano-chan!
Sorry, let me go get some air...
Are you okay?
Do you want me to go with you?
No, you guys came to help Naganohara-san on her draft,
and I'll be right back anyway.
Nano-chan must have it tough.
Oh, crap!
It's already this late!
I don't have time to waste like this.
We're going to finish it all up before Nano-chan comes back.
Tomorrow is the deadline for submission!
Roger, roger!
I'm a pretty good artist myself!
I'll speed through this!
Operation commence!
Just kidding.
Nichijou 83
Hey, Yukko, stop slacking already.
Wow, you're fast.
Let me check it over.
If you
struggle
too much,
I'll blow
you away.
Hey!
I'll blow you away.
Hey, Mai-chan, what did you draw?!
Kuuya Shounin.
TL Note: This is a classic sculpture from the Kamakura period of a monk chanting sutras.
That's not what I'm asking.
Why did you draw it?!
Because the blank space in the background was weeping.
What do you mean?!
Just hurry up and erase it with white-out.
I just need tones there.
I don't want anything fancy.
That was possibly the worst pain I've ever experienced.
I guess I'll shade the hair.
Um...
Oh yeah,
tell me right away if you make a mistake or something.
Right away?!
Here!!      Lip Robber~
Tonight:
Shikotama
Don't make a funny
lip expression.
This isn't good!
I need to hurry and fix it!
Here.
Oh, you finished.
You didn't draw anything extra this time, did you?
If you
struggle
too much,
I'll graveyard you.
Hey!
Graveyard?!
What is this?
A graveyard.
Idiot!
This is supposed to be a really nice palace in Daikanyama!
I told you not to draw things!
Why do you keep drawing things?!
Because there was space there.
I can't take this!
Just erase it.
I just want you to erase it.
Only erasing! Nothing else!
Got it.
I was able to make him cool-looking.
I made him cool-looking, but...
But maybe...
It doesn't look right?
Showing her this would be like throwing oil on a fire!
I'm done.
Did you actually erase it this time?
Don't do anything unnecessary.
If you
struggle
too much,
I'll graveyard you.
Hey!
Why?!
What is this?!
I erased it.
Should I erase you?!
Why do you keep doing these things?!
Because this manga isn't very interesting.
That's too straightforward!
I'll give you a new page,
so just lay out frames in the same way as that page.
I got it.
Nothing but the frames!
Helvetica
Standard
Ten seconds.
Twenty seconds.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Time's up.
I can't get it right!
It's no longer a problem of whether it looks like the character or not...
Who the heck is this?!
Showing her this would be like throwing oil on a fire!
Finished.
It's just the frames, right?
Once upon a time, there was an old man and an old lady.
The old man went to gather firewood in the mountains.
A soldier came out of a peach.
I don't care!
Mai-chan, go read a book.
Got it.
This...
It's no good!
The more panicked I get, the more messed up it gets.
This isn't good.
What should I do?
What should I do?!
Mai-chan!
Leave it to me.
Can she do it?
She can draw?
Mai-chan!
That's right.
Of course not...
There's no way she cou- huh?
Mai-chan?!
This is good!
Amazingly good!
It's too good.
But this...
It's way too far off!
I'll go back to that time...
...when I didn't know left from right,
and everything felt fresh.
I'll go back to that time...
...and express it.
Express myself.
I'm sorry!
Please re-draw it!
I don't have any more manuscript paper!
Morals
Um, don't run in the hallwa-
Sasahara!
Word Of The Day
Damn. I can't get it off.
There is no point.
Nichijou 84
Gotcha!
Oh, Naganohara-san!
What are you doing in a place like this?
Oh, me too!
Oh, well...
What were you doing?
Nothing, really...
Actually...
...even though there's a tournament coming up,
I can't concentrate very well.
When you were in high school, Naganohara-san,
did you ever have that kind of problem?
Like, feeling the protective gear becoming incredibly hea-
Not even listening...
Shiitake Zanmai sure is a weird manga!
She's completely worthless at anything other than kendo.
What? Are you talking about something interesting?
It's nothing.
Don't you have a national tournament coming up, Naganohara-san?
Oh, that's right.
Right? Even Mihoshi says she has to train-
I came to do some shopping.
Huh? Wait...
I'll give you these crackers.
Bye.
What was with her?
Nee-chan!
What are you doing, hanging out around here?
Naganohara-san was just here.
No way!
But tomorrow's the national tournament!
It's tomorrow?!
Did she say anything?
Not really...
Oh, she left these.
Want some?
Sure.
Whoa, so red.
It sure is red.
So spicy!
Melon Bread
Expiration date is marked on the bottom of the bread.
Expir
Love-Like
Hey, hey, Mio-chan.
Take a look at this.
What do you think?
I thought I should change my image every now and then.
Does it look good?
Yeah.
It's like you.
Are you ready yet?
Nichijou 85
Not yet!
Are you ready yet?
Ready!
All right!
Ready or not, here I come!
Where are you, Professor?
I'm ready!
Sakamoto-san, I found you.
Whim can be a frightening thing.
Sorry.
I normally wouldn't play along with such a kid's game,
but I guess I have to play with you from time to time.
What are you doing?
Hurry up and continue!
Shabba-dabba-doo!
Professor!
Where are you?
Hey! Kid!
Professor!
Where is that kid hiding?
I can't find her anywhere.
I definitely won't be found here.
She's a kid, so she might be hiding somewhere outside.
That's true.
Let's take a short break.
Okay.
But we might never find her.
P-Professor!
Did you make this?
But why did you come out?
It's not hide-and-seek like that.
Geez.
I started to think that you'd never find me.
Well, that's true.
Professor.
Did you blow your nose?
Oh, Professor. You're just making more laundry.
Well, I guess I have no choice.
This time, I'll be it.
Let's get started!
I'll wash it for you.
You'll ruin it, so don't worry about it.
I won't ruin it.
No, you'll definitely ruin it.
Eh? It'll be fine.
Pyon is like this!
And what did you say then?
Well, listen-
I won't listen!
Nichijou 86
See, I'm glad that you wanted to help out,
but you're the one who spilled the ink, Yukko.
I had no paper left,
so I asked you to go buy some for me, and what did you say?
At that time, what did you say?
Well then...
Should we leave who goes to buy it...
...up to this?
How impertinent!
You should go buy it, since you spilled the ink!
I still have work to do!
Well, whatever.
When you finally agreed to go, what did you say?
Hey, hold on-
What did you say?!
Hey, hey.
How old do I look?
I don't care!
If you don't hurry up, the stationery shop will close!
Why are you asking that now?!
You look your age!
Well, whatever.
You were finally leaving.
What did you say when you were putting on your shoes?
It sure is cold today.
By the way, I feel a bit sick.
Make a sacrifice for the sake of justice!
How long do you intend to stall?!
Besides, it's not cold at all today!
Well, that's all fine.
But what did you end up buying?
Sweet
Sake
What's wrong with you?!
I asked for some manuscript paper!
Um, well...
Stop with the lame jokes!
When I said that, what did you pull out?
Here.
No thank you!
I'm in a lot of trouble!
What do you expect me to do?!
When I said that, what did you say?!
Forgive me, hyacinth.
Hyacinth!
This isn't something you can brush off!
Where the heck did "hyacinth" come from?!
But still, I believed in you!
You bought the manuscript paper for me!
It was just a stupid gag!
But...
...when I asked you to hurry up and take out the manuscript paper,
what did you say?!
Mio-chan, cryocinth your head.
TL Note: Hyacinth is a pun on "hiyasu", which means to cool.
Hyacinth!
Which one of us should cool her head?!
Which one of us is a hyacinth?!
Well, I'm telling you...
So I asked you one more time!
You had bought the manuscript paper, hadn't you?
And what did you say?!
Plz forgive me.
What happened to "hyacinth"?!
I don't even care about the hyacinth!
I need the manuscript paper!
And what did you finally take out?
Here.
Yeah, yeah, this.
I guess I'll write a pornographic story.
You twit!
How thick-skulled can you be?!
What are you trying to do?!
When I asked that...
The truth isn't always correct, right?
It is!
Since you weren't helping at all, I asked Nano for help...
I asked her to buy some manuscript paper.
But then...
She was absorbed in it!
Her eyes were glued to it!
She was really happy!
I had no choice, so I went to ask Mai-chan!
Mai-chan, could you buy some for me?
Going
Home
She had left!
She left without a word!
She always goes at her own pace!
Mai-chan's pace is really Mai pace!
And then,
when you saw that note, Yukko, do you remember what you said?
Going
Home
Is this a prank by God...
Going
Home
...or a trick by the devil?
It's a trick by the devil!
It was already a trick by the devil when you two came over!
And then you...
I don't get it!
I'm tellin-
I don't want to hear your excuses!
You stupid twit!
No, no, no, see...
I don't want your "sees" or your "peanuts"!
You...
Stupid peanut!
I'm telling you, this...
I keep telling you-
Manga
Manuscript Paper
Forgive me, hyacinth.
ano subarashii ai wo mou ichido
あの素晴らしい愛をもう一度
Let me have that wonderful love one more time
inochi kakete to chikatta hi kara
命かけてと　誓った日から
Ever since the day I swore to put my life on the line
suteki na omoide nokoshite kita no ni
すてきな想い出　残してきたのに
I've had many wonderful memories
ano toki onaji hana wo mite
あの時　同じ花を見て
That time we saw the same flower
utsukushii to itta futari no
美しいと言った二人の
We both said it was beautiful
kokoro to kokoro ga ima wa mou kayowanai
心と心が　今はもう通わない
Our hearts are no longer together
ano subarashii ai wo mou ichido
あの素晴らしい愛をもう一度
Let me have that wonderful love one more time
ano subarashii ai wo mou ichido
あの素晴らしい愛をもう一度
Let me have that wonderful love one more time
Manga
Manuscript Paper
Hello! I'm the gondolier of dreams: manga manuscript paper!
Now is the time to hold your head high and reach for your dreams!
Next time on Nichijou: Episode 21.
Narration:    Koyama Mami
I take walk-ins, too.