I was only the vice-captain at the time.
Flame Snake was the captain.
He was referred to as Enjya.
What?
I'm in search of that man myself!
That man who inflicted a wound upon me...
...the Flame Snake!
I want to burn that man.
That's all I wish for!
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君のそばにいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai ga bokura wo tameshitatte
どんな未来が僕らを試したって
No matter how the future tests us
kitto…
きっと…
I’m sure…
aa futari no unmei
ああ 二人の運命
Ah, it’s our destiny
meguriaeta no wa
巡り合えたのは
I was able to meet you
kimi no koe kikoeta kara
君の声 聞こえたから
Because I heard your voice
sou pinchi na dekigoto
そう ピンチな出来事
Yeah, even if crisis events
oshiyosete kite mo
押し寄せてきても
Press on at me
kimi to ireba norikoerareru
君といれば乗り越えられる
If I'm with you, then I can overcome them
tokimeki to makenki to
ときめきと負けん気と
Palpitations and competitive spirit
urahara de haraharasuru kedo
裏腹でハラハラするけど
Excite me on the contrary, but-
Stay with me
tada kimi o mamoritai yo
ただ 君を守りたいよ
I only want to protect you
tooi sekai de umareta futari da kedo
遠い世界で生まれた二人だけど
We were born in distant worlds
I say yes
zutto kimi no soba ni iru yo
ずっと 君の側にいるよ
I’ll be by your side forever
donna mirai mo kibou ni kaeyou
どんな未来も希望に変えよう
Let’s change any future into hope
Forever
The Flame of Atonement
They don't know that we're here.
That's the key to this surprise attack.
They're professionals!
Cheap tricks won't work against them!
You stay out of this!
But...
All right, let's come up with a plan.
Someone should rush in as a decoy.
Simply rushing in won't do.
We need the enemy to focus only on that person.
Hold on.
What?
I can bring an end to this matter.
So leave this to me.
Sensei.
Saito-kun, lend me a hand.
Just reminiscing gives me a chill.
The captain who razed Dungletale was amazing.
He burned the village instantly, without any change in emotion,
into ashes.
I was attracted to him because of his perfection.
So I ambushed him form behind.
A little mistake from the aberration that was my youth, I tell you.
"How strong is our captain? Is his strength real?"
I wanted to confirm his strength.
He was the real thing!
He burned me with ease!
What will you be using these for?
Just keep your hands moving.
Okay...
You said that in your world, everyone is equally skilled at using all technologies, correct?
Well, with some studying and training, yes.
I see. That's a wonderful thing.
I'd like to take a look at your world one day.
How long are they going to make us wait? Geez!
We need to hurry, or else everyone will...
Forget it, we'll go by ourselves!
Wait a while longer.
Fine.
It's done, Sensei.
Okay, let's go.
You're... insane!
Maybe I am.
Let us stop talking about the past now.
It's about time for negotiations.
Principal.
Send a messenger to Henrietta.
Have her sign a pledge in which she promises to withdraw her troops from Albion.
What?
An unconditional agreement to withdraw her troops.
T-That's impossible!
I don't have the right to make Her Highness do that!
You don't mind having your cute students burn to ashes?
Saito-kun, when you... head eastwards...
When you decide to go back to your world...
Yes?
Take me with you.
Saito!
Sorry to make you all wait.
What took you so long?
What's that?
I'll need to borrow everybody's strength.
What a stupid method.
Stop it, Julio-kun.
When the front line hears of this,
they'll respond with a full-scale attack.
You're only cornering yourself.
Albion doesn't think enough.
It looks like you have a death wish!
What's this?
What are these doing here?
Our top priority is to rescue everyone, okay?
Don't bother with the enemies!
Understood.
All right, now!
Now!
Gotcha!
Let's go, Tabitha!
No, don't fight with them!
You brats...!
Saito!
Agnes!
Looks like our strategy worked.
All right, get everyone out!
Kirche! Tabitha!
Nice try.
Don't tell me... your eyes...
Ever since my eyes were burned, they couldn't sense light.
How can you see, then...?
They say snakes perceive prey via their temperature.
Since I use flame, I started to get rather sensitive, too.
I can tell one person from another by their temperatures.
I want to smell it.
I want to smell the scent of you burning!
No...
Sensei!
Colbert-sensei!
Get away from my student.
It's you!
It's you, it's you, it's you!
This is the temperature I've been searching for!
I've been looking for you! How nostalgic!
Captain-dono!
What?!
You've... lost your ability to see?
Yes, thanks to you.
Colbert-sensei was... the captain?
Sensei...
Sensei?
You're a teacher?!
No wonder I never saw you in any wars!
I would've never imagined that you'd become a teacher.
You, who were once called Enjya!
En... jya?
Yes, he was referred to as Enjya the Flame Snake.
He's the one that burned everything, woman and child!
And he's the one who stole the light from both of my eyes!
As expected of my captain.
It looks like you haven't lost your skills.
That's right... that's how it should be!
Miss Zerbst. Take Miss Tabitha and get out of here!
Y-Yes.
Saito-kun, Miss Vallière, take everyone out of here.
Yes!
Hurry, Louise!
Um, the spell to undo a rope is...
I did it!
Wasn't it pure luck?
Well done, Louise.
This way!
Colbert is my foe.
The man who killed my father and mother.
The one who took everything away from me!
Die!
Agnes-kun!
Stay away!
Don't fuck with me!
I'll be the one to kill you!
Butt out, plebeian.
I have no business with you!
It's dangerous! Get away from me!
Never!
How does it feel to burn to death, Captain-dono?!
I've been waiting for this moment.
The day I burn you to death!
I thank you, Captain-dono.
Kam Diela...
I was able to become this strong because of my devotion towards exacting revenge upon you!
Dil Ryofu.
I would expect this much from you, Flame Snake.
I'm no longer the inexperienced lad I once was!
My flame...
...has surpassed yours!
You're no... d-different from before...
What?
You're still... so full of yourself!
Damn you!
Waz Wagaraz Wagaruze Winde!
Take this!
Take my village's rancour!
Are you all right?
I'm glad...
Why did you save me...
...that day you burned Dungletale?
I realised... my mistake.
Colbert-sensei!
Sensei!
Step away!
What do you plan on doing?
Don't get in my way!
Stop it, Agnes!
Please, stop!
Move!
I've lived only to see this day!
Twenty years...
For twenty years!
Stop it, Agnes!
Please stop, I beg of you!
Move!
Miss Zerbst.
Please... move...
Agnes-kun... has the... right... to... kill me.
Sensei...
Tye Gyoph.
Something's strange, Captain.
I don't see any signs of an epidemic here.
What?
It was then that I realised... the sin I had committed.
I always thought that... obeying orders was... the correct... thing to do.
But...
...that's wrong.
Even during war... killing a person is...
...a sin!
Agnes-kun, kill me.
But... make this your last... and... stop killing... any further.
Who do you think you are to tell me this?!
Agnes!
Stop it!
Don't get in my way!
Agnes... sheathe your sword.
Don't fuck with me!
He has passed away...
What...?
Agnes.
So this was where you were.
Take it.
A letter?
We found this when we were cleaning up Colbert's room.
I can't read it, though.
"Saito-kun, I am writing this letter with the
intention of giving it to you when you go to war."
I should tell you this:
I've once committed a sin.
In order to atone for my sin, I've devoted myself to research.
Recently, a thought has been crossing my mind...
...and that thought is, "atoning for sin is impossible".
So Saito-kun, I want you to promise me.
Don't get used to people dying.
Don't get used to fighting.
Don't get used to killing.
Saito-kun, you've told me many stories.
Stories of the world that you came from.
I want to see that world.
Please take me there some day.
That's all.
Thank you.
He's just rambling on...
Will you never be able to forgive Colbert-sensei?
How would I know?
Agnes...
Colbert-sensei wanted to go to your world, right?
He was a strange person, after all.
Don't cry.
I'm... not crying.
You don't have to hide it.
chanto koko ni ite watashi no chikaku de
ちゃんとココにいて! 私の近くで
Be right here! close to me
zutto watashi o itsumo itsumo mitsumete nasai
ずっと私をいつもいつも見つめてなさい
Always, always look at me at all times
yosomishiteta desho hoka no onna no ko
よそ見してたでしょっ 他の女の子
You looked away, didn’t you? At other girls
o-shiokisuru wa furari furari furachi na yatsu wa
お仕置きするわ　フラリフラリ不埒なヤツは
I’ll punish those who are wavering and insolent
Don't touch! kikanai kara ne iiwake wa
Don't touch! 聞かないからね　言い訳は
Don’t touch! Because I won’t listen to excuses
Touch me... tsukareta kara nee kata o kashite yo
Touch me… 疲れたから… ねぇ肩を貸してよ
Touch me… because I'm tired… Hey, lend me your shoulder
suki yo nante uso yo
スキよ　なんて嘘よ
I love you, it’s a lie
kirai sore mo uso da wa
キライ　それも嘘だわ
I hate you, that’s a lie, too
nai nai nai dame yo kanchigai
ないないない　ダメよ勘違い
Nay nay nay, it’s useless, it’s a misunderstanding
dakara suki yo nante iwanai
だから「スキよ」なんて言わない
So I won’t say, “I love you”
Non non non dokka e ittara
Non non non　どっかへ行ったら
Non non non, because I absolutely won’t forgive you
zettai ni yurusanai kara ne
絶対に　許さないからね!
If you go to somewhere else
datte
だって
But
honto wa dare yori soba ni itai no
ホントは誰より傍にいたいの
The truth is, I want to be by your side more than anyone else
ai no kusari de sanposhimasho
愛の鎖で　散歩しましょ!
Let’s go take a walk in chains of love!
Next Time
You dog!
We'll freeze to death if we crash into a snowy mountain!
What? Warm each other up with our body heat?
Zero no Tsukaima. Futatsuki no Kishi.
The Enemy at the Snowy Mountain.
The Enemy at the Snowy Mountain
If you want to meet me again next week, then sit tightly and wait!