Shinonome Institute
Nano!
Nano?
Nano~
Nano!
Yes?
Nano, Nano!
Nano!
Yes, yes.
It's Nyan~
Nano!
Look, look!
It's Professor, nyan~!
Nyan.
You too, Sakamoto... Look, look!
It's Professor, nyan~!
Professor.
That's probably... moe!
Nyan~?
Nyan~!
It's Professor, nyan~!
It's moe!
It's Professor, nyan nyan~!
It's Professor, nyan~!
It's moe!
It's Professor, nyan nyan~!
The Shinonome household was at peace again today.
tatta ima hajimete kizuita
たった今 初めて気づいた
I just realised it for the first time
koi ni ochita no dana
恋に落ちたのだな～
That I had fallen in love~
nijyuuyo jikan kimi kimi kimi
24h キミ☆ キミ☆ キミ☆
Twenty-four hours a day thinking of you, you and nothing more than you!
ishiki sezaru o emasen
意識せざるをえません!
It's something I wasn't consciously aware of
nanka (nanka) itsumo to chigau
なんか (なんか) いつもと違う
Somehow (somehow) I'm feeling different from the usual
kimi to (futari) gikochinai kaiwa
キミと (二人) ぎこちない会話
With you (the two of us) and our dull chatter
masaka (ryouomoi) iya kataomoi
まさか (両思い) いや 片思い
Don't tell me (mutual love?) Nope, it's a one-sided crush
yabai shisen acchatta
やばい! 視線合っちゃった!
This is bad! Our gazes met!
nani nani kono doki doki
なになに?! このドキドキ?!
What, what? Why is my heart pounding like this?
shikoukairo guccha guccha konsen
思考回路 ぐっちゃぐっちゃ 混線・・・
Did a short circuit just make a mess out of my mind?
konna koto hajimete dayo
こんなこと 初めてだよ
This is my first time... feeling like this...
netsu demo aru no kana
熱でもあるのかな～
I wonder if I have a fever~
kyuutenchokka irasshatta koigokoro
急転直下 いらっしゃった 恋心
Suddenly and precipitately, love has arrived.
acchuuma kao hakka de makkakka
あっちゅうま 顔 発火で まっかっか
Instantly igniting my face into a bright red
ba ba baka na te ga furueruzo
バ・バ・バカな?! 手が震えるぞ
T-That's stupid?! My hands are shaking
kore ga zoku ni iu koi nano
これが 俗に言う 「恋」 なの?!
Is this really what they call "love"?
yayayacchatta kaiwa kami makuri
やややっちゃった 会話 噛みまくり
I-I did it! A conversation filled with stutters
kimazui chinmoku mamimumemo
気まずい沈黙 マミムメモ
This awkward silence... *mumble mumble*
kimi no (kimi no) kimochi shiritai yo
キミの (キミの) 気持ち 知りたいよ
Your... (Your...) I want to know your feelings.
kakakata kataomoi
カカカタ☆カタオモイ
O-One-sided love
hatsukoi itsumo no tsuugakuro
初恋! いつもの通学路
First love! The usual way to school
pika pika hikaru I do fall in love
ピカピカ光る I do fall in love!
The shining light. I do fall in love!
sora mo tobesou sa
空も飛べそうさ
I feel I could fly towards the sky
kakakata kataomoi
カカカタ☆カタオモイ
O-One-sided love
Why is the Earth round?
Why do rockets fly?
Why do magnets pull toward each other?
Everything in this world can be proven by science.
Grave
In this world, there are talks about the afterworld,
ghosts, ghost stories and other spiritual phenomena.
There's no way those kinds of sleep-inducing things could be real!
Grave
It'd be bad if they were...
In other words...
Mt. Osore
I don't believe in spiritualists!
Nichijou 19
Using my day off, I spent 8 hours going one-way to Mt. Osore.
Getting closer to the summit, the beating of my heart increases.
I wonder if a spiritualist really exists here.
If so, where?
I wonder if she would live alone here.
Or...
Spiritualist
There she is!
A-All right!
Let's have her summon something already.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Um... Please summon some soap!
Ah, okay.
Bubble, it's Soap!
Mic test... mic test... mic test, test, test.
What's this sensation of helplessness?
Could it be there's someone called Soap...?
I-It's S-Soap.
No, there can't be.
What if I keep asking... Eventually, a contradiction point will appear.
I have a question.
What's the blood type of Soap?
Who knows?
Let's try a simpler person.
Excuse me.
Nobunaga... Please summon Oda Nobunaga!
Please give me a break.
Rejecting me before even trying to summon him?
No, she's old after all.
She has to look after her health.
I shouldn't scold her here.
Excuse me.
Let's go home.
Scolding people is not for me.
Just by knowing that, I should reap what I've sown.
Oh, Onii-san?
That'll be 5000 yen.
Daruma Otoshi
100 Points
Sneezing
No way!
...of men.
Nichijou 20
2nd Period
Self Study
Okay, here goes.
Rock, paper, scissors.
W-Whoa!
You got it wrong, Mai-chan! Didn't I just explain it?
You have to hit me if you win!
It's amazing. You've got incredible concentration.
In a way, it's even crueller than hitting me.
Listen.
As I've just explained,
when you lose, you defend. When you win, you hit. Okay?
Not now! Why did you hit me now?!
Because I won just then.
It wasn't now, was it? It was just then!
It's the moment!
Live for the moment!
We're that kind of living thing, you know!
First comes rock, next comes paper. Rockscispaper doesn't count,
rock, paper, scissors!
It's Nano, nyan~
Okay then, let's do it again.
Rock, paper, scissors.
You have zero motivation to play?!
You are a clown!
How much of a clown can you be?!
Something is coming... mentally.
Ah, hold on, Mai-chan.
There it is.
Mai-chan, w-what's with that?
I carved it.
Thank god!
I thought it had been reincarnated!
I will put this here.
Somehow, she looks really happy.
Ah, well, that doesn't matter. Let's start.
Okay. Rock, paper, scissors.
M-Mai-chan.
That's...
...rockscispaper...!
No way... such a brutal...
Seriously, Mai-chan, that doesn't count.
Rockscispaper doesn't count.
Also, hitting with the Buddha doesn't count either.
Okay, let's do it again.
First comes rock-
Rock, paper, scissors.
Mai-chan...
That, that!
That's it Mai-chan.
See, you can do it if you try!
Okay, let's do the next one.
First comes rock-
God is dead!
God has died.
Hey, why did you hit me?!
You did it properly just now!
How do I say it... Because I don't want to play.
Can I take a look at your Maitreya?
Sure.
Shinonome Institute
Then, I'll be going to the library to return the books!
Make sure you look after the house, okay?
Yes!
Nichijou 21
You can't have too much
ice cream and juice!
I wonder why Nano's daruma has only one eye...
That's it!
If Professor gave it another eye, Professor might get praised!
Or perhaps...
...Nano may say "it's okay to eat as many snacks as you like"!
I might've got it a little bit wrong...
It's Nano's, so what do I do...
Oh!
She might get mad at me!
You won't get any snacks for a long time!
Um... here... and here...
What are you doing?
S-Sakamoto, what should I do? This...
What is this?
What were you doing?!
This is hers, right?
You see, it didn't have an eye...
It can't be helped, try doing what I say.
I'm home!
Stay in good health.
Ah, Sakamoto!
Ah, Sakamoto-san, you're going out?
Professor, I'm home.
I'm late because it took me some time to choose some new books to borrow.
What are you doing?
Eh, what's with that stomach of yours?
It's not "Ehehe"!
I-It'll be born!
No, no, no, that's not possible.
It'll be born!
Um, is this some kind of game?
No, it's not!
Nano's little brother is about to be born!
It's your little brother.
T-This isn't good.
Kokkuri-san
Mio-chan, Mio-chan!
What is it?
Let's play Kokkuri-san!
Hm? What's that?
Oh, you don't know it?
I don't.
Okay, I'll briefly explain it then.
First, you need to prepare a piece of paper by drawing a gate in the middle like this,
then you write "yes", "no" and the 50 characters of the Japanese syllabary on the page.
Mm.
Although in some regions, you're supposed to draw a fried tofu on the paper instead...
For now, let's just keep it simple.
Mm.
Then, for Kokkuri-san to be able to come in,
you open the north-facing window.
Mm.
Then you set this 10-yen coin on the gate.
We put both of our fingers on it and ask a question that you want to know about,
such as a person's secret, or who someone likes, or something that's bothering you.
Mm.
If you do that, the 10-yen coin will move all by itself
and Kokkuri-san will answer your question.
Isn't it amazing?
There are some taboos, though.
First, don't do it by yourself.
Second, don't mess around when doing it,
or else you will be haunted by spirits...
Also, if you stop halfway through, you will be haunted, so be wary.
I see.
It's something like that.
It's a pretty dangerous game, don't you think?
Anyway, why don't you give it a try?
It's okay.
What?
Nichijou 22
Um... well, that's all for today.
Tomorrow we have a mini-test, so everyone please study for it.
Eh? Postpone it, postpone it!
Wouldn't the outcome be exactly the same for you no matter how long it's postponed?
Mini-test
English
Probably.
Sakurai-sensei.
What is it, Aioi-san?
There's something I want to ask you.
Yes?
Um... about the test we had before.
What is this?
Um... That's a fly.
No, not the answer.
I'm talking about this thing that looks like it'd vanish
pretty easily. Did you draw it, Sensei?
Yes. I thought that if I included some
pictures, the test might be a little easier...
You draw very interesting pictures, Sensei.
I'm sorry.
I'm bad at drawing, so it was hard to understand wasn't it?
Ah! That's right.
Could you include a picture that I've drawn next time?
I'll draw something really cool!
Okay.
Ah, Mio-chan!
Listen, listen.
My picture's going to be in the test.
Eh? Why?
Sensei said she'll put them in.
If you draw something right now,
she'll definitely put yours in, maybe.
It's "definitely", but it's still "maybe"?
Uh... you're not going to draw something?
No, I'm fine.
I'll pass on that.
Besides, I have to return this.
Oh, really?
All right!
One cool guy-
Something like this?
Uwah! He's so cool!
Aioi-san, you're so good at drawing.
You have my respect.
No, I'm not that good... I'm awesome at it!
Just kidding.
Incidentally, his name is Samidare George.
That's even cooler.
Cool?!
Hold on a second you two.
Normally, what you'd call cool is...
Piss off
...something like this, right?
Piss off!
Uwah! Amazing!
It's just like a manga.
Naganohara-san, do you draw manga or something?
No- Well, only a little.
Amazing!
Please show me next time.
That is, well...
Eh? You can't?
I want to see it.
Please show it to me.
Eh... Ah... But...
Give that back to me!
Mine are much cooler.
You just ripped off mine!
I didn't rip it off.
Yes, you did.
This kind of rip-off is known as a homage.
You just admitted it!
Uwah! So cool!
Anything works for you?!
Well, how about this?
Glasses!
An intelligent and cool look that appeals to all women of any era!
Glasses, huh?
Is his eyesight bad?
He should just wear contacts.
These two just don't get it!
Then I'll do... this!
They're underneath his ears!
Anyhow, this is a rip-off too!
Tsk, tsk, tsk... they're sunglasses.
Uwah! So cool.
You're okay with it?!
Then... how about this?
A butler!
From picking you up to serving you tea... you'll feel like a real lady.
Feel the magic of Darjeeling!
Glasses again?
I'm sorry, I don't really get it.
She didn't listen to my advice about contacts...
Mio-chan, you don't get it, do you?
You see, what's really cool is...
...this!
It's floating!
No, hold on... This... It's running?!
Uwah! It looks so fast and cool!
I can't believe this!
What cool is...
Rationally speaking...
If you think about it rationally...
Cool is...
...this, right?
Oh no...
Just kidding!
In front of the 1-Q lectern
Naganohara Mio:
Sunk
Word Of The Day
I drew this while listening to jazz music.
The Next Day
Morning!
Ah! Sensei, good morning!
Who are you calling sensei?!
Well then, I'll hand out this morning's mini-test,
so please pass them around.
I'm done for...
I wanted to keep secret the fact that I draw.
I can't believe I drew a picture like that...
English
Anyway, even though I lost control, only going to that level was a blessing amongst all the misfortune.
It was pretty close.
Yukko's going to tease me for two or three days though...
No, no!
I have to keep my chin up and move forward.
Mio-sensei, hurry up.
Um... begin!
Mio-sensei!
asa okite hao migai te
朝起きて 歯を磨いて
Woke up in the morning, brushed my teeth
attoiuma gogo juu ji
あっという間 午後10時
In the blink of an eye, it's 10pm
kyou mo takusan waratta naa
今日も たくさん 笑ったなぁ
Today, we laughed a whole lot
takusan tokimeita naa
たくさん ときめいたなぁ
We had a great time
tomodachi to baka mitai ni sawai deru toki ni mo
友達と バカみたいに騒いでる 時にも
At times, with my friends, acting like fools, being noisy
chirachiratte me ga au
チラチラって 目が合う
Fluttering, our eyes met.
guuzen dayo ne
…偶然、だよね。
It's a coincidence, right?
hatsukoi nante ie nai
初恋なんて言えない
I wouldn't call this my first love
kyara janai n da mon
キャラじゃないんだもんっ!
It's not my character.
nee ashita mo aeru yo ne
ねえ あしたも会えるよね?
Say, will we be able to meet again tomorrow?
mabuta o tojiru to
まぶたを 閉じると
As my eyelids close
kirakira kimi darake
キラキラ キミだらけ
I see you sparkling all over the place
kyou mo tanoshikatta ne
今日も 楽しかったね
Today was fun, too, wasn't it?
aa koi shite n da naa
あー 恋 してんだなぁ
I'm in love~
ureshii na ureshii na
うれしいな うれしいな
So happy, so happy
hajimemashite koi gokoro
はじめまして こいごころ
It is my pleasure to meet you, my new-found love.
ashita mata aeru ne
あした また あえるね
Surely, we'll meet again tomorrow~
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
Have a good night
yume de sugu aeru ne
ゆめで すぐ あえるね
We'll meet immediately in our dreams
oyasuminasai
おやすみなさい
So have a good night
Pleased to meet you.
I'm onomatopoeia!
You can't help but say "Cock-a-doodle-do" in Japanese even though it's not Japanese.
Narration:     Koyama Rikiya
The next Nichijou is the sixth. Look forward to it.