Do you think she can do maths in her head?
Whom?
I'm talking about Nano-chan.
Nichijou 59
Since she's a robot, don't you think she might have robotic features?
What are you talking about?
There's no way she's a robot.
But she has a key on her back.
You think she's a robot just because of that?
There's no way that's true.
No, but think about it.
She's definitely a robot.
Isn't it amazing?
Like, honestly,
isn't it amazing?!
What is that?
There's no reasoning behind that.
And so, I want to investigate to see if Nano-chan is a robot.
No, you shouldn't...
It's all right.
I have a plan.
jou jou yuu jou banjin maji kaichou
じょーじょーゆーじょー万事マジ快調
Amazing friendship, the absolute best!
na na na na na na na
ななななななな
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
hai! icchaimashou!
ハイ!言っちゃいましょう!
All right! I'll say it!
kimi wa best best friend
キミはベストベスト フレンド
You are my best, best friend!
(furai!) chotto fuzakete mitara
(フライ!) ちょっとふざけてみたら
(Fly!) When I joke around a bit,
(shain!) motto fuzake kaeshite kuru
(シャイン!) もっとふざけ帰してくる
(Shine!) You joke around more in response.
(La La La) ikogochi ii ttara arya shinai
(ラーラーラー)居心地良いったらありゃしない
(La La La) Nothing is better than this!
(wai!) iya na koto attatte
(ワイ!) 嫌なことあったって
(Why!) Even if something bad happens,
(fain!) sokkou wasurechaunda
(ファイン!) 即効忘れちゃうんだー
(Fine!) I immediately forget about it!
(La La La)
(ラーラーラー)
itsudatte jan jan yarimasho
いつだって、じゃんじゃんやりましょ♪
Always keep it going!
24 jikan issho demo mondai nai
２４時間一緒でも問題ない
Being together 24 hours a day isn't a problem.
marude futago ka oyako ka clone saibou
まるで双子か親子かクローン細胞
Just like twins, or a parent and child, or clone cyborgs.
kore ja me ga sumu hitsuyou wa nakunakunai!?
これじゃ目が澄む必要はなくなくない!？
Then isn't there no reason to clear your eyes?
sore to kore to wa mattaku mattaku betsumondai
それとこれとは まったくまったく 別問題
Those are completely, completely different issues.
(faito!) kenka shichatta toki mo
(ファイト!)喧嘩しちゃった時も
(Fight!) Even when I get in a fight with you,
(daoun!) kanari hekonda toki mo
(ダウン!)かなり凹んだ時も
(Down!) even when I get really down,
(shai!) hitori de itai you na toki mo
(シャイ!)一人で居たいような時も
(Shy!) even when I feel like I want to be alone,
futokizukeba chikaku ni iru shinaba morotomo
ふと気付けば 近くに居る 死なば諸共
before I realise it, you're right there; we'll be together even in death!
nande daro
なんでだろ
I wonder why it is.
soba ni itainda
そばに居たいんだ
I want to be with you.
kimi to issho nara
君と一緒なら
When I'm with you,
tokei hyakubai soku
時計百倍速
time goes 100 times faster!
tanoshii na
楽しいな
It's fun, isn't it?
tanoshisugirunda
楽しすぎるんだ
It's way too fun!
sasuga saikou friend
流石 最高 friend
As expected of my best friend!
Hey! na na na na na na na
Hey! ななななななな
Hey! Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
nannanoyo
なんなのよー
What is it?
yabai synchro
ヤバいシンクロー
The synchro is amazing!
itsumo oosawagi
いつも大騒ぎ
Always making an uproar,
kanari gokinjo meiwaku
かなりご近所迷惑
bothering the neighbours a lot.
ima nanji
今何時
What time is it now?
ato ne yorereihifu
あとねヨレレイヒーフ
And then yo de le hi hoo!
wake wakannainai
訳分かんないない!
I don't get it at all!
soredoshira
ソレドシラ
So re doh si la!
souzou ijou nante iu ka saiko
想像以上なんて言うか最高
It's better than I imagined, the absolute best!
aa da kou da ittetemo tomodachi (wasshoi!)
あーだこーだ言ってても友達 (わっしょい!)
Even if I say this and that, we're still friends. (Hooray!)
jou jou yuu jou banjin maji kaichou
じょーじょーゆーじょー万事マジ快調
Amazing friendship, the absolute best!
cha cha la cha la cha cha
ちゃちゃらちゃらちゃちゃー
Cha Cha La Cha La Cha Cha!
Nano-chan.
Ah, yes!
Here's a question.
What is 3260 plus 260 divided by 320?
Eh?
Um...
Three-thousand two-hundred and sixty plus...
If it's too hard for you...
You can use your features.
Wait, Yukko.
That was your plan?
Sorry about that.
Well, I guess I'll do just that.
I got her!
It's an abacus.
Well, let's see...
Start by clearing it...
How basic!
One, two, three...
She's a b-beginner!
Three-thousand two-hundred and sixty plus...
She's not using the abacus!
Hey, Yukko?
Aioi-san?
Are you okay?
I'm all right.
I get the feeling that was a correct answer in various ways...
Geez.
I told you she's not a robot.
Are you okay?
Would you like something to drink?
Could it possibly be...?
Could it be...?
Oil has come!
It's soup!
Yukko!
Um...
Minakami-san.
Here.
She threw a fastball!
Oil!
You can have it.
Oh, really?
Thank you very much.
She'll drink it!
It was a miss!
I want you to have this, too.
A curveball!
A monkey wrench!
Oh, thank you.
This'll come in handy.
She'll eat it!
It was a miss!
Hey, you two should cut this out.
You're troubling Nano-chan.
It's skinship.
Well, I just wanted to become friends...
Geez.
This is a step in the wrong direction.
Sorry...
Geez...
No, don't worry about it.
But...
Since you don't need this soup, I'll drink it.
See? Nano-chan says so, too.
Geez. What are you talking about?
Did my crown come off?
Put yourself in Nano-chan's shoes and think about it!
I want to know.
How are they able to make something of such high quality?
Shinonome Nano, who transferred here the other day...
Her existence...
Yes, that key...
No matter how you look at her, she is a robot.
Why hasn't she been shown to the scientific community?
Why is she attending this school as if it isn't a big deal?
I want to research.
I want to research her.
And I want to make her mine.
Nichijou 60
Oh, Nakamura-sensei.
I brought the books you asked for.
She's here!
All right!
Jump into action!
Well, then, I'll excuse myself.
Shinonome, hold on a second.
Would you like some coffee?
Oh, no, I don't want to trouble you.
Don't make excuses like that.
I was just making some.
It's a thank you for bringing me the books.
Just drink some.
Well, then, just one cup.
First, I'll test whether or not sleeping medicine works on her.
If that doesn't work, I'll use the "Short Circuit-kun" that I created yesterday on her from behind.
Here, drink up.
Thank you very much.
I drank it!
I must endure.
I must endure!
Well, I'll excuse myself now.
At least...
Use Short Circuit-kun...
Short Circuit-kun...
Oh, that's right.
I heard the science teacher, Nakamura, fainted.
She sure faints a lot. Nakamura, that is.
That was pretty close today.
But Aioi-san and Minakami-san seem like really good people.
Maybe they could become my friends...
Take this!
Rocket punch!
This is the maximum power of a rocket punch!
Shinonome Institute
Professor, Professor!
Oh, Nano, welcome back.
Huh? Why did you say it twice?
Wait. More importantly,
can you hurry up and take this off of me?
Nichijou 61
Why?
Because it's hard for me to sit in a chair.
Everyone looks at me like I'm strange,
and on top of that, I was recorded on video.
I had to try to cover it all up.
But it's cute.
But people won't treat me like a
normal girl if I have this key attached.
You'll definitely get popular.
No, I don't want to.
I just want to live a normal school life...
Why did you put a weapon like this on me?
I'm glad it didn't come out at school.
Why don't you want people to find out you're a robot?
It's obviously because robots aren't cute.
Robots are cute!
They are not cute.
They're cute!
This gun is, too?
It's cute!
The toe USB, too?
Sweets coming out of my forehead, too?
It's cute!
Geez!
Professor, you're a mad professor!
It's cute!
I want to be more normal!
Wow, it's a chikuwa!
TL Note: Chikuwa is a tube-shaped fish cake.
Chikuwa sure is delicious.
Three, two, one...
Daihuku Fair ①
All right, we have daihuku!
They're cheap!
It's daihuku!
Oh, Nakanajou-san.
Good work!
Daihuku don't talk!
I'm sorry... but I...
Daihuku Fair ②
I'm not doing this half-heartedly!
I'm putting my life on the lin-
Don't make me say it so many times!
Crap, I failed last time.
The sleeping medicine scheme was badly thought out.
Nakamura-sensei, Short Circuit-kun
After all, she is a robot.
She probably won't lose consciousness without a really powerful hit.
And that's where this comes in!
I wasn't able to test it out before.
For use against robots, Short Circuit-kun!
Using this, I can knock her out.
Today, I'll finally capture her.
It's almost time.
Run away!
Oh, Nakamura-sensei!
Hey, you can't leave your top button undone!
Jeez. You're annoying.
I can do it if I want to!
No, you can't!
I may not look like it, but I'm actually in charge of student guidance!
Seriously?
How did you get that position?
How rude!
Here, let me do this.
I'll do it myself.
This is embarrassing.
Um...
What's going on?
Nichijou 62
Well, Mako-chan, you can't fix it yourself, can you?
You really are annoying.
"Mako-chan"?
Come on!
What are you doing?
You
Stop it!
I'll button it for you.
Button It
"You"? "Button it"?
Don't hang around me at school!
H... "Hang around"?!
What kind of relationship do they have?
See? It came off.
That's just perfect.
Well, I have stuff to do, so bye.
Hey! Hold on!
You'll be laughed at if you look sloppy like that.
What's with you?
You're always sloppy at home, aren't you?
At home!?
S-Sloppy-looking!?
Sloppy-looking, yes!
No, that's not right!
Am I an idiot for getting excited like that?
And why is a Chinese dress sloppy!?
It's just a normal sloppy-looking appearance!
What am I thinking?
I should be ashamed as a teacher!
A normal sloppy-looking appearance...
Sloppy-looking!
Good enough!
What's good enough, idiot?!
Well, I'm leaving now.
Hey, what about the button?
Oguri Cap is like this!
Idiot!
Well, I'm leaving now.
Hey, what about the button?
I'll go after them!
Takasaki-sensei!
Nakanojou-kun passed out in the science room!
I need you to come immediately!
Wait!
Drop it!
All right.
Listen up.
Yes?
Nakanojou hasn't passed out!
That's right!
He might just be taking a nap!
But his eyes have gone completely white!
Draw them in!
I'll try it!
Wait!
W-What is going on there?!
Watching out for illicit relationships is more important than someone passing out!
That's an educator's... Um, well, what it means to be an educator!
That's Sakurai-sensei's younger brother!
Let's go.
Okay.
All right. Here it goes.
I'll hurry on.
That's what being a teacher is about.
It's this way!
Love-Like
Taking Home
Next stop: Kokusadame Station, north entrance.
The bus will stop.
Hey, you're not getting off there.
I just wanted to press the button.
Didn't you press it earlier?
Someone got off then, so it was fine in the end, right?
I see. So it's like helping someone out.
See? Someone got off here.
Well done!
Hey Mum, do we have a tear-off calendar?
Isn't there one in the cupboard?
Shinonome Institute
Professor! Professor!
Oh, Nano. Welcome back.
Could you please just remove this key?
It causes so many problems for school life!
For the high jump, all I could do was a belly roll!
I got called off-sides in soccer, too.
It can be taken off.
Nichijou 63
You should have told me earlier if it could be taken off!
Understood.
I'll take it off right now.
Every day of youth is important.
But now, I can finally live as a normal high schooler.
Could you please hurry and take it off?
Stare
Professor, that's...
Could it possibly be...
I took it.
TL Note: "Toru" means "to take off" as in to remove, but also "to take" as in a photo.
Oh, no!
Please don't make stupid jokes like that!
Sorry, sorry.
So, can this key be removed?
Well...
I don't want any more stupid jokes!
So, can you take it off or not?!
I can.
I've taken lots of keys before.
Yours can be easily...
Taken.
Coin! Coin! Coin! Zoom!
You went "Coin! Coin! Coin!"
Then, you went "Z-Zoom!"
Professor, I have a question.
My breath...
I can't breathe...
I laughed too much.
Professor, I've been having really unnatural reactions all day today.
Have you done anything?
To me?
Actually, yesterday, I added a reaction feature to you.
What kind of messed up feature is that supposed to be?!
Why would you add a feature like that?
Because it seemed funny.
Reaction!
Goal!
I'm going to die.
If this continues, I'm going to die from these reactions.
See? Isn't it funny?
It's not funny at all!
Professor, putting the key aside,
could you please remove this feature?
That'll be a hundred yen.
toki ni wa nazeka oozora ni
ときにはなぜか　大空に
Sometimes you just get the desire
tabishite mitaku naru mono sa
旅してみたく　なるものさ
To travel for some reason.
kikyuu ni notte dokomade ikou
気球にのって　どこまでいこう
Let's ride a blimp to a faraway place,
kaze ni notte nohara wo koete
風にのって　野原をこえて
Ride on the wind, pass over fields.
kumo wo tobikoe dokomademo yukou
雲をとびこえ　どこまでもゆこう
Pass through clouds, let's keep on going forever,
soko ni nanika ga matteiru kara
そこに　なにかが　まっているから
Because something is waiting there.
La La-LaLa LaLaLaLaLaLa
ラン ラランラン ランランランランランラン
La La La-LaLa LaLaLa
ラン ラン ラランラン ランランラン
La La-LaLa LaLaLaLaLaLaLa
ラン ラン ラランラン ランランランランランラン
La La La-LaLa LaLaLa
ラン ラン ラランラン ランランラン
LaLaLaLa
ララララ
La
ラー
Word Of The Day
This is my maximum capacity.
I'm Oil.
I've been told that I'm slippery.
But I'm oil, so I can't really help it.
I'm told that a lot by my boss.
Who's the boss of Oil?
Next episode of Nichijou is episode 16.
Narration:      Sakakibara Yoshiko
Be prepared.