Inside the human body,
roughly 37.2 trillion cells
work energetically,
DENDRITE
All day every day.
ANTIBODY ENCYCLOPEDIA
24 hours and 365 days.
WHITE BLOOD CELL
They are all working very hard.
UNDER CONSTRUCTION
PLATELETS
This is the inside of a human body.
What is this place?
Nobody's around. What's going on?
I'm so scared!
Th-There it is!
CELL
What is this thing?
Behind me, too!
Somebody help me!
Target sighted!
Hey, are you okay?
WHITE BLOOD CELLS (NEUTROPHILS):
Their main task is to eliminate
foreign substances from outside,
such as bacteria and viruses.
Neutrophils comprise over half
of the White Blood Cells in the blood.
Thank you very much!
Uh, hey. You're welcome.
By the way, what were you doing
in a place like this?
Where are you from?
M-My name is Naive T Cell.
I'm an underling with the T Cell battalion,
a-and I'm on patrol.
But there are tons of zombies here.
What kind of place is this exactly?
NAIVE T CELL:
An immature T Cell
which has never
encountered an antigen.
Naive T Cell.
An immature T Cell
which has never encountered an antigen.
I mean, how'd you come through the wall?
It's called "migration."
MIGRATION
To move freely through the system.
These guys are just former common cells.
The thing is,
it seems like they got infected.
EPISODE 3:
INFLUENZA
Influenza.
They've been infected by a virus.
A virus?
Right.
An influenza virus.
INFLUENZA VIRUS:
A virus that can trigger influenza,
an infectious disease.
Falls into three main categories,
A, B and C. Causes symptoms
such as fevers over 100 degrees,
headaches, joint pain and muscle cramping.
The influenza virus.
A virus that can trigger influenza,
an infectious disease.
Falls into three main categories, A, B and C.
Causes symptoms
such as fevers over 100 degrees,
headaches, joint pain and muscle cramping.
When an influenza strain
that never infected humans
mutates to the point
that it does infect them,
it is called a "new influenza strain."
See, they bind to the bodies of cells
and then multiply.
Our only hope is to kill them
before their numbers swell any further!
You're my backup!
Huh?
Hey!
No way can I do that!
I can't take on a virus!
H-Hey! Listen, you!
You're a T Cell soldier, aren't you?
I'll stay put right here so that I can
at least avoid getting in your way!
Give a guy a hand, will you?
Look, they're starting to gather
because we're here!
Can't do it! Too scary!
My, my...
MACROPHAGE
A type of White Blood Cell.
Captures and kills foreign
substances such as bacteria,
and finds antigens
and immunity information.
Also acts as a cleaner,
tidying up dead cells and bacteria.
Is everything all right here?
I can see that the virus people
have multiplied significantly.
A hatchet?
Now then, time to get to work!
W-Watch out!
MACROPHAGE'S DEADLY FORCE:
Significantly potent.
Rest assured.
Right.
Let's see, this is...
A Type B virus.
This is Macrophage.
It appears that a Type B influenza virus
has invaded this body.
Right!
Understood! Please give it your all!
Right! Goodbye!
Helper T Commander,
that was Macrophage
presenting antigen information.
Very well.
We've just received word
that a Type B virus has invaded this body.
Yes, yes. Yes, that's correct.
The Killer T Cells will start
aggregating immediately!
I've notified each organ
through Dendritic Cell,
so the Killer T Cells
will soon be here to assist you.
Hey, that's great news.
The Killer T Cells?
U-Um, White Blood Cell, Macrophage,
I'm sorry!
Could you please tell them
I brought down
just one of these zombies?
Why do you want us to do that?
B-Because if you don't, I...
The senpais will...
Okay, dammit, is this the place?
Where are those viruses at?
KILLER T CELLS
(CYTOTOXIC T CELLS):
Mobilize under orders
from the Helper T Cells.
They kill virus-infected cells,
cancer cells and the like.
The Killer T Cells are here to wipe 'em all out!
Macrophage, thank you for your hard work!
Thank you for your hard work!
And thank you, as well!
Hey, so you're here, too.
Yeah.
Hey, Naive!
You let someone else
do your work for you again, huh?
When are you gonna learn
to pull your own weight?
And you call yourself a T Cell like us?
S-S-S-S-S-Sorry! I'm so sorry!
I see. So the senpais
like to bust his chops, huh?
Yoo-hoo! We're here as backup.
Hey, there's still
a whole horde of them over there!
Let's see you slaughter at least one of them
this time, ya hear me, you little punk?
Got that?
C'mon, dammit!
Could you give me a yank?
Sure.
Obliterate every last one of them!
MEMORIES
Memories of viruses
Listen up!
Don't let your guard down, any of you!
MEMORY T CELL:
Part of the Killer T Cells.
Equipped to attack again
when an enemy reappears
for the second time.
According to my memory
of encountering those guys,
compared to bacteria, the influenza virus's
proliferation speed is on a different level!
Right, Memory T Cell!
Memory...
Kill 'em all!
Don't allow any more common cell casualties!
Eradicate those viruses once and for all!
Hey! You join in, too!
Right!
Give it your best shot!
Th-That's right.
I've got to give it my all, too!
After all,
I'm a T Cell, too just like the senpais!
Naive!
Are you okay, Nai—
Hey, you!
What are you doing, spacing out like that?
He made a run for it.
Hey, Naive!
Oh my...
Just forget about him!
For now, let's deal with the virus!
Right!
Did something happen?
Run!
U-Um, excuse me!
Is something going on?
There's been a report
about a viral infection up there!
Thank you very much!
Senpai, what should we do?
That's a good question.
I'm...
What's the matter?
Hey, you're a T Cell, right?
Did something happen?
DENDRITIC CELLS
Their role is to present bacteria
that have invaded the body,
and fragments of viral infection cells
as antigens, and to notify
other immune system cells.
As their name implies, they feature protrusions.
Dendritic Cell.
Their role is to present bacteria
and virus-infected cells
that have invaded the body
as antigen fragments,
and then notify other immune system cells.
Wait, are you struggling in battle?
All right. I'm going to make a call right now.
Th-That's not it!
I ran away from the battle!
No way can I fight
those scum that terrifying!
I'm... I'm...
I'm just not powerful like White Blood Cell,
Macrophage or my senpais!
It's better not to have
a weakling like me around!
That's not true, Naive T Cell.
Chin up, all right?
You're not the only one.
Nobody starts out powerful, you know.
I've got the chills!
Here, take a look at this.
T CELLS
MEMORIES 18905 - 20105
SEALED
B-But these are
pictures of the senpais from long ago?
T CELL CATEGORIZATION:
Upon recognizing an antigen,
Naive T Cells activate
and turn into Effector T Cells.
Keep up the good work...
Failure leads to...
Get well soon!
That's right.
Long ago, your senpais were just like you.
They were all Naive T Cells, too.
They're crying. Just like me!
There are tons more where that came from.
Here!
I'm getting goosebumps for some reason!
Hey, what's wrong?
Did you get infected by the virus?
Like that would ever happen.
It feels like the dark past
that we sealed away has been released!
Those kinds of chills!
The reason your senpais give you
such a hard time
might be because they see
their past selves in you, don't you think?
Hey, Naive!
When are you gonna learn
to pull your own weight?
Let's see you slaughter at least one of them
this time, ya hear me, you little punk? Got that?
C'mon, dammit! This way!
Hey! You join in, too!
I had no idea.
Don't worry.
There's no reason to be afraid, Naive.
We're all here for you.
All here for me!
White Blood Cell goes on patrol
to spot the enemy.
Macrophage relays information
on the enemy.
Because of that, Helper T Commander
is able to issue commands,
and the Killer T Cells
can then bring the enemy down.
See? You have all these friends working
with you, taking pride in their work!
So you know what it is
you have to do, don't you?
I...
My job is...
Well, encouraging the T Cells
and activating them in this way...
DENDRITIC CELL'S ABILITY:
Can activate Naive T Cells.
I guess you could say that's my job.
Cells at Work!
Cells...
...at Work!
They've proliferated again, dammit!
INFLUENZA VIRUS PROLIFERATION:
The influenza virus is said to proliferate
to 100 after 8 hours inside the body,
and to one million after one day.
Influenza virus proliferation.
The influenza virus is said to proliferate
to 100 after 8 hours inside the body,
and to one million after one day.
Kind of hot, isn't it?
INTERNAL BODY TEMPERATURE
NOW RISING
They're infected!
Don't come this way!
Let's get out of here!
Dammit, can't make a dent in them!
There's just no end to these guys!
Everybody...
I apologize for behaving
in such an unsightly manner earlier.
But I've overcome
my past self's weakness and returned,
newly activated!
I am the former Naive T Cell!
EFFECTOR T CELL:
A Naive T Cell after being activated.
Effector T Cell.
He's been activated!
I've also proliferated!
There's more of him!
Hey! So he finally did it! Freakin' Naive!
This gives us
Herculean strength, huh? Literally!
No. Isn't this scary?
Hey, I'm here, too!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm B Cell! And I've made some antibodies!
B CELL (ANTIBODY-PRODUCING CELL):
A type of Lymphocyte that fights antigens
such as bacteria and viruses
by producing weapons called "antibodies."
B Cell. Antibody-producing cell.
A type of Lymphocyte that fights antigens
such as bacteria and viruses
by producing weapons called "antibodies."
We've got nothing to fear
now that we have this!
We can round 'em all up just like that!
All right! Let's go!
Yeah!
Wait! Uh...
C'mon! We're gonna singlehandedly
wipe out all those viruses!
Yeah!
All right!
Take that!
Take that! Take that! Take that!
And so, along with the efforts
of the immune cells...
HOT WATER
Stay away!
FEVER:
Suppresses the proliferation of invasive bacteria
by raising the body temperature.
Also accelerates the immune system.
CONSTRICTION
IN PROGRESS
...and each cell's hard work...
CHILLS:
Constrict the veins at the body's surface
in order to prevent body heat from escaping.
When the surface temperature
of the extremities decreases,
one experiences the chills.
SNEEZE TWENTY-FIVE
Achoo!
SNEEZE TWENTY-FIVE LAUNCH SUCCESSFUL!!
SNEEZES, COUGHS:
A reflexive reaction
caused when the body attempts
to expel foreign bodies such as viruses.
Achoo!
Hey! This is no time to be cooking dinner!
This is an emergency!
Let's have them use
the stomach's digestive energy!
DECREASE
INCREASE
APPETITE LEVEL
DECREASED APPETITE:
A reaction to heal disease,
utilizing the energy
normally used for digesting.
- It stopped!
- No way!
INTERNAL BODY TEMPERATURE
NOW RISING
All right, we're good.
We're sufficiently hydrated.
Sweat! Cool off the body surface!
Roger that!
ECCRINE
SWEAT:
Expels toxins and adjusts
body temperature.
THE SWEAT GLANDS
IN ACTION NOW
Thanks to the teamwork
between each organ,
and everyone joining forces...
Take that!
...a week later, the influenza virus...
...had vanished from this body.
You did it!
Now you're a full-fledged T Cell!
Senpai...
Huh! The latter half
was mostly thanks to me!
My antibodies...
Well, yeah.
No one's more powerful than us Killer T Cells!
No cell or virus stands a chance against us!
We did it!
Thank you for your hard work.
Right.
Hey, check that out!
Over there!
It's a virus!
Hey, looks like a new one just snuck in!
What a fool.
After tens of thousands
of his friends just got eradicated...
I'll just annihilate him with one blow,
so he won't suffer at least!
Wow, he's Mr. Aggressive now.
Take that!
H-Huh?
The antibodies aren't working!
Which means that...
No way.
Could this be
Type A Influenza?
TYPE A INFLUENZA:
Type A features
numerous internal mutations,
and is prone to triggering
epidemics on a global scale.
Type A Influenza.
Type A features
numerous internal mutations,
and is prone to triggering epidemics
on a global scale.
My, my!
Dendritic Cell, this is Macrophage.
It seems that we've been invaded
by a Type A Influenza virus this time.
All right, then, I'm gonna go
whip up some new antibodies!
I'm leaving the rest to you T Cells!
H-Hold up!
We don't have the strength, either!
Right, right. Understood.
Hello? Dendritic Cell speaking.
Requesting reinforcements!
Right.
Right, right.
Yes. Oh no!
NEXT EPISODE
PREVIEW
Today's snack is glycogen ice cream
and hot spring bean paste buns!
Hey, don't overeat.
Next episode of "Cells at Work!",
"Food Poisoning"!
Hey, wait! Don't tell me it's me!
EPISODE 4:
FOOD POISONING
Of course it's not.