The Third Plate
Twenty-Two
Man, the day's finally come.
Right. It was fast.
But we're different from before.
Let's show Central how far
our training's taken us.
Yup! We've got a full team
we can depend on now, too!
You can see it now.
That's Rebun Island, where we'll
have the Team Shokugeki.
Food Wars
The Third Plate
Totsuki Train Arc
Good day! My name is Nakiri Alice.
To the Final Battleground
I was just expelled from Totsuki Academy.
The gloomy bunch of people with
me have also been expelled.
Ugh, they're so depressing!
Erina-sama... Erina-sama... Erina-sama...
Well, they're still doing a lot
better than Miss Secretary.
A lot of things have happened.
Defeated by the Elite Ten during
the stage three examinations,
we were about to be forcibly
sent back to Tokyo.
We are with Erina, until death do us part!
But I went on a full-on tantrum and
managed to have us stay in Hokkaido.
Our fates are entwined!
So we have to see the exams
through to the end—
After we heard Erina and the others
were going to do a Team Shokugeki,
we've been traveling north
alongside their train
and reached this island.
And why are you all still so depressed?!
You came to cheer them on, didn't you?!
Pull yourselves together!
But Alice-cchi...
We promised each other to survive
together, but we all lost.
How can I show myself to Erina-sama?
Stop feeling so down, Miss Secretary!
Don't call me that.
Why do I have to be here?
I betrayed you all once—
You want to say you have no right to be here?
I'm tired of hearing that!
We share a bond as classmates.
And above all, the bond we share
as the White Coat Trio is absolute!
I know. Thanks.
You can let me go now.
Hey, Hayama.
Since you lost to Yukihira,
that means you might also lose to me.
Let's have a match.
Sure, any time.
Okay. Right now, then.
Uh, that's not possible.
Hey, over there.
Let's step right into the special
arena for the Team Shokugeki!
So many people.
There are students who cleared the final
stage of the exams and the lecturers.
Culinary heavyweights are also here,
but they're all Central supporters.
They want the rebels to lose.
Honored guests!
You can see the majestic
Mount Rishiri Fuji next to Rebun Island!
Against this gorgeous backdrop,
your host for this final battle
is me, Urara, the idol of the 92nd class!
Te-he
Well then, let us pray for our beloved
Azami administration's victory
and welcome the Elite Ten members
to the arena by chanting "Central"!
Here they come!
"Central"! Let's hear it!
Central!
C-C-C-C-Central!
Yuck.
We're totally in enemy territory.
I can't hear you! Central!
Yukihira and the others are
going to fight in front of them?
C-C-C-C-Central!
Bro...
Erina-sama...
Director Azami is here, too!
Azami-sama!
Director Azami!
I see.
A Team Shokugeki.
It'll determine whether we
advance to next year or not—
You'd better not lose!
Yup, we'll show up ready.
You can count on us!
I wish we could've fought
together on the same team.
I'm sorry all of you have
to shoulder everything.
Huh?
Listen, I'm only thinking about fighting
the Elite Ten so I can take the No.1 spot.
I see.
So, Yukihira.
Is it just you four entering
the Team Shokugeki?
No, we have a couple other people in mind.
We're gonna rustle up more
allies while we train.
We'd like to be the same, numbers-wise,
as the other side if we can.
I wonder if they managed to find four more.
Next are the ignorant trash who
foolishly oppose the noble Central—
The hated rebels! Come in!
Isshiki-senpai!
Mimasaka Subaru!
Kuga Terunori!
And not to mention...
The former third seat, Megishima Tosuke?!
They managed to scrounge up the best allies
they could find from the remaining students!
The final battle will be an even
match between two teams of eight!
What's up?
I'm here to take back my seat!
Look!
Erina-sama is on the enemy team!
She's rebelling against Director Azami?!
What's going on?!
Hi, Nakamura-senpai!
Man, but it's cold.
Hello, Erina.
I trust you've been well?
Yes, Father.
First, let the teams come
to an agreement as to
how many should face off in one round!
How about three per round?
Very well.
That was fast!
Let's have both teams select the three
chefs who'll compete in the first round!
Totsuki Elite Ten
Tsukasa Eishi
Kobayashi Rindo
Akanegakubo Momo
Saito Somei
Kinokuni Nene
Eizan Etsuya
Kaburagi Shoko
Shiratsu Jurio
Rebels
Nakiri Erina
Megishima Tosuke
Isshiki Satoshi
Kuga Terunori
Yukihira Soma
Takumi Aldini
Mimasaka Subaru
Tadokoro Megumi
Isshiki-senpai! We've been expelled!
If you lose this round,
even you'll get expelled.
That's not a real reason not to fight.
I'm here for my beloved underclassmen.
Isshiki-senpai!
Well, and I've got backup plans
in case I'm unable to win.
Huh?
Let's start a farm together!
I've already identified
several potential locations.
What?
I made arrangements to have our produce
featured on an online organic produce site.
We'll start small-scale.
His plans are so specific... I don't
know how to feel about them.
We'll post a lot of social
media savvy photos.
As for uniforms...
How'd you recruit Megishima-san,
the former third seat?
Oh, it wasn't easy.
All right!
You ex-students there!
There are special seats for you!
Uh, okay.
This is just a prison!
You've got to be kidding me!
What're we supposed to
do if we wanna go potty?!
You're only spectating
thanks to Azami-sama's mercy.
Be grateful!
Are you okay?
Even I, a Nakiri...
I feel calmer here.
Why's that?
This is humiliating.
Don't feel so down.
You'll worry Erina-sama.
You're right.
All right!
We have our first bout's chefs!
Megishima Tosuke
Megishima Tosuke!
Isshiki Satoshi
Isshiki-senpai!
Yukihira Soma
There's Yukihira!
Isshiki, let's take it on like we're
trying to crush the whole lot of them.
I'm cheered by your
motivation, Megishima-san.
As for Central...
Kaburagi Shoko
VS
Megishima Tosuke
The new fifth seat...
Kaburagi Shoko.
Shiratsu Jurio
Isshiki-senpai's opponent will be
the eighth seat, Shiratsu Jurio.
Shiratsu Jurio
VS
Isshiki Satoshi
And Yukihira will go up against—
The sixth seat, Kinokuni Nene!
Kinokuni Nene
So you're my opponent, Yukihira Soma-kun.
I apologize in advance if
I were to make you cry.
Don't be too hard on me!
Kinokuni Nene
VS
Yukihira Soma
Yukihira Soma, I hope you get beat into pulp!
Nene-senpai, murder those rebels!
I dislike mean-spirited heckling.
Man, that ice-cold stare.
I love it!
Yukihira-chin!
Pigtails over there is always in a bad
mood and has a barbed tongue. Be careful.
She's probably on the rag today, too—
Kuga!
Die.
Kinokuni Nene
VS
Yukihira Soma
The sixth seat...
It's a higher tank than Isshiki-senpai's
former seventh seat.
If I remember correctly, her specialty is...
Japanese cuisine in general.
Her family runs a soba restaurant in Kanda.
Their top-notch establishment has safeguarded
the tenets of Edo soba for generations.
She learned classic dance, calligraphy,
and the zither, among other things.
But of course, she has received exhaustive
instruction in the tea ceremony, kaiseki,
and other aspects of Japanese cuisine.
Her soba-making skills are without question!
She is a gift to the world
of Japanese cuisine—
A thoroughbred in every sense of the word.
All right, each match's topic
will be chosen by raffle!
Draw one, please!
Okay. I defer to you, Kinokuni-senpai.
Oh, I don't mind if you do it.
I'd like to have a clean,
fair fight—unlike Eizan.
But I'll say this much...
Don't think that I'm limited to soba and
Japanese cuisine, Yukihira Soma-kun.
Whatever topic in whatever
culinary genre you may draw,
I will still crush your dish.
Nice trash talk.
Well, I'll go ahead and draw, then.
Soba
Great!
The third match's topic is
Kinokuni Nene's specialty, soba!
The Elite Ten is even closer to victory now.
Eat it, rebels!
Yukihira!
What's with your bad luck?!
He's finished...
Soma-kun!
It's not my fault.
Whatever topic in whatever
culinary genre you may draw...
My family runs a soba restaurant.
Oh, uh, sorry.
I don't want you to apologize.
You're a miracle worker as always, Soma-kun.
As for me, it seems it'll be the eel.
Eel
Huh.
The topic has been decided!
There's no point in waiting! Let's start!
The Team Shokugeki has begun!
The first bout in the
Team Shokugeki will now begin!
First Match
Kaburagi Shoko vs. Megishima Tosuke
Second Match
Shiratsu Jurio vs. Isshiki Satoshi
Third Match
Kinokuni Nene vs. Yukihira Soma
Time Remaining
You have two hours!
The three matches will proceed in parallel!
Chefs, please proceed to the food
storage unit adjoining the arena!
The basic staples are available onstage,
but more specialized ingredients
can be found there!
I'll leave you to it.
Thanks.
You're also allowed to
bring your own ingredients.
Our honored judges will soon arrive, too.
Our chefs have begun cooking!
No, only Yukihira Soma has yet to return!
What?
What's he doing?!
It'll be fine. He just got back.
I thought diners don't
leave their customers waiting.
Nice smell.
She's already starting
to make the soba dough.
That's a big wooden bowl.
Very authentic.
First comes the hydration step.
Water is added to sifted buckwheat flour,
then mixed in by hand to
hydrate the whole mixture.
It's coming together quickly!
She's efficient.
I've never seen such elegant execution.
It's almost like you're watching
an artisan, rather than a chef.
This is true technique.
The fingers deftly nurture each clump
of buckwheat such that it grows in size.
This delicate process allows optimal
hydration of the buckwheat flour.
The soba granules have grown
to the size of fava beans.
She's entering the gathering stage, where the
dough is brought together into a ball.
You can tell that the dough is coming
together and gaining elasticity.
It's hard to believe she's doing
all that with sticks for arms.
What strength.
The secret is her lower body!
She's firmly grounded herself,
and is transferring the energy from her feet
to the dough through her legs and waist.
Nene's flexibility may be an innate gift.
Because she's mixing the dough so thoroughly,
there's no need to add
more water than needed.
It's authentic soba that has the
minimum possible water content.
Served cold,
it'll have a smooth throat feel, with a
good affinity for the dipping sauce.
Served warm,
it'll have an exquisite, mild flavor
that comes from the mingling
of the soba's flavors and the broth.
It's textbook perfection!
Let's have some applause for the lady!
There is a saying in the soba-making world.
Three days to master the knife,
three months to master the rolling pin,
and three years to master the mixing bowl.
It refers to the length of time required
to master each step in the process.
You can tell just from observing her work—
The weight of the years
spent mastering her craft!
There's no way he can
compete on the soba front!
Yukihira!
What are you going to do?!
All right! I've figured it out!
The dish I'm going to make
is this instant yakisoba.
Chance
Yakisoba
Cup
What's he saying now?!
All right, guess I'll go with an
8:2 ratio for the buckwheat flour
and wheat flour for the binding agent.
While the soba I'm making uses a
9:1 ratio, he chose an 8:2 ratio.
Some believe that the greater the proportion
of buckwheat flour to wheat flour,
the higher the quality,
but that is a major misconception.
9:1
8:2
Flour (Binding Agent)
Buckwheat
Of course, the closer to
100 percent buckwheat,
the stronger its fragrance,
and the greater the buckwheat
flavor and sweetness.
But the lack of a binding agent
would come across to the uninitiated
as a dry, crumbly texture.
I can respect that you didn't go for
the pure buckwheat option. But...
Instant yakisoba? Really?
Hm? What was that, Senpai?
Yukihira Soma-kun, that's how
you've been winning so far, right?
With impulsive creativity, rapid-fire ideas...
And maybe offbeat bluffs?
But this time, that won't work.
Only the accumulation of time and history
can make the beauty of soba shine.
And you lack both.
Don't think for a second that
you can beat me at soba.
Time and history, huh?
Thanks for the advice, Kinokuni-senpai.
But all I'm doing here is making a soba
dish that really represents who I am.
All right, Soma.
How are you going to beat the Elite Ten?
How?
Well, just think on my feet, whatever
the topic might be, and... yeah.
But you lost in the Autumn Elections'
Pacific saury match, didn't you?
You lost because you couldn't overcome
Hayama's fragrance bull's-eye attack.
The Elite Ten you're about to face
are a bunch of guys who've
perfected their specialization.
I'm not sure improv alone is going to cut it.
But see, Soma...
You do have one long-time thing you've got
going for you that you won't
lose to them at, don't you?
Huh?
The fact that you're from a diner.
Soba that represents me...
That wouldn't be some rarefied thing
that only a select few can understand.
Taste with widespread appeal that would be
enjoyed no matter who the customer might be!
I'll bring that kind of soba to life here.
Man, modern day noodle-making
machines are amazing.
They make really nice noodles.
What the hell?! He's using a
machine to make the noodles!
He gave up on handmade noodles,
and he's using a machine!
This is no good.
It's a done deal.
Yukihira...
He didn't give up, did he?
No.
Not yet.
Right.
He's not that weak.
Yukihira-kun has not thrown the fight.
He's quietly waiting for his chance.
Right!
Though "handmade noodles" are highly
sought after in the soba and udon world,
the noodles aren't good
because they're handmade.
They're good because they
were skillfully made by hand.
There are many well-regarded restaurants
who only do the hydration step by hand
and do the rest using machines.
The phrase "machine-made is better
than poorly-done hand-made"
is common knowledge among soba aficionados.
That's true.
He has skill.
You could even say he's
kept pace right behind me.
But the reality of it is,
the difference in quality between
our soba noodles is undeniable.
Your victory is impossible.
If you think you have another trick up
your sleeve, I dare you to show it,
Yukihira Soma!
Good job.
You're calm, Soma-kun.
Um, what about your cooking, Isshiki-senpai?
Oh, don't worry about me!
Cheering on your team mates
is part of teamwork!
Remember the joyous times we spent
at our Polar Star Dormitory!
Got it!
Isshiki!
I ask that you refrain from being distracted!
Cooking is an art that also encompasses
our behavior during the cooking process.
We, ourselves, are part of our work.
Face me, and let us create
one work of art together.
You and I can do it!
Oh, here it comes!
His finisher!
It's the one he calls the Pepper Mill Rondo!
Let's weave together the ultimate
competitive performance—the sessione!
Sorry, what's your name again?
New Elite Ten Member
2nd Year, High School Division
Shiratsu Jurio
Isshiki!
You make me sad!
You should at least remember
the names of your classmates.
Rindo-senpai, wearing your
hair up looks good on you.
Oh, really?
Can you stop chatting each other up?
Fine, Isshiki!
I'll etch my very existence into
your heart with this match!
It's not just Yukihira
we need to worry about.
Yeah, we need to support Isshiki-senpai
and Megishima-senpai, too.
Look!
Jurio-senpai has begun to cook the eel!
The eel has been seasoned
with salt and pepper.
To that, he's adding onions and garlic!
And white wine in a rondo!
His techniques, trained in Italy,
are exploding onstage!
The Shiratsu family
has been tasked with providing food to
the Italian consulate for generations.
They are known far and wide
in both Japan and Italy.
He does have good skills.
So eel is the topic, and the opponent
is skilled in Italian cuisine—
This may be a tough match.
It may come as a surprise to the Japanese,
but eel dishes are mainstream in Europe.
The eel matelote Kurokiba served in the
Autumn Election semifinals
is but one example.
In southern Italy, it's traditional to
eat eel during Natale, or Christmas.
Huh.
Shiratsu Jurio must be pretty
confident in his eel dishes, too.
What cuisine does Isshiki-san specialize in?
Based on his uniform, he seems
to be good at Japanese cuisine.
Among eel chefs, there's a phrase
similar to the soba world's,
"Three days to master the knife, three
months to master the rolling pin,
three years to master the mixing bowl."
Three
years
to master
the skewer
"Three years to master the skewer,
eight years to master the fillet,
Eight
years
to master
the fillet
A lifetime
to master
the flame
a lifetime to master the flame."
Eight years?!
A lifetime?!
It's on a different level.
I'm not sure that Isshiki
guy has that much skill.
I know!
Maybe we should start an eel farm.
If we grow them in greenhouses,
they won't hibernate,
so they'll grow fast.
Really?
Wait, now's not the time for this, Isshiki!
She's not being polite to him anymore.
Goofing off in the middle of a match!
You're always like that!
You never show your true colors
and just wing everything!
I have sincere respect for your talent,
as much as Donato Gotoda-senpai,
whom I admire!
Huh?
Meraviglioso!
I have dreamed of the day you and I
would flourish in Central side by side!
Why won't you bend the
knee to Director Azami?
You're an idiot!
A gaping idiot!
He totally doesn't care!
Kinokuni!
You tell him, too!
Tell him he's a disgrace to his
renowned family, the Isshiki family!
A disgrace to a renowned family?
Wow, talk about insults.
But it's true. I guess it's appropriate.
Isshiki, do you have no pride?!
I heard you were removed
from the seventh seat
and that you've continued to stay
at some place called Polar Star Dormitory,
a hangout for riffraff.
I say this for your sake!
As a member of the Isshiki family, you should
not be mingling with such lowlifes!
Uh, Shiratsu-kun, was it?
Let's have some quiet, shall we?
What the hell?
It was like the severed blood vessels took
a while to realize they had been cut.
Shit!
Now I can totally tell that he
wasn't even half serious that time.
His skills are superhuman.
Who is he, really?
Is that all you can do? My, my.
Regardless of what you said about me,
I didn't think you'd run your
mouth about everyone at the dorm.
Fine. I've made up my mind.
Shiratsu-kun?
Maybe I'll be serious about crushing you.
Totsuki
Food Wars
The Third Plate
Next Episode  Bearing Polar Star Dormitory
Would anyone like to choose from
a wide range of Shokugekis?