Inside the human body...
...roughly 37.2 trillion cells
are working hard every day.
DENDRITE
ARTERIES
Sorry for the wait!
FRAGILE
CONDENSED GAS
Here's today's oxygen delivery!
RED BLOOD CELLS
Red Blood Cell.
Her red color is due
to the large amounts of hemoglobin.
She carries oxygen and carbon dioxide
using blood circulation.
EPISODE 1: PNEUMOCOCCUS
If you could please sign here...
Thanks!
Thanks for your hard work!
Well, I hope to serve you again!
Huh?
What is this?
Oh, no! Here they come!
Run!
Whoa! The vascular endothelial cells...
Seems like a pretty damn comfortable place!
Not too hot, not too cold.
And looks like there's tons and tons of food!
It's settled!
Starting today, this is our land!
First of all...
Let's get these annoying residents outta the way!
WHITE BLOOD CELL
Die, germ!
Die!
Who are these guys?
This is White Blood Cell
Neutrophil Division, U-1146.
The invading germs
have been exterminated.
WHITE BLOOD CELLS
(NEUTROPHILS)
White Blood Cell. (Neutrophil.)
His main task is to eliminate
foreign substances from outside,
such as bacteria and viruses.
Neutrophils comprise over half
of the White Blood Cells in the blood.
LET'S BID THEM
A PLEASANT GOODBYE!
"BYE-BYE GERMS!"
Listen up! Don't let a single bacterium get away!
Because there'll be hell to pay
if even one escapes!
Whoa! It's the White Blood Cells!
Scary!
CELL
Seriously, talk about merciless!
He's splattered with blood!
Hey, any over there?
Negative.
S-So they're the White Blood Cells?
Hey, what are you looking at?
Can I help you?
Y-Yes! I mean, um...
Th-Thank you for saving me!
I was in such danger...
No need to thank me.
I was only doing my job.
No, I mean you're welcome.
Right!
Any more over there?
I'll kill them!
I swear I'm gonna kill them!
Dammit!
You wretched White Blood Cells!
Don't think it's over yet!
Boy, that was scary!
I'm gonna deliver this to the lungs fast!
THE RED BLOOD CELLS' JOB
Well, to get to the lungs,
I need to make a right here.
VENOUS VALVE
Hey, that entrance is one-way.
I-I'm sorry! I'm new here!
Lungs are that way.
Again?
Where?
This is it!
Oh, this is the spleen...
MACROPHAGE
SPLEEN
Are you lost perhaps?
Y-Yes! I'm sorry! I made a mistake!
Don't worry!
Hey, you! This is a lymph duct!
What do you think you're doing here?
No Red Blood Cells allowed! Moron!
Another blunder!
Please forgive me!
They're always doing construction
around here.
So these maps are hard to figure out!
I-Is that right?
I don't think I'll ever get there...
STORAGE #7
Let's see... The lungs, the lungs...
WASTE
There's nobody here!
I wonder if anyone's in here.
Excuse me?
There's something I'd like to ask you!
Um... Excuse me...
Don't act like nothing happened!
Target sighted!
I found you, you bastard!
Die!
You germ!
Sniffed me out already,
you damn White Blood Cell?
No way am I gonna let you capture me!
So long!
O-Oh no!
CAPSULE
Is this a bacterial capsule?
Dammit! I can't see the bacterium!
Please stop pulling!
Did he get away?
Um, thank you for earlier!
Oh, right. Sure.
You're that Red Blood Cell from before!
Yes! What was that bacterium?
The survivor of the group
that just invaded us! Damn!
This isn't looking good!
He's a Pneumococcus!
If I don't kill him right away,
he'll start dividing!
And if that happens, this world will...
Pn-Pneumococcus?
Yeah.
The Pneumococci are pathogenic bacteria
of the respiratory system
that trigger pneumonia
and other diseases,
not to mention highly toxic germs
that wield capsules!
No way! I'm actually on my way
to the lungs myself!
URINE
This is a kidney.
Oh, I'm lost!
It's not just the lungs that are at risk.
The germ fled into the blood vessels after all!
What do you...
I mean, we're not untangled at all yet!
Pneumonia's not the only disease
that's caused by the Pneumococci.
There's something
called "pneumococcal bacteremia."
The Pneumococci attack each organ
through the blood vessels,
seizing control of the meninges
enveloping the brain,
PNEUMOCOCCUS BACTEREMIA
ultimately destroying this world!
Those guys are super fast!
They've been known to invade
an entire body in a mere 24 hours.
Th-There's a disease like that?
Yeah. Since this body's immune system
has been compromised.
Normally, it can withstand
something like this, but...
This is U-1146.
Requesting backup
to pursue the invading germ.
We're short-handed, too!
Try to get by on your own!
What's this?
RECEPTOR
My receptor's responding!
He must still be nearby.
Couldn't they have come up
with a better design?
SALT
Hey, did you hear that guy say anything?
Like where he was headed?
Also, what was he doing there?
- A response!
- Um...
He was looking at a map!
He seemed to be looking
for the lungs!
So he was lost, too?
Yeah, probably.
All right.
The lungs, huh?
Gotcha.
I've got to get there, too!
Even if I'm afraid of the Pneumococcus!
That's my job!
Lungs are this way.
DENDRITIC CELLS
All right, follow me.
Since we're heading
toward the same destination.
I'm so sorry!
Let's get moving.
Remember the way there.
R-Right!
BLOOD VESSELS
This is an amazing area
we're passing through, huh?
Well, yes.
DENDRITE
- This way.
- Hello!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
It's the Platelets!
Oh my! They're so cute!
PLATELETS
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
They're called Platelets?
Right.
Hello!
Thanks for your hard work!
Good work.
SAFETY FIRST
Excuse me!
Roadwork is delayed,
and we are deeply sorry.
THE PLATELETS TEAM
ROAD CLOSED
PLATELETS
We're still doing some construction up ahead!
The road's closed?
But we're in a hurry!
Did something happen?
We're so sorry!
You see, you see...
There was some trouble,
so construction's been delayed.
And so, you see,
the delivery people made a fatal mistake!
We can't unload the cargo.
It's too high! Can't reach!
Bring the ladder!
ABSENT
Heave-ho!
- Th-That's adorable...
Then, we'll unload it for you.
Sorry to trouble you when you're busy!
Not at all!
Did you see that Pneumococcus?
The one who looked like this?
I don't know.
Thank you!
BLOOD CLOTS
Still, it doesn't make sense.
Well,
the fact that my receptor's been acting up...
You're right, it is!
Do you think maybe it's broken?
Well, it's pretty beat-up.
Oh well, whatever.
It's not like anything
particularly strange is going on.
This is the Helper T Cell.
HELPER T CELLS
HELPER T
COMMANDER NEWS
We've been informed
that a Pneumococcus is on the run
within these very blood vessels!
We are mobilizing the Killer T Cells!
Since our most elite Lymphocyte force
is on its way,
you have nothing to worry about!
We are ready to put our pride on the line
to exterminate the enemy! No matter what!
Commander Helper T Cell?
You have cookie crumbs
all over your mouth.
You're right! Oh man...
Well, anyway, so there you have it!
Is that them?
LYMPHATIC VESSEL
KILLER T CELLS
(CYTOTOXIC T CELLS)
In the name of the Killer T Cell Division,
finish the target within two seconds of sighting!
Any moron who lets him escape
will be sent to the spleen!
Yes, sir!
They're pretty pompous, aren't they?
They're actually related to us,
White Blood Cells.
LYMPHOCYTES
They're called Lymphocytes.
Oh, never mind.
Let's get moving.
You're right!
Hey!
What's that Red Blood Cell doing here?
She's the one
who saw the Pneumococcus.
Well, you look pretty nonchalant.
For someone about to get killed.
No, I wouldn't say nonchalant.
She probably just doesn't know.
Then here's your chance to learn something!
Pneumococci are alpha-hemolytic cells
that crave nutrients.
In other words,
you Red Blood Cells, who transport
nutrients, will become their target!
HEMOLYSIS
So better watch your back, all right?
They just want to scare you.
Don't pay any attention.
We're out of time, so let's get going.
WELCOME TO THE LUNGS
So these are the lungs?
LUNGS
Yeah.
I don't see anyone making a commotion.
You think maybe we overtook him?
The Pneumococcus?
All right, time to say goodbye.
Good job.
Oh, right! Thank you
for showing me the way!
Right. You be careful now.
DANGER!
RUNNING STRICTLY FORBIDDEN
Please take care!
Sure.
Thank you very much!
Thank you so much
for your hard work!
Sure.
Watch where you're going.
All right, what do I do now?
Now that I can't use my receptor...
What's this?
DENDRITE
Smoke him out, no matter what!
Yes, sir!
Right.
We'll continue our pursuit
of the fleeing bacterium.
Where the hell did he go?
That damn Pneumococcus!
THIS IS THE LEFT LUNG
ALVEOLUS 50th-120th FLOOR
ELEVATOR RIGHT LUNG
Right Lung? Left Lung?
I'm getting on, too!
Let's see...
I'm supposed to pass through the capillaries
to get to an alveolus.
CAPILLARY 049
Huh?
Wait!
Over here, too?
CAPILLARY 062
There, too?
CAPILLARY 052
Th-There are so many capillaries!
Hey, you there!
S-Senpai!
What are you doing here?
Are you getting your job done?
Please help me!
Let me see.
All right, in these situations, look here.
See those numbers?
Yes!
You'll find the same numbers
on every door.
CAPILLARY 053
You're right! Sorry about that!
I see you're the same as ever.
Oh, well. You just need to learn step by step.
Right!
Good luck!
See ya!
Thank you very much!
95, 96...
Dear Red Blood Cells,
The capillary is cramped,
so please enter one at a time.
Be courteous!
CAPILLARY 095
CAPILLARIES
Here it is!
"Be courteous and only one at a time," huh?
ALVEOLI
ENTRANCE
Is this an alveolus?
I wonder where that Pneumococcus went.
I just hope I don't run into him.
Hey!
Thanks! For transporting me all this way!
He's here!
EXIT
You moron! You're not getting away!
Seriously, how stupid is that?
To not even realize
what it was you were delivering!
Now that I'm here in the alveolus,
it's the best place to lie in wait
for Red Blood Cells transporting nutrients!
For starters,
I think I'll take the edge off my appetite!
S-Somebody...
You sure are delivering a ton of nutrients!
Yes! Since I just stopped
by the small intestine.
Sorry! This one's occupied!
ALVEOLUS
OCCUPIED
You idiot!
You think you just protected your friends?
Talk about an exercise in futility!
And right before
you're about to be massacred no less!
Go ahead and call out for help, for all I care!
Not that anyone will be able
to come to rescue
if you block the way like that!
He's going to kill me!
S-Somebody!
I can see you haven't done
your homework.
We, White Blood Cells,
are transmigrating cells.
MIGRATION
Meaning we can slip through
blood vessel walls to reach our enemies!
White Blood Cell!
How did you know I was here?
The instant that Red Blood Cell left me,
my receptor stopped responding, you see!
I never would've thought
you'd be hiding inside the package!
No way am I gonna let myself be killed
after I've come this far!
White Blood Cell,
he says he's going to attack
any Red Blood Cell carrying nutrients!
Gotcha!
Hey, you'll do! I'm gonna obliterate you!
It's a germ!
White Blood Cell!
Stay back!
A capsule, huh?
A capsule? Like before?
It's not like the one
he used as a smokescreen!
It's a more powerful screen
he can use to directly shield himself!
I have no chance against something
that powerful in close combat!
White Blood Cell!
You shouldn't let him know that!
ENCAPSULATED CELLS
I see. Thanks for clueing me in.
Change of plans!
Before I launch my all-out invasion,
I'm gonna torture you guys to death!
Why did you tell him that, of all things?
My bad!
It's all over!
White Blood Cell,
forget about idiots like me and run!
Maybe I'll go for that.
BRONCHIAL TUBES
Run that way!
This way?
Go!
R-Right!
RESPIRATORY TRACT
MUCOSA
Scurrying around like that...
What's wrong, White Blood Cell?
Red Blood Cell, step back a little further.
O-Okay!
Do you surrender?
Are you outta moves?
What a letdown.
After you massacred all my buddies!
I'm gonna see to it
that you share the same fate!
Die!
We have succeeded
in capturing the bacterium.
We will now remove the bacterium.
Hey! Hold up! What's going on here?
DRINK CORNER
ALL YOU CAN DRINK
Don't ask me.
Listen to me!
It's no use.
You can't destroy that capsule
from the inside, no matter what.
And this is inside the bronchial tubes.
Do you know what that means?
Wh-What the hell's up with that?
Aren't you ashamed, using tactics like this?
Not really.
Liar! Don't look away from me!
TEA
- Listen to me!
- Red Blood Cell?
I know you can hear me!
Damn you! Stop messing with me!
Can I get you
something to drink, too?
Hey! Don't ignore me!
Okay, I'll have
what you're having.
Here. Tea.
- Well, thank you very much.
- Hey, you! Say something!
What's going on?
Come watch with me over here.
THANKS FOR YOUR HARD WORK...
PUT YOUR AD HERE
LEAVE IT
TO YOUR HELPER T CELLS!
CALL THE WBC
IN TIMES OF TROUBLE
ELIMINATING PARASITES
EOSINOPHILS
No more games!
Wh-Where are you taking me?
Who knows?
Where do you think?
No way!
This is the bronchial tubes.
SNEEZE ONE
SNEEZE
S-Stop it!
Starting the countdown.
Three, two...
One!
Stooop!
Bye-bye, germ.
Achoo!
SNEEZE ONE LAUNCH SUCCESSFUL!!
Now, then...
You're leaving already?
Yeah. Since I have to get back to work.
Um, W-White Blood Cell!
W-Will I...
see you again?
No.
NEW MEMBERS TRAINING
I mean, there are
so many of us White Blood Cells.
NUMBER OF WHITE BLOOD CELLS
N-Now that you mention it,
there are even more of us Red Blood Cells!
NUMBER OF RED BLOOD CELLS
Yeah.
Well, since we both work in the same world,
we'll run into each other someday.
See you.
Right!
Incident! It's Bacteria! They're close!
Kill them! Annihilate them!
All right, then, please take it easy!
Die! You germ!
NEXT EPISODE
PREVIEW
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
So cute!
Isn't it peaceful, White Blood Cell?
I sure hope it is.
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Next episode of "Cells at Work!",
"Scrape Wound."
EPISODE 2:
SCRAPE WOUND
All right! Time to work! Time to work!