The Third Plate
Twenty-Three
The Team Shokugeki has begun!
Instant yakisoba? Really?
Hm? What was that, Senpai?
Don't think for a second that
you can beat me at soba.
Isshiki, do you have no pride?!
I heard you were removed
from the seventh seat
and that you've continued to stay
at some place called Polar Star Dormitory,
a hangout for riffraff.
I say this for your sake!
As a member of the Isshiki family, you should
not be mingling with such lowlifes!
Uh, Shiratsu-kun, was it?
Let's have some quiet, shall we?
He butchered the eel with lightning speed!
All in one stroke of the knife!
The former seventh seat
has formidable skills!
But he is no match for Central.
Let's look forward to the moment
his smile is twisted by defeat.
His skills have not changed.
If he'd chosen a different path, he would've
been rich beyond his wildest dreams.
Why'd he rebel against Central?
That idiot.
Jurio!
Don't be outdone by him!
Show him who you are!
I'm so happy, Isshiki.
Your skills are so sublime.
Whoa!
I don't really get what's going
on here, but he's into it now.
Good, good.
What was that technique
Isshiki-san used just now?
He slit the eel from the stomach
with such precision and speed.
He chose to slit the eel from the stomach.
It's unbelievable.
Eels have no rib cage,
so it's beyond difficult to insert a knife
into the soft body cavity with precision.
Compared to slitting the eel from the back,
this method requires much more
advanced knife technique.
It's hard to imagine him doing this, given how
he's usually naked except for an apron.
Yeah.
Naked except for an apron? What's that about?
Tell me, Miss Secretary!
Don't call me that.
Nikumi-chan!
Slitting the eel from the
back is more mainstream.
I've heard before that slitting
the eel from the stomach
is a technique that developed in Kansai
regions like Osaka and Kyoto.
Why would Isshiki-senpai know that?
Of course he would.
The Isshiki family has operated a traditional
Japanese restaurant in Kyoto's Gion
district since the Muromachi period.
The Kinokuni family in the east,
and the Isshiki family in the west...
Kinokuni
Family
Isshiki
These two families are the two famous
pillars of Japanese cuisine.
What?!
And Kinokuni-senpai and Isshiki-senpai's
connection doesn't end there.
What?
A boy from another family's going
to come live with us, Father?
Kinokuni
You know about the Isshiki
family in Kyoto, don't you?
It's their ancient tradition.
Once the presumed heir turns four years old,
they are to be trained somewhere
far away from their home.
Okay.
Kinokuni Nene
(Age 4)
Our two families are very close.
He's the same age as you, so you
may even become friends.
Say hello, Nene.
He is the Isshiki family's heir, Satoshi-kun.
Isshiki Satoshi
(Age 4)
What? That means...
They're childhood friends?!
Huh.
I suppose that's true.
No, it's not!
He just stayed with us to train!
We didn't become close or anything!
My goodness, you're prickly
as ever today, Kinokuni-kun.
Why are you so against me?
Don't act naïve.
You know why.
Food Wars
The Third Plate
Totsuki Train Arc
Bearing Polar Star Dormitory
The Team Shokugeki is in full swing.
Here comes the First Bout!
Kaburagi Shoko
VS
Megishima Tosuke
The first match is the fifth seat,
Kaburagi Shoko versus the former
third seat, Megishima Tosuke.
The second match is the eighth seat,
Shiratsu Jurio
VS
Isshiki Satoshi
Shiratsu Jurio versus the former
seventh seat, Isshiki Satoshi!
Kinokuni Nene
VS
Yukihira Soma
The third match is the sixth seat,
Kinokuni Nene versus the son
of a diner chef, Yukihira Soma!
Well, it appears the judges
have just now arrived!
Allow me to introduce them to you!
Oh, judges.
They are important, indeed.
That was so heavy.
Um, Miss? Are you okay?
Um, what?
The books she's carrying!
They say "WGO" on them.
Could they be...?
Wow. I've never seen them in person before.
So they're the judges for this Shokugeki.
They came all the way to Japan?
Huh?
Am I the only one who's clueless here?
The World Gourmet Organization.
Their main function is to rank all
fine dining establishments
worldwide out of three stars.
Their assessments are published
once a year in print.
Receiving a rating of even a single star
would catapult a chef into high standing.
On the other hand, there are chefs
who had highly profitable businesses,
but shut down their restaurant because
they lost a star and with it, all confidence.
All chefs respect and fear
that organization, the WGO.
Huh.
Come to think of it, Master Shinomiya
said he was going to get three stars.
I guess that's what he meant.
The printed publication of
their evaluations is a bible.
Also known as "The Book,"
the organization's front line
staff are called Bookmen.
In other words, WGO Bookmen
are our judges today!
Excuse me.
I see the words "Yukihira Diner"
on your shirt.
Oh, yeah.
My family runs a diner.
What about it?
Yukihira...
There is no need to feel bad.
Huh?
Many say that if it's not listed in
The Book, it's not a real restaurant.
That may be true.
But so what?
You're still here, alive!
You should be grateful to your parents!
Huh?
I think she pities me.
Hey, is it gonna be okay
to have them judge us?
Idiot! Don't be rude!
Yukihira Soma!
A lowbie diner shouldn't speak up!
You only make second-rate gourmet food!
WGO would never accept such cooking—
Silence!
I made fun of—
I encouraged him on account of him
not having received any stars yet.
Did she just say she made fun of me?
But the fact that he has zero stars
WGO Marshal, Rank 1
Anne
will have nothing to do with
the dish he's to serve today.
That's right.
WGO Marshal, Rank 2
Charme
The only basis for our decision
will be what's on the plate.
I swear to God and The Book that our
judgment will be absolutely fair.
WGO Marshal, Rank 2
Histoire
So please make a good
dish today, Yukihira Diner.
I thought you were just full of hot air,
but you say some good things.
Hang on!
It's not a very dynamic cooking process.
Is he gonna make it?
Isshiki!
You have no time to be distracted!
My dish will soon be complete!
I will crush you with this dish!
Oops. I suppose I should pick up the pace.
Hmm. I think Isshiki wants to use this match
to make a point not just to Jurio,
but also to Nene and the rest of us.
All right! Done!
Well then, honored judges! Please try it!
Here it comes!
The first one up is our
very own Shiratsu Jurio!
What Italian eel dish has he crafted?
Impressive.
The concentrated and refreshing
flavors of the tomato
and the richness of the eel have given
rise to a most delectable fragrance!
Yes, that is the
dish's greatest, unique charm!
It is a collaboration
between the umami and fat
of the eel, and the richness of the tomato—
Capitone in Umido!
Looks delicious!
Then, without delay...
The eel's umami and fat
are rushing toward me.
They are brilliantly enhanced by the
flavors of olive oil and tomatoes.
Perfection!
This Capitone in Umido has
been wonderfully prepared.
It sure looks really good.
But what's "capitone" and what's "in umido"?
"In umido" means stew.
"Capitone" is an eel.
However, only female eels of
large size are called that.
It's considered an upscale ingredient
due to its meaty, fatty flesh.
Other eels are called anguilla to
differentiate them from the capitone.
There is yet another secret that refines
the delicious flavor of the capitone
in these tomatoes simmered
with the eel, correct?
Ha ragione!
That's right!
The San Marzano tomatoes I selected
are the hidden star of the dish.
San Marzano
This tomato strain has less
water content than the others,
so it prevents the stew from becoming watery,
making possible the creation of a rich sauce.
The depth of flavor provided
by the San Marzano tomatoes
has synergized with the spices
to heighten the eel's flavors.
This polenta, made by boiling
cornmeal into a thick porridge,
then finished to have a crisp outside
and a tender inside, is also wonderful.
The sauce required him to
enhance the garlic's fragrance
and concentrate the onion's sweetness while
reducing the water content of the tomatoes.
The dish will not be perfect unless the
chef communes with the ingredients.
Jurio seems to have proven
himself capable of doing so.
Numerous ingredients and
their numerous melodies
have heightened each other's beauty.
A rondo, indeed!
It's as though the substantial capitone
and tomatoes cleanse your body and soul...
...and then bulks them up!
These delicious flavors...
...make you feel as though
you're being squeezed...
...between two voluptuous breasts!
Meraviglioso!
Well done, Shiratsu Jurio!
It is a wonderful dish that does
justice to your family's reputation!
Of course.
I've been wearing myself
to the bone to hone my skills
in order to catch up to Isshiki.
All right, Isshiki Satoshi! Come at me!
Let's wrap up this ultimate sessione!
Of course I will.
The dish I'm about to serve employs
several special ingredients.
Hey, that's the stuff we had
stored at Polar Star Dormitory.
Several Months Ago
Yeah, I guess we can go with this.
Let's try to make our own
natural cheese, Nikumicchi.
Okay. Cheese, huh.
I'm sure we can get our hands on high-quality
milk through my family connections,
but we lack the knowledge.
Don't worry about that!
We have an expert in fermentation
right here in Polar Star Dormitory.
Why're you so exhausted?
Huh?
I'm researching new directions for the
rice juice with Marui-kun right now,
so I'm short on sleep.
I found resources!
So heavy!
Who knew making smoked food
was tough manual labor?
Hey, why aren't you breaking a sweat?
Once you're done carrying that,
there's more to come.
Let us take a break!
How nice! The joys of youth!
Wait, he's going to use the
ingredient we came up with?
He brought it here?
Yes, I stole it myself!
Why are you looking so proud about it?
Oh, come on.
We were still in the early stages of testing!
You're charming even
when you're mad, Sakaki-kun.
Shiratsu-kun, I'll show you
what cooking means to me.
Isshiki Satoshi of the rebel
team is now serving his dish.
Please enjoy.
My eel dish is Hitsumabushi:
Polar Star Style.
Polar Star Style?
"Hitsumabushi"...
Typically, the dish is first enjoyed by
eating chopped grilled eel with rice.
Then, the dish is savored by adding
condiments such as onions and seaweed,
after which you add a liquid
such as broth and green tea
and eat it like ochazuke.
The dish is meant to be enjoyed
in several stages as it changes.
And yet...
It looks like a cheese risotto.
Wow, he's come up with something special.
Sorry, I know risottos
are your thing, Soma-kun.
Huh, what?
Oh, I just like using rice
cause my family runs a diner.
Yukihira
Insulto!
Insult!
If he just used a mishmash of
ingredients made by his juniors,
there's no way he could have pulled
together a coherent dish!
Let us taste this dish.
This is indeed a cheese risotto.
It seems we are to pour the contents of
this pot over the dish at the very end.
The melted cheese is entangling the rice.
No!
It's so delicious, it's torture...
The Japanese peppers are what
brings this risotto together.
Their vivid, sharp fragrance brings
out the mild richness of the cheese
and allows the delicious
flavors of the eel to explode!
And the key player tying everything
together from the shadows...
...is garlic!
Garlic?!
He used garlic in Japanese cuisine?
The smoked garlic chips made by my juniors
used walnut wood, which enhances
the flavors of seafood.
By using it as crumbled topping,
it also adds some crunchy
texture to the dish.
And what's most important is that this
eel was broiled in the Kansai style.
Unlike the method used in the Kanto style,
the eel is never steamed during this process.
That results in a more crisp
and fragrant broiled eel
with a stronger expression of the eel's fat,
which in turn allowed me to pair it
with a strong ingredient like garlic.
Above all, the garlic is infused
with Ibusaki-kun's passion,
and the blood, sweat, and tears of
his helpers, Aoki-kun and Sato-kun!
Of course it'd be delicious!
Don't say our sweat's in that!
Gross!
This alone is of sufficient sophistication
to qualify it as a gourmet dish,
but what's inside this pot?
It's eel liver soup.
Prepared eel liver and garlic
chips were sauteed in olive oil,
then this ingredient made by
Sakaki-kun and Marui-kun was added
along with dried bonito stock.
It gently melds with the cheese
made by Yoshino-kun and Nikumi-kun
to create a beautiful aftertaste.
Shiratsu-kun...
If you think this dish is delicious,
I'll have you apologize for insulting
everyone at Polar Star Dormitory.
And I don't think of my dish
as something Japanese at all—
I simply made a dish I consider
my own brand of cooking.
In one Shokugeki,
a gourmand who judged Isshiki Satoshi's
dish characterized it as the following...
"An extremely combative Japanese cuisine."
Meraviglioso!
The eel's crisp skin and sizzling fat...
The clear rich flavors of the liver soup...
The ingredients' flavors and
mouthfeel have been unified
into a singular and most
sublime deliciousness!
Its fragrance is too pronounced.
But that allowed it to
complement the fragrant eel.
He transformed the ingredient's
flaw into delicious flavor.
Well, Shiratsu-kun? How's it taste?
I don't care about myself, personally.
But I need to uphold the
honor of people at the dorm.
This isn't about what I want,
but about my responsibilities
as their senior.
So I'd like you to apologize.
You will, won't you?
This dish...
...allows no resistance!
Now, apologize.
Shit!
Mi scusi...
I'm very sorry.
The evaluation is complete!
The winner of the first bout,
second match is...
Isshiki Satoshi!
Isshiki-senpai, you're awesome.
Thank goodness.
Isshiki-senpai...
Using our ingredients without even asking...
What were you going to do if you'd lost?
I trust your work.
I'm still upset!
That was still a prototype.
Mister Isshiki, may I taste
what's in the bottle?
Yes, of course.
What?
I think I understand now what you're
hoping to protect in this Shokugeki.
Exercise your skills to the utmost.
You will receive an absolute and
just evaluation of all your dishes
from us WGO Bookmen.
Jurio! Leave the rest to me.
You did well!
Isshiki...
Meraviglioso.
Too wonderful.
Shiratsu lost, but he looks happy somehow.
Isshiki's strengths came out
full-force in that match.
So he only fights for his juniors' sake, huh.
Heh. He just loves the idea
of being David to our Goliath.
That's the kind of guy he is.
Is he?
I sensed a strong resolve to uphold
his own principles from him.
We still have two matches left in this bout!
First Match
Kaburagi Shoko vs. Megishima Tosuke
Second Match
Shiratsu Jurio vs. Isshiki Satoshi
Third Match
Kinokuni Nene vs. Yukihira Soma
As long as Central wins them both,
there will be no issues!
So precise!
So fast!
She's like a precision machine!
Highly trained soba artisans
can slice noodles to the same width,
down to a tenth of a millimeter.
There is no doubt that she
has reached that level.
Yukihira's starting to slice
his soba noodles, too!
Although with a machine...
The difference in their
intensity is pretty huge.
Yukihira... What kind
of soba is he going for?
Will it be cold or warm soba?
First, I'd like to congratulate you.
Make sure you face me in the second bout.
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
You're the sixth seat, and I'm
the former seventh seat.
You don't have to take it so seriously—
There's no need for you to play dumb anymore.
The only reason I have a
higher rank than you did
is because you were never serious.
Cat's cradle or juggling—which one?
Nene-chan, what's this?
Oh, it's a traditional Japanese
instrument called the dragon flute.
Do you want to try it?
It's really hard to even
make a sound at first.
That's how you've always been.
You easily master techniques
that took me a long time
while looking like you still
haven't tried your hardest.
Can you even begin to understand
how miserable that made me feel?
So I'll show you which one
of us in the 91st class
is the best chef!
Sorry, that will unfortunately
not come to pass.
Because you'll lose to a chef by the
name of Yukihira Soma before that.
What?!
Oh!
Yukihira Soma's bringing something out!
It's a giant wok!
He's putting it over roaring flames!
He was actually serious?!
Instant yakisoba.
Chance
Yakisoba
Cup
All right, time for the finishing touches.
Hey, is that—
Soba?!
No way.
He's stir-frying it!
He's ruining the 8:2 ratio soba he
went to the trouble of making...
The delicate flavors will all be lost.
Yukihira Soma-kun, you will
meet your end here.
In the end, your dish is
a desperate improvisation.
I'll shatter it right along with the
high expectations Isshiki has of you!
Totsuki
Food Wars
The Third Plate
Next Episode  The Basis for Strength
The final stop is coming up.
Please don't miss it.