We are now in a state of emergency.
We have detected
life-threatening damage.
The tissue and blood vessels near the head area
have been severely damaged.
All immune cells,
prepare for an antigen invasion
from the damaged areas,
and hurry to the scene immediately.
EPISODE 13:
"HEMORRHAGIC SHOCK" (PART 2)
"Hemorrhagic Shock." Part 2.
Hey!
WHITE BLOOD CELL
Is anybody there?
Hey! Anybody?
Isn't anybody here?
BLOOD VESSEL
Hey, you guys!
There are no blood cells!
Hey you there!
White Blood Cell?
Hold up! Don't be afraid!
Tell me what's going on.
WHITE BLOOD CELLS
(NEUTROPHILS):
Their main task is
to eliminate foreign
substances from outside,
such as bacteria
and viruses.
The cells that were here...
Don't tell me they're all...
Th-That's right! I saw it myself!
Tens of thousands...
Hundreds of thousands... Millions...
Help us!
No, even more than that!
Zillions of blood cells getting swept up
and sucked toward the mouth of the wound!
And the bleeding still hasn't stopped!
You know what that means, don't you?
There are no Red Blood Cells
to distribute oxygen throughout the body!
The oxygen that we cells need in order to live!
The lungs and the secretion system...
I'm sure the tissue cells all over the body
will do whatever they can,
but there's just nothing
anyone can do to fix this!
NOW CONSTRICTING
Eventually, the inside
of this body will grow cold,
and starting with the distal cells,
we're all going to die from lack of oxygen!
It's all over for this world!
LUNGS
FRAGILE
CONDENSED GAS
Cell!
Are you all right?
I've come to deliver your oxygen!
Can't breathe!
C-Cell?
Oxygen!
Give me some oxygen!
Cell!
Wh-What's the matter?
Senpai, look!
Everybody's acting strangely!
CELL
Still no oxygen delivery?
I can't breathe!
I'm gonna die!
What's going on here?
Are you all right? What happened?
O-Oxygen!
I can't breathe!
Please get a hold of yourself, Cell!
I'll leave this oxygen here!
Please wait! I'll bring you
some new oxygen right away!
Come on, Li'l Kouhai!
Senpai!
I'm not seeing any of our friends around!
What about you?
C-Come to think of it...
WELCOME TO THE LUNGS
What is this?
The lungs!
Why are they pumping so violently?
What is this wind?
Somebody please deliver this oxygen!
The lungs are breathing so hard!
And they're inhaling oxygen!
Still...
Somebody please deliver this oxygen!
It's not circulating
to all parts of the body!
Hurry! Please deliver this!
So,
there aren't nearly enough
Red Blood Cells to deliver it?
Heave-ho!
S-Senpai?
This is no time to stand around and gawk!
We've got to deliver this pronto!
The cells are all waiting for us after all!
Senpai!
Please hold up a second!
How can you have such nerves of steel?
Thank you for waiting!
Here's your new oxygen!
I've come to deliver today's oxygen!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Here's your new oxygen!
Thank you for waiting!
I'll be bringing you
more oxygen right away!
Thank you for waiting!
Here's your oxygen for the day!
I'm here to deliver your oxygen!
I'll be bringing you some new oxygen
right away! Please wait!
This is the blood vessel
leading to the wound area!
DANGER
WE ASK FOR YOUR COOPERATION
PLATELETS
Blood cells, please try
not to get blown away!
This is the entrance to the blood vessel!
Please try not to get blown away!
Blood cells, please be careful
as you move forward!
Let's go!
Dammit!
What's going on?
There are fewer Red Blood Cells passing
through this blood vessel than ever before!
Hurry! Hurry!
BLOOD PRESSURE
We haven't been able to procure
nearly enough, either!
There aren't enough blood cells!
What about oxygen transport?
GIVE ME OXYGEN!
OXYGEN GAS
Not enough supply!
CAN'T BREATHE
If this keeps up, we're not gonna be able
to send enough oxygen to the cells!
Now that it's come to this,
we're gonna have to provide backup!
Use blood pressure
to prod the Red Blood Cells!
Make 'em circulate like there's no tomorrow!
Right!
Start prodding!
Attention. Blood pressure now rising.
Heave-ho!
Heave-hai!
H-Hang in there, Li'l Kouhai!
Hey, no pushing!
It's not me!
I'm getting shoved from behind
by the rising blood pressure!
Stop pushing!
Watch out!
Don't raise the blood pressure
when there's a wound! Idiot!
A SYMPTOM OF HEAVY BLOOD LOSS:
RISING BLOOD PRESSURE:
In the early stages,
the sympathetic nerves
grow agitated,
and blood pressure rises.
A symptom of heavy blood loss.
Rising blood pressure.
In the early stages, the sympathetic nerves
grow agitated, and blood pressure rises.
WARNING
We're in trouble! Increasing the blood pressure
has caused even more heavy hemorrhaging!
Whaaat?
Don't look behind you, Li'l Kouhai!
We're almost there.
So let's hang in there! Okay?
Please, just keep transporting!
A SYMPTOM OF HEAVY BLOOD LOSS:
TEMPERATURE DROP:
Because of a decrease
in the amount of circulating blood,
body temperature drops.
A symptom of heavy blood loss.
Temperature drop.
Because of a decrease in the amount
of circulating blood, body temperature drops.
S-Snow?
A blizzard?
Senpai!
Hold up a second!
In this snow, we can't...
But we've got to go!
If at least you and I
don't keep delivering oxygen,
the cells will all die!
Come on!
Li'l Kouhai!
My hands are so stiff!
Li'l Kouhai?
Li'l Kouhai!
Are you all right?
Give me your hand.
Will you stop already?
Just look around you!
Even if we try our hardest,
do you really believe it'll change anything?
At this point, there's no way
we can supply enough oxygen in time!
Aside from you and me,
there aren't any other Red Blood Cells!
You're just trying to show off
in front of your kouhai,
stubbornly trying to hang in there!
It's so pointless!
Haven't you ever heard of it?
Death from hemorrhagic shock!
Hemorrhagic shock.
HEMORRHAGIC SHOCK:
When the body loses massive amounts of blood
due to external injuries or internal bleeding
from the digestive tract and such,
it can no longer maintain blood pressure,
and consciousness grows hazy, sometimes resulting in fainting.
Unless appropriate measures are taken, it can result in death.
It is said that the body goes into shock
once it loses about a third of its blood supply.
When the body loses
massive amounts of blood
due to external injuries or internal bleeding
from the digestive tract and such,
it can no longer maintain blood pressure,
and consciousness grows hazy,
sometimes resulting in fainting.
Unless appropriate measures are taken,
it can result in death.
It is said that the body goes into shock
once it loses about a third of its blood supply.
Once it loses a third of its blood,
the body dies!
This body doesn't have a chance anymore!
We should—
Hey, stop!
What are you...
I'm going to keep delivering oxygen
until the very end!
Because that's our job!
S-Senpai...
Senpai!
Wait!
Please just stop!
My hands feel heavy.
So do my feet.
Everyone's waiting.
I've got to...
I've got to hurry
and deliver this oxygen!
Die, you miserable germ!
I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
We're going to bulldoze right through them!
Everybody...
is giving it their all!
You idiot! Don't be such a wuss! Live!
UNDER CONSTRUCTION
Everybody, try not to get blown away
by the wind!
I...
have to do this, too!
I've got to deliver...
...this oxygen.
Senpai!
Sorry for being
such a lame senpai.
It's so dazzling.
Hey, you okay?
Wh... Wh... Wh... Wh... Wh...
Who are you?
Where are we?
Beats me!
We're all together, right?
What kind of cell are you?
Jeez, this place is freezing!
Hey, that girl is dressed like a Red Blood Cell.
What kind of work do you do?
You're a young Red Blood Cell,
just like us, aren't you?
Huh? But that uniform design
is a little different.
But she looks like us, doesn't she?
Nice to meet you!
So, why are you all worn out?
You're covered with snow.
U-Um...
The thing is, there was this huge wound...
We all did our best,
but we just didn't have enough people
to deliver the oxygen!
What? You mean, unless we do something,
this body that we're in right now
could be history?
I mean, we got dragged here
without any explanation,
so this is really outrageous!
Hey! Big trouble, you guys!
Such-and-such, yadda yadda.
So you see, no road is long
with good company!
This was all meant to be!
And since we're all Red Blood Cells,
we've got to go with the flow!
I see!
You're absolutely right!
You're so wise!
We may have started out in different workplaces,
but our job is the same.
All together now, let's take this oxygen!
And deliver it!
Yeah!
These Red Blood Cells,
who appeared out of nowhere,
managed to send oxygen
to every corner of the body in a flash.
Who are you?
UNDER
CONSTRUCTION
Please plug it up with your fibrin!
Okay!
Who are you?
I'm a Red Blood Cell!
You don't have to hold your breath anymore!
Who are you?
What a nice place this body is.
Even if it's kind of in a shambles.
And then...
LAST WORDS:
PLEASE HANG
THE BEDDING TO DRY
-CELL
I'm done for—
Don't be so prepared to die!
Oxy... gen...
Huh?
I've come to deliver your oxygen!
Please forgive me for being so late!
You saved my life!
Thanks to the efforts
of this great horde of Red Blood Cells,
and of each of the other cells,
the dangers of hemorrhagic shock
were averted.
I finally managed to make my deliveries.
Hey, hold up, you...
I got you!
Hey.
Good job.
I wonder how many blood cells we lost.
I don't know the exact number,
but probably too many to count.
Where did those new Red Blood Cells
come from, I wonder.
Who knows?
But thanks to them, we were saved.
BLOOD DONATION:
To provide blood free of charge
for transfusions and blood product manufacture.
As blood for transfusions has a short shelf life,
blood donation is a constant need.
One day, out of the blue,
we got sucked into a strange tube,
and I don't know how to explain it,
but we got twirled around,
then they made us sleep in a huge room!
And then, the next thing we knew,
we were here!
TRANSFUSION:
A type of treatment in which
missing blood components
are replenished. Among
the components that can be
replaced via transfusions
are red blood cells, platelets,
plasma components and clotting factor.
The appropriate blood product
is selected and then transfused.
Transfusion.
A type of treatment in which
missing blood components are replenished.
RELAXING TEA
How strange!
This is a different body
than the one we were in before,
but we're glad to be able to work
in a body again.
It's like they've always been here.
Wonder where they came from. Seriously.
All right, now I'm going to go
look for my li'l kouhai!
Okay.
Thank you so much for the tea!
Senpai! Senpai!
Li'l Kouhai!
There's something
I'd like to say to you, Senpai.
- Y-You look so fierce!
Regarding my rookie training...
Thank you very much!
Until now, I've always thought of myself
as one of the more competent ones, but...
Oh, well, I actually am, but...
Yeah!
But today, I learned something important
from you regarding work, Senpai.
Work isn't just about knowledge,
but also experience,
and it's also important
to have a passionate heart!
Li'l Kouhai...
Thank goodness!
I was afraid there wasn't anything
I could teach you,
but now that you put it that way...
S-Senpai, please don't cry.
I'm sorry that I'm such a lame senpai!
But let's keep working together
from now on, too! Okay?
Oh yes, nice to meet you. Who are you?
Nice to meet you!
Hey, right back atcha!
S-S-S-Sorry, wrong person!
Huh? Huh?
Where are you, Li'l Kouhai?
It wasn't long
Hey you! Are you all right?
before Red Blood Cell found herself
getting flustered by her competent kouhai
and this horde of new friends.
ARTERY
Thank you for waiting!
All right!
Sorry! It's still under construction!
Sorry for the inconvenience!
Hey, Memory! How are you?
Thank you for waiting!
This is your oxygen for the day.
Thanks for your hard work!
That was a massive amount again today!
Hey you!
Move it, you slowpokes!
Huh?
Hey, Red Blood Cell.
What are you doing in a place like this?
White Blood Cell!
Don't tell me you're lost.
O-Of course I'm not lost!
I've matured, you know!
Well, but your map's upside down.
H-Here!
I was just about to make a delivery here!
Antigens!
I'll kill 'em all!
Get back here, you antigen!
Red Blood Cell, good luck to you!
Right!
Target sighted!
Good luck to you, too, White Blood Cell!
Um...
That...
I'm so sorry!
Thank you for waiting!
Here's your oxygen for the day!
The cells are all working
energetically again today.