EPISODE 12:
"HEMORRHAGIC SHOCK" (PART 1)
"Hemorrhagic Shock." Part 1.
Inside the human body,
roughly 37.2 trillion cells
work energetically,
DENDRITE
all day every day.
ANTIBODY ENCYCLOPEDIA
24 hours and 365 days.
WHITE BLOOD CELL
They are all working very hard.
UNDER
CONSTRUCTION
PLATELETS
This is the inside of a human body.
Welcome. We are happy to see you.
This is the pulmonary alveoli.
We will collect your carbon dioxide here.
OXYGEN GAS
Thank you for waiting.
Please take your oxygen.
All righty! Next, I'll deliver
this oxygen to everyone in the liver.
Okay!
FRAGILE
CONDENSED GAS
Here I go!
Hey, someone's working hard.
Senpai!
I see you're starting to get the hang of it.
Though you're still making blunders.
You really think so?
Senpai, it's all thanks
to your warm guidance every—
Oh, forget that.
I'm not one to stand on ceremony.
Oh, so soft!
Anyway, there's something
I'd like you to do for me.
Wh-What could that be?
I'd like you to take on
this rookie Red Blood Cell, and train her.
Nice to meet you.
- So there you have it.
- Huh?
I'm counting on you. Okay, good lu—
W-Wait!
H-Hold up a second, Senpai!
I-I can't do that!
Not when I'm not even full-fledged myself!
Don't be like that! This is part of your job!
When you were a rookie,
you had other Red Blood Cells
looking after you, too, didn't you?
Th-That's right.
So think of this as your way
of paying them back.
That's how it was for me, too.
Got it? Try to get along!
And if anything happens,
let me know right away!
O-Okay!
PULMONARY VEIN
N-Nice to meet you!
Likewise...
Senpai.
Jeez, she's so calm and collected!
Senpai?
Why are you speaking so formally to me?
I am your kouhai, aren't I? Theoretically.
Oh, that's right, you are!
Th-That's right!
Now I've gone and thrown my kouhai
into a state of confusion!
Jeez, I'm such an idiot!
I'm the senpai here,
so I need to be strong!
It would only cause her misery
if she sees me as a flaky senpai,
so take charge!
I'm her senpai! Okay!
Now then, l-let me show you
all kinds of things!
Yes, I look forward to your guidance.
Um, first off, my notes...
Huh? Huh?
Listen, let me start by explaining
what it is we do.
Oh, right.
The six functions of the blood.
One, retaining moisture.
Two, exchanging gases.
Three, transporting nutrients and such.
Four, regulating body temperature.
Five, protecting the body.
Six, repairing wounds.
Of these six, our main job as Red Blood Cells
is the exchange of gases, right?
Although we also take on
the extra task of transporting nutrients
which isn't really our job.
After we deliver oxygen
to the tissue cells, they burn up glucose,
producing energy,
carbon dioxide and water.
And since carbon dioxide is toxic
to the body and must be expelled,
we transport it to the pulmonary alveoli,
and exchange it for oxygen.
Then rinse, lather and repeat, I hear.
And that's why we, Red Blood Cells,
are indispensable
What can I teach this kid...
no, I mean this hotshot?
for maintaining the cycle of life, correct?
And I am honored to be charged
with such a job.
Uh, Senpai?
I see, so you already know all that, huh?
Then...
for now, let's go circulate for real!
It's okay if you don't understand.
Just try to learn stuff as you go along!
Just do it!
Oh right, I suppose.
Huh? Come to think of it,
what should I say to a kouhai?
Introduce myself?
If only she'd save the job descriptions
and all for when we're on the move.
This one's a little inefficient, I see.
Um...
Turn right here? Is that the path?
Hey, you! This is the lymphatic vessel!
No Red Blood Cell brats allowed!
I-I made a wrong turn!
That was scary!
Sorry to shock you like that.
Oh, you didn't.
I'm always making wrong turns.
I'm such an airhead.
No.
But that person right now
was more aggressive than he needed to be.
That was what didn't sit well with me.
After all,
it's not our job to get screamed at
by that person, is it now?
Oh yes.
I mean...
Hey, hey, hey!
Die! Die!
It's White Blood Cell!
Senpai, you know those
from the immune system?
Yes! They're all so nice!
Hey you!
What are you talking about?
Neutrophils are a gang of anomalies
who confuse justice with violence.
Th-That's not true!
He's gentle when you talk to him.
Thanks for your hard work,
White Blood Cell!
She doesn't care.
Yo, Red Blood Cell. Good work!
That Red Blood Cell next to you...
Is she your kouhai?
That's right!
I've been given the task of training her,
and I've been showing her the ropes!
Not that I've taught her anything yet.
Is that right? Nice to meet—
Wait, it's still breathing?
You see, there are different types
of White Blood Cells working in this blood vessel.
Like Neutrophils and other kinds!
Hey, White Blood Cell!
Tell her all about it!
Huh? Oh sure!
We, White Blood Cells,
have several types of jobs.
Neutrophils, Eosinophils, Basophils...
H-Hey you!
Particularly Macropha—
Die!
And then, you have
your lymphatic vessels, too.
You bastard!
Everyone's a little scared
of White Blood Cell here,
but he's really such a nice guy!
Here's the finishing blow!
So I think
you should be friends!
Senpai, blood spray! Get out of the way!
Sorry! I'm really sorry, okay?
That's your brand-new uniform,
and now it's sticky with blood spatter!
Forgive me.
No. I don't mind at all.
Look, since you're soaking wet,
I brought you something warm to drink.
Which do you want? Coffee or tea?
There's milk and sugar, too.
Let's both drink and warm up!
No, normally, shouldn't you
bring me a towel and not a drink?
She's absolutely right!
This won't do!
I've got to be more senpai-like!
As for who we're going to deliver the oxygen
we're transporting from the lungs...
I know. Anyway, we'd better
hurry up and hand it over.
R-Really?
Then, when you hand it over,
look them in the eye and say with a smile,
in a clear voice,
"I've come to deliver your..."
- You don't have to tell me that, either.
- Oh, and then...
after they take it,
get their signature or stamp,
Um...
and some people will say,
"Thank you for your hard work."
Senpai...
So, I always say,
"Oh no, I'm just doing my job."
The oxygen...
Never mind that!
Just hand it over already!
This person is called Eosinophil.
I know that.
She's not just pretty!
She's really amazing, too!
Pret—
You want to know how amazing?
She took on this gigantic enemy
called a "parasite,"
and stabbed it from mid-air like this!
Oh hey...
I wish you could've seen her that day!
I mean, she was totally, unbelievably cool!
P-P-Please, don't heap
so much praise on me! Really!
Senpai, you're embarrassing her.
The little Platelets' job
is to close up wounds,
and even though they're tiny, they protect
the peace inside this blood vessel.
I know all that.
Senpai!
Please don't get tangled in the fibrin!
Thank you for your cooperation!
Hello there!
Dendritic Cell, Macrophage,
thank you for your hard work!
Oh my.
By any chance, are you a trainer now?
That's great! You're all grown up!
Oh please, no!
I've still got a long ways to go!
Senpai, we'd better make that delivery.
Okay! Right, let's go!
All right, if you'll excuse us please!
Senpai, I don't think it's that way.
Let's take breaks here and there
when we get tired!
GLUCOSE
Right.
I told you!
That wasn't my fault, all right?
You let out too much histamine!
That was definitely the cause!
Right, Memory?
What do you say?
Um... Um... Um... Where? Where? Where?
Memory!
I can't remember a thing!
Now, now, just calm down, Memory!
Jeez, would you mind
not losing it all of a sudden?
You're a grownup.
Don't ever let things faze you!
Yummy!
Oh my!
Senpai, wrong place!
Senpai, you'll be in the way if you stand there.
Step aside please.
Senpai, you're going the wrong way.
Senpai, please get a hold of yourself.
Senpai!
Look, Senpai!
Wow, is this where they produce
all the transmitters?
That's right.
There are a bunch of different types, too.
Are you a rookie?
Yes.
Huh? Where's Senpai?
Sob...
Red Blood Cell...
Wonder if she's handling
her kouhai all right.
Senpai?
S-Sorry for being
such an unreliable senpai!
No, please don't worry about it.
This time, I'm going to do
a good job guiding you!
Let's see... So this is that way,
and that way is...
If you're going back to the lungs
from here, make a right. Right.
Like this...
Right, I think! Yeah!
What? Is it that complex? This map?
CELL
Let's go!
New cells are born
and go to work.
Inside the body,
a day just like any other was unfolding.
T CELLS
ROAD CLOSED
Yes.
That is, until this moment.
Li'l Kouhai!
Senpai...
What? Wh-What's going on here?
I don't know.
Hey! Are you okay?
White Blood Cell! Platelet!
What in the world happened?
I'm not sure!
But the order is for all blood cells
to gather in the center of the body!
You'd better hurry
or the blood cells here will...
Look!
This overpowering blood pressure
is sweeping them towards us!
We're getting swept away!
Senpai! What's causing
this spike in blood pressure?
I don't have a clue, either!
Broadcast Will Begin Shortly
What's this? What happened?
Emergency! All migrating White Blood Cells,
please gather immediately!
Hey, no pushing!
What's going on anyway?
What's the damage?
Extremely severe issues
are cropping up everywhere.
It's chaos out in the field,
and it looks like it's going to take time
to get to the bottom of this!
At this rate, it's only a matter of time
before we're invaded by antigens. Damn!
Captain!
All right.
We have no choice!
As of now,
I'm declaring a state of emergency!
State of Emergency
We are now in a state of emergency.
We have detected
life-threatening damage!
The tissue and blood vessels near the head area
have been severely damaged.
No way.
All immune cells,
prepare for an antigen invasion
from the damaged areas,
and hurry to the scene immediately.
I repeat.
We are now in a state of emergency.
We have detected
life-threatening damage.
The tissue and blood vessels near the head area
have been severely damaged.
All immune cells,
prepare for an antigen invasion
from the damaged areas,
and hurry to the scene immediately.
All right!
Let's go!
All Platelets are requested
to gather at the damaged areas at once.
Please stop the bleeding immediately.
Excuse us! Please let us through!
All Red Blood Cells are requested
to continue transporting oxygen
in order to maintain homeostasis.
All right! Let's keep transporting!
That way!
What's going on?
Come on!
Get flustered later, okay?
For now, let's deliver this oxygen!
PRIDE
SINCERITY
Welcome to the heart!
Hey, don't push!
This is weird.
The blood flow's faster than usual!
And the heartbeat's getting faster!
Stop pushing!
The flow is really fast!
Is something wrong?
I'm sure it'll be fine!
RIGHT ATRIUM
RIGHT VENTRICLE
But the body temp hasn't gone up!
All right! Release a cold sweat! Hurry!
STATE OF THE SWEAT PORES
So cold!
Let's hurry!
Now's our chance
to take over this body for our—
Damn! Those White Blood Cells
show up so soon in the tissue!
I'll have to escape somewhere
far from this vessel!
You're not getting away!
I'm getting closer to the wound, huh?
So the Red Blood Cells must be
under attack by the antigens there!
I should look for them!
It's so quiet in here.
No way!
Impossible!
No blood cells...
in sight!
We are now in a state of emergency.
We have detected life-threatening damage.
The tissue and blood vessels near the head area
have been severely damaged.
All immune cells,
prepare for an antigen invasion
from the damaged areas,
and hurry to the scene immediately.
NEXT EPISODE
PREVIEW
Where are all the blood cells?
Don't tell me they're all...
Th-That's right! I saw it myself!
I need oxygen!
Please transport this oxygen!
S-Senpai?
It's all over for this world!
EPISODE 13:
"HEMORRHAGIC SHOCK" (PART 2)
I'm going to transport oxygen
until the very end!