The Third Plate
Thirteen
Saiba Joichiro...
He's... my dad.
Saiba-sama and Yukihira-kun...
father and son...
Saiba-senpai...
I will achieve a total
revolution of this world
in order to save victims
like you, Saiba-senpai.
Totsuki
Are we really going ahead with this?
I've said it before... I'm not the
type to make public speeches...
Start talking, Tsukasa!
If only Isshiki or Nakiri were here...
And how much more time do
I have before we go live?
The cameras are already rolling.
Talk!
What?!
Um, hello. I'm Tsukasa Eishi from Central.
Advancement Exam
Polar Star
Dormitory
I'm here today to tell you all
about the major event awaiting high-school
first-years at the end
of the second semester—
the advancement exam.
Last year, more than half of
the first-years left the Academy
due to the excessively rigorous exam.
But from now on, that will change.
Director Azami has liberated
you from unnecessary weeding.
You can easily pass most of the exam
by demonstrating mastery of the
techniques we have taught you in class.
You are no longer bound by
the old, outdated system.
If you side with Central, you can
all become first-rate chefs!
But the exams will also clearly
demonstrate what happens to those of you
who do not fall in line with
Director Azami's vision.
Um, well, that's it.
Whew, I was so nervous.
Totsuki
Next time, you or Kinokuni
should do it, Rindo.
No way.
I refuse.
The advancement exam, huh.
Having it at the end of second
semester sounds super early,
but I guess we'll just have
to put our backs to it
if we want to be second-years, huh?
What, what?
Why are y'all so glum?
Didn't you notice anything
about what they said?!
Central basically declared us
rebels as targets in the exam.
That announcement was tantamount
to a death sentence.
It was a notice that anyone who does
not obey Nakiri Azami will be expelled!
Sorry, Mom.
Sorry, harbor folk...
You all sent me out to Tokyo for nothing.
I need to write a letter
to the folks back home.
I have such fond memories of the
fun we had at the camp from hell.
The camp from hell...
The Stagiaire we endured.
The Stagiaire...
What are you doing?
The Moon Festival where we all came together.
You don't have to get that depressed...
The Moon Festival...
Calm down, everyone.
You should all write letters, too.
The exams will also clearly demonstrate
what happens to those of you
who do not fall in line with
Director Azami's vision.
Who is it?
Door's open.
Nakiri?
What's up? You need something?
U-Um...
About the match with Tsukasa-san!
Any complaints you might have about my not
choosing your dish are unfounded, okay?
It's your fault for taking on
a match you couldn't have won!
Well, yeah. I was outmatched,
so that was a no-brainer.
What? F-Fine, as long as you understand.
Is that all?
N-No!
I'm actually here to talk
about something else.
I don't really get it, but sure, have a seat.
Until a certain day, it may
have been that I...
No, I definitely did not have
any strong feelings about food.
As someone with the God Tongue,
I was forced to face an overwhelming
number of dishes on a daily basis.
I thought I had no choice.
No choice but to be disappointed
by what I tasted every single day.
That's when I met Saiba-sama.
It was a short while after
Alice left for Scandinavia.
That day, my taste-testing appointment
was canceled, a rare occurrence.
There were no other visitors, so I
remember it being very quiet at home.
What's that?
Grandfather...
Who are you with?
What a wonderful smell...
Hungry...
Erina?
Come now, Senzaemon-dono.
This isn't what we agreed to.
I only came because you said you'd
make sure no one else would be around.
My taste-testing appointment
was canceled by the client.
I see.
Erina, this man is an old friend of mine.
This is a private meal.
I'm sorry, but—
I'm sorry.
I'll go now.
Hungry...
Erina-chan, was it?
I see.
So you're Azami's...
If you'd like, you may stay and try some.
It's a bit lonely with just
the two of us at the table.
There you go. Go ahead.
I can feel a warm glow
spreading from deep within...
This is totally different from
anything else I've ever eaten.
It's fun.
I'm having fun!
U-Um...
May I know your name?
It's Saiba.
That was the first time I ever
thought food was wonderful.
Then...
Never allow an imperfect dish to pass.
Anything other than what I,
your father, acknowledge is trash.
Filth.
Garbage.
Six months later was when
Father's "education" began.
I still remember the wonder I felt
when I ate Saiba-sama's cooking.
But... I also understand where
Father's principles are coming from.
There are so many imperfect
dishes in the world...
I grew up seeing the reality of
it for as long as I can remember.
I don't know anymore what food means to me.
I'm very lost, not knowing what to believe in.
Hmm...
Sorry.
I came here on an impulse,
but of course I'm just bothering
you by telling you all this.
Excuse me.
Hey, hang on.
Maybe you just need to taste
it one more time, huh?
I'll make it for you.
I'll make Yukihira food for
you right here, right now!
Please wait a moment, Nakiri Erina-dono!
Erina-sama.
Erina-sama, where are you?
Erina-sama!
What's up, Miss Secretary?
Don't call me that!
I can't find Erina-sama anywhere!
Maybe she's using the
restroom or taking a bath?
I looked, but she wasn't there!
Azami-dono may have abducted her!
That must be it!
Azami-dono took her because I
let my guard down for a moment!
How could this have happened
with me by her side?!
I could've prevented this with a body double
or 3D printer or body-swap ninja technique—
I think she's in Soma-kun's room...
What?!
You're going to have me taste
Yukihira food here right now?
And what would that accomplish, exactly?
The dish Saiba-sama prepared
was wonderful beyond comparison
to the likes of your crude creations!
Oh, you're not all meek anymore!
You're back to your normal self.
Dad trained me hardcore at home, you know.
Maybe you'll remember something if
you taste some Yukihira food, yeah?
Hmph.
And what are you planning to make?
A tempura bowl.
A tempura bowl?
Well, just wait and see.
I'll let you taste something
I'm really proud of.
He totally just made that face he makes when
he's about to create something grotesque!
What kind of tempura are you
planning on making, Yukihira-kun?
He's going to serve that to the God Tongue.
If her sensitive palate were to
meet one of Yukihira's grotesque dishes...
In the worst case scenario, death.
It'll be fine!
Soma-kun's preparing a dish because he has
something he wants Nakiri-san to understand.
Megumi...
Hearing you say it...
...as someone who's fallen victim
to his grotesque dishes the most...
You've got zero credibility.
Yukihira...
Soma-kun...
Bonito's good.
Batter's good.
I already had some rice soaking,
so that was lucky!
Hang on tight.
I'll serve up an unbelievably
tasty tempura bowl!
Yukihira Soma, you look just
like you did that day...
when you were facing the Elite Ten's
first seat, Tsukasa Eishi.
Despite challenging an insurmountable wall,
you still looked like you were having
an incredible amount of fun cooking.
I'm sure I looked like that
when I was little, too.
Erina-sama, you have a responsibility
to the Nakiri family.
Please prioritize the
family name over your own self.
That's the God Tongue.
I should curry favor with her now.
Hey, Erina!
I'm going to become the top chef
at Totsuki Academy some day!
I think it'll be really fun
to perfect the dishes I love!
I'm not going to hold back
just because we're cousins!
Let's give it our best, okay?
R-Right. Okay.
Sorry, Alice.
I don't think cooking's fun at all...
You're looking depressed again.
You're usually all high and mighty,
but you sometimes get like this.
Wh-What's your point?
Perk up, will you?
After all, I'm super stoked that
I can finally get back at you
for what happened the day we first met.
It's disgusting!
Just you wait!
I'll make you say "delicious!"
Today's the day I'll make
you say "delicious!"
Here you go!
You have confidence, if nothing else.
What dish could you have
possibly prepared for me?
I can answer that.
It's a Yukihira-Style Chicken's Egg Tempura Bowl!
Chicken's egg tempura?
What does he mean by that?
What?
The egg white is barely set,
and the yolk is perfectly soft-boiled!
It's silky smooth!
What?
So he made raw egg tempura?
How did he even fry it?
You can't just chuck a raw egg into
hot oil to get a tempura egg, right?
The batter wouldn't stick
to it in the first place.
No way! Did he fry it inside its shell?
Is she supposed to eat it shell and all?
Did he batter and fry a
soft-boiled egg, perhaps?
No, the heat would've fully cooked the yolk.
How did he make this dish?
Mysterious, huh?
Aren't you curious?
You're as irritating as usual!
The secret's inside here.
You took the egg from the freezer?!
That's right!
This tempura was made by coating
a frozen raw egg with batter!
That's the star of this tempura bowl.
Peel a frozen egg, dip it in batter,
then fry it up nice and crisp.
Drizzle a good amount of sauce
on freshly-made piping-hot rice,
pair the egg tempura with fried perilla,
pour more sauce on top,
and it's done.
Well, just dig in!
I see.
But novelty foods don't impress me.
A dish with egg as its main
ingredient will be simple.
That means the chef's skills
and the ingredients' quality
are directly reflected by the dish!
Let's hope you won't regret serving
this dish to the God Tongue.
Hey! Erinacchi's gonna taste it!
Yeah... I wonder if it's up to snuff?
Ryoko-chan?
I actually saw Yukihira-kun
making a bulk purchase earlier.
Of bargain eggs...
Bargain Eggs
Sold for 106 yen a dozen...
What, bargain eggs?
That's not good.
Since infancy, Erina-sama has been surrounded
by only select, high-quality ingredients.
Who knows how her body might react
if she were to taste something cheap?
What?
Erinacchi!
Don't!
I could tell right away
that the egg you prepared is different
from those of high-class silky fowl
and other brand name eggs.
This egg is of the same quality as those
served at the common kitchen table.
It should be a far cry from refined cuisine.
And yet...
How...
How is it even possible to achieve...
such delicate and complex... flavors?!
About how freezing changes the egg...
There's another advantage to it.
It intensifies the flavor of the yolk.
The flavor... intensifies?
Freezing chicken eggs causes the proteins
to coalesce into a gel-like state.
That results in a creamy,
gelatinous mouthfeel,
and a much richer yolk flavor.
Basically, freezing the egg
is the single most important
contributor to this dish's taste!
There's also a generous amount
of a sweet-and-spicy umami sauce,
a Yukihira special blend.
It's a strongly-flavored sauce with a
bonito stock base, soy sauce, and mirin.
There's no question that it pairs
well with the egg and rice!
But if you used an egg
that's too rich in flavor,
the overall dish would become overwhelming.
Is that why you...?
That's right!
The frozen egg's mouthfeel and richness,
plus the special sauce's strong flavors—
It's best to use a lighter-tasting
egg to maximize the two components!
Bargain Eggs
Oh, right!
So he chose bargain eggs for a reason!
Good job, Soma-kun!
Come to think of it,
eggs were the topic you assigned back then.
Don't you think this is the perfect dish
to settle our score once and for all?
How...
Hm?
How did you even come up with this idea?
It's common knowledge that
freshness is key to egg quality.
Besides, isn't it the norm
to focus on obtaining the
rarest and highest-quality eggs?
And yet, how did you...
How did you come up with this—
Because this is more fun.
This is just my opinion,
but I don't think people who
only know one "correct" answer
can get themselves to reach
even greater heights.
Besides, above all...
Um, how did you come up with those
combinations of ingredients?
Each dish was so innovative.
Unconventional, yet meticulous...
Do you know from the start that
the dish will turn out well?
Nope.
What?
Whenever I test a new dish,
I'm 50 percent certain and
50 percent taking a gamble.
Even today, several dishes were
using your gramps as a test subject.
Why do you go so far?
That's obvious.
If you know exactly where
you're headed, it's no fun at all.
Ah, that's right.
I remember now.
I...
...wanted to do that kind of cooking.
I remember now.
Listen, Erina.
Only dishes I acknowledge and Central
creates can be considered food.
No.
Eradicating all else as
"feed" from the Academy
and nurturing the entire
student body into a loyal army
will strengthen Totsuki as a whole.
No.
What I advance as true gourmet food
will become absolute justice.
No!
Father, I believe the
chefs and their dishes...
want to be free.
So, how was it?
How was the Yukihira special?
So, let's hear it for the taste, Nakiri.
It was delicious, yeah?
Delicious?
Right?
I've decided!
Huh?
Yukihira-kun!
Do exactly what I'm about to tell you!
Huh?
Tomorrow morning at seven o'clock!
Have all the Polar Star Dormitory
first-years assemble before the entrance!
S-Sure.
Fine by me, but how was the taste?
Okay, I'm counting on you!
I have to make preparations!
H-H-H-Hey!
What about the taste?!
And one more thing!
Tell Tadokoro-san that she can dispose
of the letter she was writing home.
Huh?
I wonder what happened.
The Next Morning
Brr...
It's technically winter now.
I guess we won't have much longer to
breathe in the morning air at the dorm.
Our lives are over once the
advancement exam happens.
I wonder what Nakiri-san wants,
gathering all of us here.
Oh, she didn't tell me anything.
Erina-sama...
Oh, Erinacchi!
Ahem...
Good day, Polar Star Dormitory residents.
What the hell?
Hmph.
You all look dejected again, like before.
Huh?
It's obvious now what the
outcome of the advancement exam would be,
before it even happens.
Maybe it'd be better for all of you
to just leave the academy now?
Wh-What's wrong with you?!
You had us all show up just to tell us that?!
We all want to keep on cooking
at this academy, too!
Why...?
You didn't have to say it like that!
It's been some time since I came
into this dormitory's care.
During that time, I have sampled
your creations numerous times.
At times, they tasted unusual.
At other times, they tasted absurd.
I've lost count of how many times
I scolded you all for it!
But your dishes were always free!
If you stay down like you are now,
you will be terminated without even
getting to build on your strengths!
How pathetic!
Is that really how you want things to end?!
B-But how can we pass the exam, anyway?
There's no question about how!
You'll have to get through it
with the power of your cooking!
Wow.
She's starting to sound like Yukihira.
Erina-sama!
I've started to think about
what I really want to do, too.
If you have the determination
to survive this,
I will support you using everything I
have in my power as the God Tongue!
If you don't have the willpower
to survive, then just leave now!
Those who stay will face the exam with me!
Come!
If you are true chefs with any pride at all,
follow me!
Totsuki
Food Wars
The Third Plate
Next Episode  Onward on the Totsuki Train
Hop on that train, and go, go, go!