The Third Plate
Fifteen
Tokyo International Airport
The first-years should be in the
middle of the second stage by now.
Who knows if we'll actually participate,
but it's always better to be prepared.
What's the matter, Akanegakubo?
I hate planes.
I don't want to go!
Don't be a spoiled brat.
Let's go.
No!
Totsuki Elite Ten
Akanegakubo Momo
Saito Somei
It's great to tour Hokkaido for free!
Totsuki Elite Ten
Kinokuni Nene
Eizan Etsuya
Hey, Tsukasa, look!
It looks really tasty!
Rindo... Don't forget about the exams, okay?
Totsuki Elite Ten
Kobayashi Rindo
Former Totsuki Elite Ten
7th Seat
Isshiki Satoshi
Former Totsuki Elite Ten
8th Seat
Kuga Terunori
Former Totsuki Elite Ten
3rd Seat
Megishima Tosuke
Totsuki Elite Ten
1st Seat
Tsukasa Eishi
Totsuki Elite Ten
10th Seat
Nakiri Erina
Food Wars
The Third Plate
Totsuki Train Arc
The train might've stopped
in Sapporo Station,
Jeanne D'Arc Rises
but we totally went right
through the city itself.
It's too bad, given that it's
a famous sightseeing spot.
Totsuki Academy Advancement Exams
Stage Two Examination Hall
We got taken to the middle of nowhere.
There's nothing but mountains around here.
I wish we could've taken the
time to walk around and stuff,
like in Odori Park.
Hi, everyone.
You must be tired after the long train trip!
I am Endo, Totsuki lecturer and
your examiner for the second stage.
This stage will be an individual exam.
Also, instead of specifying
an ingredient to prepare,
you are to make a noodle dish!
Noodle...
...dish?
Speaking of noodles, Hokkaido is famous
for having a wide variety of ramen.
Sapporo ramen, Hakodate ramen,
Asahikawa ramen, and so on.
There are many restaurants renowned
for their udon and soba, too!
Hokkaido is the top domestic producer
of buckwheat by far, actually.
Given how vast the prefecture is,
it's not surprising that
Hokkaido gave rise to
a diversity of noodle dishes that
reflect regional differences.
With that in mind, let's try
making a noodle dish today!
So we can make any noodle dish?
When there are so many
options, it's hard to choose.
But there are only basic ingredients here.
What?
We have many different kinds of noddles here.
In addition to green onions
and other basic vegetables,
we have already prepared basic
components such as broth and stock.
But those aren't enough to construct
a gourmet dish, as you know.
So you'll be tasked with sourcing
any missing ingredients.
If you can present a single serving
of a noodle dish that can impress me,
you'll pass!
You have three hours!
Seriously? We have to start
by getting ingredients?
But if we get a taxi, we can get to an
urban area within thirty minutes or so.
The central wholesale market's close, too.
We'll have to get high-quality ingredients.
Enter the exam hall in the order in which
your name is called and start cooking.
Erina-sama, this way to Hall A, please.
Okay.
The next three, off to Hall B!
Next, Hall C!
H-Huh?
We rebels are being left until the very end.
Next!
Ibusaki Shun, Marui Zenji,
Isami Aldini—to Hall A!
Oh, we got called.
Sakaki Ryoko, Arato Hisako, Nakiri
Alice, Kurokiba Ryo—to Hall B!
Yoshino Yuki, Mito Ikumi,
Sato Shoji, Aoki Daigo!
You're in Hall C!
The remaining three of you, to Hall D!
Hall D
Uh, Mister Examiner?
Even though we're supposed
to make a noodle dish,
there are no noodles left.
I believe I told you.
You are to source any
ingredients you don't have.
That's what you need to do for this exam!
Look!
There are barely any ingredients
like flour or rice flour left
that might help us make noodles!
I see how it is.
They won't even give us any ingredients.
But what's the big deal?
Sapporo is a major city.
I'm sure we can find a noodle factory.
We can hand-make noodles by getting flour
and buckwheat flour and stuff, too.
Yeah.
I'm sure we'll figure something
out in three hours.
All right!
Now that that's settled, let's go!
That wasn't the only reason why you
weren't called until the very end.
What?
I'll try to call a taxi.
Huh?
That mansion all the way up in the mountains?
Sorry, that's not possible right now.
You'll have to wait for the
snow plows to come through.
I see.
We have no way of getting out!
If we were in a novel or a movie,
someone would definitely get
killed right about now.
Rock, paper...
No way!
You can't be serious about walking!
Do you want to get lost in the mountains?!
Severe Storm in Sapporo Until Evening
The snow that began falling around
noon has quickly intensified
into a major blizzard in the Sapporo
mountains rarely observed in recent years.
The other students have all passed the exam.
If we can fail those who remain,
my job is done.
Farewell, rebels.
Glory to Central!
What?
Internal Line 1
What is it?
Lecturer Endo!
The rebels are somehow, uh...
Just please come now!
Takumi!
Once you have enough for your
own dish, send the ingredients over!
Right!
We need enough for Tadokoro-san, too.
Don't use too much!
H-How are they starting
prep like nothing's wrong?!
There are no more noodles left!
Did they manage to get
noodles in this blizzard?!
No, impossible!
Why are you looking at us
like that, Mister Examiner?
You didn't honestly think you could stop
us with something like that, did you?
After all, we've been through
training a hundred times worse
than childish tricks like this.
Help
Well, hang on tight.
We'll serve up
the ultimate bowl of noodles!
Th-They're working steadily, as though
they already have noodles ready to go.
Hmph! It's just an act!
There's no way they will pass
under these circumstances!
They're completely finished!
I'm going back to my waiting room!
Endo-san!
What now?
Er, well, Hall C...
And apparently Hall A and Hall B, too...
It's hard to believe, but...
All the rebels are finishing
up their noodle dishes!
What?!
Mister Examiner, if you wanted to fail us,
you really shouldn't have
left this lying around.
Potatoes?
Home cooking from
Hokkaido's Kutchan region...
Ah!
Kutchan City
Kutchan City is known for very heavy snowfall,
even by Hokkaido's standards.
They are a major producer of potatoes.
That's where the noodles
highlighting the starch
from the renowned variety,
Irish Cobbler, was born.
Potato starch comprises up
to 95 percent of the noodles!
Potato
Starch
95%
Other
5%
That's right!
It's gosetsu udon!
First, steam Irish Cobbler
potatoes and remove the skin!
Make them into fluffy mashed potatoes.
Then add water, salt, and flour,
and knead into a dough!
There wasn't enough wheat flour, of course,
but potato starch can be a substitute!
Potato Starch
The potato starch that was to be used
to flour the noodle prep surface...
Potatoes are the base ingredient, too!
It's not typically used in noodles,
but it's a different story
when it comes to gosetsu udon!
It works great as a binding agent,
and makes a great starchy, elastic dough.
All right!
But so what?
If you think you can just plop some
green onions on that and call it a day,
you're wrong!
The others all sourced high-quality
ingredients before the blizzard hit
and created dishes worthy of
being called gourmet food.
Listen!
Potatoes are an extremely
versatile ingredient!
If you can understand and leverage
their unique characteristics,
they will help you in a time of need!
Maybe I can use that as the topping...
Yukihira!
There are other tasks left to do
after making the noodles!
Don't fall behind!
Yeah, I know!
It's done!
The Hokkaido Seminar Special Gosetsu Udon!
Dig in!
Hm?
I thought the only ingredients left
they could've used as toppings
were green onions and perilla leaves, but...
Could this be...?
Could you please eat before
the noodles get soggy?
R-Right.
What's with this mellow broth?!
It's been thickened just
enough to coat the noodles!
What broad umami!
I added grated potatoes to the broth.
That's how the broth got
thickened in a good way.
Besides, potatoes have
a lot of glutamic acid.
That umami compound has
spread throughout the broth.
The potatoes were coarsely grated,
so the tiny potato bits throughout
the broth provide texture, too!
And what about the critical topping?
It's potato mochi, a popular souvenir
for Hokkaido's visitors to take home!
Light and chewy,
it's crispy on the outside...
Complimented by the thick soup,
it contrasts with the slippery noodles
and heightens the diner's satisfaction.
How can this be?
The full range of the potato's
characteristics are crammed into this bowl!
That's right!
This is the Irish Cobbler's—
The Irish Cobbler's starch, texture,
and umami concentrated into one dish.
In a nutshell, it's the
ultimate potato noodle dish.
What?
Please score the dish!
Huh?
These are impressive variations
on the gosetsu udon, too!
How did they manage to
create these on the fly?!
Well, Mister Examiner?
Yukihira Soma, Takumi Aldini,
and Tadokoro Megumi—
Y-You all pass!
Glad you enjoyed it!
Pass!
You all pass, too!
Erinacchi!
We did it!
Thanks to your Hokkaido Seminar, we passed!
I managed to do it all
on my own, thanks to you!
Don't cry!
I see it now.
If only you had not interfered, Erina-sama,
scum like this would've been easily eliminated.
They only survived thanks to your mercy!
If only you had not put
ideas into their head...
You are wrong!
I only taught them about the unique
characteristics of potatoes.
They're the ones who thought of how to
build on gosetsu udon as the main concept
and highlight the strength of potatoes!
Heed my warning!
These chefs are far beyond the likes of you!
I-Impossible!
How could the rebels have
banded together like this?
Such is Erina-sama's
awe-inspiring leadership.
It's as though...
It's as though she is Jeanne d'Arc,
the saintly female knight commander,
trying take back Totsuki
from Central's rule!
I've lost.
Yeah!
All the rebels have passed stage two.
Yes, we will send for them.
Yeah!
Sapporo!
Major city!
Shopping district!
I'm so glad they're letting us sightsee
the city before the train leaves.
Yeah.
The train won't leave till the evening,
so we have a good bit of time.
Hey, let's eat something good!
Ramen!
Sushi!
Genghis Khan.
Maybe we should split up.
Listen, think of this as part
of the Hokkaido Seminar.
There's no better lesson
than to taste local dishes!
Got it, Erina-sensei!
What is this rich flavor?!
It's just the right amount of sweetness!
Pure, yet rich!
It's too rich!
What kind of milk are they using to
make such good soft serve ice cream?!
Hokkaido is amazing!
Guess we'll just have to try everything!
Yeah!
We must carefully discern
what is worth trying.
Hm, Tanukikoji?
Let's try going all the way to Susukino!
The diner duo's going full throttle, too!
You're not going with your bro?
I've been wanting to walk around
the Odori Park area, so...
There's supposed to be a famous processed
seafood store in front of Sapporo Station.
Would you like to come with, Arato-san?
What?
They have dried goods, too,
like for your medicinal cuisine.
But I...
It's fine, Hisako.
Go.
You have the right to do what you want, too.
Erina-sama... Thank you!
Nakiri-san, let's walk around here, then.
Yes, let's.
Loyalty
All right, you'll keep her safe.
Take care of Erina-sama!
Okay!
Well, this a group you don't see often.
Oh, there's an event going on!
I wonder if there will be anything good.
E-Er, Erina-sama...
Would you like anything to eat?
I can go get something!
I'm fine, Mito-san.
I-I see.
I've been to Sapporo many times,
but this is the first time I've had
any time to take the sights in.
Really?
As the one possessing the God Tongue,
I've spent my days serving as a taster,
meeting all the heavyweights
in the food industry.
It was almost always for those reasons
that I would leave my home.
Looking back now,
I may not have been trying to
see anything out in the world.
I was struggling to fulfill my
responsibilities as the Nakiri family's heir.
That's not true.
You were always amazing, Erina-sama.
As a scion of the Mito family,
I saw you on several occasions.
I think I understand the
hardships you've endured.
Mito-san?
Oh, sorry!
My family and yours are worlds apart,
and I know it's presumptive of me to think
that you and I were in a
remotely similar situation!
But I was bound by my house, too, so...
Even though you must have felt
so much more pressure than I did,
you always had a commanding presence.
So, I... um, really respect you, Erina-sama.
Um, so...
I-I'm going to check out
what's going on over there.
Excuse me, Erina-sama!
Oh, are you sure you'll be all
right by yourself, Mito-san!
I'm glad you were able to
patch things up with Mito-san.
We were never really at odds.
I just cut her off after
she lost that Shokugeki.
And yet... I didn't know she
thought of me like that.
Tadokoro-san, thank you for the
roasted brown rice green tea, too.
Oh, you don't need to thank me!
Let me know if there's anything
I can do to help, okay?!
If you have other manga you want
to read, I can lend them to you.
What?
With Heart
That manga was yours?
Huh? Yeah.
Hisako and Yukihira-kun
wouldn't say whose they were.
Well, it's also my fault
for not really asking.
I'm sorry I haven't returned them to you.
Don't worry about that.
I'm glad I like something you like, too.
There you are!
Soma-kun, Takumi-kun! What's wrong?
Oh, we found a totally awesome-looking place,
but there's way too much
we want on their menu!
You two haven't eaten dinner yet, right?
Will you come with us?
Let's order a ton and share
everything between the four of us!
Oh, sure.
All right!
Now that that's settled, let's hurry!
Okay, Nakiri. Let's go.
Huh? Okay.
I really wasn't trying to
see anything at all before.
I didn't know this city was so beautiful.
Huh?
Where are the other guys?
Maybe they already got on the train.
It's almost time to leave, too.
I guess.
Hisako
Oh?
Erina-sama!
Where are you right now?!
Hisako, what's wrong? Why are you so anxious?
Oh, it's because I don't see you.
We're about to board.
Something's wrong, then!
What?
Because...
The train left 30 minutes ago!
What?
What's there to be so surprised about?
You knew how things would
go from the very beginning.
Rindo-senpai?!
Hey, it's really cold, isn't it?
Um, what do you mean?
The pamphlet mentioned that the
train route will diverge, didn't it?
In the worst case, you'll only see the
others at the final stage of the exam.
And that's if you all make it to that stage.
In the third-stage exam
that's coming up next,
all the rebels will be going
up against the Elite Ten!
Let's make this a fun trip.
Right, Yukihira Soma?
I woke up super early just thinking
about how we'll face the Elite Ten.
Hey.
Morning, Tadokoro.
I guess you were too nervous
to sleep long, too.
No, I was too excited.
You're unbelievable!
You're like a kid looking forward
to a day at a theme park!
Under-Eye Circles
I guess you're excited, too, Takumi-kun.
I confirmed this later by phone,
but we, the rebels, were split
into four different routes.
I see.
I hope everyone's okay.
Hey.
Over here!
You haven't had breakfast yet, right?
Come eat with me, since you're here.
But...
Come on, Tadokoro-chan.
Eat, eat.
It's not bad.
More importantly, can you tell us
what the next exam will be about?
The exam topic for the rebels—
I would hope it involves
a fair and just match.
There'd better not be any of the
cowardly tactics we've endured so far.
Well, yeah. That was all
what the examiners chose to do.
We don't play dirty.
So who am I gonna face?
Will it be you, Rindo-senpai?
No, your opponent's already right there.
Huh?
The newest member of the Elite Ten—
Hayama Akira.
Totsuki
Food Wars
The Third Plate
Next Episode   Revenge Match
Once we got through the tunnel,
there was a snowy mountain.