The Third Plate
Eighteen
Congratulations on your battle
royale victory, Hayama Akira.
Now, you are an official member of Central.
I don't give a shit about that.
As promised, set up the
research lab for Jun and me—
I am aware.
But before that, you have
your first assignment.
It's a simple matter.
Once and for all, finish off the opponent
you've already defeated twice before.
You can't do this, Hayama-kun.
Leave Central right now.
I told you not to join Central, didn't I?
Why won't you listen to me?
Even if you listen to Azami-senpai,
there's no guarantee that he'll
let you do what you want—
So what?
Is there any other way we
can continue our research?
You just don't get it, Hayama-kun!
Wh-What the hell?!
Do you even get how much everything
we've been through means to me?
Fine.
No matter what you say,
I'm going to protect this place.
I don't care what I have to sacrifice.
Here's the chicken-fried bear.
Please enjoy.
Food Wars
The Third Plate
Totsuki Train Arc
For Whom
The bear dish prepared by the master
of fragrance, Hayama Akira—
chicken-fried bear.
Hayama, where's mine?!
Hurry up, and let me try it!
Shut up.
Here.
After you've tasted it and
accept defeat, leave the academy.
You're really acting like you
have no time for me, huh?
I've always felt that way.
We're no longer on equal footing.
Get that through your thick skull.
He's really confident.
He must've had to walk the same tightrope
of smelliness and umami, and yet...
Yeah.
The first test is whether
he succeeded in his wager
to remove the smelliness...
But there isn't much to doubt there.
On to the tasting.
Hot, hot, hot!
The light batter is shining
so brightly, it's almost blinding.
Hayama's skills are the real deal.
N-No way. What is this?
Just bringing it close to your mouth
is enough to make the spices sing!
Now, if I may!
So good!
No, Berta!
Keep it together!
Yeah, Cilla!
We have to stay calm and analyze this.
This pungent spiciness is the
piperine from black pepper!
Its synergy with pyrazine, an aromatic
compound resulting from heating paprika,
has formed the foundation of
the dish's flavor profile.
Thyme is countering bear meat's gaminess.
Thymol, that sharp and
astringent compound, is at work here.
Oh, and cayenne and oregano's... um...
I can't stand this anymore!
I'm losing all sense of reason!
How exquisite!
The bear meat's smelliness has been
converted into a powerful umami in its entirety!
The complex buildup of umami
and the layers of flavor...
This clearly surpasses
Yukihira Soma's creation!
In addition to the obvious Cajun spice mix,
I've added to the marinade juniper berries
that have been crushed with
a mortar and pestle to
heighten their fragrance.
The more you chew,
the more the exquisite and
even sweet umami of the bear
should spread like a torrent
through your mouth.
Yukihira-dono even chose
smellier parts of the bear
and used schisandra berries to
enhance the bear's flavors—
And that wasn't enough?
It must mean that Hayama's spice use
skills are that much higher.
Even humans are said to be able to tell apart
several thousand to nearly
ten thousand odors.
I simply used that ability in this dish.
Yeah, right.
As if anyone could've made that dish
without Hayama's superhuman
sensitivity and sense of smell...
Now, for the finishing blow.
Wow, I wouldn't have thought
to use a blow torch to sear
the fish to bring out
the oils and fragrance...
How'd you come up with that?
C'mon, tell us.
Well, I won't take a back seat next
time now that I know your tricks.
Don't think you're better than anyone else.
Did you guys come here to pick a fight?
Man...
Sorry, Yukihira.
But I have something I want to protect,
even if it means defeating you guys!
He couldn't surpass Hayama.
That means that, with this match...
...Yukihira-dono's expulsion is confirmed?
It is too early to judge.
We have merely tasted the
fried meat by itself.
We have yet to taste it with the sauce.
Oops, that was close.
I was about to finish the whole thing.
Okay, I'll dip Hayama-san's
fried bear into the gravy.
A sauce made from deglazed
bear fond, with a generous dose
of the juniper berry's fragrance...
There it is!
An offshoot of the chest-baring
ability that the Nakiri clan
has passed down for generations!
The explosive tearing of
cloth due to willpower,
also known as "The Explosion"!
The Explosion
This is almost like...
A flavor bombardment!
It is almost terrifying
how polished this dish is.
Juniper berries and Cajun spices!
Spiciness and sweetness!
A golden ratio to enhance
the bear meat's flavor...
He has achieved the perfect balance!
It is the result of his
scientific pursuit of how
fragrance and deliciousness
are interconnected.
If I were to make an analogy,
it demonstrates ironclad
perfection from every angle!
The dish is akin to an impenetrable fortress!
There's no way you can catch up to me.
It's just not possible without
my superhuman sense of smell.
You're finished.
Did you just say "finished"?
Hayama, don't get the wrong idea.
He hasn't given up yet.
The final bell hasn't been rung yet!
Next, I'll have Yukihira Soma's
minced meat cutlet with the sauce.
What a nice smell.
Like Hayama-san's sauce, this seems
to be based on bear broth.
Yeah.
The schisandra berries steeped
in sake provide a focal point.
What a gentle garlic fragrance.
Where is this mildness coming from?
I see.
In comparison to Hayama's juniper berries,
Yukihira-chin used that ingredient
as the main player in the sauce.
Huh?!
What?!
The entire dish has taken
a 180 degree turn.
What a lingering fragrance...
Thought persistent, it's not clinging.
It's as though the bear meat's sweet
flavors have been sharpened...
...and are rushing right through you...
What's going on?!
Our clothes came off!
There it is.
This technique is the more advanced
version of the earlier Explosion ability.
The Explosion
More advanced than The Explosion?
Upon tasting a dish full of spiritual
harmony that is worthy of chest-baring,
the willpower that flows in a Nakiri's
veins is unleashed as a wave.
This temporarily imparts the
baring ability to outsiders.
It is known as The Gift!
The Gift
The Gift?!
Yukihira-dono was able
to create such a dish?!
Hmm, this secret behind this
sauce's delicious flavors
are honey and balsamic vinegar, correct?
That's right!
The honey's faint sweetness brings
depth of flavor to the sauce,
and the vinegar's acidity brings the
flavors together into a sharp focus.
No, depth and sharpness alone
cannot result in strong flavor.
This fragrance... is from caramelization.
The honey has been slowly caramelized.
That's an oxidation process that occurs
when you heat sugars, right, Berta?
Yes, Cilla.
It's an important technique that is
employed in a wide range of dishes
from French cuisine to sweets.
That's right!
First, I slowly caramelized the honey,
then thinned it with balsamic vinegar
until it reached a good consistency.
I then added garlic and minced onions
that had been sauteed separately,
and simmered it with schisandra berries.
Finally, I added the bear broth
and seasoned it with salt
to create the ultimate sauce, which can
accelerate the minced bear cutlet's flavors!
Huh.
I see.
He enhanced bear meat with honey,
then used balsamic vinegar
and caramelization to
"subtract" and "emphasize."
In other words, I managed to demonstrate
two theoretically opposing principles—
the subtraction of aroma and its emphasis—
in unison with this single dish.
Sorry, but I decided to use the principles
you used in the finals against you.
He really can't let go when
it comes to a match, huh.
I do like that about him.
Hayama Akira's chicken-fried bear was
an exquisite and elegant dish.
The fried meat itself was
overwhelmingly superior.
However, if we were to judge
the sauce on its own merits,
Yukihira Soma is the victor!
He caught up!
But who's the overall victor?!
Well, then!
We will now begin evaluations!
Nakiri Soue-dono,
Cilla-dono,
Berta-dono—
Please cast your votes!
If the fried meat and the sauce
are judged together as a whole,
which dish achieved better success
in showcasing the bear's flavors?
I've made my decision!
Me, too!
This one!
A split vote!
Does this mean they're equal?
For whom will you cast your
final vote, Nakiri Soue-dono?
An impeccable umami!
An impregnable fortress on one hand,
and a siege machine that focuses all of
its flavors into one strike on the other!
Which one will Nakiri Soue-dono choose?
My chicken-fried bear had no flaws.
But he's managed to catch up to me.
Yukihira...
You're an eyesore.
I can't lose.
Absolutely not.
In this match, both of you
are near equals in flavor.
That is reflected by Berta
and Cilla's split vote.
If there was a factor
that'd decide the outcome,
it'd be one's obsession with one's dish.
Yukihira Soma, you did not use just
any honey in the sauce, correct?
Indeed, the faint tannic notes of
this honey's fragrance are from—
I'm glad you noticed!
I used honey from the Amur cork tree!
A honey from a member of the Rutaceae family,
the same family as the mandarin orange...
Yeah, it's known for having a light sweetness
and a faintly bitter aftertaste.
Other types of honey could
have complemented the
bear meat with richness and mellowness,
but it could have led to an
overly-heavy flavor profile
if its flavors simply amplified the
minced meat cutlet's strong punch.
But when the honey from the
Amur cork tree is used...
The faint bitter and tannic aftertaste
is an excellent match with the bear meat—
it is almost miraculous!
Yukihira Soma did not overlook the
potential drawbacks of using honey
and pursued better taste
to a far greater extent.
But how'd he come up with this combination?
Yeah, it's hard to believe he was randomly
inspired to use this particular honey.
I was done in by you at
the Moon Festival, too.
I gotta admit, you never
give up until you find an
answer you're satisfied with, Yukihira-chin.
If there's anything you find that
might work as an ingredient,
please let me know right away!
Let's scrounge up as many ideas
as we can find before sundown!
Yukihira-dono!
We've found acorns and kiwi berries for now!
We've gathered Yezo spruce leaves!
Great!
Thanks!
Okay, let's go over to the ridge next!
'Kay.
All right!
Let's go down to the creek!
Crap...
We'll go as long as we can
to increase our options as much as possible.
Then I'll test everything out at the kitchen!
I'm gonna test dozens and hundreds,
even thousands of combinations!
So we'll be going into the
mountains again tomorrow.
Thanks for your help.
Again?!
The Chinese RS members are well trained.
You can abuse them as long
as you don't kill 'em.
Chief!
So we just scrambled
around all over the place
and finally found honey as an option.
But there are a lot of kinds of honey,
so it took a little longer
to settle on Amur cork tree honey.
What lies at the very
foundation of this dish
is none other than a chef's boundless
curiosity and obsession with flavor!
There, I see who the chef is as an individual!
What?!
The deciding factor
was to what degree the dish was
a reflection of the chef as an individual.
The one who deserves victory
is the chef who best pursued his own cooking!
The chef who truly sought
what his cooking should look like!
Impossible!
How can he possibly reach my dish's
level of sophistication—
Do you really believe that?
Chef Dojima...
So, you're saying you pursued true gourmet
dining to the best of your abilities?
Of course.
I constructed a sublime
and perfect balance of—
All by yourself,
without even knowing who you're cooking for?
Wow.
That's amazing, Hayama-kun.
It has such a rich smell.
Of course, this is nothing.
I'm going to be the top student at Totsuki.
Yup, yup, yup.
Good.
Perfect.
But should I use a coarser grind of
the spices used in the Cajun blend
to let the flavors stand out more?
What do you think, Jun—
I don't even need to taste the dish to know
that this dish is clearly
different from what you served
at the Autumn Elections finals.
Hayama Akira, can you
say with utter sincerity
that you approached this
dish with true passion
and did everything you could
during the testing process?
Were you perhaps missing the zealous desire to
have someone say that the dish is delicious?
Then how'd Yukihira...
How'd he get as far as he did?
Where'd your motivation come from?
Were you really that greedy
about your dish because
you wanted to survive the advancement exams?
The hell you talking about, Hayama?
It was for you! All for you!
It's because I was gonna make
you eat the dish, of course!
It was all to make you say it's delicious!
To crush you!
That's why I've been working so hard!
So I can't stand to see you all distracted!
Here's one piping hot.
Dig in, Hayama!
I see it now.
Yukihira's passion for this dish—
all of his trials and tribulations—
are flooding into me.
He kept me in squarely in his sights,
even though I'd closed myself off,
and only thought about
how to improve this dish.
He wasn't me, who'd lost
sight of why he was cooking
and could only wear himself down to the bone.
Jun?
Oh, sorry.
Did it hurt?
Are you okay?
Why are you here, Shiomi-senpai?
I invited her.
We know each other from our
Polar Star Dormitory days, after all.
That was a shock.
Jun's never hit me before.
I'm also your guardian,
so think of that as parenting.
Okay, I'm going to tell you my conclusions
after thinking about all that's happened.
I don't need a research lab anymore.
There was something I wanted you to do more
than I wanted to get my
equipment and budget back.
What?
What I've really wanted to see...
is you really enjoying your cooking
and devoting yourself to your craft
with lots of friends your own age.
You're still a kid, Hayama-kun.
You don't have to feel responsible
for the research group shutting down.
What? Don't treat me like a kid, Jun.
Don't call me that!
Hayama, I don't care what Central does,
but I still want to work on cooking with you.
I won't let you give up on your own cooking.
That's right. I...
Being here...
with everyone...
I was actually really enjoying myself.
That's what you let me remember.
It's like... a message from God.
Finally.
Finally, it's happening.
With a vote of two to one,
we declare Yukihira Soma the victor!
Glad you enjoyed it!
We have nowhere to call home now, I guess.
Why are you laughing?
Oh, about that.
Why don't you just come to Polar Star?
You'll at least have somewhere to cook, too!
Shiomi-senpai, you used to live there.
We have tons of empty rooms.
Right?
Say "yes"!
Yukihira-kun...
Thanks, Yukihira.
I really appreciate the thought.
Yukihira-kun!
Hey, Nakiri.
How did it go?
Oh, I managed to redeem myself.
S-So you won?
Did you run all the way here?
Your hair's a mess.
Well, of course!
Ah, here you are.
Aide to Nakiri Azami
Aida Sean
I am Aida, Azami-sama's aide.
Excuse me.
Hayama Akira, you understand
what is happening, correct?
Yeah.
Given the most recent results,
you are being expelled.
We have received reports from exams that
have occurred on other routes, as well.
Erina-sama... I am so sorry!
Shit!
All of the above have been expelled.
Totsuki
Next Episode  Declaration of War
Food Wars
The Third Plate
Right, let's go to the station up north!