What's wrong? Everything okay, Akari?
Yeah. It's nothing.
Weird.
Look, we're about to land.
What's the matter, Akari?
It's your first time back to your
home country in fifteen years.
Aren't you going to say "Yay!" or "Woohoo!"?
Yay. Woohoo.
No enthusiasm!
Mom, the lady behind us is playing
house with a teddy bear.
Why's an adult doing that?
Oh, how nice.
Miss?
We're about to land, so please return
your seat and tray to the upright position.
R-Right!
Thank you very much.
One Police Plaza building, please.
Welcome to New York, Akari.
And welcome to the Strategic
Response Group HQ.
NYPD HQ
"One Police Plaza"
Thank you.
I'm Akari Kido from the Tokyo
Metropolitan Police Department.
Nice to meet you.
I'm happy to have you here as the first
cooperation exchange intern from the TMPD.
Judging from your record, nobody
would be better suited than you.
New York City Police Department
Strategic Response Group
I'm sorry, everyone's currently out.
We'll have formal introductions tomorrow.
No, I should apologize for arriving
the day before beginning my duty.
New York City Police Department Strategic Response Group
Superintendent Victoria Johansson
As the NYPD's most respected superior,
I know your father would be happy, as well.
Thank you.
Tokyo Metropolitan Police Department Mobile Investigation Unit
Police Officer Akari Kido (Temporary)
My father would probably be
surprised to see me here at his work.
No doubt.
During your internship, you'll be working
as part of our investigation unit.
Try to take in as much as possible,
for your future career, as well.
I will. My father often used to say,
"I'm going to protect New York."
I'm hoping to get a little bit
closer to that sentiment.
Good.
Emma, did you hear that?
Akari, that's Emma, your partner.
My name's Akari Kido.
Nice to meet you!
Hi, I'm Emma Wattstone.
Don't "huh" me.
You just thought, "Is she Emma
Watson or Emma Stone? Nope!"
"She looks nothing like those
pretty film stars, anyway," right?
N-No, I didn't! I really didn't!
New York City Police Department Strategic Response Group
Police Officer Emma Wattstone
A likely story.
I promise, I really didn't think that!
Looks like you two have hit it off already.
H-Huh? What?
Y-Yes?
Okay, Akari, good luck starting tomorrow.
Thank you.
Emma, please take Akari to her apartment.
Roger.
Eh? Huh?
Let's go. Hurry up.
Right!
Excuse me!
Not that I care, but your crafted
persona is super obvious.
Or is that the Japanese style?
Coming to work with a teddy bear in your arms?
N-No, I just—
I had to wait for freaking ever just for
some newbie coming from Japan.
It's this late already?
No wonder I'm starving.
Why do I have to deal with this
on Christmas? My life sucks.
Too fast!
Welcome. What'll it be today?
From here to here.
How can you like donuts that much?!
It's time to begin!
This'll be a Christmas party for everyone!
My gut's finally stopped growling.
Seriously, how can you like
that teddy bear so much?
Why would you bring it to work?
Is there something valuable in it,
like jewels? Secret blueprints?
Please don't tell me it was
a present from your daddy.
Th-That's it. It's a present he left
behind for me the day he died.
It's my most important friend.
It's basically my life.
Your dad, he—
Yes, he died in the line of duty
fifteen years ago, on Christmas.
This teddy bear's name is Apple.
I feel safe when we're together.
It feels like I'm with my father.
I still can't help wondering what
made my father choose this bear
for my present that day.
My only regret now is that I
didn't get to thank him for it.
How dare you hit me right in the feels?!
Just so you know, I cry easily, all right?
Ow! Eye in my sugar! Sugar in my eye!
God damn!
A-Are you all right, Emma-san?
Of course I'm all right.
You'd best not be late on
your first day tomorrow!
You got that?!
Of course.
Thank you for giving me
a lift tonight, Ms. Emma.
Emma's fine.
I mean, buddies can't be all formal.
All right!
Goodnight, Emma.
Same to you, jeez.
This feels so good.
Until I got here, I thought that
Christmas in New York would be rough.
Emma sounds gruff, but she
seems like a good person.
What have we here?
Are you alone?
Alarm
Tap for snooze mode
Uh... Huh?
What? Huh?
Huh? Huh? Eh? Wha...
Huh?
What?!
This is the first intern in
the cooperative program
between the NYPD and the
Tokyo Metropolitan Police,
First Response Investigation
Officer Akari Kido.
N-Nice to meet you!
What? Your bear was stolen?!
When I woke up this morning, it was gone.
Maybe it ran away.
I won't comment on that, but you're going
to freeze to death dressed like that.
When you think of Christmas and the NYPD,
you think of this: traffic control!
NYPD's Winter Spectacle: Traffic Control
And when you come to New York any
time of the year, you gotta have this.
New York Specialty: Hot Dog
There's nothing better for
my frozen body than this.
Just so you know, New York's Christmas
is the best in the world.
That's why so many people flock
here from all over the world.
Why won't a nice guy or two fall
from the sky for me? Sheesh!
Wh-What is that?!
Wow!
I did hear that they were shooting a
movie, but I didn't know it was here.
A movie? That looks so real!
Hey, everyone! It's time for our
sparkling Christmas to begin!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Guns don't work!
My God!
This isn't a movie shoot!
It's an actual emergency!
Akari?!
Now, all of you, time to start moving!
You—
Merry, merry Christmas!
Have lots of fun, everyone!
That's right, my greatest pleasure
is to see people having fun!
Hey, you! Don't interrupt my Christmas party!
You're safe now, Akari.
I will protect New York and you!
Akari!
Who's that girl?
Big Attack!
Are you all right, Akari?
You're...
We've always been together, ever since
Dad gave me to you as a present.
Apple?!
That's right!
That's so weird! You're Apple,
but you have no fur!
That's right!
That's so weird! You're Apple,
but you're not a stuffed animal!
That's right!
You're Apple, but you're super strong!
Liberty!
Hi! I'm everyone's idol, Liberty!
Tell me, bear, why are you the only one
who turned into some kind of hero?
Oh, well. Whatever.
I'm just going to keep on
pumping up this party. Enjoy!
Bye!
She disappeared?
A toy?
Fortunately, there were no
casualties when the giant snowmen
and toys appeared out of nowhere
here in snowy New York.
It is thought that this was some
sort of publicity stunt,
but as of yet, nobody has
claimed responsibility.
This is a video submitted
by one of our viewers.
This was an attack by monsters!
This was a monster str—
This is all we have from the scene.
You said your name was Apple.
So are you a bear?
I wonder.
Are you human?
I've always been with Akari,
ever since that Christmas.
That Christmas?
It was when my family was
still living in this city.
Dad, when are you coming home today?
Mom said we're having a big
feast with turkey and cake!
I'm sorry, Akari.
I won't be able to come home tonight.
What? That's not fair!
But here's something you'll like!
This year you'll get a present not just
from Santa, but from me, too!
Really? What? What is it?!
You'll see when you wake up in the morning.
I'm off now.
Okay. Work hard, Daddy!
Sure will. I'm going to protect New York.
Especially because tonight is Christmas Eve.
Bye-bye!
But after he left for work
that Christmas Eve night,
my dad never came back home.
I named it Apple.
Because the city that my father protected,
New York, was called the Big Apple.
Ever since then, we've always,
always been together.
Stop, stop, stop.
I'm gonna lose all the salt in my body!
So how come you're a human instead
of a stuffed animal now?
The reason I have this form
is because of that sorceress.
Sorceress? You mean that
flashy girl from before?
Yeah.
Her name is Liberty.
She can give life to all sorts
of things with her magic.
Magic?!
So that's why all the toys started
their rampage in the city earlier.
Yeah.
That Liberty girl was saying that she
was going to keep pumping up the party.
What is she really trying to do?
As you've heard, the actions,
motives, and abilities of Liberty,
the suspected mastermind
behind this case, are unknown.
There are too many question marks.
Our first priority is to determine
what she's after, so that we can keep
the chaos to a minimum this Christmas Eve.
That said, firearms don't work against them.
All of you, please be extra vigilant.
Over.
How are we supposed to be vigilant
against someone who can use magic?
Start wizard training right now or something?
That's...
Apple?
Don't worry, Akari.
I'm going to capture Liberty.
Apple!
Everyone! Let's play together!
Let's make this an unforgettable Christmas!
Huh?
Oh, you want me to play with you, little bear?
You're good, little bear!
You—
Oh, you got me.
I guess I'll grant you this one.
Happy holidays!
Oh, no!
You're not getting away!
Everybody, you can't sit in the
dark like this on Christmas!
Wakey, wakey!
Stop it already!
Jeez, you just never give up!
What is that?
A blackout?
What's going on?
What is this?
I'm scared!
Of all the times for this to happen...
What is that?!
It's at the American Museum
of Natural History.
That's where Apple went.
What... is that?
He's absorbing the city's electricity.
What the?
What's going on?!
For your own safety,
please do not leave your vehicles.
HQ, do you copy?
It's Christmas in the dark!
Yay!
Happy holidays!
Collision between motorbike and
bicycle on 42nd by the park.
Requesting an ambulance stat.
What's the scale of this blackout?!
We need to go after Apple.
But you see what's going on.
Wh-What are you doing?!
My apologies, but I need to borrow this!
I'll return it afterwards!
Wha... Bu...
Please contact me there!
Wait... I can't read Japanese.
Tokyo Metropolitan Police Department
Mobile Investigation Unit
Police Officer Akari Kido
Turn right at the next intersection.
There should be fewer people
there, so you can go faster.
Roger!
Leave the navigating to me.
And the pedaling—
I've got it!
This is like an entirely different city.
Of course.
Any city will look nice from far away,
but the closer you get, the more
you see the grime and dirt.
That's especially true for New York.
I guess so. But still...
There are things you can't
find out unless you get close.
Here you go.
Thank you.
It's so warm!
You can't see that kind
of light from the sky.
That's true.
I wouldn't have seen who you are
if I hadn't gotten closer, either.
You're more abrasive and rough
than anyone in the world,
but in reality, you're a wonderful
person who cries easily.
I wouldn't have seen that from afar.
D-Don't think you've gotten
close to me already.
Emma, we're going to protect this city!
Better believe it!
Apple!
Apple! Apple!
What is that monster now?
He's the source of this darkness.
I have to stop him.
Apple...
Apple!
Go ahead! We'll be right behind you!
Okay.
No matter what happens, you and
I will always be together!
Right!
That said, how are we going to chase them?
Ah, here they come.
I thought this might come in handy.
Emma!
Let's get to chasing, Akari.
Right!
Nice catch.
Liberty!
Come on, little bear. Stop struggling.
Doesn't it kinda look like we
awakened some serious trouble?
Kinda.
Wait, what do you mean, "we"?
Hey, Akari, even if we do catch up to that
thing, what are you planning to do?
I don't know. But we have
to stop him somehow.
I'm going to stop him.
I will stop him.
This isn't a happy, happy,
happy Christmas for me.
This isn't everyone's Christmas!
Everyone's Christmas?
Time to get serious now!
Give New York its light back!
It's Christmas, after all!
Where are his arms?
Ow!
Stop!
How dare you do that to me?!
I'm Mister Empire!
Hey! What's up?
Defeat that guy!
Aye, sir!
My God!
Gigantic Shuriken Tornado!
It's the best climax!
Akari!
That was too close! We almost died!
Akari, you're bleeding!
I'm fine.
What are you talking about?
A woman's life depends on
her face. And her hair!
A woman's life depends
on all sorts of things!
Someone's there!
It's the helicopter pilot!
I'm glad he's alive.
Oh, he's a cutie!
You can leave this one to me.
Sh-She's fast.
Ow...
Oh, man! My favorite dress is in tatters!
Liberty!
Oh, you're that bear's owner, aren't you?
Liberty, you're behind all this chaos, right?
I might be!
Sorry.
Really?!
I said I was sorry.
To make up for it, kinda...
So, officer, are you a good shot?
What do you mean?
Akari?
Wait, where are you going?!
I need a favor from you.
During the fight earlier, there was a spot
he was desperately guarding.
Long story short, it's where he's vulnerable.
His weak point.
It's the eyeball inside his mouth.
But his defense is essentially perfect.
That's why I want you to shoot
that eyeball with your gun
while the bear and I face off with his arms.
Akari!
Huh?
Wow!
Liberty!
What the?!
I did it!
Not yet! It didn't reach!
Apple!
Akari!
Liberty!
Now, Akari!
Right!
Nice!
Apple! Liberty!
Let's do this, Apple.
Yeah.
Apple!
I'm going to protect New York and Akari!
The lights!
Yay!
The electricity he absorbed is back.
The city is shining again.
I'm honestly very sorry.
This was all my fault.
Look, if "sorry" was enough,
we wouldn't need the NYPD.
Hey, Liberty, what did you mean when
you said "everyone's Christmas"?
Ever since I was a kid,
I've loved this shining city.
I've loved the shining smiles on people's faces.
And above all else, I've loved
this city's Christmas.
Thank you.
That man protected me when I was all alone.
It was just for a brief moment,
but he brought me happiness.
Yes, almost like he was Santa.
But I was so happy and
embarrassed that I ran away.
I haven't been able to find him since.
That's why I decided that I'd make
everyone in this city happy in his stead.
So that children like me wouldn't
have to feel sad on Christmas Eve.
Even so, your methods were too extreme!
Emma...
And he was a really kind and cool Santa.
As I ran away, he called out to me,
"Don't worry. It'll be all right.
I'm going to protect this city."
That was Akari's dad!
I guess your dad protected
Liberty's Christmas that day.
Yeah.
I feel like I understand what he meant now.
This is the city that he wanted to protect.
Right?
Yeah.
I think I can fall in love with
New York's Christmas again.
Just like I did when I was a kid.
Yeah!
Merry Christmas, Dad.
Merry Christmas, Apple.