They need him to do his best,
don't they, Mr. Kiru?
It was a lazy, but normal day after
Obon at the height of summer.
That's true. You never know
how a match is going to turn out.
It was a lazy, but normal day after
Obon at the height of summer.
Next, stepping up to the batter's
box we have number four,
I had absolutely no interest in
the prefectural game on the TV,
Kashima, a senior. After last year's
summer tournament,
I had absolutely no interest in
the prefectural game on the TV,
he was chosen to be part of
the team that went to Cuba.
I had absolutely no interest in
the prefectural game on the TV,
he was chosen to be part of
the team that went to Cuba.
But because of my
sympathetic personality,
In the fourth inning,
he hit a three-run home run.
I ended up kind of rooting for
the losing side.
In the fourth inning,
he hit a three-run home run.
Once I did, my cell phone
began ringing.
And there's Suzuki with
a big windup...
Once I did, my cell phone
began ringing.
Incoming call: Haruhi Suzumiya
And the first pitch is a strike.
No problems there.
Incoming call: Haruhi Suzumiya
And the first pitch is a strike.
No problems there.
Incoming call: Haruhi Suzumiya
Haruhi, huh?
And the first pitch is a strike.
No problems there.
Haruhi, huh?
And the first pitch is a strike.
No problems there.
That was a good pitch.
You're not doing
anything today, right?
That was a strong, straight pitch,
thrown a little high and inside.
You're not doing
anything today, right?
That was a strong, straight pitch,
thrown a little high and inside.
We're all meeting at exactly
two o'clock in front of the station.
Perhaps he feels like he's
got nothing left to lose.
We're all meeting at exactly
two o'clock in front of the station.
Perhaps he feels like he's
got nothing left to lose.
And just like that,
she hangs up.
Perhaps he feels like he's
got nothing left to lose.
How does she know I'm not
doing anything today?
We don't know that yet.
He winds up for the second pitch...
How does she know I'm not
doing anything today?
We don't know that yet.
He winds up for the second pitch...
I mean, I'm...
Well, okay, I don't have
any plans at all, but...
It's a hit!
Well, okay, I don't have
any plans at all, but...
It's a big one! Kashima's sent it
headed for left field. It's in!
What?
It's a solo home run!
I forgot to mention this - bring
a swimsuit and come on your bike.
And be sure to bring plenty of money.
That's all, over and out!
This gives them
yet another point.
And be sure to bring plenty of money.
That's all, over and out!
This gives them
yet another point.
Ugh, no.
And with this, Jyonan's
gotten their eighth run!
Ugh, no.
And with this, Jyonan's
gotten their eighth run!
What in the world
is going on?
And with this, Jyonan's
gotten their eighth run!
Kashima is slowly rounding
third base.
Suzuki is on the mound,
looking dejected.
It's a hard thing
to watch.
It's so sad...
it looks like the last of his
will to fight has crumbled.
It looks like the last of his
Oh well.
The team's supporters seem to have
lost their voices as well.
Oh well.
The team's supporters seem to have
lost their voices as well.
There aren't even any jeers
for Suzuki.
And with this, the score
is now 8 to 0.
The Kumamoto team has their
work cut out for them now.
DAY BY DAY unzari dayone dakara
Day by day, everything's just so dull
Doudou to kotowacchau
kimi ni narina yo
That's why you need to become
someone that can just reject it all
OH MY BOY kippari shinakya uso ni
Oh my boy, you need to be decisive
Tsukiatterarenai yo semai sekai de
I won't deal with any lies
in this small world
Jibun de mitsuketa MYSELF
suki ni natte touzen
I found myself on my own,
it's natural you'd fall for me
Kudaranai yarikara kette
Kick away the boring ways
of doing things,
subete wa atashi ga kimeru
I'm going to decide everything
I SAY I SAY MY HEAVEN
I say, I say my heaven
SUPER DRIVER tosshin makasete
nantettate zenshin
Super driver, leave everything
to the rush
SUPER DRIVER tosshin makasete
nantettate zenshin
And just keep going forward,
no matter what
Fukanou (DON'T YOU STOP ME)
Tobikoete TAKE IT EASY, GO!
Surpass (Don't you stop me)
The idea of "impossible"
Fukanou (DON'T YOU STOP ME)
Tobikoete TAKE IT EASY, GO!
Take it easy, go!
Daishouri tte doukan
I agree, it's going to be
a huge victory
Mochiron dounatta tte kaikan
Of course, it'll feel pleasant,
no matter what happens
Hanseikai? (GET BACK TO WILD)
Sore yori saa isoide yo
A review meeting? (Get back to wild)
Forget that, now hurry up
Aremo koremo mitaiken
itsudatte muriyari
We haven't tried this or that,
we always do things how we want
Marude marude mikeiken
korekara shimashou
Everything's a new experience,
let's try them out
Aremo koremo mitaiken
itsudatte totsuzen
We haven't tried this or that,
we always do things suddenly
Marude marude mikeiken
sore ga doushita no?
Everything's a new experience,
what about it?
Endless Eight
You're late, Kyon!
Show some more motivation!
Who do you think you are,
making the brigade leader wait?
There'll be a penalty
for this.
I came fifteen minutes early,
and I'm still the last one to arrive?
Okay, we're all here,
so let's go.
Koizumi, let Mikuru ride
on your bike.
Yuki and I will ride on
the back of Kyon's bike.
Well, let me ask,
where are we going?
To the public swimming pool,
of course!
We have to do summer vacation-y things
during our summer vacation!
We can never get back
the time that we've lost!
And so we're going to do
them now, during this,
our one and only summer
as tenth graders.
The time that we've lost, eh?
Oh, the scent of chlorine.
This really makes it feel like a pool!
Here I go!
Here we go!
No diving
It's dangerous
Hurry up and get in!
The water's warm so it feels fine!
Can't she read the "no diving" signs
posted everywhere?
This makes me smile, though.
Miss Suzumiya has some
rather normal ways
of enjoying her time,
don't you think?
Suddenly calling us up
out of the blue,
and only giving us a general idea
of what's going to happen...
That's not all that
normal to me.
Well, at least Miss Suzumiya,
laughing and having a good time,
isn't likely to shake up
the world.
I hope that's the case...
There's no need
to worry.
We haven't noticed any problems
since the outing a while back.
Right now, to Miss Suzumiya,
and to us as well,
the world is at peace.
Let's have lunch.
Surprise! Today Mikuru
made us sandwiches!
Wow!
This is delicious.
Thank you very much.
I'm having more
fried chicken!
Mikuru, get the tea,
would you?
Okay!
Things certainly do seem
to be peaceful.
Sorry!
Okay, here I go!
I think it'd be better to call this a
communal pool than a public pool.
Come on, Mikuru,
what are you doing?
This isn't a bad way to spend
my summer vacation.
Kyon!
These are my
brigade members.
They'll do anything you ask,
so ask for anything you want!
Okay!
I've been thinking about how we should
spend our summer vacation.
What do you think?
Club schedule: Summer outing,
bug catching, pool, test of courage...
What is this?
It's a schedule of how we'll spend the
rest of our short summer vacation.
For the SOS Brigade?
Yup. There're only two weeks of
summer vacation left, right?
And yet it feels like there are
a lot of things we've yet to do!
We're going to pick up
the pace!
Things that we have to do during
the summer vacation, you say?
Summer outing,
go to the pool,
go to a Bon festival,
go to a fireworks show,
have a part-time job, stargazing...
There's a lot here, isn't there?
So we have to do all of this
in just two weeks?
Is there anything else
you want to do?
Umm... I'd like to try
goldfish scooping.
Okay! Goldfish scooping...
We start the plan tomorrow!
Is there a place nearby
having a Bon festival?
A fireworks show
would work, too.
At least try to find
this stuff out first.
I'll check around. I'll contact
you when I find out.
Don't forget about the goldfish scooping!
It's Mikuru's sole request, after all.
Right.
Why am I always the one that
has to pick up the check?
Isn't it obvious?
It's because you were late.
Don't make us wait tomorrow!
All right, then,
we're done for today!
Good grief. So we're going to
be playing around every day?
The next morning,
it was a call from Haruhi
that awoke me
from my slumber.
They found a place that was
holding a Bon festival.
Time: Tonight.
Place: A public park.
Convenient how they found one
so quickly.
Just as I was being impressed
by that, Haruhi said,
"We're all going to go
buy yukata!"
Both Mikuru and Yuki said
that they don't own one.
There's a place selling them
in sets for cheap, so let's go!
Haruhi just went and chose yukata
for Miss Asahina and Nagato,
then headed straight for
the changing rooms.
This ended up taking
quite a bit of time.
We waited for about an hour,
while the other women ignored us,
and finally the three of
them came out at once.
Kyon!
You all look wonderful.
Of course! I chose these yukata,
after all.
Especially Mikuru.
Just what you would expect from
my choice, it's so cute on you!
There's nothing wrong
with my fashion sense!
This certainly was the
cream of the crop
Yuki is pretty too, don't you think?
This certainly was the
cream of the crop
Yuki is pretty too, don't you think?
Of all of the costumes that
Haruhi has forced on her.
Rather, it really looks great
on her!
This is a definite yes!
So this is the kind
of clothing
that the people of this country
wore in historical times.
It's a little tight around the chest,
but it's beautiful.
Okay, we're ready
to go now.
Let's go to the festival,
everyone!
Wow!
A Bon festival, huh? It's been
a while since I've been to one.
Mikuru, they even have goldfish scooping,
just like you wanted!
Be sure to catch
a bunch!
Black Demekins are worth
200 points, you know!
Shall we play, too? How about
seeing who can catch more?
I'll pass. I'm more interested
in the food.
What about you, Nagato?
Want to eat something?
You're interested
in that stuff?
This one.
Right-o, that'll be 800 yen.
Thirteen!
I caught a lot, but I don't need
so many, so I just kept one.
I didn't catch
any at all.
Scooping goldfish is difficult,
isn't it?
Oh no, it's not normal
to catch so many.
If you can figure out the trick,
it's easy!
Huh? What's with
the mask, Yuki?
I bought it.
I see.
But why that one?
Maybe it appeals to a
particular wavelength.
One only aliens
would get.
Okay, then.
There are things over there we
haven't seen yet, so let's go!
You're still going
to mess around?
Of course!
Come on!
Here.
You can have one,
but only one.
Oh, thanks.
Is it tasty?
Good.
Now, we've pretty much seen
all of the Bon festival.
Now let's launch
some fireworks!
Fireworks?
We've gone through the trouble
of getting all dressed up,
so let's do that to
finish off the day!
Why not? There was a store
over there selling them,
so let's head over
to the riverside.
This looks like
it will be fun.
Okay, here we go!
Kakizaki!
Oh, they're so beautiful.
Bon festival, fireworks...
okay, done.
Okay, tomorrow we'll
be catching bugs!
Haruhi, it's fine to
want to play around,
but are you finished with
your summer homework?
Not that I've any right to talk,
since I'm nowhere near done.
What, you can finish all of that
in just three days.
Three days?!
I finished it all
in July.
I took care of all of that
bothersome stuff
so I could have fun without
having to worry about it.
That's how you enjoy
your summer vacation.
Why is she so smart?
It seems like the guys up in heaven
that were divvying up our stats
were being pretty lax
about it.
In any case, we're going to
go bug catching tomorrow!
Whoever catches
the most bugs...
That's right. They'll get to be
the brigade leader for a day!
Ugh, no thanks.
That sounds interesting.
Are any bugs okay?
Hmm... Only cicadas!
That's it, this will be the SOS Brigade's
Cicada Capturing Competition!
Whoever catches
the most wins!
The next day, I wanted
it to rain so much
that I drove a nail
through a teruteru bouzu.
But despite that, it was an incredibly
beautiful and clear day.
It felt like the warmest day
of the summer,
and it seemed like it was making
all of the cicadas happy.
I wonder if you
can eat cicadas.
No idea.
They might be delicious if
you fried them in tempura.
Fine. Try it out yourself.
You know, sometimes, I wonder...
When it comes to tempura,
maybe it's just the outside
that's delicious.
If that's the case, maybe it's
the same with cicadas.
Apologize! Apologize to the tempura
restaurants across Japan!
So what's with making
all of us, at our age,
walk here carrying bug-catching
nets and cages?
What are you talking about?
If we didn't have
bug-catching nets,
we wouldn't be able to catch
any cicadas, would we?
That's not what I'm
talking about.
Okay, we're going
to start!
The winner is the brigade
leader for a day!
Ready... start!
She's not listening.
Umm...
It looks like she really
wants to win.
I think that's a good thing,
don't you?
Sheesh. I haven't caught cicadas
since I was in elementary school.
Same here.
Let's do our best.
Have you already
caught one?
That's not a cicada.
Oh.
That's a Hercules beetle!
And now, the results!
Mikuru caught one.
Yuki caught four.
Koizumi caught seven.
Kyon caught nine.
And the top record is...
We already know.
You don't have to say.
Me, with twelve!
I guess I can't give up the brigade
leader position, even for a day.
Sorry, everyone!
Now, you're not actually going to
make these into tempura, are you?
What? Do you want
to eat them?
Why does it come back
to me?
I'm kidding. A catch-and-release
attitude is important, right?
If we let them go, then they
might come back to repay us.
There you go! Go back to the mountains!
Don't get caught again!
Hold on a second. That may
be a good deed and all,
but all you did was catch them
and then let them go.
The next day...
Haruhi found us part-time jobs
somewhere that was glad to have us.
Our job was to bring
in customers...
Brigade Leader
Our job was to bring
in customers...
Brigade Leader
Do your best!
...for the local supermarket's
anniversary sale.
Thank you...
Here you go.
Here.
Why do I have to
wear this outfit?
If you want to work
a part-time job,
there are more appropriate ones
for the summer, you know?
And to top it all off,
Haruhi is still nice and cool!
If we end up getting the same amount
of pay, I'm going to riot!
I really understand how a snake
that's shed its skin feels.
That's a good analogy.
Good work, everyone.
The manager is thankful.
I don't care about his thanks.
Where's our pay?
This is it.
Huh?
This costume is our pay.
I've wanted this
for a while.
The owner said that he'd give it to us
for Mikuru's sake.
We'll hang this frog up in
the clubroom as a memento!
Mikuru, you can wear it whenever
you want. You have my permission!
Ribbit.
We went to the pool,
to a Bon festival,
caught bugs, and worked
a part-time job.
Next up, Haruhi had us scheduled
to go stargazing.
Wow, so this is a telescope
from this era.
It doesn't seem that different from
the ones from Kepler's time.
No, I think it's pretty different.
Did you buy this
for tonight?
No, this was my hobby
when I was younger.
I was pretty moved when I caught
a glimpse of the moons of Jupiter.
I've spotted Mars.
I wonder if they exist.
If who exists?
Martians.
I kind of don't want them to.
If there were octopus-like monsters
wriggling around,
planning on conquering
the Earth,
there's just no way I could
say that sounded like "fun".
Why not? They might be
a very friendly people.
I'm sure they're a reserved people,
secretly living in underground caverns.
I'm sure they're just trying not
to surprise us Earthlings.
Exactly how reserved are the
Martians you're imagining?
I've had enough of Mars.
Let's look for UFOs!
Their scouting fleets should
be standing by in orbit.
Come on, Mikuru,
help out!
U-F-Os, U-F-Os!
Our summer vacation continued.
The next thing Haruhi said was:
We're going to a
batting center!
Why there?
It came to me this morning while
watching the news from Koshien.
We can't be satisfied by a
mere sandlot baseball game.
I think that the SOS Brigade needs to
form its own national-level team.
Chuka soba!
She sure is something.
Where does she get her energy from?
She may have a different amount of
mitochondria packed into her cells.
She should use her gifts for the
sake of the world some more.
All right!
Home Run
After that,
in an attempt to run through the
schedule that she had set for us,
we kept going,
day after day,
too fast for anyone to
hit the pause button.
We went to a real
fireworks show.
The fireworks burst into bloom
in the sky, one after another,
leaving us with a grand feeling
in our hearts.
That one was awesome!
Leaving us with a grand feeling
in our hearts.
Goby Fishing Tournament
On yet another day, she also
made us take part
in a goby fishing tournament
at the prefectural river.
Ah! Mikuru, your fishing pole!
Leave it to me,
I'll get it back.
It continued on.
While it's admittedly a staple
of the summer,
there probably aren't many people
who do tests of courage.
We went to see a movie that was
hyped so much it was overblown,
but it was just your usual
"summer blockbuster".
We went to the beach when the jellyfish
were closest to the shore.
We went bowling, but we couldn't
leave until we all got a strike,
as if were playing some
kind of penalty game.
We went to karaoke,
singing for a long time,
as if we were trying to challenge
the limits of our voices.
In short, it felt like there were
non-summer things in there as well,
but we ended up enjoying ourselves
to the fullest these two weeks.
As of today, August 30th, we have
pretty much completed our list.
Good grief,
we're finally done.
I wonder if this was
good enough.
But, hmm, well...
I guess this works.
Hey, is there anything else
you want to do?
Not particularly.
We've done enough,
haven't we?
I'd like to sleep
for a while.
What about you,
Yuki?
I see.
That's fine, then. We were able
to do a lot this summer.
We went all over the place, we wore
yukata, and caught a lot of cicadas.
Yeah, that works.
Is there something that she
would regret not doing?
Okay, we're done
for today.
I had tomorrow set aside just in case,
but you can just take the day off.
Let's meet again in the clubroom
the day after tomorrow.
Man, I haven't done any
of my homework at all.
August 31 st, the last day
of our summer vacation.
No matter how hard I tried, there was no way
I'd be able to finish all of my homework.
I couldn't recover from all of the
running around we did, either,
so in the end I just spent
the day slacking off.
What the heck're you
talkin' about?
Boring.
Whatever.
It'll work out.
I guess I'll go to sleep...
School's starting back up, after all...
Beep.
Sora kara ochite kitanda
It fell from the sky
Subete no negai wo nosete
With all of the wishes
that were made upon it
Hitotsu no hoshi niwa
chotto omokatta kana
Maybe it was a little too heavy
for a single star
Yappari nanika henda yo
Something just doesn't
seem right
Kokoro no kimi ga kieta
The image of you in my mind
has vanished
Tashika ni oboeteru tte
ieruno kai?
Can I say that I
remember you clearly?
Tomare!
Stop!
Kako wa jibun no mono
The past belongs to me
Touzen daretomo torikaetakunai
Of course I don't want to trade it
with anyone else
Nazenara
That's because
Basudei datta watashitachi niwa
It was my birthday,
and when we saw each other
Deai ga umareta toki ni
We could see the first dream
Hajimete no yume ga mieru
That we had
when we were born
Doushiyouka tte
nayanda koto mo
Worrying about
"what do I do?"
Ima omoeba waraeru hodo
datta yo ne
Is laughable when I
think about it now
Mou wasureteta
I've already forgotten it
Kimi wo sagasou
Let's search for you