You were here... weren't you?
Ku...
You're picking me up
with a black limousine?
How extravagant.
I promised you.
It's better to be flashy if you can, isn't it?
We did cause a lot of
trouble for you in this case.
So you're aware of it.
How's number 108 doing?
She's stable.
She fell asleep right after dinner.
She doesn't seem
to have had any troubles so far.
Well, I guess I don't need to worry.
There's a scary landlady there, after all.
You don't ask about her Ashikabi.
I don't need to.
I believe I know more
about him than anyone.
Ima inochi ga hora kizashite chitte yuku
Nigirishimeta unmei
Mou mayou koto wa nai
Musubiau kizuna
Akatsuki matsu sora ni
Aishi kimi dakishimete
Orenai inori wo
Mada dare mo yoru no naka
Ima wa tada
Kokoro no oku ni sawatte
Afureru atsusa subete sasagetai
Yume miru ashita e
Hirogeru tsubasa wa
Ano hi no kimi ga kureta
Omoi wa kizamareta
Chikai no kotoba ga
Kiseki wo okosu yo
Takanaru mune habatake
Tobitateru negai haruka tataku
Feather 4:
"The Strange Tale of Maison Izumo"
Just looking at the data, he's an
ordinary dull entrance exam loser...
"Musubi"
Just looking at the data, he's an
ordinary dull entrance exam loser...
"Musubi"
Yet, he's already induced
two Sekireis to emerge.
"Musubi"
"Kusano"
Yet, he's already induced
two Sekireis to emerge.
I must say this is very interesting.
Well, I'm going now.
Have a nice day.
Do your best at your work!
The abnormally growing plants
in the arboretum were completely
eliminated overnight by the MBI.
"Teito Arboretum MBI Completely Eliminated
Unusually Grown Plants Overnight."
The abnormally growing plants
in the arboretum were completely
eliminated overnight by the MBI.
"Teito Arboretum MBI Completely Eliminated
Unusually Grown Plants Overnight."
The elimination methods were
not made public at all but MBI
claims no pesticides were used...
The elimination methods were
not made public at all but MBI
claims no pesticides were used...
This...
Ku-chan?
What's wrong?
Ku-chan.
Are you all right?
Shii-chan...
"Shii-chan"?
Shii-chan was my older
friend and very close to me.
That tree told me...
Shii-chan took the plants I grew and...
That's... what the news
was just talking about.
Shii-chan has the opposite power of mine.
Opposite?
What should I do?
Without Shii-chan,
I'll do the same thing again.
Don't worry. I'm right here.
I'm not so dependable, though.
Please stay with me forever, big brother.
Ku is... crying.
A Sekirei opposite to Ku-chan, huh?
Oh, I know.
Ah, Director?
Huh?
Doesn't Seo-san work today?
Seo?
He quit?!
He said his other job kept him too busy.
What an irresponsible guy!
Hey...
If you're scared so much like that,
why don't you watch TV inside?
Your steps aren't strong enough!
Right!
Second one, eh?
That guy can't be judged
by his appearance...
He was the first other Ashikabi I met...
I had lots to ask him...
I'm back.
Yo, youngster!
Welcome back.
Welcome back, Minato-san.
Sorry, sorry. Did I surprise you?
Why?
He is...
Seo-san was my husband's best friend.
Well, that's how it goes.
He comes here only when
he doesn't have anything to eat.
Even though he's such trash,
he's still Takehito-san's best friend...
You're still as scary as before.
Ah... excuse me but...
Huh?
You look like you
knew I'm a resident here.
Yeah, it was your lunch.
Lunch?
You gave me some.
That was Miya-chan's taste.
By the way, how's that little girl doing?
Do you mean Ku-chan?
Oh, here she is!
Hey, come here.
Huh? I'm the nice guy who saved you.
If you don't listen to me,
I'll make you cry, you brat...
Ah, my hand slipped.
You shouldn't bully such a little girl.
Ah, yes, I apologize...
Hello, excuse me!
Is that idiot over
here bothering you again?
Yo! Thank you for coming to get me.
- You again!
- You again! Bothering others!
Um... Seo-san.
Thank you very much for yesterday.
I've wanted to say that to you.
Don't worry about it.
When I look at you,
I can't leave you alone, you know?
"I handle any problems
and troubles. Kaoru Seo"
When I look at you,
I can't leave you alone, you know?
"I handle any problems
and troubles. Kaoru Seo"
Here.
You "handle any problems and troubles"?
I'll make a special deal for ya.
You charge money?!
We're friends now, after all.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry he always does this...
What is with that person?
"I handle any problems
and troubles. Kaoru Seo"
What is with that person?
"I handle any problems
and troubles. Kaoru Seo"
As I've told you, he's a trashy human.
Landlady...
I'm completely boiled.
It was you who told me you wanted to
compete on how long we can stay in the tub.
Give up, give up. Let's get out.
Come to think of it...
Your Ashikabi-sama...
That's a secret.
Aren't you lonely... Umm...
since you aren't with your Ashikabi-sama?
Of course, I'm lonely
and wish to be together.
But in my case, there are
some extenuating circumstances.
I'm happy just living under the same sky.
It's not bad having a
connection like that...
Uzume-san...
Well, each person's different,
and so is each Sekirei.
I see. Each one's different.
Yes, yes.
There are 108 of us, after all.
"Toilet"
Ku-chan?
Gh-Gh-Gh...
A ghost?
Ah. So, that's why
Ku-chan was out of the bed.
I thought Sahashi-san had taken her out.
Landlady, what was with that little laugh?
So after that, we thought there might be
a burglar, and looked around the house.
But we couldn't find anybody.
It was a long-haired woman with glasses.
She was laughing...
Long-haired, glasses?
Ah, isn't that...
Uzume-san.
Eh, ah... I don't know.
I'm quite sure Ku-chan was half asleep.
There couldn't be a ghost
here in Maison Izumo. Right?
Yes, you're exactly right...
Are you going to visit a grave?
Yes. Today is my late
husband's monthly death anniversary.
Your husband...
Now, please excuse me. Take care
of everything while I'm out, please.
What should we do for lunch?
Uzume-san, I'll cook lunch!
I'll help!
Really? I'll leave it to you, then.
Sure!
Okay then, you guys, come to my room!
Her room?
Just now... something was...
Ah! We're done.
Those outfits...
Do they look good on us, Minato-san?
Musubi-chan...
Oh no. When you dress like that,
you gotta say, "Master."
Uzume-san!
Master.
Yes.
Don't reply seriously...
Oh, Ku-chan's cute,
too. Is that... a wagtail?
But why do they have
to dress like this to prepare meals?
Now, I got to take a nap.
Wake me up when lunch's ready.
Why does she have those costumes?
Uzume-san... she's a mysterious person...
Sorry for making you wait.
Thank you for the meal!
Th-Thank you for the meal...
The more I look at him,
the more lame he looks...
Then... why is my maiden
heart skipping like this?
"JLTeito North Station"
It's really late now...
Hmm...
Ku...
Maison Izumo, huh?
It looks quite far away from the station...
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
Ah! His disheveled manner,
his eyes, his lips...
Everything about him looks so fragile...
A pretty boy!
Did you get hurt?
No, um...
Gotcha!
Honestly, running from
place to place like that...
If I don't take you with me,
I'll be scolded by my master.
No!
I won't go to someone who bullied Ku!
Geez! You're so stubborn!
Then, I'll make you feel a bit of pain!
What the hell are you guys doing?!
I don't know what's going on,
but don't worry. I will protect you!
Get away, you ordinary passerby!
No can do, stupid!
Pretty boys are national treasures!
This... uneasy feeling...
What an obnoxious woman!
I won't go easy on you!
Let's run!
I won't let you run away!
Could she be?!
Just now, I know I...
Something's here.
I should go ask Uzume-san after all...
I'm done with cleaning.
You're really working hard.
It's fun to take care of the house.
Where is Uzume-san?
She's been sleeping with
Ku-chan ever since she ate lunch.
Uzume-san seems like
she's sleeping all the time.
I heard her operational
time limit is four hours per day.
Is that a characteristic of Sekireis?
I don't know. We're all different.
MBI's choppers!
What should we do?! We destroyed
a bunch of stuff at the entrance.
They must've come to retrieve her.
Eh?! Retrieve?
Sekireis who've lost the Sekirei symbols
can no longer stay with their Ashikabi-sama.
Hey, Musubi-chan?
Yes?
Tell me about what you said in the arboretum...
"Sekireis who've lost can no
longer be with their Ashikabis."
Will you... if you lose, will you
disappear from in front of me like her?
Yes, I will.
For those who alight on earth as Sekireis,
that's the unchangeable
and absolute destiny.
That's right...
The President of MBI was
also saying that from the first.
That this was a game
called the Sekirei Plan.
It's just rational...
Since it's a game, it'll be all
finished when it's time for a game-over.
You're wrong!
It's not a game.
My feelings...
My feelings toward you are not a game!
I want to be beside you forever.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Musubi-chan.
So, I!
So, I will never lose! No, I won't!
Also, there's a reward for us Sekireis.
The last remaining Sekirei can stay
with its most beloved person forever.
So, please don't worry.
Until that day, I will never lose.
You mean...
I'm home.
Landlady! Welcome back!
Musubi-chan!
She got so close to him!
What? Could this be?
My Sekirei symbol feels like it's burning.
The secrets of Sekireis'
hearts and bodies...
There's nothing I can do but
solve the mystery with my own body.
Musubi-san, would you please
go do a little shopping for me?
Yes, Landlady.
Now then...
Number 88, Musubi...
You're my enemy, now.
Better prepare yourself.
Um... I got soy sauce and miso...
Then carrots, daikon radish, and cabbage...
"Please don't worry," huh?
Yes?
Sahashi-san, go take a bath.
Ah, yes. Thank you.
Ku-chan, you'll take a bath with me, later.
Yeah!
Say, Musubi-chan's late.
She really is.
But there's no need to worry about her.
I don't train her like hell
every day for nothing.
The military satellite made by
MBI is as good as you'd expect.
I think I can stop her for a while with this.
The main event starts right now.
So... I wonder what the
thing Ku-chan saw was?
Who is it?
Musubi-chan?
I told you, you don't
need to wash my back...
Huh?! Who are you?!
Grabbed a pretty boy, and ran and ran.
Took a train, then ran and ran, again...
What should I do now?
I brought him to my room!
Whoa! Wait! Who are you?
What's going on?
Yo, baby girls! Get ready now!
This is renai no shinansho
Don't let it go, aserazu so
Without furaingu de show time
Get the funky beat!
Hayai mono gachi?
Kono bayai wa kankei nai nai
Nozomu tokoro yo
Soudatsusen boppzatsu
Onna desu mono, maketerareya shinai nai
Fukuramu kimochi
No mou daibakuhatsu
Dame yo, yuuwaku shicha
Doite, kare no osoba
Watashi dokidoki natte ippai ippai
Naisho, nukekake shite
Daiseikou, kare to futari
Amaku mekurumeku night
Honto wa ne, watashi dake wo
Dakishimete hoshii no
Hitorijime mura mura
Furagu tatechau no ari kashira?
Yappari ne, yowaki, dou shiyou
Yasashisugite shou ga nai
Sonna toko daisuki yo
Dakara watashitachi tsukushimasu
Dear Sweet Heart!
I am number 09, Tsukiumi.
I don't need Ashikabi.
Why is that?
How could I do this
and that with a human?!
Doing this and that is easy!
Dost thou understand thy words?
No, I don't at all.
Feather 5:
"The Water Sekirei"
No, I don't at all.
Feather 5:
"The Water Sekirei"
"Episode 5: The Water Sekirei."
Feather 5:
"The Water Sekirei"
Please favor us again next time!