A month after I moved to Tokyo,
my incredible luck...
came to an end.
When I was darkness at that time
With trembling lips
In a corner of a room I cry
The more I struggle
The more this wound deepens
The broken promise hurt me
Nobody can save me
God, I have only one request
Stop tearing apart my love
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Sorrow tumbling down is your song
All alone with nowhere to go in my life
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Oh baby, help me from frozen pain
With your smile, your eyes,
and sing me, just for me
I wanna need your love
I'm a broken rose
I'm broke!
Naturally.
But why? I worked so hard
and saved up before coming here,
yet I only have 2,228 yen left.
If you spend your money,
it runs out.
You went on this crazy spending splurge
of clothes and furniture.
But Mr. Mizukoshi gave me a good deal
on everything I got from there.
On top of that, rather than cash,
he offered to deduct the amount for
the clothes I got from my salary.
That's why you didn't have much of
a salary to bring home last month.
That's right! Isn't it horrible?!
- Was I tricked, you think?!
- You did it to yourself!
What about you? Do you have
enough money to get by, Nana?
You don't have a full-time job,
just temporary stuff from time to time.
Unlike you,
I don't waste my money.
- Thank goodness.
- Don't rely on someone else's money!
I have no intention of doing so.
Then what did you mean?
You see, if we both didn't have money,
that leads to anxiety, don't you think?
You are relying on my money!
Don't count on it!
We agreed to split the rent
for this place, exactly half-half.
If you can't make arrangements
for funds by the end of the month,
I'm kicking you out.
- You devil!
- Huh?!
It wouldn't bother you if I lay
in the streets dying, would it, Nana?!
Dying once may do you good!
Please, don't abandon me!
Let go of me!
I'll be late for work.
Work?
What kinda work are you doing
at this hour of the night?
Is it an S&M club?
What do you care?
Have a good night with
the ghosts.
No way...
No. This is no time to be
afraid of ghosts.
My problem is money.
There's over half a month
until my next payday.
Will I survive on 2,000 yen?
What am I to do?
This is getting scary.
Having no money is scary!
I didn't come to Tokyo
to experience this!
Then why did you come?
To make it on my own?
Then solve this on your own.
But how?
That's for you to figure out!
But I don't know how
to be a dominatrix!
A dominatrix?
Talk to Shoji and have him feed you
until the end of the month.
I can't do that.
If I talk to Shoji about this
he'll hate me,
and no longer wanna be
with me, for sure.
Also he's very busy with work
and his studies at university,
so I'd only be a nuisance
bothering him at this late hour.
You got that right!
I get it, Nana. So don't cry.
Use this to hold you over
until the end of the month.
Kyosuke!
We cannot afford that!
I'm not giving it to her.
It's just a loan.
No way.
Give Nana cash, and you're certain
it'll be all gone in a day.
That's a cruel thing to say,
Jun-chan.
- What?
- Rice.
My parents sent me some.
I'll share it with you.
You can feast on this
until the end of the month.
No way! No way! No way!
Hey, what about meat and
vegetable dishes?
It's all right.
Calm down and think.
My next payday is on the 26th.
If I don't buy anything from the store,
I'll receive at least 70,000 yen.
But I'll be debited for my cell phone,
so I should deposit 10,000
in my bank account.
That leaves me with 60,000.
I only need to pay half the rent
and utility bills,
so 60,000 should be
more than enough.
Hey, not a problem.
But I'll only have a little left over.
And I'll hafta survive another
full month with that little amount.
Now I've gone past being scared.
I'm beginning to feel depressed.
Nana-chan.
You can go on your lunch break.
Oh, it's okay. I'll be skipping
my lunches for a while.
Huh? Why's that?
Well...
I've decided to go on a diet.
So that's why you're looking
under the weather today.
Brighten up, Hachi.
But that's unfortunate.
It wouldn't be proper to invite you
out at such a time.
I wanted to take you to dinner.
Yay! Food!
All right. We'll close early today.
Think about what you wanna eat.
Darn it.
But it's okay, I guess.
There's no big deal about
having a meal together.
After all, it's not as if
Mr. Mizukoshi has the hots for me.
So this doesn't qualify
as cheating on my boyfriend.
I was waiting for you
that whole time.
I'm really sorry about that.
So, how about next Sunday?
I think I can make it.
That's great!
Oh, right.
About yesterday...
Huh? What?
What are you saying?! That's crazy!
But it's the truth!
I really think you should pick
your friends more carefully.
But like I said,
she's usually a really good girl.
I don't believe that.
Ow!
Yo!
I get it.
Well, I was just as surprised.
You have the same employer,
go to the same university,
and enroll at the same faculty.
Guess you pretty well
hafta get along.
Yes, but Sachiko was accepted
on her first try,
so she's two years younger.
Sachiko?
I can't help it. She asked me
to call her that.
There was no reason to refuse.
She's clearly your type.
Petite and fair-skinned.
You can't help it.
But I'm telling you,
it's not like that!
I'm proud that you're holding back.
She's back.
Here, Shoji. Is coffee okay?
Yeah. Thanks.
Mr. Kyosuke,
which would you prefer?
Just call me Kyosuke, Sa-chan.
That's gonna be trouble.
Huh?
Well, I'm more for the dark-skinned
big girls like you, but...
Huh?!
Well, excuse me for
my dark skin.
But even I find her cute.
This is definitely bad.
So cool!
Shin, I didn't notice you there.
Awesome.
I never knew you could play
the drums too, Nana.
I can't.
But you were!
This is all I know.
But you're good.
When did you learn?
Back home while I was in a band,
I learned it for fun.
From Yasu?
Why do you know about Yasu?
Because when Nobu gets drunk
he always talks about Yasu.
Last night too, he kept saying
how he wished that Yasu was here.
You stayed over at Nobu's place again?
Those are Nobu's clothes,
aren't they?
Nobu's at work right now,
and said he may be a bit late.
Shin, you should return home
once in a while.
I'll bet your parents are worried.
They're not.
Really? Then it's fine, I guess.
You're unusual, Nana.
Usually, everyone says,
"You're mistaken.
Of course they're worried."
But it's a fact that there are parents
who abandon their children.
A junior high student?
That guy who came by the store
about the bassist ad, right?
Didn't he say he was eighteen?
Actually he's fifteen.
Nana cornered him with
a few questions, and he confessed.
He told us he thought they wouldn't
take him seriously
if he said he was
a junior high student.
Oh, but it's April,
so maybe he's in tenth grade now.
Although he doesn't seem to
be going to high school.
Oh? Maybe he didn't bother
taking the entrance exams.
Hmm... I really don't know.
He doesn't go into detail
about such things.
There seems to be more to it
under the surface.
Mhm.
Anyway, he doesn't go home much,
so I'm somewhat concerned.
I'm sure his parents
are totally worried.
I guess so.
And we still haven't found
a drummer.
It's like our luck's running out.
But didn't you say there was
a guy who tried out?
Nana turned him down,
saying she didn't like him.
Although the others said
he was pretty good.
Really. She must have high standards.
Or rather,
I think she's in love with Yasu
and therefore refuses to accept
a different drummer.
Who is Yasu?
He was her band's leader back
in her hometown.
He's a skinhead,
and he and Nana look so great together.
I can just imagine.
Hey, Mr. Mizukoshi, is it okay
if I order the meat and potato dish, too?
Go ahead.
I'm so full!
Happiness!
That's great. But was the tavern
really okay with you?
Yup! I love taverns.
Thank you for the meal.
Nana!
Are you all right?
I think I might've had
a little too much to drink.
How embarrassing.
Oops!
Well, I should be going now.
Wait, Nana!
To be honest,
I asked you out today
because I wanted to talk to you
about something important.
Huh? Wait a minute.
I've been waiting for the right time,
but I just couldn't bring myself
to tell you.
This could come as a surprise to you.
This is too sudden.
I'm well aware what I'm about
to say will trouble you, Nana.
I'm not ready for this.
Mr. Mizukoshi...
You see... I...
I've been waiting for
the right time,
but I just couldn't bring myself
to tell you.
This could come as
a surprise to you.
This is too sudden.
I'm well aware what I'm about
to say will trouble you, Nana.
I'm not ready for this.
Mr. Mizukoshi...
You see, I plan on closing shop.
I'm sorry.
Business isn't going well.
This is real trouble!
Oh! My shoe!
Shoji!
Huh?!
Sorry, Shoji. Go on ahead.
You'll miss the last train!
Hey!
You knew you would hafta run
for the last train.
So why did you hafta wear
those shoes?
I did it on purpose.
Nana
Hello?
Shoji!
Help me!
This is for the taxi.
Never mind.
It's on my way home, anyway.
But It was my fault
we missed the last train.
It really is okay.
Shoji, that call earlier.
It was from your girlfriend, right?
It's my policy not to accept such money
from a guy who has a girlfriend.
Good night.
It appears that this is
all the money I have right now.
Why? You're always working
so hard.
You really are spending it all
on Sachiko!
You're wrong!
In fact, I bought that!
A computer. And it's a Mac.
Nice, isn't it? I'm studying
computer graphic design, after all.
I wonder if we can get
a good price for it.
Cut it out!
But how else am I gonna get
proper food from tomorrow!
All right!
I'll share this with you.
Pickled plums my grandma
made herself.
Shoji, you idiot!
You're of no use!
So, now that I was unemployed,
I was lost,
seriously contemplating the possibility
of starving to death in the streets.
300,000 yen?!
That's right!
Mr. Mizukoshi deposited
300,000 yen for severance pay!
Are you sure you that's not 30,000?
Your remaining salary would've
amounted to around that much.
Then do you think this 300,000 yen
is to sever his relationship with me?
Did you sleep with Mizukoshi?
- No way!
- You're lying!
Why would he give you
that much if you didn't?!
It's not a lie!
Mr. Mizukoshi is returning
to his hometown
and will be getting married.
I feel that I've been deceived.
- You idiot.
- Huh?
The one who deposited
the 300,000 yen wasn't Mizukoshi.
Take a closer look.
Natsuko Komatsu.
That's my mom!
You're a long way from independence
if you're crying to your parents
for money.
Huh? But I didn't tell
I was having money problems!
I thought, if I told them
they would make me go back home.
How did she know?
Could it be maternal instinct?
Oh, right.
Hey, Nana. Now I've got all this money,
let's celebrate with sukiyaki tonight.
Huh?
Back home, my mom would
make sukiyaki
when we had something
to celebrate.
Let's go back to the supermarket
to buy what we need.
You...
You're unemployed!
What is there to celebrate about?!
The fact that I got money...
Don't celebrate!
Be remorseful for the money
you've wasted!
We're having natto soybeans
tonight as planned.
You're not eating any meat
until you find a job.
No way!
Say, shouldn't you call Natsuko
and thank her?
I'll do it later.
Oh, I see. If you call now,
you'd be embarrassed
because you'll cry the moment
you hear mommy's voice.
Well, sure.
You get homesick too, sometimes,
don't you Nana?
No. Since I don't have a home.
There you go, trying to be cool again.
Tonight calls for sukiyaki, after all!
Yasu, Blast is the band you started.
Yeah. I was so worried
I couldn't sleep at night.
Besides, there are law firms
in Tokyo too.
Hey, Nana...
Do you still think that
you don't have a home anywhere?
This dinner table by the window,
and the chairs.
They're still there,
just as they were back then.
I reached into the sky
But I couldn't reach what I wanted
They grew smaller
and disappeared into the sky
Like colorful balloons
I'm alone
My hand had no place to go
And gently you took it
Starless night
I won't look back
at the shadow of my past
I want to feel your warmth
Tears are falling down
Even if I'm unsure I won't let go
Of your hand holding mine