It was summertime.
And with final exams
coming close,
my good mood was wandering about
somewhere in Brazil,
and it didn't seem like it
was going to come back.
Hey, do you know
what day it is today?
Is it your birthday?
Nope.
Is it Miss Asahina's birthday?
Wrong!
It is Koizumi
or Nagato's birthday?
I don't know when
those are!
By the way, my birthday is...
That doesn't matter.
You don't know what an important
day it is today, do you?
It's just a hot weekday
to me.
Tell me what day of
the month it is.
July seventh...
Are you saying that you've been
talking about Tanabata?
Of course I'm talking about Tanabata!
It's Tanabata today!
You're Japanese, you've got to
remember these kinds of things!
I see.
I always make sure to take part
in events like these.
This year, the whole SOS Brigade
is going to make this a huge affair!
And here we go.
Bamboo Leaf Rhapsody
Since this past spring, it's
become my daily routine
to run aimlessly about
this way and that
when Haruhi gets going
about something.
I kind of hate the fact
that I'm getting used to it.
Yes?
Hey.
Hello.
How are you doing?
Things have been crazy for me
ever since I started high school.
Here you go.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Would you like to
try this out?
We'll eventually get bored
of othello, after all.
Unfortunately, I don't know
the rules.
That's too bad.
This is your only chance
to be so carefree.
She's come up with another
hair-brained scheme...
Hey ho! My bad, my bad,
sorry I'm late!
Where the heck did you pick up
that branch and that greeting?
The forest behind
the school.
That's someone's private property,
you bamboo thief.
Here, I also made tanzaku.
Write down your wishes,
everyone!
Tanzaku?
I see. Today is Tanabata,
after all.
There are conditions,
however!
Conditions? Hold on, we haven't even said
that we're going to write anything.
Kyon, do you know who makes wishes
come true during Tanabata?
Orihime and Hikoboshi, right?
Well, that's correct.
Ten points.
Okay, then, do you know which stars
Orihime and Hikoboshi are?
Nope.
That would be Vega and Altair,
I believe.
Eighty-five points!
That's why you have to hang your
tanzaku facing those stars!
What about the other
fifteen points?
Ahem!
Let me explain.
According to the theory
of relativity,
it isn't possible to travel anywhere
faster than the speed of light.
Incidentally,
Vega and Altair are
25 and 16 light years
from Earth, respectively.
Vega - 25 light years
25 and 16 light years
from Earth, respectively.
Altair - 16 light years
25 and 16 light years
from Earth, respectively.
Which means!
That any information that
leaves the Earth will take
at least that much time before
it reaches those stars!
You went to the trouble
to look that up?
That's why neither of
the gods will be able
to make your wish come true
at least until that long after.
So if you wish for a boyfriend
by this Christmas or something,
it won't get there
in time!
If it takes that long
to go one way,
won't it take 50 years or 32 years
for it to make the round trip?
Well, they're gods, so they'll
think of something.
It's like a half-price
summer bargain.
What happened to "according to
the theory of relativity"?
Here are two tanzaku, one each
for Vega and Altair.
So, write wishes that you want to
come true in 25 and 16 years!
We don't know what we'll be doing
in 25 or 16 years,
so what the heck should
we be wishing for?
She's always thinking of
these unnecessary things.
Where in the universe does she
get her idea of "normal" from?
Now, you can't just
say that.
Despite how it may seem,
Miss Suzumiya has a proper
understanding of "normal".
How do you figure that?
She wants the world
to be more unusual.
And she has the power
to remake the world.
But the world has not lost its rationality.
That's why.
Hey there!
No private discussions!
I hope to get better at sewing.
I hope to get better at cooking.
I think she might have
the wrong idea about this.
Harmony
Innovation
My family's well-being - Itsuki Koizumi
World Peace - Itsuki Koizumi
Mine might be a bit on
the ordinary side.
Gimme money
Give me a house with a yard big enough
to wash a dog in
Mine might be a bit on
the ordinary side.
Gimme money
Give me a house with a yard big enough
to wash a dog in
How crass.
Shut it.
Make the world revolve around me.
I want the rotation of the Earth to go
in the opposite direction.
Shut it.
Make the world revolve around me.
I want the rotation of the Earth to go
in the opposite direction.
Mine are much better
than yours.
It's a difference of values.
Be sure to remember what
you wrote, everyone.
The first checkpoint will be
in sixteen years, after all.
The challenge is to see
whose wish Hikoboshi grants!
Sixteen years, huh?
That's a long time...
After that,
Haruhi was strangely quiet,
and seemed to be melancholy.
Her being so docile was,
strangely enough, eerie.
The quieter she was, the more
I was worried about the backlash.
Would you like some more?
Yes, please.
Shh.
So cute.
Please stay in the club room,
even after we're finished. Mikuru
But of course!
I'm going home now.
Last person out
lock the door, okay?
In that case,
I'll be going, too.
Lucky me!
Hey...
If you'll excuse me.
Right.
Thank goodness we were able
to stay behind so naturally.
Is this something that it would be bad
for the others to hear?
Yes...
There's a particular place that
I want you to come with me to.
That's fine.
Where are we going?
Umm...
Three years... ago...
Thr...
I'm sorry to be making
such a strange request!
You can't?
So this would be
time travel, then?
Yes, that's right.
I'm all right
with going, but...
Why me, and what are we
going to do?
That... You'll know
when we get there.
Probably.
Please, don't ask anything else,
just say yes!
If you don't, then I...
I'll be in trouble...
She's cute!
Well...
Okay, I'll go.
Really? Thank you!
So cute!
Oh, thank goodness...
Now that I think about it,
the only time that Miss Asahina's
mentioned she's from the future
is when she admitted it
to me,
and the only proof of it is the existence
of the adult Miss Asahina.
This is a perfect chance for me
to confirm
that she's a girl
from the future.
So, where's your
time machine?
We'll be leaving
from here.
From here?
Kyon... I'm sorry.
Oh, you're awake!
Please wake up soon...
My legs have
gone numb.
Why was I asleep?
I'm sorry, but I didn't want you to
see how time jumping is performed.
Because it's classified information...
Umm... are you mad?
No, not at all.
If it was Haruhi that did it,
I'd hit her.
But since it's you,
it's completely okay.
Thank goodness.
So it's three years ago?
July seventh,
three years ago.
I'd guess around
nine PM?
Really?
Really.
This is the same park that Nagato
invited me to some time ago.
Is this a Mecca
for unusual people?
Miss Asahina?
Um...
Could this be some sort of
declaration of intent?
Hello, Kyon.
Miss Asahina!
So this is how I looked
back then.
It was her role
to guide you here.
Guiding you from this point on
is mine.
Are you the one that put
Miss Asahina to sleep?
I couldn't let her
see me,
because when I was here, as her,
I didn't meet me.
Right...
Down those railroad tracks over there
is a school.
Please help the person
you meet at the school gate.
And I'm sorry, but please give me
a piggyback ride.
This feels kind of like
a game event.
Do I get an item or something
as a reward for doing this?
A reward?
Let's see...
I don't have anything
that I can give you.
But if you want, you can give
the sleeping me there a kiss.
But only while she's asleep.
That's a little...
On an emotional
and on a situational level,
doing that would go against
my principles.
But, well, even still...
It's time.
I have to go.
Also, you have to keep my being here
a secret from her.
Promise me.
Will you pinky swear
with me?
Okay, you've sworn!
Good bye, Kyon.
See you later.
I wonder how long
it's been
since this adult Miss Asahina
and I have seen each other.
It doesn't feel like she's changed
much from the last time I saw her.
But is this really
three years ago?
I need to confirm this,
somehow.
Maybe I should call 411.
East Junior High, huh?
Hey.
Who are you?
It does certainly seem like
I've gone back three years.
This is Haruhi Suzumiya,
currently a seventh grader.
I asked you
who you were.
A pervert?
A kidnapper?
What about you,
what are you doing?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm breaking and entering.
How am I supposed to react when you
just admit your illegal activities?
I don't know
who you are,
but if you're not doing anything,
then help me out.
If you don't,
I'll report you.
It's Haruhi.
No mistaking it.
This way.
It's a good thing
it's dark out.
This way, she won't be able to
get a good look at our faces.
The Haruhi three years from now
doesn't seem to remember us at all.
So I think that if it wasn't this way,
we'd have problems.
I took it out of the storage room
in the evening and hid it.
Good idea, right?
I'll handle that.
You grab the line marker.
So, what are we doing
with this?
Draw lines the way
I tell you to.
Me?
Right, you.
Because I'm the director.
Hey, the line's shaky over there!
What are you doing!?
Her willingness to order around a
high school student she just met
without any problems
is so very her.
If I had first met her like this,
as a junior high school student,
I probably would have thought
that she was really crazy.
At Haruhi's direction,
I ran this way and that,
drawing white lines.
This was the mysterious message
that Taniguchi had mentioned,
but I never thought that I would be
the one that drew it...
Hmph. It's okay.
Well, excuse me.
Do you think aliens exist?
Well, that was sudden.
Answer the question.
I guess they do.
What about time travelers?
Wouldn't be strange
if there were.
And espers?
There are probably enough of them
to walk in formation.
People from
other dimensions?
I haven't met any
of them yet.
That's the uniform for North High,
isn't it?
Well, yeah.
What's your name?
John Smith.
Are you stupid
or something?
Let's just say that I want
to stay anonymous.
Who's the girl
you were carrying?
My big sister.
She had a sudden case
of narcolepsy.
She falls asleep regardless
of location,
so I was carrying her.
Hmph.
So, what in the world
is this?
Can't you tell by looking?
It's a message.
It's not for Orihime
or Hikoboshi, is it?
How did you know that?
Well, it is Tanabata.
I just remembered someone I knew
doing something similar.
Huh. I'd love to meet
that person.
So, that person goes
to North High?
You could say that.
North High, huh?
I'm going home. I've accomplished
my goal, after all.
Bye.
And not even a thanks
for helping her.
Miss Asahina.
Where am I?!
What happened and when
is it right now?!
Umm...
I don't have my TPDD...
Huh?
It's gone...
What's wrong?
What's a "TPDD"?
It's classified, but...
It's like a time machine.
Why would it
be gone?
I don't know.
I should have it,
but I've lost it.
Will anyone come
save us?
There's no way...
So, what's going
to happen to us?
We're stuck like this.
We're going to be left in this time plane,
three years prior,
unable to go back
to our own time!
This is a pretty grave matter.
It is!
But for some reason,
I didn't feel any sense of urgency.
It was probably the adult Miss Asahina
that took that TPDD-thingy.
That's probably why
she came to the past.
As for why, it would
be so that she could
experience losing the TPDD
when she was here.
I think that things are going
to turn out all right.
What?
Is this the home of a
Miss Yuki Nagato?
I'm not really sure
what to say, but...
Will you understand if I say I'm an
acquaintance of Haruhi Suzumiya?
Yo.
Is it all right for us
to come in?
And that is who we are
and why we're here.
Also, the you three years
from now gave me this.
I understand.
As far as you're concerned, this is
the first time we've met, right?
Yes.
Requesting access to the memory of
the unit in the other time plane.
I have downloaded
the information
from the opposite side of
the linked time boundary.
The me that exists three years from now
and I are the same being.
The me three years from now and I
have shared our memories.
How?
We synchronized.
I don't understand.
Why are you wearing
a North High uniform?
Are you already enrolled?
I am not. The current me
is in standby mode.
Standby?
So you intend to be in standby
for almost three years?
Yes.
That sounds like
an awfully long process.
That is my role.
There is more than one way
to travel through time.
The TPDD is not the only device
that can control time.
It's uncertain and primitive.
Umm... What do you mean?
The movement of life forms
that use the TPDD
is within tolerable ranges,
but it creates noise.
To us, it is an
imperfect form.
By "us", do you mean
the Thought Entity?
Miss Nagato, are you able to travel
through time in a perfect form?
The form does not matter.
As long as information can travel
back and forth, it is enough.
You don't mean to say that we
should sleep in here, do you?
Yes.
Together, with Miss Asahina?
Lie down.
Straight to the point!
You'll just be sleeping.
Well, that's my intention,
too, but...
I... I guess we don't have any choice
but to do what we're told...
Yes...
What, really?
What's the matter?
Is that the TPDD?
No, this is simply
a radio wave watch.
Thank goodness,
we're back.
It's just after 9:30 PM on the July 7th
that we left from.
How did you do it?
I suspended the flow of information
inside of a selected time-space.
I then released
the time suspension
at a pre-designated point in
the time-space continuum.
You mean you stopped time?!
Miss Nagato stopped time
in this room for three years.
And when today came around,
she released the time stop... right?
Yes.
I can't believe it!
Which means,
in other words...
That time when you told me
you were an alien and stuff...
Miss Asahina and I were in
the next room, asleep?
Yes.
I always thought that you
were pretty clever,
but you're actually omnipotent,
aren't you?
That's not true.
This was a special case.
Emergency mode.
It doesn't happen often.
It has to be something rare.
Thank you.
It was nothing.
Can you read
what this says?
"I am here."
That's what it says.
Could it be that it's written in
the language of some alien race?
Nagato didn't answer me.
I'm sorry.
Actually, I...
I don't really understand.
I'm just an underling...
No, not even that.
I mean, I'm more like
a trainee, so...
And yet you're hanging around
with Haruhi.
Well, I never thought that
Miss Suzumiya would catch me!
All I do is obey the orders
of my superior...
Maybe I should say the
people above me.
So sometimes I don't understand
the things that I'm doing.
I wonder if her superior
is the adult Miss Asahina.
The adult Miss Asahina had to know
how things turned out for us.
But it looks like she didn't tell
this Miss Asahina any of it.
I guess that people from the future
have their own rules and laws.
I'm sure that someone
will tell her.
When everything falls
into place.
The next day was,
of course, July eighth.
Consciously I knew that
it was the next day,
but physically, it had been
three years and a day
since I had come
to school.
What's wrong? Did you eat a poison
mushroom or something?
Not really. I'm just melancholy
from remembering some stuff.
Memories from
previous Tanabatas.
Is that so?
Hey, Nagato.
Miss Asahina really is
from the future, right?
Yes.
If that's the case, it feels like
the processes that link
the past and the future
don't quite add up right.
What do you mean?
Previously, Miss
Asahina said that
there's no connection between
the past and the future.
But in going back
three years,
I provided Haruhi with knowledge
she didn't need.
She ended up coming
to North High,
and she started looking for people
who weren't normal...
There's a chance
that's why.
There's a definite connection between
the past and the future.
This contradicts the explanation
that Miss Asahina gave me.
A contradictory set of theories
cannot explain its own contradictions.
Is that supposed to be
an explanation?
You'll eventually understand.
This is what she means.
Right now, my king is currently
in check by your rook.
"Oh no, what do I do?
Where shall I flee to?"
Now, what was contradictory
about what I just did?
In our case, the king really
isn't all that important.
What's important to us
is the queen.
I see.
I don't know when something
will happen next,
but when it does, I hope it doesn't
require so much thinking.
I'd prefer that things stay
nice and peaceful.
Would you prefer for
something to happen?
Why, you!
Sora kara ochite kitanda
It fell from the sky
Subete no negai wo nosete
With all of the wishes
that were made upon it
Hitotsu no hoshi niwa
chotto omokatta kana
Maybe it was a little too heavy
for a single star
Yappari nanika henda yo
Something just doesn't
seem right
Kokoro no kimi ga kieta
The image of you in my mind
has vanished
Tashika ni oboeteru tte
ieruno kai?
Can I say that I
remember you clearly?
Tomare!
Stop!
Kako wa jibun no mono
The past belongs to me
Touzen daretomo torikaetakunai
Of course I don't want to trade it
with anyone else
Nazenara
That's because
Basudei datta watashitachi niwa
It was my birthday,
and when we saw each other
Deai ga umareta toki ni
We could see the first dream
Hajimete no yume ga mieru
That we had
when we were born
Doushiyouka tte nayanda koto mo
Worrying about "what do I do?"
Ima omoeba waraeru hodo
datta yo ne
Is laughable when I
think about it now
Mou wasureteta
I've already forgotten it
Kimi wo sagasou
Let's search for you