A history of the couple's romance
that starts from the first kiss
You, the one who cast magic on
this destiny, suddenly appeared
The sky where two moons
never fade away
That's an impossibility, right?
This is the first time I've
felt anything like this
I'm feeling more and more
at ease with this place
Even if you trip and
become depressed
I will always hold you
tight with a squeeze
The story where we met that day
stays hot with a sweet kiss
See, you can cast magic, and
the wishes will surely come true
A history of the couple's romance
that starts from the first kiss
You, the one who cast magic on
this destiny, suddenly appeared
Zero Louise
Everyone, congratulations on
making it to your second year.
I am Mrs. Chevreuse,
and I have been appointed
to the Tristein Institute
of Magic for the year.
My element is earth, and I am also
known as Chevreuse the Red Moon.
I will be teaching you earth-based
magic for the next year.
Now, everyone, what are the
four major elements of magic?
Ah-hah!
The four elements are Fire,
Water, Air, and Earth!
And what coincidence! My element
is Earth, just like you, missus!
Also known as the Brass,
I am Guiche de Grammont!
Please remember me.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Grammont.
Earth is an important type of magic,
involved in the revitalization
of all things.
In order to demonstrate that to you,
I will have you memorize
a spell in basic alchemy.
Rel In Yan.
Is that gold?!
No, it's brass.
Is that it?
I'll have someone try it now.
All right, you. You over there.
What is your name?
Louise.
Louise de la Vallière.
Um, ma'am?
Something the matter?
I think it's better not to...
It's dangerous!
If Louise is going to do it,
I'll do it instead!
Dangerous? How can
alchemy be dangerous?
I'll do it! Please let me do it!
Well said.
Louise, stop it!
Quiet. You're ruining
my concentration.
Think hard about the metal
that you want to turn this into.
Rel In Yan.
Another year has started
with no particular problems.
Yes, there's nothing better.
As the Institute's principal,
I can wish for nothing more.
Oh, brother.
Taking care of your health is part
of my job as secretary, Old Osman.
Are you going to take away one of
this old man's very few pleasures,
Miss Longueville?
Please stop touching my buttocks.
Please also stop acting senile
when you're caught in a bad situation!
Come to think of it, tomorrow is
the familiar summoning ritual
for the second year students!
Damn old geezer.
The familiar is a lifelong
servant and friend,
as well as one's eyes and ears.
My familiar, Motsognir...
It's been a long journey
together with you.
Oh, I see, white! White as snow!
I think Miss Longueville'd look
better in black than in white.
Don't you think so?
Old Osman,
if you do it again, I will report it
to the royal family!
Fool!
Don't be so upset just because
someone peeked at your panties!
That's why you haven't been
able to get married yet!
Ouch... I'm sorry, I won't do it
again, really, forgive me...
That was...
I believe it's her again.
You mean the third daughter
of the Vallière family?
This is what I feared!
It looks like I screwed up a little bit.
What?!
What part of this is a little?
Your success rate to date
has been zero!
Louise the Zero!
Hey, how was it?
Another trip to detention?
Or are you finally expelled?
Just kidding!
I'm not being punished.
Why not?
They said it was partially
the teacher's fault
for making me do it after all
the students tried to stop her.
I just wasn't doing my best today.
You're always having a bad day!
You can't even get a real byname,
Louise the Zero!
Shut up!
Tomorrow will be a sight!
What kind of familiar will
you be summoning up?
As far as summoning spells...
I'm confident in Summon Servant,
if nothing else!
Just you watch!
I'll conjure up a familiar so
divine, beautiful, and powerful,
that it will be better than anything
any of you can cook up!
Hey, what do you think, Tabitha?
I don't know.
But to think that she would
say it that confidently...
Maybe...
No way.
Is it the appointed time already?
Wait, Styx!
Kirche, it's me, Pelisson.
Oh, no, Styx was coming tomorrow!
I'm sorry, Pelisson,
wait just a minute!
I'm confident in Summon Servant,
if nothing else!
I wish I hadn't said that...
Finally, today is the day
of the summoning ritual.
This is the first test since you
advanced to the second year,
and the sacred first day where
you meet your familiars,
with whom you will spend
your lives as nobles.
I'm looking forward to the amazing
familiar you're going to summon!
Leave me alone.
It's a bugbear! Amazing!
Oh, that was splendid.
And if I end up with
some strange familiar,
I'll be embarrassed
for the rest of my life!
I'm sure you will summon a cute,
charming familiar, Montmorency!
Of course!
They say that the familiar that's
summoned best suits the summoner!
So someone like me...
Next up?
That would be me, Guiche
de Grammont, Mr. Colbert.
I will now summon the finest familiar
in the history of the Institute.
Then, my fame...
Enough with the small talk.
People are still waiting their turn.
Then...
O Bremir, our grand creator
that always guides us...
O noble one who will become
a servant of Guiche the Brass!
Answer my divine summons!
Salamander! Kirche summoned that?!
At the end, you obtained quite
the familiar there, Miss Zerbst.
It fits my byname, Kirche the Fever.
Now, was that everyone?
No, we still have Miss Vallière to go.
Louise the Zero!
What will she summon?
There's no way she can
summon anything!
We'll just have another
explosion, nothing else!
After all that boasting,
you'll summon something more
amazing than this little guy,
right, Louise?
Of course!
Please...
My servant, that exists
somewhere in this universe!
What's with that spell?
Well, it's original.
My divine, beautiful,
and powerful familiar!
I wish and assert from
the bottom of my heart...
Answer my guidance!
Just as expected...
Are you all right, Montmorency?
Something wrong?
A human?!
That outfit... It looks like a peasant...
Yeah. A peasant, no doubt about it.
This is divine, beautiful,
and powerful?
Who are you?
What was that? Where am I?
You don't understand our language?
Where are you from, peasant?
English? No, it isn't...
Besides...
Nothing less from someone
who put up a huge front!
To think that you would
summon up a peasant!
I just made a small mistake!
Nothing less from Louise the Zero!
A result that meets
everyone's expectations!
Hey, wait...
Shut up!
Mr. Colbert.
What is it?
Can I try summoning again?
I can't allow that.
Why?
This ritual is a sacred one that
decides the mage's entire life.
Trying a second time is blasphemy
against the ritual itself!
Whether you like it or not,
this boy has been chosen
as your familiar.
I don't know what he's talking about,
but from what they're wearing,
these guys all are really crazy.
But I've never heard of using
a peasant boy as a familiar!
I will not allow any exceptions,
peasant boy or not.
Continue on with the ritual.
With this?
Hurry up, or you will
really be expelled!
Yeah! You heard it!
All right...
What is it?!
Go for it, Louise!
Be thankful for this.
Normally a noble would never
do this with a peasant boy!
My name is Louise Françoise
Le Blanc de La Vallière.
Pentagon that rules the five powers,
bless this individual, and
make him my familiar!
What is she doing?!
Come on, stay still!
Hold on...
What, uh, wait...
It seems Contract Servant
has ended peacefully.
Hey! What did that thing
right now mean?!
My body's getting hot...
What did you do to me?!
It will be over soon.
It's just the rune of the familiar
being burned onto you.
What?!
What was that dream just now?
So you've finally woken up.
It wasn't a dream!
I thought about it long enough
to get an ulcer.
But I've given up. I'm going
to have you as my familiar.
Be honored.
Where in the world have
I been taken away to?!
Take me back home! If you're
not going to take me back...
Wash those.
Even if you don't understand
our language,
a familiar can understand that much.
What is this...
You don't even understand
your master's orders?
If he can't understand an order,
he's worse than a dog.
Hey, why are you trying
to seduce me?!
In the first place, who are you?
Oh, be quiet! All you do is chirp!
Right, silencing magic.
I learned it last year!
This must be some bad dream!
Get me out of this dream,
and back on the 'net!
Let's see...
Ansur Ver Ang.
Notice the tracks, and
answer my requests!
Strange...
What was that just now?
I held back 'cause you're cute,
but if I have to use force...
I understand! I understood that!
Did you just say, I understand?
Say something.
What, so you can speak Japanese?
What does this mean?
I cast a spell of silence...
Another failure.
You, what's your name?
Me? My name is Hiraga Saito.
Hiragasaito?
But before that, why am I here?
I summoned you, of course.
As a familiar, right?
A familiar?!
This is it!
But it can't be...
As a precaution, I will have
to inform the principal.
So, it's like this...
This is the kingdom of Tristein,
on the continent Harkeginia?
And you're a student in
the Institute of Magic.
I won't allow a familiar
to call me "you".
My name is Louise.
Louise de la Vallière.
Yeah, right, right.
So, Louise, I'm this familiar
that you summoned.
That thing that all
sorcerers tote around.
That much I know from
movies and manga.
Why is my familiar a peasant boy?!
I wanted something cool
like a dragon or a griffon!
Hiragasaito?
A familiar ran away?! You're kidding!
I don't know if it's a new cult,
or some fantasy novel maniac,
but I can't stay here any longer!
I'm good at baking soufflés.
I would love to try one.
Really?!
Of course, Ketty.
I wouldn't lie to your eyes.
Lord Guiche!
There is nothing hidden
behind my feelings for you.
Isn't that the peasant
that Louise summoned?
Oh, crap!
In today's ritual?
It caused quite a stir among
the first year students as well.
He had suddenly fainted
and stopped moving,
so it was quite troublesome for us.
Hold on, you.
Yes?
A peasant putting a noble to trouble,
and not even a word of thanks?
Oh, was that so? Well, thanks.
Then I'll be seeing you!
Irritating jerk.
Oh, no!
A restless fellow.
Louise, your familiar just passed by.
Catch him.
He ran away.
The familiar with whom
you sealed a contract?
Nothing less from
your familiar, Louise.
Common sense doesn't apply to it.
Don't be impressed by it, help me!
I've no choice.
Being with you all alone like this
is like a dream, Kirche the Fever.
It looks like tonight won't end
with just a fever.
All right, an exit!
That guy... He's the one
that Louise the Zero...
Yes, the peasant familiar.
Oh, he's over there!
Right.
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Oh, just listen to this!
Knock it off! He's getting away!
What was that about magic?!
I gotta hurry out of this crazy place...
Help me! I'm gonna fall!
Just give yourself up.
This is the second time
that I've kept you afloat.
Is this for real?!
A familiar that runs from his master?
It's just too funny!
Then this is...
You're kidding me!
As if I were under a real magic spell
A bright smile is burnt onto my heart
But each time I see you, I give you
a pointy, cold shoulder
Why do I act mean towards the one
that I think about the most?
My true feelings,
the shards of loneliness
In the deepest part of my heart,
I'm calling for you
For the day to start from zero
Peasant or dog, now that
you're my familiar,
be prepared for some
really hard training!
Wait, what are you doing?!
Dueling against a noble?!
Next Episode: Peasant Familiar
Next episode: Peasant Familiar