Why am I in this crowd?
No no, if I make it through there's
a mountain of dojinshi waiting for me.
Based on the ones I saw in
Akihabara and in the club office...
...I can expect some good stuff...
Sasahara.
This is your first Comic Fest?
Uh, yeah...
You look tired, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay...
I've just been over-excited since
yesterday, and it's worn me out...
It's still too early to be tired.
That's true...
Kohsaka stands out...
But still...
Is it 100% otaku in here?
Genshiken
I woke up and as usual forgot
my cell and missed the Express.
My life reflected in
the train window.
I'm sure I have something that
I won't lose to anyone in Japan...
... but it's pretty sad
that no one notices it.
I can't run fast, though.
I'm not that strongly-built.
Here I go, at my dauntless pace.
Pass away, today's
sadness, raining in the sun!
Hesitation, repetition,
dreaming all night, all night.
Farewell sadness,
to outer space you go!
Look to the sky and shout
at the top of your lungs!
At this tempo!
Right now, at this tempo!
Genshiken
International Exhibition Hall Station
The foreboding of a storm...
M-Madarame's getting into
character s-so don't mind him.
Oh...
Episode 3: The Issue of Regional
Cultural Advancement and its Merits
We took the first train, so why
are so many people lined up already?
They've been here all night, of course.
I-Isn't that prohibited?
Besides, it's such bad weather...
A storm, in fact.
Oh...
Well, it's not like
I'd want to go that far.
I-lf Kasukabe were here she
wouldn't understand a word of this.
No, I don't think she'd realize
she was missing anything.
Ugh, high humidity.
Why's the air so hot?
It sure is hot.
Oh yeah!
Why are you so cheerful?
This bad weather makes
it feel like a real event.
It's times like this when things
like religious experiences happen!
You think so?
Religious experiences aside,
this weather is a rare thing.
Y-You're right.
Recently it's been otherwise, but in the
past...
...popular opinion held that it didn't rain
during the summer Fest.
Wow, is that so...
Yes!
I get the feeling
something will happen today!
Something divinely inspired!
You lost me...
Stop and go, what a drag!
But we're definitely making progress.
I've got a total runner's high.
Huh?
The world of light!
Running in place is depressing.
Why not go actually run for a bit?
We'll keep your place in line.
Good idea!
Are you serious?
Just kidding, I'd never
mess up the line like...
M-Madarame, are you all right?
He's embarrassed.
This could become legendary.
Yeah, um, well...
Am I in trouble?
It's sprained...
No, broken...
But at least my fingers move, and
it doesn't feel like it's snapped...
I need to hit the corporate
booths before dojinshi today!
My first priority is to get my hands
on the commemorative limited edition...
...Kujibiki Unbalance anime
trading cards that Kodansha put out!
All you have to do is line up for them!
I can do it!
Piece of cake!
I just need to get to them...
You sure got quiet.
Of c-course, he's embarrassed.
Good, I'll go as far as I
can, to the divine domain!
It feels like I can reach heaven!
The exhibit hall is
currently terribly crowded.
Please do not rush, but
walk slowly and carefully.
We thank you for your cooperation.
Posters, pencil boards...
Would it be best to check
what the trading cards are now?
B-Before that let's get
in the card-only line.
If it's there, we can always g-get out.
That's true.
Madarame?
We're going.
Uh, yeah.
I-I don't have
t-today's rare card.
Neither do I.
Or me...
W-Well, I'll sort
them so gather them up.
What about you, Madarame?
Sorry, Sasahara, look for me.
What?
It turns out I twisted
my wrist when I fell.
Are you all right?
Is it swollen?
Well, I haven't looked...
Anyway you look at it, that's
a sprain, or maybe even worse...
You think so too?
I even forgot to act like Tetsuo.
Huh?
In any case, you should hurry to
Medical...
...or maybe you should go to a hospital
instead?
I'm okay, I'm okay...
I can stay...
Here.
Well, if you say so...
There it is...
The rare card.
I have seen God.
You can stop now...
Man, that's brave...
Brave and risky...
Are y-you seriously okay, Madarame?
It gradually hurts less and less...
I-Isn't that bad?
Come on, here's where it really begins!
We're finally at the east hall!
But...
Y-You can't shop with
that hand, can you?
Right, so...
I'll stick close behind Sasahara,
he's just the right height...
If I like something he looks at, he can
buy two copies and I'll pay him later.
...I really don't like that idea.
Just choose stuff you're into!
I still don't like this.
Sasahara, think about this.
If you took the first subway train...
...waited in line for five hours
in humidity and a rainstorm...
...got through both this injury
and the limited edition trap...
...and now had this mountain
of treasure before your eyes...
...would you come this
far just to run away?
I don't think you've
gotten through the injury yet.
This thing's gone numb now anyway.
We'll pretend we didn't see that.
Like hell!
Let's go.
Oh, excuse me.
W-What a clown.
Madarame...
Hold on, this really looks serious!
S-S-S-Sasahara,
g-get a staffer!
Hmm, he's out.
I guess his brain finally cut
out on him, like a breaker...
He was pushing too hard after all.
I'll g-go with him.
Oh, that's all right, I'll go.
No, you won't!
You're awake?
Don't bother.
You guys buy dojinshi.
Two copies of the good ones.
I'll pay you later...
I'm counting on you!
Please don't speak.
You'll bite your tongue.
You actually see people on
stretchers quite a bit...
But you never expect it
to be someone you know.
W-Well, from here we split
up and do our own shopping.
All right...
This is our meeting place.
All right, then I'll be going.
Good luck.
Come back alive.
Please don't talk like Madarame.
Madarame mentioned it before...
...but they're all looking
at the contents before buying.
So that does happen...
It certainly is a welcome sight.
Lots of dojin shops won't
let you flip through...
But then it's not like there's anyone
to blame if you don't like it...
Ahh, there I go thinking too much.
One copy, please.
700 Yen.
Oh, a book about
Kujiun's Miss President?
Please, Miss President.
And it's my kind of art style...
But, no one else is looking at them...
Darn it! What is there
to be embarrassed about?
Didn't I train for
this at the dojin shops?
Besides, we're all the same here...
Um, is it all right if I browse?
F-Feel free.
All righty...
One copy, no, two copies please.
That comes to 1000 Yen.
Ah, forgive me, ancestors...
Here I am in this place when I haven't
even visited your graves yet this year.
International Exhibition Hall Station
Hello...
Sure, see you later.
She doesn't think she can make it past
the station, so she's going home.
N-Not bad for Kasukabe.
Right.
Thank you for posing.
Thanks a lot.
Excuse me, please look this way.
Look this way too, please.
Would you mind posing with
your fingers interlaced?
Like this?
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
Okay, here we go.
Cool, thank you much.
These are the pictures from last time.
Thanks as always.
Are you sure it's all right, Fukuro?
It's all right, it's all right.
Did I buy too much, though?
This is heavy...
Student Council of Darkness
- 500 Yen
Now I've completely blended in.
I'll take one.
Anywhere you look here,
we're all the same.
Hey, he came here with a girl?
You can't be yourself that way!
What's with him, lookin' all cool?
Why don't you dress for the occasion?
Kujiun Parody - 700 Yen
I'll buy it!
Met Warrior- 700 Yen
I'll buy this too!
Project K - 1000 Yen
I'll buy any book about her!
Uh-oh, I feel like something on top
of my head is starting to crack open...
Something on top of my head...
Sasahara!
Oh, aren't you...
...Haraguchi?
Why are you...
I'm also with the Manga Club, you see.
Then this is the
Manga Club's booth?
Komaki 3 - Komaki 4
Oh neat!
You make dojinshi?
I'll buy some.
No, just take one.
What?
Here's the latest one.
Uh, no...
I'll pay for it.
I'm giving it to you.
Here, give it a read.
Okay, thank you very much.
Is this really legit?
The other members
aren't saying anything...
Come on around behind the table.
Let's talk a bit.
Are you sure?
You can fit through that gap over there.
Right...
Have a seat.
It sure is hot.
Yeah...
Is this really kosher?
If I sit down it means
someone else has to stand.
For that matter, they're all
facing away and ignoring us.
Are you sure about this, Haraguchi?
So, are things in your price range?
Well, I couldn't afford big corporate
stuff so I went for smaller groups.
Ah, but you didn't have
a chance with the bigwigs, anyway...
...by the time you got through
the general attendee line.
If you're serious about buying, you need
to be here...
...as part of a circle from the get go.
I see, is it that much better?
Well, yeah, but I guess
Genshiken could never manage it.
I mean, is Genshiken
currently producing anything?
They aren't, are they?
Let me tell you about Genshiken.
About ten years ago, they
formed as a composite circle...
...crossing the bounds of
manga, anime, and games.
But on the contrary, what exactly
they do became blurry and vague.
Besides, nowadays all
circles are borderless.
So in conclusion, the existence
of Genshiken is valueless.
That's why it's made up
primarily of wanna-bes.
The only one who can even
remotely draw is Kugayama.
But it's just doodles,
nothing print-worthy...
Madarame talks like
he's a military otaku...
...but in reality he's just
an uninformed Zeon freak.
Tanaka does cosplay...
Cosplay...
It's just, you know...
And that Kohsaka kid?
What's his deal?
His interests are
definitely an otaku's...
...but his appearance, behavior, and
personality aren't otaku-like at all.
What an odd guy.
I wouldn't know.
In any case, Genshiken is a bunch
of lukewarm losers year after year.
They don't amount to
anything on their own.
Why not quit now and
join the Manga Club?
But Haraguchi, aren't
you part of both clubs?
In name only, really.
I attended at first, but once I knew
what they were about I stopped going.
Oh, that reminds me.
The chairman has held his
position since I was a freshman.
What year do you suppose he is?
Got me.
Well, the group's just
right for me at least.
Oh yeah?
That's too bad.
Ah, yes.
This conversation was confidential, so
don't disclose it to anyone else.
Oh, by the way, did you draw
anything in the book you gave me?
I'm something of an editor, so I have to
be the one who keeps everyone in line.
Oh...
How're they selling?
Not bad...
I feel sorry for the Manga Club guys...
Now I get it...
The reason no one looks
pleased about Haraguchi's name...
...coming up in conversation is because
that's the kind of person he is...
At this time, Comic Festival 66
Summer is now coming to an end.
Sorry I took so long.
H-Hi, y-you
really stuck to it.
Yeah, I had trouble choosing...
D-Did you buy anything for Madarame?
Yes, I tried buying
several books for him.
Oh! That one's by the fan
circle he's secretly into.
I d-did think your t-tastes
overlapped, but this is unexpected...
I'm not sure if I'm happy about that.
I b-bought this.
T-This is pretty good.
I-Isn't it?
The art's pretty good, and it's s-sexy.
So Sasahara, how was
your first Comic Fest?
Yeah, like Kohsaka said before,
I really do fit in with Genshiken...
Ah...
It wore me out.
I'll b-bet, especially with
all that happened today.
Very true.
B-But, it's not over yet.
What?
You line up to go home, too.
Save me!
We took no detours or shortcuts...
... and we weren't afraid of
what tomorrow would bring...
... as we kept walking down
Inogashira Street late at night.
Only vivid dreams extended
deep into the shadows.
We aren't quite grown up.
Simple but complicated
glistening like marbles.
The time we could see from there
sparkled, even if nothing big happened.
What we see from the marbles in
our hands now is a little different...
... but they shine faintly nearby.
Harunobu Madarame: Injury to wrist
ligaments; metacarpal fracture;
sprain of proximal interpharyngeal joint;
- Full recovery in two months
Hey, Sasahara, is this your
first time in Ochanomizu?
Yes, I always go straight
to Akihabara and back.
Check out all the college students.
Yeah, Nihon U, Meiji U...
Over there are Tokyo Medical
and Dental, and Juntendo.
This sure is a famous place.
Sundai.
What?
Athenee Francais.
Yeah, but that's...
Bigakko.
Right...
TDG.
Hmm...
Which one doesn't belong?
Uh...