In other words, you
can't protect Louise.
Saito...
You were here?
It doesn't matter where I am.
Can it be that you were crying?
Leave me alone!
You were up against the leader
of the Magic Guards.
He's the head of the guards that
protect the Royal Highness, right?
Even if you lost...
It's not like that!
When I was looking up at the sky,
I thought that maybe I'll never be
able to get back home,
and I felt so pathetic that
I shed a couple tears.
Idiot.
In any case, as long as
you're here in Harkeginia,
you are my familiar!
You take care of my everyday stuff,
and I need you to protect me.
You can have Wardes protect you.
See, the fact that you lost
is nagging at you after all!
It's not nagging at me.
That's enough of that!
You're a man, right?
Shut up!
Saito...
I'm going to marry Wardes.
A history of the couple's romance
that starts from the first kiss
You, the one who cast magic on
this destiny, suddenly appeared
The sky where two moons
never fade away
That's an impossibility, right?
This is the first time I've
felt anything like this
I'm feeling more and more
at ease with this place
Even if you trip and
become depressed
I will always hold you
tight with a squeeze
The story where we met that day
stays hot with a sweet kiss
See, you can cast magic, and
the wishes will surely come true
A history of the couple's romance
that starts from the first kiss
You, the one who cast magic on
this destiny, suddenly appeared
Louise's Marriage
Saito!
What are you dilly-dallying for?
It's almost time to depart!
Oh, is that so...
"Is that so?" You know...
What is it? An earthquake?
Guiche! Behind you!
No way... A golem?!
Why?
Fouquet?
Saito and...
Yeah, they said they
were going back now.
Why?
Actually, they wouldn't tell me why.
Shut up!
It's all right.
We can complete the
mission without them.
But...
Let's go! We don't have
much time before departure.
The pier is in sight!
What are you here for, Fouquet?!
I came here to thank you
for putting me in prison!
Not bad.
But...
I too am a mage of Earth!
Go!
Everything you do is useless!
Behold the powers of
Guiche de Grammont!
Is the situation that bad nowadays?!
Yes. The position of the
royal family is very bad.
It is known that Albion is in civil war,
due to the rebellion of the nobility.
In truth, the nobility has taken
over most of Albion's territory.
To those that side with the royal
family, forced out of the castle,
Prince Wales is their only
survivor of the family,
their only hope.
That can't be...
No need to worry, Louise.
I will protect you.
Liar.
All of them defeated so easily...
What was that?!
Kirche! Tabitha!
Saito! Have you been well?
Wait!
It's cowardly to ambush
from the side like that!
Oh? I was wondering who it was...
If it isn't that old thief.
Old?! I'm only twenty-three!
What's this about?
What is that?
Oh, well. I was able to
stop you long enough.
Stop us?
Hey now, where's that
dandy bearded fellow?
What's that sound?
That's the sign of departure!
That dandy bearded fellow
has been on my mind...
It took an entire day to figure out
where you guys were.
What persistence...
And then I find you guys
fighting a golem.
The two of them departed already.
The two of them?!
Yes. They had told me that the
people accompanying them
would be turning back from here.
This can't be happening.
Guiche! Where is the pier?!
It's useless to go to the pier now.
That was the ship that we
were planning to board.
That's a ship?
It's flying.
Of course it is.
Albion is a flying continent.
Flying continent?
On evenings that the two moons
overlap each other, like tonight,
Albion gets the closest to land.
Oh, and Viscount Wardes and Louise...
Louise!
Saito?
Is something the matter?
Oh, just now, I thought I heard Saito.
So you really feel for that familiar.
I just thought that I heard his voice!
Please don't come to
a misunderstanding.
I'm just kidding.
I told you that I would
protect you, right?
Shut up!
Lord Wardes...
I... I...
I will accept your
proposal for marriage!
Why did Viscount Wardes
leave us behind?
That Fouquet...
Fouquet?
When she ran away,
she said that she was able
to stop us for long enough.
That means that Fouquet
and the Viscount...
I can't say that for sure.
But we can be sure that Louise
is in a lot of trouble right now.
Saito!
The next flight is going to be at dawn.
All we can do now is to wait.
Can it be... Fouquet?
Oh, wait, you guys... Don't desert me!
This is...
Verdande?!
To my future wife.
Now, all we have to do
is fulfill our mission.
Yes...
And, where is the location
of Prince Wales?
That's...
The Princess told me to not tell
anyone until we arrive in Albion.
I'm sorry.
No, no, it's all right. That is
one of your missions, after all.
I'm sorry.
We still have time before we arrive.
Rest up until then.
Yes...
This is the way it should be, Louise.
Lord Wardes is strong and kind.
He's not a familiar, nor a peasant.
This is the way it should be...
Here, huh...
Nobody's here.
No...
This is Miss La Vallière, on
a special mission from Tristein!
We would like to be
shown to Prince Wales.
An emissary from Tristein?
Why don't you try a better lie?
Nobody from that country
would know of this location.
I heard it from Princess Henrietta!
Henrietta?
I have no need for any of you.
Where is Prince Wales?!
That ring...
Now...
Put forth the ring.
Um...
Now...
What's this about?
This ring is the Ruby of Wind,
that has been handed down
the royal family of Albion.
And that is the Ruby of Water.
Water and wind together
create a rainbow,
a rainbow across the royal family.
You are...
I apologize, emissary. I am the
prince of Albion, Wales Tudor.
A missive from the Royal
Highness Henrietta.
Understood.
Then, take this...
Um, Prince!
What is it?
Lady Henrietta...
Did Lady Henrietta suggest
that you go into exile?
Miss Vallière...
It's stepping out of bounds
for an emissary
to try to know what was
written in a missive.
Even so!
This is not merely a war between
the royal family and the nobility.
The Reconquista?
Right. The group that pulls the strings
behind the scenes of this civil war.
The nobles are merely their puppets.
Finally, I have discovered
their existence.
Impossible...
As the prince of Albion,
I must protect this country.
Even if it costs me my life to do so.
Please tell Henrietta that.
Prince...
That is the letter in question?
Then the mission has been completed.
Yes...
Louise, I'm going to ask Prince
Wales to oversee our wedding.
The Prince?
That means we're holding the
wedding ceremony right here?
I'm sure the Prince will be
happy to oblige.
That's so sudden!
I can't!
I haven't even gone back
to Tristein yet!
No!
You are someone I...
Hold on... That hurts...
No. We, the Reconquista, need you.
Let me go!
The Reconquista!
That means... Wardes... You're...
My Louise...
You don't have to think about
anything. Just follow me.
You've got to be kidding!
There's no way I'd get married!
You cannot escape,
descendant of the Void.
Void?
Then we shall begin.
The groom, Viscount Jean
Jacques Francis de Wardes.
On the name of our founder Bremir,
will you vow to respect
and love this individual,
and take her as your wife?
I do.
The bride, the third daughter
of Duke La Vallière,
Louise Françoise Le Blanc
de La Vallière.
What? What in the world am I doing?
Will you vow to respect
and love this individual,
and take him as your husband?
A husband?
What am I saying?
What's happening to me?!
I d...
Bride?
I'm terribly sorry. It seems
that our bride is a bit nervous.
Perfectly understandable.
Then I shall ask again.
No! Someone is moving
my body against my will!
And take him as your husband?
I d...
Someone help me!
Louise!
Saito!
Impossible! The binding?!
How did you know we were here?!
It's thanks to the princess's ring!
The ring?!
Did you see that?
Verdande never forgets the scent of
a gem that she's smelled even once!
I'll take Louise back!
Guards! Capture that fellow!
Yes, sir!
That's a mistake, Prince! This man is...
Out of the way!
Lord Wardes! What are you...
Damn you... Reconquista!
Prince!
Damn you!
No!
I won't forgive you for that!
And how are you not
going to forgive me?
I told her to take your life.
That wench cut corners, didn't she?
So Fouquet was on your side after all!
Louise, come here.
Let us take the world
in our hands together.
No!
You're not the Lord Wardes
that I know!
I am myself. Time changes people.
Someday you'll understand that too.
How dare you...
How dare you play with
Louise's feelings...
Saito...
A love that cannot be?
A peasant like you, falling for
a noble girl... Such a fool.
Like I care!
I don't have the concept
of peasant or noble.
I don't have a family,
or a home to go back to.
All I have...
What is that?!
It's coming, partner!
More, more!
All I have is the fact that
I am Louise's familiar!
Damn you!
He absorbed the magic?!
Wardes!
That's right! I'm not
the one that fights!
Your heart is shaking to wield me!
How about this?!
I won't ever forgive
anyone who hurts Louise!
You lose!
Saito!
Oh, well... Two of the three
objectives have been met.
Objectives?
One was the death of Wales,
who was in hiding.
The second
was to acquire this.
When did you...
The last objective, Louise...
Was you!
If I can't take you, I have no choice!
I'll have you disappear here.
Wait!
No!
If we hang around, it'll get us too!
But the Princess's letter!
Saito!
Levitation!
Hey, are you all right?
There's no way they'd
survive that one.
Louise...
My Louise...
It's all right.
I'm with you.
As if I were under a real magic spell
A bright smile is burnt onto my heart
But each time I see you, I give you
a pointy, cold shoulder
Why do I act mean towards the one
that I think about the most?
My true feelings, the
shards of loneliness
In the deepest part of my heart,
I'm calling for you
For the day to start from zero
Oh, that stupid dog!
He goes running off with Siesta
just because we have a tiny fight!
Treasure-hunting?
The treasure is...
What is this?!
Next Episode: Zero Treasure
Next episode: Zero Treasure