Man, it's cold...
Dammit, this is needlessly lacy.
It's so hard to wash.
Damn that conceited girl!
What is this?
It's the laundry that piled up
while you were bedridden after
doing something very stupid.
All this?!
Of course.
You know...
What?
I heard from Siesta that,
while I was hurt,
you looked over me
without sleeping, Louise.
So?
Well, now that I can,
I'd like to say thanks.
Thanks? Don't you have
the wrong idea?
A master takes good care of her
familiar as a matter of course.
In the first place, a familiar
should always have
a feeling of thanks
towards his master, no?
So saying thanks again...
You really aren't aware of your
situation as a familiar at all.
Stop with the stupidity,
hurry up and go work!
A history of the couple's romance
that starts from the first kiss
You, the one who cast magic on
this destiny, suddenly appeared
The sky where two moons
never fade away
That's an impossibility, right?
This is the first time I've
felt anything like this
I'm feeling more and more
at ease with this place
Even if you trip and
become depressed
I will always hold you
tight with a squeeze
The story where we met that day
stays hot with a sweet kiss
See, you can cast magic, and
the wishes will surely come true
A history of the couple's romance
that starts from the first kiss
You, the one who cast magic on
this destiny, suddenly appeared
Feverish Temptation
I'm in the same boat
as all of those things.
I wonder when I'll be
able to get back?
How much longer are you
going to spend on laundry,
instead of escorting me to class?!
You really are useless!
Let go! Ouch!
When the laundry is hung up,
come to the classroom immediately!
Got that?!
Yeah, yeah.
Fire, Water, Earth,
and Air magic create
a different, stronger effect by
combining multiple elements.
Furthermore, the level of
we mages is determined
by how many elements
we can combine.
What are those levels?
Yes, ma'am.
Go ahead.
Two elements combined form a Line,
three elements form a Triangle,
and four elements form a Square.
Well done.
Just a bit more...
I believe most of you can only
deal with one element at a time.
Mrs. Chevreuse, I hate to say this,
but a student that can't
even use one element,
with a zero percentage rate of
magical success, is among us.
In any case, all of you
Oh, I get it.
Should aim for a higher...
I finally understood why all the
others call you Louise the Zero.
I see. A strange, but correct,
way of putting it.
Zero elements,
zero success rate of magic.
But you're still a noble!
How wonderful!
O Master, this humble familiar
has created a song.
Try singing it...
Yes, as you wish!
Lou-Lou-Louise is no-good Louise,
a sorcerer that can't cast any spells!
But it's all right!
Louise the Zero is still a girl!
Here...
Here?
Here... This familiar...
What are you saying to your master?!
Um... Did I make you angry?
Or more like, furious?
One meal taken away for
each Zero you just said!
I'm sorry, I overdid it!
I won't say it anymore.
Anything but that!
No! Absolutely not!
I will make absolutely no exceptions!
Well...
Impossible.
I haven't said anything yet.
Lunch and dinner...
It's been only two.
You still have two more meals to skip.
You're counting?
Nightgown.
And what are you going to do
if I starve to death?
Isn't it the master's responsibility
to take care of her familiar?
Huh? What about it? Hey, master?
Hey! Come on!
Gross! Don't spit on me!
Fine! I'll make an exception
just this once and forgive you!
Really?
Oh, what a kind master you are!
I won't say Zero anymore!
Even if your magic is zero,
or your breast size is zero,
no, I will never say so!
My breasts?!
What was that?!
Oh, crap!
No meals after all!
Plus no sleeping in the room tonight!
I think I'll freeze to death
before I starve to death.
So cold... So hungry...
Mr. Saito?
I'm sorry they're leftovers,
but eat as much as you want,
Our Sword!
Our Sword?
That's right. You're a peasant like us,
but you won the duel against
that snobby noble boy.
You're the pride of the
peasants, Our Sword!
When I held that sword,
my body just moved on its own,
so I have no idea what was going on.
Did you hear that?
A true master is like this,
never boasting!
This is where he's different
from all those stupid nobles!
I expected nothing less!
Nothing less!
But do they always eat stuff
this tasty? Damn...
When it comes to me,
Marteau the head chef,
anything will end up tasting exquisite!
This is magic in and of itself.
You're right! I've never had
stew this tasty before!
A good man! Saito, you
really are a good man!
I like you, Our Sword!
Please, let me kiss you!
I'll hold off from being
called that, and the kiss!
Such modesty. As expected!
As expected!
Please come again.
Every one of them is a fan
of yours, Mr. Saito.
Thanks to this, I'm now confident
that I can survive here.
Though when I got injured
the other day,
I thought that I was going to die.
Mr. Saito, you really were
in a dangerous situation,
one step shy of a coma.
Is that so?
You only revived after Miss Vallière
ordered a terribly expensive elixir.
As a noble, she sure has
money to spend.
Um, Mr. Saito?
I would like to have a long chat
with you sometime.
Is something the matter?
Uh, no... Someday later.
Yes.
Well, I think it's about time
for me to head back.
Good night.
Night!
She's such a good girl!
What?!
You're Kirche's...
If you eat something like me,
you're sure to have an upset stomach!
Is it all right? It won't be my fault!
Hey, are you listening?
This is...
Welcome.
Kirche?
Welcome to my suite, Hiragasa Ito.
Oh, was it Hira Gasaito?
If you don't mind, just call me Saito.
All right.
Saito...
I know that it's something
that shouldn't be.
But my byname is Fever.
I tend to burn like a torch.
Uh, I see.
You still don't understand?
I'm in love with you!
Love always comes so suddenly.
It's certainly sudden.
You looked so handsome
when you defeated Guiche!
Seeing it, Kirche the Fever
became Kirche the Passion...
Um...
Kirche!
Oh, my, Styx?
I came by because you didn't
show up at our promised time.
Then change that appointment
to two hours from now.
That's not the deal we had!
This is the third floor, right?
That was...
Just a friend.
Right now, the one that
I love the most is...
Kirche!
Who is that man?!
Tonight, I want you
to burn up with me...
That was another friend?
That's right.
In any case, the night is short,
and I don't want to waste
any time with you!
Kirche!
What are you doing?! You said you
didn't have any particular lover!
Manica... Ajax... Gimly!
Well then, in six hours.
That's morning already!
Flame!
Come on...
I love you, Saito!
Um, I have an errand to run.
You know, I'm just a familiar,
so I'm really busy. It's true.
Leave them be. I'm much more
than Louise the Zero.
She's right, those aren't a zero...
Oh?
Louise?
Kirche!
I'm busy right now, Vallière.
Zerbst! Whose familiar
are you trying to seduce?!
It can't be helped.
Love and fire are the destinies
of the von Zerbst family.
I only wish to burn in flames of love.
Come here.
Wait! He may be your familiar,
but he is a proper human!
It's rather unreasonable to get in
the way of someone's romance!
Right, Saito?
That's right! It's unreasonable!
I see...
But you know, when
tomorrow comes,
you'll be skewered by
at least ten noblemen.
In the end, this is dangerous,
in all sorts of ways.
I'll say it one more time. Come here.
Oh, you're going home already?
Cute!
Ouch!
It's just her usual trick!
Wake up already!
Ouch... Don't pull so hard, I hear you!
You're going to tear my ear off!
I'm not going to give up just yet.
You're just like a dog in heat!
Sorry!
What is that?
A crop I use for horseback riding.
Crop?
I was wrong...
For accidentally treating you
like a human!
Liar!
To think you were wagging your tail
at a Zerbst, of all people!
Dog!
Young Miss!
Please, find it in your heart to drop...
I was spoiling you.
If you're a stray dog, I have
to treat you like a stray dog!
Wait... First, calm down...
Seriously, stop! Please!
What! What part of
that woman is so good?!
Let go of me, fool!
Can it be that you...
Because I was doing that
kind of stuff with Kirche,
instead of sneaking into your bed...
You were jealous?
Me? You? What was that?
No, it was just a misunderstanding...
I don't care who you date,
but she alone I forbid.
Alone?
Kirche's family, the Zerbsts,
and my family, the Vallières,
have long been archrivals!
It is a disgrace to my family
if one thread,
one dog, gets taken by
a Zerbst woman! Got that?!
Yeah... Kinda...
You were dragged to Kirche's room
in the salamander's mouth?
Yeah. It was involuntary!
How pathetic. You're
a swordsman, aren't you?
Who is?
The other day was the first time
I've ever held a sword in my life.
You're kidding!
I mean, you were so adept when
you were fighting against Guiche.
I don't know...
My body moved on its own the
moment I grabbed that sword.
Sometimes familiars can yield
special powers once contracted.
For instance, a black cat familiar
can learn to speak.
I'm no cat!
And anyway, you can't be
a swordsman when you're unarmed!
You're right.
And tomorrow, the day of
the week is Void-day...
How's that?
Anyway, hurry up and go to sleep!
We're getting up early tomorrow!
What's up with all that?
Where are you going?
Where? To the hallway.
It's all right. Sleep in the room.
You'll be in trouble if Kirche
attacked you again.
What is it?
You're really sure you don't
feel something for...
Dog!
I'm telling you, it's all a joke!
Idiot! Fool!
How should I seduce Saito today?
I'm gonna fall!
Come on, hold on to me!
Where are you grabbing?!
It's flat enough to be your stomach!
Do you want to be kicked off?!
What, they're going out today?
I guess I can use the old
"happen to run into each other
while out" pattern...
Ansur Rel An...
Tabitha! We're going
out today! Get ready!
Void-day.
I know just how important
Void-day is to you!
See here... I've fallen in love.
But he has stepped out with
that blasted Vallière!
I have to figure out exactly
where those two are headed!
You understand, right?!
Oh, right, you won't move an inch
unless I explain everything.
I want to chase after the two
because they're headed somewhere,
but I can't catch up unless I get
the help of your familiar!
Please, help me!
You understand now? Thank you!
I grow fonder of your Sylpheed
each time I see it.
Which way?
Well, I was in a rush...
A horse, with two people riding it.
Don't eat them.
Walk a bit slower!
My back is in shambles, you know.
You didn't tell me that it took
three hours on horseback.
I think it was right next
to Viemont's elixir shop...
Oh, here it is!
Swords?
Lately, it's the fad among
even the royalty
to equip their servants with weapons.
You wielded a much bigger
sword the other day.
Was that so?
I want one that's longer and thicker.
Pardon me for saying so,
but I believe this is the right size
for this individual.
I said, I want one that's
longer and thicker!
Sure.
An ignorant noble...
She's just asking for it!
Are you buying me a sword?
It's dangerous if Kirche is after you.
You have to have a way
to defend yourself.
How unusual for someone so stingy!
Who are you calling stingy?
If I spoil my familiar, he'll get
accustomed to it, no?
But I always provide
that which is necessary.
Sorry to make you wait.
Amazing!
This is the best item
we have in our store.
It was forged by the
famous alchemist mage,
Lord Schvert of Germania!
It slices steel ever so easily!
How much?
Three thousand, if you're
using new gold coins.
You can buy a nice house and garden
with a forest for that much!
A good sword is
comparable to a castle.
It's a good deal if one estate will do.
I only have a hundred
new gold on me.
What, you can't buy it?
Well, a decent claymore costs
about two hundred on average.
Isn't there something that I can buy
with one hundred gold?
One hundred? Well,
I do have something...
Isn't this junk?
Well, it's a bit old.
Don't worry, plenty of use in it
if you tidy it up.
I'll take it.
Thank you!
Something from the clearance bin?
I've had some expenses lately,
so I came up short!
Miss Vallière ordered
a terribly expensive elixir.
It's an entire millennium too early
for you to talk back
about something your master
has given you.
Got that?!
Yes, I understand.
That wench came here to woo
Saito by buying him a present!
How conceited! She's nothing
more than Louise the Zero!
Amazing... It's so shiny!
Do you like it?
What's the meaning of this, Zerbst?!
I just happened to find
a sword befitting Saito,
so I'm giving it to him as a present.
So you followed us?
How pathetic. You can't even
buy him this cheap sword.
It's hot in here. Maybe I
should take my shirt off.
Is that all right with you?
I had mistaken the price.
It was twenty-five hundred...
Isn't that a bit expensive?
Is that so? Then, two thousand.
Five hundred.
It's five hundred, right?
Yeah... Five hundred it is.
I'll buy it!
Oh, rats!
I heard this sword was
a masterpiece from Germania.
The best swords and women
come from Germania.
There's no way a Tristein woman
like you can be a match.
Hmph!
I'm sure you just flirted with
too many men in Germania,
so that nobody bothered
to deal with you,
and that's why you came to study
abroad in a neighboring country!
Wasn't that a mouthful?
It's the truth.
What is it?
Indoors.
Then let's have Saito decide.
Me?
That's right. We're fighting
over your sword.
Well, if you asked me which,
it's obviously...
But...
I don't think this is a simple
problem about swords.
Which is it?!
I can't say both, can I?
Ouch!
This is as good a chance as any,
so I'll tell you right now.
I really hate you.
Wow, we must get along. So do I!
A duel!
Seriously?
Come on, hold on, both of you...
Hey, shut up! Stupid women!
Stupid?
Women?
No! It wasn't me!
Sword...
You woke me up from my nice nap.
Um, this sword is speaking.
I'm surprised! Such a silly face,
and yet you're a user?
No wonder why I've woken up!
A user? What's that?
Isn't that an Intelligent Sword,
a sword with its own wisdom?
You sure bought
another strange item.
I didn't know! I'm going to return
this creepy thing right now!
What year is it right now? Or rather,
where the hell is this?
Dammit, answer me!
I'll take this one.
I'm Saito.
It's Derflingher.
Nice to meet you, brother.
Why is it that I get
all the strange ones?
As if I were under a real magic spell
A bright smile is burnt onto my heart
But each time I see you, I give you
a pointy, cold shoulder
Why do I act mean towards the one
that I think about the most?
My true feelings,
the shards of loneliness
In the deepest part of my heart,
I'm calling for you
For the day to start from zero
Saito!
What in the world are you thinking?!
A mere peasant barging
into a nobleman's home?!
I don't care if anything
happens to you anymore!
Next Episode: A Maid's Crisis
Next episode: A Maid's Crisis