That night, I became
worried about Nana
since she hadn't replied to
the email I sent her.
That worry soon turned to anxiety.
As it passed midnight,
unable to bear it,
I reached for my cell phone.
That's when it rang to indicate
that I had just received an email.
I'LL BE STAYING AT
REN'S PLACE TONIGHT.
I'LL LISTEN TO YOUR STORIES
TOMORROW, SO DON'T WORRY
AND GO TO SLEEP, HACHIKO.
Blinking eyes call the wind
A smile clears all the noise away
The angel in your eyes whispers
"Everything begins now"
Can you feel it now
It's like being caught in a wave
Pulling on my heart
Breath held, arms reaching out
Baby this world is
different from yesterday's
You're the only one I can see
Baby my wish on a wing
This sky is torn
By a single overflowing word
You know,
I'm actually only half Japanese.
My dad is American.
He got sick and died
when I was six.
But when Japanese people hear
that I'm half American,
they're quick to conclude
I'm pretty because of that,
and that's why I have
a good voice.
So our talent agency advised us
to keep it a secret,
so people would think
I'm super talented
in spite of me being Japanese
just like everyone else.
I don't care either way,
as long as I can sing.
The people around me can be pests
in other ways, too.
Like, they tell me not to do
or say anything that'll hurt my image.
Hurt my image or not,
this is who I am.
Being human can be so tiring.
The next day, it started raining hard
early in the morning.
As a result, people were scarce
at the supermarket where I worked.
The smell of the dumplings
that wouldn't sell,
lingered on my hair and clothes,
making work totally unbearable.
So you failed to go through with it.
Shut up!
But even Hachi must have figured out
your feelings for her, Nobu.
She could be at a loss right now
since you only partially confessed
your feelings to her.
What am I doing,
causing her problems?
These aren't any good.
Do you have a light?
I don't. Say, where did you forget
that huge lighter you had?
How do you lose something you wear
around your neck?
What am I gonna do?
I really liked it.
It's a rare item, so it's hard
to find another one.
It's divine punishment.
You've upset the Demon Lord.
You think so?
Huh?
Hey, Yasu.
Where's Nana?
Not here yet.
So, how did it go with
the record company?
I'll tell you when Nana gets here.
Come on, you can tell us.
What are you talking about?
Oh, Shin.
I couldn't reach you on
your cell since last night.
You had me worried.
I'm glad to see you're alive.
Another woman.
Give it a rest, would you?
It's work.
Don't call it work!
Yasu!
How was it
with the record company?
Like I said,
what are you talking about?!
You've been scouted?!
Wait... Wait a minute...
Calm... Calm down...
You need to calm down, Nana!
You're the one who needs
to calm down.
Okay, now calm down,
and you shall tell me what happened
in the proper order.
"You shall"?
What happened was,
we casually distributed demo tapes
and a video of our live concert
to various record companies.
Then one of them liked
what they saw and contacted us.
Gaia Records.
That's a super famous label!
Even I know them!
Yeah, I guess.
Biggest in the music industry.
Will you be able to debut?
No, not yet.
We're not quite there yet.
Aww...
You know, Yasu met with
a guy from Gaia today.
He apparently wants to come
to our next concert.
If we do well,
he'll seriously consider signing us.
I see. Then I'm sure
things'll go well.
The live performance of BLAST
is outta this world, after all.
Right? We've practically
won this battle.
It'll be a breeze!
A breeze?
You're beaming with confidence.
When's your next live concert?
The end of the month, isn't it?
The 28th.
We'd better let Misato know.
We were all pumped up
at our practice today.
Nobu's guitar strings kept snapping.
I promise you, one day,
I'll be better than him.
Takumi.
You should've come after work today.
You know... Nana...
Yesterday... Er...
The day before yesterday? Huh?
Anyway, the day of
Trapnest's final concert.
Takumi came here late that night.
Yeah, I know.
Actually, I saw you all lovey-dovey.
I called out to you,
but you didn't even notice me.
I knew it. I'm sorry.
Wh-What about?
That time, I wasn't thinking clearly.
I'll bet you were surprised.
I hadn't told you anything
prior to that.
Yeah, I was surprised,
but there's nothing to
apologize about, is there?
Since the fact that Takumi
came to our place
meant that the party was over,
I figured you had gone out
to see Ren.
But then I started thinking that
you might've left outta courtesy to us,
and started getting concerned.
No, you're wrong.
I got an email from Ren,
so I went to see him.
I see. Thank goodness.
But Nana, you told me that
you won't have Ren stay over
because I'd feel obligated
to be hospitable.
I'll be more careful from now on, too.
No, never mind.
Actually, I'm thinking of staying
at Ren's place for a while.
Huh?
Want a drink?
Yes. Or, ah...
You're gonna stay at Ren's place?
Just for the two weeks
that Trapnest has off.
He tells me they rarely get
this much time to themselves to relax,
so I thought I'd be with him
during that time.
I see. Well, naturally.
Of course she'd wanna be with Ren.
So the same goes for you.
Don't hesitate to have Takumi
come here every day
during that period.
He's not likely to
come here every day.
Takumi told me he's busy
even during the days he's off.
But I guess that could be a lie.
No, I don't think that's a lie.
Since he's normally really busy,
it's likely that
he has a ton of non-work related stuff
to catch up on during his time off.
Ren was saying something
similar to that, too.
I'm glad.
It's gonna be all right.
He'll be here again soon.
I didn't think you'd cheer me on like this.
That's why I couldn't bring myself
to tell you anything.
I'm sorry.
Why?
I thought you'd despise me.
Despise you?
Sleeping with my favorite musician
and stuff.
That's just plain foolish,
don't you think?
Even I think it's foolish.
What are you saying?
Sure, Takumi may just happen
to be a successful musician,
but regardless of that fact,
you've fallen in love with him, right?
Regardless?
Yeah.
I wonder.
To me, Takumi is simply
Takumi from Trapnest.
I've never thought of him
as anything else.
When I think of him
as some random guy,
he does seem to be
a really horrible person.
You know...
I can't stand girls who'd casually sleep
with a guy like that
just for the thrill of doing it
with a celebrity.
But how could I despise you
after seeing you shed tears
like that in his arms?
Even Takumi must've felt
pure love for you
when he saw you cry like that
straight from your heart.
If he didn't feel love,
he would've been uncomfortable.
Like, "what mess did I get myself into
having a girl cry on me like this?"
So it's gonna be all right.
Good luck.
People close to you may worry
and say things to you regarding Takumi.
Yasu especially
has a tendency to worry.
But don't let it bother you.
Which reminds me, Nana.
About that...
About what?
About me and Takumi...
you know...
You were saying
that you saw us.
Did you tell everyone about it, Nana?
Sorry. I did tell Yasu.
Is that bad?
No, it's not about Yasu,
but rather Nobu.
I wonder if
Yasu told him anything.
No, that's not it!
Nobu and Shin heard it
from Takumi at the party.
He said that she was wagging
her tail looking all pleased.
Then Nobu lost it.
What did you just say?!
Well, but he didn't mean
any disrespect.
And the fact that he went to see
Hachi after that is so unlike him.
He usually hates getting into
such hassle over a woman.
When Shin poured his drink
over Takumi,
I was sure he'd never want anything
to do with her again,
but I guess he does
have feelings for Hachiko.
What did Takumi tell them
at the party?
It seems that he told everyone
that you two started going out.
That we're going out?
I'll bet he casually and
jokingly told everyone
that "I did it with her"
in that way he always acts.
You know him well.
But what was that about Nobu
that you brought up
a moment ago?
Did something happen with Nobu?
What happened is... last night...
Nobu suddenly showed up and
said he needed to talk to me.
He said something about
becoming better than Takumi,
or something like that...
I'm not really sure what
that was all about, but... well...
Yeah. In other words,
he came to confess his love.
You think that was what it was, too?
But it's not as if
he actually said that.
He probably couldn't.
You know, everyone's sorta caught on
to the fact that he's in love with you.
I had no idea about that!
What am I gonna do?
Oh. So that's why you didn't drop
by the studio today?
Well...
Don't worry about it.
There's nothing you can really do
about it, is there?
Since you love Takumi.
But...
So you're saying Nana's met
her soul mate?
To be honest, I love them, too.
Being a romantic guy and all.
But I'd be satisfied with
a happiness closer to home.
There's not a single thing
I'm superior in.
It's impossible.
I can't compete against him.
I can't just leave it at that.
I've gotta make things clear.
If you know that,
then don't just sit there grumbling.
Go and follow up on
what you told her.
Should Hachi never set foot
in the studio again,
it'll all be your fault.
I'm going in for the attack knowing
I'm gonna get shot down.
I feel like I'm
on a suicide mission.
A suicide mission?
Shit! If only there was one thing
I could beat him at!
Sure there is.
What?
My phone.
Aren't you gonna answer it?
I'm going out.
Work?
Don't get arrested.
You can't go on stealing
other people's clothes!
And that's my best suit!
Wait, Shin.
Answer my question!
What can I beat him at?
Love.
Hello, Shin here.
Yes. Yes, I'm sorry.
I was being careless.
Then can I go now to pick it up?
You forgot it on purpose, didn't you?
Come on in.
Reira.
Payment in advance.
The wind carried Nana's song
to my ears.
It's the same song Nobu played
on that cassette player
the day he came to Tokyo.
That song's my number one
favorite song in the world.
That girl...
Ms. Yamada-whose-age-is-a-mystery
will come yelling again.
I'm sorry about suddenly
coming over last night
and blurting out weird nonsense.
So, now that I've come to see you
like this again,
this time, I'm gonna
be direct with you.
I love you.
That's not what I had in mind
when I asked you to come in.
Then I have no reason to be here,
so I'm going home.
Don't you want your lighter?
If you want it, you can have it.
I'm sorry, Shin.
You can have it back,
so don't be mad.
It's a lie that I charge
one hundred thousand a night.
I occasionally receive
expensive gifts,
but I had never had someone hand me
100,000 yen in cash.
It's the first time you ever bought
a man, isn't it, Reira?
You fooled me at first
with your act as a naughty girl,
but I can easily tell whether or not
a girl's had a history of fooling around
once we get into bed.
You don't hafta try and be so tough.
I do feel uneasy about accepting
100,000 for that,
so if you'd like,
I will spend another night with you.
Call me whenever you feel up to it.
Good night, Reira.
Sweet dreams.
My soul is confused.
My heart is shaking.
I feel as if I made a big mistake.
I know that I'm not being fair
by saying this now.
Since I know about you
and Takumi.
I didn't want you to know.
You're in love with him,
aren't you?
I really didn't want anyone to know.
I wonder, do I really love Takumi?
Maybe I just wanna convince myself
that it was okay to sleep with him.
I don't know anymore.
I'm sorry.
You couldn't come to the studio today
even if you wanted to,
because of what I said, right?
I'm sorry, that's not it!
I was working today!
I don't mind,
so please drop by
like you've been doing.
Everyone feels a bit lonely
without your presence, Hachi.
Actually, it's me who gets sad.
Thank you.
Thank goodness.
That's good enough for me.
What should I do?
I feel so happy.
Be mine forever.
I'm many times happier now than
hearing those words from Takumi
which I can't be sure
are true or not.
What good is it to keep
this empty cigarette pack?
If this hadn't happened
between Takumi and me,
I'm sure I would've
fallen for Nobu.
I would've loved to be
Nobu's girlfriend.
But if Takumi were to come
and see me again,
I'd likely end up sleeping
with him again.
I probably won't resist it.
What in the world do I want?
If I always get carried away like this,
I'll never get my hands on anything.
When I woke up the next morning,
Nana was no longer there.
There was a note on the table.
TO HACHIKO
DON'T FORGET TO LOCK THE DOOR.
LOSE THAT HABIT OF OPENING
THE DOOR TO ANYONE WITHOUT
CONFIRMING WHO IT IS FIRST.
NANA
There was a note on the table.
TO HACHIKO
DON'T FORGET TO LOCK THE DOOR.
LOSE THAT HABIT OF OPENING
THE DOOR TO ANYONE WITHOUT
CONFIRMING WHO IT IS FIRST.
NANA
It's not something I should
be feeling lonely about.
I can see her whenever I want
at the studio.
Besides, it's only for two weeks.
After those two weeks...
she will return here, won't she?
Hey Nana...
Even now, not a day passes
without me wishing to see you
on the other side of that table.
I'd call out your name from my heart.
Many times.
As many times as it takes.
I reached into the sky
But I couldn't reach what I wanted
They grew smaller
and disappeared into the sky
Like colorful balloons
I'm alone
My hand had no place to go
And gently you took it
Starless night
I won't look back
at the shadow of my past
I want to feel your warmth
Tears are falling down
Even if I'm unsure I won't let go
Of your hand holding mine