"Inspection"
Hurry up, stupid!
I don't care about crime
prevention or whatever!
That has nothing to do with us!
Idiot! Stop shaking.
Wait!
Run!
Hey! Wait!
Don't look back!
Number 95, Kuno, I presume.
What is this?
The Blue Sekirei!
What did you say?
Warning. If you go farther,
what waits for you is...
Haruka-sama, let's go back.
Idiot! What are you saying?
We've already come this far!
No! This person is bad!
Hey!
Please, I beg you! Even you'll get killed!
Over there!
Damn!
They're running away over there!
Chase them! Chase them!
They're running away.
Number 104, Haihane...
I didn't expect the Discipline Squad
to be out in public like this...
Damn Minaka! He's serious.
Ima inochi ga hora kizashite chitte yuku
Nigirishimeta unmei
Mou mayou koto wa nai
Musubiau kizuna
Akatsuki matsu sora ni
Aishi kimi dakishimete
Orenai inori wo
Mada dare mo yoru no naka
Ima wa tada
Kokoro no oku ni sawatte
Afureru atsusa subete sasagetai
Yume miru ashita e
Hirogeru tsubasa wa
Ano hi no kimi ga kureta
Omoi wa kizamareta
Chikai no kotoba ga
Kiseki wo okosu yo
Takanaru mune habatake
Tobitateru negai haruka tataku
Feather 8:
"The Closed Capital"
Ku-chan, here it comes!
What art thou doing?!
Landlady's orders! Clean well!
Musubi-chan's wearing swimwear...
I've never seen that before.
Minato...
What art thou staring at?
No! I was... ah...
If thou wishest to see
breasts so much, then...
Thou canst just see mine.
Mine, too!
Um... Ku-chan...
that is... what should I say...
Per-ver-t?
No! You've got it all wrong!
Everybody, we'll eat soon.
Yes!
Is this...
Matsu-san, meal time.
Yes, I'm coming.
What are you looking at?
MBI's ultra top secret data bank.
Ultra top secret...
The security was extremely tight,
but there are a lot of
interesting things to be seen here.
Information on which Sekireis have emerged,
each Ashikabi's detailed personal info...
Plus each Sekirei's win record,
and the losers too...
That means the Sekireis
whose functions have stopped.
To tell you the truth,
something's bothering me...
Bothering you?
"Winner Unidentified"
"Winner unidentified"?
Even among the Sekireis
who oppose each other,
there's what you could
call an unspoken rule.
The conqueror who erased
the opponent's Sekirei Symbol
stays with the loser and guards
her until MBI comes to retrieve her.
It's the minimal courtesy
we show each other in battle.
But whoever defeated this Sekirei
abandoned her lying
at death's door, and left.
I've confirmed another two
Sekireis defeated in the same manner.
Are you saying that they were
defeated by the same Sekirei?
Likely so.
I can't understand this action at all.
Isn't she just a rude one?
There's another and more important
reason the winner stays along with the loser.
That is to let MBI confirm who the winner is.
But leaving without doing so means...
...losing the reason for
the battles among Sekireis.
This feels quite suspicious, somehow...
Uzume-san, food is served.
Uzume-san!
Uzume-san?
She isn't here.
"Hiyama-kai Hospital"
Chiho...
Thank you, Sahashi-san.
You really helped me.
It's nothing.
Big brother!
What's that, Ku-chan?
Are you a mouse?
You were a wagtail the other day, weren't you?
Did Uzume-san give that to you, too?
Oh my! What a cute mouse!
Those maid uniforms and these...
Why does she own such costumes?
Come to think of it,
I don't know much about Uzume-san.
Are you curious?
Jeez, Sahashi-san.
Boys are all like that.
No! It's nothing romantic
or anything like that!
More like, you're teasing me, aren't you?!
I don't know about the details either,
but I've heard all these
are for only one person.
Only... one?
Listen, listen, Miya!
This was a big hit today!
She was so cute when she smiled!
All she wanted was to see her smile...
I heard that person's been
in a hospital for a long time.
And Uzume-san can
see her only occasionally.
Is that person... her Ashikabi?
I don't know.
But I know how strong
the bond between them is.
The bond...
Well, I'd better start preparing for dinner.
It's about the time the shoppers are back.
I'm back.
I lost... this is the third consecutive loss...
W-Welcome back.
For now, the bond between Sekireis
is the problem more than anything.
I won!
Damn! If this were a battle
of skills, I'd never lose to thee!
But a loss is a loss.
Um... I...
What?!
Um... I have something
to talk to all of you about.
I have to head back soon.
I'm sorry...
Uzume-chan?
Oops, did I wake you up?
Don't do anything strange.
When did you get here?
Just a little while ago.
Uzume-chan, were you crying?
Of course not! See?
I'm sorry...
I'm your Ashikabi,
but I can't do anything for you...
I'm sorry.
It is fine as long as you are alive.
It's just fine...
"Keep Out"
"Secret Meeting in Progress"
So, as you now know, some
dangerous Sekireis are out there...
He's right.
Safe is better than sorry,
so try not to be conspicuous
as much as possible, and...
And so...
Ah... are you listening?
Despicable! How dare they
defile the sacred Sekirei battle!
That person must be strong!
I definitely want to fight her!
I said it's dangerous...
No, Ku-chan!
Don't you get fired up too!
The master who can't even control his pawns.
It's not a laughing matter, is it?!
I'm worried you guys
might get hurt or something!
Well, I think you don't need to worry.
If things get bad, we can just run away.
Matsu-san, you're so irresponsible...
How could you say that?!
As a strategist, I'm...
Did talking to those two
have the opposite effect?
I know how strong the bond is...
The bond, huh?
W-What is it?!
Tsukiumi?
Um... well...
Art thou worrying about me?
I'm asking if thou art worried about me?!
I'm worrying! I'm worrying!
I see...
It's not bad to be worried about by thee...
Huh?
I've never noticed Tsukiumi is...
this beautiful...
W-What art thou staring at?
I'm sorry!
In any case...
There's no need to worry.
I am the strongest.
I see.
This feeling is the same as I felt before.
Right!
It's the sense of reassurance
I felt from Musubi-chan.
What art thou laughing at?!
Can't you at least say I'm smiling, please?
At any rate, thou shan't need to worry.
Even though they are so different...
Is this because she's also my Sekirei?
Ah, Minato-san.
M-Musubi-chan?!
Yes?
How long have you been there?
I just got here.
Dinner is ready, so I came to get you.
Ah... I see...
I didn't do anything to hide...
No, I didn't...
A soap opera, soap opera...
The hairs just stood up
on the back of my neck...
Dark... something
vicious and dark was just there...
Is it about time for dinner?
Oh, Uzume-tan, when did you get back?
Just a while ago.
You've been out often recently.
My jobs keep me busy.
I'm so hungry!
What's for dinner today?
Blood?
Got it?
We shall be busy starting tomorrow.
Yes! Let's do our best!
Would you mind if I come in?
Uzume-san! Of course not!
Oops! Did I get this when I changed?
Uzume-san, I'll wash your back.
Ah, oh... yup.
Thou dost not get it at all.
The real wife is me!
The rest of ye are mistresses!
I'm his real wife, too!
It's a matter of order!
Listen.
There were once Shogunate harems,
and only the top woman was the
real wife in that inner palace, and...
Minato-san doesn't have
his hair tied up in a topknot!
I'm not talking about
Japanese samurai shows!
You guys are so funny.
I wish we could be like this forever...
Acting silly here, getting scolded by Miya...
Why art thou saying such soft things?
Thou hast thy own Ashikabi.
So thou might have to fight us someday.
That's right! We've gotta fight someday.
Uzume-san?
Number 04? The one who killed
Mitsuha was the Black Sekirei?
Yes, there's no mistake.
I confirmed.
The Discipline Squad...
Why did they mess with my possession?
Members of the Discipline Squad
are also participants in this game.
They don't need any excuses.
Mutsu, what is the
Sekirei with that woman doing?
You mean number 107?
Akitsu is keeping an eye on him.
He doesn't seem to have emerged yet.
We have to make up for
what we've lost, don't we?
Meal's ready.
Ah, yes!
Here!
Ah, by the way!
Shiina, you said you're
looking for somebody, didn't you?
Yes.
If you don't mind,
would you tell me about that?
Your younger sister?
Her name is Ku.
I've been looking for her for a long time,
and when I went to town,
that person with whips chased me.
That's when I passed by, huh?
OK! Let's look for her! I'll help you out.
See, I have an older brother, too.
An older brother?
Yup! When I was little, he always
came to get me whenever I was crying.
When I couldn't get down from a tall tree
or when I got lost in a dark forest...
Yukari! There you are!
Here! Come on!
Even though he was afraid of
tall trees and dark places, too.
He always gave me a
piggyback ride when we went home.
I still remember his warm back.
But he's now a wimpy loser, though.
So I'm sure that Ku-chan is waiting
for her big brother just as I did... definitely.
I hope Ku's met somebody like that.
Just like I met you.
Yup! I hope so, too.
OK, we'll go out to search
for Ku-chan starting tomorrow!
Yes!
"Hiyama-kai Hospital"
Thank you for your hard work.
I heard you killed almost
instantly again the other day.
I suppose that's what we should expect
from the Sekirei who received
Takehito Asama's personal attention.
Mr. Higa thinks highly of you.
Cut the crap. What's the next target?
Number 95, Kuno.
This Sekirei's power is bit special...
Doesn't matter.
Please keep in mind
that your Ashikabi
doesn't have much time left.
I know.
Let's go!
Yes!
A-Are you really going out to
exterminate that dangerous Sekirei?
Of course we are! I, Tsukiumi, will not
forgive the bastard who defiles our battle!
This case doesn't
seem to need the Guardian.
But before that...
Water Celebration!
Thou hast passed.
I'll leave my back for thee to protect!
What? What was that?
A secret between a woman and a woman.
Yes!
- Minato-san, we will go now!
- Minato, we shall go now!
Ah, yes.
Kuno, hurry!
Please wait, Haruka-sama!
Idiot! You're so incompetent.
Stop falling like a fool.
My name's "Kuno," not "Idiot"!
Here! Hurry up!
Haruka-sama...
Rats! She caught up!
Ashikabi, step aside.
I don't want to hurt humans.
How can I leave my girl
and run away, you dumb shit?!
Then I'll send you to
the grave together at least.
Kuno!
What?
Let's go there, Tsukiumi-san!
Did you see Kuno's deadly skill,
the "Screaming Sob"?
Haruka-sama, that name is so lame...
Oh crap! It didn't work!
Number 09, Tsukiumi!
Fight me fair and square!
Number 88, Musubi!
Pleased to meet you!
Why are these two?
Who are these guys?
Thou! Stop hiding thy face with clothes,
and declare thy number and name!
Unable to identify thyself?
Suspicious, indeed.
A strong opponent!
We hear that recently a reprehensible
Sekirei has been haunting the capital
who fights without identifying herself and
abandons her opponent even if she is dying.
It is thee, is it not?
Not yet... I don't want to fight them yet!
If thou canst not identify thyself,
I will strip those veils!
I don't know what's going on,
but let's use this chance and run!
I-I can't stand up.
What is this woman?
She stinks like alcohol...
I don't like this...
Yo, baby girls! Get ready now!
This is renai no shinansho
Don't let it go, aserazu so
Without furaingu de show time
Get the funky beat!
Hayai mono gachi?
Kono bayai wa kankei nai nai
Nozomu tokoro yo
Soudatsusen boppatsu
Onna desu mono, maketerareya shinai nai
Fukuramu kimochi
No mou daibouhatsu
Dame yo, yuuwaku shicha
Doite, kare no osoba
Watashi dokidoki natte ippai ippai
Naisho, nukekake shite
Daiseikou, kare to futari
Amaku mekurumeku night
Honto wa ne, watashi dake wo
Dakishimete hoshii no
Hitorijime mura mura
Furagu tatechau no ari kashira?
Yappari ne, yowaki, dou shiyou
Yasashisugite shou ga nai
Sonna toko daisuki yo
Dakara watashitachi tsukushimasu
Dear Sweet Heart!
Finally, I believe I'll
have a decent introduction.
You are Number 03, Kazehana-tan
with the overabundant pheromones!
With my sexiness,
I'll slay the cherry boys in front of the TV!
But you have a faint scent of the Showa era.
Feather 9:
"The Veil and the Wind"
But you have a faint scent of the Showa era.
Feather 9:
"The Veil and the Wind"
Episode 9: "The Veil and the Wind."
Feather 9:
"The Veil and the Wind"
Please favor us again next time!
Feather 9:
"The Veil and the Wind"