First, I'd like to say, thank you!
Well that was sudden.
Me too! Thank you!
To everyone who's watching this...
It's all thanks to the warm breeze
of love that you've sent us!
Thank you!
We're really grateful.
It's a wonderful miracle, isn't it?
No kinda-sappy lines allowed!
Huh?
"Dear Ai, yesterday's rain has finally let up,
and the weather is very pleasant today."
"But Alicia will be out all day,
so the shop is closed."
"Not only that, but Aika has work
and Alice is at school."
"So, President Aria and I are going out, too!"
Do you remember that day
Oboeteimasuka ano hi o
When your heart suddenly began to race
Futo kanjita tokimeki o
The rays from the blue sky were pouring over you...
Aoi hizashi abite
...as you cut through the wind
Kaze o kiru kimi ni
I couldn't look away, and when our eyes met
Mitoreru to me ga atte
I couldn't help but smile
Egao koboreta
It's just like a spiral
Marude supiraare
I want to spend my days waving to you
Itsumademo te o furitai hibi
This is my proof that I was here with you
Koko ni tashika ni kimi to ita akashi
An eternal spiral
Zutto supiraare
There's a path which stretches on ahead
Kono saki mo tsuzuiteru michi ga aru
When you climb the next hill,
Tsugi no saka o nobottara
Let's meet again
Mata aimashou
That Little Secret Place...
This is a completely residential area, so there's
usually no reason to come here when giving tours.
But it's definitely another face of Neo-Venezia.
The scenery here never seems to change.
The rain finally let up yesterday,
so I think we have a good chance.
Ready, President Aria?
Ready, set!
Ta-daa!
It's full of laundry, just like we thought!
There's even more over here!
The laundry is blissfully swimming in the sky.
Hey!
You dirtied your clothes already?
But... there was a puddle!
And I just finished doing the laundry, too.
Honestly...
But that Sylph guy said it's good
for me to have so much energy!
Honestly...
But that Sylph guy said it's good
for me to have so much energy!
You have too much energy! For goodness' sake...
Huh?
We can see the Campanile from here too,
can't we, President Aria?
President Aria?
President Aria...
Here you go.
This scenery hasn't changed either,
from the time I first came to this city.
We're getting a little hungry, aren't we?
Well then, shall we go have lunch?
Ah, I know!
Why don't we go eat that?
You know, that exciting, heart-pounding dish
we had the other day at a restaurant near here.
Let's go, shall we?
Well then, off we go!
So, two orders then?
Yes.
Certainly. Please wait just a moment.
Exciting, exciting.
Thank you for waiting.
Well? Isn't it neat?
I've always loved getting this restaurant's polenta
served up like a volcano, ever since I was a kid.
I can really sense the history behind it.
Time to eat.
Let's order that the next time we come here.
Thank you for waiting.
It's here!
Here's your chitarra.
Exciting, exciting.
All right, go ahead.
Okay!
It's so much fun!
Yes, yes.
Go ahead.
It looks delicious, doesn't it?
That was delicious, wasn't it?
President Aria...
President Aria!
We're so stuffed, aren't we, President Aria?
Ah, I'm starving. Maybe I'll get some pizza...
Huh?
Isn't that Sideburns?
Just as I was hoping I'd run into
Alicia on my day off, too.
Geez, she just doesn't get it, does she?
Oh well, maybe I'll go yank on her
sideburns as a greeting anyway.
Why don't we try going this way?
Huh? She's gone.
Which way did she go?
Where is she?
Where is she, where is she?
Where is she, where is she, where is she?
Where is she, where is she, where is she,
where is she, where is she, where is she?!
I guess I lost her.
Ma'am, give me a slice of tomato pizza.
Sure.
Thank you for your business.
There she is!
They have some new outfits, President Aria!
What is she doing?
Akatsukin!
Huh?
Are you off today?
Yeah.
Are you going to our
middle school reunion, Akatsukin?
Yeah.
Then I'll send the RSVPs for both of us.
That pizza sure looks good.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Thanks!
She went inside.
See ya.
Yeah.
Huh? My pizza...
Where'd it go?
It looks great on you.
I'm happy for you, President Aria.
Caffè Florian's restoration
has begun, President Aria.
I'm sure it'll be more radiant
than ever when it's reborn.
I lost her again.
Stupid fast girl!
She's elusive, that's for sure.
Huh? It won't open.
This entrance is off limits to the public.
Please use the elevator like everyone else.
What? But I-
It can't be helped!
Thank you so much.
Not at all. Come again anytime.
Ah, and please send Alicia my regards.
I will!
This is taking forever!
What?!
How in the world did she...
You're not getting away this time!
Prepare yourself to be caught!
Huh? Pony-boy?
I wonder what he's doing.
He's really acting sneaky, isn't he?
Junior.
I wonder where he's headed?
Who knows.
Want to go see?
Yes!
We haven't been here for a while, have we?
It's a tourist attraction,
so there are lots of people nearby.
But strangely, no one ever notices this spot.
Not Aika, not Alice...
I bet not even Alicia knows about it.
It's my very own place.
If I stay here like this, no one can find me.
President Aria, the city of Neo-Venezia
is changing little by little, isn't it?
It's not here!
I can't find the stairway anywhere!
Where is it?!
Just how did she get up there?
Could that be it?
Is it all right to enter without permission?
Eh, whatever.
Oh, wow!
You can see the entire inside stretch
of the basilica from here.
Horse butts...
She's sleeping...
BIG-DOUBLE-SIDEBURN-YANK!!
That'll teach you, Sideburns!
Akatsuki, an ambush isn't fair.
I've finally caught you.
Caught me?
Come to think of it, why did I have to
follow Sideburns in the first place?
No, I absolutely was not following you!
At any rate, I'm amazed you
managed to find your way up here.
The stairs leading up here are inconspicuous,
so most people don't even notice them.
Hah, it was a piece a cake.
So, what brings you to this place?
The truth is, there's someone here
that I'm interested in.
So every once in a while,
I secretly come here to see him.
You see this person in secret?
Yes.
Just the two of you?
Ah, but President Aria is with us, too.
He always gazes out to sea from here, all alone.
Sideburns, just who is this guy?
Huh?
I'm asking you who he is!
It's this person right here.
But anyway, come here Akatsuki, come here.
Huh? What is it?
If you crouch here, you can see
the world from his point of view.
See?
A white seabird with a tilted neck...
Kubi o kashigeta shiroi umidori
...flew away into the endless sky
Tondetta no anna ni takai sora
Soon, a ship sailing beyond the sky...
Sora no mukou no fune ga mousugu
Surrounded by this scenery that never changes,
happy things, new things, even sad things...
...will arrive in the afternoon harbor
Tadoritsuku gogo no minato
Surrounded by this scenery that never changes,
happy things, new things, even sad things...
...will arrive in the afternoon harbor
Tadoritsuku gogo no minato
...all pile up every day, and slowly
they bring about change, don't they?
Lively people gathered among colorful glass
Nigiwau hito iro toridori no garasuzaiku
It's just like how the shapes of the clouds and
the color of the sea are always quietly changing.
Lively people gathered among colorful glass
Nigiwau hito iro toridori no garasuzaiku
The person I long to see has gone to a far-off land...
Aitai hito tooi kuni e itta
For hundreds of years,
a time so unfathomably long,
The person I long to see has gone to a far-off land...
Aitai hito tooi kuni e itta
he has been watching over this piazza,
unbeknownst to everyone.
...to a town I have yet to discover
Ima wa shiranai machi ni iru no
he has been watching over this piazza,
unbeknownst to everyone.
...to a town I have yet to discover
Ima wa shiranai machi ni iru no
It's ever so wonderful...
...to a town I have yet to discover
Ima wa shiranai machi ni iru no
...but it's also a little sad, isn't it?
...to a town I have yet to discover
Ima wa shiranai machi ni iru no
That's why...
...I made this my very own secret place.
Until the bells ring, I shall wait here
Kane ga naru made koko de machimashou
Aprecious treasure that was left behind
Oiteitta no daiji na takaramono
I dream of a birdcage that lost its key
Kagi o nakushita torikago no yume
Surely, you'll come searching for it
Kitto sagashi ni kitekureru yo
Voices fly about as a shower of flower petals dance
Tobikau koe afuredasu hanabira ga mau yo
I won't tell anyone.
Voices fly about as a shower of flower petals dance
Tobikau koe afuredasu hanabira ga mau yo
Let's make this our secret base.
I long to hear your voice, since the window I painted...
Kikitai koe enogu de kaita mado
Let's make this our secret base.
I long to hear your voice, since the window I painted...
Kikitai koe enogu de kaita mado
Yours and mine.
I long to hear your voice, since the window I painted...
Kikitai koe enogu de kaita mado
...was washed away by the passing rain
Toori ame ni nagasareta
And President Aria's, and that guy's, too!
...was washed away by the passing rain
Toori ame ni nagasareta
Okay!
Now now, don't mind us. Go on, go on.
Uh...
Sorry to interrupt.
We were really just passing by.
Hold it right there!
Oh
Ho
Hold it right there!
Oh
Ho
Stop getting the wrong idea, Gachapen!
You better not tell Alicia anything! Understand?!
This was supposed to be my secret place...
I see...
It just became everyone's
special place, starting today.
The person I long to see...
Aitai hito
"In this city that never changes,
little by little, things begin to change."
The voice I long to hear...
Kikitai koe
"I'm sure that I will, too."
The voice I long to hear...
Kikitai koe
"Akari, the next time we meet, both you
and Neo-Venezia will have changed a little bit."
Lively people gathered among colorful glass
Nigiwau hito iro toridori no garasuzaiku
"Akari, the next time we meet, both you
and Neo-Venezia will have changed a little bit."
Lively people gathered among colorful glass
Nigiwau hito iro toridori no garasuzaiku
"Wait..."
Lively people gathered among colorful glass
Nigiwau hito iro toridori no garasuzaiku
"Does that mean I will have
changed a little bit, too?"
The person I long to see has gone to a far-off land...
Aitai hito tooi kuni e itta
"Does that mean I will have
changed a little bit, too?"
The person I long to see has gone to a far-off land...
Aitai hito tooi kuni e itta
...to a town I have yet to discover
Ima wa shiranai machi ni iru no
I'm back!
My, my. Welcome back!
Next Episode
This is really a mystery!
Junior, you look so serious.
Next Episode
What kind of mystery is it?
It's the mystery of "My, my. Giggle!"
Next Episode
That Wonderful Extracurricular Lesson...
Next time, "That Wonderful
Extracurricular Lesson..."
Next Episode
That Wonderful Extracurricular Lesson...
Now, please take my hand.