Ima inochi ga hora kizashite chitte yuku
Nigirishimeta unmei
Mou mayou koto wa nai
Musubiau kizuna
Akatsuki matsu sora ni
Aishi kimi dakishimete
Orenai inori wo
Mada dare mo yoru no naka
Ima wa tada
Kokoro no oku ni sawatte
Afureru atsusa subete sasagetai
Yume miru ashita e
Hirogeru tsubasa wa
Ano hi no kimi ga kureta
Omoi wa kizamareta
Chikai no kotoba ga
Kiseki wo okosu yo
Takanaru mune habatake
Tobitateru negai haruka tataku
The Final Feather:
"The Sekirei of Fate"
Musubi-chan! Musubi-chan! Musubi-chan!
Musubi-chan...
Musubi-chan, wake-up.
Wake-up, Musubi-chan! Musubi-chan!
The last remaining Sekirei can stay
with its most beloved person forever.
Until that day, I will never lose.
Musubi-chan...
Uh, hey...
You'd better just give up already.
The Sekirei Symbol's gone, you know?
Sahashi!
Is this the time to be
worrying about others?
Run, Kuno!
Haruka-sama!
The Sekirei Plan?
You can't just say something like
that out of the blue and expect me to...
A girl is crying and asking a favor,
so if I refuse,
that'll make me less of a man...
All right.
I'll become your Ashikabi.
Haruka-sama! Haruka-sama!
Haruka-sama...
Shit!
I'll use my incantation.
Haruka-sama, I love you.
Song of my pact,
illuminate my Ashikabi's path!
What... is this voice?
I'm losing my strength...
A song?
What a beautiful voice...
But this... really saps my strength...
Now you see it! This is Kuno's final weapon:
The Song of Mellow-Mellow!
Please don't give it a wacky title, Haruka-sama!
Ah... this comfortable
feeling of powerlessness...
I don't care about discipline or whatever...
Don't fall asleep!
Hey, Haihane!
Damn! I can't keep my strength.
What's with this song?
Crap!
Kuno! Hey, Kuno!
Haruka-sama... I was useful...
No, you're incompetent after all.
But you are the best incompetent for me.
Haruka-sama, that's not even real Japanese.
You're so stupid!
Now there's no point to what you did.
That's not true.
She... tried to protect him with all her might.
Do you understand the present situation?
A mere monkey like you...
...couldn't defy us in a million years!
Ye Sekireis who are like MBI's wild dogs...
Ye shall be the ones punished!
Tsukiumi... you came here for us!
Is she one of them?
Musubi!
Musubi-chan's Sekirei Symbol is...
Musubi, our shopping race...
I shan't forgive thee winning and leaving...
Rise! Rise now, Musubi!
Who the hell are you? You're annoying,
popping up out of nowhere like that.
How darest thee...
How darest thee do this to my friend!
Number 09, Tsukiumi! Here I come!
Crap! She's a single number!
Water Arrows!
Blue!
Bitch!
Tsukiumi!
You don't think you
can defeat two of us, do you?
Next time I'll hurt more than your clothes.
Thou art a claw user, huh?
The soul sword given to me
by the Landlady... my Water Blade...
I shall not hesitate to use it!
The Discipline Squad is out there...
the situation is dire for them.
I'm going.
It's even better
to watch in the arena, isn't it?
See ya!
Minato Sahashi...
Forgive me, Musubi.
If only I hadn't lost out
to my worthless pride...
Forgive me!
Gotcha!
What's... this?
That Ashikabi... he even
scored a high-level Sekirei like this?
In the end, I can't do anything...
All I did was mix up everyone in a battle...
Sahashi!
You seem like you'll be an obstacle
for Natsuo someday if I leave you alive.
Minato!
Your opponent is... me!
Get away from Minato!
Tsukiumi!
I shall... never let thee touch Minato!
This is it, number 09.
Bad news!
Big Sis?!
Not yet.
But at this rate, everyone will!
I haven't been shown, yet.
What's this?
No doubt about it.
The only one who can do this is Ku.
Soon I won't be able to stop the satellites...
Let's contact Mina-tan.
What?
I feel it.
Mina-tan...
Reunite with her in the underworld.
No.
Huh?
No!
Something's going wrong
with Mina-tan and the others!
Kusano-tan, anything wrong?
No...
We'll hurry to the railway bridge.
Ku!
Who are you?!
Hey, what are you touching, bastard!
You're reacting so passionately,
and yet you leave him un-emerged?
Huh?
The one who chased Shiina before...
Why don't you be mine?
What's this?
This can't be happening!
A-A monkey... hit me...
Benitsubasa, you're so lame.
Bastard!
Sahashi, you idiot, run!
Minato, what art thou doing?!
I won't run away.
Musubi-chan, Tsukiumi...
I can't run away and leave
people who are precious to me behind!
Minato...
Oh, yeah?
Then die now!
Sahashi!
Minato!
It's love.
Musubi-chan?
Just now... I heard a voice!
A voice?
Mutsu!
I'm sorry but... you've gotta go.
Watch out!
Yukari-san.
Shiina?
I love you.
Me, too...
You know, this is my first kiss...
Hey, Mutsu! He's emerging!
Corpse of my pact, decay my Ashikabi's cross!
It's coming!
The World's End Garden!
What a terrible day!
Akitsu!
Wh-What... is this?
Love...
Please teach love to the little birds.
That is your...
Wait...
W-Why?
She stood up...
Mu-Musubi-chan?
It's love!
If you stand in the way of love,
I, number 08, Sekirei of Fate,
Yume will be your opponent!
Who?
You been hit too much and gone mad?
Silence!
Since when have the
Discipline Squad sunk to bullying the weak?
As your senior, I must discipline you!
You're pissing me off!
You don't make any sense!
Haihane!
What the?
Mu-chan!
What was that laser beam?
What? What's with this?!
Who are you?
MBI affiliate, protector of the S Plan,
Chief of the Discipline Squad,
Sekirei of Fate, number 08, Yume!
The... S Plan?
That's the old name for the Sekirei Plan.
Matsu-san!
Ku-chan, too!
Chief? The head of the
Discipline Squad is Karasuba!
You don't seem to have enough love yet.
You still have lots to learn as
members of the Discipline Squad!
Try again!
She threw them?!
She effortlessly threw away the
opponents that gave us such a hard time...
That was over so fast...
Ah... there is plenty of love here...
The strong, selfless care for each other...
The warm care for friends and masters...
And...
Your feelings for Musubi...
that very warm heart...
That heart of yours woke me up.
How dare thee take
advantage of this confusion!
Get away, Minato! I said, get away!
It's pouring into me... your very kind heart...
Musubi tied the knot with a good person.
How shameless! That's enough!
Tsukiumi-tan! Down, girl! Down!
That is...
The Black... Sekirei!
You appeared, as I thought you would.
You look fine, Karasuba.
I'm really... really glad
to be able to see you again.
Yume!
Karasuba, I am not the one you should fight.
The one who will stand
in your way someday is...
Definitely...
Huh? Karasuba-sama?
Um... all I remember is I was downed by the
people from the Discipline Squad and then...
If you've been downed by
Benitsubasa, you still need to train more.
Everybody is really strong!
Musubi-chan... Is that you, Musubi-chan?
Minato-san!
Musubi-chan!
Mi-Minato-san?
The Black Sekirei!
If thou tryest to stop us as well...
Isn't there something you
need to worry about more than me?
What is that sound?
The satellites have resumed operation!
Minato! Musubi! Hurry up and run away!
Yes!
Shigi-kun!
What?
Kuno-san!
C-Clothes wrapped around us...
Then, suddenly the wind blew, and we're here.
Wind?
Clothes?
Yukari-san.
We'll be together from now on.
Yes. Many years to come...
Plants grew like crazy all of the sudden...
...then died all at once?
Sahashi, aren't you coming with us?
I... feel like I still have
something I have to do here.
Something to do?
Love...
Please teach love to the little birds.
I don't know what it is, yet.
But I think there's something only I can do.
I see.
Let's go, Kuno.
Yes!
Sahashi, do your best!
See you again!
I'll work harder, so someday...
Yes, somewhere, let's meet again!
A young couple running
toward the morning sun...
How romantic!
I guess.
It's still not enough to
forget about my old passion,
but now I've seen the
man you are, Minato-kun!
Get strong quickly, Musubi...
We saw them off safely.
Shall we go home before MBI shows up?
Kusano-tan, time to withdraw.
Everyone, I'm sorry.
I underestimated things...
I couldn't do anything. I only relied on you...
In the end, I put you all in such danger.
Minato-san.
Because of you, we can all do our very best.
As long as you are you, it's enough.
Musubi-chan...
How shall I put this... Musubi is...
...always stealing the best part of the show.
Mm-hmm!
Whoa! Wait! This isn't the place!
I'm telling you, we have to get out of here!
Hey! Are you guys listening?!
MBI officially announced that the
large-scale growth of giant vegetation
"Giant plants appeared in the capital.
Gone in one night."
And the mysterious collapse of the
rail bridge before dawn the other day
"Giant plants appeared in the capital.
Gone in one night."
Were completely unrelated...
"Giant plants appeared in the capital.
Gone in one night."
Were completely unrelated...
Shii-chan...
We're sorry! We're sorry!
We're very sorry he always does this!
It's okay, even though this
is the third consecutive day...
Taking care of a recuperating
husband is the real wife's job!
I am his real wife, too!
Hey, little brat!
An epic battle for Mina-tan!
And for now,
the curtain closes on this story...
However...
Number 88 was reactivated?
That can't happen!
This requires a detailed investigation.
I can't believe he emerged
right before my eyes!
I wonder if there are some
new Sekireis left around.
Don't be so greedy.
How many do you think you have at home?
Ouch! I will never forgive
that huge-boobed woman!
Unforgivably huge breasts...
Even in a padded bra, you're only a B cup.
So what?!
Natsuo hates big breasts anyway.
You look cheerful these days.
You can tell?
Did something good happen to you?
Well... I'm looking forward to what is coming.
It's been so noisy lately, and...
She assisted number 95's escape?
Yes, this is an obvious act
of betrayal against you, Higa-sama.
No, she still has her uses.
Too strong...
Who are you guys?!
Hey, you?
What?
Do you know where the number 108 Sekirei is?
Shit!
Both of our bodies are honest, huh?
What are you talking about?
See you later!
Must thou go to this "prep school"
even though thou art so injured?
Yeah, I've played hooky so much lately.
Have a nice day, Minato-san!
Have a nice day!
Sending a husband off is the real
wife's duty, as I've said a thousand times!
I'm his real wife, too!
- Both of ye, stay out of this!
- I'm begging you, don't fight...
When we Sekireis meet our destined partners,
we react whether we like it or not, you know?
Damn!
That's right! The story is not over.
No, the story weaved by
the little birds begins now!
Ladies and gentlemen, wait and see!