"Kusano's First Shopping Trip"
I'm home!
Ah, Landlady!
Welcome back.
Musubi-san won again today?
Yes!
This is my tenth consecutive win!
Tsukiumi-san, thank you, too.
Here! Open your mouth!
I'll pass you the fish.
I-I'm telling you, I can do it by myself...
Tension zings through the room even
in an ordinary scene of domestic bliss.
Matsu-san!
Say, Musubi-chan.
Yes?
Maybe... you can switch
with Tsukiumi sometimes...
I refuse!
Forget about Little Kusano.
That position next to Minato
rightfully belongs to me, his real wife!
Therefore, it is meaningful
to get it back by my own hands!
Isn't that a bit over the top?
It isn't. It's a matter of
my pride as thy real wife!
What's the matter, Ku-chan?
I'm your wife, too!
So, I will compete in
the shopping race, too!
That's her eleventh lap.
She's full of fighting spirit.
There's one problem.
Kusano-tan's never really gone
out of the house, and she may get lost,
or face something
even more dangerous.
But looking at her,
I fear she shan't listen to us,
no matter how hard
we try to convince her.
Ku-chan always asks me
what she can do to help me.
I wonder if
because she's the littlest
that she wants to work as
hard as everybody else does.
Well, I do rather
understand her feelings.
Yes...
But I worry about her
going out shopping alone.
Then I'll give her a hand.
What?
I'm leaving!
Here I go!
I'm going!
Take care!
Do your best, Ku-chan!
Right!
Now...
Let's start the shopping race!
Musubi, I trust thou understandest.
We'll watch over her
stealthily from the shadows
so she can succeed
at shopping, won't we?
Right.
We shall put aside our duel this time.
Yes! Let's do our best!
System on!
Now I can pinpoint her
position no matter where she goes!
It's kinda nice... that
everybody's working hard for Ku-chan.
Because of you.
Huh?
I'm sure that they are good kids
because you're the one they're with.
Landlady...
Looks like Ku-chan's lost.
The landlady put
the map in her shopping bag!
Look at the map! The map!
It seems like she's completely
forgotten about the map.
What?!
Kusano-tan's straying from the planned path.
We don't need you to tell us that!
Musubi, do something!
Yes!
Ahem. This road has closed.
Please take another road.
Okay!
Ah, if you have a map,
you should look at it.
I just blocked the road and told
her about the map. It's perfect!
Good work, Musubi!
She calls this
"just blocking the road"?
That's it, huh?
The shopping district is straight ahead.
It's going well.
A kitty cat!
She's going into the alley!
She looks like she's chasing Mr. Cat.
What?!
They're going to collapse.
Hey Kusano, that's dan... dan...
She's off of her route again.
Shut up! This is not the time for that!
Oh no!
What are we even doing?
Tsukiumi-san, look at Ku-chan!
What?!
No!
If that's how you want to play this...
Tsukiumi-san, where are you going?
Why is Kusano-tan taking
such a complicated route?
Um, it was Mr. Cat...
Huh? Who?
Water Arrow!
I see. We can just lead Mr. Cat
toward the shopping district.
Let's go, Musubi!
Yes!
To the right!
She's getting close to the shopping district.
But... what are all these...
"Supermarket Maruyama"
No more kitty cat...
We managed to lead her to her destination...
Y-Yes.
All that's left is to buy potatoes and carrots.
"Organic Vegetables
Corner"
I wonder if she's forgotten what to get.
What?!
I have an idea!
What's that?
"Meat"
Why do I have to act so suspiciously?
No, no, Tsukiumi-san.
You must disguise your voice.
Like this?
Ah, this is the season when
potatoes and carrots taste the best!
You're right! Those are
absolutely the things to get.
Potatoes and carrots!
Yes, potatoes and carrots!
Good! Now, all she
needs to do is go home.
Yes.
Kusano-tan's made it home safe and sound!
Let our solemn duel begin now!
Yes!
I have the superior sprinting power.
The seat next to Minato shall be mine!
I won't lose!
W-Who came first?
I don't know... Where's Ku-chan?
Come to think of it...
Tsu-chan, Mu-chan.
- Kusano!
- Ku-chan!
Thank you.
You helped me a whole lot
with my shopping, didn't you?
Oh well, considering how flashy they were
about it, it would be odd if she didn't notice.
I couldn't shop by myself.
So I lost the shopping race.
No, the seat next to
Minato belongs to thee.
Thou didst well in thy
very first shopping trip.
Thou art certainly qualified to be his wife.
Out of respect, we have decided to
grant thee a seat next to Minato forever.
Isn't that right, Musubi?
Yes, we have!
Welcome back.
Welcome back, Ku-chan.
I'm back, big bro...
Ku-chan?!
- Kusano!
- Ku-chan!
She fell asleep...
Our plan was a complete failure.
We did it so secretly, too...
Yeah...
That lack of self-awareness might
be the biggest cause for this failure.
My, it's unusual for all three of
you to be in the bath at once, isn't it?
We're reviewing our game
today while we wash up.
Reviewing your game?
Ku-chan found out we were
helping her behind the scenes.
But I think you were both admirable.
You gave her a seat next
to Sahashi-san, didn't you?
That is... well...
Yes...
If our other choice is to
worry this much each time...
It's much easier for us
to just race by ourselves.
Ah, you're awake?
Where's everyone?
They're taking a bath so we can
have dinner together after you wake up.
How about we all go out
shopping together sometime?
With no races or anything.
Yes! Hey, big brother.
I like Mu-chan, Tsu-chan,
Ma-chan, and everybody very much!
Yes.
Me, too.