The treasure that was
stored in your house
has definitely been transferred
into my hands.
Fouquet the Sculptor.
A history of the couple's romance
that starts from the first kiss
You, the one who cast magic on
this destiny, suddenly appeared
The sky where two moons
never fade away
That's an impossibility, right?
This is the first time I've
felt anything like this
I'm feeling more and more
at ease with this place
Even if you trip and
become depressed
I will always hold you
tight with a squeeze
The story where we met that day
stays hot with a sweet kiss
See, you can cast magic, and
the wishes will surely come true
A history of the couple's romance
that starts from the first kiss
You, the one who cast magic on
this destiny, suddenly appeared
Tristein's Princess
Straighten your back more!
Like this?
Your right arm and right leg
are moving together!
You know, I suck at this stuff
when I have to think about it.
"When I am conscious of something,"
"I cannot perform
as well as I wish to!"
It's all terrible... Mannerisms,
pattern of speech...
What's with this all of a sudden,
complaining about this and that!
I was so careless...
I had completely forgotten
about the exhibition.
Exhibition?
There is a gathering that
happens every year.
All students exhibit their summoned
familiars to the whole Institute.
How stupid. Why don't
you just skip out?
All second-year students
are required to attend!
In any case... I just want to
avoid being embarrassed.
Since you can speak,
I thought you could make
a witty speech or something.
I know! I have something new
that I've gotten really good at!
Really?
Washing panties!
So, how about I demonstrate
washing your panties?
Goodness, my master
may have a face like that,
but she wears lacy panties like this!
She's so fashionable, even
where people can't see!
Is that all you want to say?
It wasn't true! I'm just joking!
That's right! Saito, you can
wield a sword, right?
Why don't you show some
of your swordsmanship?
That's no good.
I thought that when I decided
to barge into Mott's place.
You couldn't even swing once?
That time when I was
fighting Guiche...
I think it was all some sort of mistake.
Well, what happened
in Count Mott's manor
turned out to be for
the best in the end.
But come to think of it, it's strange.
What is?
Because my familiar did
something like that,
it wouldn't be strange for me to
receive some kind of scolding.
But nothing ever since...
Anyway, we don't have any time.
Think up something that you
can do before class is over.
Here goes...
Hey, what's that?
Such a strange dance...
How embarrassing.
I'm suddenly asked what
tricks I can show...
Well, you just do your best, partner.
Hey, Derf, since you're a sword,
don't you know at least one trick
to knock everyone's socks off?
Don't be stupid!
Unfortunately, I'm more
of a practical model.
Oh, what should I do?
Mr. Saito?
What are you doing?
Siesta...
Well, y'know...
Perhaps you're practicing
for the exhibition?
Yeah, that's it! But how
did you figure it out?
All the second-year students
are training very hard.
This year, Lady Henrietta
will be coming as well.
Lady Henrietta?
About preparations for
tomorrow's exhibition...
From cleaning all areas
of the Institute,
set-up of the guest seats,
preparations for the banquet...
Under Mr. Colbert's guidance,
everything is moving along
without interruption.
Concerning other
potential problems...
Oh, that was rather close, Motsognir.
So, today's color was?
What?! You couldn't get a look?
That's unfortunate.
Be kinder to your elders...
Keep it up, Flame!
Right there, a spin, a dance of flames!
You're the best, Flame!
Right, good job, Kubacil.
Maybe the ribbon isn't working...
Verdande...
I'm sure the princess will be sure
to understand your elegant grace.
I see...
So the princess will be coming
to watch all this.
Lady Henrietta is a symbolic
existence to all the citizenry,
ever since the King passed away.
So she's popular.
The gift from the Palace will be mine!
A couple people out there
have a different objective.
We're terribly busy getting
ready to welcome her too.
See you later.
Yeah, later.
Please do your best as well, Mr. Saito.
Sure.
Make sure to guard the gates
on the actual day.
Yes, sir!
Mr. Colbert...
You are taking the guard from
the vault to guard the gates?
After all, everything is so sudden
that we're shorthanded.
But didn't I hear that Fouquet the
Sculptor was after the treasure here?
Even so, what thief would
choose the precise time
that the Royal Princess' guards
were on the premises?
In the first place, not even
Triangle-class mages
would stand a chance
against this door.
Even this Institute's guards
have to show off to the Palace.
That's very true.
Princess of the Kingdom of Tristein,
Her Highness,
Lady Henrietta has arrived!
What beauty...
That's the princess of Tristein?
I'm more beautiful than she is!
Don't you think so?
Well...
Hey, she's cute.
You stay quiet! You're only
a familiar, you're being rude!
Yeah, yeah...
Mr. Osman, I apologize for
this sudden, selfish request.
Not at all!
The students and I have all been
eagerly awaiting your arrival.
This one year, I really wanted
to see it with my own eyes.
Oh, is that...
A personal matter.
Hold on...
What part of that is your
vaunted swordsmanship?
Are you taking this seriously?
It's impossible to attempt to
do something in just one day.
After all...
What?
I'm more used to panty-washing...
Hold it! Hold on! I'll be serious!
I'll do it, yeah yeah yeah!
A guest, a guest...
Sheesh... Who is it so late at night?
Right, coming right up...
Who are you?!
It's been a while...
Louise Françoise!
Your Highness, the Princess!
Louise! Louise, it went that way!
Wait!
If anything happens that
makes you want to cry,
please make sure to tell me.
I will make sure to embrace you.
Then, I will make sure to help you
out when you're in a bind, Louise!
Louise, Louise... Good old Louise...
You should not, Princess!
To come to such a humble
abode by yourself!
Stop those formalities,
Louise Françoise.
We are friends, are we not?
Princess, those words
are too much for me...
Um, how do you guys
know each other?
When the Princess was
but a young girl,
I was honored to be her playmate.
Please say "childhood friends."
Oh, I've wanted to
see you all this time.
Princess...
I'm sorry.
Ever since Father passed away,
I haven't had anyone that
I could open my heart to.
Princess, I was surprised when
I received a letter from you.
Oh, I see. Because the
Princess was coming,
you quickly wanted me to show off...
You stay quiet!
Why are you standing there like an
idiot, right before the Princess?!
It is well.
Please be at ease, Mr. Familiar.
She's too cute...
What are you staring at?!
Please forgive him.
He really knows no manners.
So much that he stands up
against Count Mott.
I have been wanting
to see you as well.
I wondered what kind of person
the familiar that stood up
to a nobleman was.
Princess?!
Rest assured, Louise.
It caused a bit of a stir
within the Palace,
but there will be no punishment.
Then, Princess, you...
Did you forget?
I promised you long ago
that I would help you out
when you were in a bind.
I am a princess for now, you know.
Princess...
There is no way that I can thank you!
Louise, you summoned
a splendid familiar.
On the contrary!
Such a vulgar, strange creature
is the biggest mistake of my life!
Ouch... That hurts...
I'm telling you it hurts!
I'm telling you, stay put!
This was the most fun I have had
in the past few years.
Thank you, Louise Françoise.
The same goes for me, Princess.
Mr. Familiar...
Me?
Please do your best tomorrow.
Well, you can look forward to it.
Damn you!
Such behavior to the princess!
Why do you always...
Damn it, don't dodge them!
Stay quiet! Damn you,
why are you such an idiot?!
Freedom is the best treasure, after all.
Good night.
Princess?
We will now begin the presentation
of this year's familiars.
That was Tabitha the Snowy Wind.
Understand?
One bow, and you come back.
Don't you dare try to do
anything unnecessary!
After all that you've made me
practice, is that it?!
It's all right now.
The Princess already saw
what you were really like!
Next up... Miss Louise de La Vallière!
Here goes.
Okay...
Let me introduce you.
This is my familiar, Hiraga Saito.
His type is a...
Go for it, Louise the Zero!
...peasant!
He's a peasant-type?!
That's his social rank!
Just what we expect
from Louise the Zero!
She sure meets expectations!
Shut up! Stay quiet and watch!
Let's go, Derf!
Saito?
Go? Where are we going?
Hey, don't you realize
the situation we're in?
Like I know!
You're the one who drew me
all of a sudden!
What's up with that?
He's arguing with his own sword!
Oh, darling, everything you do
is strange and wonderful.
All of you, watch closely!
I'll show you some elegant
swordsmanship now...
Let go!
This is the worst.
Let go! That hurts, you're too strong!
To think that this fixture
magic was so sturdy...
If that's the case...
Then we will now begin the judging.
I have no time left.
I thought a physical shock
would do the trick.
I told you, nothing more than a bow!
But they were all cracking up.
You just made a fool of yourse...
Golem?!
What is this?
Is this also someone's familiar?
No, this is...
You're out of luck!
Look out!
Now, I would like to announce
this year's grand prize winner...
Saito!
Louise! Run!
Let go of Saito!
What are you doing?! I'm telling you
to run away from here!
In Ex...
You're wasting your time!
Louise! Hurry up and run!
Bet... Flame...
Fireball!
Hey, did you just hear something?
To think that my Verdande
was not chosen...
It was Tabitha's Sylpheed after all.
Well, that was an adequate choice.
It was an amazing familiar.
If you don't mind, may we
see it fly one more time?
Are you trying to kill me?!
Shut up! It was only a small mistake!
What part of that was a fireball?
The wall?
That magic just now?
Let go of Saito!
Listen to me! I'm serious this time!
Stop it! I'm telling you to run!
In any case, this is
a lucky break for me.
Go, Golem!
What is it?!
Protect the Royal Highness!
Golem!
I thank you for this!
Saito...
The Staff of Destruction has been
transferred into my hands.
Fouquet the Sculptor.
She got us.
No signs of the thief have been found.
All we found was an earthen clod.
What a catastrophe!
To think that the vault
would be broken into...
That's a surprise. That it was
that Fouquet the Sculptor...
Hey, Tabitha, did you see her face?
She hid her face.
Is that so? How boring.
To control such a large golem,
there's no doubt that she was
a Triangle-class mage.
Well, in any case, since both
of us survived, it's all right.
That's not how things go!
I am so glad both of you were safe!
Princess!
I am terribly sorry!
The Palace's treasure...
It was not your responsibility,
Louise Françoise.
Even so...
Princess, please hurry.
I must report this incident
to the Palace.
I will see you in the near future,
Louise, Mr. Familiar.
I just hope the princess doesn't
have to take responsibility for this.
Responsibility? Just because
a thief came when she was visiting?
I've been hearing bad rumors
about the Palace recently.
Not that worrying about any
of it does me any good...
Hey, Louise... Can I
ask you something?
What?
When I got caught, why
didn't you escape to safety?
You're an idiot.
A mage who forsakes her familiar
is not a real mage.
As if I were under a real magic spell
A bright smile is burnt onto my heart
But each time I see you, I give you
a pointy, cold shoulder
Why do I act mean towards the one
that I think about the most?
My true feelings,
the shards of loneliness
In the deepest part of my heart,
I'm calling for you
For the day to start from zero
Saito! Why are you so spaced out?!
Come on, we're heading out!
We're going to go capture
that thief Fouquet, of course!
Next episode: A Thief's Identity
Next Episode: A Thief's Identity