Wait! Please just listen to me for now.
Not on your life!
Ku-chan!
No! Don't bully my big brother!
Wait, Ku-chan!
I must make her our companion at any cost.
That's why...
That's why I must do it.
What is this little girl?
No, it can't be...
You got your claws into such a little child?!
Claws?!
Filthy! Thou art a filthy man!
Water Celebration!
Ima inochi ga hora kizashite chitte yuku
Nigirishimeta unmei
Mou mayou koto wa nai
Musubiau kizuna
Akatsuki matsu sora ni
Aishi kimi dakishimete
Orenai inori wo
Mada dare mo yoru no naka
Ima wa tada
Kokoro no oku ni sawatte
Afureru atsusa subete sasagetai
Yume miru ashita e
Hirogeru tsubasa wa
Ano hi no kimi ga kureta
Omoi wa kizamareta
Chikai no kotoba ga
Kiseki wo okosu yo
Takanaru mune habatake
Tobitateru negai haruka tataku
Feather 6:
"Maison Izumo Flower War"
I didn't use even one-hundredth
of my power for the last attack.
What does such a weak
monkey want to say to me?
I want you to be my... my Sekirei.
W-What?
Didst thou just tell me to be thy Sekirei?
That's right!
L... we need your power.
How couldst thou be
so shameless in public?!
Shameless?
I thought to spare thy life but...
I shall obliterate thee after all!
That's bad! She's dead serious!
Big brother!
I was so angry, I missed my aim.
I'll eliminate thee next time!
Even so, I can't move
until you listen to me!
Why?
Why does my chest feel like this?
Wait! Your opponents are us, right?!
Haven't learned your lesson yet?
A Sekirei not yet emerged
doesn't know anything!
Seo!
This man! Is he an Ashikabi, too?!
Geez, guess I've got no choice.
Hey! Close your eyes, kid!
This is a little too stimulating for ya.
Enough! Just do it!
Wh-What art thou going to do?
"Don't look!"
Don't look, Ku-chan!
Wh-Wh-What are ye doing?!
This is how...
...Sekireis fight.
Thunderstorm of our pact,
destroy our Ashikabi's misfortune!
This is an incantation only
emerged Sekireis can use...
That is...
The special words to chant
when we use major power...
Every Sekirei has his or her own incantation.
The incantation...
"God's Song"
- God's Song!
Watch out!
High energy reaction!
"Musubi-tan"
They are in big trouble!
Hello? Musubi-tan?
Thunder?
"Incoming > > > > > Matsu"
Matsu-san!
Go to the place on the map I'll send you.
Mina-tan might be in danger!
He's in our way!
Thou!
We can't have him as
collateral damage, you know?
A-Are you okay?
This man protected me with his own body...
We won't miss next time.
Is that the best thou canst do?
It escaped.
Hey, stop there!
Seo-san, please calm down!
Don't come any closer!
How will you pay me back, huh?
Why?! My strength is...
You stomped over my girls too, didn't you?
I can't work up an ounce of strength... Why?
My ability as Ashikabi is endorsed by Takehito.
It's a bit special.
Now, how will you pay for this?
Well, how about I force you to emerge
and make you into my dedicated slave?
No, this is not the man.
I don't want it.
The one... the one I want is...
S-Seo-san!
Could you please... let her go?
She is... she is my Sekirei!
Seo!
Are you cheating on us in front of our eyes?
Quite the nerve!
T-Time out!
You told us we were the only
Sekireis for you, didn't you?
I haven't done anything, yet!
Listen to me first!
Thou...
...calledest me "my Sekirei."
Thou must take the responsibility.
R-Responsibility?
Don't play dumb!
Thou hast said I was thy Sekirei, correct?!
Y-Yes, I did, Ma'am!
Not only wert thou not afraid of me, but
thou also protected me with thy own flesh.
Furthermore, thou savedest
me from the wicked Ashikabi.
Wicked?
For a monkey, thou art a man of mettle.
Strange...
My heart, which once clamored so
loudly in protest, is surprisingly calm now.
What is thy name?
Minato.
I'm Minato Sahashi.
Minato...
I-I don't know
anything about you, but...
The reason I met you
in my dream must be...
because we could definitely
grow to understand each other!
So!
Thou art a magical man...
Very well! I, the Sekirei Tsukiumi, accept
thy marriage proposal with good grace!
M-Marriage proposal?
Thou hast said I'm thy Sekirei!
I did, I did! I'm sorry!
Minato!
Yes?
From now on, the only one
allowed to kill thee is me, Tsukiumi.
Wh-What is this?
The feeling welling up from my heart...
Something warm and strong...
So this is... emergence...
Tsu-Tsukiumi-san!
"Tsukiumi" is fine.
Thou hast become my Ashikabi...
with this as a wedding ceremony.
Many... years to come...
We... just wasted a fight?
Seems like it.
Ku-chan!
As I thought...
that little child is thy Sekirei...
Well, she's a mere child
so I can tolerate it, but...
- the real wife is me...
- Minato-san!
Are you all right?
Musubi-chan!
Oh, good! You weren't in danger.
Yes. See, she's Tsukiumi-san.
She's joined our group.
Minato... thou... thou...
How many Sekireis dost thee have?
Um... you are...
"Calling Minato-tan"
Mina-tan! Mina-tan!
What happened?! I can't identify
the situation. All I can see are trees!
...the fourth.
Wa...
Wa?
Water Celebration!
Everyone's so late...
It'll be dinner time soon.
When you're like that,
you look like their mother, Miya.
Did you say... mother?
No! Big sister! You look like a big sister!
I guess you're right.
From their point of view,
I am really kind of their big sister...
We're back!
Ah, they're back.
Oh dear!
We've just come back.
Landlady, we've just come back!
Minato, who is this woman?
She's Miya Asama. She's the landlady here...
Sahashi-san... who is she?
Ah, eh, um...
I'm his wife!
W-Wife?!
What art thou so surprised at?
We have gotten married,
so I've become thy wife.
Wife...
Wh-What was that?
Such tangled-up feelings in my heart...
What's with this little brat?!
Get away from him!
Musubi-chan, what's wrong?
I am...
His wife, too!
Out of my way! The real wife is me!
This is a soap opera. Soap opera world!
Don't you need to join them?
Even though I'm not participating
in the soap opera there, I attack...
no, attract Mina-tan in my own way.
What a lame joke...
To think he made Tsukiumi,
who hated Ashikabi so much, emerge...
Minato Sahashi... he's a mysterious man.
Now we shall fight!
That's what I want!
Enough!
I won't allow any violence
here in Maison Izumo.
She is... good!
I'm sorry, Landlady.
How about you?
They say when in Rome, do as the
Romans do. I shall obey the landlady here...
Landlady... ah, this is...
The Sekirei Plan.
H-How did you?
I already told you. My husband
worked in the MBI's research section.
Then, when Ku-chan came...
Yes, I could guess the situation...
You are his Sekirei, right?
Welcome to Maison Izumo.
I'm his wife, Tsukiumi.
Pleased to meet thee, Landlady.
I'm his wife, too!
Thou... couldst thou be?
Hmm, who art thee, again?
I feel as if I'm well acquainted
with one looking like thee, but...
Maybe it's just a chance resemblance.
I'm Kagari.
I look forward to getting to know you.
I just took off my mask.
Should I feel relieved or pathetic?
Kagari-tan.
What?
How are the burns from the other day?
You should stabilize your ability soon.
Are you telling me I should get emerged?
Yes. Even without the
burns, your body is still...
What a thing to say to
a defective being like me.
I won't be chosen by anybody,
nor will I choose anybody.
I only have one wish...
To kill that man with my own hands.
Kagari-tan!
I'm going out to work,
so please tell Miya I don't need dinner.
Kagari-tan...
I-I wanna take a peek... No!
In the end I let him stay last night,
but I can't believe I'm alone with a boy...
I'm sure... I'm your Sekirei.
Please give me your... seal.
Hold it!
What do you mean, seal?!
The symbol to prove that I am yours.
Wait a sec! I can't understand
what you're talking about at all!
So, what's a "Sekirei"?
The Sekirei Plan...
That's the name of the game
unfolding here in the capital.
Game?
And we Sekireis were released
in order to meet our individual
Ashikabi-sama, our masters.
Normally I could never
believe something like that,
but he doesn't look like he was lying...
I'm number 107, Shiina,
and probably your Sekirei.
Probably?
I said probably because I haven't
confirmed my body's reaction.
And to confirm,
I must have mucosal contact, so...
Mucosal... like a kiss?
If you wish, I can do more!
I...
"More"...
Thank you for the bath.
Is anything wrong?
No, nothing.
I could never tell Mom or Bro about this...
Hey, how about going
out shopping tomorrow?
There aren't any boys' clothes here,
and you need to change, don't you?
But what if someone
chases me like yesterday?
No problem. I thought of a plan.
What?!
Didst thou say she's also Minato's Sekirei?!
Yes... I'm sorry.
That's how it is.
Nice to meet you, Tsukiumi-tan.
Stop that "tan" thing!
Whoa! You've got another one, again!
I'm sorry.
Minato! Don't tell me she is also...
No, no! She's definitely not!
My Ashikabi's not here.
That's good. I'm Tsukiumi.
Pleased to meet thee.
I'm Uzume.
You've got a lot of competition. Good luck!
Uzume-san! Stop adding
more fuel to the flame!
Ha! They aren't even worthy
to be called my competition.
Because... I am Minato's real wife.
I am his real wife, too!
Dost thou understand what "real wife" means?
No, I don't.
Here, Minato-san. Open your mouth wide.
Minato, I'm sure thou understandest
that if thou shouldst eat that,
thy life would be forfeit.
Ah... thank you,
but I can eat by myself...
Here!
You're only a child!
This place has become quite lively.
Yes, it'll be more fun.
That Minato...
I told him I would wash his back, but...
He refrained.
Sharing bath and berth are
the privileges of Ashikabis.
What is "sharing a berth"?
It's when a man and a woman
sleep cocooned together.
"Cocooned"?
Ugh, I feel a chill. I did get
doused with water a lot today...
Big brother...
Who do you like?
Y-You can't just ask me
out of the blue like that...
Well... I like all of you.
Thou dost not need to know.
- Musubi-chan, Tsukiumi...
- Eh? I'm his wife, too!
Matsu-san,
And Ku-chan, too.
All of you chose someone like me who doesn't
have any special abilities or qualifications.
So I want to repay you for caring for me.
Something I can do...
Well, I don't even know
what I can do yet, though.
Was that too complicated for you, Ku-chan?
Ku-chan!
I like you very much, big brother.
Stay with me forever.
And then, when I get bigger,
please make me your wife.
What was that?! I just felt like
someone got the better of me.
Me, too!
Really, it'd be best if we could
stay like this, with no fights at all...
Number 09. I confirmed her emergence.
It's time.
The time has come.
The economy, technologies, networks...
there's nothing to fear any longer.
For the sake of the lovely birds who
flew to land, I shall willingly play the fool!
It's a festival!
The stage Shintou Teito!
The Sekirei Plan moves to phase two!
Yo, baby girls! Get ready now!
This is renai no shinansho
Don't let it go, aserazu so
Without furaingu de show time
Get the funky beat!
Hayai mono gachi?
Kono bayai wa kankei nai nai
Nozomu tokoro yo
Soudatsusen boppzatsu
Onna desu mono, maketerareya shinai nai
Fukuramu kimochi
No mou daibakuhatsu
Dame yo, yuuwaku shicha
Doite, kare no osoba
Watashi dokidoki natte ippai ippai
Naisho, nukekake shite
Daiseikou, kare to futari
Amaku mekurumeku night
Honto wa ne, watashi dake wo
Dakishimete hoshii no
Hitorijime mura mura
Furagu tatechau no ari kashira?
Yappari ne, yowaki, dou shiyou
Yasashisugite shou ga nai
Sonna toko daisuki yo
Dakara watashitachi tsukushimasu
Dear Sweet Heart!
Kagari, good morning.
Uzume! You're walking
around looking like that again...
What's the matter?
I'm wearing my panties...
Gah! I forgot them!
You really are so...
Oops, I did it again!
Wait, Kagari, don't you think
your reaction is kind of lacking?
Episode 7: "The Black Sekirei."
Feather 7:
"The Black Sekirei"
Episode 7: "The Black Sekirei."
Feather 7:
"The Black Sekirei"
Please favor us again next time!