I made another mistake...
Geez, you must be such a handful for Alicia.
Did she scold you?
No.
Then, what did she say?
She said "My, my," and giggled.
She's way too nice...
But I guess "My, my. Giggle!"
is what you'd expect from Alicia, right?
No, what she should have
said was, "Hey, hey. Grumble."
Such big strawberries!
Yeah! They're also very sweet.
Sir, I'd like these, please.
Here's your change.
Thank you.
Athena, you forgot to take what you bought!
Akari! Your change, your change!
Ah, my mistake!
Geez, what are you doing?!
Sorry, Aika.
Why are you always like this, Athena?
It's you...
Hello!
Hello Alice, Athena.
Hello.
"Akari, I got scolded by my mother again."
"Ai, I get scolded by Aika a lot, too."
"I know she scolds me because
she cares about me, but..."
"I wish I didn't have to get scolded at all!"
"...I wish I didn't have to get scolded at all!"
Do you remember that day
Oboeteimasuka ano hi o
When your heart suddenly began to race
Futo kanjita tokimeki o
The rays from the blue sky were pouring over you...
Aoi hizashi abite
...as you cut through the wind
Kaze o kiru kimi ni
I couldn't look away, and when our eyes met
Mitoreru to me ga atte
I couldn't help but smile
Egao koboreta
It's just like a spiral
Marude supiraare
I want to spend my days waving to you
Itsumademo te o furitai hibi
This is my proof that I was here with you
Koko ni tashika ni kimi to ita akashi
An eternal spiral
Zutto supiraare
There's a path which stretches on ahead
Kono saki mo tsuzuiteru michi ga aru
When you climb the next hill,
Tsugi no saka o nobottara
Let's meet again
Mata aimashou
That Wonderful Extracurricular Lesson...
Huh?!
A-Are you helping me practice, President Aria?
He's... helping?
So heavy!
I see, President Aria!
This is strength training, isn't it?
This is visual acuity training, isn't it?
Visual acuity?
President Aria fell asleep already...
This is balance training, isn't it?
Hey, Akari! No playing around allowed!
Yes!
You...
...always end up enjoying
practice a little too much!
You're going to get scolded by Alicia
if you keep this up, you know.
Right, Junior?
Th-that's right...
Sorry...
Scolded...
Reflect! Reflect on your actions!
Um, Akari, how does Alicia scold you?
Huh?
I don't think... Alicia... has ever... scolded me...
Say what?!
Not even once?!
Nope.
Now that you mention it, I don't think
I've ever seen her get angry, either.
I see... I guess that makes sense...
Knowing Alicia, there's no way
she'd scold someone...
Let alone get mad...
After all, this is Alicia we're talking about!
Impressive, as expected of Alicia!
She truly is a water fairy descended
from the heavens! Miss Perfect!
But, come to think of it, I've never seen
Athena scold you either, Alice.
That's really obvious.
I may scold clumsy Athena at times,
but I never get scolded myself.
Oh?
Well, I guess that makes sense.
Even I'm forced to scold Athena sometimes,
so it's really a mystery why
Alicia doesn't scold Akari.
P-President Aria!
I was about to really make a loud noise there.
My, my.
Are you all right?
Yes...
Even Alicia is human.
There must be times when she's irritated
or angry, when no one's around.
Besides, if she truly cares about Akari,
she should scold her properly.
I'm really sorry!
Besides, if she truly cares about Akari,
she should scold her properly.
It's all right.
Besides, if she truly cares about Akari,
she should scold her properly.
It's all right.
Alice?
W-What are you doing, Alice?
A-Ah, yes...
Since the members of the
Aria Company always treat me so well,
I thought I'd secretly return the favor
by helping out with the cleaning.
Oh, no!
What are you doing up there?
N-Nothing...
U-Um...
I woke up early, so I thought I'd come by
and say hello before going to school.
Eh?
Huh? Alicia, what happened?
My customer had another commitment,
so I finished early today.
Why don't we all have some tea together?
Yay! I get to have tea with Alicia!
I'm happy for you, Aika-
Oh, impressive, President Aria!
I-I'm so sorry, President Aria.
Are you all right, President Aria?
Come to think of it, where's Alice?
She said she had something
to do today, and went home.
President Aria?
Huh?
Wha-?!
Alice?
What are you doing here?
I thought you had something to do?
S-Something to do...
I-I finished early and had a hunch that there
might be a tea party with Alicia, so I came back.
Huh?
A hunch?
I was right, wasn't I?
Are you all right?
Geez, what are you doing?
W-W-W-W-What am I going to do?!
This was Alicia's favorite teacup...
My, my, what was that sound?
What?!
I-I'm sorry!
Thank goodness...
...none of you were hurt.
I'll help clean it up.
I'm really sorry!
My, my, it's all right. Don't worry about it.
Again, she didn't scold her.
I'm really, really sorry!
Oh, no! Akari's gondola is drifting out to sea!
Don't worry!
I'll go after it!
Aika, what should I do?!
This is all because you
didn't tie the rope properly!
Oh, no!
This is a really good chance to see her get mad!
This is a really big mistake.
Even Alicia will have no choice
but to scold Akari for this.
My, my...
It looks like the mooring rope was
hit and severed by something sharp.
Thank you so much, Alicia.
It's all thanks to President Aria
for noticing it right away.
Thank you so much, President Aria!
Come now, let's all finally have some tea.
Yes!
Just what you'd expect from Alicia!
Akira would have just jumped to conclusions
and yelled, "Hey Aika! You tied it wrong!"
She really was calm, wasn't she?
But...
...if this really had been Akari's mistake...
...then surely, even Alicia would have scold-
Surely she would have scolded her... right?
Could it be...
...that she doesn't scold Akari,
because she's given up on her?
That couldn't be it... Could it?
Alicia...
It's been a week since then.
I've been unable to find any clues
to reveal what Alicia is thinking.
Maybe Akari making a really big mistake
is the only way to find out, after all?
Thank you for waiting.
Here is your special parfait.
This is to replenish the blood sugar in my brain,
so I can come up with a much better plan!
What a coincidence, Alice.
Are you on your way home from school?
Y... Yes.
Would you mind if we join you?
P-Please...
Th-This is really awkward.
I-Is this some kind of...
...punishment?!
Same one, please.
Yes, certainly.
Has she figured out that I've
secretly been observing her?
Say, Alice.
Y-Yes?!
My, my
My, my.
Naughty troublemakers who snoop on
other people from the shadows...
...must be punished, don't you agree?
I-I'm really in a pinch!!
Could this be the first time
we've ever been alone together?
Eh?
Ah, yes...
Now that you mention it...
Isn't it strange, considering
how long we've known each other?
Yes.
So Alice, is there something
you'd like to ask me?
Thank you for waiting.
W-W-What do you mean?
You've been watching me
a lot lately, haven't you?
You were looking at me so intently,
it made me a little self-conscious.
Since we're alone, you're welcome
to ask whatever you like.
Giggle
I knew it, she saw right threw me!
She truly is Miss Perfect!
In that case... Go for broke!
Um... Alicia, why don't you scold people?
Akari told me. She said that
she's never seen you be angry.
I was wondering why that is.
You never scold your apprentice,
no matter how grave a mistake she makes?
If that's true, don't you think
you're being a bit cold?
Excuse me, President Aria.
Could you please go give this
to that little girl sitting over there?
Um...
Alicia?
U-Umm...
Alicia...
Hello?
Mr. Cat, is this candy for me?
Thank you!
My, my.
President Aria, that was amazing!
The errand was a big success!
That girl is really happy, too.
Now this time, go to the boy
sitting at the next table.
Thank you!
Amazing, amazing! That was
much quicker than before!
What do you think?
Ah, yes...
He delivered them successfully.
Alice, why don't join me for
a walk after you finish your parfait?
Eh?
Um...
His first try took a while, didn't it?
Why didn't you point out his mistakes, like when
he got sidetracked or went to the wrong table?
You see...
...say President Aria and I were playing a game,
trying to split a watermelon blindfolded.
I wouldn't shout, "Not that way, not that way!"
I'd keep shouting, "This way, this way!"
If I kept shouting, "not that way," President Aria
would become afraid of making mistakes.
Eventually, I don't think he'd be able to move.
That's my way of doing things.
Umm...
What would you do if he kept on
making mistakes, though?
Well...
If that happened, I'd reflect on my own
lack of knowledge alongside him.
Eh?
After all, I'm just an imperfect human being.
As a mentor, when you
instruct your apprentice...
...there are times when things
just don't go the way you want them to.
When that happens, I often think to myself,
"Ah, teaching and being taught are,
in fact, very much alike."
So, in that case, all I can do is try to
see things from Akari's point of view.
I'll share her challenges, share her defeats...
And, in the very end, I hope to
share her happiness as well.
Alicia!
Alice!
My, my.
It's one coincidence after another today, isn't it?
President Aria, I was wondering where
you went, and here you are with Alicia!
We were also wondering where Junior
could be, since she was late for practice...
...and we catch her strolling
around with Alicia? No fair!
Alice, please keep the conversation
we had just now between us, okay?
Why?
Because...
...it's embarrassing.
I don't see any point in keeping it a secret.
The two of you are so alike, I get
embarrassed just watching you both.
I'm sorry.
That was really disrespectful of me.
Please scold me.
My, my.
Yay!
Hey! No monopolizing Alicia allowed!
"I wish my mother was like Alicia."
"Hmm... But then my mother
wouldn't be herself, would she?"
A shore awash in golden waves
Kin no nami kishibe ni
Filled with yearning, I open my eyes and it's morning
Akogare mezameru no asa ni
As my thoughts focus intently on someone,
Dareka no koto o tsuyoku omou toki
Love rests on my palm, held high
Kakageta te no hira ni ai ga tomaru
A future guided by the flow of water and wind
Mizu no yukue to kaze ga shimesu mirai
I gaze at the hope that surrounds this world
Kono hoshi o tsusumu kibou mitsumete
The distant clouds of light are beckoning now
Tooi kumo hikari ga sasou you ni yureru ima
A shore awash in golden waves
Kin no nami kishibe ni
Filled with yearning, I open my eyes and it's morning
Akogare mezameru no asa ni
And my day begins
Hajimaru
Next Episode
President Aria, come to think of it, how long
have you been with the Aria Company?
Next Episode
My, my.
"In That Gently Passing Time..."
Next time, "In That Gently Passing Time..."
Next Episode
"In That Gently Passing Time..."
Now, please take my hand.