I realized that the time had come to face
the problem I had been ignoring
by not thinking too deeply
about it.
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, keep going on
Baby I'm standing alone
An unforgettable rainy day
Chasing after your shadow
And it's over, it's like sand now
I sigh every night
I scream like a child and cried
It hangs there quietly, my sorrow
Please, please God, forgive my sins
I don't need to hide no more
Flowing toward the turquoise light
Just keep going on
You've got the chance now
You've got the power
Know you gotta be so true to yourself
I show you my life now
I show you my love now
I show you my everything yeah yeah
You'd better change now
You'd better catch now
Don't ever change so be yourself
I'll show you my strength now
I'll show you my love now
I'll show you my everything yeah yeah
Baby don't be afraid
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, keep going on
RE: IT'S ME, REIRA
Why does being pregnant make me
so sleepy every day?
NEW MESSAGE
UNREAD EMAIL: 01
UNREAD TEXT MESSAGE: 01
SEPTEMBER 24
NOBU
HOW ARE YOU?
RECEIVED MAIL
SEPTEMBER 2402:36
NOBU
HOW ARE YOU?
I WANT TO HAVE A PROPER TALK
WITH YOU. IS IT POSSIBLE?
I'LL BE WAITING FOR YOUR REPLY.
NO NEW MESSAGES
Nobu!
Yasu says lunch is ready.
Spaghetti with mushrooms!
I think we can count on a tasty meal.
Yasu's cooking is the best.
Who are you expecting a reply from?
You've been checking
your email all morning.
Well, you know,
because the reception is bad here.
But you usually leave your cell phone
in your room.
Shin, do something about that habit
of yours of closely observing others.
Sorry. But you're easy to figure out
even without observing closely.
I don't want you figuring me out!
But I can.
It's dangerous here.
Looking at the night sky,
it's as if you can reach the stars.
You get the feeling that
your dreams will come true.
Shin, thank you for your email.
I feel it's been a long time since
I've seen that many stars.
Even if I close my eyes,
I can only imagine artificial neon lights
like in a planetarium.
SHIN, THANK YOU FOR YOUR EMAIL.
I FEEL IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE I'VE SEEN THAT MANY STARS.
EVEN IF I CLOSE MY EYES,
I CAN ONLY IMAGINE
ARTIFICIAL NEON LIGHTS
LIKE IN A PLANETARIUM.
SHIN, THANK YOU FOR YOUR EMAIL.
I FEEL IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE I'VE SEEN THAT MANY STARS.
EVEN IF I CLOSE MY EYES,
I CAN ONLY IMAGINE
ARTIFICIAL NEON LIGHTS
LIKE IN A PLANETARIUM.
Because I thought I'm no different
from such neon lights.
SHIN, THANK YOU FOR YOUR EMAIL.
I FEEL IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE I'VE SEEN THAT MANY STARS.
EVEN IF I CLOSE MY EYES,
I CAN ONLY IMAGINE
ARTIFICIAL NEON LIGHTS
LIKE IN A PLANETARIUM.
SHIN, THANK YOU FOR YOUR EMAIL.
I FEEL IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE I'VE SEEN THAT MANY STARS.
EVEN IF I CLOSE MY EYES,
I CAN ONLY IMAGINE
ARTIFICIAL NEON LIGHTS
LIKE IN A PLANETARIUM.
Your words have saved me
once again, Shin.
BECAUSE I THOUGHT I'M
NO DIFFERENT FROM
SUCH NEON LIGHTS.
YOUR WORDS HAVE
SAVED ME ONCE AGAIN, SHIN.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
Your words have saved me
once again, Shin.
BECAUSE I THOUGHT I'M
NO DIFFERENT FROM
SUCH NEON LIGHTS.
YOUR WORDS HAVE
SAVED ME ONCE AGAIN, SHIN.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
BECAUSE I THOUGHT I'M
NO DIFFERENT FROM
SUCH NEON LIGHTS.
YOUR WORDS HAVE
SAVED ME ONCE AGAIN, SHIN.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
Thank you so much.
BECAUSE I THOUGHT I'M
NO DIFFERENT FROM
SUCH NEON LIGHTS.
YOUR WORDS HAVE
SAVED ME ONCE AGAIN, SHIN.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
PHEW
Thank you, Nami. You have quite the tan.
No! Yes! I mean,
I'm sorry, I'm kinda nervous!
I've been a big fan of Trapnest
since your debut!
Really?
Don't question her.
She's being polite.
Honey!
You think this pattern is too flashy?
You don't need to wear a tie.
Gotta look dignified as a father.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Takumi Ichinose.
You sure are tall!
H-How tall are you?!
A meter and
eighty-three centimeters, right?
I wasn't asking you.
Fawning all over him...
I apologize that it took so long
before I could come.
These are some gifts from England.
Though, the only thing British
about it is the tea.
- Oh my, this much?
- What is it?
Wow, thanks brother!
I'll follow you for
the rest of my life!
How cozy!
It's beautiful! Your father would never
buy me things like this.
You certainly seem to be well-off,
Mr. Ichinose.
Do celebrities get paid that well?
It depends on the person.
After all, you're profits are determined
by your popularity.
That's true.
Are you sure you can provide for
my daughter and her child
for the rest of their lives?
I'll do all right, sir.
"Sir"?!
He seems like an untrustworthy guy.
I may be a celebrity on the outside,
but I'm just a workman.
It's difficult to continue a band
regardless of its popularity.
I'd like to be in the same band forever,
but that's not something that
I alone can determine.
Today, I wore a wedding dress
while filming our promo video.
TODAY, I WORE A WEDDING DRESS
WHILE FILMING OUR PROMO VIDEO.
IT'S A SONG ABOUT A WOMAN
WHO CAN'T GET MARRIED.
THE STAFF JUST DOESN'T GET IT!
(BUT THEY SAID IT HAS
A LONELY EFFECT AND THAT I WAS
THE ONE WHO DOESN'T GET IT.)
Today, I wore a wedding dress
while filming our promo video.
TODAY, I WORE A WEDDING DRESS
WHILE FILMING OUR PROMO VIDEO.
IT'S A SONG ABOUT A WOMAN
WHO CAN'T GET MARRIED.
THE STAFF JUST DOESN'T GET IT!
(BUT THEY SAID IT HAS
A LONELY EFFECT AND THAT I WAS
THE ONE WHO DOESN'T GET IT.)
TODAY, I WORE A WEDDING DRESS
WHILE FILMING OUR PROMO VIDEO.
IT'S A SONG ABOUT A WOMAN
WHO CAN'T GET MARRIED.
THE STAFF JUST DOESN'T GET IT!
(BUT THEY SAID IT HAS
A LONELY EFFECT AND THAT I WAS
THE ONE WHO DOESN'T GET IT.)
It's a song about a woman
who can't get married.
TODAY, I WORE A WEDDING DRESS
WHILE FILMING OUR PROMO VIDEO.
IT'S A SONG ABOUT A WOMAN
WHO CAN'T GET MARRIED.
THE STAFF JUST DOESN'T GET IT!
(BUT THEY SAID IT HAS
A LONELY EFFECT AND THAT I WAS
THE ONE WHO DOESN'T GET IT.)
TODAY, I WORE A WEDDING DRESS
WHILE FILMING OUR PROMO VIDEO.
IT'S A SONG ABOUT A WOMAN
WHO CAN'T GET MARRIED.
THE STAFF JUST DOESN'T GET IT!
(BUT THEY SAID IT HAS
A LONELY EFFECT AND THAT I WAS
THE ONE WHO DOESN'T GET IT.)
The staff just doesn't get it!
TODAY, I WORE A WEDDING DRESS
WHILE FILMING OUR PROMO VIDEO.
IT'S A SONG ABOUT A WOMAN
WHO CAN'T GET MARRIED.
THE STAFF JUST DOESN'T GET IT!
(BUT THEY SAID IT HAS
A LONELY EFFECT AND THAT I WAS
THE ONE WHO DOESN'T GET IT.)
WE FILMED THE ENTIRE DAY FOR
A FEW SCENES THAT WILL ONLY
BE A FEW SECONDS. EVERYTHING
WE WORK ON IS LIKE THAT.
We filmed the entire day for a few scenes
that will only be a few seconds.
WE FILMED THE ENTIRE DAY FOR
A FEW SCENES THAT WILL ONLY
BE A FEW SECONDS. EVERYTHING
WE WORK ON IS LIKE THAT.
WE FILMED THE ENTIRE DAY FOR
A FEW SCENES THAT WILL ONLY
BE A FEW SECONDS. EVERYTHING
WE WORK ON IS LIKE THAT.
Everything we work on is like that.
WE FILMED THE ENTIRE DAY FOR
A FEW SCENES THAT WILL ONLY
BE A FEW SECONDS. EVERYTHING
WE WORK ON IS LIKE THAT.
THE WORK TAKES A LOT OF EFFORT,
BUT THE THRILL OF COMPLETING
SOMETHING TOGETHER IS LIKE
NONE OTHER, AND WITH
MY FRIENDS, I'M ABLE TO FEEL
THAT I BELONG HERE.
The work takes a lot of effort,
THE WORK TAKES A LOT OF EFFORT,
BUT THE THRILL OF COMPLETING
SOMETHING TOGETHER IS LIKE
NONE OTHER, AND WITH
MY FRIENDS, I'M ABLE TO FEEL
THAT I BELONG HERE.
but the thrill of completing something
together is like none other,
THE WORK TAKES A LOT OF EFFORT,
BUT THE THRILL OF COMPLETING
SOMETHING TOGETHER IS LIKE
NONE OTHER, AND WITH
MY FRIENDS, I'M ABLE TO FEEL
THAT I BELONG HERE.
and with my friends,
I'm able to feel that I belong here.
THE WORK TAKES A LOT OF EFFORT,
BUT THE THRILL OF COMPLETING
SOMETHING TOGETHER IS LIKE
NONE OTHER, AND WITH
MY FRIENDS, I'M ABLE TO FEEL
THAT I BELONG HERE.
THINKING BACK, THAT'S PROBABLY
WHY I WAS ABLE TO COME THIS FAR
WITH MY SINGING NO MATTER
HOW TOUGH THINGS GOT.
Thinking back, that's probably
why I was able to come this far
THINKING BACK, THAT'S PROBABLY
WHY I WAS ABLE TO COME THIS FAR
WITH MY SINGING NO MATTER
HOW TOUGH THINGS GOT.
with my singing no matter
how tough things got.
All right, okay. We're done.
Done already?
We've done enough.
At your current level as a singer,
it'll be the same, no matter
how many times we record.
In other words, you've given it
all you've got for now and it was great.
What's that supposed to mean?
We can artificially adjust the high notes
you have trouble reaching.
Do some voice training before
the live performance,
so you don't embarrass yourself.
Otherwise, even the music magazines
will start writing nasty things about you.
Shut up! Stop laughing!
Let me sing it again!
Well then, now that we're done
with the recording,
what do you say we go fishing?
Yeah, that sounds like fun.
All right!
That's the one thing I've been looking
forward to doing here.
The one thing?!
Matsuo!
Let me sing some more!
Keep it down!
You'll scare off all the fish!
Say, why did your wife leave you?
I think the number one reason Gaia
decided to record at that training camp
I THINK THE NUMBER ONE REASON
GAIA DECIDED TO RECORD
AT THAT TRAINING CAMP IS TO
STRENGTHEN THE BONDS BETWEEN
THE BAND MEMBERS
AND THE STAFF.
I think the number one reason Gaia
decided to record at that training camp
I THINK THE NUMBER ONE REASON
GAIA DECIDED TO RECORD
AT THAT TRAINING CAMP IS TO
STRENGTHEN THE BONDS BETWEEN
THE BAND MEMBERS
AND THE STAFF.
is to strengthen the bonds between
the band members and the staff.
I THINK THE NUMBER ONE REASON
GAIA DECIDED TO RECORD
AT THAT TRAINING CAMP IS TO
STRENGTHEN THE BONDS BETWEEN
THE BAND MEMBERS
AND THE STAFF.
THE STAFF YOU'LL BE WORKING
WITH FROM NOW ON WILL BE LIKE
YOUR FAMILY, THERE TO SUPPORT
THE BAND. I THINK PARTICIPATING
IN THAT CAMP HAS GREAT MEANING
TO IT. LET'S BOTH DO OUR BEST.
The staff you'll be working
with from now on
THE STAFF YOU'LL BE WORKING
WITH FROM NOW ON WILL BE LIKE
YOUR FAMILY, THERE TO SUPPORT
THE BAND. I THINK PARTICIPATING
IN THAT CAMP HAS GREAT MEANING
TO IT. LET'S BOTH DO OUR BEST.
will be like your family,
there to support the band.
THE STAFF YOU'LL BE WORKING
WITH FROM NOW ON WILL BE LIKE
YOUR FAMILY, THERE TO SUPPORT
THE BAND. I THINK PARTICIPATING
IN THAT CAMP HAS GREAT MEANING
TO IT. LET'S BOTH DO OUR BEST.
THE STAFF YOU'LL BE WORKING
WITH FROM NOW ON WILL BE LIKE
YOUR FAMILY, THERE TO SUPPORT
THE BAND. I THINK PARTICIPATING
IN THAT CAMP HAS GREAT MEANING
TO IT. LET'S BOTH DO OUR BEST.
I think participating in that camp
has great meaning to it.
THE STAFF YOU'LL BE WORKING
WITH FROM NOW ON WILL BE LIKE
YOUR FAMILY, THERE TO SUPPORT
THE BAND. I THINK PARTICIPATING
IN THAT CAMP HAS GREAT MEANING
TO IT. LET'S BOTH DO OUR BEST.
THE STAFF YOU'LL BE WORKING
WITH FROM NOW ON WILL BE LIKE
YOUR FAMILY, THERE TO SUPPORT
THE BAND. I THINK PARTICIPATING
IN THAT CAMP HAS GREAT MEANING
TO IT. LET'S BOTH DO OUR BEST.
Let's both do our best.
Mr. Ichinose. What about your family?
How many siblings do you have?
You have a big sister, right?!
We're not asking you.
Honey...
Would you let me talk too?!
This isn't any fun!
But you hardly know a damn thing
about my family, do you?
"Damn"?
Excuse me.
Oh, that's not a problem at all!
You can use that language with me
whenever you damn please!
It's not fine! Not at all!
And your Japanese is funny!
Nami, go buy some sake.
Yes, you do that.
And pick up some ingredients
for the sukiyaki too.
Huh? No way!
Besides, what are the ingredients?
Meat?
Let's take the car and
go together, Nami. Okay?
You wanna go out with
your new handbag, don't you?
Don't tell me you like Nami.
Please, anyone but her.
I'm so sorry! Nana and Nami
are both such noisy girls.
Me too?! Don't group me with Nami!
Not at all.
I'm enjoying this very much.
My mother was very weak,
and the rest of my family
was rather dark.
Perhaps because of that,
since I was small I've always been
drawn to energetic, happy people.
That's why I find this so attractive.
The feeling of a loving family
like yours. This is fun.
I see.
Well, one thing I can guarantee
is Nana's in good health.
So how is your family doing now?
My mother passed away six years ago.
My sister married a local man.
They now live with their
two children and our father.
Okay, then we should give them
a visit sometime soon.
We'll all go and pay our respects
at your mother's grave.
Yes, we should.
No, it's okay.
- Huh?
In fact, my father is
a complete alcoholic,
and lately he can't even manage
a proper conversation.
I'm sorry.
An alcoholic.
That must be tough for you.
But we still should go and
introduce ourselves.
No, it's really all right.
He's the type of man
that wouldn't even attend
my sister's wedding or
my mother's funeral.
Besides, I have no intention
of inviting him to our wedding.
I wouldn't want him ruining it.
If there's something not right
about the father,
the child isn't gonna amount to much.
I'm a good example.
More importantly, about the location
of the wedding ceremony,
would you mind taking a look
at these documents?
Hey, guy. You're not a salesman.
Honey! You just called him "Guy"!
Ren?
Ren. You'll catch a cold
if you sleep here.
Here. Come here like a good boy.
Come on.
Reira?
I'm sorry. I guess I dozed off.
Did Mr. Honjo have a bit
too much to drink?
Is he okay?
Yeah. This always happens.
Help me carry him to the bed.
Sure.
Shin. Right now, I'm really
regretting having left in Japan
SHIN. RIGHT NOW,
I'M REALLY REGRETTING
HAVING LEFT IN JAPAN
THE LIGHTER
YOU PURPOSELY FORGOT.
Shin. Right now, I'm really
regretting having left in Japan
SHIN. RIGHT NOW,
I'M REALLY REGRETTING
HAVING LEFT IN JAPAN
THE LIGHTER
YOU PURPOSELY FORGOT.
the lighter you purposely forgot.
SHIN. RIGHT NOW,
I'M REALLY REGRETTING
HAVING LEFT IN JAPAN
THE LIGHTER
YOU PURPOSELY FORGOT.
I LEFT IT BECAUSE I DIDN'T WANT TO
RISK LOSING OR BREAKING IT,
BUT I FEEL UNEASY
NOT HAVING IT WITHIN REACH.
TAKING CARE OF SOMETHING
IS SO DIFFICULT.
I left it because I didn't want to
risk losing or breaking it,
I LEFT IT BECAUSE I DIDN'T WANT TO
RISK LOSING OR BREAKING IT,
BUT I FEEL UNEASY
NOT HAVING IT WITHIN REACH.
TAKING CARE OF SOMETHING
IS SO DIFFICULT.
but I feel uneasy not having it
within reach.
I LEFT IT BECAUSE I DIDN'T WANT TO
RISK LOSING OR BREAKING IT,
BUT I FEEL UNEASY
NOT HAVING IT WITHIN REACH.
TAKING CARE OF SOMETHING
IS SO DIFFICULT.
I LEFT IT BECAUSE I DIDN'T WANT TO
RISK LOSING OR BREAKING IT,
BUT I FEEL UNEASY
NOT HAVING IT WITHIN REACH.
TAKING CARE OF SOMETHING
IS SO DIFFICULT.
Taking care of something is so difficult.
I LEFT IT BECAUSE I DIDN'T WANT TO
RISK LOSING OR BREAKING IT,
BUT I FEEL UNEASY
NOT HAVING IT WITHIN REACH.
TAKING CARE OF SOMETHING
IS SO DIFFICULT.
I'LL BE RETURNING TO JAPAN
ON THE 27TH. WHEN WILL YOU
BE RETURNING TO TOKYO, SHIN?
I WANNA TALK WITH YOU
FACE TO FACE.
I'll be returning to Japan
on the 27th.
I'LL BE RETURNING TO JAPAN
ON THE 27TH. WHEN WILL YOU
BE RETURNING TO TOKYO, SHIN?
I WANNA TALK WITH YOU
FACE TO FACE.
I'LL BE RETURNING TO JAPAN
ON THE 27TH. WHEN WILL YOU
BE RETURNING TO TOKYO, SHIN?
I WANNA TALK WITH YOU
FACE TO FACE.
When will you be
returning to Tokyo, Shin?
I'LL BE RETURNING TO JAPAN
ON THE 27TH. WHEN WILL YOU
BE RETURNING TO TOKYO, SHIN?
I WANNA TALK WITH YOU
FACE TO FACE.
I'LL BE RETURNING TO JAPAN
ON THE 27TH. WHEN WILL YOU
BE RETURNING TO TOKYO, SHIN?
I WANNA TALK WITH YOU
FACE TO FACE.
I wanna talk with you face to face.
I'LL BE RETURNING TO JAPAN
ON THE 27TH. WHEN WILL YOU
BE RETURNING TO TOKYO, SHIN?
I WANNA TALK WITH YOU
FACE TO FACE.
BECAUSE I BELIEVE LOOKING
SOMEONE IN THE EYE
WITHOUT ANY PRETENSES
IS LIKE LOOKING AT YOURSELF.
IF YOU LOOK AWAY YOU LOSE.
AND I DON'T WANNA LOSE.
REIRA SERIZAWA
Because I believe looking
someone in the eye
BECAUSE I BELIEVE LOOKING
SOMEONE IN THE EYE
WITHOUT ANY PRETENSES
IS LIKE LOOKING AT YOURSELF.
IF YOU LOOK AWAY YOU LOSE.
AND I DON'T WANNA LOSE.
REIRA SERIZAWA
without any pretenses is
like looking at yourself.
BECAUSE I BELIEVE LOOKING
SOMEONE IN THE EYE
WITHOUT ANY PRETENSES
IS LIKE LOOKING AT YOURSELF.
IF YOU LOOK AWAY YOU LOSE.
AND I DON'T WANNA LOSE.
REIRA SERIZAWA
BECAUSE I BELIEVE LOOKING
SOMEONE IN THE EYE
WITHOUT ANY PRETENSES
IS LIKE LOOKING AT YOURSELF.
IF YOU LOOK AWAY YOU LOSE.
AND I DON'T WANNA LOSE.
REIRA SERIZAWA
If you look away you lose.
BECAUSE I BELIEVE LOOKING
SOMEONE IN THE EYE
WITHOUT ANY PRETENSES
IS LIKE LOOKING AT YOURSELF.
IF YOU LOOK AWAY YOU LOSE.
AND I DON'T WANNA LOSE.
REIRA SERIZAWA
BECAUSE I BELIEVE LOOKING
SOMEONE IN THE EYE
WITHOUT ANY PRETENSES
IS LIKE LOOKING AT YOURSELF.
IF YOU LOOK AWAY YOU LOSE.
AND I DON'T WANNA LOSE.
REIRA SERIZAWA
And I don't wanna lose.
BECAUSE I BELIEVE LOOKING
SOMEONE IN THE EYE
WITHOUT ANY PRETENSES
IS LIKE LOOKING AT YOURSELF.
IF YOU LOOK AWAY YOU LOSE.
AND I DON'T WANNA LOSE.
REIRA SERIZAWA
REN
MESSAGE FOR NANA
I GOT BACK IN JAPAN TODAY.
PLEASE GIVE ME A CALL.
- Did you read it?
- Yeah.
Without delay, the eight-day
seven-night long recording
at the training camp finally
came to an end.
But even after returning to Tokyo,
I can't go home while the place is
still infested with them mosquitoes.
What are you reading, Shin?
You're into literature, I see.
An erotic novel. Mika bought it
for me at a book stand.
Is it any good, Shin?
Not at all.
Huh?
- No use trying to tease him, Mika.
- Oh, Mika.
- I think Shin knows more about that
- You can only touch him
- than you do.
- from the neck up.
But this is good study material.
What study is that?!
THE HOUSEWIFE NEXT DOOR
AI YAZAWA
"The Housewife Next Door"?
THE HOUSEWIFE NEXT DOOR
AI YAZAWA
Starting today,
we're all being thrown into
the so-called agency's dormitory.
They just call it a dormitory.
It's really a regular apartment building.
It's for our agency's talents only, though.
Everyone gets his own room,
there's no curfew,
and no nosy dorm supervisor.
But security and facilities are
above standards,
so it's safe and comfortable!
I don't care what it is, as long as
I can relax and get some sleep.
You're better off not opening
the window.
That's a love hotel next door.
They're not likely to open
their window too often either.
What's comfortable about this?!
I don't get any sunlight here!
You have your own toilet and shower.
Where's the bathtub?
You're such a complainer!
Who do you think you are?
If you wanna live the high life,
then work your way up there.
I'll make certain that you have
a full schedule starting tomorrow.
Wait, Ginpei! Is there a phone?
There's one on the first floor
at the front desk!
The front desk?
At least buy a cell phone!
Work will be
- so inconvenient without one.
- That's not a front desk!
And the security guard's asleep!
What's the point of having one?
He's bored,
which is proof of how safe it is.
I'll pick you up
tomorrow morning at seven.
Don't go wandering off outside!
There's something wrong.
Something's definitely wrong about
this production company.
Even the president was a weirdo.
Well, do your best.
No, I can't judge people
on their appearances,
but this guy also looks like one of them.
Who are you, miss?
I'm Nana from the Black Stones!
I just introduced myself
to you moments ago!
Oh right. Did you want something?
I wanna use the phone.
Go ahead and use it. It's free.
Forget it. I don't wanna be overheard.
I'll borrow Nobu's phone.
Really, go ahead and use it, miss!
But say I call Ren,
what am I gonna say to him?
We're not gonna be able to see
each other for a while anyway.
I actually would prefer
that he leave me alone
rather than have him half-heartedly
show some affection toward me.
That's what I should say to him.
I'm finding it hard to breathe.
It must be because the air is dirty.
That's why I hate Tokyo.
Huh? The Black Stones?
I know the band!
You do?
Well, it's famous, in a way!
No, not nearly as famous as you.
This is so exciting!
Hey, come on in!
Huh? But...
Come on! Hurry!
Ow!
What are you doing, little man?
You seem to be having fun.
Well, I was just saying hi
to my neighbor.
Nana?
She's gorgeous!
She sure is a celebrity!
It's the real Nana!
Please give me your autograph!
Huh? Yuri Kosaka?
That adult video star?
You all seem to know her.
What the hell kind of agency is
"Shikai Corporation"?!
Why are there adult video actresses
working for it?!
Well, she did start out as an idol.
But when her popularity dipped,
she took her clothes off.
You know a lot about her, Yasu.
And how could you make
the dormitory coed?
That's borderline outrageous!
I'm guessing it's to accommodate
or shelter their talents
with some sorta problem.
Like Ginpei was saying,
they just call it a dormitory.
You're right.
But Miss Yuri's been in
so many adult movies,
she must have money.
So why is she living in
a shabby place like this?
MISS YURI?
Miss Yuri?
Nobu!
Switch rooms with me.
Huh?
With a starving wolf like
you living next door,
"Miss Yuri" would be in danger!
I'm not gonna do anything!
She's a pro!
I don't care! Just switch!
Why are you always so bossy?
Nobuo. I couldn't care less
if you get off on porn videos.
But I hope you haven't
forgotten our plan.
Plan?
To get Hachiko back!
We pledged to fight together!
So don't get involved
with other women!
What are you saying?
You're misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
You were bashfully and
gleefully chatting with Yuri!
No, not that.
I'm not necessarily fighting
to get Hachi back.
And this is unrelated to that.
For me, Hachi and the band
are separate issues.
Besides, why do I have to
take care of Hachi
just so you can own her
in your yard?
Honestly speaking,
I have completely given up on her,
so do whatever you wish on your own.
But...
What? Damn, you're being stubborn.
Then what are we fighting for?
That's a stupid question.
We're fighting so our music will be
accepted as that of a professional.
Hachi has nothing to do with it.
Nana?
Nobu is free to date
whoever he wants.
But then, how do I
stay connected to Hachi?
I can no longer go home
to that place,
and even if I did, Hachi's
no longer there.
Hey, Yasu, how do you read
this kanji?
"Itsuwari."
"Lie."
Thanks.
NOBU
Yes?
Yasu!
Nana's...
Nana!
Shin, call an ambulance!
The number's 119.
What's the address here?
Tell Mr. Yamagishi, the security guard
and have him call one!
Okay!
We were talking and
then all of a sudden,
she was short of breath and
seemed to be in pain,
like she was having an attack.
Nana, are you okay?
An ambulance will be
here soon.
It's okay. Don't worry.
I won't leave your side.
I'm not going anywhere.
I think she's hyperventilating.
It's so painful you think
you're dying,
but you will never die from it.
It's a living hell.
Hey, wait!
Nobu! Do you have a paper
or plastic bag?!
Huh? Why?!
Just hurry and find one!
Hey, Hachi.
Humans are such
pathetic creatures.
The harder they struggle,
the deeper they sink.
If I were to be born again,
I wanna be a fish.
Ren and I, just the two of us would
swim in a small fish tank.
I reached into the sky
But I couldn't reach what I wanted
They grew smaller
and disappeared into the sky
Like colorful balloons
I'm alone
My hand had no place to go
And gently you took it
Starless night
I won't look back
at the shadow of my past
I want to feel your warmth
Tears are falling down
Even if I'm unsure I won't let go
Of your hand holding mine