I shouldn't have gotten
a cell phone.
I know I'm the one who's staying out
without telling her,
but Hachi didn't even
email me once.
That made her look more selfish to me
and it irritated me.
I don't want the strength
of our bonds
to be tested by
some communication device.
Blinking eyes call the wind
A smile clears all the noise away
The angel in your eyes whispers
"Everything begins now"
Can you feel it now
It's like being caught in a wave
Pulling on my heart
Breath held, arms reaching out
Baby this world is
different from yesterday's
You're the only one I can see
Baby my wish on a wing
This sky is torn
By a single overflowing word
CHECKING FOR MESSAGES
NO NEW MESSAGES
I haven't been home for nine days.
The more time passes,
the harder it becomes for me to go home.
But I can't continue living here.
What am I gonna do?
How does Hachi spend her time
all alone in that room?
Trapnest's recording schedule
was extended past
what was originally planned,
and the band members were
all stuck inside together.
It was clear that Hachi
was lonely every day.
I couldn't imagine that self-centered guy
contacting her much.
But I couldn't feel
any sympathy for her.
This is the life that Hachi chose.
Good morning!
You sure are up early, Takumi.
Did you get some rest?
No. I'm about to take a nap now.
Is that so?
You've been working hard, haven't you?
How is Reira doing?
She's sleeping well.
It seems that the medicine the doctor
prescribed for her is working.
Sleeping pills?
Maybe I should get some, too.
You can't sleep either, Takumi?
I may be able to sleep if
you came to my room.
I'm not going!
How lonely.
I can't take it anymore...
this ascetic life.
Then we have to be sure and
get this finished today.
Right. Our schedule's been
really messed up.
Take's in tears.
I'm sure your fiancée's also
in tears from loneliness.
You know,
that's really not the case.
She sends me several emails a day,
and she says stuff like
I KNITTED SOCKS (^-^)
"I knitted socks."
She seems to be having fun.
Socks?
She's thinking way, way ahead.
The baby's not due until
May of next year.
Oh, for the baby!
But why is it that
women don't want to talk
about the real important things,
but want to report unimportant stuff?
Don't think of it as unimportant.
Please just remember to reply, okay?
I am. I write things like,
MAKE A PAIR FOR DADDY TOO (^3^)
"make a pair for Daddy too."
Really?
But what if she really knit me a pair?
An identical pair to the kid's?
That would be too painful.
You'll hafta wear them.
It would be a sight not to be missed.
I was hoping Hachi would be so lonely
that she'd be longing for me.
Nana Osaki? Yeah, I remember.
The rabbits, right?
Huh? The rabbits?
Oh, hey! Don't film this!
Is this gonna air on TV?
No, it's for a magazine article.
Don't worry.
I don't wanna get involved.
Did Osaki do something?
When we were in fifth grade,
the rabbits in the rabbit cage were found
slaughtered one morning.
Everyone accused Osaki
because you'd expect something like that
from a gloomy kid like her.
Miss Osaki was pretty,
so she stood out in junior high,
but she was so anti-social.
People hated her for that.
She was bullied?
I'm not too sure about that,
but I did hear rumors
that she got angry and beat up
a senior who harassed her.
Osaki's the girl who
got kicked outta school
when they found out that
she was selling her body, right?
What did she do this time?
So, as you can see,
it was almost like investigating
a criminal's past.
She's the best! That Nana Osaki!
There is so much to write about her.
But I am so exhausted.
Why do I, a photographer,
end up having to go after stories like this?
We're short of staff!
Can I go home for the day?
Ren Honjo's still locked up
in the studio, right?
Yeah. Why are they taking ten days
to record just a couple of songs?
Are they having some issues?
Chief, it appears that Trapnest
has finished recording.
The band members have
started going home.
Kurata!
I'll have an article ready
and reserve a big space for you.
I'm counting on you.
For a shot of the two.
How do you like the new song,
Director Matsuo, Producer Kawano?
I like it. It's complete with energy
- and a little sexiness!
- Great!
That was more than satisfactory!
Then please let us record it right away.
And we really need you to decide on
an agency for us soon.
We are working on it little by little.
Is he really?! That raccoon bastard!
- Raccoon!
- It's not a laughing matter!
Yeah, that name suits that man,
all right.
You drunk already?
There's no use trying anymore
for this.
Shin. Are you at all serious
about doing this?
You've gotta realize that
the company's not about to invest
in a risky new band.
They say Gaia's not about
to invest money
in an old fashioned punk band like ours.
What's this?
Who said that?
I am really sorry.
I'm sorry it's not going anywhere,
all due to my lack of ability.
It's not your fault, Mr. Kawano.
Our band just doesn't have
what it takes.
No, your band is not the problem.
Due to the recession, Gaia is
reluctant to promote new bands.
This is a tough time
for bands in general.
But Trapnest's album has sold
almost three million copies.
Well, I guess a big part of their success
lies with their vocalist Reira.
She is attractive enough
to ride the diva boom.
I'm worthless unless I sing.
But the same goes for
your vocalist, Nana.
I'm not about to give up, Yasu.
We're not giving up that
easily either.
Then will you give me
a bit more time?
Our temporary contract is
for three months, right?
We signed the contract
because we trust you, Mr. Kawano.
We'll keep our promise.
Really? Thank you.
I should be thanking you.
I appreciate that you put
this much heart into this.
But you can't do business
on heart alone.
But I have no desire to turn music
into a heartless business.
In our band, we have people
like Nana and Shin
who have had the misfortune of
not being loved by those around them.
I don't want them thinking
this world is nothing
but money and greed, after all.
But I'm sure there will be
many more situations in the future
when they will be forced to
think that way.
So it would be so encouraging
to have someone like you
who will support our band
with passion and love.
Is it too much to ask?
The burden you carry on
your shoulders seems much greater.
Let me carry half of it.
Don't try to carry all that you can.
If both your hands are full,
you won't be able to take action
when you need to.
Here.
I guess you're right.
You still drinking, Nobu?
How could I not drink?!
Who cares about the recession?
It feels like I've been laid off.
Have Hachi comfort you.
I can't blame it on the recession.
I just need to write songs that
will convince the guys at Gaia.
Give me that!
Say, did something happen
between you and Hachi, Nobu?
Nobody talks about Hachi
anymore at the studio.
Shin.
Don't you ever mention that name again.
Even Nobu has a thing or two
he would rather not talk about.
By the way, why did you buy
this acoustic guitar?
No real reason. I'm going out.
Must be nice. The little boy has
many older women to comfort him.
Even one who would
buy him a guitar.
I bought it on my own.
But you bought it with the money
you got from women, right?
It's the same thing.
Nana...
When you get everything
you want so easily,
you lose that hungry spirit within you.
"There's no use trying"?
If you have the time to play
your acoustic guitar,
practice the bass.
I shouldn't hafta be lectured
by some vocalist
who can't even stop smoking.
- What?!
- Ah, Nana!
Same goes for you, Nana.
Where did you get your new guitar?
It's not something you could
buy with your pay.
And it's unsuitable for someone
like you who can hardly play it.
I borrowed it from Ren!
Then what about those clothes?
They've all been given
by Misato and Ren, right?
Nana!
What's wrong with that?!
Don't compare me with someone
like you who sells his body!
Don't be provoked!
I'm the one who doesn't wanna
be compared with you.
I receive what's appropriate
for my efforts.
But Nana, all you're doing is cuddling up
to Ren's kindness.
Shin!
That guy... Is he at the rebellious phase?
Wh-Why are you taking your clothes off?!
Damn it!
Is it wrong?
Is it wrong to accept kindness?!
No, there's nothing wrong about that.
Don't worry about it, okay?
Shin's only trying to justify himself.
I think you should let Ren spoil you more.
Don't let some stupid pride
force you into a corner.
REN
Hello.
Oh, Nobu.
Sorry to call you at this hour.
Were you asleep?
No,
I'm still up.
Things going well?
Yeah.
Are you sure about that?
There's no way you don't know
about Hachiko, right?
Yeah. But...
I guess it can't be helped.
Honestly, there's nothing I can do
for her right now...
So you're finally able to
face the reality.
Try and relate to the trouble your parents
went through to raise you, okay?
Yes, I'm sorry.
You're being too obedient.
You're no fun to tease.
By the way,
Nana's at my place right now.
Huh? She's at your place?
I was getting worried because
I can't reach her on her cell phone.
And she hasn't replied to my emails.
Huh?
Really? Maybe she's forgotten
to switch it on.
After band practice, Nana, Shin
and I were drinking together.
Actually, Ren, .,
Nana's been acting a bit strange lately.
She's always been short-tempered,
but her mood swings are intense.
Even just now,
she got into an argument with Shin,
she got all panicky,
and started crying.
Also, she told me not to tell anyone,
but at one point,
she said she sometimes can't remember
what she's been doing.
Yeah, she has been acting a bit strange.
Nana...
Nana, get up!
At least put your clothes on.
Shut up.
If you're a man come at me.
Show me what you're made of.
Ren said he's coming to pick you up.
If he sees you like that
he'll get the wrong idea.
He should be here any time now.
He doesn't hafta come!
Why not? First, get dressed!
What if he got followed by a mosquito?!
That'll be trouble.
A mosquito?
The paparazzi are after us!
I hear Naoki was saying so.
There's no doubt about it.
But I'm sure it's fine.
If it weren't, I doubt Ren would say
he'd come pick you up.
He has no idea of the damage
a scandal can cause!
He kept calling me to his place
without saying a word about being targeted.
He only thinks of himself.
I don't wanna draw attention
as "Ren's girl."
Return the guitar to him.
And tell him that I won't be
seeing him for a while.
Is your pride that important to you?
Ren needs you, you know.
You're the one who's only thinking
about yourself.
A moon that's not quite full.
That's how I feel when I'm with Ren.
No matter how deeply
we love each other.
I'll bet there's no one who can
really make me feel complete.
But when I'm on stage...
I become complete.
I must protect it. My dream.
No matter what I end up sacrificing.
I wonder if Hachi's sleeping.
What time is it now?
Where's my cell phone?
It's annoying to have,
but so inconvenient not to have.
Takumi might be there.
But it is my home.
There's no need for me to hold back.
It's quiet.
Isn't she here?
Maybe she's sleeping with Takumi.
But she may be alone.
Whatever, I don't know what to think.
TO NANA
What's this?
What's she up to?
Hachi!
Hachiko, are you here?!
You know, Hachi...
Back then, when you kept
losing yourself in love...
Maybe you too were struggling
to feel complete, just like me.
If so, then I can understand
some of those feelings you had.
It's just that I couldn't back then.
Does the new life you protected at all costs
make you feel complete even now?
I can't count
how many nights
I wished tomorrow
would never come
To live as I am
without being fake
What do I need
If I don't believe in myself,
what can I believe in
The answer is
too close to see
Black tears are
falling down
I have nothing,
only sadness
I can't put it
into words
My whole body
starts to ache
I can't stand it anymore
on my own