Something seems off.
It just somehow felt that way.
One out, with the score
still seven to zero.
I had absolutely no interest in the
prefectural baseball game on TV,
The gap between the
scores is big,
I had absolutely no interest in the
prefectural baseball game on TV,
but Kumamoto still has a chance
if they can hold out here.
I had absolutely no interest in the
prefectural baseball game on TV,
but Kumamoto still has a chance
if they can hold out here.
But Kumamoto still has a chance
But I kind of ended up
rooting for the losing side.
Once I did, I kind of got the feeling that
Haruhi was going to start something.
The passionate voices cheering from the
third base bleachers have not died down.
Once I did, I kind of got the feeling that
Haruhi was going to start something.
There's Suzuki, they need him to do
his best, don't they, Mr. Kiru?
That's true.
Kyon, the phone's ringing.
After all, you never know how a match is
going to turn out. They still have hope.
I know, you don't
have to tell me.
After all, you never know how a match is
going to turn out. They still have hope.
You're not doing anything today, right?
We're meeting at 2PM in front of the station.
Right.
You're not doing anything today, right?
We're meeting at 2PM in front of the station.
Next, stepping up to the batter's box we
have number four, Kashima, a senior.
You're not doing anything today, right?
We're meeting at 2PM in front of the station.
Next, stepping up to the batter's box we
have number four, Kashima, a senior.
Be sure to show up.
Next, stepping up to the batter's box we
have number four, Kashima, a senior.
After last year's summer tournament, he was
chosen for the team that went to Cuba.
I didn't even say anything...
In the fourth inning,
he hit a three-run home run.
I didn't even say anything...
In the fourth inning,
he hit a three-run home run.
What?
And there's Suzuki
with a big windup...
What?
And there's Suzuki
with a big windup...
I forgot to mention this - bring
a swimsuit and plenty of money.
And the first pitch is a strike.
No problems there.
I forgot to mention this - bring
a swimsuit and plenty of money.
And the first pitch is a strike.
No problems there.
And be sure to bring your bike.
That's all, over and out!
That was a good pitch.
And be sure to bring your bike.
That's all, over and out!
That was a good pitch.
And again, I had the feeling that I
knew what Haruhi was going to say.
That was a strong, straight pitch,
thrown a little high and inside.
And again, I had the feeling that I
knew what Haruhi was going to say.
Perhaps he feels like
he's got nothing left to lose.
And again, I had the feeling that I
knew what Haruhi was going to say.
Perhaps he feels like
he's got nothing left to lose.
No, not quite.
Perhaps he feels like
he's got nothing left to lose.
To be precise, it felt like this exact
same conversation had happened before.
We don't know that yet.
He winds up for the second pitch...
To be precise, it felt like this exact
same conversation had happened before.
We don't know that yet.
He winds up for the second pitch...
I guess it's what you
would call deja vu.
It's a hit!
And it's a big one!
It's headed for
left field...
Summer's almost over.
And it's good!
DAY BY DAY unzari dayone dakara
Day by day, everything's just so dull
doudou to kotowacchau
kimi ni narina yo
that's why you need to become someone
that can just reject it all
OH MY BO Y kippari shinakya uso ni
Oh my boy, you need
to be decisive
tsukiatterarenai yo
semai sekai de
I won't deal with any lies
in this small world
jibun de mitsuketa MYSELF
suki ni natte touzen
I found myself on my own,
it's natural you'd fall for me
kudaranai yarikara kette
subete wa atashi ga kimeru
Kick away the boring ways of doing things,
I'm going to decide everything
I SAY I SAY MY HEAVEN
I say, I say my heaven
SUPER DRIVER tosshin
makasete nantettate zenshin
Super driver, leave everything to the rush
and just keep going forward, no matter what
fukanou (DON'T YOU STOP ME)
Tobikoete TAKE IT EASY, GO!
Surpass (Don't you stop me) the idea
of "impossible," take it easy, go!
Daishouri tte doukan
I agree, it's going
to be a huge victory
mochiron dounatta tte kaikan
Of course, it'll feel pleasant,
no matter what happens
hanseikai? (GET BACK TO WILD)
Sore yori saa isoide yo
A review meeting? (Get back to wild)
Forget that, now hurry up
aremo koremo mitaiken
itsudatte muriyari
We haven't tried this or that,
we always do things how we want to
marude marude mikeiken
korekara shimashou
Everything's a new experience,
let's try them out
aremo koremo mitaiken
itsudatte totsuzen
We haven't tried this or that,
we always do things suddenly
marude marude mikeiken
sore ga doushita no?
Everything's a new experience,
what about it?
Endless Eight
You're late, Kyon!
Show some more motivation!
Yeah, yeah.
Sorry I made you wait.
I just got here, too.
- Okay, we're all here, so let's go.
- Where are we going?
To the public swimming pool,
of course!
Well, I guess that makes sense
considering what I brought.
We have to do summer vacation-y things
during our summer vacation!
We can never get back the time
that we've lost!
And so we're going to do them now, in our
one and only summer as tenth graders.
By the way, we're going
to the pool by bike.
Did you ride
your bikes, too?
No, the only two bikes we have
are yours and mine.
Kyon, you'd better not lose
to Koizumi.
This train is leaving
the station!
No psychic powers allowed!
Hurry up and park your bikes,
you two.
Kyon, we're about to go have fun.
This is no time to be exhausted.
Whose fault do you think
this is?
Oh, the scent of chlorine.
This really makes it feel like a pool!
Hurry up and get in!
The water's warm so it feels fine!
Can't she read the "no diving" signs
posted everywhere?
That looks like fun.
She has some rather normal ways of
enjoying her time, don't you think?
Miss Suzumiya, laughing and having
a good time like that,
isn't likely to shake up
the world, after all.
I hope that's the case...
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing...
It's probably just
my imagination.
Let's get ready
to go in, too.
It's so bitter.
One more cup, please.
It feels like I've seen
this scene once before.
Where Nagato kind of looks
like she's bored...
Kyon!
Right, and then Haruhi
says this...
These two are my
brigade members.
They'll do anything you ask,
so ask for anything you want!
Okay, let's have some fun!
We're going to play water dodge ball.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, deja vu isn't
all that uncommon.
I thought about what we'll be doing
from here on. What do you think?
What is that?
"Things we have to do
during our summer vacation"
What is that?
"Things we have to do
during our summer vacation"
It's a schedule of how we'll spend the
rest of our short summer vacation.
I realized that we only have two weeks
of summer vacation left.
That fact
blew me away.
We still have so much left to do, but
we've only got this much time left!
We're going to pick up
the pace!
All this in just
two weeks?
Is there anything else
you want to do, Mikuru?
Umm... I'd like to try
goldfish scooping.
Okay!
Goldfish scooping...
Pardon me
for a moment.
- Thank you.
- We're starting tomorrow!
Is there a place nearby with a Bon festival?
A fireworks show works, too.
I'll check around.
I'll contact you when I find out.
Don't forget about
the goldfish scooping!
It's Mikuru's one request,
after all.
Roger that.
All right, then,
we're done for today!
- If you'll excuse me.
- I have to go, too...
Nagato.
No, it's nothing important.
How have you been?
Everything fine?
Fine.
I see. That's good
to hear.
What the heck?
Why did I talk to her?
Your attention please, we have a lost child.
Five-year-old Takashi Satou is...
A Bon festival, huh?
I guess it makes sense
for there to be this many people.
That tower,
those vendors...
It's been a while since I've come to one,
but it feels like I have recently.
Mikuru!
They have goldfish scooping,
just like you wanted!
- Be sure to catch a bunch!
- Okay!
Shall we play, too? How about
seeing who can catch more?
I'll pass.
What about you, Nagato?
Want to eat something?
You're interested
in that stuff?
- Which one?
- It's all right.
- This one.
- Right-o, that'll be 800 yen.
I kind of got the feeling that
Nagato had been helping us out,
so I thought it would be appropriate
for me to at least buy her that, but...
Hamster Fishing
Thirteen!
Wow, what a haul!
But I don't need so many,
so I just kept one.
And one
for Mikuru, too.
You can have one,
but only one.
Thanks.
Huh? What's with
the mask, Yuki?
I bought it.
I see.
No Obtrusive Fireworks Allowed
It was summer,
and summer vacation.
That's why I wanted
to forget about it,
...but there was one thing
lingering in my mind.
Haruhi.
It's fine to want to play around, but are you
finished with your summer homework?
What? You can finish homework
like that in just three days.
Three days!?
You get that stuff out of the way so you can
have fun without having to worry about it.
Why is she
so smart?
It seems like the guys up in
heaven that were divvying up...
the stats for us were being
pretty lax about it.
Everyone, tomorrow we'll be
catching bugs!
Whoever catches
the most bugs...
Okay, they'll get to be the
brigade leader for a day!
- No thanks!
- That sounds interesting.
Are any bugs okay?
Hmm... only cicadas!
That's it, this will be the SOS Brigade's
Cicada Capturing Competition!
The next day was yet again
a beautiful day.
It was on this day that we had the SOS
Brigade Cicada Capturing Competition.
That's sour!
It was on this day that we had the SOS
Brigade Cicada Capturing Competition.
That's not a cicada.
A yanbaru
long-armed scarab!?
It looks like each of us did try,
in their own way,
but of course, or something to that effect,
the winner ended up being Haruhi.
A catch and release attitude
is important, right?
If we let them go, then they
might come back to repay us.
What could a cicada do,
even if it did come back?
There you go! Go back
to the mountains!
For some reason, I kind of feel like
Pandora opening her box.
W-Welcome!
The next day, we met up, even though
we had no idea what was going on.
And we remained in the dark even as we
were made to wear frog costumes...
and then pass out balloons in front
of a supermarket as our part-time job.
I really understand how Unit-o felt
when it got hit by that beam.
Good work, everyone.
What's with this difference
in how we're being treated?
Thanks for the hard work.
The manager is thankful.
I don't care about his thanks.
Where's our pay?
This is it.
I've wanted this
for a while.
We worked, sweat pouring down
our foreheads, for that?
Let's hang this up in the
clubroom as a memento.
Mikuru, you can wear it whenever
you want. You have my permission!
Okay...
What?
- Oh, nothing.
- Don't look at me.
- Come on, Mikuru!
- M-Maybe later!
Your popsicle is going
to fall down.
That night, a single phone call
stole me away from my slumber.
The number you have
called is...
What in the world!?
Kyon...
Miss Asahina?
Yes, it's me...
Something... very not good has...
At this rate, I...
- Umm...
- Hello, this is Koizumi.
Why are you with Miss Asahina
at this hour?
Certain circumstances
came up.
Would it be possible for you
to come join us right now?
What in the world happened,
Miss Asahina?
Kyon... I... can't go back
to the fu-
In other words,
this is what's going on.
We are going through an eternal loop
of the same time period.
Even if you say something as impossible
as that with a smile on your face...
Koizumi, do you realize
what you're saying?
I do. Much more than
I wish I did.
I had just been speaking
with Miss Asahina.
Call me too, when you
have talks with her.
And as a result, what we realized
was that recently,
the flow of time
was a bit strange.
You might want to credit this
to Miss Asahina.
Thanks to her,
I was able to confirm it.
Confirm what?
That we have experienced the same
span of time numerous times.
You said that earlier.
To be precise, we've been repeating
the time from August 17th to the 31st.
We're in the middle of an
endless summer vacation.
Well, it is summer
vacation, but...
It's a never-ending
endless summer.
This world has lost all time
after September 1st.
Who'd believe that?
We'd like for you
to believe it.
Umm... I'll explain, too.
Well... because of
"classified information",
I'm always contacting the future
and "classified information"-ing,
but I hadn't received any "classified
information" for about a week or so,
which I thought
was strange.
And so I
"classified information"
I was so surprised I tried to
"classified information",
but it was completely
"classified information."
Oh, what do I do?
Are we trapped inside one of
those closed spaces?
That's not it.
A single portion of time
has been torn away.
At exactly the point when it becomes
midnight on August 31st,
everything resets, and we go back
to August 17th. That's the process.
So what about our...
no, humanity's memories?
Those are reset as well.
Everything starts over from the beginning.
So you mean that time does
that thing that you mentioned.
Well, we do have someone from the future
here, I guess it can't be helped.
Oh no, Miss Asahina
isn't involved in this.
Okay then,
what's the culprit?
I would guess
Miss Suzumiya.
I'm sure she doesn't realize it,
but somewhere inside of her...
...is a desire to not let
summer vacation end.
What the heck? Do you mean she
feels regret over something?
That's what I believe.
Perhaps she feels that
there's something left...
that she wants to do during
our summer vacation?
I've been wondering this since I got here,
but you seem awfully cheerful about this.
It's because we've finally been
able to solve the mystery
of the frequent feelings
of deja vu that I've had recently.
Now that I think about it, those inexplicable
feelings may have been
remnants from when our memories
have been reset.
Is it possible that other people
across the world feel this, too?
It doesn't seem that way.
You and I are a special case.
It appears that the people who
are closest to Miss Suzumiya
are able to sense
this strangeness.
What about Haruhi? Does she
sense any of this at all?
Not at all, it seems. It would probably
be bad for us if she did.
However, I believe that there is one
person who remembers everything,
more than the deja vu
that we do.
- Is that right?
- It is.
- You remember all of it?
- Right.
So, how many times have we repeated
all of this, this time?
This is the 15,521st time.
15,521?
What do you mean
by 15,521?
Are you serious?
I am.
You're saying that we've done the
exact same things that many times?
They're not all guaranteed
to happen.
Out of 15,521 repetitions,
there are two occasions,
#2,391 and #11,054, where we
did not go to a Bon festival.
A pattern where we did
go to a Bon festival,
but did not go to a goldfish scooping
stand, occurred 437 times.
We had a part-time job 9,048 times,
and when we did,
there are six different kinds
of jobs that we did.
In addition to handing out balloons,
we also worked as movers, cashiers,
handed out flyers, worked as call center-
I got it, that's enough.
Handed out flyers, worked as call center-
15,521 times,
that's what Nagato said.
Times two weeks, hmm,
that's around 595 years.
She alone has memories of all that time,
repeating it all over and over...
Nagato, how must it feel to experience that
same period of time over and over again?
I've heard yet another
crazy story.
- I wonder if they exist.
- If what exist?
- Martians.
- I kind of don't want them to.
It doesn't look like anyone's
on the surface,
so they're probably a reserved
people, living underground.
When man finally
sets foot on Mars,
I'm sure that they'll come out from
under their cover and welcome us,
saying, "Welcome to Mars!"
How about if they just
appear normally?
Oh, I'm bored of this.
UFOs. Let's look for UFOs.
The next day,
we went stargazing.
The location was Nagato's
apartment,
and the telescope was one
that Koizumi had gotten for us.
Exactly what does
she want to do?
Now what could
that be?
If we could figure that out,
this would all be solved...
How about trying
this out?
Give Miss Suzumiya a sudden embrace
from behind
then whisper "I love you"
into her ear.
And who would
be doing that?
Is there anyone else who could
fill the role other than you?
No, I refuse.
All right, how about
if I do it?
I'm kidding. I'm lacking a certain
something for the role.
And all that would do is cause unnecessary
confusion in Miss Suzumiya.
Hey, Nagato,
you were aware of this loop before
Miss Asahina said anything, right?
Yes.
If that's the case, why didn't
you say anything?
SOS Brigade Test of Courage Challenge
Leave the doll here as proof!
It's my job to observe.
I see...
We continued to run through a torrent
of summer vacation events.
We went to a real
fireworks show,
and we even took part in
a goby fishing tournament.
We also went to a batting center,
watched some movies,
went to the beach, went bowling,
and even sang karaoke.
We were always
doing something.
Of course, I knew that this wasn't
going to satisfy Haruhi.
Even so, there wasn't anything
I could do about it,
and the last days of our
summer vacation ticked away.
And so we ended up
at August 30th...
With this, we've finished
everything on our list.
Hey, no scribbling.
I wonder if this was
good enough.
But, hmm...
I guess this works.
Hey, is there anything else
you want to do?
That's fine, then.
We were able to do a lot this summer,
so that's enough, right?
No, it's not.
You're still not satisfied.
Okay, we're done
for today.
I had tomorrow set aside just in case,
but you can just take the day off.
Let's meet again in the clubroom
the day after tomorrow.
Wait... Haruhi...
Okay, we're done
for today.
I had tomorrow set aside just in case,
but you can just take the day off.
Let's meet again in the clubroom
the day after tomorrow.
I can't let Haruhi leave.
If she goes, we'll end up repeating
these past two weeks
for the some-thousandth time.
Okay, we're done
for today.
I had tomorrow set aside just in case,
but you can just take the day off.
Let's meet again in the clubroom
the day after tomorrow.
What should I do?
What should I say?
There must have been a hint
somewhere in what Haruhi said.
But what was it?
What has she said
up to this point?
I don't know...
I can't remember...
Okay, we're done
for today.
I had tomorrow set aside just in case,
but you can just take the day off.
Let's meet again in the clubroom
the day after tomorrow.
Whatever, it doesn't
matter anymore.
August 31st. I haven't
touched my homework.
Oh, forget it.
If we're just going to do it all over again,
then there's no point to doing it.
Whether tomorrow comes or not, I'll leave
it to the me at that time to deal with it.
Sora kara ochite kitanda
It fell from the sky
subete no negai wo nosete
With all of the wishes
that were made upon it
hitotsu no hoshi niwa
chotto omokatta kana
Maybe it was a little too heavy
for a single star
yappari nanika henda yo
Something just doesn't
seem right
kokoro no kimi ga kieta
The image of you in my mind
has vanished
tashika ni oboeteru tte
ieruno kai?
Can I say that
I remember you clearly?
Tomare!
Stop!
Kako wa jibun no mono
The past belongs
to me
touzen daretomo torikaetakunai
Of course I don't want to trade it
with anyone else
nazenara
That's because
basudei datta watashitachi niwa
It was my birthday,
and when we saw each other
deai ga umareta toki ni
We could see
the first dream
hajimete no yume ga mieru
That we had when
we were born
doushiyouka tte
nayanda koto mo
Worrying about
"what do I do?"
Ima omoeba waraeru hodo
datta yo ne
Is laughable when I
think about it now
mou wasureteta
I've already forgotten it
kimi wo sagasou
Let's search
for you