Hey, what do you think of Akira?
She's the most levelheaded
of the Three Great Water Fairies.
She's organized, dependable, and takes charge.
What's the matter?
Did something happen to Akira?
Well, it's more like nothing...
What do you mean by "nothing"?
You're really not making any sense.
I guess so. It's not something
you two would understand.
Huh?
"Dear Ai, it's been so warm here in Neo-Venezia
lately that I find myself breaking into a sweat."
"And also!"
"Today, we changed uniforms!"
"That's right! We switched
into our summer clothes!"
Oh yeah, Akari.
I heard you worked on a traghetto recently?
Yes, it was really fun.
After it was over, it motivated
me to work even harder.
I can't afford to lose to you!
You're both really motivated.
Now that we've changed into our summer
uniforms, let's give it all we've got during practice!
Okay!
Roger.
"I wish I could see you and the others
in your summer uniforms again."
"I'm sure they'll be a breath of fresh air
as Neo-Venezia changes seasons."
Oh my, Akari. Is that your summer uniform?
Yes! We switched our uniforms today!
Do you remember that day
Oboeteimasuka ano hi o
When your heart suddenly began to race
Futo kanjita tokimeki o
The rays from the blue sky were pouring over you...
Aoi hizashi abite
...as you cut through the wind
Kaze o kiru kimi ni
I couldn't look away, and when our eyes met
Mitoreru to me ga atte
I couldn't help but smile
Egao koboreta
It's just like a spiral
Marude supiraare
I want to spend my days waving to you
Itsumademo te o furitai hibi
This is my proof that I was here with you
Koko ni tashika ni kimi to ita akashi
An eternal spiral
Zutto supiraare
There's a path which stretches on ahead
Kono saki mo tsuzuiteru michi ga aru
When you climb the next hill,
Tsugi no saka o nobottara
Let's meet again
Mata aimashou
That Keepsake Clover...
I heard a really good bakery
opened around here somewhere...
Oh?
I'll go ask that shopkeeper over there.
Excuse me!
Welcome! Our tomatoes are on sale today.
Ah, no. That's not...
That voice!
Her voice is wonderful, no matter
how many times you hear it.
It sure is.
Her voice is wonderful, no matter
how many times you hear it.
It sure is.
Now, back to work, back to work!
Her voice truly is heavenly, isn't it?
Th-That's right. Athena's singing voice is the
one thing about her that's really amazing.
Wait!
That's...
Alicia!
Such graceful...
Oar control...
Wow, amazing!
Bravo!
Here you go.
Thank you, Miss.
Of course. You're very welcome.
Alicia is so wonderful!
Back to work, back to work...
You know, no matter how
many times I see her sculling...
She always has such wonderful, graceful,
masterly oar control, doesn't she?
She sure does.
Thank you very much.
Athena and Alicia were both amazing
just now, weren't they?
I really agree.
You're right. If only we had
their incredible talents,
we'd be promoted to Primas in no time.
Yeah.
But I don't think Alicia's graceful
demeanor and Athena's singing voice...
...are things you can get
by just wishing for them.
Those two were bestowed with natural talent.
They're actually geniuses, don't you think?
True, Athena's voice is one in a hundred...
No, one in a thousand.
Well, you could say her clumsiness
is one in a thousand, too.
Is something wrong, Aika?
Being so close to two such
extraordinary Undines the whole time...
I wonder how Akira felt?
But Akira's really, really amazing, too.
That's right. She's the most levelheaded and
hardworking of the three, don't you think?
Yeah, I guess you're right.
We're going right back to practice
once we're done eating, okay?
Right!
You're amazing, Alice!
Akari, you look lovely in your summer uniform.
Thank you very much!
Ah, Akari, you look nice and cool in that uniform!
Yes, it's very cool and comfortable.
Oh, you already switched
to your summer uniform?
Yes!
As always, she's a genius at making friends.
It looks nice on you, Akari!
Yes, thank you very much!
She really looks happier than usual, too.
I am, because everyone could feel the
coming of summer by seeing my uniform.
It feels as though I've become a part
of Neo-Venezia's wonderful summer.
Enough! No sappy lines al...
It feels as though I've become a part
of Neo-Venezia's wonderful summer.
Enough! No sappy lines al...
What's the matter? Aren't you
going to scold her today?
No sappy lines... allowed...
Those two were bestowed with natural talent.
They're actually geniuses, don't you think?
See you, Aika!
Good work today!
I see...
Those two haven't realized.
You can be levelheaded...
...or a hard worker.
But compared to being
gifted with natural talent...
...it's not the same.
Oh! Welcome back, Aika!
Are you still cleaning?! How many days
has it been since you started?!
It can't be helped. I'm doing it
a bit at a time, in between work.
Besides, your stuff is blocking the hallway!
It can't be helped. I'm cleaning, after all.
You're blocking traffic!
You're feisty today.
Did something happen?
Excuse me...
I cordially decline...
I'm... not... going to... help...
You understand, don't you?
Cleaning your room is like cleaning your heart.
It feels great when it's clean, doesn't it?
We're not done yet.
Wow, you look young!
Oh, you found some nostalgic stuff there.
Akira's the only Single...
This photo is back from when
Athena was promoted to a Prima.
Between the three of us, I was promoted last.
Pathetic, right?
How can you...
...say that with a smile?
It was difficult, wasn't it?
It was painful, wasn't it?!
I know you hate to lose...
So it definitely must have... hurt...
Unlike those two...
...I didn't have any special
talent that made me stand out.
Working hard wasn't enough
to make me a Prima.
That's why I ended up
taking longer than those two.
That's all.
Wasn't it hard for you?
It sure was!
After getting left behind as the
only Single, I was really depressed.
But you know what?
They're both great people...
...and they're also my friends.
Their rank and mine were two separate issues.
How can you be so strong?
What is it that gives you the strength...
...to be like that?
Can I tell you an old story?
It was when Athena got
promoted to Prima after Alicia.
Yeah, it was right after we took this photo.
Congratulations, Athena!
Thank you.
To think the day would come when
Athena would become a Prima...
Ehh?
My, my.
Just kidding!
Congratulations, Athena!
Thank you.
Now it's your turn, Akira.
Yup! Leave it to me!
They always say, "Save the best for last!"
Another beautiful day...
I wonder when it started?
My heart sinks when I smile in their presence.
This anxious feeling that I might
get left behind... it refuses to leave me...
Those two really are amazing.
They were born with extraordinary
gifts that I don't possess.
The sky is so blue...
...and so high...
Clover?
Just ordinary, three-leaf clovers...
I wonder if there's a four-leaf?
None.
I always tried not to think about it.
Am I really one of the unblessed?
None, none!
There are blessed, special people
who can become Primas...
...and ordinary people who can't...
None, none, none!
I have no heavenly gift...
...so what can I do?
Hey lady, are you looking
for a four-leaf clover?
Ah, yeah...
If I recall correctly, she's the
daughter of Himeya's owner...
Is there something on my face?
Ah, no...
Of course she wouldn't know who I am.
An ordinary Single Undine like me...
Hmm... Nope, none here.
You can tell there aren't any four-leaf clovers
here because it's such a small flowerbed.
Why don't you give up?
You don't have what you don't have.
It can't be helped.
Miss?
You don't have... what you don't have...
It's all right!
If you don't have something,
all you need to do is make it!
See? A cute four-leaf clover, done!
I like this kind a lot better!
Look, this red rose petal is your heart.
Now you'll be okay, right, Miss?
At that moment, a girl much younger than I
taught me something very precious.
If a genius is someone who's been
bestowed with a gift from the heavens...
...and if my two rivals are geniuses...
...then I just need to create a talent
that excels through hard work.
Yes... I'll become a prodigy!
What a great story!
I guess she doesn't remember.
Makes sense, though.
Aika, you can have that bookmark if you want.
Eh? B-But isn't this your precious treasure?
Yup, and it's also an effective
good luck charm for aspiring Primas.
I'll treasure it!
Ah, Akira, this red petal is from a rose, right?
Yeah.
Could this be where you got your
alias "Crimson Rose" from?
Well, well, I wonder about that one!
Hey, Akari! Stop daydreaming!
Ah, sorry.
Junior, your face looks scary!
You need to smile more!
I-I know...
Geez, I'll do it, so just watch.
Okay, here we go!
Ah, sorry.
No one knows what their talents may be.
But I have something that no one can beat.
I have the best person in the world,
the person I'm most proud of, by my side.
That's a wonderful miracle
that Neo-Venezia itself created...
Ahh! I just said a sappy line!
No, I thought it! I was thinking it!
I'm so embarrassed!
Not allowed! Not allowed! Not allowed, Aika!
No sappy lines allowed! No sappy
lines allowed! Not allowed, Aika!
Calm down, Aika.
No sappy lines allowed! No sappy
lines allowed! Not allowed, Aika!
You're really not making any sense...
No sappy lines allowed! No sappy
lines allowed! Not allowed, Aika!
No sappy lines allowed!!
A shore awash in golden waves
Kin no nami kishibe ni
Filled with yearning, I open my eyes and it's morning
Akogare mezameru no asa ni
As my thoughts focus intently on someone,
Dareka no koto o tsuyoku omou toki
Love rests on my palm, held high
Kakageta te no hira ni ai ga tomaru
A future guided by the flow of water and wind
Mizu no yukue to kaze ga shimesu mirai
I gaze at the hope that surrounds this world
Kono hoshi o tsusumu kibou mitsumete
The distant clouds of light are beckoning now
Tooi kumo hikari ga sasou you ni yureru ima
A shore awash in golden waves
Kin no nami kishibe ni
Filled with yearning, I open my eyes and it's morning
Akogare mezameru no asa ni
And my day begins
Hajimaru
Next Episode
President Aria, since we're closed today,
why don't we go for a walk?
Next Episode
You always go on walks,
whether your shop's closed or not!
Next Episode
That Little Secret Place...
Next time, a Special Navigation,
"That Little Secret Place..."
Next Episode
That Little Secret Place...
Now, please take my hand.