At the time, I didn't have a TV
or a phone in my room.
As a result, I was the last one
to join the party.
It couldn't have been
more annoying.
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, keep going on
Baby I'm standing alone
An unforgettable rainy day
Chasing after your shadow
And it's over, it's like sand now
I sigh every night
I scream like a child and cried
It hangs there quietly, my sorrow
Please, please God, forgive my sins
I don't need to hide no more
Flowing toward the turquoise light
Just keep going on
You've got the chance now
You've got the power
Know you gotta be so true to yourself
I show you my life now
I show you my love now
I show you my everything yeah yeah
You'd better change now
You'd better catch now
Don't ever change so be yourself
I'll show you my strength now
I'll show you my love now
I'll show you my everything yeah yeah
Baby don't be afraid
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, keep going on
Kyosuke! Turn on the TV!
The TV!
What's the matter this early
in the morning?
Just turn it on!
You'll know when you see it!
Did something happen?
REN HONJO'S LOVE LIFE REVEALED!
The guru is on TV!
Hey, that's that cute girl!
Hey, you're right.
That cute girl is just as cute
on TV, isn't she?
I think she's more beautiful than cute.
No way!
Why is my sister's friend going out
with Ren?!
What's the meaning of this?!
- I don't get it!
- You're too loud. I can't hear the TV.
Could that mean the man who got
my sister pregnant is also a celebrity?
She said he works in
the music business, right?!
Who is he?! Who is he?!
How should I know?
Why didn't you ask her?
What kinda parent are you?
The guy got my daughter pregnant!
He must be a jerk!
Damn him! Leave me alone!
So that's it?
You only pretended to be lenient
to hide your jealousy.
Nami.
Let's just hope he works for
a proper company.
He's coming over on Sunday.
Don't say anything rude to him, okay?
Huh?
He's coming over? I can't wait!
Black Stones is a band that Ren
started back in his hometown.
The vocalist Nana,
who was 16 years old at the time,
apparently frequented Ren's place,
where Ren was living alone.
Ren was invited to join Trapnest
just before their major debut,
so he left his band to join them, right?
And the two broke up once
at that time.
Yes. Leaving a band could get ugly
and I hear Nana has a temper problem.
She apparently bad-mouthed Ren
to people around her.
That's a lie!
Be quiet! Whether it's true
or not doesn't matter!
We're going to a commercial break.
What do you mean it doesn't matter?
Oh, Take.
Yeah, I'm watching it.
Why at a busy time like this?
Give me a break.
I kept telling him to be careful.
This is gonna be so troublesome.
What do you mean troublesome?!
That's a terrible thing to say!
I said be quiet!
Outsiders like you need to shut up!
No, sorry.
Outsiders?
So where's Ren?
He's not with that woman, is he?
Is that so? Then keep an eye on him,
so he doesn't get out.
Just make certain that he doesn't go
and see that woman.
Yeah.
No, I'll go to the office right away.
Nana!
Where do you think you're going?
I'm going back home to see
how Nana's doing!
I'm worried about her!
Please don't do anything unnecessary.
But this isn't unnecessary!
Takumi, there's something not right
about you as a person!
If you think that,
then don't force yourself to marry me.
If there's something not right
about the father,
the child isn't gonna amount to much.
I'm a good example.
Just having parents doesn't
make it all right.
If it's hard by yourself,
then go back and raise it
at your parents' place.
And don't worry.
I'll support the child.
In any case,
the way things are shaping up,
I won't be able to come here
for some time.
Do as you wish.
Hello, Nana?!
Could the Takumi you were talking
about be Takumi of Trapnest?!
No. That's not possible, is it?
You're lying. Tell me the truth.
When I think about it,
everything adds up.
Why are you hiding it from me?
That's so cold of you.
Did you think I would tell anyone?
What's the matter?
Why are you crying?
Jun-chan. I, .,
I'm not forcing myself to get
married only for my baby's sake.
I know that.
I really love Takumi.
I know. I'm glad you realized that.
But I thought it was Nobu
I'm in love with.
That's just your imagination.
As long as a man treats you nice,
it doesn't matter to you who it is.
That's not true.
I know that you feel bad for Nobu,
but it's much healthier to come
to terms with your feelings
rather than convince yourself that
you're doing it for money or for the child.
But it was easier to think that
it was for those things.
Why is it that when I go
after a guy,
I always end up with self-centered jerks
like Mr. Asano and Takumi?
Huh? I don't know.
So she loved Asano that much?
Enough to still talk about him?
Why can't I treat the guys like
Shoji and Nobu
with as much care as they showed me?
If Shoji didn't get sick of me,
I'm sure we would've lived peacefully,
and that would've been the best for me.
CHILLS...
Why is she talking about Shoji
at this stage?
CHILLS...
And that would've been the best?
At this rate, I'll never be happy
for the rest of my life!
- Pass.
- Huh?
HUH? PASS
- Pass.
- Huh?
Calm her down.
Come on. Just say something
that'll make her feel good.
Hello, Nana?
Do you have to delay your wedding
because Trapnest is caught
in this mess?
WAAAAAAAA!!
WAAAAAAAA!
Takumi, you idiot! You bastard!
Anyway, come by our place.
We'll listen to your complaints.
What about class?
No, I'll be fine.
But above everything,
I wanna see Nana.
I wanna apologize to her properly
and make up with her,
and I'm thinking about going now
to see how she's doing.
Huh? Go to the apartment?
Right now would not be
a good time.
Huh?
There are reporters at your apartment.
What?
We are in front of the residence
of BLAST's Nana.
Oh no!
I'm gonna be late!
Who is it so early in the morning?
Yes?! Who is it?!
We're from Search.
Huh? If you're selling something,
I don't want it!
You're Nana Osaki, right?
We would like to ask some questions
regarding your relationship
with Ren Honjo.
It's one thing to show Ren's place,
but why are they showing
the guru's home, too?
She's not a celebrity yet!
It's a unique building,
and coupled with the surrounding view,
you can easily tell where it is.
They should sue them for this!
What's Yasu doing?
Isn't he a lawyer?!
Do something about it!
Anyway, Nana,
given what we're seeing,
it's quite possible that they've already
found out that Nana had a roommate.
You could end up being showered
with questions.
It's better if you don't go.
But Nana's...
I understand how you feel,
but think this through.
It would be nothing but trouble
if they find out who you are.
What if they find out about
your relationship with Takumi?
If the media made a big deal about it,
Takumi will end up in
an unfavorable position,
and you and your child will have
a tough time living a normal life.
Please don't do anything unnecessary.
Nana will be all right.
She's a smart girl and
she has her band members.
I'm a lot more worried about you.
Don't go now.
Nana Osaki!
Search... does he mean "Search,"
the weekly magazine?
Please come out for a moment
and talk to us.
We saw you on TV.
TV?
If you don't hurry up and
give us an explanation,
things could get pretty ugly for you.
An explanation?
Is that okay with you?
I don't understand what
he's talking about.
Is he threatening me?
And finally, let's take another look
at BLAST's live video.
Their debut single is expected to be
released soon by Gaia Records.
I can hardly wait.
Nobu...
This program is kinda strange.
It's like they're taking advantage
of Ren's scandal to promote us.
Nobu! Shin!
- You're here.
- Mr. Kawano.
Neither of you would answer
your cell phone,
so I was getting worried.
I'm sorry. I had turned mine off because
friends were calling me nonstop.
Then did you see the broadcast?
Yes, we saw it.
Then I can get right to the point.
There's a car waiting outside.
Pack your bags quickly.
Pack our bags?
Just in case, you are to hide in
a hotel until things calm down.
There's a good chance reporters
will come here.
Wait a minute!
What in the world's going on?!
How come we're debuting all
of a sudden?!
We'll talk about it in the car.
We should hurry.
What about Nana?
I left Nana to Yasu.
I'm sure he'll be able to deal with
the media in a professional manner.
Don't worry about it.
I am worried!
With all this mess going on,
Nana won't be able to sing!
Is Gaia behind that show?!
That's the video we sent in when
we were promoting ourselves, isn't it?!
But that video had been sent
to many places, right?
I hate to say this,
but I can't trust you, Mr. Kawano.
You keep saying things to satisfy us,
but they've all been lies.
I don't think I'm gonna be able
to trust anyone anymore.
In fact, both Yasu and I received
blocked calls this morning
telling us to "watch Morning Seven."
What's that?!
A telephone threat?!
TOO SCARY
What's that?!
A telephone threat?!
TOO SCARY
Whoever's behind this,
I'm not clear what their motive is,
but what's clear is that they're doing this
so the public will pay attention to you.
But who would do such a thing
other than Gaia?!
The only one who would benefit now
by promoting our band is Gaia!
You really are a good person
right down to the core, Nobu.
You don't think that perhaps the objective
is not to promote the band,
but to crush it?
Everyone who watched that
on TV will think it's weird.
You're a member of Black Stones,
aren't you?
Did you watch Morning Seven?
Is it true that Nana's the one
who put that padlock on Ren?
What did you think when Ren left
your band to join Trapnest?
What's going on?!
He's a friend of Ren's woman!
Didn't Nana sell
this information herself?!
It's a publicity stunt!
Taking advantage of
Trapnest's popularity!
SILENCE
Listen, you guys.
If you have the time to mess
with other people's gardens,
try making your own flowers bloom.
REN HONJO'S
LOVE LIFE REVEALED?!
Back to you from
Ren's love interest Nana's home.
Oh, boy. He's made enemies outta
the media. That idiot.
He's so cool!
TAKUMI!
Yasu is really awesome!
I'm sorry that I called him baldy!
I LOVE YOU
Yasu is really awesome!
I'm sorry that I called him baldy!
I LOVE YOU
I wanna be Yasu!
But I don't wanna be bald!
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
I wanna be Yasu!
But I don't wanna be bald!
But look at Ren's popularity.
All the talk shows are talking
about the same subject.
Isn't that nice? It just shows
how peaceful this world is.
PEEVED...
But it's supposed to be about
Ren's passionate love,
but they're talking about BLAST
more than our band.
Oh? You hate to lose, huh?
No, I don't care if I win or lose,
as long as we get attention.
Let's hold a press conference, Takumi.
We'll have Ren tell them
something really cool.
Like "Don't pick on my woman"
or something like that.
Get real.
I'm not gonna be part of
this silly party.
Don't come crying to me if BLAST
walks off with everything.
That's fine by me.
We'll maintain our own pace and
rely on our talent.
As long as our CDs sell,
everything's fine.
You sure are confident.
Do you really think that you're the best
in the whole wide world?
Of course not.
But I do think that
you're the best in the world.
Don't add any more pressure!
- I hate you!
- Mari. Coffee.
Yes.
Nana!
This is the worst.
Rumors are out that
this is your publicity stunt.
Doesn't that make you angry?!
The last thing I wanted was for
my name to be known as "Ren's woman."
If you'll talk to me, I'll write an article
to explain your views!
You're being a pest, damn it.
Nana!
Don't try to be friendly with me.
It's all over now.
- It's all fallen apart because of you guys!
- Nana!
The guy from Black Stones.
Don't dare come inside!
Go away!
Come on. I'm only giving her
a chance to redeem...
Don't act like you're doing us a favor.
Never come close to
our vocalist again.
I'm gonna write about
what happened just now!
If you wanna save the reputation of
the legal firm that's been so good to you,
submit your resignation letter!
Nana.
Are you all right?
Ow!
You idiot!
What are you acting so cool for?!
Think about the position
you're in first, baldy!
It's okay. I don't hold
an important position at the firm,
so quitting won't affect anyone.
But it will affect you!
If word gets out that you used violence,
no one's gonna hire you!
Don't throw your life away!
It's okay. Now I can go out and
gamble to my heart's content.
This guy's a fool.
All our members are fools.
Nobu got disowned by his parents
and dumped by his girlfriend.
Yet he still clings onto his guitar.
Unless something's done about Shin,
he's on a direct path to destruction.
If I don't sing, we have no future.
We are in front of the home
of Trapnest's Ren.
PUBLICITY STUNT BY BLAST?!
WHAT ARE REN'S THOUGHTS?
The person at the center of
this vortex has not appeared yet.
PUBLICITY STUNT BY BLAST?!
WHAT ARE REN'S THOUGHTS?
Moments ago,
his agency has announced that
PUBLICITY STUNT BY BLAST?!
WHAT ARE REN'S THOUGHTS?
they will be taking a "no comments"
stance on this subject.
PUBLICITY STUNT BY BLAST?!
WHAT ARE REN'S THOUGHTS?
This adds to the speculation about
PUBLICITY STUNT BY BLAST?!
WHAT ARE REN'S THOUGHTS?
this being a publicity stunt
by Black Stones' Nana...
Mr. Honjo!
We got directions from the agency.
"You're to fly to England this afternoon."
I'm running away?!
Am I a criminal?
It's for a shoot for the cover
and promotion video.
We had planned to do it in Japan,
but with this commotion...
You'll spend about half a month there,
so you should be able to relax a bit.
The other band members and staff
will be going tomorrow,
but you and Mr. Takeda
will be going ahead.
I'll drive you to the airport.
I got it.
I'll get ready right away.
Things should be a lot quieter
if it's only me and Take.
Um, Mr. Honjo.
Are you sure you don't have
to help your girlfriend out?
If you wanna retaliate on the media,
I won't stop you.
Sadly, my woman has too much pride.
The more I try to protect her
in front of the public eye,
the more miserable she'll be.
What do you mean? I doubt that!
Why do you always do exactly
as the agency tells you to?!
No, she really is like that.
This aggressive change in schedule
must be Takumi's idea!
Mr. Honjo, you ought to do as you wish!
Kinoshita, you're missing the point here.
Music is not fun and games for us.
Trapnest is no longer
Takumi's own castle.
It's a major project that
involves the agency,
the record label, and other companies.
I can't just do as I please.
Being in a band is like sharing
a single destiny.
Right now, the people I must protect
are not the friends
I abandoned long ago.
Nana, please make a statement.
When Ren was invited to
join Trapnest,
was it you that broke off
the relationship?
Did you get back together with him
to take advantage of him?
Ren says he has no comment about this.
How do you feel about that?
Are you happy that you're getting all
the attention according to your plan?
This is stupid.
Say something.
I don't need to say anything.
Ren understands me,
and I know the position Ren is in.
There's no need to make a fuss.
But right now, there's one thing
I must say no matter what.
Please say something!
I won't let them ruin my life.
Just watch me, Hachiko.
I will make your wishes come true!
I hope you'll be on TV a lot.
Let me see you as you continue singing.
Oh, I feel much better now.
I'm glad.
That's all from the home of Nana,
the woman of the hour.
She just threw them a smoke bomb.
The title of the next show
will be something like
"A fearless Nana sends
a mysterious message to her pet dog."
That will take them even further off track.
Yeah, she's fearless all right.
And I'm sure they thought
she was talking about a dog.
You know, Hachi...
Ever since that day,
I was able to get right back up,
no matter how many times
I got struck down...
REN HONJO
THE DARK PAST OF THE BEAUTIFUL
WOMAN WHO STOLE
THE ROCK-N-ROLL HERO'S HEART.
REN HONJO
THE DARK PAST OF THE BEAUTIFUL
WOMAN WHO STOLE
THE ROCK-N-ROLL HERO'S HEART.
...because I knew you were
always watching me.
REN HONJO
THE DARK PAST OF THE BEAUTIFUL
WOMAN WHO STOLE
THE ROCK-N-ROLL HERO'S HEART.
I can't count
how many nights
I wished tomorrow
would never come
To live as I am
without being fake
What do I need
If I don't believe in myself,
what can I believe in
The answer is
too close to see
Black tears are
falling down
I have nothing,
only sadness
I can't put it
into words
My whole body
starts to ache
I can't stand it anymore
on my own