The sound of the waves is clearer than usual,
and the moonlight is very bright.
They gently surround me, filling me with warmth.
It's true...
If you're able to enjoy everything
this world gives to you, then surely...
"Dear Ai, autumn is quickly coming
to an end here in Neo-Venezia,"
"and winter will soon be upon us."
"Because Alice was
promoted to Prima before us,"
"it's just been Aika and I at joint practice lately."
It's gotten really cold, hasn't it, Aika?
Huh?
...Yeah.
Autumn is almost over, isn't it?
Hey, Aika.
Yeah?
Doesn't practice with just the two of us
remind you of when we first met?
I'd be lying if I said it
doesn't feel a bit lonely, but...
...it's something we should
be really happy about.
We just need to catch up to her, don't we?
All right! Let's focus on
becoming Primas, and do our best!
Huh?
Aika?
I'm sorry, Akari.
I...
...can't practice with you anymore...
I'm sorry.
What?!
Why are you apologizing?
Well...
You've been dreaming of this day
and working hard for it, haven't you?
Congratulations on your promotion to Prima, Aika!
Thanks. I knew you'd say that.
Also...
...there's one more thing I have to tell you.
What?!
Do you remember that day
Oboeteimasuka ano hi o
When your heart suddenly began to race
Futo kanjita tokimeki o
The rays from the blue sky were pouring over you...
Aoi hizashi abite
...as you cut through the wind
Kaze o kiru kimi ni
I couldn't look away, and when our eyes met
Mitoreru to me ga atte
I couldn't help but smile
Egao koboreta
It's just like a spiral
Marude supiraare
As the days begin to swirl in brilliant colors
Azayaka ni mawaridashita hibi
Always and forever, they're filled with love
Itsumo itsudemo ai ga michiteita
Surely, it's a spiral
Kitto supiraare
The days passed by, each one filled with warmth
Atataka na mainichi o kasanetara
And before I knew it, off in the distance...
Itsunomanika tooku ni
...there you were
Kiteita no ne
Embraced By That Blue Sea And Wind...
My!
Aika was promoted to Prima?
Yes!
My, my! Well, well!
That's wonderful news, isn't it?
Yes! Her alias is "Rosen Queen."
The Queen of Roses!
So that's the one she chose.
Eh?
For a while now, Akira has been agonizing
about when to give Aika her promotion exam.
"Not only does Aika have to become a Prima,"
"but she'll also have to carry
Himeya someday," she said.
Ah, I see.
I'm sure Aika will be fine, though.
Actually, I have another piece of good news.
A new Himeya branch will be opening
near the Santa Lucia Station,
and Aika will be working there
as the branch manager.
So, she said she'll be really busy from now on.
But, I wonder why?
She should have been really happy
about it, but Aika was in tears.
Akari.
Yes?
Your Prima Promotion Exam
will take place tomorrow.
Okay.
President Aria...
I feel kind of nervous.
I can't fall asleep.
"Ai, my Prima Promotion Exam
will finally happen tomorrow."
"I'm too nervous to fall asleep,"
"so even though it's the middle of the night,
I'm going to go practice for a bit."
"Akari, it's finally time, huh?"
"I'm getting kind of nervous, too."
Thank you for keeping
me company, President Aria.
Calm down. Just do what you
always do during practice.
Huh? That voice...
I dropped it!
Sideburns!
Hey, I'm in trouble!
I dropped it! I can't believe I dropped it!
What happened?
I was on the way back from
my middle school reunion.
And then I realized my wallet was gone!
I even had it tied to an elastic band!
But I still dropped it!
But hey, what are you
doing out this late, Sideburns?
My Prima Promotion Exam is tomorrow. So...
What? I see.
I'll be taking my promotion exam soon, as well.
So I know exactly how you feel, Sideburns.
Let's both do our best!
Akatsuki...
Right!
Hey, Akatsukin!
I found your wallet!
What?! Where was it?
It fell in the restaurant toilet!
It fell in?!
It fell in!
Curse you, wallet!
How dare you fall in such a place!
Stupid thing! I can't even go
to the bathroom in peace!
Calm down, Akatsukin! Calm down!
Stupid thing! I can't even go
to the bathroom in peace!
Calm down, Akatsukin! Calm down!
You little!
Huh? Akari!
You're practicing at this hour?
Ah, yes!
Sideburns!
Good luck on your exam!
You dropped it again!
I hope the weather doesn't turn bad.
I have to try and get some sleep.
Good morning, Alicia.
Good morning.
It's raining, isn't it?
Yes...
Ah, but the sky is bright off in the distance.
It seems like it might stop
in the afternoon, doesn't it?
Why don't we postpone the promotion exam?
This is an important day, after all.
Let's hold the exam another day
when the weather is nice.
It's all right.
Eh?
I've been waiting for this day
to come for a long time.
This is also the day you decided on
for the promotion exam.
So today is already an important day to me.
Akari...
Although I guess it can't be helped
if it's still raining in the afternoon.
Akari.
Yes!
It stopped raining.
So, shall we begin?
Yes!
The preparations are complete.
I'm at your service.
All right.
Thank you for waiting.
Now, please take my hand.
Right.
My, is this?
It's a hot water bottle.
My, my, such wonderful service.
Both the seat and the blanket are nice and warm.
Yes, yes.
Well then, off we go.
Between here and the Canal Grande, you can see
the Campanile in many different locations.
But on a day when the rain has just let up,
I recommend seeing it from this alleyway.
My!
Hey, Akari!
My, my.
This gentleman is one of the rowers
in the regatta. He makes his own oars.
That's right!
Carve out your own path, I always say!
You'll regret it if you don't.
We're going to win it next year!
Good luck!
Gondola coming through!
We've finally reached the Canal Grande.
It's the great reverse-S-shaped canal
that splits Neo-Venezia in two.
Are you cold?
Not at all.
This is Rialto Bridge, a bridge that spans the
entire Canal Grande with its single arch.
It's a place where people crossing over the water
and people enjoying the view cross paths.
Oh! Here she comes, Akatsukin!
All right. Hey, Woody.
Let's go ahead with our plan!
Got it!
Good luck!
Hurrah, hurrah, Akari!
Hurrah, hurrah, Sideburns!
Do your best, Akari!
Akatsuki, Woody...
A-A-Alicia, best wishes to you, too!
H-Hey! Get down from there! You'll fall!
My, my.
I see you gazing up at the endless sky
Dokomademo tsuzuku kono sora nagameteru yokogao
Your long hair brushes your cheeks as it sways in the wind
Hoho ni fureru nagai kami ga yureteiru
Though this heartache can't be expressed with words,
Setsunasa wa kotoba ni naranai keredo
As I always have, both now and forevermore...
Ano koro mo ima mo zutto
...here in this city, overflowing with light,
Hikari afureteru kono machi ni
I'll gather up these feelings that will never change
Itsumademo kawaranu omoi o yosete
Whenever I am blessed with kindness,
Yasashisa ni meguriau toki
I can always feel the wind as it sweeps past
Fukinukeru kaze wa itsudemo
It fades away in the distance, as I gently close my eyes
Haruka tooku tokete yuku sotto me o tojita
Gondola coming through!
We spoke a little while ago, it was a moment full of smiles
Sakki made futari hanashita hohoemi no hitotoki
As the sun starts to set,
We spoke a little while ago, it was a moment full of smiles
Sakki made futari hanashita hohoemi no hitotoki
both Piazza San Marco and the inland sea called
"the laguna" gradually begin to change colors.
These nostalgic, happy days... I'm leaving them behind
Natsukashikute tanoshii hibi nokoshiteku
It feels as though those warm colors
surround us and soothe our hearts, doesn't it?
These nostalgic, happy days... I'm leaving them behind
Natsukashikute tanoshii hibi nokoshiteku
There's just one thing I'm praying for
Hitotsu dake negai o komete inoru no
Akari, your sculling and tour guide
skills have really improved.
There's just one thing I'm praying for
Hitotsu dake negai o komete inoru no
You have your own style,
which can be easily felt.
A bridge to connect our hearts
Kokoro o tsunagu kake hashi
You have your own style,
which can be easily felt.
A bridge to connect our hearts
Kokoro o tsunagu kake hashi
That's very important.
As you cross that bridge,
Ano sanbashi no mukougawa e
That's very important.
As you cross that bridge,
Ano sanbashi no mukougawa e
Thank you very much.
As you cross that bridge,
Ano sanbashi no mukougawa e
Look around, and you'll see the sun-dappled canal
Furimukeba kirameku komorebi no michi
Well then, let's continue on.
Look around, and you'll see the sun-dappled canal
Furimukeba kirameku komorebi no michi
Right.
Look around, and you'll see the sun-dappled canal
Furimukeba kirameku komorebi no michi
If you visit here, come with open arms
Kono basho ni otozureta nara ryoute hirogete uketomete
Alicia, isn't this canal?
If you visit here, come with open arms
Kono basho ni otozureta nara ryoute hirogete uketomete
Yes, it's normally restricted.
If you visit here, come with open arms
Kono basho ni otozureta nara ryoute hirogete uketomete
The blue sky and the starry night will be here to greet you
Aoi sora mo hoshizora mo mukaetekureru
But right now, we have
permission to pass through.
The blue sky and the starry night will be here to greet you
Aoi sora mo hoshizora mo mukaetekureru
Now, let's go...
The blue sky and the starry night will be here to greet you
Aoi sora mo hoshizora mo mukaetekureru
...toward the future that
awaits you on the other side.
Of that I'm certain
Sou kitto
...toward the future that
awaits you on the other side.
Of that I'm certain
Sou kitto
Right!
My heart races like the rhythm of the waves
Takanaru kodou wa namima o utau rizumu
It's really narrow.
My heart races like the rhythm of the waves
Takanaru kodou wa namima o utau rizumu
Narrower than any other canal
I've ever passed through.
As I discover that intangible certainty
Katachi no nai tashika na mono mitsukete
Narrower than any other canal
I've ever passed through.
As I discover that intangible certainty
Katachi no nai tashika na mono mitsukete
I never knew a place like this existed.
As I discover that intangible certainty
Katachi no nai tashika na mono mitsukete
Whenever I am blessed with kindness,
Yasashisa ni meguriau toki
But, I wonder why...
Whenever I am blessed with kindness,
Yasashisa ni meguriau toki
For some reason, I'm not worried at all.
I can always feel the wind as it sweeps past
Fukinukeru kaze wa itsudemo
It fades away in the distance, as I gently close my eyes
Haruka tooku tokete yuku sotto me o tojita
I can feel it.
It fades away in the distance, as I gently close my eyes
Haruka tooku tokete yuku sotto me o tojita
I'll be all right.
It fades away in the distance, as I gently close my eyes
Haruka tooku tokete yuku sotto me o tojita
Ah, I see...
It fades away in the distance, as I gently close my eyes
Haruka tooku tokete yuku sotto me o tojita
It's because the three of us
always practiced together.
If you visit here, come with open arms
Kono basho ni otozureta nara ryoute hirogete uketomete
That's why I'll be okay.
If you visit here, come with open arms
Kono basho ni otozureta nara ryoute hirogete uketomete
From the oar, to my fingertips...
If you visit here, come with open arms
Kono basho ni otozureta nara ryoute hirogete uketomete
I can feel the deep, calm,
melodic waves of the water.
The blue sky and the starry night will be here to greet you
Aoi sora mo hoshizora mo mukaetekureru
I can feel the deep, calm,
melodic waves of the water.
The blue sky and the starry night will be here to greet you
Aoi sora mo hoshizora mo mukaetekureru
Those precious days spent with friends...
The blue sky and the starry night will be here to greet you
Aoi sora mo hoshizora mo mukaetekureru
...are now supporting me...
The blue sky and the starry night will be here to greet you
Aoi sora mo hoshizora mo mukaetekureru
...and firmly pushing me forward.
They'll welcome you
Anata no koto o
...and firmly pushing me forward.
They'll welcome you
Anata no koto o
Of that I'm certain
Sou kitto
Gondola coming through!
Akari, that was a wonderful ride.
It was slow and gentle, as if the
gondola became one with the water.
Alicia...
Now for the final course.
Our next destination will be
wherever you choose.
After all, it's up to you to decide
what kind of Prima you want to be.
What kind of Prima I want to be...
All right.
Say, Akari.
The moment when things begin
to change is so mysterious, isn't it?
Even though everyone is
walking down their own path,
our changes are connected, as if
we were all calling out to each other.
It's as though everything
was fated from the beginning.
Alicia...
Alicia, we can see it now.
That...
That is my goal.
I want to be...
...like Grandma...
...like you, Alicia...
I want to be a Prima that embodies
the Aria Company itself.
Akari.
Yes?
Ever since you came to Aqua,
my world has completely changed.
My ordinary days...
The way I viewed the world...
They all began to shine,
so wonderful and bright.
Yes...
As if a magic spell had been cast on them.
Just like the endless sky and sea
that gently surround all of Aqua...
I'm so glad that I met you.
Thank you...
...my Aquamarine.
Aquamarine...
The distant, endless blue.
Congratulations on your
promotion to Prima, Akari.
Thank you very much, Alicia!
President Aria!
I did it!
I've finally become a Prima!
I've always...
...always, always yearned to be one.
From the first day I came to this planet. Always.
Akari.
Yes?
I have something important to tell you.
A shore awash in golden waves
Kin no nami kishibe ni
Filled with yearning, I open my eyes and it's morning
Akogare mezameru no asa ni
As my thoughts focus intently on someone,
Dareka no koto o tsuyoku omou toki
Love rests on my palm, held high
Kakageta te no hira ni ai ga tomaru
A future guided by the flow of water and wind
Mizu no yukue to kaze ga shimesu mirai
I gaze at the hope that surrounds this world
Kono hoshi o tsusumu kibou mitsumete
The distant clouds of light are beckoning now
Tooi kumo hikari ga sasou you ni yureru ima
A shore awash in golden waves
Kin no nami kishibe ni
Filled with yearning, I open my eyes and it's morning
Akogare mezameru no asa ni
And my day begins
Hajimaru
Changing days...
Beloved times...
Our respective futures...
And so, I move forward.
Final Episode
To That New Beginning...
The final episode, "To That New Beginning..."
Final Episode
To That New Beginning...
Now, please take my hand.