My hometown, where I was born,
is a city surrounded by mountains -
neither too large nor too small,
neither too rural nor urban.
There's nothing special about it
to appeal to tourists.
I'm the middle of three children,
brought up by parents
neither rich nor poor
who didn't pay
much attention to me.
I'm a high school student
about to graduate from
just your normal girls' high school.
When I was darkness at that time
With trembling lips
In a corner of a room I cry
The more I struggle
The more this wound deepens
The broken promise hurt me
Nobody can save me
God, I have only one request
Stop tearing apart my love
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Sorrow tumbling down is your song
All alone with nowhere to go in my life
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Oh baby, help me from frozen pain
With your smile, your eyes,
and sing me, just for me
I wanna need your love
I'm a broken rose
Tokyo?
Yeah. From next week.
It's not a business trip?
I'm being transferred.
The head office needs me
to go immediately.
- Give me a break.
- But...
I can't have this. But wait.
Tokyo is only two hours away
by bullet train.
Besides, I only see him
once in a while anyway.
It's gonna be lonely
not being able to see you, Nana.
I had lots of fun until now.
Thank you.
That happened on
the seventh month of 1999...
minus four months,
when the terrible Demon Lord
fell from the sky, aiming for me.
I knew that this love had no future.
But for it to end so suddenly...
so easily...
It's so stupid, I can't even cry about it.
But you ARE crying!
But... Jun-chan!
I warned you not to get involved.
Nothing good comes out of
a high school student involved in adultery.
Don't say adultery! Makes it sound
like lyrics to some country song!
Then prostitution?
I've never asked for as much
as a penny from Mr. Asano!
You idiot! You should've gotten
as much from him as you could.
So he did it with you and fled.
Jun-chan! Did it and fled?
I'm joking, Nana.
I know you were really serious
about that guy.
Jun-chan...
But from his perspective,
you were just an easy teenage girl.
Easy?! What makes you think
I'm easy?
Many older guys look at
all high school students as easy.
Mr. Asano's not one of them!
From a high school girl's perspective,
if he's wearing a suit,
he's one of the "many older guys."
Why is it that nothing
goes right for me?
It's my name, "Nana."
It's bad luck.
It means seven, the number that appears
in a Nostradamus prophecy,
so it's gotta be cursed.
No, even if your name
was "Eight,"
I'm sure he'd still go to Tokyo.
I've decided. I'm going.
Huh? To Tokyo?
No, to the beauty parlor that
just opened at the station.
I'm gonna change my hairdo
so the next time I fall in love,
I won't be looked at as
an easy teenage girl.
B-But we're graduating today,
so you'll no longer be looked at
as an easy high school girl.
No way! The graduation ceremonies
have started, Jun-chan!
Oh, no!
Thinking back, it would not be
an exaggeration to say
my high school years started with love
and ended with love.
I entered an all-girl high school believing
I'd never find a crush,
until I fell in love with Mr. Okamoto, the art
class teacher. It was love at first sight.
I joined the art club with Jun-chan,
my classmate and best friend.
He-heh!
That's well drawn.
I joined the art club with Jun-chan,
my classmate and best friend.
Thanks to that,
I became fond of drawing pictures,
She's talented in drawing.
Thanks to that,
I became fond of drawing pictures,
but one year later,
he moved to a different high school.
I even had my hair done
to resemble yours.
but one year later,
he moved to a different high school.
I even had my hair done
to resemble yours.
My next encounter was
fashionable Mr. Nakamura,
who was working at
the neighborhood video rental store.
One day, I built up the courage
to talk to him,
Make me your girlfriend.
One day, I built up the courage
to talk to him,
Same hairstyle.
Make me your girlfriend.
One day, I built up the courage
to talk to him,
Same hairstyle.
Make me your girlfriend.
but he coldly brushed me aside.
Miss Customer,
I cannot do that.
but he coldly brushed me aside.
Miss Customer,
I cannot do that.
Then it was cool Mr. Kawasaki,
a co-worker at the restaurant
I worked at part time.
And then the refreshing Mr. Yoshida
who delivered my pizza.
But despite all these encounters,
none of them ever led to a relationship.
I was convinced that
I wasn't attractive enough,
and went on a diet.
It wasn't long after
I was lecturing myself
to first get to know a person better
before falling in love, when...
That was the start of summer
during my senior year.
I finally met him.
Hey, what's the matter?
Are you all right?
Excuse me. I'm fine.
You face is very pale!
Takashi Asano, 29 years old.
Thinking back, he might've been using
a fake name and lying about his age.
It was love at first sight.
A diet?
Yes. That's why I've been getting
these dizzy spells.
There's no need for you
to go on a diet.
You're cute as you are.
I'm cute?
Do you come to
the movies alone often?
Yes! Um, I love movies.
And I really like going
to the movies on my own.
Sure. I understand.
It's the same for me.
But I wouldn't mind
going with you.
Well then, I should be going.
Since you seem to
be feeling better now.
Um, I'd like to return
the favor in some way.
Don't worry about it.
It's already late, so be careful
on your way home.
He's cool, he's kind,
and he's a gentleman.
He's perfect!
Um!
I'm working part time at
a restaurant near here.
I'd be thrilled if you would
drop by some time.
To thank you,
let me treat you to something.
Two weeks passed,
but he never came.
My longing for him kept getting stronger.
Then, on that one day,
when I left the restaurant
after finishing work...
He was outside waiting for me.
The moment I saw him standing there,
I fell so deeply in love, there was
no way my feelings could be stopped.
I noticed the ring on
his ring finger right away,
but decided to ignore it.
I was really in love with him
and I believed he loved me too.
But about the only thing I knew
about him was his cell number.
I didn't know where he lived
or where he worked.
We could only meet two,
three times a month,
and our dates would always
be the same.
A drive, then straight to the hotel -
a low risk course of being seen.
But like a fool,
I still convinced myself that he loved me.
If our relationship had continued,
I'm certain my youthful days
would've gone down the drain.
I've decided to think positively
and believe I was fortunate to have been
able to break up with him.
The local art school I'll be going to
starting this spring is coed,
so I'll be doing my best
with my studies
while keeping my expectations high
for a wonderful encounter.
Graduate representative, Nana Komatsu.
In other words you're here
to meet guys, right?
You're wrong, Jun-chan!
I'm here because
I seriously wanna study art!
That's good.
Because there's no way the guys would
be interested in you with that hair.
No way!
You know, there's one major thing
I realized.
The guys I liked have all
been older than me.
And that's major?
Perhaps things never went well
because they were older.
There are many guys in this school
who are the same age,
so we could have more in common,
opening the door to a love relationship.
She did come here to meet guys.
In any case, stay away
from love at first sight.
Our eyes met.
Me and that boy with pretty eyes.
What?
Why's he coming this way?!
Junko!
You're Junko, right?
Shoji?
That's right. It's me, Shoji!
You've got longer hair.
I didn't recognize you.
It's been so long.
Since we graduated junior high,
so three years?
So, what are you doing here?
What a drag.
Yet another noisy one?
Enough already!
Oh, your friend?
She's noisy?
A friend from high school,
but she's as noisy as it gets.
What's your name?
I'm Nana Komatsu.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Shoji Endo. A pleasure.
He's got a great smile!
I'm here with a friend
from high school, too.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kyosuke Takakura.
He's good-looking too.
The start of a happy campus life.
Right, Jun-chan?
What's that about a campus life?
We're not university students,
just students of a specialty school.
I'm sorry. But not to worry.
I know, Jun-chan,
Shoji's your trump card.
I'll make sure not to take him
from you.
Trump card?
You're greatly misunderstanding something.
I'm just concerned about
your ever-worsening lack of fidelity.
Shoji is nothing more than
a friend to me.
Liar! If you were in the same class
with a good-looking guy like that,
there's no way you wouldn't
have a crush on him.
I'm not the same as you!
I had many guy friends back
in junior high,
but I didn't go around falling
in love with them.
Many guy friends? I see.
Come to think of it,
I've never had a guy friend. Why?
Because you see men as male species
rather than a fellow human being.
I see. That makes sense.
So I need to see them as human...
Okay, I've decided!
I'm becoming friends with Shoji!
Huh?
Is becoming friends something
you make a determination to do?
If I don't make that determination
to be friends,
I might fall in love with him.
Well, if you fall in love,
you just fall in love.
But in your case,
it might be good experience
to start as friends.
Thank you, Jun-chan!
I'll do my best!
Best at what?
Hello!
Oh, Shoji?
No!
- That'll be fine. Then come over.
- I don't hafta become excited.
- Nana's here, too.
- We're just friends.
Hello!
Thanks for having us.
Wow, such a cool room!
You've got it made, living on your own
even though you're from this city.
But my home is far from the school.
I live far from here, too.
You're just too lonely
to live away from your grandmother,
aren't you, Shoji?
Actually, that's true.
Where do you live, Mr. Takakura?
Close to here.
Where exactly?
Behind the convenience store.
- That is close. About a five-minute walk?
- Friends, friends...
You're really quiet, Nana.
I thought you were noisy.
Might you be the shy type?
No, that is not the issue here.
Oh no! What was that?
That's odd language to a friend.
Oh, perhaps you're nervous around guys
because you went to a girls' school.
It is definitely not that.
Nana had a boyfriend until recently.
Jun-chan!
What's wrong?
The more you tell them about yourself,
the quicker we get to know each other.
So, let's make a toast.
I see. They're guy friends,
so I should disclose more.
- Cheers!
I should get drunk fast.
That way, I won't feel as nervous.
Then after that,
the next love at first sight
was "refreshing Mr. Yoshida,"
the pizza delivery guy.
- Refreshing Yoshida?
- But he was really refreshing!
His smile was totally refreshing!
Hey, keep it down, you two over there!
You've had too much to drink.
You know, I gained three kilos for him
because I kept ordering pizza.
Yeah?
But suddenly, maybe he quit his job,
he stopped coming.
I got fat for nothing!
That's funny!
Nana, you're the best!
Nana, don't drink anymore!
It's okay. She's amusing.
So, what's next? Who was next?
The next person was...
So there's still more?!
The man whose name I didn't know.
I thought I'd never see you again.
I never asked you your name.
Takashi Asano.
Stop.
That name can't be
his real name, anyway.
Nana?
Does she cry when she's drunk?
Hey, hey, what's the matter,
all of a sudden?
No!
Nana! Sorry, Shoji.
Don't worry about it.
Jun-chan!
Come on, Nana.
You had too much to drink.
Don't touch me!
You don't really love me.
Don't touch me.
Junko.
I should be getting back.
I don't wanna miss the last train.
Oh right, you live far from here.
Also, Kyosuke's fallen asleep.
You mind if I just leave him there?
No. I don't care.
Thanks. Bye.
You know, Shoji.
You don't have a girlfriend, do you?
Have you fallen in love
with me, Junko?
What's with that face?!
I had five, maybe ten girlfriends easy
during high school!
I just happen to not have one right now.
I knew it. You came here today
to see Nana, didn't you?
But Nana hates me.
She said "no"...
I don't believe she does.
Her first words after seeing you that
first time were "adorable" and " cool guy."
She kept talking about you.
No way!
Well, good luck with her.
What's that supposed to mean?
Where am I?
My head hurts! What's this?
Oh, that's right,
I'm at Jun-chan's place.
- Cheers!
Shoji and Kyosuke brought beer,
and we made a toast, and then...
I can't remember much
but I think we were having fun.
Oww!
But I stayed over
without calling home.
I'm in trouble.
Jun-chan, do you have something
for headaches?
Well, how should I put it,
we spent the night talking and found
that we really get along, and you know...
It just seemed like
the appropriate thing.
Why is she making excuses?
Well, I really liked Junko
from the moment I saw her.
Way to go, Kyosuke!
You said it!
Falling in love is not about logic!
Nana, you're the expert
on love at first sight, after all?
Huh? Expert? Why do you know?
Jun-chan, you gossip!
You told them yourself!
Don't you remember?!
No way!
Look at the time.
I'm going home to get changed
and then go to school.
Nana, you'll be late for class
if you go home now.
Want me to lend you
something to wear?
I told them? What did I tell them,
and how much detail?
Well, you started with Okamoto
the art class teacher,
then Nakamura of the video shop,
Kawasaki the cook
and Yoshida the pizza boy.
You were making a joke out of it all.
No way. I did that?
But Nana, I'm guessing
you still haven't been able
to forget Mr. Asano.
That's not true. I forgot about him.
If I'm making a joke outta him...
No, you cried.
When you started to talk about him,
you broke down in tears
and stopped talking.
Say, Nana, what about Shoji?
If you like him, I'll help.
Jun-chan, are you feeling bad
because you got together with Kyosuke?
That's not it.
Shoji is a really nice guy,
so I think he'd be loyal
to his girlfriend.
He'd treat you with great care, Nana.
I guarantee it.
Jun-chan!
If you were a guy, Jun-chan,
I'd definitely be your girlfriend.
No way! I seriously won't
wanna go out with you.
But it's all right. I was able to become
good friends with Shoji.
Huh?
Shoji's an important guy friend.
It would be a waste
to make him a mere boyfriend.
Mere boyfriend?
Junko! Nana!
Good morning!
Thank goodness,
you look fine today, Nana-chan.
I'm feeling super-fine.
I had a hangover headache
but with a little medication,
the pain's gone.
When did you go home, Shoji?
- She's taken charge of the conversation!
- I got on the last train.
I can't sleep unless
my grandma sings me a lullaby.
Really?!
Well, never mind.
A movie?
Yeah. You said that
you like movies, right?
If you're free this Sunday,
maybe we could catch a movie together...
No.
I prefer going to the movies
on my own.
Having a friend sit beside me
is so distracting.
Yes, I understand.
It's the same for me.
Ouch!
Infirmary
Won't you ever forgive me, Demon Lord?!
Demon Lord?
The lord of all fears.
I've been cursed.
What's that supposed to mean?
You were just clumsy.
Here, give me your hand.
- Ow, ow, ow, stop it!
- We've gotta do this.
- It's too painful!
- Or it'll get infected and hurt a lot more.
It will hurt more?
I'm guessing you still haven't
been able to forget Mr. Asano.
Not only can't I forget him,
it's like an infection spreading,
Jun-chan.
It gets worse as time goes by.
The more I look back on the memories,
the more I start thinking that
every move of his was a lie.
The pain's so bad,
I feel that I'm gonna faint.
At this rate, my body's gonna rot.
No way!
Calm down! Your hand will be okay.
The wound will heal quickly.
Thank you. You're so kind, Shoji.
Hey, don't mention it.
Yeah, maybe I'm a little kind.
Say, Shoji, what should I do
to heal a broken heart?
A broken heart?
I think the only way is
to find a new love!
What do you think?
I agree.
Nana...
Okay, I've decided!
Shoji, where in the city do
the fashionable young people hang out?
Young people?
Yes, youngsters not wearing
suits and stuff.
At the arcade, maybe?
No way. There are also kids
and older guys there.
And it's not at all fashionable.
Then maybe a club.
Bingo!
I will fall in love.
I'm gonna find new love.
I'll stop crying over a love
that has already vanished.
I should fall in love.
I'll fall in love over and over again,
and throw this pathetic side
of me into darkness!
I reached into the sky
But I couldn't reach what I wanted
They grew smaller
and disappeared into the sky
Like colorful balloons
I'm alone
My hand had no place to go
And gently you took it
Starless night
I won't look back
at the shadow of my past
I want to feel your warmth
Tears are falling down
Even if I'm unsure I won't let go
Of your hand holding mine