Don't let her get that back!
What's going on?!
Keep your guard up!
They're not human!
They're...
D-Don't come closer!
Fire! Don't hesitate!
Hey, Yu-chan.
You didn't stop me, so I killed all of them.
It's boring.
They're so weak.
All in all, this is an
unnecessary species, as I thought.
Don't you think so, Yume?
Now my life is blooming then falling
I grab destiny tight
There's no more hesitation anymore
Tying our bond
To the sky waiting for the dawn
Holding you, my love, tightly
I present an unbreakable prayer
We all are still in the darkness
Right now I just
Want to touch you deep in your heart
And give you all of my overflowing passion
I spread out my wings
Toward the future of our dreams
On them are engraved
The feeling you gave me that day
The words of our oath
Will make a miracle happen
My pounding heart, take off now!
My wish can fly high, high up
"Nation of Japan, Capital, Shintou Teito"
- I passed!
- Lt's really there!
- How about me?
- Congratulations!
"Applicants Who Passed the Entrance Exam"
- How about me?
- Congratulations!
Minato Sahashi,
nineteen years old.
Cherry blossoms fell... a second time.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I failed again this year.
Eh? What will you do now?
Will you come back here?
Sorry, please let me think for a while.
I'll call you again in a few days, so...
Bye.
Continuing on, news on the economy.
CEO Minaka of the giant conglomerate MBI
announced that his company bought
up 80% of the of Shintou Teito stocks.
In response to this,
Teito organizations objected...
A company that can buy out the capital city...
What is all that about?
MBI, huh?
The company owns that building, right?
I heard that's the tallest in the capital.
Shintou Teito, huh?
I was attracted to big city
life and came to the capital,
but I failed to be accepted
by the university twice
and I don't have anything
else in particular I want to do.
Not to mention, as long as I'm like this,
there's no way I can find a girlfriend.
Get out of the way, please!
Eh?!
Please move from there!
Ah, it was too high to jump from after all.
Ah, thank you very much.
You caught me, didn't you?
Well, not really "caught"...
She's so cute!
Watch out!
There's no use running away.
Fight with us.
I don't fight, yet!
Even if you don't feel like it...
W-What's that "zap"?
We sure feel like fighting!
- Wait!
- Why, you!
Ouch!
Huh? I tossed and turned in my sleep...
And I ended up in such a place...
No! I didn't do anything!
Huh? Good morning.
Thank you very much for the pajamas.
And I took the futon
all to myself... I'm sorry.
Minato-san?
S-Sorry! You'll change, right?
I'll wait outside!
Call me when you're done!
This is bad! This is really bad!
Real boo-boo-boobs!
It was not a dream after all.
We should be safe here... huh? Eeeeek!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry!
For getting you into this.
Why did I do that?
I could've run by myself but
I grabbed your hand without thinking.
It was very soft...
A girl's hand...
Ah! I'm sorry I haven't introduced myself.
I am Musubi.
Ah, I'm Minato Sahashi.
Minato-san, I thank you again for saving me.
Oh, no! I really didn't do...
What?!
Mu-Musubi-chan? Musubi-chan?!
You fainted because of hunger...
I really, truly owe you my life! Not only
did you save me, but you gave me this...
OK, OK... Just eat as much as you can.
Yes.
But still... looking at her unusual clothes...
What was that all about?
Jumping, exploding...
On top of that, all those "zips" and "zaps"...
Minato-san!
Yes?
I'll tell you the truth...
You don't have anywhere to return to?!
Well, yes... so...
If it's not too much trouble for you,
could you please let me stay tonight?
Huh?!
Ah, eh... I don't mind but...
Great! You really are my savior!
Uh... by the way, you were chased
by somebody a little while ago...
W-What?!
I wish someone like you
would be my Ashikabi-sama.
Ashikabi?
Yes. I've been looking for a long time.
Someone precious, one who I haven't met.
We were all born for our own Ashikabi-sama.
To guide them to the higher sky.
Eh?!
What was that?
Sahashi-san?
Ah, Landlord?!
Is there anyone else in your room?
Ah, it's just my friend visiting me...
Ah, huh.
This apartment house
is exclusively for singles.
If you bring a woman in...
You gotta get out immediately!
Y-Yes.
Minato-san!
Yes!
Ah, you finished changing.
I'm... sorry.
Was I... lacking modesty?
Oh, your boobs... No! I don't...
Rather, I was happy... Oh, no! I mean!
Good...
Well, you better not do that anywhere else.
Minato-san!
Ah, I mean... I'm not saying it's
okay if you do that in front of me...
I'm hungry.
Ah, yes, I got it.
"Skyland"
That was so delicious!
I'm glad you're satisfied.
Ah... she completely finished dishes for ten.
Minato-san!
Please let me cook dinner.
Eh?! Really?
Yes! Please look forward to it!
Ah, then I'll just stop by the bank,
so go ahead to the grocery store.
Do you know the way?
Yes, I do.
I want you to get out...
How can I say that?
Here it is.
"Donnamondas" family restaurant
has now reopened. Please visit.
Please visit.
Ah!
Hey! You're the guy with that cocky Sekirei!
You're yesterday's S&M costume ladies!
Where is that Sekirei?
S-Sekirei?
Minato-san!
I forgot to ask what you want to eat!
No! Run away, Musubi-chan!
Eh?
Too bad for you, meeting us two days in a row.
The capital city's small, huh?
You two!
You are too slow!
Musubi-chan!
'Cause you're with a man,
I thought you'd emerged already.
But it seems you haven't.
Lucky.
Musubi-chan!
Minato-san?
If you do anything to her,
I will...
Eh?!
Why do you protect her?
You aren't her Ashikabi, are you?
Musubi-chan, run!
So, do you wanna die with her?
- M-M-Musubi-chan, run now!
- I... my body... why do I feel like this?
Hey!
Wait!
Shit! He's running around!
Hibiki, let's attack them on both flanks!
That was rough.
What happened to you?
Your face is all red.
Ah, Musubi-chan?!
What should I do?
What should I do, Minato-san?
My body is... getting hot!
Wha... Musubi-chan, hey!
I-I'm sorry!
Minato-san, I...
I...
This is bad... really...
Do you think you can escape from us?
You're trapped like rats in a bag. Now give up!
Ah, Musubi-chan?
Hikari, look!
That's bad!
- She's done it!
- Oh, no!
Who would have thought she'd
make contact in a place like this?
We let our guard down.
But... it's so annoying.
Now that she's emerged,
there's nothing we can do about it.
Anyway, would you die so we feel better?
Let Minato-san go!
You got tough all of a sudden.
If you don't let him go...
Tell me, what will you do if I don't?
Hikari, above you!
Not bad.
I underestimated you since
you've just made contact.
We don't fight against ones
who've emerged, on principle.
Well, do your best to ascend to the higher sky.
We've lost our jobs.
So annoying!
Now we have to find another girl!
What's the point of fighting without a master?
Homura!
Obnoxious guy!
Were you keeping watch on us?
You only go after the ones
who haven't emerged yet.
Do you really think you
can win this game like that?
Oh, shut up!
You're just acting like a guardian!
Wanna fight?
If you wish.
Oh, crap! We'll get charred again.
But that girl seems to have met her master.
A fight between emerged Sekireis is...
Not my business.
I don't get that guy.
Well, there must've been others watching us.
What we are doing is a
battle royale staged in this city.
A noticeable rookie is easy prey.
Are you alright, Minato-san?
Forget that... your chest! Your chest!
What on earth are you guys?
We are...
Sekireis.
Ha, ha, ha, ha! Big bro, I heard you
failed the entrance exam again this year.
Yukari, your voice is too loud.
Well, I want you to send
some of your used clothes.
Yuck! What are you going to do
with a high school girl's clothes?
Big bro, you're completely
tainted by the urban life...
What are you talking about?!
You're wrong...
Oh, whatever!
I'll pick some interesting ones.
Normal ones are just fine. Normal ones!
I'm counting on you.
Dinner will be ready soon.
This kind of thing is sort of nice...
Musubi-chan, then those two...
What are they?
She said they're... Sekirei.
I saw it with my own eyes,
and yet, it feels unreal.
Ta-dah!
Was the TV on?
Wait! Don't turn it off!
Congratulations!
You are chosen as the Sekirei's partner!
Professor!
Is he your acquaintance?
Yes! He's my professor
and the company president.
To think you can't even recognize my face.
You should at least read
newspapers, Minato Sahashi.
No wonder you failed the
entrance exam for the second time.
How could you know?!
There's nothing I don't know.
The Sekirei Plan.
That's the name of the game
happening to you right now.
The Sekirei... Plan?
Do you understand?
In short... Musubi-chan is what you call a
"Sekirei," and they secretly fight each other,
and I am her partner
who is called "Ashikabi," right?
Great! You're a quick learner! Ha, ha, ha...
But... even if I'm told
such things all of the sudden.
By the way, this is a highly secret project.
Now that you know about it,
you are obligated to maintain
confidentiality whether you like or not.
Whether I like it or not?!
If you breach in confidentiality we, MBI,
will bully you with all our might.
So, keep that in your mind.
"Bully"? "All your might"?
Now, I'm busy, so I'll excuse myself.
Wait!
What do you mean "bully"?
Well, take care of yourself,
Number 88, Musubi-kun.
Yes, Professor!
So what do you mean by "bullying"?
Yes, who is it?
Huh? M-B-I.
No! I haven't told anybody! I didn't tell!
More like, you got here too fast!
W-What the heck?
Ah, my clothes!
Oh man! I didn't need to ask Yukari.
Hey! Wait!
I'll be outside!
Minato-san.
I will fight for Minato-san.
And I will definitely win.
So we'll ascend to the higher sky together.
Musubi-chan.
Landlord!
Here she is.
Uh, well... this is...
Get out!
"Apartment Info."
"Room Information"
You are a student who failed the exam,
with no guarantor. And what's your budget?
No way.
That was the fifteenth.
Looking for a room is hard.
Budget is a problem,
but more than that, the guarantor is...
There's no way I can ask my mother.
Minato-san?
Ah? It's fine. It's fine.
Now, let's go to the next one!
We tried more than thirty
and all turned us down.
Reality is harsh, huh?
Minato-san?
Hey, Musubi-chan.
Yes?
Ashikabi... right?
Why me?
I'm not good enough.
I'm nothing special. I failed
to enter the university twice, and...
Someone special like an Ashikabi...
I'm not the kind of person who can be one.
It's supposed to be a
beautiful moon out there tonight.
I like you, Minato-san!
You are special just because you're you.
My special person.
I can do anything you wish for.
I'll break those thick clouds,
and get to the moon...
And someday, I'll reach the higher sky!
My fists of the pact,
shatter my Ashikabi's perils.
Now, let's go!
Eh?!
Whoa!
Let me tell you a story,
from a long, long time ago...
Gods and Goddesses lived in a
place called "Takama-ga-Hara."
One day, a ship with the gods'
treasures came down to the earth,
and the ship was called "Ama-no-lwafune."
But it's an old story.
A faded myth not even written
in the ancient history books.
But the new legend has already begun!
One hundred and eight
Sekireis have been let out.
Sekireis must fight each other
for the Ashikabi whom
they choose for themselves.
And the last remaining one
leads its Ashikabi to the higher sky,
and grasps the fate of the world!
Now let's begin...
The new legend,
a lovely war chronicle,
a miraculous love story!
See? It's as beautiful a moon as I said.
Yeah.
The spring when the cherry blossoms
fell for the second time in my life,
Musubi... I met her.
Feather 1:
"Sekirei"
I think I'm caught up in something huge...
Be confident, Minato-san!
Musubi-chan!
Minato-san is a typical "caught up in
something bigger" type of character.
"Character"? What?
The second episode:
"The Door to the New Residence."
Feather 2:
"The Door to the New Residence"
The second episode:
"The Door to the New Residence."
Feather 2:
"The Door to the New Residence"
Please favor us again next time!
Feather 2:
"The Door to the New Residence"