Kitty, come on, come here.
It's time. Let's go back to the lab.
Ashikabi? Ku's big brother?
Yes. If you're a good girl,
you will meet him for sure.
Really? For sure?
Yes. For sure.
Kusano!
You guys!
No!
No, Kusano!
Help me...
Now my life is blooming then falling
I grab destiny tight
There's no more hesitation anymore
Tying our bond
To the sky waiting for the dawn
Holding you, my love, tightly
I present an unbreakable prayer
We all are still in the darkness
Right now I just
Want to touch you deep in your heart
And give you all of my overflowing passion
I spread out my wings
Toward the future of our dreams
On them are engraved
The feeling you gave me that day
The words of our oath
Will make a miracle happen
My pounding heart, take off now!
My wish can fly high, high up
Feather 3:
"The Green Girl"
I don't feel like I slept
well because of that dream.
Ku-chan?
Ah, good morning.
Mu-Musubi-chan, that outfit...
This is easy to move in.
Well... It's true that's
what they're designed for...
lai Sword technique?
That's amazing!
Ah, good morning.
"Sparkle, Sparkle, Sparkle..."
Landlady-sama!
Ah! Musubi-chan!
Would you please spar with me?
I won't be easy on you.
That's what I want!
A sparring?! Wait!
Here I come!
Wait!
Heh, look at 'em go.
Uzume-san, please stop them!
It's fine, it's fine. Miya's used to it.
Your sides are open.
Ouch!
Your sides are open because you
put too much strength into your shoulders.
Be more relaxed and let
your strength flow naturally.
Yes, Ma'am!
See, they seem to be having fun.
By the way, those gym clothes...
Is that what you're into?
No! My younger sister
misunderstood and brought them...
She's so full of energy...
Someday, we must fight each
other anyway, no matter what we want.
Must fight?
Because we are... Sekireis.
Miya, I'm starving!
Oops! I start work today!
"Safety First"
Okay. Time for lunch!
This is tough...
Sahashi-san, here's your lunch.
The landlady's hand-made lunch...
Wow! This is great, Landlady!
Thank you very much.
Yo!
H-Hello...
Would you... like one?
Yeah? Thanks, man.
This taste...
What is it?
Nothing...
Are you a college student, youngster?
No, I'm trying to be. And you?
Me? A college student,
but in my sixth year...
Well, I don't go to school at all though.
Oh! That fried chicken looks delicious.
If you want to, please go ahead.
Thanks, man...
Seo, you bastard!
Ah, Hikari-chan.
Don't give me that!
You're sponging food off of people again!
How embarrassing!
I'm so sorry. This guy is really...
Oh, no, it's nothing...
Huh?
The lightning women!
My lunch...
My lunch the landlady made for me...
Sorry...
You were the one shaking
him down for it in the first place!
Um... We bought some
bread, so let's eat together.
I'm sorry. Our master
doesn't have any bad intentions.
Your master?
Man, what a small world!
To think we'd see another
Ashikabi in a place like this.
Idiot! Where are you touching?!
I'm their Ashikabi, Kaoru Seo.
You're so annoying!
The abnormally growing plants are to be
exterminated today by the capital and MBI.
What is all this about?
I'm sorry. That idiot e-mailed the
Ashikabis before I was aware of it.
E-mailed?
"There is a Sekirei in the arboretum.
First one there wins."
"It could be you who
makes the Green Girl emerge."
Are you even listening?
Hello?
What about all the effort I spent
watching her day and night so
nobody could get close to her?
Because of that, I may fall from
the number one status this month.
I get it, I get it.
I'll accompany you at work,
or whatever you want.
So please, protect that girl.
I'll do my best.
And tell Minaka: Someday, the fire
that burned lzanami will burn him out, too.
That guy can't understand
such literary expressions.
Then just tell him straight...
that I'll kill him someday.
Another Ashikabi...
So, since you are here,
that means you also got the message, right?
Eh?
Don't pretend you
don't know. The Green Girl.
The Green Girl?
Oh, more MBI...
Hey, we're done for today.
You guys can leave now.
Already? What happened?
It's those guys.
There's an evacuation order for a two
kilometer radius around the arboretum.
An evacuation order?
I see...
Hey, how about we go see the Green Girl?
Oh dear. Dinner's not ready, yet.
Um... Is Minato-san?
Sahashi-san? Now that you
mention it, he hasn't come back yet.
Musubi-san? Is anything wrong?
Ah... Minato-san forgot this.
His cell phone?
I feel uneasy... I've never felt like this.
I will bring this to Minato-san.
Musubi-san.
Yes?
I'll put a spell on you.
May gods and goddesses protect you.
Thank you!
Hey youngster! Let's go!
Y-Yes!
Dear Mom...
I've gotten in with bad company...
"Here / Convenience store /
Bank / Restaurant"
Ah... It should be around here.
Eh?
"Today's work has finished.
- Construction Inc."
Eh?
"Today's work has finished.
- Construction Inc."
Minato-san.
It's like a jungle here.
We got in, but I have no
idea where we should go.
Ku-chan?
You are over there?
Ku-chan!
What's that, youngster?
Do you have a crush on me?
I'm sorry!
She was wearing a
white dress, wasn't she?
Did you also see her, Seo-san?
- Could you see it?
- Nope.
Is she the one inside here?
I don't know.
But I must go.
She was crying all alone. So I must go.
I just came to see what would
happen here, but I've changed my mind.
I'll see you and the Green Girl through.
How flashy...
Who the hell did this? Invading
from the front gate openly like this.
Oh dear, long time no see, Homura-san.
The ringleader herself.
Number 43, Yomi!
You call me the "ringleader"?
That's not nice.
I just came to receive her, since
the first one wins... The Green Girl.
I can't hand over number 108 to somebody
who says things like "the first one wins."
How nauseating! You're just a
rogue Sekirei acting like a guardian.
Akitsu!
Your opponent is this girl.
Now, excuse me!
Wait!
Your opponent is me.
That's my master's wish.
If I don't complete the task,
I'll get thrown away... again...
The Sekirei symbol on her forehead...
Are you... a discarded number?
Ah, it's Kagari-san!
Oh, I made a mistake.
Kagari-san doesn't wear a mask.
I'm sorry!
Wh-What?
Take care of your cold.
Do you have a cold?
No!
If I catch a cold,
it'll be after fighting against you.
How much do you know about Sekireis?
Um...
Since you are an Ashikabi, you
know how to make Sekireis yours...
How to let them to emerge, don't you?
Eh... emerge?
In short, it's the mucosal contact.
Usually, a Sekirei reacts to the DNA
of someone with Ashikabi aptitude,
and makes the contact from her side.
So, under normal conditions, a
Sekirei finds her own Ashikabi by herself.
The trouble is that Ashikabi
can force a Sekirei to emerge.
Even if the Sekirei doesn't want to.
If she doesn't want to?
So there are some creepy guys
who force Sekireis to emerge,
to increase the number they possess.
Ah, um... Seo-san, did you?
Do you think they'd
let anybody force them?
I'm sorry.
If you are the human who
was called by the Green Girl,
and are supposed to be her Ashikabi...
You gotta teach those dumbasses a lesson:
That there's no such thing as
"the first one wins" in destiny.
Big brother?
So this is where you've been hiding?
Now, come on. Your master is waiting.
Hey, why are we running?
I got a sudden feeling that I must run!
What are we doing?
Geez, hurry up!
No!
I came all the way out
here personally to get you!
Stubborn children like
you must be punished.
Ku-chan!
What the heck?
You pervert! Get away from me!
I won't!
Hey! Where are you touching?!
Enough!
Yo, weakling, stay still!
Huh?
Why me, too?
You two!
Hikari and Hibiki, the girls with a
good-for-nothing sponger of an Ashikabi!
Shut up, nasty woman!
He's much better than your
good-looking, smart and rich Ashikabi!
Hikari, that's not even sour grapes...
I have no idea what is what...
Big brother...
We finally meet.
Ku's... big brother.
Ku-chan!
You, perverted guy over there!
Get away from her.
She's the Sekirei my
master's had his eyes on!
Hikari!
Musubi-chan!
Minato-san!
Oh, she's the youngster's Sekirei, huh?
Let go!
It's dangerous to swing
around a blade like this!
Let's break it.
Bam!
Ah! My precious death scythe!
Why are you?
Here. You forgot this.
Did you come all the way
here to bring this to me?
Unforgivable... Absolutely unforgivable!
Musubi-chan!
Nice expression!
Here's payback!
You're so easy!
Ohhh! What nice tits!
Those are too good for that youngster
who is preparing for a entrance exam.
Seo...
Well, aren't you a fine sight!
This pathetic pervert is your Ashikabi?
Impossible!
Such a dumb and dull looking man!
Someone like you would never
understand what's good about Minato-san!
For such a pathetic pervert Ashikabi,
a pathetic looking Sekirei fits well!
What should we do? Back them up?
No, that Sekirei has already
chosen her Ashikabi. This is their battle.
Oh, how embarrassing, how embarrassing!
You look so embarrassing.
Now, I'll take that last
piece of cloth off you, too!
Musubi-chan, run!
Musubi-chan!
Don't worry, Minato-san,
Musubi will not lose!
Here I go!
You don't know when to give up.
Be more relaxed and let
your strength flow naturally.
Let my strength...
...flow naturally!
My fists of the pact,
shatter my Ashikabi's perils!
Impossible... I-I lost... Mikogami-sama...
Musubi-chan! Are you all right?
Yes, I am! And...
I guarded my modesty, too!
Your... modesty?
Um... Is that girl?
Um...
Yomi's presence has disappeared.
Dammit, she's useless!
That's enough, Akitsu. We'll head back.
Wait! Why is a
discarded number outside?!
Seems like Mikogami
failed to seize number 108.
That was a boring show.
We're home!
Welcome back.
Oh dear, Musubi-san!
What is that outfit?
Huh? Who's that girl?
Ah... she's my relative, and I
unexpectedly have to take care of her.
Take care of her.
Ku-chan?
I'm hungry...
Oh my! I'll prepare dinner quickly.
That tree... I met with you there.
It was so strange...
We fell from such a height,
but we didn't get injured badly at all.
It was as if the tree caught us.
I heard a voice... saying "help me."
So Ku asked this tree.
I see...
Then you and this tree saved my life, huh?
Let me say formally:
Thank you, Ku-chan.
Um... Be Ku's big brother...
Please become Ku's Ashikabi-san...
Yo, baby girls! Get ready now!
This is the textbook of love
Don't let it go, don't get upset so
Without false starts, it's show time!
Get the funky beat!
First ones win?
No such thing in this case! No, no!
That's perfect for me
A sudden scramble!
But I'm a woman, I can't lose. No, no!
My feelings grow
No, and then a big bang!
Don't seduce him
Get away from him
My heart is pounding hard, so hard!
Secret, going off by myself
Big success, just two of us
Sweet and dazzling night
To tell you the truth, I want him to
Hold only me, just me
I want to monopolize him so badly
I wonder if I could stick a flag on him?
I knew it, he's so wimpy, what should I do?
He's just too gentle
I love that about him
So we are devoted to him
Dear Sweet Heart!
Finally!
I, Matsu, in order to capture his heart...
Hara, hara, hara.
Deploy the attractive womanly weapons!
Hara, hara, hara...
Ah... Those meaningless reactions...
Para, para, paow...
She is... quite a dreadful enemy!
Episode 4:
"The Strange Tale of Maison Izumo."
Feather 4:
"The Strange Tale of Maison Izumo"
Episode 4:
"The Strange Tale of Maison Izumo."
Feather 4:
"The Strange Tale of Maison Izumo"
Favor us again next time... please!