A customer booked a tour,
and she specifically requested me!
It's time to show how much
you've learned from your training.
Please do your best.
Okay!
If you're ever in trouble, just shift your "wonderful"
power into overdrive and do your best, okay?
Okay!
Or you could always escape
by sculling backwards at full speed.
Okay!
Uh, no...
"Dear Ai, ever since the end of Carnevale,"
"spring has been coming
ever closer to Neo-Venezia."
Welcome back, Alicia!
Good job.
That was really fun!
Here, please take my hand.
Thank you.
"Now that the tourist season is over,
we Undines aren't as busy anymore."
We have one more appointment left today.
Tomorrow, we have one appointment in the
morning, but none in the afternoon as of yet.
Hello, this is the Aria Company.
Eh? P-Pardon me.
Yes, we will be waiting for you.
Well then, I'll see you tomorrow.
My, my. What's the matter?
Umm...
It was a booking request.
And the customer said
she'd like me to be her guide.
Oh, my!
Congratulations, Akari.
You'll have to work hard tomorrow.
Yes! I'll do my best!
Do you remember that day
Oboeteimasuka ano hi o
When your heart suddenly began to race
Futo kanjita tokimeki o
The rays from the blue sky were pouring over you...
Aoi hizashi abite
...as you cut through the wind
Kaze o kiru kimi ni
I couldn't look away, and when our eyes met
Mitoreru to me ga atte
I couldn't help but smile
Egao koboreta
It's just like a spiral
Marude supiraare
I want to spend my days waving to you
Itsumademo te o furitai hibi
This is my proof that I was here with you
Koko ni tashika ni kimi to ita akashi
An eternal spiral
Zutto supiraare
There's a path which stretches on ahead
Kono saki mo tsuzuiteru michi ga aru
When you climb the next hill,
Tsugi no saka o nobottara
Let's meet again
Mata aimashou
That Smiling Customer...
No big springtime yawns allowed!
Right! Sorry...
It's just that I couldn't decide
today's route until this morning.
That customer sounds suspicious.
Eh? How so?
If this person called the Aria Company and wanted
you, a Single, even though Alicia was available...
...there has to be some kind of reason behind it.
What kind of reason?
For example, maybe this customer
wants to have fun teasing a Single!
Huh?!
S.S.
Akari
Big Catch
Huh?!
S.S.
Akari
Big Catch
S.S.
Akari
Big Catch
I heard there are customers
who request Singles...
S.S.
Akari
Big Catch
...just so they can toy with them by making
impossible and unreasonable demands!
If this customer's like that, Akari will be
teased like crazy, and it'll end in disaster.
Wait!
If this customer's like that, Akari will be
teased like crazy, and it'll end in disaster.
Wait!
Maybe...
Huh?
This customer could be
the legendary surprise examiner.
Surprise examiner?
It's just a rumor, but...
...supposedly there are examiners
sent by the Gondola Association.
They ride in a Single's gondola and conduct
surprise inspections on their aptitude.
So, what happens if you fail the inspection?
Apparently, if you fail, you get
demoted from a Single to a Pair.
W-W-What should I do?! W-What should I do, Aika?!
W-Wait! Calm down, Akari!
See you later, then.
Akari.
Do your best, even if your
customer is difficult, okay?
Please try not to fail, okay?
Okay. Thank you, Aika, Alice.
Well then... Let's go practice, shall we, Junior?
Yes, Aika.
I'm back.
Welcome back, Akari.
It's almost time for your booking, isn't it?
Yes.
I'm... a little nervous, though.
My, my. It has been a while, hasn't it?
Yes.
Oh, that's right.
I marked my chosen guide route
on a map yesterday.
Umm...
Found it!
I'm Amarantha. I believe I have
an appointment for today?
Ah, yes!
Welcome to Aria Company!
My name is Akari Mizunashi,
I'll be your guide today.
Pleased to meet you!
Pleased to meet you, too.
Please wait a moment
while I prepare for our trip.
Please watch your step.
Thank you.
Excuse us.
Why don't you sit next me?
Let's enjoy this together.
Ma'am, is there any specific place
that you'd like to see?
Let's see...
I'll leave it up to you.
Eh? You'll leave it up... to me?
I've been a big fan of Neo-Venezia
ever since I was young.
I've visited this city several times, so I've
already seen all the major sightseeing spots.
I see.
So, if you don't mind, could you show me
a side of Neo-Venezia that only you know?
Yes, I'll do my very best!
They're off.
Aika, I thought we were going to practice?
W-Well, aren't you worried about Akari
being out there on her own, though?
Besides, you can leave if you want, Junior.
No, I'll accompany you.
If she is the legendary examiner, I'm really
curious what kind of inspection she performs.
I-I see...
Okay, Junior! Let's get going then!
Go!
Roger!
Ma'am, please look at the
building up ahead on your right.
It's not a historic building, but...
If we move over here...
Please notice the statue on the roof.
Oh, my.
When you're in this exact spot,
the statue appears to be holding Ukijima.
Oh, my! How interesting.
It really is.
Thank goodness!
Akari?
Yes?
Could you move the gondola
forward a little, please?
Yes ma'am.
Is this okay?
Yes.
Could you go in between
those two palina, please?
Of course.
Is this spot okay?
Yes, thank you.
It's two statues now!
This view can only be seen when
you're in between these two palina.
You've been here before,
haven't you, Ms. Amarantha?
Yes, I've been here once before.
But it was fun.
Where are you going to take me next?
Well then, allow me take you
to our next destination.
Is there something special about this spot?
Not that I know of...
It looks like everything's going well.
So far, sure. But the scary part is yet to come.
Junior! Back up, back up!
This pastor is creating an accurate
miniature replica of Neo-Venezia.
It's been two years since I started this as a hobby.
The main island of Neo-Venezia
is finally starting to take shape.
I wonder what they're looking at?
Who would have thought there'd be
a sightseeing spot here?
What's the matter, President Aria?
Oh, is that so?
Last time I was here, you had only
completed the District of San Marco.
I'm guessing it'll probably take me another
five years to complete the whole thing.
Feel free to come back and see it anytime.
Thank you very much.
There are many different kinds
of people here, aren't there?
Yes!
Everyone's a big fan of Neo-Venezia.
Fans
Pontedi
Rialto
San Marco
The Original
Buttered Baked Potatoes
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
Here, Alicia.
Thank you, Akari.
Yes, yes. There's one for you, too.
It's delicious.
Yes. It's the best buttered
baked potato in Neo-Venezia, after all!
President Aria, it's hot,
so I'll cool it down for you.
Here you go.
Excuse me, Mr. Shopkeeper.
Yes?
Have you changed the butter recently?
Well, the shop I always used to
purchase my butter from closed down.
Does it taste bad? I thought
I chose a good new butter, but...
Not at all, it tastes even better now.
Really? What a relief!
Thank you for your continued patronage!
Continued?
I want to eat buttered potatoes, too!
Please restrain yourself, Aika.
But...
Oh, my.
Our scheduled time is almost up.
Ah, yes. It is, isn't it?
Thank you very much for
today, Akari. I had so much fun!
Um, Ms. Amarantha, Alicia.
There's one more really special
place I'd like to show you.
Is there any way you'd allow me
to take you to one last spot?
I still have some time. Please, let's go see it.
Thank you very much!
I wonder what happened?
Maybe... the lady said she failed?
Ehh?! N-No way!
L-Let's hurry and follow them!
Yes!
That's such a narrow canal...
I wonder where they're headed?
How far are they planning to go?
We've arrived.
We'll be going through some narrow passageways,
so please keep to the center of the gondola.
This is the back garden of a convent,
which was submerged and abandoned
when the water level rose.
What a spectacular place.
I hope you're satisfied with the tour?
Akari?
Yes?
What's behind that door?
Umm...
I'm not sure.
Why don't we go have a look?
Ah, yes!
Let's keep going straight.
Okay.
A forked canal, huh?
I wonder which way they went?
This way!
Let's go beneath that tree, Akari.
O-Okay.
Amazing!
But it's still early in the season
for the wisteria to be flowering...
It gets plenty of sunlight here, but...
...notice how it's shielded from the cold winds
because it's surrounded by buildings?
That's why, compared to outside,
this tree always flowers a little earlier.
So that's it!
That's wonderful.
Ms. Amarantha.
By any chance, were all the
places that I showed you today...
...places that you'd already been before?
I see...
I took to you to places which I thought
were my very own special spots, but...
I'm sorry.
Akari.
Right now, my heart is filled with
wonderful memories from today.
But...
You showed me so many places today,
and I was able to feel your heart in all of them.
I could feel that your heart was eager to share
your favorite parts of Neo-Venezia with me.
My heart...
That's what's most important.
No matter how delicious the food is,
no matter how beautiful the scenery is,
in the end, if your heart isn't in it,
it won't be a truly wonderful memory.
What I truly wanted to see today was you,
doing your best to show me around.
I can see you've definitely inherited
the Aria Company's spirit of hospitality.
I'm relieved.
Yes!
Oh?
Aika, Alice!
Um, Aika said she was w-worried about you, so...
Wha-?!
N-No I didn't! You're the one who was
hung up on some legendary examiner!
Um, Aika said she was w-worried about you, so...
N-No I didn't! You're the one who was
hung up on some legendary examiner!
You have wonderful friends.
It was your idea first, Aika.
Yes, they truly are.
What are you talking about?!
Say, Akari.
I'm not the only one who likes to
take tours on a Single's gondola.
Is that so?
The current system of allowing rides on a
Single's gondola for a lower price...
...was created so that everyone
could help nurture them.
In that way, the whole city helps to
raise the next generation of Primas.
I guided Ms. Amarantha
when I was a Single, too.
So did Akira and Athena.
Eh? Akira, too?
Um, did Athena cause you any trouble?
Not at all.
I have very joyful memories with all of them.
I feel that every time a wonderful
Undine masters her craft,
the city of Neo-Venezia
becomes even more wonderful.
That's why I choose to
tour on a Single's gondola.
Seeing you all grow as Undines
is my greatest happiness.
One day...
One day, when I mature as
an Undine and become a Prima...
...may I guide you again?
Yes. I look forward to it.
Thank you very much for today.
My thanks to you as well.
Please come visit us again!
Yes, of course. Let's meet again.
See you then.
Alicia.
I have to do my best
and become a Prima, don't I?
That's right.
"Dear Ai, today I felt as though
the entire city of Neo-Venezia..."
"No, as though all of Aqua
was watching over me."
"She was a wonderful
customer, wasn't she, Akari?"
"Maybe it was Aqua itself that sent her to you."
"Don't you think so, Akari?"
A shore awash in golden waves
Kin no nami kishibe ni
Filled with yearning, I open my eyes and it's morning
Akogare mezameru no asa ni
As my thoughts focus intently on someone,
Dareka no koto o tsuyoku omou toki
Love rests on my palm, held high
Kakageta te no hira ni ai ga tomaru
A future guided by the flow of water and wind
Mizu no yukue to kaze ga shimesu mirai
I gaze at the hope that surrounds this world
Kono hoshi o tsusumu kibou mitsumete
The distant clouds of light are beckoning now
Tooi kumo hikari ga sasou you ni yureru ima
A shore awash in golden waves
Kin no nami kishibe ni
Filled with yearning, I open my eyes and it's morning
Akogare mezameru no asa ni
And my day begins
Hajimaru
Next Episode
I discovered a new shop!
What, what? What kind of shop?
Next Episode
You're acting really childish, Aika.
What, what? What are you talking about?
Next Episode
Those Feelings Within...
Next time, "Those Feelings Within..."
Next Episode
Those Feelings Within...
Now, please take my hand.