In the northern area...
Multiple Ashikabis and
Sekireis are moving suspiciously...
I see, in the north, huh?
Red is heading there.
Don't you mind letting Red
have all the fun by herself?
I'll go, too.
Ah, that's better.
Hey, did the Discipline Squad
exist before I became an Ashikabi?
Yes, it did. It was only
two of us then, though...
The Sekirei of Fate, Number 08, Yume.
An individual Sekirei larva was
stolen by underground operatives!
Retrieve it without fail!
The Sekirei engine was destroyed.
That chick's done.
My unfulfilled wish...
I ask you to realize it for me.
Someday, you will spread your wings,
and meet your destined
one somewhere in this world,
then fall in love.
Yume.
You can't mean to...
Stop messing around!
Was that other Sekirei strong, then?
She was in the Discipline Squad...
Yeah, she was strong.
Then it's a shame she's dead.
Yes, it's a shame indeed.
I was going to kill her with my own hands...
I wonder if Mu-chan can survive tonight.
Now my life is blooming then falling
I grab destiny tight
There's no more hesitation anymore
Tying our bond
To the sky waiting for the dawn
Holding you, my love, tightly
I present an unbreakable prayer
We all are still in the darkness
Right now I just
Want to touch you deep in your heart
And give you all of my overflowing passion
I spread out my wings
Toward the future of our dreams
On them are engraved
The feeling you gave me that day
The words of our oath
Will make a miracle happen
My pounding heart, take off now!
My wish can fly high, high up
Feather 11:
"The Sekirei Symbol Disappears"
Ah, what a pleasant wind!
It's just right for the
romantic departure of the young.
Are you observing, too?
As the Guardian of Sekireis,
I'd like to see the whole story
of this violation of our rule.
Don't you need to help them?
You seemed to be quite excited last night.
That's because if I
go out to help, I can't watch.
You can't watch?
That boy...
What will he show me?
The plan goes like this.
Matsu can only hack the
surveillance satellites for about an hour.
That means we must be done
within an hour of commencing the plan.
You'll make a fuss at the checkpoint
on the bridge and attract their attention.
"Danger Keep Out"
Meanwhile, we'll hit the
railroad's electric power substation,
- This is so boring...
- We have no choice. It's part of the plan.
Meanwhile, we'll hit the
railroad's electric power substation,
- This is so boring...
- We have no choice. It's part of the plan.
And stop the trains.
Enough to so they can't
resume service for a while.
Take that chance to run
along the rail track to escape.
Five seconds left.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Commence the operation!
Musubi-chan!
Yes!
Let's go!
It's time.
Now, go!
Thunderstorm of our pact,
destroy our Ashikabi's misfortune!
God's Song!
What was that?
What are you doing here so late all alone?
Where is your mom or dad?
No...
Wait! She's on the checklist!
She's a Sekirei!
What happened?!
What are these?!
That's amazing, Ku-chan!
Hey!
Yeah?
This has become a really big deal.
Are you sure it's all right to do this for us?
We no longer have a choice,
now that we've come this far.
Sahashi, you might be an incredible guy.
What? Why?
They're doing things
in a pretty flashy manner.
You know what they say: "Fires and
fights are the highlights of the capital."
Oh my!
It appears the winds have changed.
I've just gotten a report that the
surveillance satellite system's gone down.
It's me.
An explosion at the substation?
Don't panic. Report on the situation!
Excuse me, but I'll contact you later.
The checkpoint at the north block...
What?
...has been taken over by Sekireis.
You bastard, how could you!
You knew it from the start!
Takami-kun, I'm the Game Master.
Games are more exciting when
the players make improvised moves.
As the Game Master,
I have but to enjoy it.
Trains on all the lines have stopped.
Good! How about the checkpoint?
Kusano-tan's
diversionary tactic is also succe...
That's strange.
What's wrong?
The soldiers are moving too fast.
In addition to that, their
numbers are increasing quickly.
Emergency alarm!
Everybody, move away from
where you are immediately!
Move away? To where?
Wherever you can.
It's likely MBI figured out our plans.
Ku-chan!
It's so exciting, isn't it, Takami-kun?
Shit!
They've read our movements, huh?
We're completely surrounded.
I'll find an escape route right now.
The three of us can manage somehow.
But... those guys are...
Sorry, our aim was off!
Be careful!
The cell phone's dead!
Anyway, we'll leave here now!
Seo-tan?! Seo-tan! What happened?!
Matsu-san!
Y-Yes!
I'm going to help Ku-chan.
Don't be crazy, Mina-tan!
I can't run away leaving Ku-chan behind.
But if the Discipline Squad is there...
Even though you're an Ashikabi,
you'll be killed without any mercy!
Killed?!
Even so, I have to go!
I promised Ku-chan.
Don't worry. I'm right here.
Please stay with me, big brother.
So I have to go. I'm sorry.
And yet thou hidest thyself in this place...
In the end, thou art the same as those two!
Let's go, Minato-san!
Yeah.
Shigi-kun, go ahead toward the railway bridge.
Matsu-san?
There's a change in the plan.
A change?
The four of you, continue
forward toward the rail bridge, please.
What do you mean?
Leave Kusano-tan up to me!
Why am I so irritated about this?
It's nothing to do with me.
W-What's going on?!
I, Matsu, will save Kusano-tan without fail!
M-Matsu?!
This sound of exhaust!
Didst thou not say thou
couldst not leave Maison Izumo?!
Mina-tan is... that wimpy Mina-tan is
doing his best, even putting his life at risk.
So even I can take a risk sometimes.
Oh, my, that disturbs the neighbors.
Even armored trucks are
out and around now, huh?
You!
Bummer! There are soldiers all over.
I wonder if the other guys are fine.
Everything rests on their luck, now.
This is the bridge.
Will Ku-chan be all right?
Matsu-san told me she'd save her without fail.
I believe in her.
Shit!
Is the tear gas ready?
Yes!
Big brother!
Ready!
Fire! Fire!
Kusano-tan, it's Matsu! Matsu is here for you!
Maa-chan!
I secured Kusano-tan!
Great...
But wait! Matsu-san,
isn't it bad that you're outside?!
Oh well, it's too late to back out now.
Now that I've stepped outside,
I won't end up just running away!
Kusano-tan, please go all-out!
Right!
Fire!
What? A toy?
We'll paralyze the capital,
and sow enough confusion so that Sekireis
will be the least of our enemies' concerns!
An emergency in Block C!
A water pipe's exploded!
Call from a civilian in Block D!
Report the situation! What happened?!
This is Block A. Unusual vegetation is...
I'm sorry, but please sleep for a while.
Incredible...
Now, let's go!
R-Right...
Huh? It's so noisy.
What time is it now?
What's the matter?
It's Ku.
Are you sure it's Ku-chan?
I have no doubt!
They're out just in time.
All right! We're almost
to the prefectural border!
A little bit more, Kuno-san!
Y-Yes!
That's right.
Once we cross there, we'll be free.
I can call everyone now and...
Stop, please!
Jeez, you guys!
Where do you think you're going?
You know that from here
on is the outside of the capital.
Those who try to escape
need to be punished harshly.
These guys are...
The Discipline Squad, number 104, Haihane.
Likewise, number 105, Benitsubasa.
The Discipline Squad!
Shit!
Number 88, Musubi.
I won't lose to someone junior to me!
We'll cross this bridge!
Musubi-chan!
Now we're the one starting the fight...
How fun! It was worth the wait.
Have we been underestimated?
I don't like that.
Here I come!
You're a close range fighter, huh?
Same type as me.
Just as Black told me.
Looks like I can have some fun.
Number 88,
Black has her eye on you, I heard.
Black?
Karasuba! Karasuba!
Can't you tell that from the context here?!
Context? Huh?
A born fool...
Benitsubasa, she's your born enemy.
Rats! It's complete
nonsense to deal with this idiot.
Don't call others idiots!
My stomach hurts!
You made me really mad!
I'll kill you instantly.
Take this! And this! And this!
One down.
M-Musubi-chan!
This inexpressible unease...
Is this what Minato is feeling?
Tsukiumi-san, you are aiming to be strongest
so you can live happily ever after
with Sahashi-san, aren't you?
Landlady! You promised not to say that!
Matsu-san, Ku-chan... even
though they choose different ways,
their feelings of trying to be his wife,
of wanting to help someone precious...
Those must be exactly the same as yours.
You aren't his wife.
Even I can take a risk sometimes.
At this rate, they'll get ahead of you.
Tsukiumi-san!
How boring! I expected she'd be more fun.
Ow! Hey! What was that?!
I told you... I won't lose to my junior.
Musubi-chan!
Hey, let go!
Now, ready, set...
Musubi-chan, are you okay?
That was nothing for me!
Well, you sure act fresh...
I'll show you what happens
when you defy the Discipline Squad...
I won't just shut you down; I'll kill you!
Watch out!
Extreme Quake!
"Extreme Quake"
What was that?
Minato-san!
I'll save you right now!
Is this your Ashikabi?
What should I do with him?
Sahashi!
Today, I won't let you go.
Don't move!
I'll fall. I'll fall. I can't swim!
Minato-san!
Good, good. Stay still.
Don't move.
Pulverizer!
"Pulverizer"
Damn it!
Minato-san...
Your hand...
Musubi-chan, it's enough. Get away.
Musubi-chan!
We, Sekireis are born to meet Ashikabis.
And I... I met you. I met you!
Here's the finisher.
She was so annoying. Idiot.
It seems I was so obsessed
with being the Sekirei I aimed to be
that I lost the most important thing.
Minato...
I'm the real wife!
Landlady, I'm going.
Yes, be careful.
I don't want to become a widow
before we've even exchanged vows.
It's all over now.
What will you do?
Shit!
Musubi-chan, Musubi-chan... Answer me!
Musubi-chan!
Musubi-san's Sekirei Symbol...
Musubi-cha...
No! It can't be!
Musubi-chan!
Clouds drifting through the faraway sky
I watched them next to you
Now, a gentle wind has wrapped around me
No matter how many seasons pass
I want to burn my beloved
moment eternally into memory
Every time you smile
I keep falling in love
Never-ending story with you
With you
Finally, this game is
about to get to the climax.
Will there be an ending to the
game woven by the little birds?
But however things may
turn out, do not come crying to us.
The final episode, the Sekirei of Fate.
The Final Feather:
"The Sekirei of Fate"
The final episode, the Sekirei of Fate.
The Final Feather:
"The Sekirei of Fate"
Please favor us again next time!