What's going on?
W-Who are you?!
Sekirei number 02. The name is Matsu.
Se-Sekirei?
Now my life is blooming then falling
I grab destiny tight
There's no more hesitation anymore
Tying our bond
To the sky waiting for the dawn
Holding you, my love, tightly
I present an unbreakable prayer
We all are still in the darkness
Right now I just
Want to touch you deep in your heart
And give you all of my overflowing passion
I spread out my wings
Toward the future of our dreams
On them are engraved
The feeling you gave me that day
The words of our oath
Will make a miracle happen
My pounding heart, take off now!
My wish can fly high, high up
Feather 5:
"The Water Sekirei"
I'm home!
Welcome back...
Oh, no! Your clothes are all torn up.
Something fell down from
the sky while I was shopping.
Did you get hurt?
No, and I also finished shopping... Ah!
I was in such a hurry I forgot
to buy daikon radishes and cabbage.
I'm going right now!
Musubi-san, that look isn't modest.
You don't need to go shopping, so
go take a bath and change your clothes.
Minato Sahashi, 19 years old.
You're part of a family of four with
your mother, sister, and grandmother.
No data is available about your father.
You got top grades
all through elementary,
junior high and high school
in your hometown.
But you never do yourself
justice in critical situations,
and now you've failed the
university entrance exams twice.
Why do you know about me?
In short, you're what we call a wimp.
But you are my Ashikabi.
Please cool down my
hot body with your DNA.
Huh? Is there anybody in the bath?
Minato-san!
Musubi-chan!
Wow! I can wash your back.
No, um, actually, uh...
Huh? Who is that?
Here you are, my enemy.
You came back 300 seconds
earlier than I expected.
Quite impressive...
but this is within my calculation!
Where the hell is that coming from?!
Musubi-chan!
Special synthetic fiber net made by MBI.
It's impossible to sever.
I can't get out!
I've contained the obstacle, so...
Now let's have love's intercourse!
No!
You don't need to be scared like that.
I'll experiment on you gently.
I was wondering why the bath
was noisy, so I came to take a look.
Illicit sexual relations in the bath
are prohibited in Maison Izumo...
Matsu-san...
Please let me introduce myself.
My name is Matsu.
She's also a resident of
Maison Izumo, and lives in room 201.
Room 201?
Well, just like this.
Th-There was a trick door?
Then, the ghost Ku-chan saw was...
Yes, that was me. I'm living in hiding.
How come?
Ah... some things
happened when I left MBI, so...
To tell the truth, I'm being chased.
Being chased?
As I told you before...
My husband never
refused anyone who came.
This door was also made by him as a lark.
As a matter of fact,
my husband was a part of MBI...
He got acquainted with
Matsu-san because of that.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
Oh, not at all!
But since she caused such trouble...
I may have to take steps...
"Kick out, Kick out, Kick out..."
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I will never
do it again! Forgive me, Miya-tan!
Do you really mean it?
Yes, I really, really mean it.
Everyone, I'm very sorry.
Now, please excuse me...
Ghost...
How did it go?
Me too. I looked and looked, but...
To think some ordinary passerby took him!
What can I say to Master?
A Sekirei and Ashikabi
led by their fate properly...
are brought together even
though they don't intend to be.
You are...
That's why their bond is valuable.
Ignoring that and making Sekireis
emerge like they're some collection
is nothing but bad taste!
Mind your own business!
I know that you are a
Sekirei not yet emerged!
Do it, Akitsu!
The discarded number... you again.
I missed number 107,
but maybe I can take you instead.
Master will force you to emerge
and become his submissive Sekirei!
Good grief...
You cannot beat me.
I'll let you owe me one for today.
Akitsu!
Wait!
I brought him to my room on impulse...
What should I do?
Man, though, he really is cute...
A small face!
Slender hips!
And even more, he's wearing short pants!
Um...
Yes?!
I'm sure... I'm your Sekirei.
Please give me your... seal.
I used my full power only for
a short time... Damn this body!
Well, there's no help for it.
I gotta ask Takami-san to retrieve me...
If this goes on, maybe
I'll be all ash in the morning...
Self-cremation, huh? I don't like that...
For shame, Homura!
Tsukiumi...
Thou shalt be defeated by me.
I shall not permit thee to die thyself.
You are so cool, Tsukiumi.
But you're showing off your panties.
Bastard! How dare thee!
Sekireis can bring out their
true powers only when emerged.
Why don't you get emerged?
Never mind me, what about thyself?
Ah, I'm defective...
Ever since the ages of myth,
those who belong to fire have
been abhorrent to the gods.
You are trying to be
the strongest, aren't you?
Then, you'd better find
your Ashikabi soon, and...
Don't say such absurd things!
Ashikabis are only lowly monkeys!
For such a thing to co... co...
Co?
Couple with me! I won't accept it!
I will never ever accept that!
But... I feel a bit strange lately.
I keep having a blazing
feeling deep in my chest.
- That is...
- I know!
If this is a reaction toward
an Ashikabi, it's opportune.
I will find that human,
and execute him by my own hand!
"...my Ashikabi."
That's definitely what she said.
Who is it?
Ku-chan?
Whoa! You again?!
I made a blunder...
I forgot about the... important ceremony...
Next time, please let me
experiment on you properly.
For many years to come...
"Night crawling" is also
prohibited in Maison Izumo!
As a penalty, no breakfast for Matsu-san.
Eh?! Miya-tan, please forgive me!
Or for you, Sahashi-san.
Wh-Why me, too?
The treatment of the arboretum
was handled very well by number 107,
whom we just released.
The event I prepared ended
more plainly than I expected.
I was expecting...
more of a fierce battle to the death.
It seems like over 90%
of Sekireis have emerged.
It's the time.
Minaka, you bastard! You seriously
mean to make this capital into...
Now, how will the pages
of the next myth begin?
Let's look forward to
that with keen interest!
"Boing"
"Jiggle"
I will die...
If I have more Sekireis, I will die!
"Smirk"
Good morning, Mi-na-to.
Now, for a morning kiss...
This isn't Minato-san...
Good morning.
What would happen
if Sekireis paired with each other?
She's a pervert...
I no longer need to eat in hiding.
Having breakfast with
everyone is the best.
Huh? Where's Uzume-san?
She's still asleep.
She often comes home late these days.
Is she working?
Here, open your mouth.
I can do it by myself.
You can't hold chopsticks, can you?
Here.
M-Miya, I told you I don't like spinach...
Kagari-san, what happened to your hands?
Well... it's more like whole body...
I just got a little burned.
Looks like you can't read my moves yet.
That was interesting.
Do it again, please!
Yes.
Who?
Who are you?
I have, at last, found thee.
I shall kill thee!
A dream...
Ah, I'm sorry. I woke you up.
"You've got mail"
"Inbox / One New Mail 14:35
From: Yukari
Subject: None
"I have some stuff to take care of"
"Inbox / One New Mail 14:35
From: Yukari
Subject: None
"I have some stuff to take care of"
It's just Yukari.
"I have some stuff to take care of
so I may visit you later than I thought...
I'll write you again soon.
Say hi to Musubi-chan!"
She never changes...
Anyway, that dream I had...
It was the same feeling
I had when I met Ku-chan...
Right! Matsu-san might know something.
I have many more questions I want
to ask her... like about the Sekirei Plan.
The Sekirei Plan.
That's the game that releases
108 Sekireis into the capital
and lets them fight with their chosen
Ashikabis until there is only one left.
The game master is Hiroto Minaka,
a monster who rules the
giant global conglomerate MBI.
As long as we stay in here,
Shintou Teito, which is MBI's stronghold,
Sekireis and their Ashikabis cannot
escape from the Sekirei Plan's system.
Letting the released Sekireis emerge was
more important than fighting until now, but...
Most Sekireis have already
emerged at this point in time, so...
The main event of the game finally starts.
The main event?
In other words, the battle
royale between Sekireis to survive.
And the Ashikabi who's the
partner of the last one remaining
will be awarded a lavish reward from MBI.
Matsu-san.
Can I... do anything?
I couldn't care less
about the reward or whatever...
But...
Can a guy like me do anything to prevent
everyone from disappearing like that?
Don't worry.
I, Matsu, am here for you.
Matsu-san...
After all, Mina-tan, you're the
Ashikabi who made even me emerge.
Be more confident about yourself.
Oh, right!
So, that woman told you she'd kill you?
Her appearance?
Uh... Long hair,
black dress, and a scary face.
You met Kusano-tan in a dream, right?
Yup.
There is nothing strange about a Sekirei
who is reacting to a specific Ashikabi like that
being connected with him unconsciously.
Especially when you are an Ashikabi
who's already made three emerge.
Wh-What do you mean?
An Ashikabi gains more
power as he gains more Sekireis.
Thus, it's now highly possible
that stronger Sekireis will react to you.
Is that so?
Mina-tan, can this be the
girl you saw in the dream?
"Tsukiumi"
Mina-tan, can this be the
girl you saw in the dream?
Ah, yes, yes. She's the one!
That's bad.
To be frank,
this person is really dangerous.
The worst!
Number 09, Tsukiumi.
She's a Sekirei with water powers,
and she's infamous for
her hatred toward Ashikabi.
Huh?
If she did react to you...
It would have hurt her pride badly.
I shall kill thee!
What should I do?!
To survive the game, we
must strengthen our party, but...
Number 09 the
Ashikabi hater, of all people?
You'll be fine.
Musubi-chan!
Minato-san will be fine.
Musubi-chan...
What's that?
The landlady is... really strong.
Ouch.
I'll go looking for the person in the dream.
I'll get her to join us somehow.
I'll do my best.
"Kill, Kill, Kill, Kill..."
But you might get killed.
Matsu-san!
Minato-san, I'm sure you can
come to an understanding with her.
With your words and... fists!
What do you mean, fists?
I got it.
As a start, I'll search for her with
the surveillance satellites from here.
"Capital Map"
As a start, I'll search for her with
the surveillance satellites from here.
"Capital Map"
Musubi-tan, you'll look where the satellites
can't reach, using your physical strength.
"Capital Map"
Yes!
Mina-tan, you make
yourself appear as bait.
Bait?!
Sekireis know when the
Ashikabi they're reacting to is nearby.
If number 09 lives up to her reputation,
she will come to kill you.
I see... she'll come to kill me, huh?
So, Kusano-tan, you'll guard him, please.
Guard me?
Now then!
It's called the "Thrilling Kill-or-Be-Killed
Sekirei Hunting Mission of Love"!
Now let's go!
Kill-or-be-killed, huh?
Ku-chan!
Good job, youngster!
S-Seo-san!
This feeling...
It's getting stronger every day.
Damn you! A plague on thee, Ashikabi!
I'll find thee for sure and
kill thee with my own hands!
What do you feel?
You are a pre-emerged Sekirei, aren't you?
I've heard of you: Twin Sekireis
who target only pre-emerged Sekireis.
Despicable villains!
Do ye want to win like that?!
What did you call me?!
No, we aren't interested in those things.
We only want to get Sekireis out
of this game before they emerge.
Very well! I was feeling irritated anyway.
Come on!
What are you so proud of?
Lightening bolt!
Thou art... at this level?
Crap! She's pretty strong.
Water Celebration!
Hikari! I think she's number 09, Tsukiumi.
What? A single number?!
You were looking for a cat?
Yeah, though I figured if it got away,
I could trick the client with a look-alike.
Oh man! You saved me!
Huh? You added more Sekireis, didn't you?
How could you know that?
And that feeling...
Matsu in Maison Izumo, right?
You knew about Matsu-san?
Idiot. I'm the one who
made that hidden door.
Takehito asked me to.
Takehito-san is... the landlady's?
Takehito Asama... He was my best friend.
Seo!
Yo! I found our money-spinner!
We don't need to worry about
food for the next three days or so...
It's not the time for that!
- We are being chased
by a troublesome one!
- That man over there!
Thou art in my way! Move!
Monkey!
I told thee to get out of my...
What is this ghoulish feeling
crawling around all over my body?!
No! This mass of heat!
Th-This person!
Thou!
Couldst thou be my...
Our meeting here spells thy doom.
Before thou canst violate my body,
I shall obliterate thee!
Th-This is going exactly like the dream!
Yo, baby girls! Get ready now!
This is the textbook of love
Don't let it go, don't get upset so
Without false starts, it's show time!
Get the funky beat!
First ones win?
No such thing in this case! No, no!
That's perfect for me
A sudden scramble!
But I'm a woman, I can't lose. No, no!
My feelings grow
No, and then a big bang!
Don't seduce him
Get away from him
My heart is pounding hard, so hard!
Secret, going off by myself
Big success, just two of us
Sweet and dazzling night
To tell you the truth, I want him to
Hold only me, just me
I want to monopolize him so badly
I wonder if I could stick a flag on him?
I knew it, he's so wimpy, what should I do?
He's just too gentle
I love that about him
So we are devoted to him
Dear Sweet Heart!
How come our Ashikabi is such trash?
He's undependable,
and lazy, and... I could go on and on.
Hey! I lost all the money I earned
today at pachinko. Ah, sorry, sorry!
Don't give us that crap!
Episode 6: "Maison Izumo Flower War."
Feather 6:
"Maison Izumo Flower War"
Episode 6: "Maison Izumo Flower War."
Feather 6:
"Maison Izumo Flower War"
Favor us again next time...
Feather 6:
"Maison Izumo Flower War"
Did I have to say that?