I didn't have the energy to
come up with excuses
like the bed was too small
or that I forgot my wallet.
When I was unbearably lonely,
it wasn't Ren...
who I wanted to have by my side.
Blinking eyes call the wind
A smile clears all the noise away
The angel in your eyes whispers
"Everything begins now"
Can you feel it now
It's like being caught in a wave
Pulling on my heart
Breath held, arms reaching out
Baby this world is
different from yesterday's
You're the only one I can see
Baby my wish on a wing
This sky is torn
By a single overflowing word
Wow!
What a great vocalist!
Where'd you find her?
She's Ren's girl, isn't she?
Yeah. But before that,
she was Nobu's classmate, and...
She's great!
She's got the looks,
and a great voice. She is so cool.
I really think you've got a chance.
I finally understand what made you
decide to go pro, Yasu.
You had this secret weapon.
Well, I'm not so confident
we'll make it that big, but...
Well, depending on how it's done,
Nana's got potential to be
a great solo artist.
Are you at all serious
about doing this?
Who could it be this late at night?
Reira? A new scandal uncovered?!
Maybe it's a neighbor complaining
about the noise.
Huh? Isn't this place soundproof?
What's the point of having
your drums here then.
Hello. I'm sorry for making
all this noise.
Yasu, .,
Who is it?!
What's the matter?
Yasu, I'll be going home.
Yeah. Sorry.
No, it's okay.
Thanks for your time.
NAOKI
GREAT SCOOP!
Great Scoop!
NAOKI
GREAT SCOOP!
REN's WOMAN CAME To
YASU'S PLACE CRYING!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
KYAAAAA! A PAPA-RAKKYO!!
REN'S WOMAN CAME TO
YASU'S PLACE CRYING!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
KYAAAAA! A PAPA-RAKKYO!!
Ren's woman came to
Yasu's place crying!
REN'S WOMAN CAME TO
YASU'S PLACE CRYING!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
KYAAAAA! A PAPA-RAKKYO!!
REN'S WOMAN CAME TO
YASU'S PLACE CRYING!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
KYAAAAA! A PAPA-RAKKYO!!
What's going on? Kyaaaaaaaa
A papa-rakkyo!!
Takumi got Hachi pregnant!
It's gotta be Takumi's kid!
Hachi said he would do it
without a condom!
What?! Doing it without
any protection is inexcusable!
DIZZY
She's being a tattletale.
It's open.
Nana, are you asleep?
Nana...
I'm coming in.
Nana!
Don't scare me like that, damn it!
I told you, I'm a sensitive man.
And where's Nobu?
HACHIKO & NOBUO
Do you love him that much?
Didn't you break up with him?
Please make up an excuse.
I don't care if it's a lie.
I'll believe you.
Who could it be at this hour?
I can only think of two insolent people
who would come by someone's place
in the middle of the night unannounced.
Yeah. I wonder which one it is.
Yes? Which one is it?
WHICH ONE?
Jun-chan.
I was suffering so badly...
I could barely breathe.
Before I knew it, I was here.
I poured my entire heart out,
but I'm not sure
whether or not I was able to
explain myself well enough.
Why do I want Hachi so much?
Why do I hate Takumi so much?
I don't even know myself.
Nobu said that I'm strange.
Am I strange?
What's a friend supposed to do
at a time like this?
I want to become...
normal friends with Hachi.
Yasu listened to everything
I said without saying a word.
He might've said something
to comfort me from time to time.
To be honest, I don't remember.
But I remember...
for some reason,
being enveloped by the sweet smell
of Black Stone calmed me down.
Kyosuke, don't smoke!
Oh, right. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Kyosuke.
No, it's okay.
I mean, guys are pathetic.
We don't know what to do
at a time like this.
How come you're nervous?!
Well, you're right,
but it makes me feel bad.
On the other hand...
Takumi, was it?
From what I hear from you,
he seems to be almost too manly
and decisive about this.
I'm impressed.
Really? To me, he just sounds like
some coercive guy thinking only of himself!
You think so?
Think about it.
He used Nana's cell phone to
call Nobu out of the blue
and talk to him about this.
It's natural for Nobu to be
overly suspicious of Nana and quail.
He's trying to take away
Nobu's will to fight for Nana
and encourage him to withdraw.
On top of that, he locked himself
in Nana's room so she couldn't interfere.
If he was really thinking of Nana,
he wouldn't have taken such actions.
He's the type of person who would
manipulate others without thinking twice
about it if it's for his own good.
If he really planned all that
on the spur of the moment,
he's an extremely clever guy.
In a way, I'm impressed.
I'm pretty sure Takumi didn't give it
that much thought.
It's because I told him that
Nobu's my boyfriend,
so he simply did it outta jealousy.
Oh, isn't that nice.
It's just that he has a lot of pride.
You call that pride?
Huh?
If those are his true feelings,
then he's as immature as a kid
whose toy's been taken away.
- You may be right.
- Really?
SCALE
- You may be right.
- Really?
Oh well, in any case,
he's gotta be pretty serious about this
to say he'll be the child's guardian.
If he was a classmate of Yasu,
then that would make him 23 or 24, right?
Is he financially sound?
What does he do?
He's a musician.
Is that not a concern?!
Does he make any money?!
Why are you keeping quiet?
Well, if he said he'll be the guardian
without hesitation,
he's gotta be somewhat
financially sound.
I actually don't like the way
he used the word "guardian."
That's almost like saying,
"I'll pay child support."
But I think that's what he meant.
Huh?
What the hell?!
Why won't he marry you?!
Does he have a wife and kids?
Is this another extramarital affair?
No. But getting married would
be a great burden to him.
I couldn't impose on him like that.
I don't get you!
Are you okay with that?!
That's good enough for me.
So you wanna have this baby
that much?
At first, I hoped that it was
just my imagination.
I was escaping from myself,
trying not to think about it.
But there were signs,
so I became more and more anxious.
So when the test showed positive,
it scared me because it was like
I no longer had anywhere to escape.
I thought, if I really am pregnant,
I should get an abortion right away.
I could keep the abortion a secret
from everyone,
and continue on with my life...
as if nothing had happened.
But then at the hospital,
I realized that there was, in fact,
a child living inside me.
It was like reality suddenly
struck me.
OBSTETRICS AND GYNECOLOGY
NAKAZATO CLINIC
I thought to myself that
OBSTETRICS AND GYNECOLOGY
NAKAZATO CLINIC
I would never wanna have an abortion
and pretend nothing happened.
I no longer had a sense of fear
or anxiety.
All I could think about then was
that I had to pull myself together.
I don't know how to say it, but...
like, I felt that I'm the only one who
can protect the life of the child inside me.
I thought about the possibility of
giving birth
and raising the child on my own.
But I don't have any money.
In addition, I can't work because
my morning sickness is so bad.
I was at a complete loss,
thinking that there's no way
I'm gonna make it.
So when Takumi said
what he did to me,
it surprised me,
but it made me really happy.
Maybe I shouldn't be relying
on him, but...
No, there's nothing wrong with that.
It's most likely his child, right?
Nobu was using protection
at all times, right?
So chances of the child
being his are low.
It's a horrible situation, isn't it?
Nobu always used protection.
And he treated me like
I was so precious.
But I'm trampling all over that
and am running to Takumi
to have the baby.
Can someone so selfish be forgiven?
Well, Nobu may never forgive you.
Given the circumstances,
it appears that he believes
you were dating them both
at the same time.
No, I think she needs to resolve
this misunderstanding.
But how? There's no proof.
I don't think he'll believe
her explanations.
What I'm saying is,
from Nobu's perspective,
he probably wanted her to explain things
just to show that she cares.
That could even light a flame
to his fighting spirit,
and he'll say,
"I'll take care of everything."
For Nobu's sake, he may be better off
not having such a flame lit.
Because you can't raise a kid
on love alone.
He'd no longer be in a position
to dream about his band succeeding.
He might hafta give up his dream
and take over his family inn.
I'll do everything I can
to make you happy.
It's one thing if the child were his
without a doubt.
He's only twenty, right?
It would be too cruel to have
his future decided in this way.
And that's why you felt it's not right
to rely on Nobu, right, Nana?
I guess it's not something
you could say to him.
Nana, you really are seriously
in love with Nobu.
She's Nobu's girlfriend,
but she's also a follower of BLAST.
The success of the guru and her group
is her dream as well.
Life doesn't always go
as planned, does it?
Maybe there really is a Demon Lord.
What are you saying?!
It's Nana's fault for not insisting
on protection!
And also for doing it with Nobu right after
without any decent break in between!
Your tendency to get carried away
in your foolish actions
has finally caught up with you!
Do you understand that?!
This is not the time
to be lecturing her.
This is about the only time
Nana will listen to me!
DON'T SPOIL HER!
This is about the only time
Nana will listen to me!
Do you really understand that
you can't have a normal happy family
with a guy who won't marry you?
Uh-huh.
Then you'd better be faithful to
that man for the rest of your life.
You are prepared to properly break up
with Nobu and give him up, are you?
I want to hear your answer!
Yes!
Even if the child is Nobu's,
you will have no problem raising
the child as Takumi's, will you?
Keep in mind that even if Takumi
becomes the child's guardian,
whether he'll love the child or not
is a different issue.
Yes.
Okay. If you wanna have it that bad,
I won't stop you.
As long as you never forget
that determination you have.
Yes.
Now that you've made that commitment,
I don't wanna ever see you
crying over this.
I pity a kid who has to put up
with such a gloomy mother.
Try to be like your own mother.
Bye. I'm really grateful for everything,
Jun-chan, Kyosuke.
I feel much better now that I had
you hear what I had to say.
I'll be in touch.
At the least, take good care
of your body.
Stay well.
Mhm.
I wonder if she really plans to have it.
It not only affects the rest
of Nana's life,
this is also about the life of a child.
I'm so worried I'm getting
a stomachache.
But Nana came to
that decision herself,
so we really don't have the right
to interfere with that decision.
The best we can do now is
just to support her.
I guess you're right.
Nana's dream was to become
a normal housewife.
If she had an abortion and things
went well with Nobu,
her dream might have come true
in the near future.
But she's sacrificing that to
have this baby.
She must be really determined.
But as her father, I would've loved
to see Nana in a wedding dress.
Father, you say?
FATHER
Why won't Takumi take Nana
as his wife?
Probably because Nana's harder
to take care of than the child.
I see.
Huh? My keys...
Nana!
Oops, I fell asleep.
Welcome home.
Where did you go leaving
the door unlocked?
I was worried.
Did you talk things over with Nobu?
Ah, yes.
Sorry. I thought you had gone home.
I went shopping.
Want some grapefruit juice?
Damn! I should've put it
in the fridge.
Yasu, you mind if I have one?
Go ahead.
Smoking's so tough to quit.
It's unlike me to try and
be stoic about it.
It's stressing me out in other areas.
That's right. There's not much meaning
for you to quit smoking,
so don't force yourself.
Isn't it more proper for you
to tell me to quit
because it's bad for my health?
I can't tell someone to do anything
I can't do myself.
Does it taste good?
It's terrible.
I should be heading back.
The first train will be running shortly.
Huh?
Sorry for intruding when Naoki
was here.
Are you dating him?
No.
Somehow I think
he got the wrong idea,
but tell him I said hi.
Are you all right, Nana?
Huh? What about?
You idiot! I'm not that broken.
Don't worry. I'll be fine.
I don't really know
what a normal friendship is, but...
No matter what Hachi decides to do,
I won't get in the way
and I'll gently watch over her.
Exactly like you're doing with me.
It's not as easy as it sounds.
I'm sorry, Yasu. Thank you.
Don't worry.
Everything will be fine.
Because Hachi and I are both women.
But maybe that's why it's so difficult.
I begin recording today.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
We start in the afternoon.
But we'll be confined to
the studio for at least a week.
So before I go, could you
let me know what you decided?
As things are, I'd feel so restless
I wouldn't be able to keep
my mind on work.
Sorry for being so pushy.
I wanna have this child and raise it
as your child, Takumi.
If it's okay with you.
Wanna get married?
Huh?
You don't wanna raise it
as an illegitimate child, do you?
If the public finds out, it'll look bad
no matter how we spin it.
But if we get married,
there shouldn't be a problem.
Besides, if I marry an ordinary girl
the media won't go too crazy
over this.
No?
No matter what path in life
you take with who,
as long as you're happy,
then that's fine with me.
I may never become a person
who can wish for that from
the bottom of my heart...
But I wanted to appear strong
and graceful in your eyes.
Like a manga heroine,
who's too perfect to be real.
I can't count
how many nights
I wished tomorrow
would never come
To live as I am
without being fake
What do I need
If I don't believe in myself,
what can I believe in
The answer is
too close to see
Black tears are
falling down
I have nothing,
only sadness
I can't put it
into words
My whole body
starts to ache
I can't stand it anymore
on my own