As a child, I thought
your mother is just your mother.
A teacher is just a teacher,
and a police officer is just
a police officer and nothing more.
And celebrities were just celebrities.
They were different from me.
And I still felt that way, even now,
at twenty.
When I was darkness at that time
With trembling lips
In a corner of a room I cry
The more I struggle
The more this wound deepens
The broken promise hurt me
Nobody can save me
God, I have only one request
Stop tearing apart my love
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Sorrow tumbling down is your song
All alone with nowhere to go in my life
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Oh baby, help me from frozen pain
With your smile, your eyes,
and sing me, just for me
I wanna need your love
I'm a broken rose
But this is such coincidence.
I'm surprised.
Yes.
Well, surprised doesn't even
begin to explain how I felt.
So, where should we go?
Do you mind if we get home late?
Tomorrow's Saturday. You don't
hafta work tomorrow, do you?
Yes.
What I wanna know is...
Is this reality?
Don't be so nervous.
Yes. I'm sorry. It's just...
It's fine. There's no need to apologize.
Yes. But... Oh boy,
what am I gonna do?
Now you're making me nervous.
Huh?! Why?
Because, well, I never imagined
in my wildest dreams
that I'd meet you in this manner.
I wasn't prepared for this.
That's my line.
But I was thinking how
nice it would be to see you again.
No way. That's impossible.
No, really. Otherwise,
I wouldn't have called you.
The truth is, I'm terrible at
doing the small things.
Yeah, this has to be a dream.
Because in reality,
these things just don't happen.
Even if they do, at least there's
no way it would happen to me.
Green light already?
What a restless traffic light.
And so am I.
He seems to be quite the player.
That dream-like kiss
abruptly woke me up from my dream.
This is not a fairytale. There's no way
Takumi could be a prince.
He'll sleep with me once
and dump me.
Wait here.
Should I go home right this moment?
I didn't plan for this to happen.
Hey, isn't he that guy from Trapnest?
Wow! Cool! He's so tall!
Then why did I get into his car?
I'm not that foolish to believe he would
even think of making me his girlfriend.
And I'm not that naïve to think this'll
end after a drive and dinner.
There must be a part of me
that was hoping for this.
There's no need to hesitate. I'll never
be in a situation like this again, ever.
I don't have a boyfriend now,
so there's no reason to feel guilty.
Think of this as creating
a once in a lifetime special memory.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
- He's from Trapnest...
- Ren?
No, the long haired guy.
Th-They saw us. And what's worse,
while he had his arm around me.
We'll be in the tabloids.
We'll be on TV.
I'm hungry.
Um... Mr. Takumi...
Mr?
But you've always
just called me Takumi.
Well that's true, but...
that's not the point.
It may not be something
for me to point out,
but aren't you concerned
of the risks of being seen
entering a hotel with a girl?
At the least, perhaps you should
wear some kind of complete disguise.
Some kind of complete disguise?
But if I wore a costume,
I'd stand out even more.
You'd look good in one!
This is no time to be joking!
What's with this guy?
He's pretty funny!
You'd look good in one!
This is no time to be joking!
Not to worry.
The entertainment reporters are too
busy to be following my every step.
Our band keeps a lid
on our public appearances,
so people don't recognize us enough
that we need to be overly cautious.
What are you saying?
Trapnest is really famous.
I guess Reira is.
She may need a costume.
I'd say all four of you share
about the same level of fame.
You think that because you're a fan.
The general public may
also recognize Ren, but that's it.
Naoki and I are known as
the blonde guy
and the long haired guy.
That's not true! You're number one
in my book, Takumi!
I'll bet he thinks of me as
a foolish, easy woman.
But that's basically
the type of woman I am.
With all I've been through,
I thought I had become
more cautious towards men.
But nothing's changed since that summer
back when I was seventeen.
If only I could remain high
on this moment of happiness,
I wouldn't even care about tomorrow.
What's this?
Awesome!
It's huge! There are two rooms!
So pretty! It's like a castle.
Would this happen to be...
A suite room?
Do you like it?
Right now, I'm so happy
I could just die.
If I could die here,
I'd die a happy woman.
If you must die, do it in bed.
But before that let's
get something to eat.
Choose anything you like.
Huh? Are you suggesting
that we eat in the room?
Oh, if you prefer not to,
we can dine out.
No, I've dreamed of
ordering room service in a hotel!
Their specialty is duck.
Duck? I've never had duck.
Really? Never? It's great.
Then how about foie gras?
I've totally never had foie gras.
Then should we get some caviar too?
Yay!
Why not take a shower
and relax until the food arrives?
There's a bathrobe, so use that.
Yes. A bathrobe?
He knows this place
like it were his own castle.
These are brand name cosmetics.
I wonder if I can take them home.
I'm sure tons of foolish girls like me
approach Takumi,
and I'm no more than
one of the many.
But if I'm here, well aware of that,
there should be nothing wrong
with me spending one night
to purposely enjoy a dream, right?
Delicious!
Isn't it? But to me,
that food you prepared
was better than this, Nana.
That's impossible.
No, I'm serious. While on tour,
we always eat out
and I get sick and tired of it.
By the way, you're back on your tour
starting tomorrow, right?
Are you okay for time?
Not a problem.
We leave early in the morning
so I hafta leave during the evening,
but you can take it easy
and spend the night here, Nana.
What? He's gonna leave?
Come on, don't make such a sad face.
It'll make it hard for me to go.
Oh, no, I'm sorry. That'll be fine.
I don't mind.
I'm not thinking of anything as dreamy
as keeping you here with me
until the morning.
Once the tour is over...
I'll come directly to see you.
When I do, would you mind
cooking for me again?
I mustn't take him seriously.
It's okay. I'm not that stupid.
I guess I am different from
when I was seventeen.
Thank you for the meal.
Then I'll go take a quick shower.
You can warm up and wait for me.
You are really impatient, Takumi.
I'm not thinking of
quickly running home
after eating all that I can.
So take your time.
But I can't help but wonder
how many women Takumi's slept with,
using this method.
Is he really satisfied
with commoners like me
who have little money and no skills?
I've gotta warm up. Gotta warm up.
The phone.
Should I turn the power off?
090... who is it?
Hello.
Hachiko!
You're late, so I'm getting worried.
Where are you wandering
at this hour?
Nana? Huh? Whose phone
are you calling from?
Mine.
So you bought a cell phone.
Well, Ren bought me one.
He insisted I carry one.
Is that so? That's great.
But I don't understand how to use it.
Like how to email.
Doesn't it have a manual?
It's thick, so I don't wanna read it.
I thought I'd have you teach me
when you got home,
so I've been waiting.
But unless yours is
the same model as mine,
the functions are
gonna be different.
Is that so?
Then hurry home, read the manual
and teach me how to use it.
What about Ren?
Have Ren teach you.
The person who bought that for you
should be responsible.
Ren left a short while ago.
Of course. He has to leave
early tomorrow morning.
I'm surprised you know that.
B-Because Ren said so yesterday!
Yeah?
Mhm! He totally did!
So, where are you now?
When are you coming home?
Well... um, sorry... maybe not today.
I'm at a friend's place,
and I might stay over.
Really? So there are friends
who are willing to have you stay over,
knowing how troublesome you are.
A guy?
N-No! I-I'm at Jun-chan's!
I'm joking. Don't take it so seriously.
All right. I'll study my cell phone
on my own.
Say "Hi" to Junko for me.
I can't tell Nana.
I don't want her to know.
If she finds out that I'm knowingly
being such an easy woman,
she'll never look at me the same.
But you know, Nana...
The truth is, I too wanna love someone
as diligently as you do.
Like you and Ren, I too wanna have
that connection with someone.
Hey, Nana. The truth is,
I'm not at all okay.
I'd hate to be dumped by Takumi
after a one night stand.
What should I do? I'm scared, Nana.
But I can't run away at this stage.
I can't bring myself to tell him
I want him to love me.
This isn't good. I could end up
feeling hurt all over again.
If anyone asks, I'm staying
at your place tonight.
Nana
If anyone asks, I'm staying
at your place tonight.
Nana
Say. What do you think
of this alibi creation?
Nana's roommate is a woman, right?
Mhm.
But that woman is more handsome
and manly than your average man.
Nana seems to have a serious crush
on her. Maybe those two are a couple.
But never mind that.
Really?
There's something fishy about this.
About what?
Jun-chan. You feeling drunk?
It's the smell of a new man.
I just hope she hasn't been
caught by some guy so terrible
she can't even tell her roommate.
Takumi's hair was so long,
it showered my body.
As I let it caress me, I laid there
wishing he would always keep it long.
Even though I may
never touch it again.
He said it'll be hard for him to go,
but once he's done,
he's quick to leave.
Even his departure is hurried.
Such a busy prince.
I should go home too. I'm done with
playing a make-believe princess.
What? I can't. I've got no strength.
It's as if I have no bones.
I have to pull myself together.
I must quickly return to reality.
In the morning, I've gotta look for
whatever job's available.
And this time, I'm gonna
take my work seriously.
Damn! The last train left long ago.
And I don't have enough money to
take a taxi home from the city center.
I might as well spend the night here.
It's likely a once in
a lifetime opportunity
to stay over at
a place like this anyway.
Trapnest's tour ends
on the eighth of July,
with a performance in Tokyo.
I don't have a ticket,
so I'll prepare something
and wait at home.
I'll be waiting with a little bit of hope.
Just a little bit of hope.
You met with Yasu? What the heck?
Why didn't you invite me?
Be quiet, blonde guy over there.
Is Yasu doing okay?
I guess so. He hasn't really changed.
Is he still a skinhead?
- Yeah.
- Nose piercing?
- Yeah!
- So? What's Yasu doing now?
I mean it, shut up, Naoki.
I haven't had much sleep.
Let me sleep.
Someone switch seats with him.
Then I'll switch with Naoki.
Hey, Take, which side is Mount Fuji?
Which side can we see it from?
Are you listening?
- Say, Takumi...
- Yasu?
He's a lawyer now, apparently.
That's not what I'm asking.
But you wanted to know.
So he really did become one,
even with that look.
Even with that look?
So his dream came true. I'm glad.
He had already passed
the qualification exam
during his fourth year in university.
That's really something,
don't you think?
Is that unusual?!
Would you stay outta this,
blonde guy?
But now he's moved to Tokyo
because of his band.
So isn't his dream to become
a professional musician?
Huh? Moved to Tokyo?
Because of his band?
The band he and Ren had
before Ren joined us.
They found a new bassist,
and have been giving it
some serious effort.
What's this?
After snobbishly telling me repeatedly
that bands are nothing more than
a hobby? I don't get him.
Yeah. Leaves a bad taste, doesn't it?
Want me to rough him up?
What made him decide
to do this now?
Yasu!
Why are you smoking?!
Never mind, continue smoking.
I know very well that you
only stop smoking in front of me.
You're only considerate like that
on the surface.
But then you secretly do stuff
in the shadows.
What else are you hiding?!
Nothing really.
You have too many secrets!
I'm really pissed off, you know!
Why didn't you say anything
about you and Reira?!
Oh, that. I'm sorry.
"Were you that impressed
by Reira's voice?"
It's not funny!
I said I'm sorry.
She was really great, that Reira.
I felt so defeated.
I'm no match for her.
Was she like that since the old days?
Is that what you call a genius?
I guess.
But she has defined abs.
Hmm... You sure are well informed.
Where's Hachi?
Isn't she coming today?
Nobu, that's all you've been saying.
Huh?
Hey, Nobuo.
Are you in love with Hachiko?
No, I, ah...
It's just that, it's kinda lonely
without our regular audience.
But Hachi's only one person.
I want to perform live!
I need to release this tension!
Then let's do it.
We got an offer to perform.
Tell us more.
Our performance at the Live House...
The crowd liked us, so they asked if
we'd be interested in doing another.
Let's do it.
- All right!
That day I checked the classifieds
for job offers
and went to three job interviews.
For a dentist's receptionist,
a supermarket cashier,
and a phone operator
for a pizza place.
I got turned down by them all.
What could they have found about me
that they didn't like?!
I wanna know why you got fired
from your job in the first place?
Well, because I started
making a habit of skipping work...
But at the interviews
I told them in clear terms
that I will take work seriously this time.
Then you told them that you got fired
because you skipped work?!
You're such a fool!
You've gotta realize, if you take
just any job that you can get,
you'll end up with the same result.
Why not look for a job
that suits you better?
What would be a job that suits me?
Well, maybe not specifically
one that suits you.
Any job will do as long as
it's a job you enjoy doing.
If the workplace deals with
things you like,
you'd be more motivated,
don't you think?
When you were working
for Mr. Mizukoshi,
you were surrounded by nice things
and you wore those pretty clothes.
You seemed so alive at that job.
Why not look for another job like that?
I see. That makes sense.
She's right.
I wonder how Mr. Mizukoshi is doing.
Never mind Mr. Mizukoshi!
But I sometimes think about him.
I don't mind telling you now,
but I kinda had a crush on him.
You don't have to tell me. I could tell.
But, you know, taking Mr. Mizukoshi
and Takumi into consideration,
you have a thing for long hair,
don't you?
No way!
What's with your overreacting?
Because you're saying strange things!
Strange? I prefer men
with short hair...
You have it wrong!
Mr. Asano had short hair!
- Asano?
- And so did Shoji!
Well, I think his hair is pretty long.
Yeah? Well, I guess that wouldn't be
considered short.
Seeing that you're comfortable
talking about him,
I guess you're over him now.
It would be nice if you could find
a boyfriend soon. With long hair.
There was just no way that
I could talk to Nana about Takumi.
Being who he is, I couldn't even
tell Jun-chan about him.
I wasn't able to discuss him
with anyone.
I've never had that experience
with love, and it was very painful.
Shoji, are you moving?
What?! Shoji's moving in
with Sachiko?!
They're such a lovey-dovey couple.
That's nice. I envy them.
They seem so young.
You're right.
You're playing in Kyushu
starting today, right?
Take care of your health
and best of luck to the end of the tour.
Nana
You're playing in Kyushu
starting today, right?
Take care of your health
and best of luck to the end of the tour.
Nana
During his tour, I gathered my courage
You're playing in Kyushu
starting today, right?
Take care of your health
and best of luck to the end of the tour.
Nana
and sent Takumi
one short email message.
But I never got a reply.
Ren
Concert Congratulations
Taste the euphoria.
From the Guitar Genius
Hey, Nana...
I always admired you.
I wanted to be like you.
I lived life always thinking that.
So please.
Please sing again, once more.
I reached into the sky
But I couldn't reach what I wanted
They grew smaller
and disappeared into the sky
Like colorful balloons
I'm alone
My hand had no place to go
And gently you took it
Starless night
I won't look back
at the shadow of my past
I want to feel your warmth
Tears are falling down
Even if I'm unsure I won't let go
Of your hand holding mine