Are memories precious?
Yes! I wish I could gather every single one
and keep them in a treasure box.
No sappy conversations allowed,
especially in the intro!
Huh?
No sappy conversations allowed,
especially in the intro!
Wouldn't you want to forget
all the bad things, though?
Alice?
Athena's...
Her what?
Athena's treasure box won't unlock!
"Dear Ai, the weather in Neo-Venezia
has been beautiful lately."
"When you look up at the sunny, clear blue sky,"
"doesn't it sometimes make you feel like
you're a fish at the bottom of the sea..."
"...looking up at the water's surface?"
Ehh?!
You're going with Athena...
On a picnic?!
...on a picnic?!
Yes, we're going tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
By any chance, is she
the one who invited you?
If she did, that means...
I invited Athena.
Eh? You did?
Really?
It was Athena's idea at first. She said,
"Once it gets warmer, let's go on a picnic," but...
But?
Spring came, but Athena's been so busy,
we haven't had the chance to discuss it.
That's why...
So that's why you invited her.
What was Athena's response?
Eh? Yes, well...
It just so happens that Athena
has a rare day off tomorrow, so...
Well, I guess picnics are nice once in a while.
I hope you two have a fun picnic, Alice.
Me too.
Do you remember that day
Oboeteimasuka ano hi o
When your heart suddenly began to race
Futo kanjita tokimeki o
The rays from the blue sky were pouring over you...
Aoi hizashi abite
...as you cut through the wind
Kaze o kiru kimi ni
I couldn't look away, and when our eyes met
Mitoreru to me ga atte
I couldn't help but smile
Egao koboreta
It's just like a spiral
Marude supiraare
I want to spend my days waving to you
Itsumademo te o furitai hibi
This is my proof that I was here with you
Koko ni tashika ni kimi to ita akashi
An eternal spiral
Zutto supiraare
There's a path which stretches on ahead
Kono saki mo tsuzuiteru michi ga aru
When you climb the next hill,
Tsugi no saka o nobottara
Let's meet again
Mata aimashou
The Memories of That Precious Person...
We'll leave early tomorrow morning.
First, we'll head towards the Canal Grande.
If we turn around at this point in the canal,
the morning sun should be sweeping over
Neo-Venezia. It's supposed to be really beautiful.
After that, we'll head to
Murano Island and have lunch.
Athena's late, isn't she?
I know! I'll draw up a schedule for tomorrow.
That way Athena will understand right away.
Yes, yes.
I'll bring two bananas tomorrow,
one for dessert and one for snack time.
It gets really chilly after dark, doesn't it?
President Maa, it's still a little early,
but let's go take a bath and warm ourselves up!
But before that...
"To Athena."
Okay, let's go, President Maa.
Oh, that's right. We need to
go to the cafeteria later...
...and ask them to make us
sandwiches for tomorrow's lunch.
Let's bring lots of different teas, too.
How about a tea-naming quiz?
Why don't we ask the cafeteria lady
if she can recommend some rare teas?
It's great, isn't it?
They gave us so many bananas.
Ah, looks like Athena is back.
Athena, you need to close
the door properly, or...
She's asleep.
I guess we just missed each other in the bath.
Athena. Athena!
I guess she's exhausted.
Dear Athena
She must have had a last-minute booking...
President Maa, leave the lunch alone
until we get to Murano Island!
Okay! This is now Murano Island!
We have sandwiches for lunch.
Eh? You're already full?
That's no good. This lunch is for two people...
Alice!
Umm... I finished... work, so...
W-Welcome back...
Um, today... I suddenly got...
I know.
Um, it wasn't something I could...
It's fine.
Um, Alice, why don't we go right now?
We can't go very far, but-
I said it's fine, didn't I?!
Um, I... I'm sorry!
Why are you apologizing?
Alice!
Why am I being so harsh to her?
It's not her fault...
Umm...
President Aria's favorite mug!
My, my!
Oh no! The phone's ringing!
Akari, I'll clean this up,
so could you get it please?
Yes!
Coming!
Hello, this is the Aria Company.
Th-Th-Th-Th-Th-Th...
Th?
This is a really big SOS, Akari!
What's the matter, Alice?
We were worried.
You sounded so panicked over the phone...
Welcome. You must be my friends.
Here.
Thank you.
And one for you, too.
Athena's unusually quick
and responsive today, isn't she?
Now that you mention it...
On top of that, she said we
"must be her friends."
To tell you the truth...
...I have amnesia.
A... Are you all right?
Athena...
Athena!
Please snap out of it!
Athena! Athena! Athena! Athena!
Athena-
Thank goodness! You woke up...
You are?
Eh? Umm...
Who might you be?
And that's what happened.
And that's what happened!
We also have black tea, if you'd like.
No, thank you. I'm fine for now.
I see. Please tell me
when you'd like some more.
Looks like her memory loss
altered her personality as well.
My, my.
I'm at a complete loss about what to do...
I'm so sorry! I know it's really sudden.
It's all right. After all, it's for Athena's sake.
Has she seen a doctor?
Eh?
Ah, right, first stop should be
the hospital, shouldn't it?
Yes! I think...
President Aria.
If you don't lose some weight,
you'll get diabetes someday.
Athena, his name!
You remember President Aria's name?
Yes.
It just happened to come out naturally.
Maybe now she'll remember...
Ah, y-you're right.
Athena.
Yes?
What's my name?
Who are you?
What's her name?
Who is she?
Who is that?
I knew it! It's really no use!
It's no use, it's no use!
A-A-Alice, calm down!
Athena.
Eh?
What is it, Alicia?
She remembered again!
She recognizes Alicia!
What kind of magic did you use?
Wow...
My, my. Did it seem like magic?
It's nothing to worry about. I'm sure
it's just a temporary memory mix-up.
In the meantime, why don't you stay with
her today and see if she gets any better?
If she doesn't, we'll take her
to the hospital tomorrow.
How does that sound?
Y-Yes, we'll do that.
Well then, I'm off to work.
Have a good day!
Thank you very much, Alicia.
Somehow, I feel much better now.
Yeah.
Hey, why don't we take her
to places she knows?
You're right.
Instead of staying in this room,
Athena might recover faster elsewhere.
I'll keep you two company!
I'm sure she'll remember lots of things
if we go to places she's used to.
What is it?
Now that I've calmed down,
I just had a scary thought.
Right now, Athena is quick,
responsive, and isn't clumsy at all.
Maybe it's actually okay if
her memory doesn't come back...
You know that's not right...
The shop we're headed to now
serves lots of different hot chocolates.
Really? I'm looking forward to it!
On top of that, Athena is a regular,
so they have a special menu just for her.
Athena, have you remembered anything?
No...
I... see...
Welcome. Would you like the usual?
Yes. We'll also have this, this... and this please.
They all look so delicious!
That's really correct!
Ah, it is?
That's amazing, Athena!
Thank you.
President Maa, say pretty please.
Athena!
You recognize President Maa!
Do you remember me?
Now, now. Easy now, easy...
That was delicious!
Where shall we go next?
This isn't working!
We're going back to Orange Planet!
Huh?
Is our walk over already?
I'm going to try and jog her memory
in a more familiar setting.
My, Athena!
You finally have a day off,
and you're not going out?
Please have your friend make herself at home!
Who was that person just now?
Athena, just concentrate on one thing at a time.
Out of all of these...
Athena, which one is your
favorite oar that you always use?
Wow, this is really hard!
Th-That's correct...
That's amazing!
You're recovering slowly but surely, Athena!
Thank you, Akari.
Amazing! You remembered my name!
Umm...
I'm sorry.
Ah, I know! How about this?
I'm sure Alicia will be back soon,
so why don't we all go to the Aria Company?
I'm sorry for asking you to
carry President Aria, Athena.
It's all right. I like the way President Aria feels.
What's the matter? Are you all right, Alice?
I'm the only one Athena doesn't remember...
Athena?
What kind of person was I to you?
You were a very clumsy mentor...
As your roommate, you always used to
trouble me with your constant mistakes...
I guess you hated me, huh?
Ah! I didn't hate you...
Then, did you like me?
If I had to choose one or the other,
I guess it'd be the latter...
Alice...
Don't you think that's enough, Athena?
Alicia!
Right, Athena?
Yeah.
I'm sorry, Alice.
I was lying.
Huh?
My amnesia was all a lie.
Wha?
What?!
I'm always causing you trouble
because I'm so clumsy, right?
Yes.
After what happened this morning, I thought
you might have finally gotten fed up with me.
I became really worried...
So I wanted to know how you truly felt...
That's why...
That's why I thought, if I got amnesia,
I'd be able to ask how you felt
about me and get an honest answer...
I'm really sorry.
Athena...
Yes?
Next time, please don't be so
sneaky about it. Just be direct.
Okay.
Athena, I...
...really hate that about you!
Ehh?!
My, my.
First of all, if you can be graceful
like that, then be that way all the time!
But it's really exhausting to act like that...
Alicia, by any chance...
...did you know right from the start?
It's only because I've seen Athena pull some
unbelievable stunts from time to time.
Were you surprised?
Yes, I was really surprised.
It never occurred to me that someone
like Athena, one the Three Great Water Fairies,
would worry about things like that...
We're just like any other girls, after all.
We all wonder how the people
we hold dear feel about us...
...and we worry about it, sometimes.
Especially if it's our cute apprentices.
Let's go home.
Okay...
C'mon Athena.
Then, do you get worried about me too, Alicia?
Wait, Alice!
That's a secret.
Huh?
"Ai, when you like someone, that feeling
might bring an equal amount of worry, too."
"Akari, I'm sure that after this incident,
Alice and Athena will become even closer."
A shore awash in golden waves
Kin no nami kishibe ni
Filled with yearning, I open my eyes and it's morning
Akogare mezameru no asa ni
As my thoughts focus intently on someone,
Dareka no koto o tsuyoku omou toki
Love rests on my palm, held high
Kakageta te no hira ni ai ga tomaru
A future guided by the flow of water and wind
Mizu no yukue to kaze ga shimesu mirai
I gaze at the hope that surrounds this world
Kono hoshi o tsusumu kibou mitsumete
The distant clouds of light are beckoning now
Tooi kumo hikari ga sasou you ni yureru ima
A shore awash in golden waves
Kin no nami kishibe ni
Filled with yearning, I open my eyes and it's morning
Akogare mezameru no asa ni
And my day begins
Hajimaru
Next Episode
Alice, congratulations on your graduation!
I'm really gonna work you hard now!
Next Episode
But before that, I'm going
on a picnic with Athena.
Next Episode
Surrounded By That Orange Wind...
Next time, "Surrounded By That Orange Wind..."
Next Episode
Surrounded By That Orange Wind...
Now, please take my hand.