That day, my world was all white.
My hands and feet
felt numb from the cold.
I couldn't find my Ashikabi-sama...
Wait!
This is for your own good!
Just let us defeat you!
Hey, are you okay?
Shit! She's gone.
I don't have the strength
to fight with other Sekireis.
All I can ever do is cry.
I'm no good, I'm hopeless...
Hey.
You've been sitting there quite a while.
Eh... um...
you looked like you were crying.
So, here.
When the weather's cold like this,
these are the best things.
They'll make you feel better,
so eat them while they're hot, okay?
Wait! Why are you crying?
Those meat buns were really warm.
Really, really warm...
See ya!
I found you.
My Ashikabi-sama.
Ima inochi ga hora kizashite chitte yuku
Nigirishimeta unmei
Mou mayou koto wa nai
Musubiau kizuna
Akatsuki matsu sora ni
Aishi kimi dakishimete
Orenai inori wo
Mada dare mo yoru no naka
Ima wa tada
Kokoro no oku ni sawatte
Afureru atsusa subete sasagetai
Yume miru ashita e
Hirogeru tsubasa wa
Ano hi no kimi ga kureta
Omoi wa kizamareta
Chikai no kotoba ga
Kiseki wo okosu yo
Takanaru mune habatake
Tobitateru negai haruka tataku
Feather 10:
"The Night Before the Escape"
Wow! What a nice story!
Feather 10:
"The Night Before the Escape"
Grabbing a scarf...
the beginning of the little love story...
"Carp?"
Grabbing a scarf...
the beginning of the little love story...
"Carp?"
I knew it! Sekireis should live for love!
You don't need to be ashamed
of not fighting, Incompetence-chan!
I'm Kuno.
Sekireis' real nature is love!
- All the Sekireis in the world...
- Why is she here?
- Should live for love...
- After I talked about the escape plan,
she just came along with us...
So?
I understand those two kids
want to escape the capital but...
Kids?
Why the hell did all you guys barge
into here this early in the morning?!
I'm sorry.
Well, I wasn't happy about the
way MBI's been doing things lately.
Then?
Yeah, I'll help you guys.
Thank you very much.
So, pay up.
Are you going to charge a fee?!
Ha! That's why I said you're kids.
Grownups don't move for free.
Don't call me a kid!
This is Sahashi.
I'm twenty, already!
Seo-san.
For me?
Kaoru-san?
No! I wasn't bullying them! Really!
You won't let me eat there anymore?!
No! That's bad! That's really bad!
Who did you call?
The Landlady.
Ah, she's unbeatable.
You bastard! Using a dirty trick on me!
I thought you were a pure and amiable kid!
That Minato... What is he thinking?
If that will let them stay together,
then I want to help them.
Yes! Let them run
away as fast as they can!
If that's what you want,
I won't spare any cooperation.
Thank you.
Trying to help someone who
doesn't fight escape... Unthinkable!
I warned him how
dangerous this plan was.
He decided knowing that.
In truth, thou art not keen
on this plan either, art thou?
To do the best for one's
Ashikabi is the Sekirei's duty.
The first duty of a Sekirei is to fight on!
And yet thou hidest thyself in this place...
In the end, thou art the same as those two!
Ah, Tsukiumi-san!
Landlady.
I cannot understand what Musubi and even
Number 03 are thinking by helping them thus...
They may not be thinking anything.
There is somebody in trouble,
so you help them...
That may be the
natural thing for a person to do.
But we are Sekireis!
Sekireis must fight until the end!
Refusing to fight is!
Tsukiumi-san, I wonder if you mean,
"It's not fair for her to live
happily ever after with her Ashikabi
even though she won't fight!"?
La-Landlady!
But, well... perhaps thou art right.
Number 95's feebleness irritates me,
but on the other hand, I might envy her.
I heard you are aiming to be the strongest.
At first, I thought I could be the
strongest even without an Ashikabi.
But now...
I'm aiming to be strongest in order
to live happily ever after with Minato.
Don't tell this to Minato!
Yes, yes.
Well then, shall I train you, too?
Train me?
Ku-chan, please take care of the laundry.
Okay!
Come to the empty lot in the back.
I'll judge your ability.
The capital is divided into four areas
centered around the Teito tower:
North, West, South and East...
The areas other than the North
area are territories of three Ashikabis.
You're connected to one of them.
Eh? Me?
The one who was after the Green Girl.
Number 43, Yomi, whom you guys defeated...
Her Ashikabi, Hayato Mikogami.
He reigns over the South.
The West is the territory of a man named
Sanada, but I don't know much about him.
I have met Higa of the East several times,
but he is opposed to the Sekirei Plan,
and there are even other Ashikabis
who follow him. A cunning man.
I'm sure he'll cause trouble sooner or later.
And then, it's so funny. That girl...
What's the matter, Uzume-chan?
Ah, nothing. I just feel a bit thirsty,
so I'll go buy something to drink.
What?
You lost your target, did you?
Someone disturbed me.
You have only one more chance.
There's no more next times.
I know that.
Please don't forget the life of your
precious Ashikabi depends on Higa-sama.
Well, then...
We'd better avoid their territories if we can.
Excuse me,
how can the North be controlled by nobody
despite there being three
such powerful Ashikabis?
Because there lives a very,
very scary monster to the north.
Ah! Maison Izumo is in the north!
Here I come.
Come on!
Water Celebration!
What the?!
You open yourself up too much.
You still have a long way to go.
You don't use your power properly.
I have lots to teach you.
Landlady, who art thou?
She won't do anything unless we bother her.
So the North is the best
escape route from the capital.
In the north, there's a big river dividing the
capital from the outside called the Araha River.
Once you cross it,
MBI can no longer pursue you.
Are you suggesting we swim across?
Idiot! Who said that?
They are watching not only all
the train stations, airports, ports
and the junctions of the main roads,
but also the sea and rivers.
Then how can they?
Now, the only way is to run
across the bridge straightforwardly.
There are checkpoints on
the bridges. We were there and...
Even so, a loophole can exist.
"The Araha River"
Here. The bridges for regular roads
and for railroads stand in parallel.
There are guards on this side of the railroad
bridge, but there are no inspection stations.
So one risk can be eliminated there.
But there are two problems.
One is MBI's surveillance satellites.
If you're caught by one of these, you
could be killed instantly by its laser beam.
Ah... um... how about asking
Matsu-san to hack the satellites?
Hack the satellites?
She's very good at those things.
All your Sekireis are truly amazing.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- I haven't said anything!
Now then, the only remaining
problem is MBI's hounds.
The Sekireis called the Discipline Squad.
The Discipline Squad?
The Blue Sekirei,
the Red Sekirei, and the Black Sekirei.
They exist to purge other Sekireis,
and they are outrageously strong.
That one, huh?
I'll fight with them!
Musubi-chan.
Then I'll explain the plan.
We'll carry it out tomorrow night.
Tomorrow?!
Three Ashikabis secretly doing something.
There's no way MBI won't notice.
We'd better make the
move as soon as possible.
So we're seriously skipping out by night...
I'm sorry.
Because I'm so weak, you have to...
See?
You should've listened to us
and let us shut you down that time.
She's right. If you'd been shut
down before your emergence,
you wouldn't need to go through all this.
But she found him after all.
Kuno-san could meet Shigi-san
because she didn't give up.
Don't worry. You are my girl,
so you just shut up and follow me.
Got it?
Then stop crying!
Yes.
It's love, indeed!
Sekireis get stronger from their love!
By the way, why are you with them?
It's just how things went.
Are you acquaintances?
Anyway!
I regret helping free
of charge, but nonetheless
since I'm in it, I'll enable you guys
to escape from the capital without fail!
Let's kick MBI butt!
I wish you luck, youngster.
R-Right.
Ah, so pure...
This boy really does rather remind me of him...
Incredible!
I received the outline of
the plan from Seo-tan by e-mail.
And... do you think it's possible?
There's nothing that I, Matsu can't do.
Great!
But... there's a time limit of how long
I can hack the surveillance satellites.
Time limit?
This will be different from
invading stealthily like before,
so more than an hour
would be quite tough...
So you mean that we
must escape within an hour?
Everybody!
The preparation for the party is all done!
- Party?
And now, wishing for
their successful elopement.
Cheers!
- Cheers!
Now, I'll take off all my clothes!
No!
And yours!
Am I the only one
feeling tense about tomorrow?
Hey, Sahashi?
What?
Don't you want to come with us?
Retiring from this bogus game.
Don't you want to live peacefully
with those girls on the outside?
That is...
Excuse me for a sec.
Tsukiumi.
What is it?
It's so noisy.
Kazehana-san insisted on a farewell
party for Shigi-kun and Kuno-san.
Why don't you join us, Tsukiumi?
Nonsense!
Did you get hurt?
No need to worry. Just a scratch.
Hey.
What?
You told us that you wouldn't help the escape
plan, but would you please change your mind?
No! I do not go back on a
decision once I have made it!
If... If we're attacked by the
Discipline Squad or the Veiled Sekirei there,
Musubi-chan is the only one who can fight...
So if... If something
happened to Musubi-chan, I...
Minato, art thou worrying about the plan,
or is it Musubi thou art worried about?
I'm home!
Huh? It's lively.
Ah, welcome back!
Hurry and come join us, too!
What? A party?
We're in the middle of a farewell party.
A farewell party?
Yup! A farewell party for the eloping couple.
I'll pass.
That's too bad.
Later.
You're not doing it willingly, are you?
I wonder what the person
forcing you to do it is after.
If you talk about that again here...
You're so scary.
Oh, right, I just came to get sake. Later!
I'm sorry. I said something very insensitive...
Minato.
It's been a while since I married thee.
Dost...
Dost thou not wish to make love to me?
Mina-tan!
Kazehana-tan brought more sake.
Ah, yes.
A stray impulse.
That was just a trivial
stray impulse! Forget it!
Otherwise,
I'll kill thee, Minato. I'll kill thee!
- I'll strip you!
- Please stop!
Tsukiumi's...
Is anybody there? The bath is not ready...
It's fine! Just leave me alone!
This is the perfect temperature
to cool my overexcited head.
When did this happen?!
Yukari? What is it?
You haven't called for a long time...
That's the same for you, Big Bro!
I'm quite busy these days.
I can't go there so easily.
Yes, I know. Then, later.
I'm sorry. Because you are helping me...
Don't worry. Looking for
number 108 is our priority now.
We'll make the move tonight.
She's always like that.
Don't you want to live peacefully
with those girls on the outside?
Shit!
Good morning.
It sounded like fun last night.
You should have joined us.
No, I get more than
enough partying in the club.
You've been taking off from
your work for a while, haven't you?
I'm not in good shape these days.
The change has begun, hasn't it?
What are you talking about?
I can tell looking at your body.
It's not completely decided, yet.
This is great, Landlady!
She really is the strongest!
L... will not... lose to... her!
I'll protect everybody!
Kusano?
What dost thou want?
You aren't his wife.
Somebody who can't help with
big brother's fervent wish isn't his wife.
You can run faster than
Ku but you don't do anything!
So you are not big brother's wife anymore!
Wow! It's the perfect
star-filled sky for the escape!
Now everybody, let's go!
Right!
Tsukiumi... never came out...
Sahashi, we really owe you.
Don't worry about it.
And... about what I said yesterday...
For right now, the success
of the plan is the top priority.
You're right.
Okay then, Operation:
Escape from the Capital...
...begins now!
Yo, baby girls! Get ready now!
This is renai no shinansho
Don't let it go, aserazu so
Without furaingu de show time
Get the funky beat!
Hayai mono gachi?
Kono bayai wa kankei nai nai
Nozomu tokoro yo
Soudatsusen boppatsu
Onna desu mono, maketerareya shinai nai
Fukuramu kimochi
No mou daibouhatsu
Dame yo, yuuwaku shicha
Doite, kare no osoba
Watashi dokidoki natte ippai ippai
Naisho, nukekake shite
Daiseikou, kare to futari
Amaku mekurumeku night
Honto wa ne, watashi dake wo
Dakishimete hoshii no
Hitorijime mura mura
Furagu tatechau no ari kashira?
Yappari ne, yowaki, dou shiyou
Yasashisugite shou ga nai
Sonna toko daisuki yo
Dakara watashitachi tsukushimasu
Dear Sweet Heart!
I am happy I met Minato-san.
Musubi-chan...
I fight for Minato-san.
No! That isn't... that isn't...
Musubi-chan!
Episode 11:
"The Sekirei Symbol Disappears."
Feather 11:
"The Sekirei Symbol Disappears"
Episode 11:
"The Sekirei Symbol Disappears."
Feather 11:
"The Sekirei Symbol Disappears"
Please favor us again next time...