I got it.
The reprogramming
of the surveillance satellite,
the mobilizing of personnel...
Everything's completed.
The time has finally come.
Bastard, do you know what you are...
Takami-kun, what are you afraid of?
I'm not afraid, I'm simply fed up.
Everything is inevitable.
It has been ever since we
touched the corpse of the god,
when I qualified as game master.
Then, eh?
"Kamikura Island"
We've come all the way
to this unknown island.
If you're a man, you must go on a
journey of adventure at the end of century!
Dungeons! Go forth and quest for treasure...
That hurts, Takami-kun!
If you don't shut up,
I'll give you another!
This island appeared as a result of
a geologically impossible upheaval.
We can't predict what
will happen at any moment!
Even so, you came here as if you're
going to a picnic, saying, "I wanna go see!"
This is supposed to be the super genius,
the smartest person since
our university was founded...
But he's one mere step from a nutcase!
Hey, wait, Minaka!
Wait, Minaka!
Takami-kun!
A discovery! A discovery!
The King of Terror!
What is this?
If it's the end of the century,
it's obvious this is the King of Terror.
No way...
She... doesn't look like the King of Terror.
Now my life is blooming then falling
I grab destiny tight
There's no more hesitation anymore
Tying our bond
To the sky waiting for the dawn
Holding you, my love, tightly
I present an unbreakable prayer
We all are still in the darkness
Right now I just
Want to touch you deep in your heart
And give you all of my overflowing passion
I spread out my wings
Toward the future of our dreams
On them are engraved
The feeling you gave me that day
The words of our oath
Will make a miracle happen
My pounding heart, take off now!
My wish can fly high, high up
Feather 7:
"The Black Sekirei"
Get away from there!
Only the real wife can share his bed!
I'm his wife, too!
I-I had a feeling this would happen...
Well, Ku-chan, it's time to go to sleep.
Art thou retreating, Minato?!
I'm just taking Ku-chan
to the landlady's room...
Little brat, art thou challenging me?
This is such a typical scene of carnage.
Matsu-san, you too.
You'll get in trouble with landlady again.
I'm simply observing these
unruly and wild women fight.
And in the end, I let them have their way...
Sahashi-san...
I told you illicit sexual
relations are not permitted.
U-Um... it's not like that...
Even Ku-chan...
And so I have decided
to formally allocate the rooms.
Ku-chan will keep
sleeping in my room as before.
Musubi-san and Tsukiumi-san
will be in the vacant room 204.
I can't understand! I'm his wife.
It's unreasonable to be
separated from one's husband!
I'm his wife, too!
It is already done.
"Hisssss..."
Understood?
Yes...
Well...
as the landlady has decided so...
Now the obstacles to my
experiment are eliminated...
The private army's deployment has changed.
Why so suddenly?
That wench! Why must I, the real wife,
be kicked out from Minato's room?
Honestly, I cannot accept this at all!
I'll be out shopping,
so please water the garden.
Yes, have a safe trip, landlady.
See you!
Huh? Where is Tsukiumi-san?
If she'd join us watering the garden,
I'm sure it'd be a lot of fun...
Why must I help with these chores?
They had better not think of me
as a water sprinkler or something!
H-Hi.
You really look alike...
What are you talking about?
See you later.
I'll be back soon.
I just came to see her today.
I wonder if Mu-chan's doing well.
No, Ku-chan. You'll get wet.
I-I'm sorry!
You're still a scatterbrain as always...
...Mu-chan.
Karasuba-sama!
Why are you here?
I heard a rumor about you.
Am I causing trouble?
No, not at all. I'm very glad you're here!
Musubi-chan, is someone here?
Please wear my clothes until yours get dry.
I'm really sorry about that.
Don't worry.
By the way, that guy is your Ashikabi?
Yes, he's Minato-san.
A Sekirei symbol!
Right. I've emerged, too.
Congratulations!
I heard you crushed number 43.
Number 43?
Ah! The sickle person!
She was such a bully. So I...
You haven't changed, Mu-chan.
Tell you the truth, I came here to confirm.
Confirm?
Do you remember that promise, Musubi?
Of course!
Mina-tan, Mina-tan! I have to talk to you.
Is somebody here?
Yeah, an acquaintance of Musubi-chan...
An acquaintance?
I wonder if my clothes are dry now.
Probably.
W-Why is that here?
- Um... Matsu-san?
- I'm not here!
There's no such person as "Matsu" here!
Excuse me, but I'm leaving now.
Ah, I see...
I wanted to talk with you more!
Somebody's waiting for me. Later.
Later!
Sekirei number 04, Karasuba.
MBI's hound.
Called the "Black Sekirei."
Matsu-san, she's left.
L... will... be... killed!
What do you mean you'll be killed?
Mina-tan! Watch the TV!
That hurt... TV?
Ladies and gentlemen in Shintou Teito,
I'm MBI's Hiroto Minaka.
I now declare to you,
the capital has been seized by us, MBI.
Seized?
Now the new age of
the god has begun here!
There's no need to worry at all
even though the capital is seized.
- What's going on? Ah, Professor!
- Please continue living as usual.
However, please allow us to inspect
your persons when leaving the capital city.
Thou hast done it, Minaka.
Inspection? By MBI?
It's finally started. The Sekirei Plan, Phase 2.
Phase 2...
I have just noticed a little while ago.
As you see, this capital city,
Shintou Teito, is surrounded by rivers,
and MBI's private army has been
deployed to all the city's exit bridges.
But why would they inspect?
Mina-tan, me, and everyone else...
At last, we must prepare ourselves.
Prepare...
MBI... that is, Hiroto Minaka is going
to make this Shintou Teito into a battlefield.
Oh?
That's a nice place... Maison Izumo, right?
I didn't touch anything... at least not today.
This is the only time I'll overlook this.
I will not forgive you if you
step into Maison Izumo next time.
Ah... you are as good as ever.
You haven't changed. Scary, so scary...
You give me a chill.
Too bad. I didn't bring my sword today.
Are you going to fight with that?
Go away! Your sinister form
is too repulsive to look upon!
You're the same as always...
Number 01, Miya.
Let's meet again.
Next time, let's both bring prey.
Wait.
That apple costs 143 yen!
Looks like... it has begun, Takehito-san...
What happened?
You look like you're having fun.
Can you tell?
Yes, I can tell. I'm your "Ashikabi"
or whatever, and we're connected, right?
You're flippant, Natsuo.
Flippant? You're not nice.
Stop the car, Natsuo.
What?
I got too excited because of Number 01.
I'll go out to play a bit.
The plan's gone into Phase 2,
and there are only a few un-emerged
Sekireis left to present to Master.
It's getting tough to perform our duty!
Ever since we let number
107 get away, we've been out of luck.
I wonder if it's time to quit this task.
Hey, you guys.
If you have time to spare,
could you be my opponents?
What are you? A Sekirei?
Get out.
She's the Black Sekirei.
Are you saying to run away
from one who challenges me?
Impossible!
Anyway, who is this Black Sekirei?
Ignorant and arrogant...
I kinda like that.
Shut up!
Who do you think you are?!
Can you do it?
Ah, she ran away...
I have to ask them to pick this up.
I don't know how to respond,
being told to "prepare" all of a sudden...
And who was that person who came here?
Ku-chan's taking a nap.
I see.
Do you know where Tsukiumi is?
I haven't seen her for a while.
Beats me...
It's kind of quiet here.
Uzume-san's been
out since this morning too.
She said she had something to do.
What?
We're all alone right now, aren't we?
Yes, we are...
So this is the best time.
There's something I must tell you. Only you.
The promise I made with Karasuba-sama...
The promise between a Sekirei and a Sekirei.
A promise?
Yes, it is the promise we must keep.
Humans are an unnecessary
species on this planet.
My Ashikabi-sama who I will meet someday...
I'm really sure I will like
that person very, very much.
They are not an unnecessary species.
You say the same thing as Yume said.
Yume-sama did, too?
Then, how about this?
We will fight and survive until
we are the last two remaining.
Then, we fight until one of us loses.
Karasuba-sama and me?
If you win, what you are saying is right.
If it's the opposite and...
My promise with Karasuba-sama is to survive
the fights until we are the last two remaining.
And I will definitely win over her,
and free all the broken-winged
Sekireis into the sky again.
Being separated from their
Ashikabi-sama forever... It's too sad.
Musubi-chan...
I like you very much!
Thanks.
Here!
Can you feel it?
It's beating so hard.
Y-Yes...
It's so warm...
I'm grateful to the gods and goddesses.
For the happiness that I
have here, for the people I love.
Landlady, Ku-chan, Matsu-san, Tsukiumi-san...
For the miracle I could meet everybody.
This feeling...
How this feeling of loving
someone makes us much stronger.
I want Karasuba-sama
to know this feeling too.
That person who doesn't
know anything, like a child...
I really want her to know no matter what.
That's my ambition!
Is it too big?
Not at all.
You can do it, Musubi-chan.
I believe in you.
Yes!
I believe in your strong words. Your smile.
What a farce!
You should've known.
Homura!
The plan was always for this city to be
readied as a battle arena for Sekireis someday.
I shan't fight against a convalescent.
You're the one who's always
one-sidedly starting the fights.
Then leave now.
The Sekirei Plan has progressed to Phase 2.
This means a certain number of
Sekireis completed their emergence.
Is it... because I became Minato's Sekirei?
Anything wrong?
N-None of thy business!
If thou hast no intention of doing battle,
do not show thyself without good reason!
We're together all the time, actually...
The seizing of the capital in order
to bring Sekireis to fight full scale...
From now on, any Sekireis who show
their backs will be squashed instantly.
Yukari-san, are you sure
this outfit isn't strange?
You look good! You look good!
You definitely look like a girl!
I-Is that so?
They'd never notice you looking like that!
Interesting...
Is something up, Mikogami?
That little bird who flew away from
me doesn't seem to be emerged yet.
A Sekirei, huh?
Once I look at it, I really want it.
That's your bad habit.
Well, do whatever you want.
I left it to the Sekireis,
but they failed twice.
I'll grab that kid by myself.
What is this?!
The clothes Uzume-san gave me.
I'm not asking thee that! I'm asking why
the heck I have to be dressed in such things!
Because your dress is so
frilly and not suitable for chores!
Chores?
Why the hell do I have to do such?!
What?
Shopping.
I'm counting on you.
So, why do I have to?!
Those who don't work don't eat.
But...
The one who comes back first will sit
next to Sahashi-san at the dinner table.
This side is mine!
What's the matter?
Well, how should I put it...
I wonder if it's okay
to be so ordinary like this.
Because it's ordinary...
It's good.
Ashi... kabi... sama...
My veil of the pact,
dispel my Ashikabi's nightmares.
Wind...
An unpleasantly colored wind is blowing...
Yo, baby girls! Get ready now!
This is the textbook of love
Don't let it go, don't get upset so
Without false starts, it's show time!
Get the funky beat!
First ones win?
No such thing in this case! No, no!
That's perfect for me
A sudden scramble!
But I'm a woman, I can't lose. No, no!
My feelings grow
No, and then a big bang!
Don't seduce him
Get away from him
My heart is pounding hard, so hard!
Secret, going off by myself
Big success, just two of us
Sweet and dazzling night
To tell you the truth, I want him to
Hold only me, just me
I want to monopolize him so badly
I wonder if I could stick a flag on him?
I knew it, he's so wimpy, what should I do?
He's just too gentle
I love that about him
So we are devoted to him
Dear Sweet Heart!
Musubi! Let's have a shopping race!
Today we shall settle our battle!
Yes, Tsukiumi-san! That's what I wish for!
Hold it! Thou art running without shoes!
Ah! I also forgot my wallet!
That's enough of thy scatterbrained ways!
Feather 8:
"The Closed Capital"
That's enough of thy scatterbrained ways!
Feather 8:
"The Closed Capital"
Episode 8: "The Closed Capital."
Feather 8:
"The Closed Capital"
Please favor us again next time!