So far, he's hit a right fly
and been struck-out.
Something's off.
So far, he's hit a right fly
and been struck-out.
There's the first pitch.
It's a ball.
Something's off.
Kumamoto's pitcher, Suzuki,
had started the game...
Something's off.
Kumamoto's pitcher, Suzuki,
had started the game...
...having already pitched
fourteen innings.
Something seems off.
It just somehow felt that way.
What an incredible spirit, he's able to
keep going despite giving up seven runs.
Something seems off.
It just somehow felt that way.
What an incredible spirit, he's able to
keep going despite giving up seven runs.
I had absolutely no interest in the
prefectural baseball game on TV,
The second pitch is...
I had absolutely no interest in the
prefectural baseball game on TV,
And it's up... a left fly ball.
One out.
But I kind of ended up
rooting for the losing side.
The score is still seven to zero.
But I kind of ended up
rooting for the losing side.
The score is still seven to zero.
Once I did, I kind of got the feeling that
Haruhi was going to start something.
The score is still seven to zero.
Incoming call: Haruhi Suzumiya
The gap between the
scores is big,
but Kumamoto still has a chance
if they can hold out here.
But Kumamoto still has a chance
Kyon, the phone's ringing.
The passionate voices cheering from the
third base bleachers have not died down.
Kyon, the phone's ringing.
The passionate voices cheering from the
third base bleachers have not died down.
I know, you don't
have to tell me.
There's Suzuki, they need him to do
his best, don't they, Mr. Kiru?
You're not doing anything today, right?
We're meeting at 2PM in front of the station.
That's true.
You're not doing anything today, right?
We're meeting at 2PM in front of the station.
After all, you never know how a match is
going to turn out. They still have hope.
You're not doing anything today, right?
We're meeting at 2PM in front of the station.
After all, you never know how a match is
going to turn out. They still have hope.
Be sure to show up.
After all, you never know how a match is
going to turn out. They still have hope.
I didn't even
say anything...
Right.
I didn't even
say anything...
Next, stepping up to the batter's box we
have number four, Kashima, a senior.
- What?
- I forgot to mention this...
After last year's summer tournament, he
was chosen for the team that went to Cuba.
- What?
- I forgot to mention this...
After last year's summer tournament, he
was chosen for the team that went to Cuba.
Bring a swimsuit
and plenty of money.
In the fourth inning,
he hit a three-run home run.
Bring a swimsuit
and plenty of money.
In the fourth inning,
he hit a three-run home run.
And be sure to bring your bike.
That's all, over and out!
And there's Suzuki
with a big windup...
And be sure to bring your bike.
That's all, over and out!
And the first pitch is a strike.
No problems there.
I still haven't...
And the first pitch is a strike.
No problems there.
That was a good pitch.
I had the feeling that I knew
what Haruhi was going to say.
That was a strong, straight pitch,
thrown a little high and inside.
I had the feeling that I knew
what Haruhi was going to say.
That was a strong, straight pitch,
thrown a little high and inside.
No, not quite.
Perhaps he feels like
he's got nothing left to lose.
No, not quite.
Perhaps he feels like
he's got nothing left to lose.
To be precise, it felt like this exact
same conversation had happened before.
We don't know that yet.
He winds up for the second pitch...
To be precise, it felt like this exact
same conversation had happened before.
We don't know that yet.
He winds up for the second pitch...
I guess it's what you
would call deja vu.
It's a hit! And it's a big one!
It's headed for left field...
And it's good!
It's a single-run home run!
Jyonan has gotten their eighth run!
This gives them yet another point.
Kashima is slowly rounding
third base.
Summer's almost over.
DAY BY DAY unzari dayone dakara
Day by day, everything's just so dull
doudou to kotowacchau
kimi ni narina yo
that's why you need to become someone
that can just reject it all
OH MY BO Y kippari shinakya uso ni
Oh my boy, you need
to be decisive
tsukiatterarenai yo
semai sekai de
I won't deal with any lies
in this small world
jibun de mitsuketa MYSELF
suki ni natte touzen
I found myself on my own,
it's natural you'd fall for me
kudaranai yarikara kette
subete wa atashi ga kimeru
Kick away the boring ways of doing things,
I'm going to decide everything
I SAY I SAY MY HEAVEN
I say, I say my heaven
SUPER DRIVER tosshin
makasete nantettate zenshin
Super driver, leave everything to the rush
and just keep going forward, no matter what
fukanou (DON'T YOU STOP ME)
Tobikoete TAKE IT EASY, GO!
Surpass (Don't you stop me) the idea
of "impossible," take it easy, go!
Daishouri tte doukan
I agree, it's going
to be a huge victory
mochiron dounatta tte kaikan
Of course, it'll feel pleasant,
no matter what happens
hanseikai? (GET BACK TO WILD)
Sore yori saa isoide yo
A review meeting? (Get back to wild)
Forget that, now hurry up
aremo koremo mitaiken
itsudatte muriyari
We haven't tried this or that,
we always do things how we want to
marude marude mikeiken
korekara shimashou
Everything's a new experience,
let's try them out
aremo koremo mitaiken
itsudatte totsuzen
We haven't tried this or that,
we always do things suddenly
marude marude mikeiken
sore ga doushita no?
Everything's a new experience,
what about it?
Endless Eight
You're late, Kyon!
Show some more motivation!
Yeah, yeah.
Sorry I made you wait.
I just got here, too.
- Okay, we're all here, so let's go.
- Where are we going?
To the public swimming pool,
of course!
Well, I guess that makes sense
considering what I brought.
We have to do summer vacation-y things
during our summer vacation!
We can never get back the time
that we've lost!
And so we're going to do them now, in our
one and only summer as tenth graders.
By the way, we're going
to the pool by bike.
Did you ride
your bikes, too?
No, the only two bikes we have
are yours and mine.
Kyon, you'd better not lose
to Koizumi.
This train is leaving
the station!
Come on, you two, hurry up
and park your bikes.
Hey now, Kyon, we're about to go have
fun. This is no time to be exhausted.
Whose fault do you think
this is?
Oh, the scent of chlorine.
This really makes it feel like a pool!
Come on, let's get in!
We're going to race!
No diving
It's dangerous
Come on, let's get in!
We're going to race!
Oh, Miss Suzumiya, wait!
That looks like fun.
It sure does.
This makes me smile, though.
It feels peaceful.
She has some rather normal ways of
enjoying her time, don't you think?
Calling out of the blue to invite someone
out to do something and only giving
a general idea of what's going to
happen isn't what I'd call "normal".
In my opinion,
that's really nothing.
Miss Suzumiya, laughing and having
a good time like that,
isn't likely to shake up
the world, after all.
I hope that's
the case...
What's wrong?
It's nothing... It's probably
just my imagination.
Because so much has happened
since the beginning of spring,
I've become
a little paranoid.
Oh, I lost again!
Yuki, let's go
one more time!
Here I come!
Delicious!
This is delicious, Mikuru!
Jeez.
I think it would be better to call this place
a communal pool than a public pool.
I wonder why Haruhi
chose this place.
Jeez.
I think it would be better to call this place
a communal pool than a public pool.
I wonder why Haruhi
chose this place.
What is this feeling?
Right, and then Haruhi
says this...
"These two are my
brigade members."
"They'll do anything you ask,
so ask for anything you want!"
Okay, let's have some fun!
We're going to play water soccer.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, deja vu isn't
all that uncommon.
Summer outing, pool, Bon festival
fireworks show, part-time job, stargazing...
What is that?
It's a schedule of how we'll spend the
rest of our short summer vacation.
I realized that we only have two weeks
of summer vacation left.
We're going to pick up
the pace!
All this in just
two weeks?
Is there anything else
you want to do, Mikuru?
Umm... I'd like to try
goldfish scooping.
Okay!
Goldfish scooping...
Done!
Pardon me
for a moment.
- Thank you.
- Done already?
Yes.
Okay then,
we're starting tomorrow!
Is there a place nearby with a Bon festival?
A fireworks show works, too.
I'll check around.
Don't forget about the
goldfish scooping!
Roger that.
I'm paying again?
All right, then,
we're done for today!
If you'll excuse me.
I have to go, too...
Nagato!
Umm... no, it's
nothing important.
How have you been?
Everything fine?
Fine.
That's good to hear.
Right.
S-Sorry about
stopping you.
Sorry!
What the heck?
Why did I talk to her?
The next morning, it was a call from
Haruhi that awoke me from my slumber.
They found a place having a Bon festival.
It was tonight at a public park.
Kyon! You're last again!
Jeez.
Oh well. Let's go
buy yukata!
Haruhi entered a women's
clothing outlet store.
Come on, hurry up!
She just went and chose yukata
for Miss Asahina and Nagato,
Leave it to me!
She just went and chose yukata
for Miss Asahina and Nagato,
Leave it to me!
And then headed straight
for the changing rooms.
After making us wait about an hour or so,
the three of them finally came out at once.
What do you think?
We're pretty hot,
aren't we?
You all
look wonderful.
Of course! I chose
these yukata, after all.
Especially Mikuru!
It's so cute on you!
It's just too cute!
Just what you would expect
from my choice!
O-Of course.
Miss Asahina!
Twirl... twirl!
Wow, this is amazing!
Yeah! It's nice and lively!
A Bon festival, huh?
I guess it makes sense for there
to be this many... people.
There... there it is again.
What is this feeling?
Mikuru!
They have goldfish scooping,
just like you wanted!
Be sure to catch
a bunch!
Okay!
Shall we play, too?
How about a competition?
I'll pass.
What about you, Nagato?
Want to eat something?
Oh, you're interested
in that stuff?
- Which one?
- It's all right.
- This one.
- Right-o, that'll be 800 yen.
I kind of got the feeling that
Nagato had been helping us out,
so I thought it would be appropriate
for me to at least buy her that, but...
Thirteen! But I don't need
so many, so I just kept one.
That's amazing.
You can have one,
but only one.
Thanks.
Huh? What's with
the mask?
I bought it.
Huh. I see.
Now then, next up is fireworks! Let's
launch some fireworks to end the day!
It was summer,
and summer vacation.
I won't let you destroy it!
That's why I wanted to forget about it,
but there was one thing
lingering in my mind.
All right, tomorrow we'll be
catching bugs!
Haruhi.
It's fine to want to play around, but are you
finished with your summer homework?
What? You can finish homework
like that in just three days.
Three days!?
You get that stuff out of the way so you can
have fun without having to worry about it.
That's how you enjoy
your summer vacation.
Why is she
so smart?
It seems like the guys up in
heaven that were divvying up
the stats for us were being
pretty lax about it.
And so, tomorrow we'll
be catching bugs!
Whoever catches
the most bugs...
Okay, they'll get to be the
brigade leader for a day!
No thanks!
That sounds interesting.
Are any bugs okay?
Hmm... only cicadas!
That's it, this will be the SOS Brigade's
Cicada Capturing Competition!
The next day was yet again
a beautiful day.
It was on this day that we had the SOS
Brigade Cicada Capturing Competition.
Oh, no!
It was on this day that we had the SOS
Brigade Cicada Capturing Competition.
Oh, no!
It looks like each of us did try,
in their own way,
but of course, or something to that effect,
the winner ended up being Haruhi.
A catch and release attitude
is important, right?
If we let them go, then they
might come back to repay us.
What could a cicada do,
even if it did come back?
There you go! Go back
to the mountains!
For some reason, I kind of feel like
Pandora opening her box.
W-Welcome!
The next day, even though we had
no idea what was going on,
we were made to wear frog costumes for
our part-time job at the supermarket.
Good work, everyone.
What's with this difference
in how we're being treated?
Thanks for the hard work.
The manager is thankful.
I don't care about his thanks.
Where's our pay?
That's it.
I've wanted that
for a while.
The owner said that he'd give it to us
for Mikuru's sake.
We worked, sweat pouring down
our foreheads, for that?
Let's hang that up in the
clubroom as a memento.
Mikuru, you can wear it whenever
you want. You have my permission!
That night, a single phone call
stole me away from my slumber.
Oh, come on!
Hello?
Kyon...
Miss Asahina!?
Yes, it's me...
Something... very not good has...
At this rate, I...
What do I...
- Umm...
- Hello, this is Koizumi.
Why are you with
Miss Asahina?
Certain circumstances
came up.
Would it be possible for you
to come join us right now?
Why you... why you!
What in the world happened,
Miss Asahina?
Kyon...
I... can't go back
to the future...
I can't understand
what she's saying...
In other words,
this is what's going on.
We are going through an eternal loop
of the same time period.
Even if you say something as impossible
as that with a smile on your face...
Koizumi, do you realize what
you're saying? Do you?
I do. Much more than
I wish I did.
I had just been speaking
with Miss Asahina.
Call me too.
And then don't come.
And as a result, what we realized
was that recently,
the flow of time
was a bit strange.
You might want to credit this
to Miss Asahina.
Thanks to her,
I was able to confirm it.
Confirm what?
That we have experienced the same
span of time numerous times.
You said that earlier.
To be precise, we've been repeating
the time from August 17th to the 31st.
We're in the middle of an
endless summer vacation.
Well, it is summer
vacation, but...
It's a never-ending
endless summer.
This world has lost all time
after September 1st.
Who'd believe that?
We'd like for you
to believe it.
Are we trapped inside one of
those closed spaces?
That's not it.
A single portion of time
has been torn away.
At exactly the point when it becomes
midnight on August 31st,
everything resets, and we go back
to August 17th. That's the process.
So what about our...
no, humanity's memories?
Those are reset as well. Everything
starts over from the beginning.
So you mean that time does that
thing that you mentioned.
Well, we do have someone from the
future here, I guess it can't be helped.
Oh no, Miss Asahina
isn't involved in this.
Okay then,
what's the culprit?
I would guess
Miss Suzumiya.
I'm sure she doesn't realize it,
but somewhere inside of her
is a desire to not let
summer vacation end.
What the heck? Do you mean she
feels regret over something?
That's what
I believe.
Perhaps she feels that there's
something left
that she wants to do during
our summer vacation?
Man, the hopeless situations she causes
unfold on a galactic scale.
So, what are you saying
I should do?
If we knew that, we would
have this problem solved.
I've been wondering this since I got here,
but you seem awfully cheerful about this.
It's because we've finally
been able to solve the mystery
of the frequent feelings of
deja vu that I've had recently,
and that you may
have had, too.
Now that I think about it, those inexplicable
feelings may have been
remnants from when our
memories have been reset.
Is it possible that other people
across the world feel this, too?
It doesn't seem that way.
You and I are a special case.
What about Haruhi? Does she
sense any of this at all?
Not at all, it seems. It would
probably be bad for us if she did.
However, I believe that there is
one person who remembers everything,
more than the
deja vu that we do.
And who would
that be?
I think you know,
even without my saying.
- Is that right?
- It is.
- You remember all of it?
- Right.
So, how many times have we repeated
all of this, this time?
This is the 15,527th time.
15,527?
What do you mean by 15,527?
Nagato, what are you saying?
Are you serious?
I am.
You're saying that we've done the
exact same things that many times?
They're not all guaranteed
to happen.
Out of 15,527 repetitions,
there are two occasions,
#2,391 and #11,054, where we
did not go to a Bon festival.
A pattern where we did
go to a Bon festival,
but did not go to a goldfish scooping
stand, occurred 437 times.
We've had a part-time job 9,052 times,
and when we did,
there were six different
kinds of jobs that we did.
In addition to handing out balloons,
we also worked as movers,
cashiers,
we handed out flyers-
That's... enough.
See you later.
15,527 times,
that's what Nagato said.
Times two weeks,
hmm, that's around 595 years.
She alone has memories of all that time,
repeating it all over and over...
Nagato, how must it feel to experience that
same period of time over and over again?
The next day,
we went stargazing.
The location was
Nagato's apartment,
and the telescope was one that
Koizumi had gotten for us.
I wonder if they exist.
- If what exist?
- Martians.
I kind of don't
want them to.
When man finally
sets foot on Mars,
I'm sure that they'll come out
from under their cover and welcome us,
saying, "Welcome to Mars!"
Oh, I'm bored of this.
UFOs. Let's look for UFOs.
Exactly what does she
want to do?
Now what could
that be?
If we could figure that out,
this would all be solved...
How about trying
this out?
Give Miss Suzumiya a sudden
embrace from behind,
then whisper "I love you"
into her ear.
And who would
be doing that?
Is there anyone else who could
fill the role other than you?
I love you... No, I'm graduating
from your control.
All right, how about
if I do it?
I'm kidding. I'm lacking a certain
something for the role.
And all that would do is cause unnecessary
confusion in Miss Suzumiya.
Next, we went off
to a batting center.
Hey, Nagato,
you were aware of this loop before
Miss Asahina said anything, right?
Yes.
If that's the case,
why didn't you say anything?
It's my job
to observe.
I see.
Home run
We continued to run through a torrent
of summer vacation events.
A fireworks show.
Goby fishing tournament.
Test of courage. Movie watching.
We went to the beach.
We just kept going.
Of course, I knew that this
wasn't going to satisfy Haruhi.
Even still, there wasn't anything
I could do about it,
and so we ended up
at August 30th...
With this, we've finished
everything on our list.
Hmm. I wonder if this
was good enough.
But, hmm, well...
I guess this works.
Hey, is there anything else
you want to do?
That's fine, then.
We were able to do a lot this summer,
so that's enough, right?
No, it's not.
You're still not satisfied.
Okay, we're done
for today.
I had tomorrow set aside just in case,
but you can just take the day off.
Let's meet again in the clubroom
the day after tomorrow.
W-Wait, Haru-
Okay, we're done
for today.
I had tomorrow set aside just in case,
but you can just take the day off.
There it is again!
And it's a strong one,
stronger than ever before.
I can't let Haruhi leave.
If she goes, we'll end up repeating
these past two weeks
for the some-thousandth
time again.
But what should I do?
There must have been a hint
somewhere in what Haruhi said.
But what was it?
What has she said
up to this point?
I don't know...
I can't remember...
August 31st.
Impossible
I haven't touched my homework.
Whatever, it doesn't matter anymore.
If we're just going to do it all over again,
then there's no point to doing it.
Whether tomorrow comes or not, I'll leave
it to the me at that time to deal with it.
Sora kara ochite kitanda
It fell from the sky
subete no negai wo nosete
With all of the wishes
that were made upon it
hitotsu no hoshi niwa
chotto omokatta kana
Maybe it was a little too heavy
for a single star
yappari nanika henda yo
Something just doesn't
seem right
kokoro no kimi ga kieta
The image of you in my mind
has vanished
tashika ni oboeteru tte
ieruno kai?
Can I say that
I remember you clearly?
Tomare!
Stop!
Kako wa jibun no mono
The past belongs
to me
touzen daretomo torikaetakunai
Of course I don't want to trade it
with anyone else
nazenara
That's because
basudei datta watashitachi niwa
It was my birthday,
and when we saw each other
deai ga umareta toki ni
We could see
the first dream
hajimete no yume ga mieru
That we had when
we were born
doushiyouka tte
nayanda koto mo
Worrying about
"what do I do?"
Ima omoeba waraeru hodo
datta yo ne
Is laughable when I
think about it now
mou wasureteta
I've already forgotten it
kimi wo sagasou
Let's search
for you