Genshiken
I woke up and as usual forgot
my cell and missed the Express.
My life reflected in
the train window.
I'm sure I have something that
I won't lose to anyone in Japan...
... but it's pretty sad
that no one notices it.
I can't run fast, though.
I'm not that strongly-built.
Here I go, at my dauntless pace.
Pass away, today's
sadness, raining in the sun!
Hesitation, repetition,
dreaming all night, all night.
Farewell sadness,
to outer space you go!
Look to the sky and shout
at the top of your lungs!
At this tempo!
Right now, at this tempo!
Genshiken
Episode 4: The Sublimated Process of Mental Blocks
Regarding the Dissimilation Between Dress and Costume
Hey, Kasukabe.
Why don't you try cosplaying
at the next school festival?
What?
For starters, I recommend
Parn and Deedlit.
I can't stand this guy.
Well?
What the heck is a Parn?
Parn is a knight, and Deedlit is an elf.
Oh! An elf?
Like in Lord of the Rings!
What should I do?
I love Lord of the Rings!
To be precise, she's a high elf.
But she's not thin
enough to be an elf...
Yeah, I figured it might work if
he's Deedlit and she's Parn.
What a maniac!
Well why not?
All we do is set up and show
the same stuff every year.
This might liven things up.
Ow!
Full recovery in two months, huh?
Want it to take a little longer?
I get the point, let go!
Hey, I just know you
two would look great.
Not on your life!
Then how about Bridget and Ino?
I don't even know them, but no!
Well then...
Come in.
Uh, excuse me...
Um, um, is this Genshiken?
Yeah, it is...
I want to find out more about it.
You do?
Aren't you making some mistake?
This is the Society for the
Study of Modern Visual Culture.
I know.
It's a haven for otaku.
A chair, Sasahara.
R-Right.
Have a seat.
Oh, all right...
Here you go.
T-Thank you.
For the record, I'm not one of them.
This is my boyfriend, and he's a
member.
My name's Kohsaka and I'm a freshman.
I'm Kanako Ohno, also a freshman...
Um, I've just returned from living in
America, and I'll enroll next semester...
You lived abroad, huh?
Yes...
This Genshiken crew would
joke, saying it's just "so-so."
I'm Saki Kasukabe.
I'm a freshman too.
Nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you too.
Take my word for it, forget this club.
You'd have to cosplay and whatnot.
What?
No normal person would ever do that.
Uh, I've done it before.
You see?
What?
Wait a second, seriously?
T-Then why don't I
make you some costumes?
Oh, that would be nice.
All mine so far have been pre-made.
For real?
You've done it before?
Uh, yes...
like Queen Amida from Waremono
Chuiki...
That's kind of on the old side.
Wow, if she j-joins, it'll be the
b-birth of Genshiken's female cosplayer.
Tanaka is crying.
You look like you'd be cute if
you took care of yourself, so why?
They'll find out your sizes!
They'll measure you!
Uh, um, um...
When it comes time to measure,
I'll let you do it, and...
...I swear not to divulge the numbers.
That's even creepier.
What's the big deal?
This is something she wants to do.
What?
When someone knows the fun of
cosplaying, you can't talk them out of it!
That said it all.
Mr. Chairman, let's do this
for the Culture Festival.
But she hasn't said she's
joining the club yet.
What character would you like, then?
I'll get to it on the double.
I don't know much about the
latest things in Japan...
She really is into this.
That's fine.
Choosing a character you
like is most important.
Um, then, a character
I can do with my hair.
In that case, I think the
Vice-President from Kujiun or...
...Jam Kuradoberi from
Guilty Gear would work.
Are we really measuring at my place?
It still hasn't been put away.
That's fine.
I don't want to go to their pads,
and I don't want to let them in mine.
So yours is the only one left.
That was mean.
I-Is that so?
Come on, let's just go.
A female otaku's place...
I have to see this...
Um, would you mind
waiting here a minute?
I'll clean up a little.
Oh, then I'll help you.
It won't take long.
Damn!
Damn?
She didn't lock the door just now.
You shouldn't do that.
Oh no?
I won't go.
Fine.
I will.
Bamboo poles for laundry!
Baldies?
Uh, um...
This is what you had to clean up?
Is this a gag?
No.
Oh, you're serious.
Yes...
Tanaka!
Come and see!
Ow!
Wait a minute! Wait!
Tana...
Am I weird?
Am I weird after all?
Wait wait!
I give up...
Tana-
I knew you would act like this!
Beautiful characters
are what's popular at the...
...Manga Club and
Anime Research Society.
I got laughed at a lot by
my friends overseas too.
Am I weird?
What's wrong with it?
The world's full of
people into older guys.
It's a more dangerous thing to...
...hide yourself and be distant
from other people because of it.
If it's really a secret you have to hide,
remember it's just your preference.
You really just want friends.
I'll bet that's why you
didn't lock the door...
You all really are some lonely people...
But still, bald guys
with sunglasses is weird!
You're right, it's weird.
But, they're cool.
I really thought I
was gonna die, though.
I'm sorry.
That was a big step for
me to take all at once.
Am I starting to understand otaku?
No way.
I don't know anime, but it's
definitely pretty boys for me.
Oh, your boyfriend is one.
I guess I don't really go for that.
That makes me happy and
annoyed at the same time.
I'm surprised they sell
this kind of poster.
No, these were never on the market.
Members of a Japanese group I met on
the Net made them and gave me some.
She does have friends,
and they make her stuff...
But what do tastes like
that have to do with cosplay?
They're totally separate.
Cosplay is cosplay, tastes are tastes.
Maybe she's stronger than I thought...
No facial hair?
Ah, no, that's part of it too.
What's with you?
Suioh University
The customer is either out of their
calling area or their phone is turned off.
Genshiken Comprehensive Exhibition
Hey.
Oh, an outsider.
You seen Kohsaka?
I knew you'd make a
good "Jam Kuradoberi."
Cranberry jam?
Jam Kuradoberi. She's a
fighting game character.
Huh...
You look kind of like an alien.
Um, um...
Don't say "Um, um."
Ah, right...
People who don't know the
character won't understand.
It's a type of symbol.
Huh?
Conversely, people who
don't know the character but...
...still say things like "how
cute" won't personally grasp it.
You'll understand if you try it!
You won't if you don't!
She's right, it's a kind of fun you have
to experience through your body.
Actually, I brought
this along with me today.
If you put this beauty on...
...suddenly you'll be cosplaying
even in your regular clothes.
It's surely the strongest of...
I shouldn't have come here.
Oh wow, do they sell those?
Well, they do sell them but...
...this one is a handmade
gem I picked up at an event.
Kohsaka's not with you?
He won't answer his cell.
Maybe he's seeing some
woman from his past?
What?
I doubt it.
If his phone's turned off, that would
make it seem all the more suspicious.
But, it's probable that some
girl might go after him...
Hello?
Hi, yeah...
No way, you're here?
Okay, got it, be right there...
A man from her past?
You could at least say "ex-boyfriend."
All right! Let's make
sure Kohsaka sees this!
Tail her, Sasahara.
No, thank you.
If you want Kohsaka...
T-There's a Guilty Gear
tournament at the Anime Club...
...so don't you think he'd go there?
If you thought that,
you should have told her sooner.
Well, I c-couldn't find
a chance to say it...
Then let's go to the Anime Club.
Is it all right for her
to walk around like that?
Why not? It's a festival.
She can just put a coat on.
But, s-someone has to stay behind.
This is the dokutsurutake, loaded
with alpha amanitin and beta amanitin.
Also called the "Angel of Death,"
just one is enough to kill an adult.
Mureohfuusentake, nicknamed
kurodaikoku.
Porcini yamabushitake...
Yeah, this place sure
is up in the mountains.
Why are you here?
I mentioned in my message the
other day that I might come by.
You did?
Geez, that's cold.
So, want to go have drinks or
something?
You can't have much to do around here.
It may not look it, but I do.
Really, in a drag place like this?
You must've found a new man.
What?
I mean, you were always complaining.
Now you've got things to do?
No way, I'm too late!
I wish you wouldn't put it that way.
You had no chance
even if you were early.
But I thought I had a
chance, judging by your email.
You shouldn't read into
email that deep, you know.
Gotcha.
So, what's he like?
Um...
C-Cute's a good word...
Isn't it better for
you not to know much?
Yeah, I guess so...
For the sake of mental hygiene, eh?
They saw me...
I've got to go.
You do?
And also, let's stop emailing.
What?
I don't think it's a bad thing...
...but I'm really into my boyfriend...
...so I'm going to keep away
from anything remotely dangerous.
Right...
Bye!
Darn it...
Don't tell Kohsaka.
I broke up with that
guy a long time ago.
He came here today on his own,
without even telling me first.
Well, well! He really
was an ex-boyfriend.
You looked compatible
enough... Just right, actually.
Yeah, yeah.
Why'd you break up?
I guess a lot happened?
Don't tell him!
Yes, I swear.
We swear.
Good.
Anime Club: Repertoire, Day 1
Inter-Circle Game Tournament
Oh my, he got behind him!
There he is.
I should have known he'd be here.
Crap, crap, crap.
Another chain!
Whoa, this is amazing!
Kohsaka's really in a
dimension all his own.
He always plays at the
highest form you can imagine.
He's probably on a national level.
Kohsaka is amazing.
So that's all you've got?
Congratulations.
Your prize, 25 years
worth of game software.
Thanks a lot.
You all came by.
25 years worth of crap
games, what the hell?
Some of the ones we
provided are mixed in too.
It's not a big deal, let's
all play them together.
Well, crap games are
good for a laugh at least.
You could say that.
Leave that in the club room
so you and I can go out.
Uh, but I've got
reception duty after this.
Skip it!
Easy for you to say.
You wanna know what she was just...
What?
Nothing.
Huh?
Yeah, nothing.
Jam, please look this way.
Okay.
This way too, please.
Ah, very nice.
Excuse me, please look this way next.
Okay.
Hey, Tanaka.
Yeah, I have permission
from the Anime Club.
No, I mean we could
charge money for this.
You can't have cosplayers
charging money for photography.
But, for free...
If you try it too, we could at
least collect enough to cover costs.
I told you I won't.
I thought so.
It's just the...
...cat ears!
Uh, no sweat.
I mean, you already broke up with him...
You look cute, Saki.
Yes, Saki, you look great.
They work so well on you.
Who would've thought...
C-Can I take your picture?
Saki?
That's a pretty complicated display of
anger.
Especially with those on...
We took no detours or shortcuts...
... and we weren't afraid of
what tomorrow would bring...
... as we kept walking down
Inogashira Street late at night.
Only vivid dreams extended
deep into the shadows.
We aren't quite grown up.
Simple but complicated
glistening like marbles.
The time we could see from there
sparkled, even if nothing big happened.
What we see from the marbles in
our hands now is a little different...
... but they shine faintly nearby.
The allure of cosplay?
I haven't given much
thought to it, but...
Um, um, if anything it's like
floating 3mm off the ground...
...or your body temperature
going up about 3 degrees...
That's the kind of feeling it gives you.
You could say it lets you
be a little more daring.
Say, Kohsaka, what was
your first time like?
Um, it's okay if you don't want to say.
Hmm, I'd have to say it was MS
Gundam.
From there I moved to magical girls
shows, Momo, Mami, Persia, Emi.
Uh, wait...
For RPGs I guess it
was Ultima, on the PC.
Oh, yeah, do you know
the game Life & Death?
I don't even know how many
people I killed in that.
Then Manhole and whatnot.
Umm, what were we talking about?