Genshiken
I woke up and as usual forgot
my cell and missed the Express.
My life reflected in
the train window.
I'm sure I have something that
I won't lose to anyone in Japan...
... but it's pretty sad
that no one notices it.
I can't run fast, though.
I'm not that strongly-built.
Here I go, at my dauntless pace.
Pass away, today's
sadness, raining in the sun!
Hesitation, repetition,
dreaming all night, all night.
Farewell sadness,
to outer space you go!
Look to the sky and shout
at the top of your lungs!
At this tempo!
Right now, at this tempo!
Genshiken
Shall we get going?
Is today a serious meeting?
So it seems.
Not the usual boring fare?
No.
Saki!
Does it still hurt?
There's a lump.
Clean your room up.
Sure, eventually.
Episode 11, The Position of Malice
in the Phenomenon of Urban Crime
Wow, this manga sure
is getting good again...
The cuteness and the hotness!
The clincher is that she's
Tokino's little sister.
She's flat-chested like Renko
while being a total villain.
Come to think of it, she's the first
little sister character in the story.
Koyuki's one too, but having a
crush on her's a little wrong.
We don't really want to
look at her that way, do we?
I-I wonder if the sister relationship
is going to s-stir things up.
I'm not sure Yuu Kuroki can manage it.
But I myself like things like that.
Until now we've seen glimpses
of the more severe aspects...
...of the president's childhood.
Oh, good point.
It's not as if he's
bad at muddled plots.
Yeah! Hurry and publish that manga!
Hey.
What were we here for today?
We need to talk about
the school festival.
Regarding materials for this year...
They're the same as last year's.
Adjourned.
Speedy!
Um, um...
I got permission for a photo shoot.
I won't do it.
This club truly has no motivation.
You really go for the throat, Saki.
So that's it?
What about the manga club?
Since you mention it...
...it seems the manga and anime clubs
are holding a joint large-scale event.
The towns around here are getting
together for some area revitalization...
...and it's called
Animefesta or something...
Towns? You mean local governments?
Yeah, yeah, it's like
they're linked to them.
Who would've thought?
Well, they've also invited guests
from anime studios for a symposium...
...and then they're
having a cosplay contest.
That means it's quite a serious event.
What about us?
Aren't we involved?
Not at all.
They didn't even ask us.
This club really is useless.
We might as well close
down Genshiken altogether.
Are you all right?
Thankfully it was empty.
It hit the same spot.
It hit the same spot!
Time for a major cleanup!
What brought that on?
I've decided, we're doing it!
I can't stand this anymore!
Come on, this meeting
was worthless anyway!
If we don't clean up,
I won't come anymore!
Well, I don't think that
would be such a bad thing...
Don't talk that way, stupid!
Everyone up, then.
We'll start with the magazines!
Did something happen?
She hit her head just as we left...
Why aren't we throwing those out?
We can't decide that for things
that've been here longer than us...
Then try asking the original chairman.
He doesn't come to meetings.
Let's at least get rid of things we have
plenty of or that we obviously don't need.
Uh, well...
That's tough to judge...
Very important.
Let's throw out the porn.
Especially those dojinshi and whatnot...
Well, some of those might
have a premium and be valuable.
Is that so...
Probably...
Then let's sell them.
She's evil.
Hey, why don't we also tear
down all the posters?
N-No, those have too much to
do with the group's identity.
But they're the most
unsightly things in here...
Right...
These look like old club mags.
Mebaetame
From when?
It says '87!
Wow, what a flashback!
That drawing is from
Silver Cyclone Zillios.
'87?
How long ago was that?
Then Genshiken's been
around since then...
The founding
president... r-right now he's...
Don't say it!
Let's pretend we didn't see them.
Well, the magazines are more
or less our personal property...
...so that leaves the toys.
All of the action
figures are in these...
They're mostly broken from being
tossed into cardboard boxes.
It doesn't feel like we've
made much progress, though...
The room's small to begin with.
Yeah, good point.
No need to throw it out right away.
Wrong.
This stuff needs to go ASAP!
She'll make an excellent mother
someday.
She throws out whatever she wants to.
And sh-she calls models
toys and b-breaks them.
Ahh, I want to burn it all.
What're you doing?
Nothing in particular.
What about you?
Well, you were just
staring at the old books.
Yeah, I was thinking
"So these are my enemies"...
And maybe I should burn them.
They're burning.
Watch out!
Put it out!
Holy crap!
They're burning! Burning up!
They're antiques!
Water! Water! Water!
Water!
Fire extinguisher!
I found water!
This water kind of stinks.
I'm sorry!
But why are you standing there?
Burning! Burning! Burning!
What the hell's this?
I'll go get Kitagawa!
And then tell the student council!
Fire extinguisher,
where's a fire extinguisher?
The fire! Action figures on fire!
Smoke! Nasty smoke!
Trip the fire alarm!
Hurry and broadcast an
emergency evacuation!
Yes, ma'am!
Emphasize that it's not
a drill or a mistake!
The evacuation route is the east stairwell!
Yes, ma'am!
Kimura, get on the phone! Not a cell, use
the one in the council office.
Call the fire department
and the university office.
W-Which one first?
Fire department!
Yes, ma'am!
Shouldn't someone call an ambulance?
Was someone injured?
He means a fire engine.
Oh, right, right, fire engine.
Um, I need to be hosed down too.
Aren't you cold?
It's hot...
F-Fire extinguisher!
Where?
You guys clear the hell out of here too!
Let's see, I got called down to the
student council a while ago...
Sure enough, club activities are
suspended indefinitely as a penalty...
...we're banned from using the office...
...and in addition we're banned from
participating in the school festival.
F-Figures.
This was bad timing...
That's odd, we went out of
our way to apologize, too.
It feels like enough apologies
for a whole lifetime.
This isn't a problem you can
just say you're sorry for...
E-Excuse me...
W-What about the cosplay photo shoot?
It's toast too...
Hey I'm sorry, Ohno.
But you don't look too well anyway.
No need to push things.
It just so happens that I got this way
after you splashed me with that water...
Does that mean you can't cosplay, Ohno?
We can still enter
the cosplay contest...
Rather, I think they want us to.
Do you mean that?
It's been advertised, so
even the public can enter.
But they want to see as much
school participation as possible...
That's what I was told.
Yeah.
Thank goodness!
At this point, I'll
have Saki go instead.
No!
That might work.
I didn't want to say it, but all
this happened because of Kasukabe...
What?
I don't want to say it
either, but I agree...
Oh, but wait, a costume!
I don't have a costume.
No problem!
Given a week, I can make anything.
Actually, I already have one for you.
For what reason?
So that if you changed your
mind you could wear it anytime.
What about my sizes?
I saw you at the beach.
It's slightly off, but...
Oh yeah!
Tanaka is to be feared...
Here I thought you only looked at Ohno.
Hah, what say you?
But one week really
is too short a time...
If she were to cosplay,
I had planned to...
...diligently train her on the
charm of her chosen character...
I really wanted three weeks for
her to get into it perfectly.
With only a week, she'll have to pour
over materials night and day.
And I'm sick, to top it off.
But, I might never have a second
chance for Saki to cosplay...
D-Don't get carried away, Ohno!
I still haven't said I'd do it.
No, but cosplaying while not
understanding the character is...
...straying from the path, heresy.
It's not how things should be, but...
You know what, forget it!
Go on, do it!
Think of it as a penalty game.
Kohsaka says he wants to see it too.
I do!
That won't change my mind!
You know what, Kasukabe.
I really don't want to say this, but...
...our activities are suspended and we
can't be part of the school festival.
No matter how half-assed a circle
we may be, this really stings.
You should take responsibility!
Now that's how a chairman talks...
Do I have to no matter what?
Here comes the crying act!
I know I'm at fault for this...
But cosplay has nothing to do with it...
So I still have to
do this no matter...
Yes, you do!
Suioh University
Where's Saki?
She hasn't answered her
cell since yesterday...
Say what?
So she ran...
What?
Don't worry, steps
have already been taken.
Huh?
Kichijoji Station
Shichimei Kan
Welcome!
H-How'd you know I was...
Intuition.
N-No time like the present...
Okay, all you guys please leave.
It's time for Saki to get changed!
Gotcha!
Kohsaka...
Do your best.
They let us in the club room
just for this, after all...
Bye.
It's in your hands, Ohno.
Roger!
You guys are not allowed
to take any pictures!
Oh really?
I think there'll be plenty
of other cameras there though.
Whatever, just not you guys!
When I say that I mean it! Got me?
Did you take a look at the
manga and videos you borrowed?
Of course not, I had no
intention of being here.
Hmm, a person like you shouldn't
be doing this in the first place...
Then let's forget it!
Take your clothes off, please!
She's looking pretty healthy, dammit.
What is that?
A handy portable dressing room, my
own.
I closed the curtains.
Well, better safe than sorry.
Am I seriously doing this?
So, how much do I take off?
Does your bra have shoulder straps?
Yeah, the usual kind...
Then please take it off.
It would be visible.
For real?
It's okay, I guarantee your safety.
I'll bet.
You can keep your bottom on.
Have you finished?
Well, more or less.
Then I'm coming in to put it on you.
All right.
Oh come on, you still
haven't taken it off.
Lay off, I'm doing it now!
You're so gorgeous, Saki...
What?
Do you even think like an old man?
I'm sorry, it's just my honest opinion.
So it's really going to be Kasukabe.
That's right, we're shocked too.
Hey, I'm counting on you.
I don't want you forgetting some critical
piece and the whole thing falling off.
Aren't there gonna be
lots of guys with cameras?
Don't worry, when it comes to
cosplay I don't make mistakes.
I sure hope not.
Okay, first, please
put these pantyhose on.
Yeah.
It's too bad we can't see Ohno,
but this should be priceless...
Yeah, it's just my opinion, but
we probably won't see this again.
But you know, it's like more than half
of this excitement is due to worry...
Yeah, it does feel that way...
Saki, you look mahvelous...
Uh, yeah well I've been
sweating badly for a while now...
Can you move?
It's not too heavy?
Try turning around once.
Yes, ma'am.
Aieee! That's so cute...
I don't get this, I mean, please.
No.
You must be careful about saying and
doing things that cast a pall on the room.
In your case, please take
a "I don't know her well..."
"...but I thought I'd try her
since she's cute." stance!
Right, right, I'll just
act like a fool at this point.
You mustn’t be a fool!
All right...
And so, our special guest is the
former director of Kujibiki Unbalance...
...Tsutomu Mizudori!
Don't say "former!"
So, that lining is really pretty.
You sure get right down
to details, Mr. Director.
How 'bout you get out of the way?
Um, you can only buy cloth
for real school uniforms...
...straight from the manufacturer, so
it requires lots of careful planning.
There you have it, Mr. Director.
In the first place, this
color must be tough to find.
Because it's a bright blue...
We really argued over
this in the planning...
...whether to drop it
another shade or not...
Ahh, you don't say.
So, a lot happened and partway
through, you got dropped.
I'm the one and only Mizudori, you!
Yeah, I guess I succumbed to politics...
I should've asked where we were in line.
Yeah, I'm all nervous about
when she'll be coming out.
Oh crap, Kitagawa's here.
I-I wonder if she's on the lookout...
I hope nothing happens.
...so unfortunately we weren't able to
get Director Yamabata to come today...
That's because he's such a hard worker.
I'm sorry for the tangent there.
This was our second
Vice-President of the day.
Let's have a big round of applause...
I can't take this anymore.
Entry no. 9.
She represents our own school's Society
for the Study of Modern Visual Culture!
T-There she is!
This is our third Ritsuko
Kubel Kettenkrad of the day!
Ugh, they're taking pictures...
Did you make this costume yourself?
No, a friend made it for me.
Who is that friend?
Um, an upperclassman in my club.
It's an amazing arrangement.
It's a combat uniform for the President
based on the Vice-President's.
Then, does that mean this
is an original design?
That's right.
Ugh, they're here too.
Oh, Kohsaka.
Are you happy?
You're too far away to tell...
Why're you here?
And are you laughing?
Ohh, let this end soon...
Okay, thank you very much!
Our next person is Maori Haru.
What are you filming?
F-Filming...
Spy camera!
Who is in charge here?
That's me...
The executive committee will deal
with this person, so please continue.
Bring him along!
Miss President...
Miss President.
It's the president.
Miss President!
S-Say what?
Miss President?
Congratulations, Saki!
O-Ohno?
That was just amazing!
I'm not all that thrilled
at praise from people like them.
The most important thing is to
have fun wearing it yourself.
Did you have fun?
In terms of just clothes, I can't
say it felt fun to wear this.
But maybe, on the contrary...
...the real idea is the fun
of becoming a manga character.
Right, right!
You were totally the president.
If you say so, I must have missed it.
Too bad.
Yeah...
I might as well at least find out
what the character I did is like.
Guess I'll read those manga I borrowed.
By all means!
Um, Miss Kasukabe?
I'm with the student council,
Could you come to our office?
The police are here about what happened
and they'd like to question you...
Okay, I'll get changed and come over.
Well, they want you to come
right away, as you are.
Huh?
Hey, hold up.
Is this necessary?
Did Kitagawa set this up?
It's harassment, I swear it!
Saki!
In the end, she underwent
police questioning in costume.
Also, the policeman displayed
quite an interest in said costume.
In fact he asked more questions about it
than the crime itself...
Never...
I'll never cosplay again!
We took no detours or shortcuts...
... and we weren't afraid of
what tomorrow would bring...
... as we kept walking down
Inogashira Street late at night.
Only vivid dreams extended
deep into the shadows.
We aren't quite grown up.
Simple but complicated
glistening like marbles.
The time we spied from there sparkled,
even if nothing big happened.
What we see from the marbles in
our hands now is a little different...
... but they shine faintly nearby.
I don't see what the big deal is.
After all, I did a good deed for
you guys, so about those penalties...
That's apples and oranges.
One must be punished
for one's wrongdoing.
Anyway, the police want to commend
you, but only if you go in costume.
Then I won't go!
Being discontinued
really sucks, doesn't it?
What're you saying?
Did you see Gundam?
Layzner? Yamato? Triton?
Well, yes, I saw them...
You hear talk about business
proposals with the hopes of...
...long term broadcasting
periods of one, two years...
...then ratings or toy sales go into
a slump and the dream is shattered...
...and the original story,
not to mention episode count...
...gets condensed and it ends abruptly.
However!
Series that were discontinued yet
called masterpieces are not few.
No! Rather the fact they're discontinued
is proof they're masterpieces!
Huzzah for discontinuation!
Huzzah!