Which will it be,
as God in heaven says...
Two hearts in balance!
Kujibiki Unbalance!
Love, dreams, yearning,
don't let them stop.
The dazzling sun through the trees
sparkles and dances in your eyes.
I want to gaze at
you beside me always.
Do you remember?
Our childhood promise.
Two hearts in balance!
Kujibiki Unbalance!
Come on, predict where
we'll be tomorrow.
It's just so-so, balance.
Kujibiki Unbalance.
Love, dreams, yearning,
don't let them stop.
Sis! Time to get up!
Uh-oh.
Episode 1: The Study
of Modern Visual Culture
Suioh University
You by yourself?
Y-Yes.
Like mahjong?
Every played it for fun?
Sure...
Oh, you have?
It's handy when you get a job, and it
pays off a lot more than part-time work.
No, uh, I'm not interested...
Hey, are you a freshman?
Have you picked a club?
I like your style.
You should come see our
Media Club, it's great.
Lots of our members end
up in big-name media jobs.
But we have fun, too. We start
off by playing tennis at Tateshina.
Get lost.
Just split, right now.
Hey, you!
What?
What year are you?
Is that you, Saki?
Huh?
No way!
Kohsaka?
B-But didn't you have short hair?
That was in grade school.
It's been years since then.
So, what were you listening to?
A CD by the voice
actress Sumire Matsuzawa.
Really?
Voice actress?
Anime Research Society
That was an editorial decision.
Nakamoto promotional cels sure suck.
What a letdown.
Tsutomu Mizudori...
Wasn't he his apprentice?
Why does he make harem anime?
Manga Research Society
His boss said at Animerama that...
...he was an incompetent apprentice...
Manga Research Society
...and he personally
expelled him or something.
I saw one episode, it was okay.
H-Hey, you're really
interested in the Manga Club?
Yup.
Astronomy Research Society
How about the Astronomy Club?
You used to have a telescope, Kohsaka.
I sure did.
But for now, I'll try
talking with the Manga Club.
Anime Research Society
Um...
Manga Research Society
All right!
Excuse...
Excuse me!
What kinds of things does
the Manga Club do here?
Oh, you want to join?
Yes.
Well we've got more of a
history than the Anime Club.
We do various things...
...but I guess the main ones are
releasing hand-drawn mags and...
...drawing likenesses
at the school festival.
Unfortunately there're only a few of us
now, but we used to have around fifty.
Oh, of course there's no hazing
like in the physical clubs.
And we deal with the student
council, but that's about it.
Society for the Study of Modern Visual Culture
I've decided on my summer costume.
Y-You'll make Miss President's helmet yourself?
Society for the Study of Modern Visual Culture
As long as I use a
German army one as a base.
T-The problem is how heavy it is.
In reality it won't be.
I-lf you make this, you
should do it right.
The Society for the Study
of Modern Visual Culture P23
The Society for the Study of
Modern Visual Culture Room 304
Here we are.
A few days later
The Society for the Study
of Modern Visual Culture
Genshiken
Here we are.
Oh?
Are you with Genshiken?
Are you one of the upperclassmen?
No, l-I'm a freshman...
Just like me, then.
Have you joined already?
No, not yet, I thought I'd come see...
Is that so.
I've already joined.
Huh?
Care to see?
Sure.
Hello!
Hello.
This guy wants to check out the group.
I'm okay...
You don't have to...
Ah, there's some over...
Ugh, it's warm...
Kohsaka, is Kasukabe coming today?
Who knows?
I haven't heard.
Then today we're without our
"straight woman" Kasukabe.
She's so good at it, though.
I'm really sorry.
But it's not like she's joined yet.
Right.
Did you see the Kujiun opinion site?
It felt very divided.
Whatever they thought of it,
there were a lot of screen captures.
T-There were already
comments by French people.
W-What a laugh.
Maybe it's not such a badly made
show...
...and it's easy for
first-timers to get into it.
T-The scriptwriter Yokotari
o-originally did Crusher.
Yeah, I think it's an adventure
framework, like Tarurun Family was.
T-They all get blown up.
Yeah, yeah.
It has good points so will it be a good
adventure or just go out on a limb?
I wonder which way Kujiun will go.
Hmm, i-it's okay...
Yeah.
Have you seen it?
Huh?
Kujibiki Unbalance.
Uh, no. Sorry...
I-It said "Muranaka" on
the original drawings.
It didn't really seem to fit.
Didn't he originally do action stuff?
N-No, lately he's been doing
p-promotional cels and whatnot.
He's generally involved
in Studio Pulp productions.
Maybe he gets used for
convenience, since he seems speedy.
Ah, that's probably true.
That's Shonen Magazoone.
I still haven't read this week's...
What's up?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Oh, okay.
Hey, the cooking match has started.
Start!
Let's go!
Yamadoritakemodoki...
A c-cooking match in
the first episode, h-huh?
It's cool to show off,
but that's pushing it.
It could also be because
it's the first episode.
To present a world view and
developments to the viewer.
Doesn't that make it
too hard to understand?
At first glance, you can't tell if it's a
romantic comedy or an action show.
The director spends some time
making this fight the central point.
F-Fight?
K-Kujiun isn't about fighting.
But to introduce Renko and
Yamada, they had to have a fight.
What a dilemma...
Hello.
That's Final Fantasy, but
I'm not sure which one...
Oh, okay. I got it.
Mr. Chairman.
Let's go.
Don't have too much fun.
That was from Laputa.
S-Sorry, I have to do something.
Huh?
S-Somebody should
c-come back before long.
Oh, you have to go?
S-Sorry.
It's down to just us.
So? Will you join?
Hmm, I don't know.
What made you join?
Hmm.
Well, the easygoing
atmosphere seems to suit me.
Flower Girl Lunlun?
Yeah, I'm in the club office...
Okay, all right.
Sorry, my turn.
Saki needs to see me.
Oh, okay...
It's cool, just watch some Kujiun.
Oh right...
In a room like this, there's
bound to be some erotic stuff...
I've wanted to, but
I've never bought one...
This is a dojinshi!
Wow!
We saw everything, you know.
W-What?
A figure's just not the real
thing if you can't see panties.
Or maybe you've only seen them
in model magazine photos?
Wha...
Take a look out the window.
Huh?
Higher up.
Hi, Mr. Chairman, good work.
You can come back.
Don't sweat it, this happens every year.
They get everyone.
T-They got me too last year.
They haven't gotten me.
So...
You're one of us!
Why not join?
Yo.
Gimme back Kohsaka.
Huh? Another one?
What's with him?
His baseless pride has crumbled.
A-Are you a member too?
Do I look it?
Do I look like I'm one of them?
What?
That wasn't a hard question!
Suioh University
Hi, Sasahara.
Can I sit here?
Sure, go ahead.
You aren't really
showing up at Genshiken.
Why not?
Um, well...
It's not like I actually joined...
Oh, I see.
Why's that?
It don't really think it suits me.
You think so?
You look like a perfect fit.
Well, maybe you're right then...
You don't really look that way.
Oh, really?
I mean, you've got a girlfriend.
Not now, I don't.
You don't?
But the other day...
Well, that doesn't mean we're going out.
But, we are together a lot.
Maybe Saki's interested in me.
What do you think?
I-I suppose you're otaku...
Otaku, and yet...
That's right, they're otaku.
It's 30 minutes from Shinjuku,
but it doesn't feel like Tokyo with all
those mountains!
It's the middle of nowhere!
There's not a single fun thing to
do around there for a young couple.
That's hilarious!
Why do they spend so
much time playing games?
Want to come over today?
We'll go head to head.
What?
Night Shift Academy
Do you play adult games?
N-No thanks.
Oh, okay.
Then, fighting games?
S-Sure, okay.
Yeah!
Uh, I'm sorry, I don't think I can win.
Then, what to do?
Let's call the club guys.
I think they're about
as good at this as you.
No, um...
Greetings, we're here.
Capcom Vs. SNK?
Forget that, let's play some COF.
I don't have the system.
Okay, that then.
Let's do league matches.
I'll make a chart.
What about regulations?
Can we switch characters?
I think we should be able to.
Cool.
K-Kohsaka, can I read some manga?
Go ahead.
Pick the box lunch you want.
We'll figure out the money later.
Kohsaka, I need some paper.
All right.
Just decide, already.
Become part of the group.
Come on, just say it.
Get to know me, include me, fulfill me!
Is seaweed okay?
S-Sure.
Then here.
Hello, Kohsaka speaking.
Hi, Saki.
So I went to Harajuku today,
and on the way home...
...I bought a bunch
of clothes and a cake.
Can I come over right now?
Go ahead.
Let's all hang out.
"AII?"
Right, the Genshiken guys are here.
Yeah, we're playing games.
You sure?
That's too bad.
Yeah.
Okay?
Don't worry, we're all leaving.
Huh?
You can come over, it's all right!
Okay...
Who is this, anyway?
Sasahara.
Anyway, come over,
we're leaving soon.
Are you sure?
Sasahara?
He must be the one I hit
on impulse the other day...
It'd be really messed up
if I owed him for this.
He's a weird guy.
Kohsaka?
Yeah.
Hmm...
A bit.
You don't throw a mundane girlfriend
into the same room as us.
W-We're the ones who get shafted.
S-She doesn't seem to
be his girlfriend, yet.
What?
What's with him?
Isn't Kohsaka the only
one who thinks that?
I can't really say.
Um, I'm sorry I said we were leaving.
It's just as well.
It was the thing to do.
All right then, where should we go?
To do what?
Um...
Can I suggest something?
You can try, Sasahara.
Does anyone have any adult video
games?
I've never played one.
Very well, let's go to Kugayama's place.
W-Why my place?
Because it's the biggest.
What, again?
H-Hey, you mean no matter what?
Seize the day.
What I'm lacking is determination...
The determination to
live the way I want...
We took no detours or shortcuts...
... and we weren't afraid of
what tomorrow would bring...
... as we kept walking down
Inogashira Street late at night.
Only vivid dreams extended
deep into the shadows.
We aren't quite grown up.
Simple but complicated
glistening like marbles.
The time we could see from there
sparkled, even if nothing big happened.
What we see from the marbles in
our hands now is a little different...
... but they shine faintly nearby.
I'm going to try this on, then.
Keep your head turned.
Sure.
Don't look.
I really mean it, don't.
Sure.
"Animation" comes
from the Latin "anima."
In other words, its word
root means "the soul."
"Animism" is the ideal from the
19th century anthropologist Tylor's...
..."Primitive Culture," which advocates
that souls reside in all things.
Animation is therefore what gives
movement to still pictures...
...and breathes life into them.
Namely, the power of the gods!
Some gods are evil, though.