Genshiken
I woke up and as usual forgot
my cell and missed the Express.
My life reflected in
the train window.
I'm sure I have something that
I won't lose to anyone in Japan...
... but it's pretty sad
that no one notices it.
I can't run fast, though.
I'm not that strongly-built.
Here I go, at my dauntless pace.
Pass away, today's
sadness, raining in the sun!
Hesitation, repetition,
dreaming all night, all night.
Farewell sadness,
to outer space you go!
Look to the sky and shout
at the top of your lungs!
At this tempo!
Right now, at this tempo!
Genshiken
How the wind blows...
Episode 5, The Boundary Between Rejection
and Acceptance Seen in Autonomous Behavior
This sure is sudden.
And it's this semester.
At least wait until the
end of the school year.
You said it.
Notice from Club Student Council
As a result of no evident activity
it has been determined that...
... the following clubs will be
dissolved by the end of December.
The Society for the Study
of Modern Visual Culture
S-She's all smiles.
That's a Kohsaka-esque smile.
You really look happy...
You can speak, you know...
Oh well, what can you do when the
whole club's getting closed down?
Right?
That's true.
Yeah!
What do we do?
What's that supposed...
I guess it's legit, then?
Um...
Isn't that what it means
now that they've decided?
But I only just recently joined...
I guess you should've joined the
Manga Club or whatever after all.
Well, not that I'd really know.
How can you say that, Saki?
Because I'm not a member here!
Yet you're here all the time.
It ain't because I wanna be.
Even if Genshiken is dissolved, it
won't solve your otaku problems...
Nothing.
I wonder why we got chosen.
Aren't there other clubs that
don't appear to be active?
Being chosen before Kingaiken does
certainly seem a little unreasonable.
K-Kingai?
The Society for the Study of the
Present-day Food Service Industry.
What's that?
They mainly try the food
at family restaurants.
That's it?
That's it.
And you're below them...
All righty.
Well, it is true that we
hardly ever "do" anything.
I guess recycling 90% of what we
used...
...at the school festival
was a bad idea after all...
Yeah, well...
Hmph, you guys.
You don't have the guts to
protest the council, do you?
It looks like you're just going to give in.
Hi there!
So Genshiken's going under?
I had a feeling it would
happen eventually, you know.
I mean, it doesn't serve any purpose.
Kohsaka, once this place is
gone come to the Manga Club.
Our arms are open!
Ohno, cosplay's the "in" thing.
We could really use you.
Right...
Sexual harassment.
We don't need Madarame and crew.
Is that so.
I don't like him.
Nobody likes him.
So that's it?
I can't have Kohsaka
joining that guy's club.
But once this one is gone...
You'll join them?
It's not like you don't do anything.
What about that cosplay
photo session at the festival?
But later on, the club council got mad
at us for not arranging that beforehand.
Yeah.
They were mad, all right.
Yeah, yeah.
You guys all piss me off.
So, what's it going to be?
Come again?
Are you going to let
one scrap of paper and...
...that abdominal-breathing aardvark
dude be the end of Genshiken?
Well?
Hold on, didn't you want
to see Genshiken fail?
Oh yeah, I sure do.
But, I can't stand to
see it happen like this!
Or to see you guys not
even get mad about it...
Ohno.
Yes?
Let's go.
W-Where?
The council office! Come on, stand up.
But, right now?
Yes!
Why me?
Sex appeal!
Wh-What do you think?
I think she's totally lost it.
L-Looks like trouble.
What do we do?
I don't know if it matters anymore...
Club Student Council Of fice
Ahh, I knew you'd come...
Stick out your chest.
I can't.
Maybe that notice was a little abrupt...
I'd like you to reconsider.
Mr. Chairman, I'll handle this.
I'm Vice-chairman Kitagawa.
Let me explain the situation.
One reason is that we are at
capacity for club office space.
The applications for new
clubs are listed here...
Not every one of them is legitimate...
...but several have submitted
detailed written activity programs.
Still, announcing the closure of
clubs without any previous notice is...
Wait.
There's one more important thing.
The number of clubs that hardly
do anything is considerable.
That itself wouldn't be so bad...
...but some abuse their office
simply as a gathering spot.
They chat, they eat, they smoke, they
drink, they nap, they store things.
These uses are unacceptable and they
are extremely widespread!
Why do we have to provide precious
office space to scum like that?
I don't understand it!
Uh, Kitagawa...
Furthermore, according to
something I overheard today...
...there are some who say they plan
to ignore our warning and remain!
Scum like that will be forced to vacate
with the help of the athletic clubs!
Their property will be
divvied up between other clubs!
K-Kitagawa...
Hold on.
Genshiken has been investigated.
All they do in their
office is play video games!
At the school festival
they held what became a...
...cosplay photo shoot
without authorization!
The only things of enough value to
warrant a precious club office are here!
Those game systems are older ones,
and they have a lot of research value.
Huh?
It may look like they're
just playing, but games and anime...
...are the most essential elements of
modern visual culture.
Watching over its development and
transformation is the main activity of...
...Genshiken, namely the Society for
the Study of Modern Visual Culture.
And regarding the
school festival cosplay,
it was certainly wrong to
not make advance arrangements...
...but wasn't it also evidence
of the club's activity?
That alone is enough to keep it out
of the doomed inactive club category.
Any way you look at it, I'd
say that someone is using...
...some nasty screwed up
interpretation...
...to crush Genshiken
through treachery and malice.
What'd you just say, you otaku?
I'm not an otaku!
Kitagawa, calm down.
Saki...
Saki did the best she could.
So, how'd it go?
Isn't that obvious?
She seems even more
unapproachable than usual.
S-She's dangerous right now.
Genshiken
That dick, Kitagawa...
"Dick"...
She's a woman...
A dried up sexless wench like
her is the same as a dick.
She's the type who'd strap on a
helmet...
...and plunge right into
the riot police if she could.
Ouch...
Calling people otaku...
Hey, can anyone figure
out what her weakness is?
Like with a wiretap, or hidden camera.
What makes you ask?
Is that really the light you see us in?
But you're all otaku.
None of us are techie otaku!
Useless...
Ow...
Besides, isn't this
a personal grudge now?
That's because you guys weren't there.
We can't be careless
about things about this.
Kitagawa's serious.
You're really gonna be
crushed and driven out of here.
You okay with that?
We aren't...
Dammit!
Suioh University
Takana Soba
discontinued
Excuse me, why isn't
there any more takana soba?
I don't really know, but I
guess not many people bought it?
If that's the case, I've
never seen anyone buy or eat...
...any of the "mackerel bean sprout
tendon" or the "taro gyoza" out of...
You know, you should ask
someone above me about it.
They don't have the
one you like anymore.
It's not a big deal...
Oh, I always just get this.
Hey, about those new clubs
that want to start up...
You're here alone?
And early, too.
I was wondering if there's a
good way to get at Kitagawa.
You're headstrong too, Saki.
I have something you may find useful.
Mr. Chairman, when did you get here?
Just now.
You know something I can use?
Yeah, listen to this.
The Variety Discussion Group?
Maybe it's a chat club?
That's absurd! It must be a joke!
Hi.
Hello.
What do you want?
Well...
Kitagawa, let's talk outside real quick.
Huh?
What gives?
Oh there's nothing to worry about.
Watch your step.
I don't trust this.
If Genshiken goes away, the first
problem we'll be up against is...
...losing a room where we can gather.
Are you guys cold?
Let's go to the cafeteria,
it's warm in there.
What's this about?
Winter sure has arrived.
Isn't winter great?
Huh?
I mean, summer sucks
because it's so hot!
I think summer and winter
both have their good points.
Yeah, but y'know, when it's hot and
muggy it makes you feel all itchy.
Like on your head and... feet!
How did you know?
W-Whatever do you mean?
Oh, it's not hot...
You'd even threaten me to make
sure your club can keep going?
All I'm trying to say
is that summer sucks.
Just tell me how you know.
Did you hear it from someone?
I saw it with my own eyes.
It must have been about a month ago.
A month ago?
The council office door
was slightly ajar...
You were putting on
athlete's foot medicine...
I had a feeling I was being watched...
Now, don't you have something to say?
Or rather, aren't we the ones
with the bargaining chip now?
Pardon me.
Is anything wrong, Kitagawa?
No, it's nothing...
But...
You can go back in the office...
Hey, Mr. Chairman.
What do you think about all this?
The way that notice went out
about the clubs closing down.
Don't you think it's mean, not
giving them a foot to stand on?
Hmm, it might have been better to
go through a probation period first.
Wouldn't it?
That's what Kitagawa
and I were discussing.
It looks like she understands too.
So, Mr. Chairman, let's just
pretend that never happened.
Just a moment.
Kitagawa, are you sure nothing's
wrong?
Nothing, really...
Is it the athlete's foot?
How did you know?
Well... sorry, I've seen it.
The medicine was
sticking out of your bag.
It looks like he knew...
Wait, no, that doesn't matter!
Would you like to go out with me?
All of a sudden...
Seriously?
I'm serious, I've been
waiting for the chance.
But you might catch
it from a floor mat...
Fine! Infect me!
Thank goodness.
As long as we submit a written activity
program, we can be re-evaluated.
At this rate, I'm sure
Genshiken won't be shut down.
I guess.
But in a way it feels like
this worked out too well.
Huh?
Did our chairman
already know about them?
Hey!
Listen, Kasukabe.
You're saying it here?
It's not like we're cool
with Genshiken shutting down.
So, well, we can at least help you.
Let us!
You guys are a riot, worse than useless!
We've already taken care of it.
Uh, you have?
Hello, porcini!
Tokino Akiyama spotted! Shall I attack?
Wait, a fool like you would
never hit her at that range.
Encircle her, then...
Ah, Mr. Chairman.
It went well.
The scenario turned out
a little different though.
I see.
Now the chairman and
vice-chairman are an item.
Really...
Did you know about them?
No, I didn't...
But how about officially
joining Genshiken, Kasukabe?
No.
That was prompt.
Mr. Chairman, there's no way
she'll ever join, is there?
Well, I guess you needn't
be forced into it...
You've used this
office so much as it is.
You're practically a member anyway.
What do you mean?
Kohsa...
Mr. Chairman, the student
council thing was weird enough...
...now why do you know about that?
Is it really a coincidence?
Yeah, you and Kohsaka
are also a coin...
That's a lie!
I made sure I was very careful.
Don't tell me you use spy cameras?
I would never do such a thing.
Something like that would be really
bad...
A ton of trouble for me!
What a bind...
What're you doing?
If I were that kind of person...
...there would already be
a large number of people...
...irrespective of gender who
could no longer attend this school.
But there are no such people, are there?
I'll join.
What?
What's wrong, Kasukabe?
S-Seriously?
T-Then are you going to cosplay?
I doubt it.
I'm thrilled to be "one of us."
That being said...
...for now it would be best not to
use the 1st or 2nd floor bathrooms...
That was a joke...
Frigging athlete's foot couple!
Thanks to you I had to...
It sure was a surprise when
you joined Genshiken, though.
It surprised me too.
Otaple.
Otaple?
I'd say it probably
means "otaku couple."
What'd you say?
We took no detours or shortcuts...
... and we weren't afraid of
what tomorrow would bring...
... as we kept walking down
Inogashira Street late at night.
Only vivid dreams extended
deep into the shadows.
We aren't quite grown up.
Simple but complicated
glistening like marbles.
The time we could see from there
sparkled, even if nothing big happened.
What we see from the marbles in
our hands now is a little different...
... but they shine faintly nearby.
Viva! Model Train
Viva! Mushrooms
I say we do this.
Thirty minutes remain.
We're out of time.
Chihiro, you're into computers.
I'll bet you know what kind of
homepage draws in the most people.
Well, yes I do.
Then tell us!
We can make a homepage
based on that theory!
But I don't think you'll...
This is no time to argue about it!
What? I'm not doing that!
Chihiro! What's gotten into you?
That's why I didn't want to tell you...
Fifteen minutes remain.
We've got no choice.
Huh?
Their site's lame-o!
We're about to demolish them!
WTF!
One minute remains!
What's the matter?
When you cosplayed for the school
festival, where'd you get changed?
In here...
What is it?
Hey, what's wrong?
Did you see Kujiun yesterday?
Yeah, I saw it. It was crazy.
"The Federation's art
department is a monster!"
Oh, but I saw on the homepage that the
art director is setting up a new studio.
What? "I'll become
the executive king"?
And so, it seems there's a lot
of trouble brewing there now.
"He stole something quite
precious. Your employees."
Hey, all those otaku
quotes are really stupid.
"Once again I have
said a worthless thing."
Knock it off!
Coming! I'm coming!