Congratulations, Louise Françoise.
I really am unworthy of such
an honorary title as Chevalier.
You all achieved something
that deserves that title.
Capturing the thief that had
the entire Palace up in arms...
I thank you as well,
trustworthy familiar.
Oh, no...
I trust that you will continue to
take good care of my dear friend.
You should not, Princess!
To allow your hand
to such a familiar...
To protect you is equal to
swearing loyalty to me.
There must be something in return
for such an oath of loyalty.
A hand? So I'm being treated
like a dog after all?
That's not it.
To put it bluntly, you can kiss her.
Ki...
I can't be that fearless!
Hurry up. You're being rude.
Then, excuse me.
Huh?
What did you just do to
the Royal Highness?!
You dog!
A history of the couple's romance
that starts from the first kiss
You, the one who cast magic on
this destiny, suddenly appeared
The sky where two moons
never fade away
That's an impossibility, right?
This is the first time I've
felt anything like this
I'm feeling more and more
at ease with this place
Even if you trip and
become depressed
I will always hold you
tight with a squeeze
The story where we met that day
stays hot with a sweet kiss
See, you can cast magic, and
the wishes will surely come true
A history of the couple's romance
that starts from the first kiss
You, the one who cast magic on
this destiny, suddenly appeared
Louise's Part-time Job
I am terribly sorry about this!
Hey!
Hurry up and apologize!
I'm sorry.
But you said I could kiss her.
What idiot out there
would kiss her lips?!
Right here.
It is all right...
A reward is necessary
for an oath of loyalty.
Actually, I have a favor to ask of you.
Please, go ahead and
ask anything of us.
If you tell us to die, I will immediately
throw myself out of the window,
and take this stupid dog with me!
Wait, hold on! What are...
Be silent!
I would like you two to live
in the village for a while.
In the village?
Thank you!
So dull...
But you're the one
that said we needed
to buy new clothes
to dress up as peasants.
But don't you think we can get
some clothes that are more decent?
Come on, do you really get what
we're supposed to be doing?
Of course I do!
This is a warrant published
by the Palace.
You want us to do some
spying in the village?
Lately, I often hear rumors of
nobles oppressing the peasants.
When I asked those in the area,
all of them said that such a thing
would never happen,
as the nobles were good
role models for the peasants.
However, seeing the case between
you two and Count Mott,
I cannot discount them
as simple rumors.
Therefore, I would like you
to investigate the goings-on
in the village in secret.
It will be a very difficult job.
Well understood, Princess!
I will make sure to get this job done,
as if my life depended on it!
Now I'm worried about
what's going to happen.
Next up is a horse.
A horse?!
Really... A horse costs 400 equs?
One horse uses up all
the money we were given!
200 equs?!
Our inn is top-class, one where
even nobles can spend the night.
We don't have nearly enough money.
You can look for
a cheaper inn, can't you?
No way. I can't sleep
in a cheap room!
So this job was impossible for
a girl of noble birth after all.
Fine, I'll make do by myself somehow!
Make do? What are you going to do?
Don't follow me!
Hey!
You blew it all at the casino?!
But they said I'd end up
with more for sure.
That's why I can't leave you alone.
Be quiet!
I'm thinking about what
we should do from here.
No choice but to bow down to the
Princess and get some more, right?
This task is one that the Princess
asked as a personal favor.
I'm sure she had lots of trouble
coming up with the money.
You knew that,
yet you wanted a horse,
and just had to sleep
in an expensive inn...
I'm amazed you could want so much.
Because I need them.
I'm hungry.
Finding somewhere to sleep
comes before food.
Trés bien!
Such a beautiful face!
From the looks of it, you seem
to be in some sort of trouble.
Bonjour! Bon!
As you can obviously see,
I am nobody suspicious at all.
No, better to say you are,
from the looks of it.
I am Scarron. I run
a tavern just up ahead!
A tavern?
Yes! A tavern!
Would you like me to furnish
you two with one of our rooms?
Really?
Saito!
H-o-w-e-v-e-r, on one condition.
Understood, my fairies?
Yes, Manager Scarron!
Not like that!
When we're in the shoppe, I've told
you to call me "Mi Madmoiselle!"
Yes, mi madmoiselle!
Trés bien!
Such ecstasy!
Now, good news to all fairies!
We have someone new joining us here
at the Enchanting Fairy Tavern today!
Louise, come on in!
Louise is a poor little girl
who ran away
with her older brother
right before her father
sold her off to pay for
his gambling debt!
Oh, my!
Poor thing!
I'm Louise.
Nice to meet you.
Now, applause!
Oh, man...
She looks pretty upset.
Hey, new guy, come help
clean the dishes!
We're about to open!
Sure, right away!
You have a very cute younger sister.
Thanks.
What?
Nothing. I'm Jessica. You are?
I'm Saito.
Saito? That's an unusual name.
I get that a lot.
Nice to meet you, Saito.
Ask me if you have anything you
want to know about this place.
Nice to meet you!
That stupid dog...
Now, everyone...
Now that I've introduced our new girl,
I'm pleased to announce that this
week is the long-awaited tip race!
Tip race?
The fairy who earns the biggest
tip total gets a special bonus.
And, ta-dah!
You will have the right for one day
to wear the family heirloom
that is our namesake,
the Enchanting Fairy Bustier!
So wonderful, mi madmoiselle!
Trés bien!
This bustier is enchanted with
magic that charms people,
so the day you wear this,
you can earn without limit!
Earning without limits?!
The girl who won the race
last year earned so much,
she went back to her hometown!
So all of you, do your best,
in hopes of being able
to wear this bustier!
Yes, sir!
You too, new girl!
Sure!
This is my chance!
I've brought you what you ordered.
What are you doing, girl?
Hurry up and pour it.
Serving a peasant... Me, a noble?
What are you dong? Hurry up with it.
This is a mission. This is a mission.
Then, I would like to serve you now...
What are you doing?!
I'm sorry...
You're a cutie.
It's a shame that you
don't got much boobs!
Then, to make up for it, I want you
to serve me mouth-to-mouth.
What was that for, you brat?!
You filthy scum!
How dare you do this to a Duke's...
Oh, I'm terribly sorry.
She's a new girl, so she's
not used to this yet.
Louise, bring a new washcloth.
Okay!
In her place, I'll provide you
with very special service!
Hold on, stop it... No!
You've got to be kidding!
Why do I, a daughter of a Duke,
have to deal with such a...
Calm down...
For now, we've secured
a place to sleep and some food,
and on top of that we can
make some money.
A place to sleep? Where?
You mean this attic that
looks more like a closet?
He said that a lot of his
customers were nobles.
So we're killing three birds
with one stone, right?
You're well off.
You seem to be having
fun with that girl.
Girl?
Nothing.
But you're going to make a noble
like me sleep in a place like this?
If you don't want to sleep,
you can do whatever you please.
There were too many things
going on today, so I'm tired.
How can you adapt
to things so quickly?!
Well, that's the only good trait I have.
Besides, it's not much different
from how I'm usually treated.
Geez! His master is forced
to wear something like that,
and he feels nothing of it?
At the least, he could...
Why do I...
What, she's just a kid!
I thought this place
promised sexy girls...
You're very pretty!
Coquettish girls like you are my type.
Especially those really flat...
You're Mr. Scarron's daughter?!
Oh no, you broke another one.
That's right. I'm in charge of
what goes on in the tavern.
To think someone like this can be
born into this world from such...
Louise, you just sit here and
watch how the other girls do it.
I'm sorry.
Welcome!
Why do I have to dress up
in this embarrassing outfit
and sell favors to these people?
And on top of it, they keep
saying I'm so small and flat.
Oh, really? Mr. Scarron did?
Yeah! He seems to
like you an awful lot.
He said you were his type!
Breasts!
He's after breasts like the others!
Ouch...
Huh?
Are you all right?
You passed out when a flying
bottle of wine hit your head.
Bottle? Why would a bottle...
Hey, Louise isn't your sister, is she?
What's this all of a sudden?
I can tell just looking at you two.
But it's not like you guys are
dating each other, either.
You know, Jessica, you're mistaken...
And Louise... She's a noble, isn't she?
What... What are you talking about?
There's no way that such a violent,
inelegant girl would be a noble.
Just as I thought.
She didn't even know how to carry
a plate in the beginning, right?
That unusual amount of pride
in herself, and her behavior...
She's got to be a noble.
So you're her servant or something?
I'm no servant.
It's better you keep
yourself out of this.
What's that? You're crossing some
dangerous bridge or something?
That sounds like fun!
I love stories like that!
Come on, tell me.
I won't tell anyone else about it.
Well, you say that, but...
In exchange, I'll teach you
all sorts of stuff!
Um... Teach what?!
Don't ask the obvious!
Um...
What are you doing?
Gathering information!
Did you know that she's
the owner's daughter?
So I was asking about the
customers that come and go...
What information have
you been gathering?!
You really are a stupid dog!
Hold on, Louise.
What?!
What about your work?
Shut up!
I'll go back as soon as I train
this stupid dog... stupid brother.
Do you have that much free time?
You can't even get any tips
worth a damn.
Oh well, I guess you can't help it,
with such a meager...
What is it?!
Just because I don't have big breasts,
people call me a brat, a water flea...
No... Nobody said water flea...
Just you watch! If I put my mind
to it, I'm really amazing!
Is that so?
That means that you'll win the tip
race we're having for sure, right?
Of course I will!
Today is the last day,
but at this rate, not only
will I miss first place...
Ahem!
My, my, if it isn't Lord Chelenne.
It is nice of you to come
all the way out here.
It looks like you have been
quite prosperous.
Oh, no, today is just coincidence.
Usually, we're so empty, you'd
be able to hear a cuckoo cry.
Enough with the excuses! I have
come here today as a customer.
Unfortunately, all the seats
are taken right now.
It doesn't seem that way to me.
I guess you were right when you
said the place was really empty!
Come on, is there no one to serve
the Royal Queen's levy collector?!
Who's that?
That's Chelenne, the guy in charge
of collecting the levy around here.
If we stand up against him,
he puts a huge levy on us,
Come now! Hurry up!
So no one running a business
can stand up against him.
He fondles as much as he wants,
but doesn't pay any tips at all.
No girl that works here
would serve him.
Someone's going up to him.
He's a rich-looking noble.
This is my chance!
Louise!
That idiot...
You are a charming man, sir.
Does this place employ men now?
Men?
Upon a closer look, it's just
a girl with really small breasts.
They're so flat that I thought
you were a man!
Now, let me take a closer look
at exactly how small they are!
Don't mess with me!
Non!
What?! Damn you!
Such insolence!
You are a mere peasant!
How dare you...
Please forgive her.
She just started working here.
Shut up! How dare you?!
Saito!
Knock it off, pops.
How dare you kick
the face of a noble...
So what if you're noble?
What was that?!
The only one that is allowed
to touch Louise is me!
Capture these two!
I'll have them hung!
Who's going to capture who?
You'll be surprised when I tell you!
I was the one that got
the infamous thief...
It's in the attic!
Capture him and that
washboard-breast girl!
Hold on just a second!
Capture him and that
washboard-breast girl!
Washboard is a bit much,
don't you think?!
Louise, where did that wand...
Don't put me in the same boat as you.
I had tied it to my thigh
in case of an emergency.
I went to the trouble of serving you...
Why do I have to be insulted so?!
Are you a noble?
I have no name to give to
a lowly official like you.
Before you regret it, just shut up
and get out of here!
Are you a fallen noble
that is hiding her identity?
Who do you think I am...
Who are you calling a fallen noble?
A writ from the Palace?
Please, please forget what
just happened. I'll offer this.
Please, I beg you!
Forget everything you've seen and
heard here today. Understood?
Yes! In the name of the Royal
Highness and our Founder,
I will not say one word of this!
That was amazing, Louise!
To depress that sketchy creep!
You're the best!
Idiot. You shouldn't be using magic.
But...
We don't ask any of our employees
about their background.
So we didn't see anything,
and we didn't hear anything.
Right, everyone?
Right, of course!
You're the winner.
There's no need to count.
But he just put this here.
He put it here on his own,
so it's a tip. Right, Papa?
Oui!
The winner of the tip race is Louise!
They say that,
but now that our cover is blown,
we have to leave.
What are you doing?
If you're going to change, I'll help...
Don't look!
What are you saying after all this...
That's the Enchanting Fairy...
Since I was given the opportunity,
I decided to borrow it.
I mean, it would be a shame
if I didn't, right?
It's not because of magic, is it?
What? I went through the effort
of putting it on, so say something!
Trés bien!
At the least, compliment me
in some other way.
So late at night... What do you want?
I have come to pick up our comrade.
Fouquet the Sculptor... no...
Matilda of South Gotha.
You're...
As if I were under a real magic spell
A bright smile is burnt onto my heart
But each time I see you, I give you
a pointy, cold shoulder
Why do I act mean towards the one
that I think about the most?
My true feelings,
the shards of loneliness
In the deepest part of my heart,
I'm calling for you
For the day to start from zero
Noisy Kirche and Tabitha apparently
went home for the summer,
so this Institute has
gotten quite lonely!
Wait... Hey, dog!
Who do you think you're flirting with
while completely naked?!
Next episode: Tabitha's Secret
Next Episode: Tabitha's Secret