Ah... I can't come up with anything good.
What's the matter? It's unusual
to see you lost in thought.
Ah, well, I just...
Sounds like you're doing well.
Yes! I'm in super-motivated mode right now!
Super-motivated?
Princess Motivated?!
What's that?
Little Miss Princess...
Queen Selfish...
Little Princess Predictable...
Princess Not Allowed...
Crybaby Serenade...
In her case, it's not just about becoming a Prima.
This is quite difficult.
Hey, did you hear about Alice Carroll?
Ah, I did!
Two weeks ago, she was promoted to Prima
even though she was a Pair, right?
No way! That's amazing!
She's the first one to ever do that!
And yet, Aika doesn't seem like she's
fazed by it at all, does she?
Do you think her cheerfulness is just a front?
Well, Alice is the up-and-coming top Undine
at our rival company, after all.
As Himeya's heir, I'm sure she's
feeling a lot of pressure.
Do you remember that day
Oboeteimasuka ano hi o
When your heart suddenly began to race
Futo kanjita tokimeki o
The rays from the blue sky were pouring over you...
Aoi hizashi abite
...as you cut through the wind
Kaze o kiru kimi ni
I couldn't look away, and when our eyes met
Mitoreru to me ga atte
I couldn't help but smile
Egao koboreta
It's just like a spiral
Marude supiraare
As the days begin to swirl in brilliant colors
Azayaka ni mawaridashita hibi
Always and forever, they're filled with love
Itsumo itsudemo ai ga michiteita
Surely, it's a spiral
Kitto supiraare
The days passed by, each one filled with warmth
Atataka na mainichi o kasanetara
And before I knew it, off in the distance...
Itsunomanika tooku ni
...there you were
Kiteita no ne
Those Ever-Changing Days...
Please take my hand.
Ah, thank you.
Please be careful.
There we go.
Of all the many water guide companies,
thank you for choosing Himeya today.
It was a lot of fun.
Yeah. Gondolas are the best!
Thank you very much!
From the bottom of my heart, I hope that
your vacation will be a memorable one.
I hope you become a Prima soon!
We'll be rooting for you.
Thank you very much! I'll do my best!
Both Himeya and I look forward to
seeing you again during your next visit!
Now then...
Wha-?!
Is something wrong, Akira?
Ah, no...
By any chance, did I give them
wrong information during the tour?
Ah, no...
Then, was I going over
the speed limit somewhere?
Ah, no...
Aika!
Yes?!
Flap
Umm...
After this, all I have left today is a night cruise.
Yeah, that's right. And I'll be joining you
as your assistant, remember?
All right.
I found a really good gelato shop
the other day. Let's go there.
Huh? Okay...
Here's your limone.
Thank you!
It looks delicious!
Aren't you going to have one, Akira?
Huh? No, I'm fine.
But you're the one who
asked me to come with you.
It's fine. Be thankful and just eat it.
Okay, snack time!
Yum!
It really is delicious.
You should have gotten one too, Akira.
You seem pretty cheerful.
Yes! I'm super-cheerful!
Oh, that's right!
You heard about it too, right?
About Junior skipping a rank
and getting promoted to Prima.
I got to see the very moment
it happened, together with Akari.
I was really lucky!
You were there, too?
Yes! In fact, we had front row seats.
One of her gloves was removed,
and then off came her other glove.
I can't tell you how surprised I was!
As expected of Alice!
Girl geniuses sure do things differently.
I've got a lot of catching up to do!
Aika...
To tomorrow and beyond! Let's go!
It's all right.
It's all right, Aika.
It's not all right!
Akira!
I, Aika S. Granzchesta
of Himeya, am all fired up!
You know that feeling you get when someone's
running just a bit ahead of you, pulling you along?
It's like that!
It's how you feel when you know
you're running faster than usual.
This is my chance to excel
further as an Undine, Akira!
I'm grateful to Junior...
...for letting me experience
what I'm feeling right now.
So please train me hard, okay, Akira?
Right now, I'll be able to handle
even the harshest criticisms!
I see.
Sorry about that.
Aika, do you have anything planned
for next month's holiday?
I'm completely free that day,
so I'm going shopping with Al.
I see.
All right, cancel it.
That's the only day I have off.
You'll be spending the entire day with me.
T-That's too cruel...
What happened to that spirit
you had a moment ago?
Here.
"Little Princess Predictable."
What is this?
"Queen Selfish."
"Little Miss Princess."
"Crybaby Serenade."
"Rosen..."
Is this?
Which one do you like?
I figured I should get your opinion, as well.
Akira...
I won't forgive you if you fail.
My future Queen.
Right!
But really, you shouldn't have
crumpled up this paper.
Enough! Be quiet!
Everything is for the sake
of my beloved Rosen Queen.
Orange Princess!
Orange Princess?
Alice Carroll!
Yes?
Please get used to being called by your alias.
Your customers are waiting for you.
I'm sorry!
Since I became a Prima,
every day has been frantic.
The days go by like a hectic whirlwind.
If I have time to think, I just start to worry,
so I suppose it's better this way.
Please take my hand.
Thank you.
This is the Bridge of Sighs.
It looks as though it's made of stone,
but surprisingly, the inside is made of wood.
Oh.
Let's go see it later.
Yes, we should.
If you prefer, I can put in a tour reservation
for you. Would you like me to do that?
Oh, that'd be helpful.
Could you do that for us, please?
I'd be happy to.
It's Akari and Aika.
They're practicing hard together.
Since the moon-gazing party, it's been...
Excuse me...
Yes?
What's the name of that
island over there, Miss Undine?
That's San Giorgio Maggiore.
If you climb the bell tower there,
you can see a sweeping view of the coastline.
In that case, why don't we go there
after we visit the Bridge of Sighs?
Yes!
Until recently, we used to
spend every day together, too.
I haven't been able to see them
for quite a while now.
Good work.
Good work to you, too.
It's that late already?
It's always like this, lately.
I shouldn't go see them
unannounced. I'll call first.
I'm sure it'd be a bother if I said
I wanted to come visit this late at night.
Besides, I don't have a reason.
I don't have an excuse.
Athena, you're going to be late.
Eh? Ah, okay...
Off I go.
See you later.
Anything would be fine. Do I not have any?
Any excuse...
This building, which is currently being restored,
was built in the seventeenth century.
It's the Basilica di Santa Maria della Salute.
Marco Polo was a famous Venetian merchant
and author, and this is a replica of his home.
Currently, it's open to the public as a memorial hall,
so perhaps you'd like to visit if you're in the area?
The Palazzo Pisani Moretta is famous for its
masquerade ball, and its beautiful Gothic interior.
Ah.
My.
Yummy!
Here we go!
Campanile!
That was fun!
Yeah, it was fun!
I never knew gondola rides were so comfortable!
Next time we come to Aqua, we'll be
sure to ride with you again, Alice.
Thank you very much!
See you then.
Goodbye.
Bye-bye!
Thank you again.
It's for you!
Thank you.
Bye!
How'd it go?
What did she say?
She said, "Thank you!"
I see, that's great.
Yeah!
Hey, what should we do for dinner?
Hmm... What do you want to eat?
Umm...
Something yummy!
Oh! I wasn't expecting that!
Good work.
Thank you for the towel.
Sure, just leave it here when you come back.
Every day is hectic.
But there are a lot of fun things, too.
I have so many things I want to tell them.
All I want is to see them.
But it's so hard.
Will I ever be able to see them again?
Slap
Slap-slap, slap-slap!
What a really ominous thing to say!
Slap
And after all those times Aika told me
"No negative thinking allowed!"
Slap
Slap-slap.
Slap...
I'm so lonely...
Yes?
I just got back.
No fading out allowed!
What are you doing here at this time of night?
What's with that tone of yours?
After we came all this way to see you, too.
You know that pizza shop we always go to?
This is their newest pizza!
I heard it's really delicious,
so I thought we should all try it together.
Come on, let's eat while it's still hot.
Okay, let's eat!
Ah! I'm so hungry!
Me too!
You just ate all those bananas.
You're really a glutton.
Wha-?!
The usual three...
The usual conversations...
The usual times...
The usual atmosphere...
Just a few moments ago, I was fretting about
what I would do if I never saw them again, too.
That even if I want to see them,
I don't have the time or an excuse to do so.
Just when I was thinking all that...
There you go again! You were worried about
something like that? That's a bad habit, Junior.
Eh?! Was I thinking out loud?
Yeah, you were.
If you don't have the time, you just
make it, like we're doing now.
But...
But... I don't have an excuse...
I haven't been able to do much of anything lately.
I don't have an excuse like this pizza to see you.
I don't have anything...
You do, though.
You're the excuse, Alice.
We don't need an excuse or
a special reason to see you.
You're reason enough.
Hey! No sappy lines allowed!
Huh?
I'm going to do my best
to catch up to you, Junior.
Me, too.
With these friends, I'll really be just fine!
A shore awash in golden waves
Kin no nami kishibe ni
Filled with yearning, I open my eyes and it's morning
Akogare mezameru no asa ni
As my thoughts focus intently on someone,
Dareka no koto o tsuyoku omou toki
Love rests on my palm, held high
Kakageta te no hira ni ai ga tomaru
A future guided by the flow of water and wind
Mizu no yukue to kaze ga shimesu mirai
I gaze at the hope that surrounds this world
Kono hoshi o tsusumu kibou mitsumete
The distant clouds of light are beckoning now
Tooi kumo hikari ga sasou you ni yureru ima
A shore awash in golden waves
Kin no nami kishibe ni
Filled with yearning, I open my eyes and it's morning
Akogare mezameru no asa ni
And my day begins
Hajimaru
Next Episode
I've always been waiting for this day.
I've always admired you.
Next Episode
And come what may, I always will.
Embraced By That Blue Sea And Wind...
Next time, "Embraced By
That Blue Sea And Wind..."
Next Episode
Embraced By That Blue Sea And Wind...
Now, please take my hand.