That will be 8500 yen for repairs.
Gotta get a part-time job.
Hold on! Someone!
...answer my guidance!
A history of the couple's romance
that starts from the first kiss
You, the one who cast magic on
this destiny, suddenly appeared
The sky where two moons
never fade away
That's an impossibility, right?
This is the first time I've
felt anything like this
I'm feeling more and more
at ease with this place
Even if you trip and
become depressed
I will always hold you
tight with a squeeze
The story where we met that day
stays hot with a sweet kiss
See, you can cast magic, and
the wishes will surely come true
A history of the couple's romance
that starts from the first kiss
You, the one who cast magic on
this destiny, suddenly appeared
Peasant Familiar
Earth?
Yeah, up until a few moments ago,
I was in Tokyo, Japan, on Earth.
I don't believe it.
For such a different world to exist...
I don't want to believe it either!
Anyway, take me back
to where I used to be!
Impossible.
Don't just say that so simply!
No matter who it's with
or where they're from,
the contract is absolute!
What are you doing?
I'm changing for bed.
Don't do that when I'm here!
Why?
You're fine with a guy
watching you do that stuff?
A guy?
You're nothing more than a familiar.
What?!
Okay, wash those for me.
Wait...
Why do I have to wash your lingerie...
I don't know whether to be
happy or upset about this...
No, this is where I'm
supposed to be upset!
Yeah!
Hey, I'm never going
to do your laundry...
And just who do you think
will be taking care of you?
You're my familiar, right?
Cleaning, laundry, errands...
those are to be expected.
Make sure to have my clothes
ready by morning.
Don't worry.
If you do your work right,
you'll get fed.
Fed? Are you treating me
like a dog or something?!
Well, for now, I guess
whatever happens, happens.
So cold...
Who are you?
Here's your clothes.
You're the one who told me to
have it ready in the morning!
Oh... The familiar...
That's right, I summoned
one yesterday.
And the underwear?
You can get those
for yourself, at least!
You can go without a meal.
In the bottom drawer.
Dammit!
Why me...
Here!
Hey, can you take this
thing off already?
No.
I won't run away!
I've been brought to this place
that makes no sense whatsoever,
so where do you think
I'm going to run off to?!
Shut up! Fine!
What?!
Dress me.
You can put your own clothes on.
Nobles that have servants
never dress themselves!
What do you mean, nobles?
Don't go acting all...
I see!
I guess you won't be
needing a meal then.
And you want to keep
that chain on too?
It's a promise.
Now take this thing off!
I guess I have no choice.
She'd be pretty if she
kept her trap shut.
What?
No, nothing.
Let's go.
Where to?
To breakfast, of course.
They're here.
The much-rumored runaway
familiar, and his master...
Man! What a feast!
Hurry up and pull the chair back.
You really are inconsiderate.
Yeah, sure, sure.
Is today some kind of anniversary?
This is a feast, for so early
in the morning!
Oh, I haven't eaten anything
since yesterday, so...
What?
It's... a plate?
Only nobles can sit here.
You, peasant, sit down here.
No way!
O great founder Bremir
and Her Royal Highness,
we are once again grateful
for the humble meal that you
have brought us this morning.
The humble meal's right here.
Normally, familiars wait
outside during a meal.
I specially let you stay with me.
If that's the case,
I'd rather eat elsewhere!
What's everyone doing?
All second-year students
have the day off today.
We're all supposed to communicate
with all our freshly-
summoned familiars.
I'd just as soon pass.
Oh?
It's some red thing!
Is this the first time you've
seen a salamander?
Keep it on a leash!
That was dangerous!
It's all right. Familiars under contract
faithfully obey every order
from their master,
and they never run away.
Isn't that right, Flame?
Don't give me that!
You know, didn't you just sneak in
a peasant that was
walking around the area?
You covered it up well
with that explosion.
That's not true! I made
the summons properly.
This guy just happened to show up!
Well, he's very befitting
of Louise the Zero.
What's up with that wench?!
Don't just stand there!
Bring me some tea, at least!
Oh, I'm sorry!
No, it's all right.
Excuse me.
No, please excuse me.
Could you be the one that became
Miss Vallière's familiar?
You know about me?
It's all over the rumor mill
that a peasant
has been summoned as a familiar.
Well, I don't understand much of
this noble and peasant business.
Those that can use magic are nobles,
and those that can't are
the peasants, right?
Oh, I see. That's how it works.
So are you a sorcerer too?
Quite the contrary!
I am Siesta, and I have
the honor of serving here.
I am a peasant, just like you.
I'm Hiraga Saito. Call me Saito.
Mr. Saito?
That is a strange name.
Hey!
Isn't the cake ready?
Coming right up!
I'll take it to him.
But that's...
It's fine.
This is good enough for that snob.
I talked all night with Verdande here.
I see... All night...
Yes...
These intelligent eyes...
This sensual texture...
Truly, it was destined
to become my familiar.
In any case, keep it buried
when you're with me.
Order's up!
Oh, and bring some more tea as well.
Your familiar is so cute, just like you.
You're always such a flatterer.
I won't lie to your eyes.
But I heard rumors that you're
dating a first-year recently.
Such nonsense!
There is nothing hidden...
...behind my feelings for you...
Wasn't it?
What are you...
Oh, I get it!
The color of the cape is different
for different grades.
Black is for second-years.
So the girl with the brown one
last night was a first-year.
I see, I see...
What's he talking about?
Hurry up and go back to
your business, waiter!
Wrong! I'm not a waiter.
You're the one that Louise the Zero...
Thanks for everything last night.
See ya.
Now, Guiche, what
was that all about?!
Oh, yes... You know,
I told you, right?
I had that peasant familiar to
deal with last night, that's all.
Montmorency, it's far too rowdy here.
We should talk under
that tree over there.
Hurry now... Come now, come now...
Wait! What is it all of a sudden?
Lord Guiche, where are you?
Oh, if you mean Lord Guiche,
it just so happens that
he's right over there!
Lord Guiche!
Ketty!
Hi...
I have been looking
for you, Lord Guiche!
I thought I'd bring my
handmade soufflé,
that I was talking about last night,
to the tea party today.
Oh, that is very...
Last night?
Well, that is...
Good for you!
You were saying that you would
love to have some of it.
You!
It's nothing.
Just telling the truth, right?
What is the meaning of this, Guiche?!
What is it that you're going on about?
You're going to found needless
misunderstandings with these ladies!
What's going on?
Guiche is picking a fight
with that peasant familiar.
What part of it is a misunderstanding?
You're the one at fault for two-timing.
Two-timing?!
So there really was something
going on with this first-year!
Please, Montmorency the Perfume...
Do not contort your face, one as
beautiful as a rose, from anger!
This is all a misunder...
How horrible!
You said that I was the only one!
In any case, both of you, calm down.
Liar!
You just got dumped, Guiche!
Well, you deserved what you just got.
It seems that you do not know
how to pay respect to nobility.
Unfortunately, I come from a world
that has nothing to do with that.
Very well, then.
A duel?
That's right.
I challenge you to a duel!
You are nothing but a peasant,
and a familiar to boot.
Yet you have mocked me,
and on top of that, you have
made two ladies cry!
Cry? They were both hopping mad.
Prepare yourself!
I will be waiting at Vestori Square!
You! What are you doing?!
What?
What do you mean, what?
Why are you promising to fight
a duel without permission?!
Where are we going?
We're going to apologize to Guiche.
Right now, he still might forgive you.
I refuse.
Why do I have to apologize?
You really don't understand anything.
Peasants can never win
against nobles.
You'll be lucky if you get away
with just minor wounds!
Hey, where is Vestori Square?
Oh, over there. That way.
Malicorne!
Thanks!
Wait!
Oh, this will be a sight!
Oh, geez!
He's only a familiar, yet he's
always going off on his own!
No previous case exists
of a peasant familiar.
That is not the problem at hand.
I didn't recognize the familiar's
rune that appeared on him,
so I looked it up,
and it was strikingly similar to this.
Miss Longueville, I apologize, but...
Understood.
He really amuses me.
I praise you for actually
showing up and not running off.
Who would run away?
Wait!
That's enough, Guiche!
Duels are forbidden!
Only duels between two
nobles are forbidden.
He is a peasant.
There are no problems.
That's because nothing like this
has ever happened...
Louise, can it be that you are
attracted to this peasant?
Who is? Knock it off!
Nobody would just sit and watch
as their familiar gets beaten
to a tattered heap!
A tattered heap...
No matter what you say,
the duel has already started!
I am named Guiche the Brass.
Therefore, a brass golem, a Valkyrie,
will be your opponent.
That's playing dirty!
It's nothing but natural
for a noble, a mage,
to use magic to fight a duel, no?
Do you get it now? Peasants
can never win against mages.
Out of the way!
Oh? Did I go too easy on you?
I was just caught off guard
by the sudden attack.
Why are you getting up, you idiot?!
Because he irritates me.
Mages, nobles, whatever...
It makes you all act
needlessly snobbish.
What nonsense are you talking?!
Well, I would feel bad about
breaking something Louise owns,
so I'll forgive you if
you apologize right here.
Fool! That didn't get me at all.
Your doll is way too weak.
Is that so?
This is a familiar's rune
that exists only in legend.
Furthermore, considering
that he was summoned
by that third girl of
the Vallière family...
This has something to do with
one corner of the lost Pentagon.
It can't be.
Whatever the truth behind this is,
you must not speak one word
about this to anyone!
I understand that.
Why are you getting up?!
Oh, he's still gonna get up?
I'm going home.
But this is where it gets interesting.
Please! Stop it already!
Step aside, Louise.
That's enough. You did well.
I've never seen a peasant
like this before!
It's all right. Get out of the way.
Of course it hurts!
That's common sense!
What are you thinking?!
Are you crying?
There's no way I'd cry!
That hurts!
I'm telling you, that hurts!
You still want to go on?
If you have the will to go on,
take up that sword!
If you don't, then you can
tell me that you're sorry.
You've got to be kidding!
Who would?!
No! You can't!
If you pick it up, Guiche
won't show you any mercy.
All right? This is an order
from me, your master!
I can't go back to the world
where I came from,
which means I have
to live here, right?
So what?!
I don't mind if I sleep on the floor.
I don't care if my meals taste awful.
It can't be helped, so I'll keep going.
But if I don't want to bow
my head down to someone,
I can't bow down to him!
Idiot!
The pain...
What's going on?!
I don't know.
But I do know that I feel like I can
keep fighting a little more.
I yield...
To think that a noble would
lose against a peasant...
What?
Are you all right?
Yeah...
This is nothing...
Hold on!
He's asleep...
Hey, you're heavy!
Come on, get off of me!
Get off already!
Ouch...
Have you awakened?
Thank goodness.
You've been asleep for three days
and three nights now.
Why are you here?
Miss Vallière instructed me
to bring you a meal.
She must be tired now.
She's been watching over you all
this time without sleep, Mr. Saito.
Louise was?
She's so cute when she's like this.
What a waste.
Yes?
Oh... Nothing.
Nothing at all...
As if I were under a real magic spell
A bright smile is burnt onto my heart
But each time I see you, I give you
a pointy, cold shoulder
Why do I act mean towards the one
that I think about the most?
My true feelings,
the shards of loneliness
In the deepest part of my heart,
I'm calling for you
For the day to start from zero
You stupid dog!
Why are you looking
so damn spacey?!
On top of that,
you're staring at that horny
nothing-but-boobs Kirche!
I'll never forgive you for this!
Next episode: Feverish Temptation
Next Episode: Feverish Temptation