I don't want you to go!
I'm just going to do laundry.
You're lying! You're going to
sneak off and go see another girl.
I won't see anyone, okay?
I'll be right back!
Really?
Really.
Really, for real?
Really, for real, really!
So you behave, okay?
Yeah. I'll be lonely,
but I'll be waiting.
Then...
Saito...
Hurry back.
Louise...
A history of the couple's romance
that starts from the first kiss
You, the one who cast magic on
this destiny, suddenly appeared
The sky where two moons
never fade away
That's an impossibility, right?
This is the first time I've
felt anything like this
I'm feeling more and more
at ease with this place
Even if you trip and
become depressed
I will always hold you
tight with a squeeze
The story where we met that day
stays hot with a sweet kiss
See, you can cast magic, and
the wishes will surely come true
A history of the couple's romance
that starts from the first kiss
You, the one who cast magic on
this destiny, suddenly appeared
Louise's Change of Heart
A love potion?!
It was a slight error
that Louise drank it.
You must have been there
when the effects kicked in.
Montmorency!
Can it be that you were trying
to make me drink it?!
Oh, how touching!
To think you would go that far
to capture my feelings.
It doesn't have to be
you in particular.
Seeing someone is nothing
but a way to pass time.
I just don't like being cheated on!
There is no way that I would cheat.
I am an eternal servant of love.
Save that for later!
You have no eye for the mood.
Hey, Mon-Mon!
My name is Montmorency!
Hurry up and get Louise
back to normal!
The effects will wear off in due time.
When is that?
Maybe a month from now,
or a year from now.
Wait a minute, you were
planning on making me...
You've got to be kidding!
Good morning.
Oh, Siesta...
You really were waiting
for another girl!
What are you talking about?
No matter how you look at it,
she was just passing by!
I love you so much, yet you...
Saito, you idiot, idiot!
Come on!
Don't cry...
Oh, um, this isn't what it seems to be.
There's a bit of a reason...
What isn't what it seems to be?
Saito, don't you love me?
No, nobody said such a thing...
My, aren't you popular?
Siesta, I'm telling you, listen to me!
Hey, Siesta!
You really love that woman
after all, don't you?
That's not it!
Saito, you idiot!
Sheesh!
Here we go.
You know, about earlier...
It's all right.
I don't mind at all.
Besides, there was nothing
there to begin with.
In any case, just listen to me.
That's all because of a love potion.
Love potion?
Yeah, apparently she mistakenly
ingested one somehow last night,
and she's been like that ever since.
You don't have to tell such a lie.
I really don't mind.
A lie? It's not a lie...
Even peasants like me know.
Drugs to alter people's emotions
are banned by law.
What was that?!
I'm sorry, but I'm busy now.
Hey, wait, Siesta!
So that's what it was.
Damn that Mon-Mon...
Louise must be mad.
Welcome back.
What are you doing?
At least put on a pair of panties!
I won't put one on!
Why not?
Um... if you'd like,
you can tell me why...
Because I have no sex appeal.
I know that because I was told
so many times the other day.
The other day?
Oh, at the Fairy Café...
That's why you keep going
to other girls, Saito.
That's why you won't
do anything to me
even though we're always
in the same room.
Anything?
Does that mean I can do something?
That's off limits!
Of course...
But if it's a little bit,
I'd look the other way.
If it was for like an hour,
I'd close my eyes and pretend
I didn't know about it.
You say that, but...
Anyway...
Please, put something on, okay?
I was lonely for all this time!
You idiot!
Look, you're acting strange
because of a love potion.
That's not true. It's not
because of a love potion!
When I look at you, Saito,
my heart gets all painful,
and it starts to race...
Saito!
Ouch...
Dammit!
What's wrong?
Don't make faces like that!
You wait here. I'll make sure
to turn you back to normal.
Isn't it all right?
I think it's a bit better for her
to be smitten over you
than to be scolding you
left and right like before.
Shut up!
I don't need the power
of a love potion.
Am I not always at your side like this?
Isn't it just that there's no other girls
to woo because of summer vacation?
That's not...
Hey, Mon-Mon!
Why don't you knock?!
You still have no manners at all.
Shut up!
Get Louise back to normal, right now!
Didn't I tell you before?
Until the effects wear off...
There's some potion or a way
to undo the magic, isn't there?
It's not that there isn't one,
but you can't do it here.
I don't have the potion
necessary to do it with.
And where is that?
Saito... Is that how you treat nobility?
Want to have another duel, Guiche?
Well, not really.
It's useless to speak of nobility
and peasants with you, anyway.
Montmorency, for now, I think it's
best if we listened to his orders.
You're so pathetic.
You say that, but even getting
a Spirit Tear is really difficult!
Would you like to eat
stale bread, Mon-Mon?
I heard somewhere that
making love potions is illegal...
That's...
I guess I'll have to inform
the principal about this.
Oh, all right! I guess
I have no choice!
I'll go there and get it myself soon!
Go get such a rare potion?
I know where it is.
Though whether I can get it
by going there is another matter.
All right, let's go tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Come to think of it, I think I saw
Mr. Colbert in the lab earlier.
I'll go! You want me
to go, don't you?
So where is that location?
Lake Lagdorian.
Water-based mages bind
a pact with the spirit there.
Though I've only been there once,
as a small child.
You just have to sleep
together with me!
If you don't, I'll punish you!
All right, I get it, now sleep!
We're getting up early tomorrow.
Yeah...
I've seen this often enough...
Argh, I can't sleep at all now!
Along the border with Galia?
It'll take half the day to get there.
I didn't ask you to
come with me, did I?
What would your knight be doing
if he didn't go with you
at a time like this?
So sleepy...
Is she really going to be
back to normal?
Lake Lagdorian is up ahead,
past this hill.
So we finally get to see Lake
Lagdorian, our destination.
He really is carefree. What
part of him is a knight?
You know, I knitted this
for you yesterday, Saito.
I see... It's a lovely hat.
It's not a hat! It's a sweater!
Oh, I see! You're right...
It's a lovely jellyfish sweater!
Do you like it?
Yeah...
Help me!
What's this? Water up to here?
Is the Water Spirit or
whatever really here?
It looks like the Water Spirit is upset.
Upset?
The water level is unusually high.
Unusually?
Look.
They're all underwater.
When I came here with my father
as a child, it wasn't like this.
Let's wait a little while.
The spirit won't come out
until after the sun sets.
Don't just sit there chatting idly!
Before all that, save me...
All right, Robin... I want to
contact one of my old friends.
Now, this should identify me.
Tell the old Water Spirit that
someone who bid a contract
with it would like to talk to it.
If she can find it,
Robin will bring it to us.
Will it come?
Who knows...
And the actual person
involved is asleep.
In the past, I came here
with my father,
and bid a contract with the spirit.
If the spirit remembers,
I'm sure it will come.
And after that, we collect a tear...
Do we have to tell
sad stories or something?
Idiot. It's just called a Tear.
We have to have it split off
a tiny portion of its body!
Listen, okay?
If you make the spirit upset,
we can forget the Tear,
and our lives will be in danger too!
You really have to be careful!
Gotcha.
It's here!
This is the Water Spirit...
Hey, this takes me back.
I am Montmorency Margarita
la Fere de Montmorency...
A water user, of a family that has
had a lasting pact with you.
If you remember anything
about my blood,
please answer me in a way
that we can recognize!
I remember, lonely one.
I remember the fluid
that runs in your body.
It spoke!
I'm glad. O Water Spirit,
I have a favor to ask.
A favor?
I would like to have
a small piece of you.
We decline, lonely one.
Don't say that! Please, Water Spirit!
Wait! Knock it off!
If she gets in a bad mood...
I'll do whatever you tell me to,
so just a bit...
A tiny bit...
Very well.
You would do anything, say you?
Yeah...
We are occupied with
increasing the water,
and have no time to
drive off attackers.
Attackers?
Some of your kind are attacking us.
We desire to be rid of them.
Attacking the Water Spirit?
Who'd do such a fearless thing?
There's no way I'd know that!
All right.
If we defeat them, you'll give us
a piece of your body, right?
We shall bestow it.
I don't want to be involved in a fight!
You want to be locked up, Mon-Mon?
All right! Do as you like!
Attacking the spirit that is
at the bottom of the lake...
That's quite a mage we're up against.
How do you dive into the lake?
Most likely a user of air.
I think so too.
Using air magic, you can
create a sphere of air
and use it to walk along
the lake bottom.
I think we're up against
quite a caster.
Is that so?
You're talking only to Montmorency!
You love her much more than
you love me, don't you?!
That's not it! We're talking
about something important,
on how to turn you back to normal!
Turning what part of me
back to normal?
I'm totally normal right now.
I just love you, Saito!
I understand!
I love you too, Louise, so can you
be quiet for a little while?
Yeah! I'll stay quiet.
For that to happen to Louise...
It really works well.
Don't think it's someone
else's problem!
Someone's here!
It sounds like a spell is being cast.
Well, there's no doubt about it.
Be a good girl and
stay here for a while.
Saito!
Montmorency...
As long as I am with you,
I won't let you face any danger...
It's all right! You hurry up and
go too! Hurry up and stop them!
Yeah... I guess so.
Hold on.
The opponent is a user of
pretty powerful magic spells.
There's no way we would win
going head-to-head against them.
You're going to help me?
Of course.
A noble would be shamed if he
made a peasant fight all by himself.
Sorry!
Guiche, I had totally lost
my faith in you until now.
Don't worry about it.
So, what do we do?
The plan is like this...
I'll use magic here to
draw their attention.
Use that to surprise them
with an ambush!
Understood!
Wait... Are you trying to
swing by with the easy part?
What are you talking about?
I am a mage, and you are
a swordsman, aren't you?
Considering our tactics...
Yeah, yeah...
Then I'll run by behind them,
so I'm leaving the rest to you.
Yeah...
I came here thinking it
would be a little vacation.
Why do I have to be
in such a situation?
Earth, robust mother, answer my
wishes and become a moving wall!
Huh?
They're taking turns using their
magic, so they're never off guard!
Draw me, partner!
Now!
Hot!
Look out!
Not good! Saito, run!
Don't be mean to Saito!
Saito?
Did someone say Saito?
Oh, it's true.
Looking closely, it really is Saito.
Huh?
Guiche, Montmorency... Even Louise?
Why are you all here?
I see, so that's what's going on.
But why did you make such
a dangerous thing as a love potion?
That's because...
Ouch!
I just wanted to make some.
That puts us in trouble.
We have to defeat the Water Spirit
for Tabitha to keep face.
Why do you have to defeat it?
That's because...
Tabitha's family asked her to.
The water level is rising every day,
and their territory
is getting damaged.
You have your own reasons
for being here... This is tough.
Hey, Mon-Mon, you were saying that
the Water Spirit was angry, right?
I did, but why?
For now, we can ask it the
reason why it's so upset.
Why are you overflowing
the lake with water?
It's causing everyone trouble.
Because one of your folk abducted
the treasure that we were guarding.
A treasure?
We can exist only in water.
Therefore, should we fill this
entire world with water,
we will someday have the
treasure back in our hands.
Fill the world with water?
That's a long-term plan...
That can't be helped.
Spirits are immortal,
so their sense of time
is different from ours.
All right, if that's the case,
I'll bring whatever that
treasure is back to you!
Saito, it's easy to say that, but...
What's the name of that treasure?
Andvari's Ring. A ring that
has spent much time with us.
Andvari... I've heard of it.
I think it was a magic item
that grants artificial souls.
What kind of person stole it?
One of the individuals
was called Cromwell.
We know nothing else.
Cromwell, is it?
Okay, all right.
I'll make sure to find that guy
and bring the ring back!
I promise!
You should give up.
Who would believe the promise of
someone who randomly showed up,
let alone someone like you,
who isn't even a mage?
We believe.
The Spirit Tear!
Why?!
Gundolf kept oath with us
in the distant past.
If it is Gundolf, it is worth believing.
Gundolf?
What's that?
That again?
Well, in any case, I will make sure
to keep the promise someday.
Someday?
Spirits don't die, right?
Then no matter how many years
it takes, it doesn't matter.
So can you put all the overflowing
water back to normal?
We shall so promise.
Owe you...
Saito...
How horrible!
The biggest embarrassment of my life,
no, the biggest mistake of my life!
I thought you'd forget everything
when you returned to normal!
I remember all of it!
To think! Me! To this dog!
Doing this and that!
Don't take it out on me!
It's Mon-Mon's fault
for making the potion,
and yours for drinking it!
Be silent!
You dog!
Who is it?
You are as rowdy as ever.
Can it be...
Princess?
The time has come.
It is finally time to go through with it.
As you wish, Your Excellency,
Lord Cromwell.
As if I were under a real magic spell
A bright smile is burnt onto my heart
But each time I see you, I give you
a pointy, cold shoulder
Why do I act mean towards the one
that I think about the most?
My true feelings, the
shards of loneliness
In the deepest part of my heart,
I'm calling for you
For the day to start from zero
Princess, I will take the
feelings you harbor,
and head to the kingdom of Albion.
The magic knight that will guard us...
Why is it you?
Next Episode:
A Princess's Request
Next episode: A Princess's Request
Next Episode:
A Princess's Request