In those hectic days when
we barely had time to sleep,
I had not realized the flaw in my plan.
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, keep going on
Baby I'm standing alone
An unforgettable rainy day
Chasing after your shadow
And it's over, it's like sand now
I sigh every night
I scream like a child and cried
It hangs there quietly, my sorrow
Please, please God, forgive my sins
I don't need to hide no more
Flowing toward the turquoise light
Just keep going on
You've got the chance now
You've got the power
Know you gotta be so true to yourself
I show you my life now
I show you my love now
I show you my everything yeah yeah
You'd better change now
You'd better catch now
Don't ever change so be yourself
I'll show you my strength now
I'll show you my love now
I'll show you my everything yeah yeah
Baby don't be afraid
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, keep going on
So, what do you wanna do
when we get there?
We've gotta try out some
real Italian cuisine first.
Hey listen. I looked up some stores.
Hey, isn't he from Trapnest?!
- Huh? Who?
- Ren?
No, the long-haired one.
Really? Where?
So where's Ren?
I'm sick of eating bread
for breakfast every day.
I want some miso soup.
Oh, I found this great Japanese restaurant.
Wanna go there tonight?
I want some of Nana's salty miso soup!
Ren, keep your voice down.
Ren, you're better off forgetting
about women like that.
"Women like that"?
While we're on the subject,
I'll be blunt with you.
I believe Nana is the type of girl
she's rumored to be
and you're really being fooled by her.
If she loved you,
she'd be more careful about
the salt content in her cooking...
Take, let me go back to
Japan earlier too.
That's not fair just Takumi got to go.
No, you still have your photo shoot.
Besides, he had his reasons.
What? Takumi's returning early?
He's already left. Yesterday.
What's with that?!
Why didn't he say anything about it?!
He should've arrived in Japan by now.
He's so cold...
Mom, I'm off to check in at the hotel.
If Mr. Ichinose's coming to see us
tomorrow anyway,
he should've stayed over.
But he'll be arriving pretty late,
so he didn't wanna inconvenience anyone.
He shouldn't be so formal.
He's gonna be family.
They're seeing each other for
the first time in half a month.
Of course they want some time alone.
Oh, I guess you're right.
I'm sure looking forward to tomorrow.
Talking with him over the phone,
Takumi seems like a really nice person.
Huh? When did you talk to him?
I answered the phone when
he called from overseas.
Dad is prejudiced when it comes
to celebrities
saying they're as bad as the yakuza
but even he was praising Takumi
on his manners.
Really?
But he is like a yakuza though.
HE'S GOT YOU FOOLED.
Is that so?
If he actually was a gangster,
he'd take over the world.
He's so cutthroat.
Then God must've given him
musical talent
to keep him on the right path in life.
The world of entertainment
seems glamorous,
but I'm sure it's pretty difficult.
It will be your job to create a home
where he can relax.
So stop slacking off and do your best.
Mhm.
By the way, how's Nana doing?
Have you been keeping in touch?
No. I hear that Nana broke
her cell phone.
So I haven't been able
to call or email her.
And she hasn't called me.
I see. That's a bit worrisome, isn't it?
Yeah. But from what my other friends
are telling me,
she seems to be in extremely
high spirits and working hard.
Extremely?
That's my Nana!
She's a tough girl!
I was so frantic to give Hachi the chance
to see me out there singing.
It never occurred to me to ask
how she was doing.
About her child, or about Takumi...
Honestly speaking,
I didn't want to know.
Although that was just me being jealous.
You haven't even touched your breakfast.
Are you feeling sick?
No...
Hey, Mari. I wonder if Takumi
met up with Stella.
Huh? I-I don't know.
But we've been so busy,
I doubt he had time to sleep around.
He raced through his schedule
for his fiancée, after all.
That's awful.
Huh?
Well, that might be okay for his fiancée,
but Stella has been Takumi's lover
for a lot longer!
Ah, is that so?
She might've even been secretly dreaming
of marrying Takumi some day.
I feel sorry for Stella.
SUBJECT: IT'S ME, SHIN
You sure are amazing, Reira.
Huh?
To be able to see things from
so many different perspectives like that.
I was only thinking of the feelings
of Takumi's fiancée.
Someone who can sing songs
that captivate the general public sure
is different.
You overestimate me, Mari.
It's just a matter of whose feelings
I can empathize with more.
I'm a selfish person
who only thinks of herself.
I have no idea how
Stella really feels at all.
IT'S ME, SHIN. HOW ARE YOU, REIRA?
ARE YOU GETTING ENOUGH REST
IN LONDON? RIGHT NOW, I'M
RECORDING AT A TRAINING CAMP
(WHAT THE HELL?) DEEP IN THE
MOUNTAINS UP NORTH.
IT'S ME, SHIN. HOW ARE YOU, REIRA?
ARE YOU GETTING ENOUGH REST
IN LONDON? RIGHT NOW, I'M
RECORDING AT A TRAINING CAMP
(WHAT THE HELL?) DEEP IN THE
MOUNTAINS UP NORTH.
How are you, Reira? Are you getting
enough rest in London?
IT'S ME, SHIN. HOW ARE YOU, REIRA?
ARE YOU GETTING ENOUGH REST
IN LONDON? RIGHT NOW, I'M
RECORDING AT A TRAINING CAMP
(WHAT THE HELL?) DEEP IN THE
MOUNTAINS UP NORTH.
IT'S ME, SHIN. HOW ARE YOU, REIRA?
ARE YOU GETTING ENOUGH REST
IN LONDON? RIGHT NOW, I'M
RECORDING AT A TRAINING CAMP
(WHAT THE HELL?) DEEP IN THE
MOUNTAINS UP NORTH.
Right now, I'm recording at a training camp
deep in the mountains up north.
IT'S ME, SHIN. HOW ARE YOU, REIRA?
ARE YOU GETTING ENOUGH REST
IN LONDON? RIGHT NOW, I'M
RECORDING AT A TRAINING CAMP
(WHAT THE HELL?) DEEP IN THE
MOUNTAINS UP NORTH.
THE RECORDING IS COMING ALONG
WELL, BUT WE'RE FORCED TO RUN
IN THE MORNING AND DO THE
CLEANING. WHAT'S THAT ALL ABOUT?
(YOU SHOULD SEE YASU IN
HIS SWEAT SUIT.)
THE RECORDING IS COMING ALONG
WELL, BUT WE'RE FORCED TO RUN
IN THE MORNING AND DO THE
CLEANING. WHAT'S THAT ALL ABOUT?
(YOU SHOULD SEE YASU IN
HIS SWEAT SUIT.)
The recording is coming along well,
THE RECORDING IS COMING ALONG
WELL, BUT WE'RE FORCED TO RUN
IN THE MORNING AND DO THE
CLEANING. WHAT'S THAT ALL ABOUT?
(YOU SHOULD SEE YASU IN
HIS SWEAT SUIT.)
but we're forced to run in the morning
and do the cleaning.
THE RECORDING IS COMING ALONG
WELL, BUT WE'RE FORCED TO RUN
IN THE MORNING AND DO THE
CLEANING. WHAT'S THAT ALL ABOUT?
(YOU SHOULD SEE YASU IN
HIS SWEAT SUIT.)
THE RECORDING IS COMING ALONG
WELL, BUT WE'RE FORCED TO RUN
IN THE MORNING AND DO THE
CLEANING. WHAT'S THAT ALL ABOUT?
(YOU SHOULD SEE YASU IN
HIS SWEAT SUIT.)
What's that all about?
BUT IN THESE FIVE DAYS, PERHAPS
BECAUSE OF THIS HEALTHY
LIFESTYLE, I THINK I'VE GROWN
A LITTLE TALLER. MAYBE I'M
JUST IMAGINING IT.
BUT IN THESE FIVE DAYS, PERHAPS
BECAUSE OF THIS HEALTHY
LIFESTYLE, I THINK I'VE GROWN
A LITTLE TALLER. MAYBE I'M
JUST IMAGINING IT.
But in these five days,
perhaps because of this healthy lifestyle,
BUT IN THESE FIVE DAYS, PERHAPS
BECAUSE OF THIS HEALTHY
LIFESTYLE, I THINK I'VE GROWN
A LITTLE TALLER. MAYBE I'M
JUST IMAGINING IT.
BUT IN THESE FIVE DAYS, PERHAPS
BECAUSE OF THIS HEALTHY
LIFESTYLE, I THINK I'VE GROWN
A LITTLE TALLER. MAYBE I'M
JUST IMAGINING IT.
I think I've grown a little taller.
Maybe I'm just imagining it.
It's salty!
Huh?
You're the one who said
you wanted miso soup!
Stop complaining and eat it!
Why is everything you cook
always so salty?
Misato should've come along
to this camp.
Then she could've cooked for us.
No, we couldn't do that.
She should quit school and
become our manager.
- Great idea!
- She's very considerate.
That's true. In any case,
I wanted a cute girl for a manager.
Yasu!
Are you not satisfied with me?
GINPEl MOROBOSHI (28)
MANAGER
Are you not satisfied with me?
- Not satisfied at all.
What was that?!
Ginpei! You're a man, so talk like one!
And we don't need two baldies!
Who are you to talk?!
You're a girl, so talk like one!
And my head's not bald,
it's just shaved!
Well, I'm not naturally bald either...
Oh! Smells good in here.
Ah, Matsuo! If you haven't eaten,
would you care to join us?
- I'll pass.
- Eat it.
I've decided to eat with the staff
when it's Nana's turn to cook.
That's why your wife left you, Matsuo.
Anyway, Mr. Kawano will
be arriving soon,
so we're gonna skip practice and
have a meeting instead.
Come to the studio's conference room
when you're done eating.
Man, it's cold! What's with this?!
This is crazy. It's still September.
What happened to global warming?
What's global warming?
Read the newspaper.
THESE FACILITIES BELONG TO GAIA
AND THE EQUIPMENT IS ALL
SPECTACULAR, BUT THERE'S
NOTHING BUT FOREST AND LAKES
AROUND US, WHICH MAKES
LIFE INCONVENIENT.
THESE FACILITIES BELONG TO GAIA
AND THE EQUIPMENT IS ALL
SPECTACULAR, BUT THERE'S
NOTHING BUT FOREST AND LAKES
AROUND US, WHICH MAKES
LIFE INCONVENIENT.
These facilities belong to Gaia
and the equipment is all spectacular,
THESE FACILITIES BELONG TO GAIA
AND THE EQUIPMENT IS ALL
SPECTACULAR, BUT THERE'S
NOTHING BUT FOREST AND LAKES
AROUND US, WHICH MAKES
LIFE INCONVENIENT.
but there's nothing but forest
and lakes around us,
THESE FACILITIES BELONG TO GAIA
AND THE EQUIPMENT IS ALL
SPECTACULAR, BUT THERE'S
NOTHING BUT FOREST AND LAKES
AROUND US, WHICH MAKES
LIFE INCONVENIENT.
which makes life inconvenient.
THESE FACILITIES BELONG TO GAIA
AND THE EQUIPMENT IS ALL
SPECTACULAR, BUT THERE'S
NOTHING BUT FOREST AND LAKES
AROUND US, WHICH MAKES
LIFE INCONVENIENT.
BUT AT LEAST FOR NOW, THE PRESS
HASN'T COME AFTER US, SO IT'S
A LOT MORE PEACEFUL THAN
BEING IN TOKYO.
BUT AT LEAST FOR NOW, THE PRESS
HASN'T COME AFTER US, SO IT'S
A LOT MORE PEACEFUL THAN
BEING IN TOKYO.
But at least for now,
the press hasn't come after us,
BUT AT LEAST FOR NOW, THE PRESS
HASN'T COME AFTER US, SO IT'S
A LOT MORE PEACEFUL THAN
BEING IN TOKYO.
so it's a lot more peaceful than
being in Tokyo.
Above all, I appreciate the clean air
and seeing the sky full of stars at night.
ABOVE ALL, I APPRECIATE THE
CLEAN AIR AND SEEING THE SKY
FULL OF STARS AT NIGHT.
FOR SOME REASON, WHENEVER I
SEE SOMETHING THAT SPARKLES,
I'M REMINDED OF YOU, REIRA.
Above all, I appreciate the clean air
and seeing the sky full of stars at night.
ABOVE ALL, I APPRECIATE THE
CLEAN AIR AND SEEING THE SKY
FULL OF STARS AT NIGHT.
FOR SOME REASON, WHENEVER I
SEE SOMETHING THAT SPARKLES,
I'M REMINDED OF YOU, REIRA.
ABOVE ALL, I APPRECIATE THE
CLEAN AIR AND SEEING THE SKY
FULL OF STARS AT NIGHT.
FOR SOME REASON, WHENEVER I
SEE SOMETHING THAT SPARKLES,
I'M REMINDED OF YOU, REIRA.
For some reason,
whenever I see something that sparkles,
ABOVE ALL, I APPRECIATE THE
CLEAN AIR AND SEEING THE SKY
FULL OF STARS AT NIGHT.
FOR SOME REASON, WHENEVER I
SEE SOMETHING THAT SPARKLES,
I'M REMINDED OF YOU, REIRA.
I'm reminded of you, Reira.
I wonder why.
I WONDER WHY.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
I'm reminded of you, Reira.
I wonder why.
I WONDER WHY.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
I really don't know.
Guerrilla live performances?
Yeah. Five locations in Tokyo,
starting on the tenth of next month.
Shinjuku, Yoyogi, Ikebukuro,
Ueno, and Shibuya.
We'll be setting up a special stage
in spots with lots of pedestrian traffic.
Yay! Live performances!
But won't we get in trouble
with the police?
No. Of course we've obtained permits
for the locations.
We're just not announcing to the public
that we'll be having these
live performances.
I'm sure you're sick of dealing
with the cops, right, leader?
So, our audience is
the street pedestrians.
But we'll have
twenty part-time paid applauders.
We don't need your hired applauders!
Oh no, you must have applauders.
Japanese crowds are
so hard to get fired up.
You stop talking!
Just think of them as barkers for
when a new store opens.
It's just a way to draw customers.
Oh...
Oh my! So you'll obediently listen
to what Yasu says.
You aren't actually with him, are you?
SORE LOSER
I'll kill you, shaved-head!
Oh, bring it on!
- Wow, that's amazing, Ginpei!
- S-Sorry...
That's okay, as long as you understand.
COME TO THINK OF IT, YOU MAY
NOT KNOW BEING OVERSEAS, REIRA,
BUT THE COVERAGE ON THE
MAGAZINES HAVE GOTTEN WORSE
AND NOW EVEN YASU'S BEING
TARGETED.
COME TO THINK OF IT, YOU MAY
NOT KNOW BEING OVERSEAS, REIRA,
BUT THE COVERAGE ON THE
MAGAZINES HAVE GOTTEN WORSE
AND NOW EVEN YASU'S BEING
TARGETED.
Come to think of it,
you may not know being overseas, Reira,
COME TO THINK OF IT, YOU MAY
NOT KNOW BEING OVERSEAS, REIRA,
BUT THE COVERAGE ON THE
MAGAZINES HAVE GOTTEN WORSE
AND NOW EVEN YASU'S BEING
TARGETED.
but the coverage on the magazines
have gotten worse
COME TO THINK OF IT, YOU MAY
NOT KNOW BEING OVERSEAS, REIRA,
BUT THE COVERAGE ON THE
MAGAZINES HAVE GOTTEN WORSE
AND NOW EVEN YASU'S BEING
TARGETED.
and now even Yasu's being targeted.
JUST LIKE WITH NANA, THEY'RE
WRITING GARBAGE ABOUT
WHATEVER THEY CAN.
HIS PAST AND EVERYTHING.
JUST LIKE WITH NANA, THEY'RE
WRITING GARBAGE ABOUT
WHATEVER THEY CAN.
HIS PAST AND EVERYTHING.
Just like with Nana, they're writing garbage
about whatever they can.
JUST LIKE WITH NANA, THEY'RE
WRITING GARBAGE ABOUT
WHATEVER THEY CAN.
HIS PAST AND EVERYTHING.
His past and everything.
THEY'VE MADE HIM OUT TO BE
THE CHARACTER HE LOOKS LIKE.
HE'S GOT QUITE A PRESENCE NOW.
(ALTHOUGH HE WEARS
A SWEAT SUIT.)
THEY'VE MADE HIM OUT TO BE
THE CHARACTER HE LOOKS LIKE.
HE'S GOT QUITE A PRESENCE NOW.
(ALTHOUGH HE WEARS
A SWEAT SUIT.)
They've made him out to be
the character he looks like.
THEY'VE MADE HIM OUT TO BE
THE CHARACTER HE LOOKS LIKE.
HE'S GOT QUITE A PRESENCE NOW.
(ALTHOUGH HE WEARS
A SWEAT SUIT.)
He's got quite a presence now.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S BECAUSE
THEY HAVEN'T FOUND OUT OR
THEY'RE PURPOSELY HIDING IT, BUT
NOTHING'S BEEN WRITTEN ABOUT
THE FACT THAT YOU AND HE
WERE LOVERS. SO DON'T WORRY.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S BECAUSE
THEY HAVEN'T FOUND OUT OR
THEY'RE PURPOSELY HIDING IT, BUT
NOTHING'S BEEN WRITTEN ABOUT
THE FACT THAT YOU AND HE
WERE LOVERS. SO DON'T WORRY.
I don't know if it's because
they haven't found out
I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S BECAUSE
THEY HAVEN'T FOUND OUT OR
THEY'RE PURPOSELY HIDING IT, BUT
NOTHING'S BEEN WRITTEN ABOUT
THE FACT THAT YOU AND HE
WERE LOVERS. SO DON'T WORRY.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S BECAUSE
THEY HAVEN'T FOUND OUT OR
THEY'RE PURPOSELY HIDING IT, BUT
NOTHING'S BEEN WRITTEN ABOUT
THE FACT THAT YOU AND HE
WERE LOVERS. SO DON'T WORRY.
or they're purposely hiding it,
I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S BECAUSE
THEY HAVEN'T FOUND OUT OR
THEY'RE PURPOSELY HIDING IT, BUT
NOTHING'S BEEN WRITTEN ABOUT
THE FACT THAT YOU AND HE
WERE LOVERS. SO DON'T WORRY.
but nothing's been written about
the fact that you and he were lovers.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S BECAUSE
THEY HAVEN'T FOUND OUT OR
THEY'RE PURPOSELY HIDING IT, BUT
NOTHING'S BEEN WRITTEN ABOUT
THE FACT THAT YOU AND HE
WERE LOVERS. SO DON'T WORRY.
So don't worry.
Hey Ren, has Naoki told you
about Yasu?
What's that baldy up to?
I guess Search published
an exposé about him.
Naoki says there are rumors about it
all over the internet.
An exposé about what?
All kinds of things.
Apparently he hit a Search reporter
to protect his vocalist,
and was taken in for questioning
by the police.
Then, other magazines started saying
that Nana and Yasu are actually dating
and things like that.
That's just not possible. It's all lies.
In addition, Search also wrote
that Yasu's not a real lawyer
since he doesn't have a license
to practice law.
Isn't that horrible?
That is horrible.
Um, Reira...
Oh, thank you.
You know, I've been concerned
about those rumors too.
Is it possible Mr. Takagi never served
as a law apprentice for a firm?
What's a law apprentice?
It would be equivalent to
a medical intern.
After passing the bar exam,
you must serve as a law apprentice
for a year and a half
before you can become a real lawyer.
You really know a lot, Mari!
More like you don't know anything.
What about you?!
Well, it's not exactly common knowledge.
I'm a law school graduate.
That's amazing! You're not just wearing
those glasses for show.
No, there's nothing amazing about it.
And these glasses are just for show.
Then what are you doing
being Reira's babysitter?
What do you mean, babysitter?!
You know, like changing your diapers...
She doesn't!
Enough about me.
No.
I wanna know more about you.
Are you free tonight?
Why do all our members try to
seduce every woman they see?!
Are you Italian?!
Anyway, so that's why
Yasu said he was a trainee.
So I guess he's in the midst of
his so-called apprenticeship.
But it's been a year and a half
since he graduated,
so he could already be a lawyer!
No, once you become an apprentice,
you must go where
you've been assigned.
He would've had no say as to
where he'd be assigned.
If he were devoted to the band,
it would've been difficult.
His mentor probably
saw Mr. Takagi's abilities
and hired him through the office and
had him do only desk work.
Mari, can you come here?!
Yes!
Mr. Takagi probably couldn't give up
his dreams for the band.
The fact that he hit that reporter shows just
how much he cares for his band members.
No matter what the public says,
I think Reira's boyfriend
is a wonderful man.
Don't pay attention to the rumors,
and keep your spirits high.
Mari?
Yes!
Boyfriend?
What does that mean?
Wasn't Yasu's dream to be a lawyer?
It's always been secrets and lies.
Since the old days,
I never knew what he was thinking.
I have no intention of making
a living on music,
and I don't plan on ever
leaving this town.
So I guess there's nothing
we can do about it.
If the band is that important to him,
was that just an excuse to break up
with me?
No, he didn't go that far for
the sake of the band.
This may be a problem.
I could no longer sacrifice
that much for Nana.
I wonder why.
I still love her
like I always have.
Hey, Ren. If I died,
would you die with me?
When did I become
such a cold person?
REIRA, IF YOU SAID THAT YOU WERE
LONELY NOW, I'D FLY TO LONDON
IN A HEARTBEAT. I'D GO ANYWHERE.
REIRA, IF YOU SAID THAT YOU WERE
LONELY NOW, I'D FLY TO LONDON
IN A HEARTBEAT. I'D GO ANYWHERE.
Reira. If you said that
you were lonely now,
REIRA, IF YOU SAID THAT YOU WERE
LONELY NOW, I'D FLY TO LONDON
IN A HEARTBEAT. I'D GO ANYWHERE.
I'd fly to London in a heartbeat.
I'd go anywhere.
REIRA, IF YOU SAID THAT YOU WERE
LONELY NOW, I'D FLY TO LONDON
IN A HEARTBEAT. I'D GO ANYWHERE.
IF I COULD WARM YOUR HEART
AND BODY EVEN A LITTLE,
THEN IT WOULD BE WORTH IT.
IF I COULD WARM YOUR HEART
AND BODY EVEN A LITTLE,
THEN IT WOULD BE WORTH IT.
If I could warm your heart and body
even a little,
IF I COULD WARM YOUR HEART
AND BODY EVEN A LITTLE,
THEN IT WOULD BE WORTH IT.
then it would be worth it.
IF I COULD WARM YOUR HEART
AND BODY EVEN A LITTLE,
THEN IT WOULD BE WORTH IT.
THE WAY I SAY THAT, YOU MAY
GET THE WRONG IDEA AND THINK
I'M A KIND PERSON.
THE WAY I SAY THAT, YOU MAY
GET THE WRONG IDEA AND THINK
I'M A KIND PERSON.
The way I say that,
THE WAY I SAY THAT, YOU MAY
GET THE WRONG IDEA AND THINK
I'M A KIND PERSON.
you may get the wrong idea and
think I'm a kind person.
THE WAY I SAY THAT, YOU MAY
GET THE WRONG IDEA AND THINK
I'M A KIND PERSON.
THE TRUTH IS SIMPLY THAT I DON'T
HAVE ANYTHING RIGHT NOW THAT
IS AS IMPORTANT TO ME AS YOU.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT TOMORROW,
THOUGH...
SORRY FOR BEING SO SELFISH.
The truth is simply that
I don't have anything right now
THE TRUTH IS SIMPLY THAT I DON'T
HAVE ANYTHING RIGHT NOW THAT
IS AS IMPORTANT TO ME AS YOU.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT TOMORROW,
THOUGH...
SORRY FOR BEING SO SELFISH.
that is as important to me as you.
THE TRUTH IS SIMPLY THAT I DON'T
HAVE ANYTHING RIGHT NOW THAT
IS AS IMPORTANT TO ME AS YOU.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT TOMORROW,
THOUGH...
SORRY FOR BEING SO SELFISH.
THE TRUTH IS SIMPLY THAT I DON'T
HAVE ANYTHING RIGHT NOW THAT
IS AS IMPORTANT TO ME AS YOU.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT TOMORROW,
THOUGH...
SORRY FOR BEING SO SELFISH.
I don't know about tomorrow, though...
Sorry for being so selfish.
That's different from
being a cold person, Ren.
The longer we live,
the more weight we carry on our shoulders.
And it gets harder to do what
you want...
That's why you need someone
to carry that load with you.
Don't you think you and your girlfriend
could do that for each other?
Welcome home!
You must be exhausted from work!
I'm really exhausted.
Souvenirs!
So many!
- Which do you want?
- Just one out of seven?!
How about this one!
You've got a great nose.
- You picked the diamond...
- Huh?!
earrings. That's a good choice.
- No, I'd rather have this one!
- That's some tea.
- What about this?
- A pearl necklace.
Wristwatch.
Shoes.
A handbag. Cashmere scarf.
Where's the ring?!
Well, that's different from a souvenir.
You already have it.
Your left pocket.
A magic trick?
It's that tendency to let your guard
down that let's men trick you.
I do have a list of priorities
that I cannot change.
First is work.
That makes up for more than
ninety percent of my brain.
Everything else doesn't matter as much.
But I'd say my girl comes second.
I need her so I can relax.
I won't be able to care
for you too much,
but I won't let you have a hard life.
Okay.
As long as I'm your number one
second priority.
I'm sorry but you're number two
in my second priority.
Huh?!
Maybe this souvenir would best suit
my number one woman.
Shoes?
They wouldn't fit you anyway.
She must be petite.
Sachiko...
TRAUMA
Is it you again?
You've already given her a name?
And what a traditional name.
Well, whatever name's fine with me.
Here! Then these are for our lil' Sachiko.
They're so cute! Thank you, Daddy!
So many!
But doesn't that sound awkward?
Sachiko Ichinose.
It's like a tongue twister.
Stop it with that ominous name.
You gave her that name!
REIRA, THE REASON I BOUGHT
A LAPTOP COMPUTER WAS BECAUSE
I WANTED TO SPEND ALL THE MONEY
I GOT FROM YOU QUICKLY, BUT
I DIDN'T WANNA SPEND IT ONLY
ON MYSELF.
REIRA, THE REASON I BOUGHT
A LAPTOP COMPUTER WAS BECAUSE
I WANTED TO SPEND ALL THE MONEY
I GOT FROM YOU QUICKLY, BUT
I DIDN'T WANNA SPEND IT ONLY
ON MYSELF.
Reira. The reason I bought
a laptop computer was because
REIRA, THE REASON I BOUGHT
A LAPTOP COMPUTER WAS BECAUSE
I WANTED TO SPEND ALL THE MONEY
I GOT FROM YOU QUICKLY, BUT
I DIDN'T WANNA SPEND IT ONLY
ON MYSELF.
I wanted to spend all the money
I got from you quickly,
REIRA, THE REASON I BOUGHT
A LAPTOP COMPUTER WAS BECAUSE
I WANTED TO SPEND ALL THE MONEY
I GOT FROM YOU QUICKLY, BUT
I DIDN'T WANNA SPEND IT ONLY
ON MYSELF.
REIRA, THE REASON I BOUGHT
A LAPTOP COMPUTER WAS BECAUSE
I WANTED TO SPEND ALL THE MONEY
I GOT FROM YOU QUICKLY, BUT
I DIDN'T WANNA SPEND IT ONLY
ON MYSELF.
but I didn't wanna spend it
only on myself.
REIRA, THE REASON I BOUGHT
A LAPTOP COMPUTER WAS BECAUSE
I WANTED TO SPEND ALL THE MONEY
I GOT FROM YOU QUICKLY, BUT
I DIDN'T WANNA SPEND IT ONLY
ON MYSELF.
I BOUGHT THE ACOUSTIC GUITAR
FOR THE SAME REASON, BUT I COULD
NEVER BECOME ROMANTIC ENOUGH
TO SING WHERE MY VOICE WOULD
NOT REACH YOU.
I BOUGHT THE ACOUSTIC GUITAR
FOR THE SAME REASON, BUT I COULD
NEVER BECOME ROMANTIC ENOUGH
TO SING WHERE MY VOICE WOULD
NOT REACH YOU.
I bought the acoustic guitar
for the same reason,
I BOUGHT THE ACOUSTIC GUITAR
FOR THE SAME REASON, BUT I COULD
NEVER BECOME ROMANTIC ENOUGH
TO SING WHERE MY VOICE WOULD
NOT REACH YOU.
but I could never become
romantic enough to sing
I BOUGHT THE ACOUSTIC GUITAR
FOR THE SAME REASON, BUT I COULD
NEVER BECOME ROMANTIC ENOUGH
TO SING WHERE MY VOICE WOULD
NOT REACH YOU.
where my voice would not reach you.
I BOUGHT THE ACOUSTIC GUITAR
FOR THE SAME REASON, BUT I COULD
NEVER BECOME ROMANTIC ENOUGH
TO SING WHERE MY VOICE WOULD
NOT REACH YOU.
SO FROM NOW ON I'LL SEND YOU
AN EMAIL FROM TIME TO TIME LIKE
I'M DOING NOW. IF YOU FEEL UP
TO IT, PLEASE WRITE BACK.
SO FROM NOW ON I'LL SEND YOU
AN EMAIL FROM TIME TO TIME LIKE
I'M DOING NOW. IF YOU FEEL UP
TO IT, PLEASE WRITE BACK.
So from now on,
SO FROM NOW ON I'LL SEND YOU
AN EMAIL FROM TIME TO TIME LIKE
I'M DOING NOW. IF YOU FEEL UP
TO IT, PLEASE WRITE BACK.
I'll send you an email from time to time
like I'm doing now.
SO FROM NOW ON I'LL SEND YOU
AN EMAIL FROM TIME TO TIME LIKE
I'M DOING NOW. IF YOU FEEL UP
TO IT, PLEASE WRITE BACK.
SO FROM NOW ON I'LL SEND YOU
AN EMAIL FROM TIME TO TIME LIKE
I'M DOING NOW. IF YOU FEEL UP
TO IT, PLEASE WRITE BACK.
If you feel up to it, please write back.
GOODBYE FOR NOW.
WE HAD FINE WEATHER TODAY SO
I'M SURE THE SKY WILL BE FULL OF
STARS TONIGHT. SHINICHI OKAZAKI
GOODBYE FOR NOW.
WE HAD FINE WEATHER TODAY SO
I'M SURE THE SKY WILL BE FULL OF
STARS TONIGHT. SHINICHI OKAZAKI
Goodbye for now.
GOODBYE FOR NOW.
WE HAD FINE WEATHER TODAY SO
I'M SURE THE SKY WILL BE FULL OF
STARS TONIGHT. SHINICHI OKAZAKI
GOODBYE FOR NOW.
WE HAD FINE WEATHER TODAY SO
I'M SURE THE SKY WILL BE FULL OF
STARS TONIGHT. SHINICHI OKAZAKI
We had fine weather today,
GOODBYE FOR NOW.
WE HAD FINE WEATHER TODAY SO
I'M SURE THE SKY WILL BE FULL OF
STARS TONIGHT. SHINICHI OKAZAKI
GOODBYE FOR NOW.
WE HAD FINE WEATHER TODAY SO
I'M SURE THE SKY WILL BE FULL OF
STARS TONIGHT. SHINICHI OKAZAKI
so I'm sure the sky will
be full of stars tonight.
Oh, Mr. Illegal Lawyer.
What are you working on,
hiding in the dark?
Same goes for you.
You shouldn't be walking outside alone
in the middle of the night.
It's dangerous.
It's all because that raccoon told us
about the guerrilla live performances.
I got too excited to sleep.
Sleep while you have the chance.
Once we get back to Tokyo,
we'll be really busy promoting our music.
Wanna sleep with me?
Sure. Why not.
That was a joke.
That wasn't funny.
Because you're in love with me.
You're right.
Now that I've laid all my cards
on the table,
there's no point in denying it.
Was I too obvious?
You're damn right, baldy.
What in the world are you up to?
I'm not really up to anything,
so you stop worrying and
just focus on singing.
But, Yasu.
Ever since Ren and I broke up
back home two and a half years ago,
I've felt closer to you than to Ren.
Even when I'm with Ren,
I'm still feeling a bit lonely.
He and I can no longer
become one like we used to.
Why is that?
I still love Ren like I always have.
Mai, Yui, Sumire, Akane.
Names using only
a single kanji character are best!
And it looks prettier with the last name,
which uses three kanji characters.
Like Takumi.
What's wrong with Sachiko?
No way!
Come on and help me think!
But I'm already kind of attached to it.
It's decided, the name's Sachiko!
Hey, Hachi.
With stardust spread all across,
the night sky looks awfully
bright tonight too.
Even now, when I see
something sparkling,
it reminds me of Ren.
I reached into the sky
But I couldn't reach what I wanted
They grew smaller
and disappeared into the sky
Like colorful balloons
I'm alone
My hand had no place to go
And gently you took it
Starless night
I won't look back
at the shadow of my past
I want to feel your warmth
Tears are falling down
Even if I'm unsure I won't let go
Of your hand holding mine