Every weekday's tightly packed.
Madly dashing around
again since morning.
"Rat race?" "Looks like fun."
But surprisingly death-defying.
What I'd like is a slow lifestyle.
My wish made on a shootin' star.
But there's no mercy, 100÷3.
Full of things you can't divide.
Genshiken
That's why I've carried
this in my hands...
...a limitless dream!
I jam-packed the "rest" with it...
...or at least I've tried to!
A modest happiness.
A shared joy!
We're about to etch them now
right into our youth.
So lonely to just walk on by.
So sad to have this frustration!
Let's take a break from today...
...and break into song!
Episode 13
My Name Is Ogiue and I Hate Otaku
A year sure does go by fast.
Huh?
I was thinking it's time for
the activities fair already.
Yeah, now that you mention it.
A whole year...
I wonder if any new members
will join this year.
I couldn't tell you.
I mean, you saw how Kasukabe
turned them all away last year.
Ahh... true.
It's like, I'd rather not
give my name out to otaku.
You should know that even
if this is a welcome party...
...I don't feel like welcoming anyone.
Well, I do have a feeling she's
a little more well-rounded now.
Really, you do?
Don't you think so?
Up and to the right a bit.
Okay.
So how about Kujiun: Second Term?
Heh.
I didn't think it would happen, so I guess
the fact that it did is pretty good.
Maybe.
Just so long as they give us
a certain level of...
...quality this time
and don't muddle it up.
Anime turns people into adults.
What kind of adults?
Doesn't this belong to Kugayama?
Uh, yeah. I'm pretty sure it does.
It'd be best to return it...
But he hasn't shown up here lately.
Isn't he busy with job hunting?
Looks like his parents
have some high hopes.
Tanaka said he and Ohno were in Nippori.
Ahh, excess.
You know, those two sure are close.
And they're both cosplayers.
So, speaking of job hunting?
Oh, me?
Hmmm...
Wait, what the?
Huh?
Hello.
H-hello.
You're... Kuchiki, right?
I heard you joined the anime club.
What's up?
Well, you see, I have been training.
Huh? Training? In what?
Fighting games, etc.
Select your team member.
Hey, can you do this?
Well, it'll buy time
until Kohsaka gets here.
Then we'll have him pound him.
Ouch.
You don't... seem to
have gotten very good.
So what was this training?
It was a lie.
Wha?
Hey, it's Coochy. What brings him here?
Yes, yes!
Nobody in the anime club
would call me Coochy!
I feel so moved!
Oh really. Isn't that nice.
Nobody understands me!
Just tell me why he's here.
Well, we haven't found
that out yet either.
Here's how it is, simple, concise,
plain, easily understandable, and basic!
I desire an unlimited transfer to the Society
for the Study of Modern Visual Culture...
...led by Miss Kasukabe,
the sole person who calls me Coochy...
...my self-endorsed second name!
You completely lost me.
Wow, what a great retort!
It's everything I'd hoped for!
So, the point is you want to join us.
Yes indee...
No!
Done already? Aren't you pissed?
Come on, hit me. I'll throw you out.
I'm sorry. Please let me in Genshiken.
That's what you should've said first.
Fine.
Wha?
Yes!
Yahoo!
You sure?
Huh? About what?
Uh...
She really is more well-rounded?
Or maybe it just doesn't matter
to her anymore?
Khorosho! Khorosho!
Shut up!
Come on!
Here we go!
Such nice weather.
S-so you like spring, huh?
Huh? Sure I like it... Why'd you ask?
Kasu/haru: Spring
kasu/haru: Spring
Kasukabe: Haru-hi-be, "a spring day."
You think that move'll work against me?
Wh-what?
What?
What's wrong?
Well... there's some commotion.
I can't see it, but it's
the second floor, over there.
Let's see.
Oh, there?
That's the manga club...
Wha?
What the heck?
Whoa, she fell?
Huh, for real?
I mean, she jumped?
Wh-why?
Think she's okay?
Should we call an ambulance?
Uh, well... I think her clubmates
will take care of it.
Well...
I figure you've heard the rumor, but...
...a new member got into a little
trouble with one of our girls.
So this idea is both
embarrassing yet shameless...
...but I wondered if we could
leave her in Genshiken's care.
Hmmm.
I don't know.
Which of them was more
at fault for this trouble?
I guess 90% the new girl.
And you want to force her on us?
Well, she did say she wanted
to join your kind of circle.
Genshiken doesn't have many
members, and you get along well.
We too have our share of situations.
We do?
And besides...
...won't that mean we incur the
wrath of your manga-club girl?
I don't think that'll be a problem.
Why not?
A woman's wrath is a scary thing.
Let me be candid.
Our girls already can't stand any of
the girls in Genshiken, so I don't...
...suppose adding one more now
will make much of a difference.
No way! Saki...
I could understand, but...
Cut that out.
Why don't we at least
have a look at her?
Looks like this isn't easy
for Takayanagi, either.
You have no idea what a relief
it is to hear that!
It's tough being caught
between women, eh?
Damn straight!
Hmmm, well if Kasukabe says okay...
I'll go get her.
Huh? Now?
Bandage girl...
A sullen character?
Tailor-made, huh?
She's shorter than what I was expecting.
Okay, why not introduce yourself?
All right.
My name is Ogiue, and I hate otaku.
I especially hate female otaku.
W-well, this's how she is.
Why do they like gay men so much?
Look, I don't know what happened
at the manga club, but...
...you don't need to talk that way.
Aren't you otaku too?
Aren't you?
Kasukabe! Calm down! Calm down!
Yes, I should!
I'm more "well-rounded" now!
I've got a boyfriend, see?
Huh?
Just coming here
doesn't make me an otaku!
Got it?
You're not one?
Hey, Ohno! You speak up, too!
Uh... o-okay.
No woman doesn't like gay men!
Am I included in that?
Naturally!
So Takayanagi,
this is how she ended up...
..."bailing out" of the manga club?
Uh... yeah, more or less...
Why'd you jump, anyway? To admit defeat?
You insinuate.
That hit a nerve.
Never mind tastes like
gay men and whatnot.
That pain of yours is pretty otaku-ish.
Joining a circle must mean
you want companions, right?
Work out that issue first.
Now, now! Upperclassmen, freshman girl...
...let's do this nice and civil,
Japan-style!
Let's just forget the petty things.
They're nothing.
Just bite your tongue.
Nothing! Nothing!
Hah! I kill me!
This guy's messed up.
There it is again!
Oh.
He's stopped.
Or did her glare freeze him?
Wow, that's gutl...
Ah.
What the hell's your problem?
Discipline him!
You don't go hitting women!
There, there.
Discipline?
How would we do that?
Looks like it's already done...
Genshiken
I keep wondering
if it looks too deliberate.
No! We can't expose her true nature
unless we go this far!
Uh-oh! She's looking outside!
See, told you it's suspicious.
She'll never know where we are.
Yes, well...
Today Saki and Kohsaka are on a date,
and Kugayama is job hunting.
With Kuchiki away on business in
Akihabara, this is an excellent chance!
What do you think, Tanaka?
Uh, well...
This could be the advent of Dark Ohno.
Oh, she's straightening it up.
That's no surprise.
Hey, peoples.
Oh. Here alone, Ogiue?
Yes.
Wh-why's Saki there?
Huh? She is?
Yeah, it's true.
What happened to her date?
Things were just getting good!
Kohsaka's making
the rounds in Akihabara.
We're doing our own things.
Well, the meal was good.
That'll have to do.
It must be hard, dating an otaku.
Well, it's not a matter
of sharing the same tastes.
Hm? What're these?
Are they by any chance...
Yeah, that's what they are.
These yours?
No!
They were already here
when I arrived, all for show.
You don't say.
They're Ohno's, then.
I wonder why she brought so many.
Harassment, perhaps?
Ouch.
Want to find out for sure?
Huh?
What could they be talking about?
It's not like we can hear them.
Huh? Saki's dialing her cell...
Me? Me?
What should I do?
It's Saki, all right.
Hello.
Ah!
Hey, it's Kasukabe. Got a minute?
Uh, uh, uhh, I might.
I'm not real sure.
Where are you?
Near the club building?
Y-yes, well I wouldn't say
I'm not near the building...
Meaning what? Where are you?
In... in the bathroom.
Oh, whoops. Sorry.
S'okay...
Just one question, then.
I'm in the clubroom.
Are all these homo dojinshi
on the table yours?
Yes, they are...
Okay! Yeah, thanks, that was all.
Bye.
Uh-huh...
It will seem suspicious
if I don't hurry and go.
That goes without saying.
Here's what gets me...
See, this one's based on
a foreign movie.
A regular live-action one.
I've seen it, too.
But does that mean whoever drew this...
...thinks about this stuff
when they watch it?
It's strange. I know
it never crosses my mind...
That's why such people have
something wrong upstairs.
Oh, and also, when male otaku
buy porn dojinshi...
Isn't it so they can use them?
Does that mean that female otaku...
...look at this stuff
while they #$ &% $ &#%?
I have no idea!
I mean, I look at it, and it doesn't
put me in that kind of mood at all!
But if you hate it that much,
you must have at least read some.
Otherwise you couldn't complain.
You trying to lead me?
I'm right, though, huh?
I first did in fifth grade...
a friend's copy...
Damn, that's twisted!
So that ended up being traumatic?
Well... pretty much.
Yow, that's rough, all right.
What could they be talking about?
Who knows...
Can't we bug the room?
No, we cannot.
Then I have no choice.
I'm going over there.
Oh, you are?
The surprise is ruined now.
Watching them is meaningless.
Please wait a while, then come on over.
Ayup.
So, you still go for Ohno
when she's like that?
Well, if I had to say yes or no...
Then yeah... I suppose so.
Good luck, then.
If you don't like gay stuff,
what do you like?
Anime and such?
I guess... I also play games.
But aren't there not
many girls who play?
Guys play games even
if they're not otaku...
...but hardly any of
my friends ever did.
I wouldn't know.
Hello.
Hello, Ohno.
Took long enough. Bad constipation?
P-please don't talk like that
just because it's all girls here!
Oh, that was nothing!
I went to an all-girls' school.
S-so, I just found out
that Ogiue hates...
...gay stuff because
she had some kind of trauma.
Please don't ask.
I don't want to discuss it.
Please don't tell. I don't want to know.
Things went downhill fast.
Guess we should get over there, too?
As naturally as possible, you mean?
Dear me, a yaoi book in fifth grade?
That's all it took to traumatize you?
I find that hard to believe.
In America, some girls were already
@$&% &$@% & by that age.
Don't talk like that just
because it's all girls here.
And don't look at me when you say it!
Wouldn't it be more natural to take the
plunge and get into it at that point?
You're indecent, the way you try to
push your values on to other people.
Oh, looks like a bull's-eye.
Now you're desperate
to change the subject.
For all intents and purposes,
you're still an otaku, right?
It would never have
really been traumatic.
I told you, don't say it to me.
Isn't clinging to an obvious lie
the far more indecent thing to do?
Hey, Saki. When it comes
to people like her...
Which of us is indecent, huh?
I bet you all #$ &% $ &#&
while you look at this junk!
Hey. Just because it's all girls here...
This is the kind of thing
I @#$&% $&&#& to!
Somebody...
Somebody, save me...
Hello!
Huh? Is the meeting over already?
Ohh, Ogichin! You're here, good timing!
Ogichin?
You went to Tosanbo
last Sunday, didn't you?
Heh?
See, I happened to be there
for a different event.
Hn?
Hmm?
Here's Ogichin entering the hall...
...for the all-Scram Dunk
Mitsui x Kogure book event.
Look, I even shot some video.
What's that, some otaku event?
Not only that, a yaoi-only event!
You were spying?
In effect, yes.
You ass!
The more convenience we have
in this world, the lower people get!
You're a prime example!
Um, remain calm, Ogichin.
A-ah, you see... my little brother...
Oh, you have a younger brother!
H-he...
He...
Go on!
...asked me... no, I mean...
Huh?
He plays basketball!
Aha, does he now!
This is the third floor!
Come on, Ohno! Help me out!
Oh no, emergency!
Wh... what did we miss?
Who cares what you missed?
Hold her down!
Wh-what did I miss?
We took no detours or shortcuts...
...and we weren't afraid of
what tomorrow would bring...
...as we kept walking down
Inogashira Street late at night.
Only vivid dreams extended
deep into the shadows.
We were simple
when we were young...
...with our endlessly
glistening marbles.
The time we spied from there...
...sparkled, even if
nothing big happened.
What is seen from the marbles...
...in our hands now
is a little different...
...but they shine faintly nearby.
Our guest this time is our
newest member, Chika Ogiue.
Give her a hand!
Wh-what the heck?
While we're on the subject,
your "I hate otaku" admission...
...took all of us by storm.
I wouldn't know.
I expect we'll be hearing some
more famous lines from you?
Famous lines?
Famous lines are an
essential part of a character!
It's no exaggeration to say their
first spoken line determines everything!
Episode 14
I am from the Planet Otaku
I'll keep hoping you breathe
some new life into our Genshiken.
Episode 14
I am from the Planet Otaku
Don't hold your breath!