War...
Did you say war?!
Louise...
What is it?
The teacher just said...
There will be a solar eclipse
in three days.
He told me that I should fly then.
If everything goes well, I will
head straight out of this world.
I see. Good for you!
Congratulations.
You've been wanting
to go back so much!
I hope that everything
goes well for you.
That's fine!
A history of the couple's romance
that starts from the first kiss
You, the one who cast magic on
this destiny, suddenly appeared
The sky where two moons
never fade away
That's an impossibility, right?
This is the first time I've
felt anything like this
I'm feeling more and more
at ease with this place
Even if you trip and
become depressed
I will always hold you
tight with a squeeze
The story where we met that day
stays hot with a sweet kiss
See, you can cast magic, and
the wishes will surely come true
A history of the couple's romance
that starts from the first kiss
You, the one who cast magic on
this destiny, suddenly appeared
Louise the Void
First, let's send emissaries
to talk it out!
What will come of it?
We're up against a large nation
that has entire flagships!
The two paths left for us
are to surrender,
or resist and be annihilated!
There will be no surrender!
It is the same as death to
lose one's pride as a noble!
I will take charge of the army.
Three days' time, huh...
You're sympathizing with them?
Who would, to such a girl!
Girl? I was talking about
this world as a whole.
It's so sudden that I can't
organize my feelings right!
Come to think of it, Louise
said she was in a meeting...
But she's kind of late for that.
The battle against Albion...
no, the Reconquista,
cannot be avoided now.
Under the direct orders
of Princess Henrietta,
we are reorganizing our armed forces.
The Princess is on the front line?!
A war?
This is turning out to be a huge deal.
As of today, the Tristein
Institute of Magic
will be closed for the
unforeseeable future.
What are you going to do?
I guess I have to go back home.
How pathetic. Isn't there anyone
willing to enlist for the country?
Guiche, are you joining the army?
My father is a general,
so I have no choice...
I'm more or less forced to.
So you don't want to do it.
Louise, what are you going to do?
That's a given!
Goodbye...
What's this?
Derf, can you read this?
You're fired. Go wherever
you want. - Louise,
so it says.
Fired?!
What the hell is she...
Such a waste...
Just a little more, and...
Fired?
Louise wrote this out
and disappeared.
What are you going to do?
That's a given!
I'm sure she tagged along
with Lady Henrietta.
With the Princess? Why?
War?! Against Albion?
Guiche signed up too.
Well, I'm originally from Germania,
so I'm thinking about
hurrying back home.
Princess, please let me
be at your side...
Thank you, Louise.
Hey, Derf. What will you do
when I'm gone?
I'll be sleeping again in an old item
shop. Nothing's gonna change.
I don't live in this world to begin with,
so if I go home, the war has
nothing to do with me, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Tomorrow is the solar eclipse...
When I return to the Institute,
Mr. Saito will no longer...
The kingdom of Tristein
has declined our kind
request to surrender.
Our proud warriors!
Under this holy light,
use your grand powers
to overwhelm Tristein!
What was that?!
A battleship has arrived at Talb...
They're already here?
Even if it costs my life,
I will have Talb back as ours!
May Bremir protect you.
Do you think it will fly?
I can't really put it to words,
but I can tell when I touch it.
It'll fly without any problems.
It's useful to be Gundolf.
I guess this is goodbye, darling.
But are you sure you're
all right with it?
You might never see
Louise again, you know.
Kirche...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
The dragon's blood...
Gasoline, was it?
I spent all night, and was able
to replicate this much...
Thank you so much, sir.
If everything was normal,
the entire Institute would see you off
with a grand ceremony, but...
No... I'd hate to ask for so much
at such a hard time.
The enemy army has already
planted a battleship
in the west end of Tristein,
in the village of Talb.
Who knows when they'll
reach this Institute...
Talb... You mean
Siesta's home village?!
Our army has already
begun its advance,
under the leadership of our princess.
Are you serious?!
I feel so much stronger
just by you being here
with me, Louise Françoise.
It's almost time for the solar eclipse...
Louise!
So I need to make this windmill spin?
Please!
It's reckless to head out
to the war zone!
What will you do if you break a wing?
You won't be able to
go home, you know?
I'll think about that
when the time comes!
Sir, please go for it!
All right!
Not good!
What's wrong, partner?
This is too short a distance!
At this rate, I'm going
to crash into the wall!
It's not flying...
Dammit!
Fly! Fly!
Now!
It really flew!
Tabitha, you...
Dangerous to be alone.
Sheesh... I can't just go home
all by myself, you know?!
This is fast! A dragon
can't even compare.
It's not just fast.
The bullets are still intact in here!
Just how fast is it?!
Even Sylpheed can't keep up!
Griffon squad, lure out the
enemy dragon knight squadron!
Magic Knights, rush the flagship
when that happens!
We must take the flagship
down at any cost!
Take it down?
But how would we...
Forward! Forward!
If we reach the ship's bottom,
they cannot fight back!
It looks like we don't have
a chance of winning.
Siesta, this way!
Hurry!
Lord Wales...
The sun!
Saito!
What is this sound?
I don't know.
The Robe of the Dragon!
What is that?!
That's the Robe of the Dragon!
What's the meaning of this?!
Mr. Saito?!
There sure are lots of them.
So horrible... What a riot!
I've never seen a dragon
like that before!
What power!
Gundolf!
Wardes, what is that?!
Leave it to me, your Excellency.
Matilda...
It looks like there is a need
for us to head out.
I've been waiting.
Oh, God!
Why? Why did you come?
That idiot!
Louise, where are you going?!
This is the last one!
All right!
Partner, eyes front!
It evaded!
This wind dragon has a much
higher speed than the fire dragons.
Wardes!
Unfortunately, it doesn't
have much attack power.
But my own power is
my greatest weapon!
Draw me, partner!
All right!
Gotcha!
Damn... out of ammo?
Even without dragons,
I can take care of all of you!
Even Fouquet?
This is the end!
Dammit, there's no contest
if I don't have a weapon!
What are you doing?!
If you don't hurry up, you
won't be able to go home!
Hi!
You guys...
Even Fouquet is here?
This is pretty troublesome.
What's this? We have
interesting folk here.
I'll take my vengeance from
the other day, all in one shot!
She found us!
Tabitha?
Alchemy...
I'm impressed that you didn't run.
Why would we turn our backs
to someone old like you?!
Calling me old?!
Guiche!
Okay.
Such a childish trick...
Flower petals, turn to oil! Alchemy!
Flame!
Dammit!
Hey! Wait!
Sylpheed! Why?
Tabitha!
At this rate...
This is...
Saito!
What are you doing, idiot!
That's dangerous!
And you're going off on your own,
being so selfish!
Who's the one that's being selfish?!
It's coming!
Tabitha, get away!
Why did you...
Because, because...
If you're facing danger,
I can't leave you alone!
Louise...
Gundolf!
This time, for sure, I will
bury you and that legend!
Legends, nobles, peasants,
they all mean nothing to me!
The only thing going for me
is to protect her...
I have nothing else!
I am the Familiar of Zero!
Saito...
Saito... Saito...
Saito!
What...
It's finally here!
Wake up, Louise!
You, the master of Gundolf...
...are a user of Void!
Idiot! Stay seated!
She finally got connected?
Connected?
Void magic takes time to cast.
Buy her some time, partner!
That's what Gundolf is for!
Dammit!
This is the power of the Void?
This light...
Mr. Saito...
Hold out for just a little bit longer!
The solar eclipse is ending?
I can't believe it!
That Louise the Zero?!
I still have enough power if
I can return to the mainland.
You...
With this brilliance,
become my prisoner!
What is this?
Andvari's Ring.
Then, that thing that the
Water Spirit said was stolen...
Someone!
As long as I have this, nobody can...
Fouquet got away.
So, who is this guy?
Oh, you're up?
Didn't I say you were fired?
I can't read this world's writing.
And you made a mess
out of that Robe too...
What are you going to do?
Well, I can't help things
that have already happened.
Idiot! Stupid dog!
All right?
This is a sign that we have
a new contract.
As if I were under a real magic spell
A bright smile is burnt onto my heart
But each time I see you, I give you
a pointy, cold shoulder
Why do I act mean towards the one
that I think about the most?
My true feelings, the
shards of loneliness
In the deepest part of my heart,
I'm calling for you
For the day to start from zero
You dog!