Graduation...
Gradually, everyone changes...
I've learned so many things on my journey.
To everyone I've met along the way...
...from the bottom of my heart...
...thank you.
Wait... That's really embarrassing,
I can't say something like that!
On this day, which marks the successful
completion of your academic studies,
take pride in yourselves, as the newest
graduates of this time-honored institution.
It is our hope that you spread your grand wings
and take steadfast flight towards the future.
Ah, here comes Alice!
W-What should we do?
You tell her!
Eh? M-Me?
U-Um, Alice!
Congratulations on your graduation!
I-If it's all right with you, could I have the
second button on your uniform, please?
Here you go.
Thank you very much!
I did it!
I'm happy for you.
I'd like one, too!
Actually, I've always been a fan of yours!
Umm...
Ah, no fair! I want one, too!
What the?
Alice! Alice!
Ehh?!
That was really a surprise...
I didn't tell you the graduation
ceremony was today, did I?
Don't underestimate this school's alumni.
Congratulations on your graduation, Alice!
Yes, thank you very much.
"Dear Ai, I'm happy to report that this summer,
Alice graduated from middle school!"
Do you remember that day
Oboeteimasuka ano hi o
When your heart suddenly began to race
Futo kanjita tokimeki o
The rays from the blue sky were pouring over you...
Aoi hizashi abite
...as you cut through the wind
Kaze o kiru kimi ni
I couldn't look away, and when our eyes met
Mitoreru to me ga atte
I couldn't help but smile
Egao koboreta
It's just like a spiral
Marude supiraare
I want to spend my days waving to you
Itsumademo te o furitai hibi
Why don't you just walk home normally?
I want to spend my days waving to you
Itsumademo te o furitai hibi
I thought maybe I should, but...
I want to spend my days waving to you
Itsumademo te o furitai hibi
...this is my last middle school
challenge, so I have to do it!
This is my proof that I was here with you
Koko ni tashika ni kimi to ita akashi
Ah, Athena!
This is my proof that I was here with you
Koko ni tashika ni kimi to ita akashi
An eternal spiral
Zutto supiraare
There's a path which stretches on ahead
Kono saki mo tsuzuiteru michi ga aru
Hey Junior...
When you climb the next hill,
Tsugi no saka o nobottara
Hey Junior...
When you climb the next hill,
Tsugi no saka o nobottara
...looks like you failed your
"walking backwards" challenge.
When you climb the next hill,
Tsugi no saka o nobottara
That's really no problem!
When you climb the next hill,
Tsugi no saka o nobottara
Time stands still when Athena is around.
Let's meet again
Mata aimashou
Time stands still when Athena is around.
Let's meet again
Mata aimashou
Surrounded By That Orange Wind...
Gondola coming through!
What a loud voice!
Junior, you're really fired up today!
Yes, I'm all fired up!
School used to take up most of my time,
but now I get to spend it practicing with you two.
So...
So I'm really happy about that.
All right! We'll set our sights on becoming
Primas today as usual! Let's-a-go!
Yeah!
Akari, President Aria!
Start with some vocal exercises!
O-Okay!
Gondola coming through!
So you're all fired up now that you've
graduated from school, huh?
Yes!
I'm really on a roll right now!
I don't really understand it myself,
but I feel like anything I do will turn out well.
Here, President Maa.
Here.
Say, pretty please, pretty please!
Here!
Say, Alice...
Yes?
Why don't we go on a picnic tomorrow?
This time, for sure.
Athena?
Geez... What are you doing?
I'm sorry!
Lunch is packed up and ready!
That's really perfect, Athena!
I know! Alice...
Yes?
Today, why don't we pretend that
I'm a customer and you're an Undine?
What an interesting idea.
Sure, I'm up for a challenge!
So Athena, I guess that means you're my
valued customer from this moment on?
Yes, I look forward to...
Please take my hand, ma'am.
Ma'am?
Eh?
Ah, y-yes!
Alice, your smile has gotten
so much softer, hasn't it?
Ma'am, please forgive me,
but isn't this the first time we've met?
Ah, I'm sorry.
Ma'am, the truth is, I get to practice every day
with a friend who has the best smile ever.
Ahead is Ponte di Rialto, a bridge that spans the
entire 48-meter-wide Canal Grande with one arch.
Unlike Piazza San Marco, this area is a mix of
shops, markets, bars and private residences.
Here, you can really get a sense of
everyday life in Neo-Venezia.
One might say this is
Neo-Venezia's second city center.
Your sightseeing information is very clear
and easy to understand, Miss Undine.
I owe it to a strict friend who likes to prohibit
everything, and trains me hard every day.
Well then, Ma'am.
Where shall we head next?
If you have any particular sightseeing spots
you'd like to see, please feel free to let me know.
Let's see...
Well then, I'll take you up on your kind offer.
From here on, there will be a stretch of
countryside that continues on for a while.
Please enjoy this other face of Neo-Venezia,
which is typically known for its port-town scenery.
Okay!
Hello!
Excuse us while we pass by!
Take care!
Ciao!
Buon giorno!
Hi!
You seem to be enjoying yourself, ma'am.
Yes, very much!
Ma'am, would you like some more tea?
Thank you. I'm fine for now.
It really is a perfect day for a picnic, isn't it?
Miss Undine.
Yes?
Why don't we get going?
Right!
Freshly Made
Gelato
Hello, sir!
If you please!
Sure, it's on its way down right now.
So just hang tight for a little bit, okay?
Okay!
Good luck.
What's the matter, Miss Undine?
Do I look that unreliable?
Not at all. You're very reliable.
Good work today, Alice.
Huh?
Until the water elevator reaches the top, you can
come out of work mode and take a breather.
Eh? Ah, okay...
You're really amazing, Alice.
You can do everything now, can't you?
Thank you very much.
Thanks to all that training with my friends,
even I think my sculling and guiding
have gotten pretty good, but...
But?
To be honest...
...it's my canzone...
My voice is soft to begin with, and I'm
not very good when it comes to singing...
I'm always worried I'm not singing loudly enough,
or wondering if I'm singing off-key...
The more I think I have to sing well,
the more my mind goes blank.
When you feel insecure about your singing,
that feeling is conveyed to those who are listening.
Skill is important, of course, but what's
most important is your love of singing.
Love... of singing...
If you don't love your own singing,
how can you expect others to love it?
Athena...
Miss Undine...
...our destination is just ahead!
Yes...
Did you know, Miss Undine?
Before this planet's surface was covered
with water, when it wasn't yet known as Aqua...
...they say this world was covered
entirely in the color orange.
Perhaps that's why this time of day,
when the planet takes on an orange hue,
is so dear and a bit nostalgic
to all the people who live here on Aqua.
It's as if our past and future are
both captured in this single moment.
Huh?
There's someone there...
That's... Akari and Aika?
And there's the man from the water elevator...
And behind him are our company representatives
and someone from the Gondola Association?
What's going on?
Thank you for today, Miss Undine.
Lastly, may I request a song?
Miss Undine?
Ma'am, do you know of Aqua's
famous Three Great Water Fairies?
I may not look it, but I'm actually the
top protégée of the one known as Siren.
The setting sun and the rippling waves
Vesperrugo, fluas en ondetoj
Seem like a song of pure happiness
Gi estas kiel la kanto, bela kanto de felico
The birds are like messengers, delivering kindness
Cu vi rimark is birdojn, portanta afableco
They fly beyond the sea, placing love on the winds
Super la maro flugas, ili flugas kun amo
In the twilight sky, which makes my heart tremble,
Oranga cielo emocias mian spiriton
Lies a star of hope that will shine forevermore
Stelo de I'espero, stelo lumis eterne
Shine forevermore
Lumis eterne
Ma'am, even though I was never
good at it, as a child, I loved to sing.
Your words brought back
the feelings I had back then.
Thank you very much!
The setting sun and the rippling waves
Yuuhi ga shizumi nagareru saza nami
The company has been anxiously awaiting
your graduation from middle school.
The setting sun and the rippling waves
Yuuhi ga shizumi nagareru saza nami
Your sculling skills are perfect.
The setting sun and the rippling waves
Yuuhi ga shizumi nagareru saza nami
Our concerns about your tour guide skills,
customer service and canzone...
Seem like a song of pure happiness
Sore wa marude muku na shiawase no uta no you
Our concerns about your tour guide skills,
customer service and canzone...
Seem like a song of pure happiness
Sore wa marude muku na shiawase no uta no you
...were completely dispelled, as you have
proven your progress brilliantly in today's exam.
Seem like a song of pure happiness
Sore wa marude muku na shiawase no uta no you
Athena, does this mean...
Seem like a song of pure happiness
Sore wa marude muku na shiawase no uta no you
The birds are like messengers, delivering kindness
Tori-tachi wa yasashisa o hakobu tsukai
You have exceptional talent, so you'll surely
lead the next generation of the Undine industry.
The birds are like messengers, delivering kindness
Tori-tachi wa yasashisa o hakobu tsukai
The Gondola Association, in recognition of your
extraordinary talent, and with great hope...
The birds are like messengers, delivering kindness
Tori-tachi wa yasashisa o hakobu tsukai
...has made an unprecedented decision.
The birds are like messengers, delivering kindness
Tori-tachi wa yasashisa o hakobu tsukai
They fly beyond the sea, placing love on the winds
Umi o koe tobu yo ai o kaze ni nose
Congratulations, Alice.
They fly beyond the sea, placing love on the winds
Umi o koe tobu yo ai o kaze ni nose
Or should I say...
They fly beyond the sea, placing love on the winds
Umi o koe tobu yo ai o kaze ni nose
...Orange Princess.
They fly beyond the sea, placing love on the winds
Umi o koe tobu yo ai o kaze ni nose
From this day forth, you are a Prima Undine!
Orange... Princess...
In the twilight sky, which makes my heart tremble,
Kokoro furueru tasogare no sora ni
Orange... Princess...
In the twilight sky, which makes my heart tremble,
Kokoro furueru tasogare no sora ni
Is that...
In the twilight sky, which makes my heart tremble,
Kokoro furueru tasogare no sora ni
An alias?
In the twilight sky, which makes my heart tremble,
Kokoro furueru tasogare no sora ni
Ehh?!
In the twilight sky, which makes my heart tremble,
Kokoro furueru tasogare no sora ni
Lies a star of hope that will shine forevermore
Towa ni kagayaku kibou no hoshi yo
Athena...
Lies a star of hope that will shine forevermore
Towa ni kagayaku kibou no hoshi yo
Athena...
Lies a star of hope that will shine forevermore
Towa ni kagayaku kibou no hoshi yo
Alice.
Lies a star of hope that will shine forevermore
Towa ni kagayaku kibou no hoshi yo
Lumis eterne
Ruumisu eterune
Alice!
Akari, Aika!
Junior!
Alice!
Akari, Aika!
Congratulations!
Junior!
Akari, Aika...
Thank you...
Thank you... so much...
"Ai, in the brilliant history of Aqua's Undines,"
"the legend of the first
rank-skipping Prima has been born!"
"Alice really is amazing, isn't she?
I kind of admire her for it!"
"Congratulations, Alice!"
A shore awash in golden waves
Kin no nami kishibe ni
Filled with yearning, I open my eyes and it's morning
Akogare mezameru no asa ni
As my thoughts focus intently on someone,
Dareka no koto o tsuyoku omou toki
Love rests on my palm, held high
Kakageta te no hira ni ai ga tomaru
A future guided by the flow of water and wind
Mizu no yukue to kaze ga shimesu mirai
I gaze at the hope that surrounds this world
Kono hoshi o tsusumu kibou mitsumete
The distant clouds of light are beckoning now
Tooi kumo hikari ga sasou you ni yureru ima
A shore awash in golden waves
Kin no nami kishibe ni
Filled with yearning, I open my eyes and it's morning
Akogare mezameru no asa ni
And my day begins
Hajimaru
Next Episode
Alice is a Prima now, huh?
I think it might be stressing her out.
Next Episode
I'm really super nervous!
At times like that, the best
thing to do is to take it easy.
Next Episode
The Excitement on That Moon-Gazing Night...
Next time, "The Excitement
on That Moon-Gazing Night..."
Next Episode
The Excitement on That Moon-Gazing Night...
Now, please take my hand.