Every weekday's tightly packed.
Madly dashing around
again since morning.
"Rat race?" "Looks like fun."
But surprisingly death-defying.
What I'd like is a slow lifestyle.
My wish made on a shootin' star.
But there's no mercy, 100÷3.
Full of things you can't divide.
Genshiken
That's why I've carried
this in my hands...
...a limitless dream!
I jam-packed the "rest" with it...
...or at least I've tried to!
A modest happiness.
A shared joy!
We're about to etch them now
right into our youth.
So lonely to just walk on by.
So sad to have this frustration!
Let's take a break from today...
...and break into song!
Shiioh University
Hey there, Ogiue.
Uh, hi...
Come eat with us.
Are you sure?
Positive.
Have a seat.
Huh? You wear contacts?
Yes, well, since this spring.
How's your eyesight?
Somewhere around 20l200.
Huh. So because you got into a
Tokyo school, you changed your look.
You go, girl.
It isn't that big a deal.
Well, you should've also done
something about your hair.
It's cute though.
I did change it, actually...
I once up and gave myself a
perm. I looked way too old.
Hmm, what could it be?
Your clothes, maybe?
Huh?
My switch just flipped.
The retail clerk switch!
That's the one.
Today, the direct approach:
"Stand up for a second, miss."
Hmm, it's not your size.
Is this men's clothing?
Uh, this is... on purpose.
I understand wanting to hide your
figure, but this's a little otaku-ish.
That's a little rude, you know?
But it's true.
Hmm, well, maybe it does look
bad, being the wrong size.
Although it used to be in style to barely
see your hands through your sleeves.
You went to the trouble of coming
to Tokyo. Why not do a little more?
You shouldn't treat
people like such hicks!
It might be less a hick thing and
more an overly self-conscious thing.
You're only making it worse, Saki.
Sorry, was I blunt?
Too blunt.
But hey, this is how I
get when I see people...
...who could do better or
who kinda miss the mark.
Hi!
Sorry.
This is just how Saki is.
Episode 14
I Am from the Planet Otaku
Like I said, those friends were
mundanes! I was being considerate.
That's a lie.
Ogiue was there too.
Like I could butt into a
conversation between girls!
Oh really. Then you admit
you averted your eyes.
Hey...
That's what they call ignoring,
you know. Ig-nor-ing!
I even waved to you.
Fine then, I was ignoring you!
But even if I spoke up...
...you'd probably make some
really annoyed face at me!
No, I wouldn't! First off, we
were talking about otaku fashion...
...so I wanted you to come over!
No thanks!
Um...
You know, everyone's already
aware that my boyfriend's an otaku.
And they know I frequent Genshiken!
Do not let it go to your head.
No amount of time will
make you an otaku...
...which proves you
are from another planet.
Shut up.
Someday you will break up with Kohsaka.
You piss me off, otaku!
I am from the planet Otaku.
I come in peace.
Otaku, otaku, otaku, otaku, otaku!
Your glasses.
They're square!
You only just noticed?
S-square!
So, what? You're
suddenly trying for style?
Well, it was a change, and I was
starting to need a new prescription.
Do they suck?
Huh? They don't suck... but it's like...
Your laughing suggests they suck.
It's your clothes. I was
talking about it with Ogiue too.
Oh, right.
Do none of you care?
That's what they call
otaku fashion, huh?
Are you cool with hearing that?
Does it not make any difference?
Well, it's like, no, I don't care.
And I have no taste for it.
Not to mention money.
Suddenly you get defensive?
Does it sting that badly?
An otaku accepts no
challenge he can't win.
About that. Don't you two think it's
more indecent to dress stylishly?
"We don't bother."
"We're hardcore otaku!"
Like a reverse superiority complex...
Easy for you to say.
Yeah.
Kohsaka buys both clothes
and games, and he manages.
Kohsaka's...
True, he has different
substance and taste.
But it's okay even
if you have bad taste.
What's bad is giving up
and being all defiant.
You say it's outside your specialty
and don't even try to show interest.
I think that's the
biggest problem with otaku.
Huh?
S-square!
Just can't get past that, huh?
What am I doing in a place like this?
Well, I wanted a new
jacket and pants at least.
That's all this is.
I've never been in a store like that.
I tend to set ¥2,000 as an upper
limit and shop at cheap stores.
But I guess that's a mental block.
Expand your horizons some.
You know, I didn't even look at prices.
It was all I could do to even go in.
Pathetic...
One more time!
This time I'm looking at prices!
So laughable.
That's expensive,
Kasukabe! I could never!
DVD box sets go for this much...
...but why should a single piece
of clothing need this kind of price!
I can't buy anything expensive
anyway, so I'll go for all-out cheap!
What's bad is giving up
and being all defiant.
No, stop that. Don't panic.
No need to buy anything
exorbitant. Just something so-so.
I'll think about tops again
later. Right now, bottoms!
Where're pants...
Are you looking for anything?
Pa...
No! Not pants...
Uh, uh, underwear.
Aw, dammit!
On the second floor.
Th-thanks.
Forget it.
I lose. Total loss. But I guess I tried.
I don't think I've
compared this many prices...
...since dojin shops
during middle school.
Wait. That's right. I'm
shopping the wrong way!
Just comparing prices is meaningless.
The fun level of a game isn't
proportional to its price!
I'll draw my own conclusions!
If I think, "This is nice,"
I'll shell out for it.
I take pride in the things I've chosen.
Adult games, dojinshi,
clothes, it's all the same!
After all, that's what makes me, me!
Excuse me!
That's what it's all about, Kasukabe!
Not-even-close!
...is what she'll probably say.
Genshiken
Shinjuku Station
Hi, Kasukabe!
Uh, who's he?
A friend of my boyfriend's.
Ahh, an otaku. I can tell.
What the hell. I knew
she'd just get annoyed.
Just like I said in the first place!
Oh. On your way home, Madarame?
Uh, yeah, I am.
Good timing then.
That's true.
We'll see you later then.
Then I'm headed home too.
Wha!
You are?
They've got things to do.
Oh...
What? Do you have plans?
No, no, I don't.
Weren't we having a fight?
Huh?
You call that a fight!
"Weren't we having a fight?"
Talk about overly self-conscious!
That's so otaku!
Okay, I get it now.
So, want to get some food?
Huh? Wh-why?
To "make up," of course.
I'm hungry, anyway.
Or will you say something otaku like, "I can't eat
with a friend's girlfriend."
Kaiten Sushigen
What?
Are you still mad? You could
at least enjoy some food.
You really do seem to
be from another planet.
Me otaku. No understand you.
That again?
Kohsaka's not going to mind
this, should he find out.
That's because he's from
another galaxy altogether.
How are we handling the bill?
Will we each take one?
Fatty tuna, please.
You got it!
Apparently we're not.
Here's your fatty tuna.
Where are your new glasses?
Eh?
You paid money for them.
Oh, those...
Weren't they supposed
to go with all that?
I just figured it was
time to buy new stuff.
Sea urchin and steamed abalone, please.
What is it? Shirts?
Several things.
Wear them in the clubroom.
Won't you just trash talk them?
Of course.
But the thoughtless stuff you're
wearing now is unspeakable.
It's not even worth a comment.
Geez, you're harsh.
The day you put some thought
into choosing what you wear...
...is the day I grant
you a fair appraisal.
Grant me a fair appraisal, huh?
Want me to order anything for you?
No thanks, I wasted too much money.
I can't spend any on food now.
Here's your steamed abalone.
"Wasted money." I've never
heard you say that before.
When you're from the planet Otaku...
...everything but otaku
materials is a waste of funds.
Again? You keep coming
back to that otaku thing.
It doesn't really mean you're an alien.
That doesn't sound like you.
Don't you loathe otaku?
Lest you forget, I'm dating
Kohsaka. That Kohsaka!
Like it or not, I get used to otaku.
I'm guessing not.
I've been making efforts lately too.
Oh? What kind?
Like keeping my distance
when it's anime and game time.
Isn't that you being neglected?
Shut up.
Oh, but the other day I
played a game with him some.
Well, how about that?
There's this prince guy.
Prince?
You roll this thing, and
it picks up other things.
Ahh, didn't part two come out recently?
Got me. But it's like, simple and
fun so I played for about an hour.
Wow... Uh, I mean...
Huh? This's quite a shock.
Uh, but in the end, I'm not
sure I wanted you to do that.
Huh? Why not?
Well, I'm totally cool
with you dating Kohsaka.
But it's like... I wanted
you to walk a thorny path.
That's creepy.
Aha.
Excuse me, sea bream, please.
To be honest, I'd just as soon
you were from another planet.
Huh?
What was that?
A little wish.
Looks like I'm the
one on the thorny path.
Ow, hot!
Well, what to say.
Here's your sea bream!
Shinjuku Station
Care to sit?
Huh?
I'm fine. You take it.
Ain't it indecent for
a man to sit down first?
Huh?
You're speaking otaku again.
Okay, then I will...
Well, there are no rude drunks around.
And she's more likely to take care
of things herself than ask for help.
Beautiful muscles
Welcome back.
Hi there.
So you had sushi?
Uh, yeah, we did.
I could've gone for that.
You said you were gaming all day.
Could you've made it to Shinjuku?
Guess not.
Did the new "Menma-chan" come out?
Oh, I didn't have time to check.
Oh, okay.
I'm going to Akihabara Saturday.
Want me to pick it up?
Would you mind?
Sure thing. M'kay, take it easy.
What should we do tonight?
Can I sleep at your place?
That'd be fine.
Okay!
Huh. That's not bad, is it?
¥18,000! Just for pants!
I never buy clothes above ¥3,000!
Even Kasukabe may
give her okay on these.
Uhh, but Saki's apparently fine with
spending about 100,000 at a time.
I see someone getting hit very hard!
Wait, that's me!
It doesn't really matter.
I just bought what I wanted to buy.
She who ridicules otaku is otaku.
Well said! What a great thing to say!
What's up?
She's here!
Welcome, crew of the Yamato.
Wow.
Nice. Looks good on you.
Yeah, I win!
Win what? That's so exaggerated.
Hey, well.
Are you a little surprised?
A little more open than expected, huh?
Not happy!
Well, you were so down on me before.
Aw, come on. You're thin,
but your shoulders are broad.
That look's in these days.
Aha. Maybe I'll buy something too.
There are sales next
month if you do it soon.
No, now is no time for us
to be following fashions!
Oh, do you need one too?
You screwed up!
You didn't have to buy that!
Huh?
But...
At least change your hairstyle!
Oh, the Akihabara custom outfit.
Ta-da!
Now let's get going!
I-it's kinda sad how
it's not Ch-Char custom.
We took no detours or shortcuts...
...and we weren't afraid of
what tomorrow would bring...
...as we kept walking down
Inogashira Street late at night.
Only vivid dreams extended
deep into the shadows.
We were simple
when we were young...
...with our endlessly
glistening marbles.
The time we spied from there...
...sparkled, even if
nothing big happened.
What is seen from the marbles...
...in our hands now is a little different...
...but they shine faintly nearby.
Preview
What's the worst meal you've had?
Like M-McDonald's?
I think that's pretty decent, actually.
Things like street-stall
udon or school rice balls.
Ah, those individually-packaged ones.
I know someone who put soy sauce on
tissues, toasted them, and ate them.
What? Is that good?
Dunno.
Can't you guys cook?
N-no.
I can boil water, at least.
Hey, Madarame. What's your shabby meal?
Shabby meal?
Right.
Episode 15
Then I'll Undress You! I don't eat them.
Then I'll Undress You! I don't eat them!