Get lost.
Just split, right now.
Hey, you!
Huh? What?
What year are you?
Is that you, Saki?
Huh?
No way!
Kohsaka?
B-But didn't you have short hair?
That was in grade school.
It's been years since then.
So, what were you listening to?
A CD by the voice
actress Sumire Matsuzawa.
Really?
Voice actress?
Across time, a reunion
that would seem to be fate...
Her childhood friend was an otaku...
Ah, what the heck does fate know?
Genshiken
I woke up and as usual forgot
my cell and missed the Express.
My life reflected in
the train window.
I'm sure I have something that
I won't lose to anyone in Japan...
... but it's pretty sad
that no one notices it.
I can't run fast, though.
I'm not that strongly-built.
Here I go, at my dauntless pace.
Pass away, today's
sadness, raining in the sun!
Hesitation, repetition,
dreaming all night, all night.
Farewell sadness,
to outer space you go!
Look to the sky and shout
at the top of your lungs!
At this tempo!
Right now, at this tempo!
Genshiken
You're the only one here, Mr. Chairman?
Yeah, Haraguchi.
How rare for Madarame
and the others to be gone.
Yes...
It looks like they went to Akihabara.
Ah, young and restless...
Episode 2: Comparative Classification of
Consumption and Diversion among Modern Youth
Next stop, Harajuku.
Harajuku.
Akihabara?
Yeah.
Are they buying a computer?
Oh, games.
There's that, but they
were talking about dojinshi.
What? They sell that stuff?
Isn't it Electric Town?
There's no place left that
doesn't carry that kind of thing.
No way, for real?
It's that kind of place now?
That's funny...
I've gone there to buy
CDs and whatnot, but...
They just don't catch your eye.
Don't talk like I'm
the strange one.
Next stop, Akihabara.
Akihabara.
That was fast.
Our college is still
technically in the city.
Where do you want to go?
Uh, I...
You said you wanted to come...
...so we combined this with
our freshman welcome party.
But Kohsaka isn't here.
He's with Kasukabe in Harajuku.
Oh...
Akihabara, huh?
That's pretty damn close.
It's not that close.
Oh you're right, it's not close.
Why don't we start on Takeshita Street?
Sure.
Yeah, today I take my time.
Then I make my move.
Akihabara Station
Akihabara, Torano Ana
We aren't going in here?
After we've wandered around, and
after the Sasahara-style main event.
Okay...
We'll take our time with that
kind of store after we eat lunch.
That sounds good...
Oh, this shop looks nice.
You haven't said
anything today, Kugayama.
Oh, m-my voice doesn't
c-c-carry in crowds.
That can't be true.
No, I've l-learned from experience
not to talk in places like this.
Oh...
Which one looks best?
They both look good.
You can take your time choosing.
Kohsaka...
What?
Is it okay that you didn't go with them?
Yeah, it's all right.
Really?
Yeah, I told them all
I was seeing you today.
Ah, cool!
Torano Ana
Don't worry, it's the 4th floor.
Huh?
Well, what does male-oriented
dojin-loving Sasahara think of this?
Huh?
Good enough?
No, I'm just not familiar with it.
Don't worry, he loves them too.
Look at the speed with which he checks
those Egg Eater Sakura book samples.
Wow.
Embarrassment will get you nowhere.
Oh, I wonder if this folklore
look will be in this year.
Folklore is about ethnology, so I wonder
why it's become a fashion term?
Oh, that one looks good.
"Bishojo game" means
an over-18 video game.
But what does it mean when a
game that already has sex scenes...
...is made into an over-18 dojinshi?
Hey, fighting games.
This is something I
could really get into.
This combination is really cute,
but it's expensive.
This has good art, but it's thin...
...but it's cheap.
The pants are right for the bottom, but
it feels like they might be too light...
...and I could try a skirt instead.
The one's thick but expensive,
but since it's a dojinshi...
...numerous people drew in it and
the quality will range all over.
I must think about a
point of compromise...
...between design and source material
not to mention a balance with price!
I'll just buy them all!
Hello there.
Do you have a point card?
His shopping style is amazing.
In a way, he doesn't look
at the price in the end.
I envy him, but can he afford it?
Well, it looks like he cuts
back on living expenses.
Wow...
That comes to 123,456 Yen.
Do you have a point card?
No, u-uh, l-I don't.
Pardon?
I-I-I don't.
Oh, you don't?
Shall I make one?
Um, n-no thanks.
Pardon?
N-No thanks.
You sure bought a lot.
Wouldn't it be better not to
make your dad any angrier?
Forget that, let's eat
lunch and kill some time.
Okay.
Where to?
I'd like to go to a hotel.
Someone I know opened a
gallery and I want to go see it.
Oh yeah?
Take my time, then make my move.
That clerk pissed me off,
that's why I can't stand people.
Looks like somebody's in a bad mood.
You only speak up when
you're complaining.
I'll be frank, it's really your fault!
S-Stuttering is
a h-habit of mine.
Stuttering has nothing to do with it!
You simply don't speak up!
Hey, keep it down.
Why don't we go do karaoke, then?
It can double as voice practice.
Heh, you want to?
Uh?
You sure are insensitive.
I am?
You don't think so?
Isn't that normal?
If you don't think so, it
means you're insensitive.
Why's that?
Think about it.
Your insensitivity caused us to
have this conversation in the first place.
This taro and bamboo shoot
croquette mushroom dish is great!
V V V! Victory!
Combine 1-2-3...
...4- 5, move out!
Super electromagnetic
robot who shakes the earth!
Warrior of justice... Combattler V!
Who said you could sing with me?
If it ain't your turn, put
the damn microphone down!
Why can't I?
Don't worry, it's always like this.
I'm a little drunk.
I feel all warm and tired.
Yeah, it's pretty warm
these days even at night.
Time to be direct...
Hey, Kohsaka.
Are you busy after this?
I sure am.
I'm going to Akihabara to get
in line for a midnight sale.
I haven't done this in a long time.
It's this software that
everyone's been raving about.
It creates this stimulating
ambiance all around the user.
I wonder if it's also the
guys' ultimate objective.
We didn't set anything up, but
I expect I'll run into them.
See ya!
The town of Harajuku,
a date with a sweetheart.
Akihabara, supposedly so far away.
Akihabara, was close by.
The match is officially over.
Oh boy.
It was yummy.
Oy.
Thank you.
Ritsuko.
It's you, Ritsuko, isn't it?
It's me, Chihiro Enomoto.
When did you get back?
Three years ago.
That long ago?
You were gone for so long.
I wish you'd told me.
I decided there was no need to.
If I stop being a
crybaby, will you marry me?
Let us begin the 256th "This Week's
'Kujiun' was Interesting" meeting.
Has it been broadcast that many times?
Don't sweat the details.
What?
Let's hear reflections!
"W-Will you marry me?"
S-sure was an intense part.
It was a bit much in the
scene before that where the...
...present-day Miss President won't
show her feelings to Chihiro.
Right.
But childhood friendships
sure are strong!
Why, do you suppose?
It's because you can't
share memories of childhood...
...with someone you've just met.
Right.
Also, y-y-you're so close that...
...the distance between you
can't really be shortened.
Also, childhood promises
are a standard device.
But in the original manga, the line "W ill
you marry me?" isn't actually spoken.
It's not?
She says "If I stop being a crybaby..."
...and the rest is
left up to the imagination.
Ah...
Then I like the original better...
If she actually says that...
B-But, I'd say the anime is
the more dramatic version.
I think the anime's better too.
I'm for the original, in the end.
W-What?
Hello and greetings.
Kohsaka hasn't shown up yet.
Sasahara, come here a minute.
Huh?
Move aside, Kuga-pee.
K-Kuga-pee?
You mean me?
You look the most honest...
...but why are you always so uptight?
I guess I just am...
Well lighten up a little.
All right...
Actually, it's about Kohsaka...
What the hell?
Get back over there!
Are you stupid?
I can hear you from
any part of the room!
Actually...
Well...
The other day in Kohsaka's room...
I found a bunch of dirty anime books.
W-What?
Well hey...
It isn't that big a deal.
But it's anime!
It's anime but it's porn!
You u-use them the same
way you would regular porn books.
It's j-just a question of preference.
Yeah, even we have regular porn.
I don't have any silly regular porn.
K-Kohsaka's on the same level as him...
Kohsaka!
Talk about rude.
But there are over-18 video games
in plain view around his room.
Why are you upset now?
You're right, when I looked again
they were all over the place.
Why didn't you notice?
Hmm, maybe they just
didn't catch my eye...
It's the first thing you notice!
Is th-this what mundanes are like?
Did you not notice that this room is
filled with that kind of thing?
For real?
On these shelves and in that locker.
Even the girl on the poster
behind you is from an adult game.
But this is a child.
You take her clothes off?
All of them?
You're making it sound like
it's some kind of strip mahjong...
Besides, she's in high school.
Now, now.
Undress her?
You rape her!
S-Savage...
I-I don't get it...
How could you get
aroused over this drawing?
Oh, there's lots of them.
2-D complex cases or what have you.
What?
Look, for example...
What does this look like?
A face?
And this?
A woman's body.
Yes, in this way even with abstract
symbols like these, humans...
...can use their imaginations
to see something else.
You could call it a faculty that
the human brain is endowed with.
Even looking at simple cave drawings
from ancient times tells us this.
They saw on the walls of their caves...
...the animals scampering
across the great plains!
So in other words...
...guys who say they can't get off on
anime either have some mental defect...
...or they're just
trying to act superior!
They even had pornography
in the Edo period.
Only being interested in
this is a defect, I'd say.
So, what?
Does this mean he has no
interest in real women?
We h-hear that a lot.
There are those of us
who do want girlfriends.
Well, Madarame doesn't see it like that.
I don't not want one.
More importantly, don't you think
Kohsaka's a little spaced out?
Yeah!
I have more trouble with his
personality than his hobbies.
Heh.
Aha! So you chose him not for
his personality or hobbies...
...but his outward appearance.
Huh?
You took one look at Kohsaka
and were smitten by him.
I can't understand how you
could do a thing like that.
How can you be into someone when
you don't even know them well?
Don't talk about stuff you don't know...
It's not like the first time
I met him was at this college...
Huh?
What I mean is, he and I lived in the
same neighborhood when we were little.
What?
Are you a freshman?
Is that you, Saki?
No way...
Kohsaka?
K-Kasukabe's a childhood
friend character!
Awesome!
They really exist!
I've never seen one before!
These are otaku, all right...
Uh-oh, suddenly she seems a lot cuter.
To me too...
I'm sure she has a cute side
beneath her rough personality.
I do not!
So, from my viewpoint
Kohsaka's weird now.
He didn't used to be into that stuff.
Well, hobbies change as you get older...
Was he always that good looking?
No, he was practically bald.
If I stop being a
crybaby, will you marry me?
That's why I didn't
recognize him at first.
Oh that's a riot!
Are you ready for a beating?
Wait wait... So, it was
"love at first sight."
He looked good so I talked to him.
At first I thought all this was okay...
But...
...I can't understand that kind of
hobby, and it doesn't suit him at all...
...so I want to make him give it up.
Impossible.
Even if you were to
try, he can't give it up.
If my girlfriend tried
that on me, I'd dump her.
But you don't have a girlfriend.
Ya got me!
Otaku or not... You're like,
the type of guy I can't stand!
Really?
It's my first kiss.
A kiss with you.
I will give you all my love.
Hey, what's he singing?
A famous anime song from a while
back...
Hey, what do you think?
What should I do?
So now you're depending on us for
help?
Hey Kohsaka!
Yes?
I'm tired of this.
Go have a first kiss with her.
Cut that out.
You want to, Saki?
Oh!
He s-said it.
That's fine, but say you like me first.
I like you, Saki.
Good.
T-They're kissing.
In public.
M-Madarame's frozen stiff.
He doesn't do well with adversity.
Let's go somewhere alone.
I know I just got here,
but I have to go!
Thanks, everyone!
"T-Thanks"?
Maybe th-that was her cute side?
No, I'd say it was her scary side.
Yes! Now we'll go
back to his place and...
Saki, I have to go to Akihabara.
What?
Sumire Matsuzawa's new
CD goes on sale today.
She's having a hand-shaking party at
Ishikado Electronics in Akihabara...
...and I really need to go.
Sorry, Saki.
See ya!
The train departs, leaving only smoke.
Distant feelings, fleeting hopes.
Ah, far away from Akihabara...
To be continued next week.
We took no detours or shortcuts...
... and we weren't afraid of
what tomorrow would bring...
... as we kept walking down
Inogashira Street late at night.
Only vivid dreams extended
deep into the shadows.
We aren't quite grown up.
Simple but complicated
glistening like marbles.
The time we could see from there
sparkled, even if nothing big happened.
What we see from the marbles in
our hands now is a little different...
... but they shine faintly nearby.
You know, there are some
things you just want to forget.
For example, things from your past.
Y-You said it.
Erasing the past, like magazines
that published your submissions.
You mean like a life advice column?
N-No, more like...
"Out"
No!
"Fanroad"
Y-You can't say those words
out in the open like that!
Talk about defensive...