Say, Nana Komatsu.
Do you remember
the first time we met?
I'm the type who doesn't believe
in fate one bit.
I think this was
all a coincidence.
When I was darkness at that time
With trembling lips
In a corner of a room I cry
The more I struggle
The more this wound deepens
The broken promise hurt me
Nobody can save me
God, I have only one request
Stop tearing apart my love
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Sorrow tumbling down is your song
All alone with nowhere to go in my life
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Oh baby, help me from frozen pain
With your smile, your eyes,
and sing me, just for me
I wanna need your love
I'm a broken rose
Hello! Welcome to Junko's room.
- Welcome!
I thought it was Nana's room?
No, this is my room.
I'm the master here, you know.
You are?
You know what?
I've been really exhausted
as of late.
Even though you play
a small role?
Hey, you're no different.
I'm exhausted because of Nana.
Ah, the Nana also known as Hachi.
I see.
Why won't Nana get it
into her head?
It's been one headache after another
ever since she moved to Tokyo.
It's spring!
Spring has finally come!
After the long wait,
spring has arrived!
Nana says she's on her way
to Tokyo.
- Y-Yes?!
One ticket to Tokyo. One way.
Okay, then. Let's make a toast.
A toast to what?
Well...
To Shoji passing
the University exams!
No, that has nothing to do
with me.
Then, can we at least drink
to this unique moment?
Hey, I like that.
To two girls, the same age,
arriving in Tokyo at the same time
on the same train.
That's quite a coincidence,
don't you think?
And to one more thing.
My name is Nana too, Nana.
Nana!
That's you, right, Nana?!
No way!
What a coincidence!
Who are you?
Am I such a forgettable person?
Sorry, sorry.
Are you all right, Nana-chan?
So you do remember.
Then starting tomorrow,
we're roommates, Nana-chan.
What in the world
were you thinking?!
Why not? Sharing is cool!
Like the foreigners do!
You're so easily fooled by others!
I don't think it's a good idea for you
to move in with a complete stranger.
What were you thinking?
Okay, I got it.
Let's live together.
You wouldn't wanna live with me.
You'll hate it.
I'm always wanting my own way,
and I whine.
You think I don't know that?
I'm used to it, or rather,
I've given up about that.
How dare you!
Just kidding. Let's do it, okay?
Shoji...
Thank you.
That makes me happy.
But I can't!
Those words were all
I needed to hear.
You've chosen me over Sachiko.
Who the heck is Sachiko?
You're just too kind.
If we live together,
I'm going to rely on you
too much all the time.
I don't want to be a burden
anymore than I already am.
Her effort in not wanting to be
a burden is splendid for Nana's standards,
or so I thought at the time.
But it was just a matter of Nana
now relying on someone else instead.
The other Nana.
Although that's also what
you'd expect of her.
Hey Nana, don't you think
these cups are super cute?
You'd never imagine
they're only a dollar each.
Strawberries?
No?
If you want it, go ahead and buy it.
Forget it then.
Why?!
Because. If you're not interested,
I don't want it either.
I wanna use the same things
you do.
I don't care what we use.
Let's just get the shopping done.
But you don't like this, do you?
The strawberries.
Ah, sure I love strawberries...
...to eat.
Then I'm getting these.
I feel for Shoji.
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, you're like...
You know, kinda like a dog.
I am?
You kinda stick around friendly-like
and you're real sincere,
but you need a lot of caring.
Like, not that I mind,
I was thinking about
getting a pet anyway.
Hey Hachi, want me
to buy you a toy?
Hachi? Don't you have
a cuter name for me?
So you guys are Nana and Hachi?
What a combination.
Well, actually my name
is Nana too,
but it's confusing to
have the same name, so Nana...
Was that the reason?
It's because you're like a pet dog.
- Beer. Want some?
- Yay!
No, not "yay!"
You got work, remember?
But I'm thirsty!
No, I'm hungry!
I should have bought something!
By the way, I ate the hamburger.
It was awesome good!
Thanks.
You ate it all by yourself. Not fair!
Well then, write "do not eat"
on the darn thing next time!
Found a cute bakery!
They all look really good!
I don't know which one to get!
You really do have a good nose,
don't you?
Being a dog.
Hey Nana. I've been looking
for this CD.
Would you mind if
we look in that shop?
I don't mind,
but do you have a CD player?
Well, if you wanna use mine,
that's fine by me.
Thank you!
Great, they still had a few left!
The new Trapnest album
went on sale today!
I just love them.
If you'd like,
you should listen to them, too.
They're super cool.
Hang on a minute while I go
and pay for this.
You like this?
I got it from a street vendor.
It's a Sid Vicious pad lock.
And who are you? Nancy?
So what are you going to do
putting a lock on me?
Hey Ren. If I were to die,
would you die with me?
Okay.
The other Nana also seems
to have quite a history.
You got that right.
You know, it's as if the more
she became closer to the other Nana,
the more the distance
between she and Shoji increased.
That's right.
I should've known
there was something going on,
you finding a job so quickly.
Didn't expect such a young boss.
Koichi Sato!
Another burger please.
You got it.
Hey, you know I don't care.
As long as you have a job.
Never mind the reasons
for sticking to it.
Just don't give Shoji
a hard time.
Like last night, too, he got drunk
and started saying stuff.
Saying stuff?!
"Last night, too?"
Is he always saying stuff about me?
Uh...
So actually,
Shoji really doesn't like me!
Because I'm good for nothing!
It's not like that.
Shoji is so in love with you,
he doesn't know what to do
with himself.
You're not going to find a man
like that just anywhere,
you know that?
You gotta take better care
of him, man.
Otherwise that's when
heaven'll get you back.
Work again?
What are you working so much for?
Your parents send you money,
don't they?
Not enough to live on.
When I start school,
I won't have time to work.
I've got to save up while I can.
That's what you say.
You're not spending money
on Sachiko, I hope!
Buying her Louis Vuitton bags
and Prada shoes.
But she really likes these brands.
I'm just kidding!
You're the one that keeps
bringing her up!
I know, but I came all the way
to Tokyo to be with you
and you spend all of
your time working.
I just wish you would make
some time for me.
You're the one
that's not being considerate.
Why should I always have
to adjust to your plans?
I've got to go to work now,
so I'm off.
I just remembered.
You sent me an email yesterday.
Huh?
Well, if it's not important,
never mind.
It's just that I fell asleep
without noticing it came.
Sorry.
Oh yeah, I did send one.
What did I write?
Shoji, I'm on my way home.
Call me when you get off work.
What did I write?
Shoji, I'm on my way home.
Call me when you get off work.
Come on, don't look so gloomy.
Right. Love will always have
its ups and downs.
Oh, by the way, that band
of the other Nana!
They've got
their band members now, don't they?
Y-Yeah, you're right.
That's the flower of the lotus, isn't it?
Why did you choose the lotus?
Actually, it's the ren.
Huh? Sui-ren?
Just plain ren.
You mean lotus.
I said no.
But that's totally a lotus.
Oh shut up!
But it definitely is a lotus.
Why are you being so stubborn?
Who's the stubborn one?!
Who could it be at
this time of night?
Good evening.
Nobu! What the heck
are you doing here?!
Oh wonderful!
The exact response I was expecting!
Good!
Get outta here. Go home!
Nana! Please!
Let me stay here just one night!
No way.
- In fact, I...
- I don't wanna hear it.
I ran away from home.
I told you, I don't wanna hear it!
Nana!
It's for him.
He needs to smarten up!
Now you listen to me, Nobu.
You are to follow your father's footsteps
and run that huge Japanese inn.
Get it through your head.
I didn't choose to be born
into that family.
Quit being a brat about it!
As long as I can play my guitar,
I'm happy.
And I wanna play for you.
Don't make me repeat myself.
Hello Yasu? Do something
about this stupid son, will ya?!
Oh sorry,
but he insisted that he'd go.
What do you mean, "but"?!
What are you gonna do about it?!
There's nothing
I can do about it, Nana.
Nobu's serious.
Why don't you find...
some new band members
and start over?
Oh by the way, did ya listen
to the tape?
Tape?
The new number Nobu wrote.
It's good.
If you sing it, in my opinion,
nobody's got a chance over you guys.
What's this?
Man, only one guest
in the house tonight?
Pretty shabby if you ask me.
Oh, well, I guess that's how it is
when just starting off.
One's better than none.
Good evening. We're Blast.
Welcome to
our very first Tokyo performance.
Good evening...
I'll make this a night
you'll never forget.
Looking for a drummer and bassist!
Wanna join our band and go pro?
Those of you who like the Sex Pistols
Ask the store clerk for details
I just saw the poster out front.
Ow!
Nana!
I'm sorry, did I do something weird?
No, it's not that at all.
You just surprised us.
You're a lot better than we expected.
What do you think, Nana?
This kid's good.
Let's let him in, okay?
So, your name's, Shinichi.
Is that right?
Yes.
Name a guitarist you respect.
Ren Honjo!
There's one thing you have
to promise me first.
If you can't, then you're gonna hafta
decline right this moment.
Shin, do better than Ren.
Yes! Of course,
that's what I intend to do.
Isn't that wonderful?
You found such a great bass player
in such a short time!
And he's cute!
So who do you have to thank?
Hey, who do you have to thank?
You want a prize that badly?
Let's see, then...
Don't litter!
Thank you, Hachiko.
I-I thought you didn't hit
on women!
It's not right!
I have a boyfriend!
What's she getting all uptight
about over a kiss?
It's not like she's a virgin.
Say, shouldn't you call Natsuko
and thank her?
I'll do it later.
Oh, I see. If you call now,
you'd be embarrassed
because you'll cry the moment
you hear mommy's voice.
Well, sure.
You get homesick too,
sometimes, don't you, Nana?
No, since I don't have a home.
There you go, trying to be cool again.
Yasu, Blast is the band you started.
Yeah. I was so worried
I couldn't sleep at night.
Besides, there are law firms
in Tokyo too.
The other Nana began to sing,
and she now has her band members.
I'll bet every day is new
and inspiring for Nana.
Yeah, but she's practically ignored Shoji.
And as if to fill that gap in Shoji's life...
in comes Sachiko.
That's right. The real Sachiko.
My name is Sachiko Kawamura.
It's nice to meet you.
Your first name?
Sachiko.
Do you...
Do you like Louis Vuitton and Prada?
Huh?
I get it.
Well, I was just as surprised.
You have the same employer,
go to the same university,
and enroll at the same faculty.
Guess you pretty well hafta
get along.
Yes, but Sachiko was accepted
on her first try,
so she's two years younger.
Sachiko?
I can't help it.
She asked me to call her that.
There was no reason to refuse.
She's clearly your type.
Petite and fair-skinned.
You can't help it.
But I'm telling you,
it's not like that!
I'm proud that
you're holding back.
She's back.
Here, Shoji. Is coffee okay?
Yeah. Thanks.
Mr. Kyosuke,
which would you prefer?
Just call me Kyosuke, Sa-chan.
That's gonna be trouble.
But even I find her cute.
This is definitely bad.
Oh! My shoe!
Shoji!
Huh?!
Sorry, Shoji. Go on ahead.
You'll miss the last train!
Hey!
You knew you would hafta run
for the last train.
So why did you hafta
wear those shoes?
I did it on purpose.
This seriously doesn't look good.
"I did it on purpose."
It's her secret weapon.
- So, what are you gonna do about it?
- What are you gonna do about it?
So, there you have it.
How did you enjoy
the first episode of "Junko's Room"?
First episode?
You mean there's gonna be
a second episode?
Well, that all depends
on whether or not
the Demon Lord wants it or not.
Bye-bye.
- Good-bye.
I reached into the sky
But I couldn't reach what I wanted
They grew smaller
and disappeared into the sky
Like colorful balloons
I'm alone
My hand had no place to go
And gently you took it
Starless night
I won't look back
at the shadow of my past
I want to feel your warmth
Tears are falling down
Even if I'm unsure I won't let go
Of your hand holding mine