What should I do?
Oh, you don't have
to do anything.
You can go home.
We're done for today.
It looks like our Haruhi-esque activities
are done for the day.
She was able to get her hands
on all of this stuff,
and with the kind of skill that could even
get an experienced negotiator to lean left.
On top of that, it all cost nothing.
In other words, it was free.
They used to say this a lot
in the old days:
"There's nothing scarier than
something that's free."
The problem is that Haruhi
isn't scared at all.
Actually, if there is something that would
scare Haruhi, please, let me know.
DAY BY DAY unzari dayone dakara
Day by day, everything's just so dull
Doudou to kotowacchau
kimi ni narina yo
That's why you need to become
someone that can just reject it all
OH MY BOY kippari shinakya uso ni
Oh my boy, you need to be decisive
Tsukiatterarenai yo semai sekai de
I won't deal with any lies
in this small world
Jibun de mitsuketa MYSELF
suki ni natte touzen
I found myself on my own,
it's natural you'd fall for me
Kudaranai yarikara kette
Kick away the boring ways
of doing things,
subete wa atashi ga kimeru
I'm going to decide everything
I SAY I SAY MY HEAVEN
I say, I say my heaven
SUPER DRIVER tosshin makasete
nantettate zenshin
Super driver, leave everything
to the rush
SUPER DRIVER tosshin makasete
nantettate zenshin
And just keep going forward,
no matter what
Fukanou (DON'T YOU STOP ME)
Tobikoete TAKE IT EASY, GO!
Surpass (Don't you stop me)
The idea of "impossible"
Fukanou (DON'T YOU STOP ME)
Tobikoete TAKE IT EASY, GO!
Take it easy, go!
Daishouri tte doukan
I agree, it's going to be
a huge victory
Mochiron dounatta tte kaikan
Of course, it'll feel pleasant,
no matter what happens
Hanseikai? (GET BACK TO WILD)
Sore yori saa isoide yo
A review meeting? (Get back to wild)
Forget that, now hurry up
Aremo koremo mitaiken
itsudatte muriyari
We haven't tried this or that,
we always do things how we want
Marude marude mikeiken
korekara shimashou
Everything's a new experience,
let's try them out
Aremo koremo mitaiken
itsudatte totsuzen
We haven't tried this or that,
we always do things suddenly
Marude marude mikeiken
sore ga doushita no?
Everything's a new experience,
what about it?
What's all that?
Presents for good little kids?
What, this?
Of course not.
Oh, model guns. I didn't know
you were into those.
I'm not.
These are Haruhi's.
Huh, Suzumiya's...
Well, it must be tough.
By the way.
What?
Well, the school festival
is coming soon, right?
What are you guys going
to do this time?
Why ask me?
I don't think I'd get a serious
response if I asked Suzumiya.
Nagato wouldn't say anything
if I asked her,
and Miss Asahina
won't come near me.
And the other guy...
is kind of creepy.
That's why
I'm asking you.
What, am I the P.R. Rep now,
or am I just a nice guy?
It's the latter, definitely.
I mean, you seem like the kind of
guy that will stick with someone,
even if you know that the path
you're taking is leading to a cliff.
I'm hurt. Fine, I won't tell you
when I find out, then.
Hey!
Even I know that what awaits us at
the end of Haruhi's little path
is going to be pointless.
But it isn't just Haruhi and me
walking down that path.
There are at least three others
coming along with us.
I'm sure two of them would be fine
if left to their own devices,
but Miss Asahina
would be in danger.
For someone from the future,
she sure doesn't seem to be able
to predict any of the problems
that might happen to her.
It's obvious to me that I
have to protect her.
The Sigh of Haruhi Suzumiya II
It's obvious to me that I
have to protect her.
The Sigh of Haruhi Suzumiya II
Hurry up and get undressed!
I'll help.
O-Oh no, please,
don't pull-
Come on!
Come in.
Well?
It really suits her,
oddly enough.
I thought that it was of Caean make
or something.
Hello!
Oh, excuse me.
Oh my. That looks
quite good on you.
You can tell that just
by looking at her.
What I can't tell is why there's
a waitress in here,
since this isn't a cafe
or anything.
Well, you see...
Mikuru is going to wear
this costume in the movie!
Is her usual maid outfit
not good enough?
Of course not.
A maid is a person that gives private service
to someone in a mansion somewhere.
But waitresses
are different.
They work at restaurants where they
provide their services to the public.
That's no reason to put
Miss Asahina in this outfit.
Never mind the details! This is
just a question of atmosphere.
And it's fine
with me!
Even if it's fine with you,
is it fine with Miss Asahina?
Umm...
T-This feels like
it's a bit small for me...
S-So, you see...
It's all right! This is just right.
It's like a perfect fit.
It's no use.
She's made her decision.
In other words, this is
our movie's concept!
I decided to dedicate myself
to entertainment
as the representative director
for the SOS Brigade!
Just watch! We'll get a standing ovation,
we'll leave no one in their seats!
Director
Just watch! We'll get a standing ovation,
we'll leave no one in their seats!
Yuki! You understand, don't you!
That's it!
I don't know if
that's "it."
It looks like her costume for
her class's fortune telling.
Based on the answers Nagato gave
to Haruhi's rapid-fire questions,
that seems to be
the case.
In any case, what was she up to,
walking here like that?
That costume is perfect for
the role I have in mind.
What do you mean, perfect?
This!
Is... is this my fault?
Mikuru - Fighting waitress from the future
Koizumi - Teenage esper
Yuki - Evil alien
Is... is this my fault?
Mikuru - Fighting waitress from the future
Koizumi - Teenage esper
Yuki - Evil alien
How can I put this?
It's really the kind of casting I'd
expect from you, Miss Suzumiya.
It's wonderful.
Don't smile at me.
I'll turn to stone.
I'm sorry...
Okay, Kyon! Get those guns ready
to be used by the end of the day.
We're going to start
shooting tomorrow, after all.
Oh, you have to learn how to
handle a camera, got it?
Do you think we're going to have
any particular problems?
Have we ever NOT had any problems
with anything she's done?
Don't make me laugh.
Well, it's not really a laughing matter,
but it's not a reason to despair, either.
How do you
know that?
Because those are
movie roles.
There's no way that Miss Suzumiya actually
believes that I'm a teenage esper.
The "Itsuki Koizumi" that I'm set to
play in the fiction of the movie
is an esper, that's all.
No one actually mixes up an actor with the
character they play in a movie, right?
Even if there are people who do,
Miss Suzumiya is not one of them.
That still doesn't
make me feel better.
There's no proof that what
you're saying is true.
If she was the kind of person that
would mix up the real world with fiction,
then our world would already be
a much more fantastic place.
I've said this before,
but Miss Suzumiya
actually has a fairly realistic
way of thinking.
I know that. I've been pulled
into numerous odd situations
because her realistic way of thinking sort
of ambles into her godlike existence.
Brigade leader
On top of that, Haruhi doesn't
know she's doing it.
We can't show Miss Suzumiya
any proof of this, of course.
There might come a time where we
have to, but this is not that time.
Thankfully, Miss Asahina and
Miss Nagato are in agreement with us.
I'd be okay if things stayed
this way forever, though.
So would I. I don't want to
see the world go to pieces.
I think you should be more worried
about yourself than the world.
There are replacements for
myself and Miss Nagato,
but there's no
understudy for you.
For the school festival
Practice file 3
Feh, what's the big deal about the
school festival? It pisses me off.
Why?
I'm not having
any fun at all,
so the people who are having fun
are a real eyesore.
Especially couples, they fill me
with "murderous intent".
Isn't that just you
resenting them?
And what's with our class?
A survey? Hah! How stupid.
Then you should have
come up with an idea.
If you had, then maybe Haruhi wouldn't
have come up with this movie idea.
As if. There's no way I'd let them
push me into doing more.
That's true. If only
Miss Asakura were still here.
It really sucked to have a
double A-plus class girl leave.
I wonder if they'd let me
change classes now.
Which class would you want to go to?
Maybe Miss Nagato's class?
Oh yeah, I saw her walking around in
some kind of magician outfit yesterday.
What was that
all about?
Who knows?
I sure don't.
Hm, when was it that I saw you and Nagato
in the classroom in each other's arms?
Well, you see...
I know, it was something
Suzumiya cooked up, right?
What? Y-Yeah...
This was an attempt to freak me out, right?
Nice try, but no dice.
Taniguchi misunderstanding what happened
is a load off of my shoulders...
This was an attempt to freak me out, right?
Nice try, but no dice.
Thanks, Taniguchi.
Your stupidity will save the world.
Man, but this
is boring.
Okay, everyone! We're heading
to the first location!
This is sudden.
I looked for a good place
around the school,
but it looks like we have no choice
but to go someone else nearby.
Mikuru, get ready.
A-Am I going, too?
Of course. We can't do anything
without the lead.
B-But... in this outfit?
Yup, that's right.
C-Could I at least wear
a jacket over this?
No! It's because you think you're
embarrassed that you get all nervous.
At this rate, we'll never be able
to get a Golden Globe!
Weren't we trying to get "best of the
festival" for the school festival?
Oh, yeah, Yuki!
Take this!
I've changed your role, so now
you're an evil alien witch!
And she's already screwing
with the script!
Well, it is true that Nagato's powers
seem like magic.
Come on, Kyon,
get the camera ready!
Okay, let's get going!
All together!
It looks like she's serious.
What the?
Hey, Haruhi.
You don't intend to make these two get
on the train in these outfits, do you?
- Is there a problem with that?
- Of course there is!
Why? They might get arrested
if they were buck naked,
but they're
wearing clothes, right?
Oh, would the bunny girl outfit
have been better?
You should have
said so earlier.
I don't think that's something that
someone who went to the trouble
of getting a waitress outfit
should be saying!
Wait, didn't you say that her being a waitress
was part of the movie's concept?
What's most important
right now is adaptability.
That's how all living things on the
Earth have managed to evolve, right?
If you just idly stand by, you're
going to get left behind!
If the environment
was sentient,
then Haruhi would have been thrown
out of the atmosphere by now.
Oh, the train's here!
Come on, Mikuru!
Get going already!
We're here,
as promised!
Oh, good work.
Ah, is this the girl from the day before
yesterday? I didn't recognize her.
Okay, I'm counting
on you.
Roger that!
All right, everyone.
We're going to have a quick meeting,
so gather around.
We're going to be shooting
a commercial!
What?
Ohmori Electronics
T-This shop is...
The manager is a really good person.
And he's a nice guy.
Umm... They've been around since
current owner Eijirou's grandfather.
You can find anything from batteries
to refrigerators here.
Umm... well...
In any case, please come by
Ohmori Electronics!
Okay, cut!
Hmm, I just don't feel
the emotion...
I wonder why that is...
Mama, what's that?
Shh, you mustn't look.
I've got it!
For the love of God, please
don't "get" anything else!
It doesn't make sense for a waitress
to be at an electronics store.
That's "it"!?
Koizumi, hand me
the small bag over there!
Yes, ma'am.
"Let me have a camera, and I'll put a
commercial for your store in my movie."
"Sure thing."
That's probably the conversation Haruhi
had with the owner in five seconds.
Mikuru, come here
a second.
Oh my. It doesn't look like I'll
have any lines in this part.
Actually, I'm one of the actors in
my class's stage production, too.
I'm having quite a hard time
remembering all of the lines.
Oh really.
I'd prefer it if my role for this
was light on lines, but...
How about if you take
the lead role?
Haruhi's the one controlling
the casting.
Ask her if you want
to switch.
Do you really think that I could do
something as frightening as that?
These are Miss Suzumiya's
orders after all,
and I'd rather not imagine what would
await me if I disobeyed them.
I'd rather not, either. That's why
I'm sitting here as the cameraman.
And we're back!
It's Miss Asahina's first costume
from a while back.
A perfect bunny girl.
Oh yeah, that was over
half a year ago.
Now that I think about it,
quite a bit happened then.
Right now,
they're fond memories...
As if!
Okay, this is perfect!
A bunny girl really is the best fit
for introducing a product.
Okay, we're going to take it
from the top!
Kyon, get the
camera ready!
All right,
this is take two!
And so, the commercial for the
electronics store was finished.
There's one thing you need
to remember, though.
There was one other sponsor
that we visited last time.
Yamatsuchi Model Shop
All right.
Okay then, Mikuru.
Do it just like you did
at the other store!
There were no problems
that time!
Like hell there weren't.
Okay, action!
T-This model shop opened
for business last year
after Mr. Keiji Yamatsuchi, age 28,
left his corporate job.
It's like his hobbies took over
his actions, and he just did it.
And as many thought,
sales haven't met expectations...
The first-half earnings this year
are down 80% from last year...
So shop as much
as you can, everyone!
You want me
to hold it?
D-Don't shoot while pointing
at people!
Hold off by shooting things
like empty cans!
You want me
to shoot?
All right, cut!
Today's filming
was only so-so.
But tomorrow we're going to start
shooting the movie itself.
We've already added fifteen minutes
to the movie with the commercials.
How long is the actual movie
going to be?
Well, we'll just shoot as much as
we can and edit it down later.
These days, it's a snap
with a computer.
And who's going to be doing
the snapping?
I've got the feeling that "editor" was
one of the things listed under my jobs.
Tomorrow's Saturday,
and a day off from school,
so I want everyone
to show up!
Be at Kitaguchi Station
at nine o'clock!
Hey, Haruhi. Can't you do something
about Miss Asahina's outfit?
There has to be a more appropriate
outfit for someone who fights.
You know, like a plug suit
or a stealth suit or something.
Tsk tsk.
If she wore something like that,
there'd be no unpredictability.
The audience will be surprised
and go "whoa!"
Because it's a waitress
that's fighting.
Being able to grab the
audience is vital!
That's the concept,
you know!
I wonder if she understands the
meaning of the word "concept."
Well, never mind that, then.
Why is she here from the future?
Well, that is, you know.
Umm, the character doesn't have
to be from the future, right?
It's all right!
We'll figure that out
when the time comes!
And if we can't think of something,
then we'll just ignore it!
As long as it's amusing,
it's fine!
That's only if it's
amusing though, right?
It's not much good if only the
director finds it amusing!
Are you trying to get the Golden
Raspberry award for non-pros?
What are you talking about?
There's only one thing we're going for.
That's the "best of the festival"
for the school festival!
And if we can,
the Golden Globe, too!
All right, then. At least show me
the script. How's it coming along?
No problem!
It's all up here. The script and the
storyboards are all ready to go!
You don't have to think
about a thing.
Well, that's just great.
You don't need to think
about anything, either.
You just need to sit and
stare out the window.
As long as you had a pleasant look on your
face, you'd be as cute as Miss Asahina.
What?
Nothing.
Okay, everyone.
We're going to get fired up!
You need to be idealistic if you
want to capture any glory.
When you free yourself of your inhibitions,
the latent abilities
within you will awaken,
revealing unimaginable powers!
This isn't a counterattack like you'd
see in a battle manga, you know...
- It's a balloon!
- Oh, you're right.
The next morning.
As of today, we've fallen
into a strange situation.
No, how can I
put this?
What did Haruhi say?
Something like,
Mommy, how far will the balloon go?
Huh? Huh?
What did Haruhi say?
Something like,
Mommy, how far will the balloon go?
Huh? Huh?
"When you free yourself of your
inhibitions, the latent abilities
Well, pretty far.
"When you free yourself of your
inhibitions, the latent abilities
Well, pretty far.
Within you will awaken,
revealing unimaginable powers!"
Huh? Pretty far?
But Haruhi, the one gaining
powers won't be you.
And you won't
even know it.
You're late!
It's not even nine yet.
You're still last. As punishment,
you're buying us lunch.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, I'll cover the bus fare!
It's part of our necessary expenses!
Thanks.
Oh yeah!
I need to put this on...
Why are you wearing
your school uniform?
She told me to
wear it yesterday.
It's because I'm playing a high school
student who has psychic powers.
So you're just
playing yourself.
All right, this works!
Okay, the bus stop
is this way!
Super Director
Okay, the bus stop
is this way!
Super Director
Come on, Kyon,
hurry up!
After thirty minutes of
being shaken by the bus
and thirty minutes
of walking,
we ended up in a place
that would make you ask,
"Why did we come to a place
no one wants to come to?"
Man, it's hot...
Umm...
Would you like some of mine?
If you don't mind that it's half-drunk...
Half-drunk?
Oh, thank you.
Take care of that later!
You too, Mikuru!
There's no time to give our gofer
a drink break!
Come on, we're going to
start shooting. Get changed!
But...
It's fine! If you go far enough in,
you won't run into anyone!
The half-drunk...
- Don't peek.
- Right.
Ta-dah!
It's a color contact.
Having different colored eyes
is pretty important, you know!
One differently colored eye will
increase the sense of mystery!
It's symbolic!
And there's a secret
in this blue eye of hers!
Well, it'd make no sense for her to
just have a differently colored eye.
So? What's the secret?
It's still a secret!
Come on, Mikuru, how long are
you going to loaf about?
Hey! Mikuru!
Stop being so embarrassed!
You just need to get
into your character!
Okay, try running
one more time.
It looks like this is our opening
sequence, worthy of celebration.
I thought that she'd at least
write a script or something,
but Haruhi simply declared
that there wasn't one.
We'd be in big trouble if I wrote
it down and it got leaked.
That's the reason
she gave.
I wonder when this turned
into a Hong Kong flick.
Okay! Once more, like you
did the third time!
Okay, next up is the fight scene
between Mikuru and Yuki!
Mikuru, shoot at Yuki
with all you've got!
But didn't they say to not
point these at people?
It's all right. There's no
way you'll hit her, Mikuru!
And if it looks like she'd get hit,
Yuki will be able to dodge it.
It's all right.
Fire.
See? She said it's all right!
Shoot her up!
Oh yeah, don't fire them at the
same time, but one after the other!
That's one of the basics
of two-gun fighting!
Yeah. I guess
this works.
Hey, Haruhi. How is this a movie?
I have no idea what's going on.
That's fine! We'll just cut and paste it
together during editing.
And who's going to do that?
That cutting and pasting?
At least put in
some dialog.
It's fine! If we have to, we'll mute the
sound and record the dialog afterwards!
We have to put in sound effects
and background music, anyways!
You don't have to think
too hard about this!
Even if we wanted to,
the story is only in your head,
so there's nothing for us
to think about.
Sora kara ochite kitanda
It fell from the sky
Subete no negai wo nosete
With all of the wishes
that were made upon it
Hitotsu no hoshi niwa
chotto omokatta kana
Maybe it was a little too heavy
for a single star
Yappari nanika henda yo
Something just doesn't
seem right
Kokoro no kimi ga kieta
The image of you in my mind
has vanished
Tashika ni oboeteru tte
ieruno kai?
Can I say that I
remember you clearly?
Tomare!
Stop!
Kako wa jibun no mono
The past belongs to me
Touzen daretomo torikaetakunai
Of course I don't want to trade it
with anyone else
Nazenara
That's because
Basudei datta watashitachi niwa
It was my birthday,
and when we saw each other
Deai ga umareta toki ni
We could see the first dream
Hajimete no yume ga mieru
That we had
when we were born
Doushiyouka tte
nayanda koto mo
Worrying about
"what do I do?"
Ima omoeba waraeru hodo
datta yo ne
Is laughable when I
think about it now
Mou wasureteta
I've already forgotten it
Kimi wo sagasou
Let's search for you