...but Kumamoto still has a chance
if they can hold out here.
The passionate voices cheering from the
third base bleachers have not died down.
There's Suzuki, they need him to do
his best, don't they, Mr. Kiru?
Something seems off.
That's true.
It just somehow felt
that way.
After all, you never know how a match
is going to turn out. They still have hope.
It just somehow felt
that way.
After all, you never know how a match
is going to turn out. They still have hope.
I had absolutely no interest in the
prefectural baseball game on TV,
Right.
I had absolutely no interest in the
prefectural baseball game on TV,
Next, stepping up to the batter's box we
have number four, Kashima, a senior.
But I kind of ended up
rooting for the losing side.
Next, stepping up to the batter's box we
have number four, Kashima, a senior.
Once I did, I kind of got the feeling that
Haruhi was going to start something.
After last year's summer tournament, he
was chosen for the team that went to Cuba.
Once I did, I kind of got the feeling that
Haruhi was going to start something.
After last year's summer tournament, he
was chosen for the team that went to Cuba.
In the fourth inning,
he hit a three-run home run.
Incoming call: Haruhi Suzumiya
In the fourth inning,
he hit a three-run home run.
What does she want?
Kyon, the phone's ringing.
I know, you don't
have to tell me.
You're not doing
anything today, right?
And there's Suzuki
with a big windup...
We're all meeting at exactly
two o'clock in front of the station.
Be sure to show up.
And the first pitch is a strike.
No problems there.
Be sure to show up.
And the first pitch is a strike.
No problems there.
I didn't even say anything...
That was a good pitch.
That was a strong, straight pitch,
thrown a little high and inside.
What?
That was a strong, straight pitch,
thrown a little high and inside.
I forgot to mention this - bring
a swimsuit and plenty of money.
Perhaps he feels like
he's got nothing left to lose.
I forgot to mention this - bring
a swimsuit and plenty of money.
We don't know that yet.
And be sure to bring your bike.
That's all, over and out!
I had the feeling that I knew
what Haruhi was going to say.
He winds up for
the second pitch...
I had the feeling that I knew
what Haruhi was going to say.
It's a hit! And it's a big one!
It's headed for left field...
I had the feeling that I knew
what Haruhi was going to say.
It's a hit! And it's a big one!
It's headed for left field...
No, not quite.
It's a hit! And it's a big one!
It's headed for left field...
To be precise, it felt like this exact
same conversation had happened before.
And it's good!
It's a single-run home run!
To be precise, it felt like this exact
same conversation had happened before.
And it's good!
It's a single-run home run!
I guess it's what you
would call deja vu.
Jyonan has gotten their eighth run!
This gives them yet another point.
I guess it's what you
would call deja vu.
Jyonan has gotten their eighth run!
This gives them yet another point.
Kashima is slowly rounding
third base.
Summer's almost over.
DAY BY DAY unzari dayone dakara
Day by day, everything's just so dull
Doudou to kotowacchau
kimi ni narina yo
That's why you need to become
someone that can just reject it all
OH MY BOY kippari shinakya uso ni
Oh my boy, you need to be decisive
Tsukiatterarenai yo semai sekai de
I won't deal with any lies
in this small world
Jibun de mitsuketa MYSELF
suki ni natte touzen
I found myself on my own,
it's natural you'd fall for me
Kudaranai yarikara kette
Kick away the boring ways
of doing things,
subete wa atashi ga kimeru
I'm going to decide everything
I SAY I SAY MY HEAVEN
I say, I say my heaven
SUPER DRIVER tosshin makasete
nantettate zenshin
Super driver, leave everything
to the rush
SUPER DRIVER tosshin makasete
nantettate zenshin
And just keep going forward,
no matter what
Fukanou (DON'T YOU STOP ME)
Tobikoete TAKE IT EASY, GO!
Surpass (Don't you stop me)
The idea of "impossible"
Fukanou (DON'T YOU STOP ME)
Tobikoete TAKE IT EASY, GO!
Take it easy, go!
Daishouri tte doukan
I agree, it's going to be
a huge victory
Mochiron dounatta tte kaikan
Of course, it'll feel pleasant,
no matter what happens
Hanseikai? (GET BACK TO WILD)
Sore yori saa isoide yo
A review meeting? (Get back to wild)
Forget that, now hurry up
Aremo koremo mitaiken
itsudatte muriyari
We haven't tried this or that,
we always do things how we want
Marude marude mikeiken
korekara shimashou
Everything's a new experience,
let's try them out
Aremo koremo mitaiken
itsudatte totsuzen
We haven't tried this or that,
we always do things suddenly
Marude marude mikeiken
sore ga doushita no?
Everything's a new experience,
what about it?
Endless Eight
You're late, Kyon!
Show some more motivation!
Yeah, yeah.
I came just for you.
Oh, thank you.
Okay, we're all here,
so let's go.
Go where?
To the public swimming pool,
of course!
Well, I guess that makes sense
considering what I brought.
We have to do summer vacation-y things
during our summer vacation!
We can never get back
the time that we've lost!
And so we're going to do
them now, during this,
our one and only summer
as tenth graders.
Okay, Kyon and Koizumi,
we're counting on you
until we get to the pool.
I'd rather not ask this,
but counting on us for what?
We're going
on your bikes!
Oh, the scent of chlorine.
This really makes it feel like a pool!
Woo hoo!
No diving
It's dangerous
Woo hoo!
No diving
It's dangerous
Restrain thyself. Canst thou
not read the "no diving" signs?
Hurry up and get in!
The water's warm so it feels fine!
In you go!
That looks like fun.
She has some rather normal ways of
enjoying her time, don't you think?
I don't think I can say that inviting
someone to do something
by calling them out of the blue,
and only giving a general idea
of what's going to happen
as "normal".
Well, there is the saying,
"Strike while the iron is hot."
Yeah, but when she
strikes something,
we've never gotten anything
but bad luck.
Even so, this is more than
peaceful enough.
Miss Suzumiya, laughing and having
a good time like that,
isn't likely to shake up
the world, after all.
What's wrong?
It's nothing. It's probably
just my imagination.
Because so much has happened
since the beginning of spring,
I've become
a little paranoid.
Almost! Let's go
one more time!
Delicious.
So strawberry and delicious!
Jeez.
I think it would be better to call this place
a communal pool than a public pool.
I wonder why Haruhi
chose this place.
There it is again,
that strange sensation.
It feels like I've seen
this scene once before.
Where Nagato kind of looks
like she's bored...
Kyon!
Right, and then Haruhi
says this...
"These two are my
brigade members."
"They'll do anything you ask,
so ask for anything you want!"
Okay!
Okay, let's have some fun!
We're going to play water soccer.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, deja vu isn't
all that uncommon.
I've been thinking about how we should
spend our summer vacation.
What do you think?
What is this
supposed to be?
Summer outing, Bon festival,
part-time job, batting center...
What is this
supposed to be?
Summer outing, Bon festival,
part-time job, batting center...
It's a schedule of how we'll spend the
rest of our short summer vacation.
- A schedule for who?
- For us!
I realized that we only have two weeks
of summer vacation left.
That fact
blew me away.
We still have so much left to do, but
we've only got this much time left!
We're going to pick up
the pace!
All this, in just
two weeks?
Is there anything else
you want to do, Mikuru?
Umm... I'd like to try
goldfish scooping.
Okay!
Goldfish scooping...
Pardon me
for a moment.
Thank you.
We're starting tomorrow!
Is there a place nearby
having a Bon festival?
A fireworks show works, too.
At least try to find
this stuff out first.
I'll check around. I'll contact you
when I find out.
Okay, I'll leave it
to you, Koizumi.
All right, then,
we're done for today!
Nagato.
Umm... no, it's
nothing important.
How have you been?
Everything fine?
Fine.
That's good to hear.
Right.
Umm...
Sorry for stopping you.
You can go now.
What the heck?
Why did I talk to her?
Koizumi was able to suddenly find a place
that was holding a Bon festival the next day.
Wow, so this one of this era's
summer attractions.
I guess it makes sense for there
to be this many people.
Mikuru! They have goldfish scooping,
just like you wanted!
All the fish you can catch,
and all the scoops you can break!
You're not supposed
to break them.
You're interested
in that stuff?
- Which one?
- It's all right.
- This one.
- Thanks, that'll be 800 yen.
I kind of got the feeling that
Nagato had been helping us out,
Thank you much.
I kind of got the feeling that
Nagato had been helping us out,
so I thought it would be appropriate
for me to at least buy her that, but...
Wow, what a haul!
But I don't need so many,
so I just kept one for each of us.
Now then, next up
is fireworks!
Let's launch some fireworks
to end the day!
Don't you understand the
concept of getting tired?
Well, I guess you could say that
one of Haruhi's good points
is that she's healthy and
got a lot of stamina.
Jeez, she's always
so reckless!
It was summer,
and summer vacation.
That's why I wanted to forget about it, but
there was one thing lingering in my mind.
Tomorrow we'll be
catching bugs!
Haruhi. It's fine to
want to play around,
but are you finished with
your summer homework?
What? You can finish homework
like that in just three days.
Three days!?
You get that stuff out of the way so you can
have fun without having to worry about it.
That's how you enjoy
your summer vacation.
Why is she
so smart?
It seems like the guys up in
heaven that were divvying up
the stats for us
were pretty unfair.
Everyone, we'll be
catching bugs tomorrow!
Whoever catches
the most bugs...
Okay, they'll get to be the
brigade leader for a day!
There's a title
I don't want at all.
That sounds interesting.
Are any bugs okay?
Hmm... only cicadas!
That's it, this will be the SOS Brigade's
Cicada Capturing Competition!
The next day was yet again
a beautiful day.
Come back here, cicada!
The next day was yet again
a beautiful day.
And so, as we expected,
or something to that effect,
the winner ended up
being Haruhi.
A catch and release attitude
is important, right?
If we let them go, then they
might come back to repay us.
If someone went back to the person that
caught them and then just let them go,
then I'd say they really were
about as smart as a bug.
There you go! Go back
to the mountains!
W-Welcome!
The next day, we had a part-time job that
our brigade leader had procured for us.
Here you are.
Here...
- Can I have one?
- Here you go.
Thanks!
Wearing a costume in heat like this isn't
a job, it's an endurance competition.
I said, our payment
is Mikuru's costume.
I've wanted this
for a while.
The owner said that he'd give it to us
for Mikuru's sake.
We worked, sweat pouring down
our foreheads, for that?
Let's hang this frog up in
the clubroom as a memento.
Mikuru, you can wear it whenever
you want. You have my permission!
Damn it...
Hello?
Kyon...
Hello? Miss Asahina?
Yes, it's me...
Something... very not good has...
At this rate, I...
- Is this really Miss Asahina?
- Oh, hello, this is Koizumi.
Why are you with
Miss Asahina at this hour?
Certain circumstances came up.
Quite alarming ones, at that.
We've got an
emergency situation.
Sorry to call you out
so late at night.
What in the world happened, Miss Asahina?
I'm going to kill you, Koizumi.
Kyon...
I... can't go back
to the future...
Well... because of "classified information",
I'm always contacting the future
and "classified information"-ing,
but I hadn't received any
"classified information"
for about a week or so,
and I thought, "that's strange."
And so I
"classified information"...
I was so surprised, I tried
to "classified information",
but it was completely
"classified information".
Oh, what do I do?
Could it be that your
"classified information"s
are things that cannot
be said on television?
In other words,
this is what's going on.
We are going through an eternal loop
of the same time period.
To be precise, we've been repeating
the time from August 17th to the 31 st.
This world has lost all time
after September 1 st.
It's natural that Miss Asahina
cannot go back to the future.
The future itself
no longer exists.
What's natural about there being
no future? Who'd believe it?
We'd like for you
to believe it.
They say that the believers
will be saved,
but I've yet to be saved from
a hardship, even once.
So, what's the culprit?
You really don't know?
I don't want to.
I would guess
Miss Suzumiya.
I'm sure she doesn't realize it,
but I would guess that
somewhere inside of her is a desire
to not let summer vacation end.
What the heck? Do you mean she
feels regret over something?
That's what I believe.
Perhaps she feels that there's something
left that she wants to do
during our
summer vacation?
Man, the hopeless situations she causes
unfold on a galactic scale.
Well, with this, we've finally
been able to solve
the recent mysterious and frequent
feelings of deja vu.
You've been having them, too?
Then is it possible that other people...
It doesn't
seem that way.
It appears that the people who
are closest to Miss Suzumiya
are able to sense
this strangeness.
However, I believe that there is one person
who remembers everything,
more than the deja vu
that we do.
And who would that be?
I think you already know.
- Is that right?
- It is.
- You remember all of it?
- Right.
So, how many times have we repeated
all of this, this time?
This is the 15,532nd time.
15,532?
Nagato, what are
you saying?
- Are you serious?
- I am.
You're saying that we've done the
exact same things that many times?
They're not all guaranteed
to happen.
Out of 15,532 repetitions,
there are two occasions,
#2,391 and #11,054, where we
did not go to a Bon festival.
A pattern where we did
go to a Bon festival,
but did not go to a goldfish
scooping stand, occurred 437 times.
We've had a part-time job
9,056 times,
and when we did, there were
six different kinds of jobs.
In addition to handing out balloons,
we also worked as movers,
cashiers, we handed out flyers,
call center...
No! That's enough...
This is the 15,532nd time,
that's what Nagato said.
Times two weeks, hmm,
that's around 595 years.
She alone has memories
of all that time,
repeating it all
over and over...
Nagato, how must it feel to experience that
same period of time over and over again?
I've heard yet another
crazy story.
The next day
we went stargazing.
The location was
Nagato's apartment.
Haruhi was looking through
the telescope at first, but...
Exactly what does she
want to do?
Now what could
that be?
If we could figure that out,
this would all be solved...
How about trying
this out?
Give Miss Suzumiya a sudden
embrace from behind
then whisper "I love you"
into her ear.
And who would
be doing that?
Is there anyone else who could
fill the role other than you?
It's my turn!
I activate The Veto.
All right, how about
if I do it?
I'm kidding. I'm lacking a certain
something for the role.
And all that would do is cause unnecessary
confusion in Miss Suzumiya.
We continued to run through a torrent
of summer vacation events.
We went to a real
fireworks show,
and we even took part in
a goby fishing tournament.
We also had a test of courage,
watched some movies,
went to the beach, went bowling,
and even sang karaoke.
We were always
doing something.
Of course, I knew that this wasn't
going to satisfy Haruhi.
Even so, there wasn't anything
I could do about it,
and the last days of our summer
vacation ticked away.
And so we ended up
at August 30th...
With this, we've finished
everything on our list.
I wonder if this
was good enough.
But, hmm, well...
I guess this works.
Hey, is there anything else
you want to do?
That's fine, then.
We were able to do a lot this summer,
so that's enough, right?
No, it's not.
You're still not satisfied.
Okay, we're done
for today.
I had tomorrow set aside just in case,
but you can just take the day off.
Let's meet again in the clubroom
the day after tomorrow.
W-Wait, Haruhi...
T-There it is again! And it's
stronger than ever before!
It's proof that we've done all this
tens of thousands of times.
I can't let Haruhi leave.
If she goes, we'll end up repeating
these past two weeks again.
But what should
I do?
There must have been a hint
somewhere in what Haruhi said.
What? What?
What?
Remember.
You've got to remember.
It's something I'm worried about,
but I'm putting off...
If I don't do something, she'll go home.
I can't let it happen.
If I do, nothing
will change.
What have we done
up to this point?
What didn't we do?
There's no time to think. It doesn't
matter if it doesn't work,
just say something,
anything!
I still have something
I want to do!
That's right, homework!
What are you
talking about?
I haven't done a single bit
of my summer homework.
Until I do, my summer
isn't over!
Are you stupid
or something?
Koizumi!
Are you finished yet?
No, I'm only halfway done because
we were rushing around so much.
Then let's work
on it together.
Nagato, you come over, too.
You're still not done yet, right?
Miss Asahina, please come, too.
What? But where?
Let's do this
at my house.
Bring all of your notebooks and textbooks,
and let's do it all together.
We're going to finish off
all of our summer activities.
Nagato, Koizumi, let me copy
the stuff you've finished.
Right.
All right, we're starting
tomorrow morning.
We're going to do what
we can in one day!
Wait right there.
Don't you just make
a decision like that!
I'm the leader. At times like this,
you need to ask my opinion first.
Kyon, acting without my permission
is against the rules!
I'm going too!
It looks like I hit
the jackpot.
Miss Suzumiya is a smart
and talented person.
She's probably always
been that way.
So she probably never
considered the idea
that summer homework
could be a burden.
And so she probably never had to
divide work up with her friends.
It was the first day of the term,
so I could have gone home,
but I ended up
coming here,
and so here I sit with Koizumi,
who showed up in the same way.
Frighteningly, yet importantly,
Nagato wasn't there.
You couldn't see it on her face,
but she might have been exhausted.
The idea that we experienced the latter half
of August tens of thousands of times
feels like it was all
made up.
I don't blame you
for feeling that way.
The "us" of here and now
don't share any memories
with the "us" that experienced the
sequence of the previous 15,531 times.
This is because the
15,532nd time around,
we were able to return to
the normal flow of time.
How about a game
of poker?
Sure thing. I don't have
any money, though.
Then we'll play
for fun.
But I did get
a hint.
That repeated deja vu.
Especially the last one,
it might have been sent from the
previous versions of ourselves.
I can be here, now,
thanks to the "us" that went through
those two weeks beforehand.
If I don't think of it
that way,
then it would be like me saying that all
of the summers that they went through,
with Haruhi treating them like they
didn't exist, were for nothing.
- Want any new cards?
- Nope.
Me either.
If I had the chance
to redo this day...
I'd like to remember to play
this hand for money.