I felt like such a fool
for not noticing until now.
For example, the number of piercings
they each had, and the way they talked.
Nana and Ren were so much alike.
It gave me a sense of
the deep history they had together.
When I was darkness at that time
With trembling lips
In a corner of a room I cry
The more I struggle
The more this wound deepens
The broken promise hurt me
Nobody can save me
God, I have only one request
Stop tearing apart my love
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Sorrow tumbling down is your song
All alone with nowhere to go in my life
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Oh baby, help me from frozen pain
With your smile, your eyes,
and sing me, just for me
I wanna need your love
I'm a broken rose
"What is that padlock
you're always wearing?"
"I can't take it off because
I lost the key", he says.
I'm wondering, maybe Nana
has the key to Ren's padlock.
Ever since I found out that Ren
of Trapnest is Nana's ex-boyfriend,
I took out all the music magazines
and fan-club notices I had kept
and read them thoroughly,
over and over.
I was stunned to realize
how I had just been
skimming through the articles
until now.
I'm clearly the type who only cares
to read what I'm interested in.
In fact, right now, my mind is
full of Nana and Ren,
and I can barely think of anything else.
Although I'm also purposely making
an effort not to think of anything else.
The other thing is,
if I should find a new boyfriend,
I'm sure I'll stop thinking about Shoji.
It would be nice
for such a day to come soon.
Hey, are you ready?
Shall we get going?
Mhm.
Hey... hey, Nana.
Aren't you getting changed?
Why?
Are you going to the live concert
dressed like that?
It's part of our overnight journey.
The more comfortable the outfit,
the better, right?
Say, aren't these nice?
Y-Yes, but we've been
looking forward to this concert
so shouldn't we dress up a bit?
You're meeting Ren
for the first time in two years!
You're the one who's been
looking forward to this.
Why should I also hafta dress up?
It's only a Trapnest concert.
First of all,
if she wears those sunglasses,
Ren might not recognize her.
Is she doing this on purpose?
Damn, there are a ton of things
I want to ask and say to her.
Is this ok?
However, right now my top priority
is getting Nana to the concert.
I should be careful
not to be too demanding.
Want another sugar for yours?
I won't be using any.
- N-No, I'm fine.
- Okay.
The distance between Nana and Ren
is getting shorter and shorter.
- I can't wait to see them.
- Huh?!
Your family.
Especially Natsuko.
I'm a big fan of hers.
I'm not too comfortable about
having you meet them.
My parents are no more than your
typical countryside man and woman.
My younger sister still
wears that dark makeup...
And my elder sister...
Nana!
She's gained even more weight.
They're identical.
Sorry for making you go through
the trouble of picking us up.
"Go through the trouble"?
Don't mention it. My workplace is
closed today, so I was available.
In this area you cannot
get anywhere without a car.
By the way, Nao, could you
drive us to the concert?
Sure. Where is it?
At the Idea Hall. I wanna
be there around six.
Then we should leave at around 5:30.
Yes! Thank you!
I love you, Nao!
Nana, look!
It's my old specialty college!
That brings back memories.
Brings back memories?
But you commuted there
until only a year ago, right?
Oh right. But it seems like
ten years ago.
What are you saying?
Art school, right? Was it fun?
Mhm. I knew I didn't have
much talent in that area,
but everyday was so much fun.
With Jun-chan and Kyosuke and...
We hung out together, everyday.
Oh, Nana. You know,
Nami was telling me...
Are you really
living with your boyfriend?
It's that guy, right?
The guy who often came by the house
while you were in art school... Shoji.
- No!
- I believe you're misunderstanding.
I am Nana's roommate.
Oh? Really?
You know, why don't you all come
and visit us sometime?
If you see, you'll understand.
What? That Nami, going around
spreading rumors again.
She's gotta be more careful.
I'm glad Nana's with me.
This place has too many memories
for me to visit alone.
We're back! Mom! Nana's here!
Wow, what a grand house!
You're quite the princess.
Not really. This is normal.
Land is really cheap around here.
Welcome home, Nana!
- Black!
- Did you get me a gift? A present?
Like a Louis Vuitton bag?
Tokyo is not a foreign country,
you know!
Hey! Nami, behave yourself
in front of our guest.
Hello, I'm Nana's mother.
You may find it hard to relax here,
but please make yourself at home.
Pleased to meet you. I'm Nana Osaki.
Thank you for the hospitality.
Nana?
That's right. We have the same name.
But Nana's name is written
in katakana characters.
Isn't she totally pretty?
It's amazing how different two people
with the same name can be.
Mom!
She's such an annoying girl!
Way to go, Natsuko!
You're laughing too much, Nami!
Nami, I found out you're
talking nonsense again.
Apparently Nana lives with Nana.
- What?
Why? What about your boyfriend?
Again, you're misunderstanding!
You serious? That's so boring!
Then why didn't you tell us
in the first place?
You're a source of constant worry.
I told you
- but you wouldn't listen, mom.
- So you're living with my daughter.
I can only imagine how much trouble
she's causing. I'm really sorry.
No, Nana is honest,
cheerful and kind.
Living with her
gives me encouragement.
As I imagined,
I can see she's been brought up in
a very warm family environment.
You certainly know
the right things to say.
Ouch!
You still have some time, right?
- Why don't I make some tea?
- Nana...
Oh, I have some Japanese sweets.
Nana, you're such a good actress.
Huh?
"Nana is honest, cheerful and kind"?
I really believe that.
, ., gives me encouragement.
By the way, where's your dad?
Does he work Saturdays too?
Ah, yeah. He'll be back in the evening.
Then I'll be able to meet him.
I'm looking forward to it.
He's not a father worth
getting your hopes up for.
Or rather, I'm really sorry. My family
can be so noisy. I'm embarrassed.
No, I'm really enjoying it.
Natsuko's even better than I imagined.
Meeting her was such a thrill.
What's so great about her?
She's just a normal lady.
No, that's a quality
you don't see much.
She is the ideal mother.
Really? Then what about
your mom, Nana?
What kinda person is she?
I bet she's pretty and cool.
I wonder. I can barely remember.
What do you mean?
You've only been away from your
hometown for less than half a year.
No, I haven't seen her
since I was four.
Huh? Why not?
She ran off with a guy.
She could even be dead now.
Not that I care.
Then, Nana, it was just
you and your father?
Do you have any siblings?
No.
Actually I never had a father
to start with.
I was raised by my mother's mother.
But grandma died when I was 15.
That's why I find this so attractive.
The atmosphere of belonging
to a loving family like yours.
Since I never had one, this is fun.
Attractive? But Nana...
To me, this is normal.
Sorry, here I am talking about
a gloomy subject.
I was just a bit surprised.
I'm sorry for asking all these questions
without really giving it much thought.
But I'm glad.
Oh, no, that came out wrong! Sorry.
I'm not glad about what you explained!
That part shocked me!
Calm down.
Nana. You've never talked to me
about yourself until now,
so I would wonder why that is.
It would make me sad
thinking about it.
So I'm glad you shared that with me.
I see. Sorry.
It never occurred to me
that you might be feeling like that.
I never had a close female friend
until now,
so I don't know how to
spend time together.
I'm not good at
talking about myself.
So I end up not talking about things.
But just ask me, and I'll tell you
anything you want, okay?
So stop feeling sad.
What's so funny?
Because Nana, why are you
always like that cool guy?
You're more like a boyfriend to me
than a female friend.
You just took my breath away
right now.
No, I can't have you
feel that way about me.
You'll really tell me anything
I want, right?
Yeah.
And promise to be frank with me.
Do you still love Ren?
You knew.
I'm sorry. Acting as if
I didn't know. But...
You brought me here knowing, right?
Thank you.
Nana.
Nana, I wanna buy a pamphlet
and stuff. What about you?
I'll have a smoke
and then go to my seat.
Show me your pamphlet later.
Do you still love Ren?
Nana ended up
not answering that question.
However, I could tell
even without her telling me.
The word love...
If you were able to
say that word with ease,
you would've already
gone to see him long ago.
We're smack in front of the guitarist.
You have the best seat
in the house, Nana!
The stage is much closer
to the seats than I expected.
What'll I do? I'm already
on the verge of crying.
Though there's no reason
for me to cry.
But rather than choose
happiness as a woman,
she chose to protect her pride.
Nana.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the event is about to begin.
If you are yet to be seated,
please promptly make your way
to your seats.
Now that we have our band members,
all we need is a band name.
What will it be?
Why don't we keep the band name
we had before?
There's nothing wrong with Brute.
That's so lame. Sounds too barbaric.
You're the one who
came up with the name.
Yes, but I want to start fresh.
We finally have a pretty girl on vocals,
so we can't have
anything barbaric, can we?
Right.
Then what about Olive? Popeye's girl.
Does Olive match your image?
I think not.
Same goes for you. And me.
Nana, stop laughing and help us think.
Anything you come up with
is fine with me.
Hey, are you serious about
being the vocalist of the band?
"Anything is fine with me."
Can you say you're enjoying life,
the way you take on everything
with that slanted attitude?
I never said "Anything is fine with me."
Then give it some thought.
Give some input into the band.
This coming from the most
self-centered member of the band.
What about this? This is nice.
"Black Stone".
Don't just pick the first thing you see.
But it's cool. I've never
seen anything like it.
Are those any good?
They have a strong scent.
Yeah, they're good.
They're actually cigars.
I made a trade with
a tobacco shop owner for them.
- A trade?!
Yuck! What's this? Such a weird taste!
Really?
But not bad. Black Stone.
BLAST for short. That's easy to say.
Yeah, that's nice. "BLAST".
He took my cigarette.
- Yuck!
- What the!
You know, BLAST also
means a strong gust of wind.
Really?
That's great! That's kinda cool that
we shorten the name
and it also means something!
Should we go with that then?
We're a band of four,
so let's go with "Black Stones".
It's an odd name, but we're
an odd band so it kinda fits.
Agreed! Hurray for BLAST!
Okay, it's decided. So, leader,
how about a celebration speech?
They really went with it.
Well then, band members,
an order from your leader.
From this day on, we'll all
smoke this brand of cigarettes.
- Smoke it yourself!
Why... am I crying?
But my heart's filled with emotion.
Nana...
That night, I had repeatedly prayed
so hard that the destiny waiting
for Nana after this would be
that of happiness.
That time, I wanted to continue
holding that hand
that I unknowingly was holding.
Always, forever.
I reached into the sky
But I couldn't reach what I wanted
They grew smaller
and disappeared into the sky
Like colorful balloons
I'm alone
My hand had no place to go
And gently you took it
Starless night
I won't look back
at the shadow of my past
I want to feel your warmth
Tears are falling down
Even if I'm unsure I won't let go
Of your hand holding mine