That night, we had jammed
until very late.
Our neighbors in the building
came to complain...
as was to be expected.
When I was darkness at that time
With trembling lips
In a corner of a room I cry
The more I struggle
The more this wound deepens
The broken promise hurt me
Nobody can save me
God, I have only one request
Stop tearing apart my love
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Sorrow tumbling down is your song
All alone with nowhere to go in my life
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Oh baby, help me from frozen pain
With your smile, your eyes,
and sing me, just for me
I wanna need your love
I'm a broken rose
I am so sorry!
Will you please give me a break!
Do you know what time it is?
Yes, I'm sorry!
This is the problem
with young people.
We'll be careful from now on.
Why do we always have trouble
with apartment 707?
Now, now, Ms. Yamada.
We're not supposed to talk about that.
A murder?!
In this apartment?
Whoever lived here before us
was murdered!
Who'd you hear that from?
- Ms. Yamada!
- Who's that?
I don't know!
An ageless woman!
In a nightgown, hair's done up in a twist,
wearing a mountain of make-up!
Why is that?!
I wonder if she's entertaining
some young man.
I really couldn't care less
about Yamada!
But I'm curious!
I wonder what he's like?
Do you think he's a bar host?
So this woman Yamada told you
that the person living here
before us was murdered?!
Well no, she didn't exactly
say it like that.
Apparently they're not allowed
to talk about it.
But she did say, "there's always trouble
with apartment 707!"
So that's got to be it!
There was a murder case here!
Go to bed!
Did I say something I shouldn't have?
Ah, but the rent here
is really cheap, right?
It's not unthinkable.
See? Don't you think so?
You do think so don't you?
Oh no, what am I going to do?
I'm too scared to sleep alone!
Would you like me to sleep
with you, Nana?
No way!
Thank you for your kindness,
but I do have a boyfriend!
I was kidding.
I'm sleeping in
Nana's room tonight,
so you can have my bed, Nobu.
You've had a long day,
traveling and all.
Oh, no problem.
I'll just crash somewhere out here.
No, you can't!
If you would just fall asleep
on my bed,
then Nana won't have any other choice
but to let me into her room.
Actually, she'd never let me sleep with her
unless something like that happened.
I see. So that's it.
Well then, if you don't mind,
I'll take your bed.
Thank you!
Your bedroom's big, too.
Oh... I have to work in the morning,
so I think I'll just get my clothes ready,
seeing as they all arrived safely.
- Work?
- Yup.
Oh, right. Then you've got
an early morning.
Sorry for partying so late.
That's no problem.
I can sleep in a bit, too.
As long as I get there by around ten,
I'll be okay.
Besides, I had a really
good time tonight!
I have never seen
a live band up so close!
It was so exciting!
Wait until you see us with a drum
and bass rhythm section.
You ain't seen nothing yet.
You can't really call us a band anyway,
with just the two of us.
I can't wait until we find
other members and do a real gig.
Right. New members.
I wish I could play the drums.
I'm pretty good
at the tambourine, though.
The tambourine?
You know. They've always got them
sitting around in the karaoke places.
Looks like a big ring.
I'm pretty good.
I didn't take you as one
to have rhythm.
What?!
But actually I would really
like Yasu on the drums.
You don't find a drummer
like that just anywhere.
You mean that Yasu?
So Yasu's a drummer.
Then he should come out
to Tokyo, too.
Yeah, but Yasu's got his work.
Besides, he told me he wasn't interested
in gambling his life away trying to go pro.
Gambling?
Looking like that in
a courtroom
seems a lot more like gambling
if you ask me.
Then what about bass?
Who was on bass?
Isn't that person interested
in coming to Tokyo?
Well, the bass player was also
in another band,
so he wasn't really
an official member.
In another band?
He had another band back home
and used to come and help us out
at gigs and stuff.
So that's fair game.
I guess Nana hasn't told you anything.
Yes?
About the band or anything.
Oh... No.
Nana doesn't talk about herself much.
But having heard her sing today,
I think I understand her a bit better.
She really came to Tokyo to
become a professional musician.
Yeah, her dream is to be able
to make a living by singing.
You know back home
she had some die-hard fans.
She was pretty well known locally.
I can't wait for Tokyo to listen to her.
Hey, I can help you find band members.
All you need is some members
and then she can start singing
at nightclubs right away.
Then everyone will fall in love
with Nana's voice.
Oh, and scouts won't leave her alone.
Hey Nana. Are you awake?
No.
Come on, you're awake!
I'm talking in my sleep.
My heart's beating so loud,
I can't sleep.
Are you that afraid of ghosts?
No, I'm excited about
something else now.
Huh? Sorry to disappoint you,
but I have no desire to hit on a woman.
No, it's not that either!
Would you shut up already?
I can't sleep. Do you want me
to kick you out?
Hey Nana. Do you want
a tambourine player on your band?
No, I don't.
What are these palpitations? I don't think
I've ever felt this way before.
Looking for a drummer and bassist!
Wanna join our band and go pro?
Those of you who like the Sex Pistols.
Ask the store clerk for details.
Looking for a drummer and bassist!
Wanna join our band and go pro?
Those of you who like the Sex Pistols.
Ask the store clerk for details.
What's this?
Looking for a drummer and bassist!
Wanna join our band and go pro?
Those of you who like the Sex Pistols.
Ask the store clerk for details.
Shoji! You've come!
I was gonna go to Jackson.
Wanna come?
Sure, I'll join you.
But what's this poster?
You made it, didn't you?
This is your drawing. These eyes.
Yup. Don't you think they look just
like Nana and Nobu?
Who's Nobu?
So she wants to make
a living by singing.
Now that's a pretty big dream.
Don't you think? I'm so excited!
Yeah, I guess I can get
into stories like that.
But I'm not sure if it's going
to be as easy as you think.
It'll be okay!
Everything's been going my way
since I got to Tokyo!
I don't think things going your way
has all that much to do with it.
I know! Let's go to karaoke tonight
with Nana!
I want you to hear her sing.
I'll play the tambourine!
Sorry man, I've got to work
to midnight tonight.
Work again? What are you working
so much for?
Your parents send you money,
don't they?
Not enough to live on.
When I start school,
I won't have time to work.
I've got to save up while I can.
That's what you say.
You're not spending money
on Sachiko, I hope!
Buying her Louis Vuitton bags
and Prada shoes.
But she really likes
these brands.
I'm just kidding!
You're the one that keeps
bringing her up!
I know, but I came all the way
to Tokyo to be with you
and you spend all of
your time working.
I just wish you would make
some time for me.
Oh come on. I do make time.
Like the other night.
You were the one that
went home early.
You're the one that's not
being considerate.
Why should I always have
to adjust to your plans?
Uh, I hate to disturb you at a time like this,
but your Jackson burger is ready.
- Koichi Sato!
- Yes!
I have a favor to ask.
My friend is looking for
some band members.
I wonder if you could put this up for me!
Hey Nana!
This place has nothing to do
with that band.
Besides, it's a punk band.
But...
I don't mind.
Since you're a good customer.
Really?! Thank you!
Then if anyone asks,
could you give me a call
on my mobile?
I'll write down my number here.
I've got to go to work now,
so I'm off.
I just remembered.
You sent me an email yesterday.
Huh?
Well, if it's not important,
never mind.
It's just that I fell asleep
without noticing it came.
Sorry.
Oh yeah, I did send one.
What did I write?
Shoji, I'm on my way home.
Call me when you get off work.
I can't believe it!
How could I half-consciously
send a message like this?
It's proof I'm taking Shoji
for granted.
And I didn't even remember
sending it.
Shoji probably came over
to see me before work
because he felt bad about
not being able to call.
And look at me...
I just wish you would make
some time for me.
Oh how selfish!
Am I self-centered or what?!
Why should I always have
to adjust to your plans?
I'm going to see Shoji at work
on my way home!
And I'm going to apologize. Sincerely!
Excuse me...
I wouldn't mind seeing him
in a waiter's outfit anyway.
- I'll wait for him to get off work, cheerfully!
- Um, hello...
- Then I'll let Shoji take me to his place.
- Do you mind?
And we'll make love and make up!
What a great plan,
if I say so myself!
Hello.
Oh hello! Can I help you
with something?
I just saw the poster out front.
S-So soon? And h-he's cute!
Things are really going
my way, aren't they?
Ahh...
Sorry, Shoji!
Plans for tonight have changed!
I'll make it up, I promise!
May I take your plate?
Busy again.
This place really needs more help.
Shoji, we got some new help
starting today.
- Well, that's good.
- Will you show her around?
Yes, sir!
And she's cute.
Shoji Endo. Pleased to meet you!
My name is Sachiko Kawamura.
It's nice to meet you.
What did you say... your first name?
Sachiko.
Do you...
Do you like Louis Vuitton and Prada?
Huh?
Resume Date: March 10, 2001
Name: Shinichi Okazaki
Birthdate: January 25
Age: 18 Sex: Male
You don't need a resume
to apply to be in a band.
What are you trying to pull off?
Oh really?
I had him write one out anyway
so you'd know more about him.
How am I supposed to know
a person from a piece of paper?
What are you doing?!
Can you just show me
what's in your heart
and what you can do?
Cool!
You making fun of me?!
No, not at all!
I wouldn't think of it.
You are just as cool
as Nana said you were.
Yeah? I don't think
you had to burn it, though.
How cool would it be
if you started a fire?
Please let me join your band!
If you're good.
So let me hear what you got.
Yes ma'am!
Hold on, cute boy!
Not here!
That ageless Ms. Yamada
will be back at us!
Hey, how much can
a bit of bass playing hurt?
Absolutely not!
Do you want to get kicked out?
We'll both be thrown out
on the street!
That's exactly what
the Demon Lord wants!
Demon Lord?
Go find a studio then.
A studio?
I know a cheap practice studio nearby!
Really? Hey, we could use you.
Let me ask if they have
any vacancies.
I'd be interested in listening
to your guitar and vocals, too.
Oh, hello?
You sure he's eighteen?
He looks more like sixteen.
He's lying about his experience.
So you did read through
his resume, after all.
Far out! It's available!
So cute!
He'd better not be
in elementary school.
I've never been in
a place like this before.
Okay then, you ready to play along
with one of ours?
Huh? But Shin doesn't know
any of your songs...
He can look at the score sheet.
Sure thing.
You ready already?
Yes. I'll give it a try!
Okay.
One, two...
Awesome! Awesome!
So great!
They are so tight!
You're not too bad, cute boy!
I'm glad you didn't just look the part!
What?
Ow!
Nana!
I'm sorry, did I do something weird?
No, it's not that at all.
You just surprised us.
You're a lot better than we expected.
What do you think, Nana?
This kid's good.
Let's let him in, okay?
So, your name's, Shinichi.
Is that right?
Yes.
Name a guitarist you respect.
Ren Honjo!
Huh? Ren Honjo?
You mean the Trapnest guitarist?
Yes.
Then we have something in common!
I like Trapnest, too!
I'm even in their fan club!
Although I like Takumi.
Oh, is that so.
But I guess I'm more of
a Ren fan than a Trapnest fan, though.
I played guitar for a long time
until I fell for Ren's music.
Then I started playing bass.
Huh? But Ren plays guitar.
Takumi's on bass.
Didn't you know?
Ren plays bass too.
Is that right?!
Ren does the bass on
the Sex Pistols tribute album,
and it is just incredibly awesome!
Oh really.
I guess I need to do more research!
I see. That makes sense.
Oh, did I throw you off? I'm sorry!
No. Your bass is easy to sing with.
Will you join our band?
Yes, I'd be happy to!
Your singing and Nobu-san's guitar
gave me the shivers!
Oh but... there's one thing
you have to promise me first.
If you can't, then you're gonna hafta
decline right this moment.
Shin, do better than Ren.
Yes! Of course, that's what I intend to do.
Isn't that wonderful?
You found such a great bass player
in such a short time!
And he's cute!
So who do you have to thank?
Hey, who do you have to thank?
What are you getting at?
You want a prize that badly?
Let's see, then...
Don't litter!
Thank you, Hachiko.
I-I thought you didn't hit on women.
It's not right! I have a boyfriend!
What's she getting all uptight
about over a kiss?
It's not like she's a virgin.
You'll never change.
Sorry, Shoji! I just kissed someone
other than you!
But she's a girl,
so don't take it too hard, okay?
Wait...
This must look like I'm following her.
Um...
Miss Kawamura...
I'm not some molester.
Oh, Mr. Endo, it's you.
Sorry about that.
You scared me for a minute there.
This is a quiet street.
It's not safe walking alone.
But it's a shortcut to the station
and if I don't hurry,
I'll miss the last train.
Oh, me too. Shall we run together then?
Yes!
You're not getting
on the same train are you, Sachiko?
Oh, good. I made it.
Don't tell me we're getting off
at the same station, Sachiko.
Where are you getting off, Mr. Endo?
My stop's the third one.
How about you, Sachi...
Er, ah... Miss Kawamura?
Mine's the second stop.
Oh, uh, will you be okay walking home
from the station?
Yes I'll be fine. I live right
across from the station.
Is that so?
That's a relief then.
Thank you.
You're so kind, Mr. Endo.
Good night.
She's pretty cute, that Sachiko!
Quite a difference from
the make-believe Sachiko!
This isn't good!
I'll hafta keep away from her!
That was so much fun!
Settle down! You're making me cold!
D-D-Don't come onto this side
of the bed!
Whose bed is this anyway?
If you don't like it,
sleep on the floor!
There!
Come on!
Hey!
I can tell you honestly now,
my feelings of looking up to you,
it was quite a lot like falling in love.
I really wasn't ready to grow up.
Yet within the reality of being expected
to fend for myself,
you always showed me
the sweetest dreams.
It was like first love
in its happiest moments.
I reached into the sky
But I couldn't reach what I wanted
They grew smaller
and disappeared into the sky
Like colorful balloons
I'm alone
My hand had no place to go
And gently you took it
Starless night
I won't look back
at the shadow of my past
I want to feel your warmth
Tears are falling down
Even if I'm unsure I won't let go
Of your hand holding mine