Genshiken
I woke up and as usual forgot
my cell and missed the Express.
My life reflected in
the train window.
I'm sure I have something that
I won't lose to anyone in Japan...
... but it's pretty sad
that no one notices it.
I can't run fast, though.
I'm not that strongly-built.
Here I go, at my dauntless pace.
Pass away, today's
sadness, raining in the sun!
Hesitation, repetition,
dreaming all night, all night.
Farewell sadness,
to outer space you go!
Look to the sky and shout
at the top of your lungs!
At this tempo!
Right now, at this tempo!
Genshiken
Suioh University
The weather's sure nice now.
That it is.
Hey, is this a good way
to get to building 7?
I think it probably is...
New freshmen are here already.
That they are.
Episode 7: Characteristics of Actions
and Decisions in Personal Relationships
I wonder if Genshiken
will get new members.
I hope not.
If Genshiken gets more active,
it'll be harder for Kohsaka to quit.
Hi hi!
Sup.
Oh, Saki! Saki!
Huh?
Why don't we cosplay together
for the freshman activities fair?
Absolutely not!
When on earth are you going to
cosplay?
H-Hold on, you think
it's a matter of time?
It isn't?
No, it's not, at all!
Now, now.
We've talked about basing
our recruitment on cosplay...
...but isn't that too restrictive within the
scope of Genshiken activities?
That is, it's just two of us...
We're pretty much the world of hobbies.
Our members c-can do just
about anything they want...
...but m-maybe it's too
intense for the fair.
So yeah, that's the general feeling.
But I want to do it every chance I get!
Uh, yeah...
Your personality sure changes
when it comes to cosplay...
It does?
Don't look at me if any weirdos show
up.
I'd say it's a little late
to worry about that now.
Because there's already
plenty of them here?
So, aren't you going to start the number
umpteen-hundred meeting thing?
Why wait?
Huh, so that's your disposition.
The original story goes
into a second part...
...new characters are introduced
and it causes lots of commotion.
And they get through okay.
A-At this point it's
n-nostalgic to see Alex.
There's some nice added scenes
for it being a recap episode.
Good stuff.
How can you watch this
over and over so much?
Huh?
Is it interesting?
Uh, you can't really
simplify it that much...
We watch it because it's interesting to
see whether it's interesting or not...
You're no fun, girl.
Miss President...
Our chairman!
Did he graduate?
Did he leave the school?
Um, the chairman?
No, I don't know...
She's right, w-where is he?
Who knows?
Did he find a job? Is he going to
graduate? Is he repeating a year?
Wait, what year was he in to begin with?
I'm still here.
You needn't be so startled.
You always startle me.
Because of a guilty conscience?
Not in the least!
That means you can rest at ease.
I have an announcement to make.
What?
I think I'll retire as chairman.
That's a very sudden
and weighty announcement.
I figured I would get
around to graduating.
"Get around to?" After how long?
T-Then he hasn't
thought about it until n-now?
I plan to spend all year
writing my graduation thesis.
I've gathered plenty of data.
What data?
Therefore I'd like to recommend
Madarame as the next chairman.
What, me?
Oh, good idea.
It essentially already
feels that way anyway.
A-And the only other
senior is Haraguchi...
Don't worry.
I myself left all the
practicalities to Tanaka anyway.
Oh... then maybe we should
offer it to Tanaka first...
Just do it. You're qualified.
Yeah? Okay then...
I'll give it a go...
Congratulations, you're
our second chairman.
The second?
That's all?
He's gone!
No Photographs, please
Genshiken
All right, then.
Suioh University
What? Two people joined?
They're still just provisional.
I haven't even met them.
Even a club like this
gets new members...
I wonder what they're like.
Oh.
"Oh" what?
Oh, right now...
What?
Uh, ah...
Ahh, so much for the surprise test...
Hey, new guys.
Um...
Hi there...
...how about introducing yourselves?
I'm Sawazaki.
My name is Kuchiki.
Please call me Coochy.
Not on your life!
Now, now.
As for me...
Oh forget it, whatever.
Come on now, Kasukabe.
You know, I guess I just
don't have an "otaku name."
I'm sorry, she's a mundane.
Oh, then she doesn't
cosplay or anything.
Cosplay? You mean Ohno?
Did her cosplay dazzle you?
Kasukabe...
N-No, it meant nothing!
Don't get carried away, Kasukabe.
These guys are still new.
I realize that of course, Mr. Chairman!
But you know, you two
should forget this club.
This room is actually haunted.
Huh?
By the ghost of the first
chairman who died five years ago...
Cut that out!
The original chairman's still alive!
Don't act like he's dead!
It's not a lie, though!
I've kept quiet until now,
but sometimes I see it.
A dog-like face wearing glasses
floats by gaps in the bookshelves.
You can say that with a straight face?
Don't turn around, you two.
Huh?
There's a face in the
shelf behind you...
Note: It's just an image.
Hey, that's enough of that!
Not bad, Saki.
Oh right, it really was made up.
Maybe.
Kasukabe's started messing with
the newcomers right on schedule...
I have to put an end to
this no matter what...
Yes, as the chairman!
Bar Kurokiya
Well, everyone...
Let the Society for the Study of Modern
Visual Culture welcome party begin.
Cheers.
Cheers!
Oh, you don't drink?
Then...
Nah, I was wondering if
we were going to chug.
No, we don't.
Well that's a downer.
It's not a downer, it's
just how we do things.
Excuse me!
What'll ya have?
Let's see.
A spring vegetable
pizza, handmade egg rolls some tasty...
...potato croquettes, shoronpo, fried
cheese wontons, and then...
Uh, hey...
Oh, you want to order?
How about an assorted platter?
Well hey, it's a welcome party.
O-Okay, fried chicken, and...
Noooo!
No chicken for me!
I oppose the fried chicken!
T-Then, c-cancel
the chicken.
Sure, with pleasure.
Instead, a
p-pickled e-eggplant.
Yeees!
That's outfit's a Cecil, isn't it?
It's no surprise it looks good on you.
What do you mean, "no surprise?"
Not many people can dress well.
If we knew other, that'd be one thing...
But I'm the type who thinks a
guy complimenting my clothes...
...right off the bat is up to no good.
But that's not true.
Don't waste your time.
What?
I'm just here to keep an eye on
Kohsaka.
Oh, is that so?
It doesn't look that way at all.
What do you mean by that?
Ah, well, I guess you
just look like friends.
That's none of your business.
I'm sorry, it was just a question.
You should know that...
...even if this is a welcome party,
I don't feel like welcoming anyone.
Oh come on.
Let's enjoy ourselves.
Ohno.
What'll you have next?
Um, um, another one of these.
Excuse me!
You got it!
Which will it be, as God in heaven says.
Hey.
Start a conversation.
Aren't y-you
the ch-chairman?
Kuchiki?
W-What made you decide to join us?
You see...
Probably Ohno and her cosplay.
Leave well alone with a ten-foot pole!
Not just that, or
rather what besides that?
Let's see...
I've embraced a strong
and profound interest in...
...anime, comics, and the
like since I was little.
Hey, what'll you have next?
O-Okay, a cassis orange.
Excuse me!
Coming up!
So I decided to take this
chance on entering college to...
Here's your spring vegetable
pizza and tasty potato croquettes.
All right.
Those are mine, mine, mine!
He's hogging them?
Delicious!
I guess he's come out of his shell.
You don't drink?
That's not it.
Beer might as well be water.
I've been drinking it since high school.
I really don't like how otaku-ish the
manga and anime clubs are.
We have our share of otaku too.
But you have girl members.
That alone makes you
completely different.
Just between us, I also
scoped out the Manga Club.
What a waste.
It's almost all lardass pigs.
I wouldn't know...
Anime is Japan's culture these days.
Simply enjoying it is stupid.
Being able to study it more as culture
this way, it's like, when a culture's...
Uhh...
Um, a subculture?
Yes! That's it, a subculture!
Right...
Did you know?
These days anime films are
invited to be shown at Cannes...
...and figures are auctioned
as art by Sotheby's.
No, I didn't know that.
This much is to be expected.
Hey, what's that? What's that?
It's a cassis orange.
Cassis orange?
Yes.
Let me try a quick sip.
I like!
Excuse me, Miss!
Coming up!
A cassis orange, cassis orange!
Gladly!
Want me to finish that?
No, that's okay.
Here's your cassis orange.
Excuse me.
What can I get you?
A double sweet-potato
shochu, on the rocks.
You got it!
Excuse me, could I get some shochu
too?
You got it!
There's been a shochu boom lately.
They say good shochu
is better than sake.
Is that so?
Aha, I might not look it
but I keep up with fashion.
Let's go find some good
shochu to drink sometime.
I'll scope out a good place.
Right...
I've got to go to the bathroom...
A drinking party?
That's a rarity.
Ahh right, it's the welcome party.
More or less.
How many joined?
Two, but they're provisional.
That's not very many.
Is Genshiken doing okay?
The Manga Club reserved a
private room, but it's still full.
We're just swelling with members.
Right...
I heard the news.
You're the chairman now?
Well, so it seems...
Well, even if I got passed over...
...I'm pretty busy, so I don't
think I could've done it anyway...
...but it would've been nice
to at least be told about it.
Sorry about that.
In a way, I aim to be a
guardian for Genshiken.
So, if you have any
problems just tell me.
I'll help you out.
Ohno.
Are you all right?
It's good!
Want some, Saki?
No thanks.
How much can she drink?
Don't you think guys
who let themselves go...
...because they're
otaku are the ugliest?
It doesn't really mean
they've let themselves go...
How d'you figure?
Y'know what...
A-Are you okay?
I'll go with him.
Huh, why you?
Sasahara can do it.
Have a drink, Saki.
I said no thanks.
Aren't you drinking too much?
Are you worried about me?
I love you, Saki.
Yes, of course.
I'm happy we can drink together.
I'm not drinking, you're
the only one who is.
Then you should drink some too.
Not the shochu.
But beer, that I can do.
I love you, Saki!
Come on, let's go.
Don't forget anything.
Two hearts in balance.
Kujibiki unbalance.
Love, dreams, yearning...
Hey, are you all right?
Want me to bring some water?
I'm all good, no problem!
Come on, Saki. Drink, drink.
Yes, yes, I'm drinking.
Drink more!
Give me a break!
Coochy! Shut up!
Sir, this is your last
chance to order anything.
Would you care to?
Saki!
Are you sure you're all right?
I'm fine.
I think we've had enough.
You got it.
Tanaka, w-we're leaving.
Sawazaki, you look pretty bad!
I'm takin' a dump!
Thank you so much!
You okay?
You still don't look good.
Nah, I'm fine now!
What now? Call it a night?
Let's go to the next place! Okay?
But...
I want us to be together more!
But there's nowhere open this late.
Then come to my place.
What?
There's plenty of sitting room.
Thanks for having us.
Thanks for nothing.
Hey, new guy, this is not your room.
It's all good, we're in
the same club and all.
You're still just provisional.
Oh, I like it well
enough, I think I'll join.
Then let's have a test.
An admission test.
If you beat Kohsaka in a
fighting game or whatever...
...we'll approve you joining the club.
That sounds good.
I'm pretty into fighting games.
Splendid.
Want to give it a shot?
Okay, I'll do it.
Don't do it, man, seriously.
Let's do this.
I'll go easy since
it's a friendly match.
Don't go easy, just play
the way you always do.
But...
The way you always do,
like that Puyo Pop time.
Right...
Guilty Gear Isuka, huh?
That just came out.
Have you played a lot in arcades?
Here and there.
I'll show them the difference
between a poser and the real thing!
Jam Kuradoberi make her entrance!
A throw chained into an air combo!?
Which one are you?
The guy.
Damn, he's reading my Roman Cancel!
Whoa, a Dust into a D-loop?
Did Kohsaka win?
It's a one-match game,
so why not try again?
Son of a bitch!
Did he win?
Yes, yes, he won.
I guess it makes you happy when
your boyfriend wins at games?
I suppose so.
You're not too bad.
You'd say that after
perfect-ing me twice?
Don't forget, you've
been drinking tonight.
You're absolutely right!
You didn't drink at
all, and I drank a lot!
Of course you'd play better than me.
Want to play again?
You're on.
All right!
What?
I'm going to cheer for him.
Kick his butt, Kohsaka!
Come on, Kasukabe!
Not in front of everyone!
If you win the next one, I'll kiss you.
Hey!
Are you sure that's cool?
What's your problem?
You don't have to shout.
This has nothing to do with the test!
Oh, the test, you're right.
Then, if he beats Kohsaka,
I'll even kiss the new guy.
There she goes again.
Suioh University
Hey, where's your next lecture?
What's wrong?
I could've sworn that was...
Do you remember?
Our childhood...
Where, where?
Genshiken
Are you alright?
Yeah...
You don't have one, Kohsaka?
Not at all.
I've got it.
What?
If we do the Kohsaka test every
year, I can smash Genshiken.
Right, Mr. Chairman?
We took no detours or shortcuts...
... and we weren't afraid of
what tomorrow would bring...
... as we kept walking down
Inogashira Street late at night.
Only vivid dreams extended
deep into the shadows.
We aren't quite grown up.
Simple but complicated
glistening like marbles.
The time we could see from there
sparkled, even if nothing big happened.
What we see from the marbles in
our hands now is a little different...
... but they shine faintly nearby.
Sasahara, you don't go for
the "little sister" image.
Yeah, I guess I would have to
pick the "childhood friend" image.
What about maids?
Good stuff!
I might not have brought it up before,
but I like girls with cat ears too.
I think bandaged girls are what I dig.
How about a girl who's class president?
A- Ok!
I wonder if there are any characters
like that in games or anime.
A childhood friend cat-eared maid...
...who's class president at
school, is usually stern...
...but who's also clumsy, covered
in bandages, and the main character!
That's so awesome!