When you're gazing out at the sea,
surrounded by the sound of waves...
...you lose track of time, don't you?
It just goes to show that it's better to be busy.
But if you're too busy,
you also lose track of time.
You lose track of time either way, then.
It can't be helped, I guess.
We're sorry, pui
Closed Today
We look forward
to your next visit
Aria Company
It can't be helped, I guess.
We're sorry, pui
Closed Today
We look forward
to your next visit
Aria Company
Right?
It can't be helped, I guess.
We're sorry, pui
Closed Today
We look forward
to your next visit
Aria Company
Right?
Okay, space-out time is over!
We're sorry, pui
Closed Today
We look forward
to your next visit
Aria Company
Okay, space-out time is over!
We're sorry, pui
Closed Today
We look forward
to your next visit
Aria Company
"Dear Ai, today is the
Aria Company's anniversary."
"That's right, it's the day that
Grandma founded the Aria Company!"
"We'll be closed all day today,
and together with Alicia and President Aria,"
We're sorry, pui
Closed Today
We look forward
to your next visit
Aria Company
"We'll be closed all day today,
and together with Alicia and President Aria,"
"the three of us are going on a little trip.
We've been looking forward to it for a while."
My, my.
Do you remember that day
Oboeteimasuka ano hi o
When your heart suddenly began to race
Futo kanjita tokimeki o
The rays from the blue sky were pouring over you...
Aoi hizashi abite
...as you cut through the wind
Kaze o kiru kimi ni
I couldn't look away, and when our eyes met
Mitoreru to me ga atte
I couldn't help but smile
Egao koboreta
It's just like a spiral
Marude supiraare
I want to spend my days waving to you
Itsumademo te o furitai hibi
This is my proof that I was here with you
Koko ni tashika ni kimi to ita akashi
An eternal spiral
Zutto supiraare
Wow! It's a bicycle!
There's a path which stretches on ahead
Kono saki mo tsuzuiteru michi ga aru
Wow! It's a bicycle!
There's a path which stretches on ahead
Kono saki mo tsuzuiteru michi ga aru
On Neo-Burano Island, children up to
twelve years old are allowed to ride bicycles.
There's a path which stretches on ahead
Kono saki mo tsuzuiteru michi ga aru
This is the first time I've seen
a bicycle since coming to Aqua.
When you climb the next hill,
Tsugi no saka o nobottara
This is the first time I've seen
a bicycle since coming to Aqua.
When you climb the next hill,
Tsugi no saka o nobottara
Let's meet again
Mata aimashou
There are a lot of colorful houses, aren't there?
Burano Island back on Manhome was also
a fishing village, just like this one.
It's said that the fishermen's wives
painted the houses in various colors...
...so the returning fishermen could find
their houses, even on a dark and foggy night.
It seems that tradition is still
alive and well here today.
This is the Venetian lace that was popular
in Manhome's Venice, isn't it?
Yes. Nets are necessary to fish, right?
So lace was developed
from the art of weaving nets.
It looks like the art of lace-making has been
passed down to Aqua, hasn't it?
I'm sure the bride who wears
that dress will look stunning.
The woman we're going to visit now, Anna,
was also very beautiful in her lace wedding dress.
Really?
Um, so what kind of person is Anna?
Let's see... She was a cheerful
and glamorous Undine.
She had many male fans,
and was much busier than I am now.
Wow! She sounds amazing!
It makes me kind of nervous.
My, my.
In That Gently Passing Time...
It's this house, Alicia.
Hello!
Huh...
Maybe she's not home? I'm pretty sure
this is the time we agreed on, but...
Huh?
Hello!
Wha?
Please wait! There's
something I'd like to ask you!
That boy...
What's the matter?
There were two ladies at our gate.
U-Umm...
That uniform...
Anna.
Long time no see, Alicia.
Then, you must be...
Ah, yes. Pleased to meet you!
I'm Akari Mizunashi.
Hello, Akari. I'm Anna.
And this is my son, Ahito.
Hello, Ahito.
H-Hello.
Oh? What's this, Ahito? You're blushing.
I'm not blushing!
My, my. Are you flustered?
Shut up, hag!
Whaaaat?!
Stop it!
My, my.
Such beautiful lace work.
It's wonderful!
Grandma made it.
Huh? Your grandmother?
Yeah. My grandma is a famous
lace maker on this island.
Mom's getting lessons from her right now.
She's still bad at it, though.
Hey!
That was given to me as a wedding gift.
Everything else is either my own work,
or was given to me by someone else.
Back when Anna was
working at the Aria Company...
...a fisherman from this island, now her husband,
was visiting Neo-Venezia with his mother.
She soon fell in love with that kind fisherman
who cared so much about his mother.
Thank you so much for forgiving my selfishness.
Not at all, Anna. Congratulations.
This is a wonderful reason.
To see you follow your own path without
any hesitation makes me very happy.
Thank you very much, Grandma.
Please take care.
Thank you, Alicia.
Take care of yourself.
I will.
The Aria Company was
the high point of my youth.
It's pudgy-wudgy!
It was a happy marriage, wasn't it?
Not exactly.
I'm joking.
But there were hardships.
Getting married and moving was fine, but life here
was completely different from my life as an Undine.
I didn't know anyone.
My husband was always out fishing.
I became alienated from the islanders,
so I had a hard time getting to know them.
It was really lonely.
But after I started learning how to make lace,
I gradually got to know the islanders.
In some cases, we had up to five people
working on a single lace project.
Five people?
Each of these lace embroideries
was done by a different person,
and they entrusted me with making the bridge
embroideries that connect each section.
I was so happy.
That embroidery became the real bridge that
connected you and the islanders, didn't it?
Yeah.
Whoa, great way to put it, Akari!
Ah! I'm sorry.
My, my.
I wonder if Grandma is doing well.
Ah, sounds like Alberto's back from fishing.
Welcome home.
Grandma! What are you doing here?
Alicia invited me.
Long time no see, Anna.
I'm glad to see you're doing well.
We just happened to bump into each other.
I'm so happy to see you, Grandma!
My, my, President Aria.
Hello, Ahito.
Hello.
Nice to meet you. I'm Alberto.
I'm Akari Mizunashi.
How was it?
Oh, it was a great haul!
Ta-da!
I picked out the ones
that looked especially tasty!
Looks delicious.
All right. Time to put my
cooking skills into action!
It smells delicious.
Looks like it's cooked just right.
Here I go!
All right!
Are you okay?
Alberto!
Dinner's ready!
Okay! We'll be right there!
Ow...
This looks amazing!
Okay, let's dig in!
Let's eat!
It's delicious!
The fish is so fresh, it's delicious!
Why, thank you.
Here, Grandma.
Thank you.
Yummy!
This is fantastic!
Looks like he's tired.
He woke up early today, didn't he?
He just got carried away, that's all.
There's a lot of Aria Company
history that I don't know, isn't there?
From the founding of the Aria Company,
to Akari, our newest member...
Somehow, it all makes me really happy.
I think of Ahito as a grandson, as well.
Spending this moment together is like a miracle.
That's right.
A miracle...
It's all thanks to you for founding
the Aria Company, Grandma.
If you hadn't, Alberto and I
would have never met,
and Ahito wouldn't have
been born into this world.
I see you have your feet firmly
on the ground, and cherish every day.
You've found a happiness
that suits you, haven't you?
Thank you very much.
I didn't found the Aria Company on my own.
It was President Aria who gave me the idea.
No, it was more like he saved me.
President Aria did?
Would you mind telling us about that?
Back then, I was at a loss with myself.
It was back when I was still
an Undine at Himeya.
Good work, Akino.
Good work, Akino!
Good work.
By that time, I had already been known as
Himeya's ace Undine for over fourteen years.
Akino looks wonderful today, as always.
She changes the mood simply by
passing by, doesn't she?
I heard she had six bookings
back to back yesterday.
That's amazing!
If it were me, I'd definitely be worn out.
Instead of waning, she seems to shine
brighter and brighter with age, doesn't she?
And no matter how busy she is,
she always has a smile on her face.
She truly is the greatest Water Fairy of our time!
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!
Ah, that sure was fun.
Bye bye.
Huh?
Hello, Mr. Cat.
You always seem to be here, lately.
Where did you come from?
What are you doing here every day?
Are you lost, by chance?
Don't you get tired of
always being in the same spot?
I'm sorry. It would be hard to answer
so many questions all at once.
At the time, I enjoyed my work, of course,
but I was so busy that
time seemed to just fly by.
Every so often, I would think
to myself, "What a waste."
"There are so many wonderful
things in this world."
"If only I could take the time to
cherish each and every one of them."
Say, Mr. Cat.
What are you always looking at from here?
Are you waiting for something
that's important to you?
A white seabird with a tilted neck...
Kubi o kashigeta shiroi umidori
...flew away into the endless sky
Tondetta no anna ni takai sora
Soon, a ship sailing beyond the sky...
Sora no mukou no fune ga mousugu
...will arrive in the afternoon harbor
Tadoritsuku gogo no minato
Mr. Cat!
Lively people gathered among colorful glass
Nigiwau hito iro toridori no garasuzaiku
What could you be waiting for that
you're willing to do this to yourself?
Lively people gathered among colorful glass
Nigiwau hito iro toridori no garasuzaiku
The person I long to see has gone to a far-off land...
Aitai hito tooi kuni e itta
...to a town I have yet to discover
Ima wa shiranai machi ni iru no
Mr. Cat...
...to a town I have yet to discover
Ima wa shiranai machi ni iru no
Before I knew it, it was morning.
Even though I was out in the rain
all night long, somehow I felt renewed.
Thanks to President Aria,
I realized that I was pushing myself.
The person I long to see...
Aitai hito
And then, together with President Aria,
I founded the Aria Company.
The person I long to see...
Aitai hito
The voice I long to hear...
Kikitai koe
I thought, "That world reflected in his
beautiful blue eyes... I want to see it with him."
Lively people gathered among colorful glass
Nigiwau hito iro toridori no garasuzaiku
caution,
wet paint
Lively people gathered among colorful glass
Nigiwau hito iro toridori no garasuzaiku
The person I long to see has gone to a far-off land...
Aitai hito tooi kuni e itta
...to a town I have yet to discover
Ima wa shiranai machi ni iru no
And that's how it all began.
Akari.
Yes?
Someday, your Aria Company will begin.
We're all looking forward to your Aria Company,
which will be unlike anything we've seen before.
Good luck!
Yes, I'll do my best!
My, my.
"Ai, I'm so happy I was allowed to be
a part of the Aria Company."
"Because of that, I'm able to spend
time with such wonderful people."
"Akari, the Aria Company is an amazing place..."
"...because of the thoughts, wishes
and kindness of many people."
"I'm kind of envious!"
A shore awash in golden waves
Kin no nami kishibe ni
Filled with yearning, I open my eyes and it's morning
Akogare mezameru no asa ni
As my thoughts focus intently on someone,
Dareka no koto o tsuyoku omou toki
Love rests on my palm, held high
Kakageta te no hira ni ai ga tomaru
A future guided by the flow of water and wind
Mizu no yukue to kaze ga shimesu mirai
I gaze at the hope that surrounds this world
Kono hoshi o tsusumu kibou mitsumete
The distant clouds of light are beckoning now
Tooi kumo hikari ga sasou you ni yureru ima
A shore awash in golden waves
Kin no nami kishibe ni
Filled with yearning, I open my eyes and it's morning
Akogare mezameru no asa ni
And my day begins
Hajimaru
Next Episode
A-A-Akari! Th-This is a really big SOS!
Ah, what's wrong, Alice?!
Next Episode
I really need an SOS rescue for Athena!
The Memories of That Precious Person...
Next time, "The Memories of
That Precious Person..."
Next Episode
The Memories of That Precious Person...
Now, please take my hand.