Something seems off.
It just somehow
felt that way.
What an incredible spirit,
I had absolutely no interest in the
prefectural game playing on the TV,
he's able to keep going
despite giving up seven runs.
I had absolutely no interest in the
prefectural game playing on the TV,
The second pitch is...
I had absolutely no interest in the
prefectural game playing on the TV,
but I kind of ended up
rooting for the losing side.
And it's up... it's a left fly ball.
One out.
But I kind of ended up
rooting for the losing side.
And it's up... it's a left fly ball.
One out.
Once I did, I kind of
got the feeling
The gap between
the scores is big,
Once I did, I kind of
got the feeling
The gap between
the scores is big,
that Haruhi was going
to start something.
But Kumamoto still has a chance
if they can hold out here.
That Haruhi was going
to start something.
But Kumamoto still has a chance
if they can hold out here.
Incoming call: Haruhi Suzumiya
but Kumamoto still has a chance
if they can hold out here.
The passionate voices cheering
Kyon, the phone's ringing.
From the third base bleachers
haven't died down.
Kyon, the phone's ringing.
From the third base bleachers
haven't died down.
I know, you don't
have to tell me.
There's Suzuki, they need him to do
his best, don't they, Mr. Kiru?
I know, you don't
have to tell me.
There's Suzuki, they need him to do
his best, don't they, Mr. Kiru?
You're not doing
anything today, right?
That's true.
You're not doing
anything today, right?
That's true.
We're all meeting at exactly
two o'clock in front of the station.
After all, you never know how
a match is going to turn out.
We're all meeting at exactly
two o'clock in front of the station.
After all, you never know how
a match is going to turn out.
Be sure to show up.
After all, you never know how
a match is going to turn out.
They still have hope.
I didn't even say anything...
Next, stepping up
to the batter's box
Kyon, the phone's ringing.
We have number four,
Kashima, a senior.
Kyon, the phone's ringing.
We have number four,
Kashima, a senior.
I know.
We have number four,
Kashima, a senior.
What?
After last year's
summer tournament,
I forgot to mention this - bring
a swimsuit, and plenty of money.
He was chosen to be part of the team
that went to Cuba.
I forgot to mention this - bring
a swimsuit, and plenty of money.
And be sure to bring your bike.
That's all, over and out!
And there's Suzuki
with a big windup...
And be sure to bring your bike.
That's all, over and out!
What?
And the first pitch is a strike.
No problems there.
What?
And the first pitch is a strike.
No problems there.
That was a good pitch.
I had the feeling that I knew
what Haruhi was going to say.
That was a strong, straight pitch,
thrown a little high and inside.
I had the feeling that I knew
what Haruhi was going to say.
That was a strong, straight pitch,
thrown a little high and inside.
Perhaps he feels like he's got
nothing left to lose.
No, not quite.
Perhaps he feels like he's got
nothing left to lose.
To be precise,
Perhaps he feels like he's got
nothing left to lose.
It felt like this exact same conversation
had happened before.
We don't know that yet.
He winds up for the second pitch...
it felt like this exact same conversation
had happened before.
It felt like this exact same conversation
I guess it's what you
would call deja vu.
It's a hit! And it's a big one!
It's headed for left field...
I guess it's what you
would call deja vu.
And it's good!
It's a solo home run!
And with this, Jyonan's
gotten their eighth run!
You're late, Kyon!
Show some more motivation!
Yeah, yeah.
Sorry I made you wait.
I just got here, too.
Okay, we're all here,
so let's go.
Where are we going?
To the public swimming pool,
of course!
Well, I guess that makes sense.
We have to do summer vacation-y things
during our summer vacation!
We can never get back the time
that we've lost!
And so we're going to do
them now, during this,
our one and only summer
as tenth graders!
By the way, we're going
to the pool by bike.
Did you ride
your bikes too?
No, the only two bikes we have
are yours and mine.
Okay, are you ready?
Of course not!
I am!
Kyon, you'd better not lose
to Koizumi.
This train is leaving
the station!
Dammit!
DAY BY DAY unzari dayone dakara
Day by day, everything's just so dull
Doudou to kotowacchau
kimi ni narina yo
That's why you need to become
someone that can just reject it all
OH MY BOY kippari shinakya uso ni
Oh my boy, you need to be decisive
Tsukiatterarenai yo semai sekai de
I won't deal with any lies
in this small world
Jibun de mitsuketa MYSELF
suki ni natte touzen
I found myself on my own,
it's natural you'd fall for me
Kudaranai yarikara kette
Kick away the boring ways
of doing things,
subete wa atashi ga kimeru
I'm going to decide everything
I SAY I SAY MY HEAVEN
I say, I say my heaven
SUPER DRIVER tosshin makasete
nantettate zenshin
Super driver, leave everything
to the rush
SUPER DRIVER tosshin makasete
nantettate zenshin
And just keep going forward,
no matter what
Fukanou (DON'T YOU STOP ME)
Tobikoete TAKE IT EASY, GO!
Surpass (Don't you stop me)
The idea of "impossible"
Fukanou (DON'T YOU STOP ME)
Tobikoete TAKE IT EASY, GO!
Take it easy, go!
Daishouri tte doukan
I agree, it's going to be
a huge victory
Mochiron dounatta tte kaikan
Of course, it'll feel pleasant,
no matter what happens
Hanseikai? (GET BACK TO WILD)
Sore yori saa isoide yo
A review meeting? (Get back to wild)
Forget that, now hurry up
Aremo koremo mitaiken
itsudatte muriyari
We haven't tried this or that,
we always do things how we want
Marude marude mikeiken
korekara shimashou
Everything's a new experience,
let's try them out
Aremo koremo mitaiken
itsudatte totsuzen
We haven't tried this or that,
we always do things suddenly
Marude marude mikeiken
sore ga doushita no?
Everything's a new experience,
what about it?
Endless Eight
Kyon, we're about to go have fun.
This is no time to be exhausted.
You're such a slacker.
Whose fault do you
think this is?
Oh, the scent of chlorine.
This really makes it feel like a pool!
Come on, time to go swimming!
Let's race!
No diving
It's dangerous
Can't you read this sign?
Hurry up and get in!
The water's warm so it feels fine!
That looks like fun.
This makes me smile, though.
Miss Suzumiya has some
rather normal ways
of enjoying her time,
don't you think?
Miss Suzumiya, laughing and having
a good time like that,
isn't likely to shake up
the world, after all.
I hope that's the case...
What's wrong?
Koizumi!
It's nothing...
It's probably
just my imagination.
Because so much has happened
since the beginning of spring,
I've become
a little paranoid.
Come on, let's go swim.
Hey!
Hey now!
Take that!
Get back here!
I think it'd be better to call this a
communal pool than a public pool.
This feeling...
It feels like I've seen
this scene once before.
Where Nagato kind of looks like
she's bored... and then...
Kyon!
Right, and then Haruhi shows up
and says this...
These two are my
brigade members.
They'll do anything you ask,
so ask for anything you want!
Okay, let's have some fun!
We're going to play water soccer.
Come on!
Well, deja vu isn't
all that uncommon.
Here I go, Mikuru!
Okay!
I'm sorry!
Summer outing, pool, Bon festival,
fireworks show, part-time job, stargazing...
What is this?
I thought about what we'll
be doing from here on.
It's a schedule of
how we'll spend
the rest of our short
summer vacation.
We only have two weeks of
summer vacation left.
And yet it feels like there are
a lot of things we've yet to do.
But we've only got this
much time left.
That's why we're going
to pick up the pace!
Is there anything else
you want to do, Mikuru?
Umm... I'd like to try
goldfish scooping.
Okay!
Goldfish scooping...
Pardon me
for a moment.
Thank you.
Is there a place nearby
having a Bon festival?
A fireworks show
would work, too.
I'll check around.
Don't forget about the
goldfish scooping!
It's Mikuru's sole request,
after all.
Roger that.
Okay, Kyon.
We're starting tomorrow!
Incoming call: Haruhi Suzumiya
The next morning, it was Haruhi
that awoke me from my slumber.
They found a place that was
holding a Bon festival.
It seems to be happening
tonight at a public park.
Both Mikuru and Yuki said that
they don't own a yukata.
So we're going to go buy
some to wear tonight.
I don't own one either,
and there's a place selling them
in sets for cheap!
You're coming too!
Haruhi entered a women's
clothing outlet store.
She just went and chose yukata
for Miss Asahina and Nagato,
and then headed straight
for the changing rooms.
After making us wait about
an hour or so...
(That'd make anyone yawn.)
The three of them finally
came out at once.
Excellent!
You all look wonderful.
Of course! I chose
these yukata, after all.
Especially Mikuru!
It's so cute on you! Just what you
would expect from my choice!
Yes...
Miss Asahina... it's so good,
Miss Asahina!
I guess it makes sense for there
to be this many people.
Hmm? There it is again...
This feeling...
It's been a while since I've
come to a Bon festival,
but it feels like I went
to one recently.
That tower,
those vendors...
This is...
Mikuru!
They have goldfish scooping,
just like you wanted!
This way!
Okay!
Shall we play, too?
I'll pass.
You're interested
in that stuff?
Which one?
I'll buy it...
It's all right.
- This one.
- Right-o.
I kind of got the feeling that
Nagato had been helping us out,
so I thought buying it for her
would be appropriate, but...
Wow, what a haul!
Thirteen!
But I don't need so many, so I
just kept one for each of us.
Huh?
What's with
the mask, Yuki?
I bought it.
I see.
I need to use your back
for a second.
What?
Just turn around!
Hey.
Now then, next up is fireworks!
Let's launch some fireworks
to end the day!
Don't you understand the meaning
of the word "moderation"?
It was summer,
and summer vacation.
That's why I wanted
to forget about it,
but there was one thing
lingering in my mind.
Okay, everyone, tomorrow
we'll be catching bugs!
This will be the SOS Brigade's
Cicada Capturing Competition!
Whoever catches
the most bugs
will get to be the brigade leader
for one day!
Haruhi, it's fine to
want to play around,
but are you finished with
your summer homework?
What are you talking about?
You can finish homework like that
in just three days.
Take care of all of that
bothersome stuff
so you can have fun without
having to worry about it.
That's how you enjoy
your summer vacation!
Why is she so smart?
The next day was yet again
a beautiful day.
It was on this day
that we had the SOS Brigade
Cicada Capturing Competition.
It looks like each of us did try,
in their own way,
but of course, or something
to that effect,
the winner ended up
being Haruhi.
The next day,
we met up,
even though we had no idea
what was going on.
And we continued to have no idea
what was going on,
even as we were made to
wear frog costumes,
and pass out balloons in front of a
supermarket as our part-time job.
Are you all right?
I thought I was going to die.
Actually, I am going to die.
Thanks for the hard work,
especially in this heat.
The manager is thankful.
I don't care about his thanks.
Where's our pay?
This is it.
I've wanted this
for a while.
The owner said that he'd give it to us
for Mikuru's sake.
We worked for that?
Mikuru, you can wear it whenever
you want. You have my permission!
Ribbit.
That night, a single phone call
stole me away from my slumber.
Dammit.
Yes?
Whoa!
Kyon...
Is that you,
Miss Asahina?
Yes, it's me...
Something... very not good has...
At this rate, I...
Umm...
Hello, this is Koizumi.
Why are you
with Miss Asahina?!
Certain circumstances
came up.
Would it be possible for you
to come join us right now?
Of course!
I'll be right there!
What in the world happened,
Miss Asahina?
Kyon... I can't return
to the future!
Can't return?
Err... What do you mean,
can't return?
In other words,
this is what's going on.
We are going through an eternal loop
of the same time period.
What?
We are going through an eternal loop
of the same time period.
We are going through
an eternal loop...
Koizumi, do you realize
what you're saying?
I do. Much more than
I wish I did.
I had just been speaking
with Miss Asahina.
Call me too.
And as a result, what we realized
was that recently,
the flow of time
was a bit strange.
You might want to credit this
to Miss Asahina.
Thanks to her, I was
able to confirm it.
Confirm what?
That we have experienced the same
span of time numerous times.
You said that earlier.
To be precise, we've been
repeating the time
from August 17th
to the 31 st.
We're in the middle of an
endless summer vacation.
Well, we're certainly
in the middle.
It's a never-ending
endless summer.
This world has lost all time
after September 1 st.
That is why Miss Asahina
cannot return to the future.
I suppose you could say
that it's natural
that she can't return to a
future that doesn't exist.
Cut it out. What's natural about
something as stupid as that?
Who'd believe it?
We'd like for you
to believe it.
Umm... I'll explain, too.
Well... because of
"classified information",
I'm always contacting the future
and "classified information"-ing,
but I hadn't received
any "classified information"
for about a week or so,
and I thought, "that's strange."
And so I
"classified information"...
I was so surprised, I tried to "classified",
Miss Asahina, are your "classified"s
but it was completely "classified"...
things that can't be said on TV?
Things that can't be said on TV?
Are we trapped inside one of
those closed spaces?
That's not it.
A single portion of time
has been torn away.
At exactly the point when it becomes
midnight on August 31 st,
everything resets, and we go back to
August 17th. That's the process.
So what about our...
No, humanity's memories?
Those are reset as well. Everything
starts over from the beginning.
So you mean that time does that
thing that you mentioned.
Well, I guess it
can't be helped.
Oh no, Miss Asahina
isn't involved in this.
Okay, then, what is?
I would guess
Miss Suzumiya.
I'm sure she doesn't realize it,
but somewhere inside of her
is a desire to not let
summer vacation end.
Do you mean she feels
regret over something?
That's what I believe.
Perhaps she feels that
there's something left
that she wants to do during
our summer vacation?
Man, the hopeless situations she causes
unfold on a galactic scale.
I've been wondering this
since I got here,
but you seem awfully
cheerful about this.
It's because we've finally
been able to solve
the recent mysterious and frequent
feelings of deja vu that I've had.
Now that I think about it, those inexplicable
feelings may have been
remnants from when our memories
have been reset.
You've been feeling
them too, right?
Is it possible that other people
across the world feel this, too?
You and I
are a special case.
It appears that the people who
are closest to Miss Suzumiya
are able to sense
this strangeness.
What about Haruhi? Does she
sense any of this at all?
Not at all, it seems. It would probably
be bad for us if she did.
However, I believe that there is one
person who remembers everything,
more than the deja vu
that we do.
And who would
that be?
I think you know.
Is that right, Nagato?
It is.
You remember
all of it?
Yes.
So, how many times have we repeated
all of this, this time?
This is the fifteen thousandth,
four hundred and ninety-ninth time.
15,499?
What do you mean by 15,499?
Nagato, what are you saying?
Are you serious?
I am.
You're saying that we've done the
exact same things that many times?
They're not all guaranteed
to happen.
Out of 15,499 repetitions,
there are two occasions,
#2,391 and #11,054, where we
did not go to a Bon festival.
A pattern where we did
go to a Bon festival,
but did not go to a goldfish
scooping stand, occurred 437 times.
We've had a part-time job 9,026 times,
and when we did,
there are six different kinds
of jobs that we did.
In addition to handing
out balloons,
we also worked as movers, cashiers,
we handed out fliers,
worked as call center...
I got it, that's enough.
15,499 times,
that's what Nagato said.
Times two weeks, hmm,
that's around 594 years.
She alone has memories
of all that time,
repeating it all
over and over...
Nagato, how must it feel
to experience that same period
of time over and over again?
I've heard yet another
crazy story.
The next day we
went stargazing.
The location was
Nagato's apartment,
and the telescope was one that
Koizumi had gotten for us.
I'm bored of this.
UFOs. Let's look for UFOs.
Hey! Stop it, Haruhi,
you'll break it!
Exactly what does
she want to do?
Now what could
that be?
If we could figure that out,
this would all be solved...
How about trying
this out?
Give Miss Suzumiya a sudden
embrace from behind,
then whisper "I love you"
into her ear.
And who would
be doing that?
Is there anyone else who could
fill the role other than you?
Consider me out.
All right, how about
if I do it?
I'm kidding. I'm lacking a certain
something for the role.
And all that would
do is cause
unnecessary confusion
in Miss Suzumiya.
We continued to run through a torrent
of summer vacation events.
We went to a batting center,
to a real fireworks show,
and we even took part in a
goby fishing tournament.
We also had a test
of courage,
watched some movies,
went to the beach,
went bowling,
and even to karaoke.
We were always doing something.
Of course, I knew that this wasn't
going to satisfy Haruhi.
Even still, there wasn't anything
I could do about it,
and the last days of our summer
vacation ticked away.
And so we ended up
at August 30th...
With this, we've finished
everything on our list.
Hmm. I wonder if this
was good enough.
But, hmm, well...
I guess this works.
Hey, is there anything else
you want to do?
That's fine, then.
We were able to do
a lot this summer,
so that's enough, right?
No, Haruhi...
You're still not satisfied.
Okay, we're done
for today.
I had tomorrow set aside
just in case,
but you can just
take the day off.
Let's meet again in the clubroom
the day after tomorrow.
Wait, Haruhi.
There it is again!
That deja vu!
And it's a strong one,
stronger than ever before.
I can't let Haruhi leave.
If she goes,
we'll end up repeating
these past two weeks
for the some-thousandth
time again.
But what should I do?
What should I say?
There must have been a hint
somewhere in what Haruhi said.
But what was it?
What has she said
up to this point?
I don't know...
I can't remember...
August 31 st. I haven't
touched my homework.
Whatever, it doesn't
matter anymore.
If we're just going to
do it all over again,
then there's no point
to doing it.
Whether tomorrow
comes or not,
I'll leave it to the me at
that time to deal with it.
Sora kara ochite kitanda
It fell from the sky
Subete no negai wo nosete
With all of the wishes
that were made upon it
Hitotsu no hoshi niwa
chotto omokatta kana
Maybe it was a little too heavy
for a single star
Yappari nanika henda yo
Something just doesn't
seem right
Kokoro no kimi ga kieta
The image of you in my mind
has vanished
Tashika ni oboeteru tte
ieruno kai?
Can I say that I
remember you clearly?
Tomare!
Stop!
Kako wa jibun no mono
The past belongs to me
Touzen daretomo torikaetakunai
Of course I don't want to trade it
with anyone else
Nazenara
That's because
Basudei datta watashitachi niwa
It was my birthday,
and when we saw each other
Deai ga umareta toki ni
We could see the first dream
Hajimete no yume ga mieru
That we had
when we were born
Doushiyouka tte
nayanda koto mo
Worrying about
"what do I do?"
Ima omoeba waraeru hodo
datta yo ne
Is laughable when I
think about it now
Mou wasureteta
I've already forgotten it
Kimi wo sagasou
Let's search for you