Genshiken
I woke up and as usual forgot
my cell and missed the Express.
My life reflected in
the train window.
I'm sure I have something that
I won't lose to anyone in Japan...
... but it's pretty sad
that no one notices it.
I can't run fast, though.
I'm not that strongly-built.
Here I go, at my dauntless pace.
Pass away, today's
sadness, raining in the sun!
Hesitation, repetition,
dreaming all night, all night.
Farewell sadness,
to outer space you go!
Look to the sky and shout
at the top of your lungs!
At this tempo!
Right now, at this tempo!
Genshiken
I'd like a receipt, please.
Y-Yes sir, made out to whom?
The Society for the Study
of Modern Visual Culture.
Visual Culture?
The Society for the Study
of Modern Visual Culture.
Thank you very much!
Episode 9, Concerning Whether Explanation
is Obligatory Under Special Circumstances
Howza!
Yo.
Hi...
Where's Kohsaka?
He went home.
Oh, okay.
Ah, no wonder I can't relax.
This is the first time it's just been
me and Kasukabe alone in the club room.
Why am I dwelling on that
now that a year's gone by?
I should just talk about something.
I was wondering,
did you see yesterday's...
That "Kujiun" thing?
I saw it, or rather it was shown to me.
So what'd you think?
What'd I think?
I couldn't really tell what's going on.
No, no, no, it was well on par, a
masterpiece, on a godlike level even.
I mean, it's Wakada storyboards
and Higashino dramatization.
There's no chance it won't be good.
Oh yeah?
Let me explain!
The anime director's most impressive...
...and interesting combination
of staff is Wakada and Higashino.
The extraordinarily intense devotion
to tempo and layout of Wakada...
...and the way Higashino flawlessly
unites his designs into motion.
I guess the regrettable thing is
that they don't work on many episodes...
...because their animators are a
select team of only people they know.
Select team?
Maybe they don't
really trust the studio?
The director kind of takes
a hands-off approach, too.
Really.
After all, Wakada storyboards are in
high demand for original pictures...
...so if the work were done by unskilled
hands it'd be full of problems to fix.
In that case it's faster for acquaintances
to do it, and probably less stress.
Now I get it.
Now, it's no exaggeration to say that...
...a characteristic of Wakada's
work is how light is drawn.
Oh yeah, the sunlight through
the trees scene was pretty.
Aha, you noticed?
That's it, all right!
For real?
Cool!
Right, as if!
Sorry, it's nothing.
What am I getting all delusional about?
And what the hell, do I
actually want that to happen?
Great, now I'm just being a weirdo...
Talk about something, something.
That's the "Love Letter
from Beyond" series.
Yeah, it's a masterpiece.
But, I wonder if I should
share how moving this is.
That'd be nice.
Leave it be.
I'm so inflexible.
I know full well that reality can't just
be divided up into choices like that.
Well, I'll keep it simple.
Good manga, eh?
She's ignoring me!
No, no, even Kasukabe
wouldn't do that I don't think.
Ah, volume 9!
That's an especially good part, where
Toki and Shiira are finally reunited.
She's engrossed.
Well, that makes me happy in a way.
Madarame: Good manga, eh?
"Whisper of the Flying God" is good too.
Keep quiet.
No! If I don't start doing
something I'll look suspicious.
Eeeek!
No, no, no!
That must never happen!
I'm no one-man comedy troupe!
No way can I take this out in here!
M-Mind if I turn on the TV?
Nah.
Thank you...
Wait, why am I thanking her?
Oh, excuse me.
Do aliens use the bathroom a lot?
When visiting the planet Eldo, women
especially should beware of constipation.
Say what?
I've got it!
I found the aliens' weakness!
There are actually three female aliens!
But there's always two of them...
They look the same so we didn't
notice, but they constantly swap places.
You know, even Kujiun
has its share of issues.
Even when it's for a gag, I don't like
it when they resort to dirty jokes.
The fans eat it up, though.
Maybe the problem is that until now
they've for the most part stayed true...
...to the original story, but starting with
these episodes they stray really far off.
Get set.
I'm sorry, I slipped up.
On your marks.
Get set.
I'm sorry, that time I jumped the gun...
Well...
How should I put it?
I'm getting swept away!
Get set.
S-Should I turn it off?
It'd be best if I did, it's so noisy.
Ah, um...
Uh...
That's weird...
Oh geez.
That's funny, where'd it go?
Uh...
Hmmm...
Ah man, ummm.
Uh no, it's nothing. I'm all right,
that is, I wasn't trying to sneak a peek.
Really, I wasn't.
Oh, right!
So that's it...
Talk about close calls.
Why did I leave?
Why am I running away
after that little stunt?
Although, going back right
away would be unnatural.
This is weird.
Kasukabe being around shouldn't
really bother me this much.
She's far off from my usual range.
She should be the one being careful
and uncomfortable in this situation.
What a joke.
I just I just need to
talk to her more naturally.
Naturally.
Thirsty?
Huh?
No, I'm good.
Here, it's in a can so
nothing weird got put in it.
No, that's not the issue.
There's no need, I don't want it.
Oh, yeah, all right.
Uh...
What?
That's weird, am I way off?
She must think this
is awkward too, right?
Maybe she feels sorry for being rude,
or that it'd be bad to just leave now.
That's it...
That must be it...
How are things?
Did something happen?
Like what?
Like with Kohsaka.
Not especially.
Nothing's amiss?
The usual.
Oh, that sounded kind of iffy.
What gives!
Uh, well, it's rare to
see you act this way...
...staying behind in the club
room after Kohsaka's gone home...
It's like "wow," what a surprise.
What is this, a TV interview?
No, not at all!
It's just a bit mysterious!
I'm not trying to pry at all...
...I just purely though whoa,
I never thought I'd see the day!
Actually, I hate it when people stick their
noses into other peoples' business...
Um, sorry.
Right.
Do we have the next one?
Oh, volume 10?
We sure do!
Umm, it should be around...
Here it is.
You know, "Whisper of the Flying
God" by the same artist is good too.
I'll lend it to you
if you want to read it.
No thanks.
I'm still in the middle of this one.
Quite right, that you are!
Here's volume 10.
Thank you.
Am I that unpleasant?
Am I the Andromeda Strain?
What? Hold on a second.
No girl should have something
like that hanging out of her nose.
This is just too much, too manly even...
No wait, calm down! It might
just be some trash or something.
Or maybe my imagination's
just getting away from me!
I need to not look like I'm staring,
and take another glance to make sure.
In a way, this is an awesome
chance to strike up a conversation.
On second thought, wait.
Wait just a minute...
The way it's hanging, it might
not be attached any longer.
How could a nose hair grow that long?
It'll fall off on its own.
Yeah, it'll fall off.
Or will it?
Even if it will, should she
go out of here like that?
I'd feel bad for her if
anyone else saw her like that.
It'll take another 30 minutes
to finish reading that.
No, Kasukabe's no manga reader
so it'll probably take 45 minutes.
If she's about to leave and it still
hasn't fallen off, I guess I'll mention it.
No, if someone else from Genshiken
shows up before that, forget it.
I can't tell her in
front of someone else...
Hm? What's the matter?
There's something under your nose.
Huh? Where?
Here.
Eek!
This is a nose hair!
You saw it!
I'm so embarrassed!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Yeah, I can do this.
Just keep the mood light.
Here goes.
Leave it be.
In a game when there's only one
choice, it's a real relief...
But then, when it comes to real life...
No, they don't exist!
Heroines don't have
protruding nose hairs!
It's for her sake, but more importantly
I can't let this continue!
If I give in to this, I lose
out to something spiritually.
What spirit I don't know...
But it's okay!
This kind of thing shouldn't
hurt Kasukabe that much!
...I don't think.
Nonchalantly! Naturally!
With a smile on my face...
Don't feel bad...
What's with them?
Talk about serious.
Hey, Madarame.
What do you figure
they're talking about?
Heh, stupid stuff.
Did she start her period or something?
Now he's in trouble!
W-Was I right?
I am so...
What's worse, I was the only one
who didn't get any chocolate that year.
All 18 of those girls hated my guts...
No, being slapped in
public makes one a man.
That was a medal for me.
That'll do for now, anyway.
That's not the problem, though! I need to
draw her attention to this somehow!
I've always been told I didn't
have an attention span...
...now I see what they meant!
Hey.
Just kidding.
There's something under your nose.
Huh?
Hold still.
There, it's gone.
Thank you.
C'mon, less thinking more doing!
Yes! My extraordinary
"delightful face!"
Sorry!
Nah, I'm okay.
I didn't only slap you
just now, I let you have it.
Oh, you did?
I honestly couldn't tell.
Huh? You couldn't?
No, well, seriously.
I'm totally okay.
Oh, the trash fell off.
Huh?
It was, um, stuck under your nose.
Eh...
Uh, wait, where are you going?
Just to go look in a mirror.
Mirror?
Hey, hold on...
No I'm fine, I really mean it.
Sorry, I'm sorry.
It's all cut up.
It couldn't be.
He hasn't come back.
What was that all about?
Dwelling on her...
Even though it's been a whole year...
Or in a way, maybe it's because
it's been a whole year...
We took no detours or shortcuts...
... and we weren't afraid of
what tomorrow would bring...
... as we kept walking down
Inogashira Street late at night.
Only vivid dreams extended
deep into the shadows.
We aren't quite grown up.
Simple but complicated
glistening like marbles.
The time we spied from there sparkled,
even if nothing big happened.
What we see from the marbles in
our hands now is a little different...
... but they shine faintly nearby.
Where is the Holy Land
for people like us?
I guess it would have to be Big Sight?
Wrong.
Then Kamiigusa in Suginami Ward,
or maybe Hitotsubashi or Otowa.
Wrong.
Then, where?
The Takizawa Lounge!
Where they charge 1000 yen
for a cup of coffee?
Yeah, where they say all
the employees are widows!
They also say it's the most
expensive in the business!
Even if you see someone you
know, you don't greet them.
Those are the rules and manners!
Holy Land finalized!