Nothing holds his attention
like an intense game.
Hey, Kohsaka.
Hmm?
Would you rather have been with
a girl who plays games with you?
That's not really important.
You don't choose a girl based on that...
...and you're the way
you are so I don't mind.
Well, maybe that's just
what dating him is like...
But to be honest I feel
miserable right now...
...and it makes me
worry about the future...
He doesn't look at me at all, either...
Oh, sorry, TV time.
Uh, you mean anime?
Yeah, it's about to start.
I've been looking forward to it all day.
I'm sorry I'm gutless,
but this is my limit.
Tokino!
Outside, outside, outside, outside.
Just hold out a little longer!
The heat must be getting
to our opponents too.
Let's talk about something...
Genshiken
I woke up and as usual forgot
my cell and missed the Express.
My life reflected in
the train window.
I'm sure I have something that
I won't lose to anyone in Japan...
... but it's pretty sad
that no one notices it.
I can't run fast, though.
I'm not that strongly-built.
Here I go, at my dauntless pace.
Pass away, today's
sadness, raining in the sun!
Hesitation, repetition,
dreaming all night, all night.
Farewell sadness,
to outer space you go!
Look to the sky and shout
at the top of your lungs!
At this tempo!
Right now, at this tempo!
Genshiken
That again!
That's pretty good, chaining a low
light kick into a standing super.
I can only pull it off about
one in five tries though.
These two sure are a trip to watch.
Episode 6: Subculture and its Circular
Relationship to Others Surrounding It
Ohno.
Isn't your hair too long?
Huh?
I mean, it makes you look kinda scary.
If you cut it, or even just added
some color, it'd lighten up.
Is it like this for cosplay?
Hmm, that's part of it...
...but when I was in America I
couldn't bring myself to dye it.
People told me they envied
how black and straight it was.
I guess they had a
point, but this is Japan.
That's true...
So it's for cosplay?
I guess so.
The salon I go to gives
discounts for referrals.
I'm not used to places
like that, though...
Yeah, bring it on!
Ohno.
Aren't your tits too big?
Huh?
What's your cup size again?
Don't you already know?
Yeah but I forgot.
What?
Oh my god, it takes cups that big
to support those manga-sized tits?
Saki!
F?
G?
It's just like that soccer...
J. League?
W-World Cup?
I'm going to claim sexual harassment.
That's the scary you.
Hey, are you ignoring me?
W-What?
Don't "what" me.
I'm trying to get you to
discuss something with me.
Discuss?
Well you see, this is about
one of my high school friends.
She says she's been
dating an otaku lately.
Oh yeah?
Well, at a glance he seems
different from Kohsaka.
So anyway, when they have sex
at night they leave the TV on.
The guy says it's to mask the
noise since the walls are thin.
But then last night...
Some anime came on during it...
And just before that, they
had switched to doggy style.
I wonder if he was back where she
couldn't see him watching it...
What do you think, Ohno?
Um, well...
Lasting more than 30 minutes is
amazing!
Laughing about it only
digs your own grave.
What about you guys?
Yesterday, you said? What time?
12:30, she said.
Oh, that!
You saw it, didn't you?
Yes, that.
Kujibiki Unbalance
It's quite a highly
rated anime right now.
I watched it too.
So did I.
You don't say...
Then maybe it'd be best
if she cosplayed after all!
I mean, she got a reaction
from cat ears a while back.
A-All right, why don't
I lend her a costume?
I'm sure the size difference
would just make her feel bad.
Besides, I don't think you
want it being used for that.
I see your point.
Um...
You were talking about a friend?
Of course I was.
But what about you two?
If you had a girlfriend, would
you want to have sex in costume?
Uh, well...
I don't even think about that kind
of thing, not having a girlfriend.
Ah, but I have seen cosplay
scenes in adult videos...
They're not very interesting, though.
The women are just porn
actresses, after all.
There are also cosplay
dojinshi, erotic ones.
Yeah, I saw some in a
catalog at Comic Fest.
I wonder if they're on CD-ROM.
Look at me when you're talking.
So anyway, you're going to have to
ask Tanaka about stuff like that.
Hmm...
Then I suppose...
if she liked to cosplay...
...and she understood the character,
it might be kind of fun, maybe.
Like Ohno?
Saki...
Well, you know...
But you wouldn't be able to do that...
...would you?
Not me, it's a friend of mine.
Hey, either way.
The more fundamental question is...
...can your friend become an otaku too?
That's impossible.
But that's what we're thinking
about almost all the time.
Anime, games, not much else.
Even Kohsaka shouldn't be
any exception to the rule.
You think so?
Otherwise he wouldn't
be such a good gamer.
Not to mention, he knows a
lot of system-related info.
Hmm, video games...
I guess games really are his thing.
I couldn't possibly become an otaku...
...but I guess I've got to
play at least one game...
Heh, you will?
It's better than trying to get
his attention with shabby cosplay.
She might find she's an
otaku before she knows it.
Shut up.
After careful consideration, the
game of choice is Puyo Pop Fever.
You connect and pop falling "puyos" in
this latest of the hit puzzle game series.
That's why you rotate it here like this.
Rotate?
You insert it here, these
pop, and these shift down.
Why?
She did it.
Finally.
What?
What? What?
Oh yeah!
Thuddy thud.
No way!
What the hell's with that?
It's no use asking us.
Okay, I'll give it a shot tonight.
Now that was weird.
Kasukabe played a video game.
Stop the world so I can get off.
But, thank goodness she
got to where she can do it.
Playing against Kohsaka, though...
You're right.
He'll have a 5-chain
put together in no time.
Hopefully he'll hold back
against her a little...
Know what, though, she was
talking about herself before...
...I'm sure of it...
So tonight...
I don't like this vibe...
Let's play Puyo Pop!
Huh?
Play me in Puyo Pop.
What's with you?
I played it today at
Genshiken, it was kind of fun.
Wow...
Here we go!
Whadda ya think?
Huh?
Oh?
Yeah!
Hah!
Here I go!
Ice Storm!
Take that!
You're done for!
Ha ha, you suck!
What?
Oh yeah!
Thuddy thud.
All right!
Puyo Pop cosplay.
Does it turn you on?
Well, I mean, you're a puyo.
That night was the last time Saki
Kasukabe ever played a video game...
Hello.
Where's Kohsaka?
In Akihabara...
What, aren't you playing
league matches today?
Looks like it's best not to
pour any more fuel on the fire.
Dammit, if Kohsaka were here,
she could just leave with him.
Oh yeah, that's right.
It's almost been a year
since you joined, Sasahara.
Y-Yeah.
So? Have you grown at all?
Grown?
What do you mean by
"growth" in this case?
Well, I spend a lot more money now.
But I get the feeling that's
just me being out of control...
I can't call myself an otaku
when I don't have my own computer.
Whoa, you say you're not otaku?
No, it's not that.
Maybe I just have a ways to go...
Why don't you buy a computer?
Have you got some
mental block against it?
Not at all.
Like I said before,
I spent all my money.
No, you can buy one!
If you put your mind to
it, you'll find a way.
It's like that proverb...
Think after you buy!
Th-This would be the part
where s-someone smacks you down.
But, that's exactly why I
don't have any money right now.
True.
Oh, that's me.
I don't know this number...
Then don't answer it.
I couldn't do that.
Hello...
Oh hell, it's you!
What's with this big time
un-Sasahara-like attitude?
You switched cell phones again?
Yeah, yeah...
Wait a minute!
No, I'm on my way!
Don't move.
No, not that...
Yeah...
May I ask who?
My little sister's at
the train station...
Wow, you've got a sister!
Trippy.
First a childhood friend, now a sister!
I feel s-so moved.
No, you've got the wrong idea!
She's a fashion slave, a
trashy high school chick.
She wouldn't understand us, in fact
it's best if you don't meet her.
On that note, you don't go for
the "little sister" look at all.
In fighting games you always
use the sexy older female characters.
You're right.
I can say for a fact that fad's
just an illusion for those...
...who don't actually have a sister!
You're such a fool, Sasahara.
Why would I ever need a
little sister I'm related to?
Hah, he's not pulling any punches.
B-But, in a way it's normal.
You'll think she's from
another planet if you see her.
Well, that's how it goes.
Please don't follow me!
We won't.
The station, you said?
So that's her...
Yup, she's got nothing
in common with us...
You can't even see her
face through the make-up.
T-They all look the same.
What do you think she calls him?
Big Brother is right out.
With her, probably "bro."
Or else "h-hey you..."
What's with you guys?
Took you long enough, monkey!
Monkey...
Pity...
You're still saying that?
Whatever, lend me some money.
You mean you came all this way for
that?
My boyfriend and I went
to the park zoo in his car...
...but we had a fight and I got ditched.
My purse's in his car.
Weren't you the one who said...
..."Nothing good comes of
choosing a guy by his looks?"
I know, but it's no use.
I can't stand homely guys.
My friends are all the same way too.
Besides, this is normal.
Now I go home on my own
and we make up big time.
It's the big "in" thing right
now, this whole "test" thing.
I don't get it.
So give me some money.
That wouldn't make it "on your own..."
I'll bet she's the type who's
easily influenced by friends.
Is she?
And it only takes an instant.
I can't see her growing up in
the same household as Sasahara.
What was Sasahara's first name again?
I think it's Kanji...
Y-You can't be...
Hey Kanji!
What're you up to?
I thought you were
gonna hang out with me.
What?
Oh, who's she?
Huh? Eh?
Kasukabe, look...
I asked you not to follow me
because you do things like this.
Way to kill the mood!
You really are a boring guy.
My friend's girlfriend...
You see how she is...
An otaku?
Don't hit her for that just
because she's my sister...
You two look identical in the face.
What the? Is she,
like, always this rude?
Something tells me this
is going to end ugly...
Come on, that's enough, Kasukabe.
You too, Keiko.
What are you guys up to?
They said he went to Akihabara...
That means he went and bought
more pain in the ass otaku crap.
Hello!
My sister.
Hello.
Let's get going, Kohsaka.
This is her real boyfriend.
Huh?
Oh, right!
These are the ones we had on order.
Here's yours.
Thanks...
What a coincidence, they
delivered it right before my eyes.
What's that? Looks big, must be cool.
Well, y'know...
It's about as tall as I am.
Want to see it? They're both the same.
I do, I do, I so want to!
No, don't sweat it. Not here, Kohsaka!
That'd do it...
Y-You called it...
Here it comes...
Kohsaka, let's go.
Sasahara's sister needs to talk to him.
Oh, okay.
Unrolling this huge thing
would get in the way, anyway.
There's no one around, though.
She needs to hurry home, too.
There's a test that
needs passing, right?
Huh?
That's right.
Here's some money, now scram.
I'm in no real hurry.
Right now I want to see this.
Okay, just for a bit.
Ah, not here...
Please wait a moment.
W-What a cute picture.
So looks win out, huh Keiko?
That's really nice.
Isn't it?
She's from a game I really like.
K-Kill me now...
There's no escape now...
She's so not ready for us.
9000 for the tapestry, then
5000 loaned to my sister...
...and I've got a wallet full of air.
See ya.
Sure.
Is there any chance Kohsaka
would quit being an otaku?
Not at all, he's way
more otaku than I am.
He sure doesn't look it!
Kasukabe over there is also
trying to make him quit...
...but from here it looks like she's
walking down a rough and thorny path.
Give it a rest and
stop dwelling on looks.
Just leave it to Kohsaka
to spice up the situation.
That poor little sister.
What do you mean?
That was 9000 yen, though?
If that's how you spend money,
you'll never afford a computer.
Yeah, although...
To not buy what one
likes is to deny oneself.
Sasahara...
While that's true, we're all aware
that you don't own that adult game!
You probably play it at Kohsaka's!
Just buy a computer already!
Don't eat for three months!
That's ridiculous...
W-Why not try cutting back
on games and DVDs for now?
PCs are cheap these days.
Hey, Kohsaka.
Hmm?
Will you watch anime again today?
Uh-uh.
Not today.
We took no detours or shortcuts...
... and we weren't afraid of
what tomorrow would bring...
... as we kept walking down
Inogashira Street late at night.
Only vivid dreams extended
deep into the shadows.
We aren't quite grown up.
Simple but complicated
glistening like marbles.
The time we could see from there
sparkled, even if nothing big happened.
What we see from the marbles in
our hands now is a little different...
... but they shine faintly nearby.
Suioh University
Hey, do you know much about S&M?
Huh?
What?
Heartache's been
feeling good to me recently...
I wonder if that's a kind of S&M...
Hey Ohno, is cosplay fun?
Will you do it?
No, I won't!
I can understand if foreigners do it.
So much is based on western
culture and clothing...
...they don't look that out of place
as fantasy characters and whatnot.
But it just doesn't work for Japanese.
Um...
And then these cosplay
names, why are they in kanji!?
And it's names like Reika and
Sakuya with high stroke counts!
Then their surnames sound like some
court noble. I mean, "Ayanokouji?"
I mean, it's like get
a grip and know thyself.
Saki, you just made enemies of
a million cosplayers nationwide.
Huh? Why?