Help me.
Somebody, help me.
Ima inochi ga hora kizashite chitte yuku
Nigirishimeta unmei
Mou mayou koto wa nai
Musubiau kizuna
Akatsuki matsu sora ni
Aishi kimi dakishimete
Orenai inori wo
Mada dare mo yoru no naka
Ima wa tada
Kokoro no oku ni sawatte
Afureru atsusa subete sasagetai
Yume miru ashita e
Hirogeru tsubasa wa
Ano hi no kimi ga kureta
Omoi wa kizamareta
Chikai no kotoba ga
Kiseki wo okosu yo
Takanaru mune habatake
Tobitateru negai haruka tataku
Feather 2:
"The Door to the New Residence"
The rain's suddenly stopped, and the clouds
look like they've been wrenched apart.
This became lovely moon-viewing sake.
I wonder whose work that was.
Musubi-chan.
Uh... um...
W-What?
I'm sorry, but I didn't
think about how we'd land.
Ouch!
Huh!
Are you all right, Musubi-chan?
Yes, I'm sorry.
Um...
Excuse me, but who are you?
I-I'm sorry... Ouch!
Oh my! You're hurt.
Mi-Minato-san!
Musubi-chan, your clothes!
Ah, they're all torn apart.
So noisy.
Is anybody there?
You are!
That should do it.
Um... I'm so sorry.
Don't worry about it.
I just did what I was asked by Miya.
Miya-san... is her name, then?
- By the way...
- Yes?
How come you guys were there?
Eh?!
It's... uh, um...
You are obligated to maintain
confidentiality whether you like it or not...
Um... we were blown by
a sudden wind... Hee, hee...
Sudden wind, huh?
Ah, well... ha, ha...
Well... I guess we can leave it at that.
Minato-san!
I borrowed a kimono.
Ah, you're like two flowers
standing next to each other.
I-I'm very sorry. Even I ended
up with borrowing clothes from you.
I like to meddle in people's affairs.
My husband was like me, too.
Those were my husband's clothes.
Your husband?
No, that ugly sweat suit is not mine.
He's passed away... her husband.
I-I'm sorry.
No problem at all. It's been a long time.
Ah, I haven't introduced myself.
My name is Miya Asama.
I'm Minato Sahashi.
I'm Musubi.
I'm Kagari. Nice to meet you.
Ah. Nice to meet you.
Huh? Sniff, sniff...
Smells delicious!
I was preparing for dinner.
Would you like to join us?
But we have already
caused enough troubles to you.
"Grumble"
But we have already
caused enough troubles to you.
"Grumble"
Musubi-chan!
Thanks for the food!
It's so good!
Yeah, it's really delicious.
Ah, I'm so hungry!
Huh? Do we have guests?
Uzume, I always tell you not
to leave your room dressed like that.
Why not? I'm wearing panties.
- Uh, excuse me...
- Yes?
I may be asking a rude question, but...
What's with this house?
I mean, you don't look like a family.
Ah, this place is...
"Maison Izumo"
"Room for Rent... Maison Izumo...
Two meals a day included,
Rent is 50,000 yen/ month..."
"Room for Rent... Maison Izumo...
Two meals a day included,
Rent is 50,000 yen/ month..."
A board house?!
Yes. I'm the owner,
and they are my tenants.
Well, nobody but weirdoes like us
want to live in such a battered
and cheap board house these days.
So we're perennially
looking for new tenants.
Battered?
No, no, more like it's got "charm,"
or it's old-fashioned... you know?
Looking for new tenants?
I beg you!
We were kicked out of our
apartment and have nowhere to go.
Please raise your head.
My late husband was a person who
never rejected anybody who came.
Then...
Welcome to Maison Izumo.
Minato-san!
M-Musubi-chan!
That's great, isn't it!
Miya, are you sure you
should accept them so easily?
- If they reached here by chance,
it must be fate.
- Musubi-chan, it's all because of you.
- This must be the work
of the gods and goddesses.
- Oh no, it's because Minato-san worked hard.
There's no reason to
reject them, whoever they may be.
I see. If you've already made up your mind,
I have nothing to say anymore.
Well, let's talk about the details.
Yes.
Takami-san!
What? The last number?
I understand. I'll keep watch, anyway.
This will be trouble.
Next news.
"Shintou Teito Arboretum"
"Abnormal Growth of Plants"
Next news.
"Shintou Teito Arboretum"
"Abnormal Growth of Plants"
Regarding the abnormal
growth of the plants in the arboretum,
its management company,
MBI is taking this case seriously...
Ah, I forgot!
Oh, Mom?
I'm going to be moving.
Moving?!
What are you thinking at a time like this?!
Ah, um... about my allowance...
Halved!
Eh!
I'll send you half the amount
until you pass the entrance exam.
If you are a man,
show me your guts!
I'm busy, so I'm hanging up.
Wait! Mom!
Ah, Minato-san...
Huh? What do you need?
We're out of shampoo...
"Natural Shampoo"
I'm sorry.
Hmm, at times like this...
Oh... modesty is difficult!
Well... Everyone has some strengths
and weaknesses... What am I saying?
This is not a place for someone
like you to be this late at night.
I don't have anywhere to go home to.
You are a rare one, aren't you?
Ashi... kabi?
I'll let you join... my collection.
Come on.
This is it... I think.
Yes?
Hey, long time, no see, Big Bro.
Yukari?! Why are you?
What a mess!
Why?
What are you talking about?
It was you who told me to bring some clothes.
I told you to send them.
I didn't tell you to come out from the country.
I came to see the city 'cause
I was accepted to college here.
I hadn't heard that!
It was not so easy to tell you
since I just heard from Mother about you
failing the entrance exam for the second time.
"Failed Twice"
since I just heard from Mother about you
failing the entrance exam for the second time.
Since I just heard from Mother about you
Ah, by the way, Mother seems
to be here now for her job as well.
Minato-san!
Where should I put this luggage?
Ah, she is...
Ah-huh, so this is what's happening.
No, there are lots of reasons for this...
So these clothes are for her tastes.
- Pardon?
- Hey, try to listen to me at least.
I'm his younger sister, Yukari.
Nice to meet to you!
Ah! You're Minato-san's little sister.
I'm Minato-san's Seki...
Oops!
Musubi-chan, confidentiality, confidentiality!
Oh, you're right.
Hey, enough with the PDA.
It's broad daylight still, you know.
Huh? Oh no! I'm sorry!
But anyway... why did you move so suddenly?
Well, many things have happened.
I finished cleaning the kitchen.
Okay, then, let's wipe the floor together.
Yes!
Why did you have her change?
Because I brought them all the way here.
Don't you want to see
her in those clothes, Big bro?
You must be misunderstanding something.
Huh?
Well, I promised to stay
over at my friend's house.
Yeah, I'll e-mail you my new address later.
Musubi-tan, let's take
a bath together next time.
Yes!
You!
Ah-huh!
You haven't touched these yet, have you?
Well, that...
Just kidding. See ya, Big Bro, Musubi-tan!
Yukari!
You two are close.
We don't have a father, and our
mother's always busy at her job.
So we spent a lot of time together.
Well, we'd better start going too.
Yes!
You are so strong.
Because I'm a fist-type.
This is nothing for me.
A "fist-type"?
Then those two who attacked us
the other day are... lightning-type?
I guess so.
By the way, when you caused the
twister, you were saying something.
That was an incantation.
An incantation?
Well... the special words
to chant when we use major power.
Every Sekirei has his or her own incantation.
I see.
Our new lives start right here.
Welcome!
I was waiting for you. Come on in, please!
Yes, I'm indebted to you.
Yours will be room 202.
Please go ahead.
Wow!
I've already cleaned.
Thank you very much.
Minato-san, I'm stuck and I can't move.
"Creak!"
Ah! Musubi-chan!
"15 Minutes Later"
We finally... made it.
Musubi-san, you are so strong.
Yes! Because I am a fist-type Sekirei.
You are a funny person.
Now, please come
downstairs once you settle in.
Yes.
Musubi-chan...
Yes?
The Sekirei Plan is
supposed to be confidential, isn't it?
You shouldn't say things
like "fist-type" and "Sekirei"...
Ah! I got careless...
I hope it'll be all right.
Don't worry.
Whatever the President will do to you,
everything will be fine
as long as we're together.
Whatever happens to you,
I will protect you without fail.
Oh no! What a loser I am!
A girl said she'll protect me, then I
felt oh so happy, and ah so relieved!
Minato-san?
Ah, yes, thank you.
Shall we put this stuff away?
Yes!
Um... Musubi-chan?
Yes?
Ah, well...
Thank you for your continuing support.
Yes, for many years to come.
Sekirei Number 88 and her Ashikabi...
Kagari-san, are you leaving?
Yes, I'm going to work.
Oh, you're leaving early today.
I've already prepared dinner for you.
I'm sorry. I promise to eat it when I'm back.
My.
See you, then.
Kagari-san is working at a host club.
A host... I see.
I heard he is the number one
host in the club. Isn't it amazing?
A host?
Musubi-chan, do you wish such a
cool guy would do those things to you?
I'd like you to do
anything to me, Minato-san.
Anything?! Musubi-chan,
what do you mean anything?!
Minato-san... Minato-san... Minato-san...
Anything!
Dinner will be ready soon, so how
about taking a bath before that?
Wow, a bath!
Wow! What a spacious bath!
We can take a bath together,
and I can wash your back comfortably.
No! I'll take a bath later!
Huh? Minato-san?
I think I'd get dizzy
before I got in the bath...
Hot!
I wanted to wash Minato-san's back...
Huh? Is anybody in there?
Ah! You're the new resident!
How could we survive even
though we fell from so high?
I guess this tree became a cushion.
Help me!
I'm Uzume of room 203. Nice to meet you.
I'm Musubi. Nice to meet you.
Ah, Sekirei symbol! You are a Sekirei!
See? Me too, me too!
Ah! What was... that?!
Now that I think of it, I saw her then, too...
What the?!
Whoa! Wait a sec!
I'm so excited!
Listen to me first!
I'm Sekirei number 88, Musubi, a fist-type!
This is my first real fight.
I'm inexperienced, but I'll do my best!
"Do your best"?
Here I come!
Time-out! Time-out!
I can't play with you now!
Modesty, modesty.
Hey you! You are her master, aren't you?
Heh?
I don't feel like fighting.
So, can you stop her?
Huh?
Ah! Get away from Minato-san!
Get away from Minato-san!
Mu-Mu-Mu-Musubi-chan. Stop, please!
Yeah, yeah.
Get away from... Minato-san!
Hey!
Girls shouldn't run around
dressed like that. It is disgraceful.
Yes Ma'am. I'm sorry.
Hee, hee, you've got in trouble.
Uzume-san, you too!
Yes.
I won't dare to ask you
the reason for all this,
but I will never allow any
violence in Maison Izumo...
Do you understand?
Y-Yes...
Dinner will be ready soon.
Miya is... very, very scary
when she's get angry.
She's laughing...
"From the President: There is an
un-emerged Sekirei in the arboretum!
First one there wins! It could be you
who makes the Green Girl emerge!"
These abnormally proliferating plants...
I feel something disquieting...
It's really like a stone door made of plants.
Homura!
It is thy misfortune that we meet here!
Today is the day we settle the
question of who is the strongest!
I'm really busy, you see.
Wait! Coward!
You'd better stop playing
around and go find your master.
Homura!
I don't admit... I don't admit it!
Ashikabis are just base monkeys!
Instead of having bodily
contact with such a being...
I shall finish him off
before my body is violated!
You can't get down?
Don't worry. You are just fine.
So, come on. I'll catch you.
Now... what's your name?
Ku-Kusano...
Ku-chan, huh? That's a cute name.
Hey, why were you crying?
It's all Ku's fault. Because Ku
selfishly said she wanted to go outside...
Help me...
Please help me, big brother...
Ku-chan!
Help me!
- Ku-chan...
- Minato-san?
Minato-san... Minato-san!
Musubi-chan?
You seemed to suffer from a
nightmare... Are you all right?
I was having a dream...
A dream?
The green stone door is still closed.
If we don't take action soon, those who
are after that will come to gather here.
I understand.
"Teito Arboretum"
Help me... help me, big brother...
Yo, baby girls! Get ready now!
This is renai no shinansho
Don't let it go, aserazu so
Without furaingu de show time
Get the funky beat!
Hayai mono gachi?
Kono bayai wa kankei nai nai
Nozomu tokoro yo
Soudatsusen boppzatsu
Onna desu mono, maketerareya shinai nai
Fukuramu kimochi
No mou daibakuhatsu
Dame yo, yuuwaku shicha
Doite, kare no osoba
Watashi dokidoki natte ippai ippai
Naisho, nukekake shite
Daiseikou, kare to futari
Amaku mekurumeku night
Honto wa ne, watashi dake wo
Dakishimete hoshii no
Hitorijime mura mura
Furagu tatechau no ari kashira?
Yappari ne, yowaki, dou shiyou
Yasashisugite shou ga nai
Sonna toko daisuki yo
Dakara watashitachi tsukushimasu
Dear Sweet Heart!
It's Miya.
Our Maison Izumo has added new
residents and become even more festive.
But this is certainly not "Girls Next Door"
or one of those programs,
so please don't misunderstand.
The third episode: "The Green Girl."
Feather 3:
"The Green Girl"
The third episode: "The Green Girl."
Feather 3:
"The Green Girl"
Please favor us again next time!
Feather 3:
"The Green Girl"