Something seems off.
It just somehow felt that way.
And this one's... a left fly ball.
One out, with the score still seven to zero.
I had absolutely no interest in the
prefectural baseball game on TV,
And this one's... a left fly ball.
One out, with the score still seven to zero.
But I ended up
watching it anyways.
The gap between the
scores is big,
but I ended up
watching it anyways.
The gap between the
scores is big,
Once I did, I kind of got the feeling that
Haruhi was going to start something.
But Kumamoto still has a chance
if they can hold out here.
Once I did, I kind of got the feeling that
Haruhi was going to start something.
But Kumamoto still has a chance
if they can hold out here.
Incoming call: Haruhi Suzumiya
Once I did, I kind of got the feeling that
Haruhi was going to start something.
The passionate voices cheering from the
third base bleachers have not died down.
There's Suzuki, they need him to do
his best, don't they, Mr. Kiru?
Kyon, the phone's ringing.
There's Suzuki, they need him to do
his best, don't they, Mr. Kiru?
I know, you don't have
to tell me.
That's true.
I know, you don't have
to tell me.
After all, you never know how a match is
going to turn out. They still have hope.
I know, you don't have
to tell me.
After all, you never know how a match is
going to turn out. They still have hope.
Kyon, you're not doing
anything today, right?
Right.
We're all meeting at exactly
two o'clock in front of the station.
Next, stepping up to the batter's box we
have number four, Kashima, a senior.
We're all meeting at exactly
two o'clock in front of the station.
Next, stepping up to the batter's box we
have number four, Kashima, a senior.
Be sure to show up.
Next, stepping up to the batter's box we
have number four, Kashima, a senior.
After last year's summer tournament, he
was chosen for the team that went to Cuba.
I didn't even
say anything...
In the fourth inning,
he hit a three-run home run.
I didn't even
say anything...
In the fourth inning,
he hit a three-run home run.
And there's Suzuki
with a big windup...
What?
And there's Suzuki
with a big windup...
I forgot to mention this - bring
a swimsuit and plenty of money.
And the first pitch is a strike.
No problems there.
I forgot to mention this - bring
a swimsuit and plenty of money.
And be sure-
That was a good pitch.
To bring my bike, right?
That was a strong, straight pitch,
thrown a little high and inside.
To bring my bike, right?
That was a strong, straight pitch,
thrown a little high and inside.
That's right.
You've got it.
Perhaps he feels like
he's got nothing left to lose.
That's right.
You've got it.
Perhaps he feels like
he's got nothing left to lose.
If you're late,
you're paying again.
We don't know that yet.
He winds up for the second pitch...
If you're late,
you're paying again.
We don't know that yet.
He winds up for the second pitch...
Why did I know about
the bike thing just now?
It's a hit!
And it's a big one!
It's headed for
left field...
I think that one's
going to make it.
And it's good!
See?
It's a single-run home run! And with this,
Jyonan's gotten their eighth run!
I wonder where
I put my swimsuit.
This gives them
yet another point.
Summer's almost over.
DAY BY DAY unzari dayone dakara
Day by day, everything's just so dull
doudou to kotowacchau
kimi ni narina yo
that's why you need to become someone
that can just reject it all
OH MY BOY kippari shinakya uso ni
Oh my boy, you need
to be decisive
tsukiatterarenai yo
semai sekai de
I won't deal with any lies
in this small world
jibun de mitsuketa MYSELF
suki ni natte touzen
I found myself on my own,
it's natural you'd fall for me
kudaranai yarikara kette
subete wa atashi ga kimeru
Kick away the boring ways of doing things,
I'm going to decide everything
I SAY I SAY MY HEAVEN
I say, I say my heaven
SUPER DRIVER tosshin
makasete nantettate zenshin
Super driver, leave everything to the rush
and just keep going forward, no matter what
fukanou (DON'T YOU STOP ME)
Tobikoete TAKE IT EASY, GO!
Surpass (Don't you stop me) the idea
of "impossible," take it easy, go!
Daishouri tte doukan
I agree, it's going
to be a huge victory
mochiron dounatta tte kaikan
Of course, it'll feel pleasant,
no matter what happens
hanseikai? (GET BACK TO WILD)
Sore yori saa isoide yo
A review meeting? (Get back to wild)
Forget that, now hurry up
aremo koremo mitaiken
itsudatte muriyari
We haven't tried this or that,
we always do things how we want to
marude marude mikeiken
korekara shimashou
Everything's a new experience,
let's try them out
aremo koremo mitaiken
itsudatte totsuzen
We haven't tried this or that,
we always do things suddenly
marude marude mikeiken
sore ga doushita no?
Everything's a new experience,
what about it?
Endless Eight
You're late, Kyon!
Yeah, yeah.
Sorry I'm late.
I just got here, too.
Jeez. Show some more
motivation.
- Okay, we're all here, so let's go.
- Where are we going?
To the public swimming pool,
of course!
Well, I guess that makes sense
considering what I brought.
We have to do summer vacation-y things
during our summer vacation!
Well, I guess that makes sense
considering what I brought.
We can never get back
the time that we've lost!
And so we're going to do them now, in our
one and only summer as tenth graders.
- Hey, Kyon! Are you listening?
- Y-Yeah.
By the way, we're going
to the pool by bike.
Okay. Where did you
park your bikes?
No, the only two bikes we have
are yours and mine.
In other words. You're saying.
This is what you meant!?
Kyon, you'd better not lose
to Koizumi.
This train is leaving
the station!
You demon!
You fiend!
Come on, Kyon! We're about to go have
fun. This is no time to be exhausted.
Whose fault do you
think this is?
Yeah, look at all
the people.
Oh, the scent of chlorine.
This really makes it feel like a pool!
Come on, let's find a place to
put our stuff and get swimming!
Hey, wait-
No diving
It's dangerous!
Hey, wait-
No diving
It's dangerous!
Can't she read the "no diving" signs
posted everywhere?
The water's warm
so it feels fine!
Mikuru! Yuki!
Get in here!
Please go on ahead. We'll never hear
the end of it if we leave her be.
Okay, then...
Please wait up,
Miss Suzumiya!
Oh, you're so slow!
Oh, wait, please don't pull-
This just feels kind of peaceful,
you know?
I mean Miss Suzumiya.
She has some rather normal ways of
enjoying her time, don't you think?
Calling out of the blue to invite someone
out to do something and only giving
a general idea of what's going to
happen isn't what I'd call "normal".
In my opinion,
that's really nothing.
Miss Suzumiya, laughing and having
a good time like that,
isn't likely to shake up
the world, after all.
I hope that's the case...
What's wrong?
It's nothing...
It's probably just
my imagination.
Because so much has happened
since the beginning of spring,
I've become
a little paranoid.
That's weird.
Him, too?
Hey now, stop and let me
catch you already!
Yeesh.
Hey now, stop and let me
catch you already!
I think it would be better to call this place
a communal pool than a public pool.
That's where she's been?
What's she doing over there
by herself?
What the...
What is this feeling?
It feels like I've seen this scene...
Seen Nagato like this once before...
Kyon!
Haruhi...
Right, and then Haruhi
says this...
"These two are my brigade members.
They'll do anything you ask, so ask-"
For anything you want!
We're going to play water soccer.
Everyone has to join in. Yuki!
Have I gained precognitive powers
or something?
Here's the ball,
Kyon.
Doesn't seem that way.
I guess it happens every now and then.
Deja vu isn't all that uncommon.
I thought about what we'll be doing
from here on.
What is that?
It's a schedule of how we'll spend the
rest of our short summer vacation.
- There're just two weeks of vacation left.
- All this, in under two weeks?
Is there anything else
you want to do, Mikuru?
Umm... I'd like to try
goldfish scooping...
Okay!
Goldfish scooping...
Pardon me
for a moment.
Thank you.
Okay then,
we're starting tomorrow!
Is there a place nearby with a Bon festival?
A fireworks show works, too.
I'll check around.
I'll contact you when I find out.
Don't forget about
the goldfish scooping!
It's Mikuru's one request,
after all.
I'm paying again?
I told you that you were going to pay
if you were late, didn't I?
All right, then, we're done
for today! Bye!
- If you'll excuse me.
- I have to go, too...
Okay.
Nagato.
Umm... no, it's
nothing important, but...
How have you been?
Everything fine?
Fine.
I see.
That's good to hear.
Right.
Well, that was it.
Sorry for stopping you.
What the heck?
Why did I talk
to her?
The next morning,
I got another call from Haruhi.
They found a place that was
holding a Bon festival.
It seems to be happening tonight
at a public park.
Sorry to keep you
waiting!
About time!
You all look wonderful.
Of course!
I chose these yukata, after all.
Especially Mikuru! Just what you
would expect from my choice!
- Miss Asahina, you look great... just great!
- Oh, you're making me blush...
Hmm, I wonder where the things
we care about are.
What the? It feels like
I've been here recently.
That tower, those vendors,
I kind of remember them...
Oh, Mikuru!
Look, they have goldfish scooping,
just like you wanted!
Let's catch a bunch!
M-Miss Suzumiya,
please wait!
Shall we play, too?
Nah, I'll pass.
What about you, Nagato?
Want to eat something?
You're interested
in that stuff?
- Which one?
- It's all right.
- This one.
- Right-o, that'll be 800 yen.
I kind of got the feeling that
Nagato had been helping us out,
...so I thought it would be appropriate
for me to at least buy her that, but...
Thirteen!
But I don't need so many,
so I just kept one for each of us.
You can have one,
but only one.
Thanks.
Huh? What's with
the mask, Yuki?
I bought it.
I see.
Now then, next up
is fireworks!
Let's launch some fireworks
to end the day!
It was summer,
and summer vacation.
That's why I wanted
to forget about it,
but there was one thing
lingering in my mind.
Tomorrow we'll be
catching bugs.
Haruhi.
It's fine to want to play around, but are
you finished with your summer homework?
Homework?
You can finish homework like that
in just three days.
Wha-
You get that stuff out of the way so you can
have fun without having to worry about it.
That's how you enjoy
your summer vacation.
Why is heaven
so unfair?
Everyone, tomorrow we'll be
catching bugs!
And we're only going
to catch cicadas!
This will be the SOS Brigade's
Cicada Capturing Competition!
The next day was yet again
a beautiful day.
Yay! Wait up!
The next day was yet again
a beautiful day.
Yay! Wait up!
It was on this day that we had the SOS
Brigade Cicada Capturing Competition.
I said, wait! I'm gonna get you!
It was on this day that we had the SOS
Brigade Cicada Capturing Competition.
I said, wait! I'm gonna get you!
It looks like each of us did try,
in their own way,
but of course, or something to that effect,
the winner ended up being Haruhi.
A catch and release attitude
is important, right?
If we let them go, then they
might come back to repay us.
What are you expecting from a
short-lived insect like a cicada?
For some reason, I kind of feel like
Pandora opening her box.
The next day, we met up, and even though
we had no idea what was going on,
we ended up wearing frog costumes
and passing out balloons
in front of a supermarket
as our part-time job.
Now I know how the Gundam Virtue
feels after it's released its armor.
Good work, everyone.
What's with this difference
in how we're being treated?
Thanks for the hard work.
The manager is thankful.
I don't care about his thanks.
Where's our pay?
This is it.
I've wanted this
for a while.
The owner said that he'd
give it to us for Mikuru's sake.
We worked, sweat pouring down
our foreheads, for that?
Let's hang this up in the
clubroom as a memento.
Mikuru, you can wear it whenever
you want. You have my permission!
Umm... well... thank you
very much.
That night, a single phone call
stole me away from my slumber.
Shut up...
Shut up... Dammit...
Yes?
Kyon...
Miss Asahina?
Yes, it's me...
Something... very not good has...
At this rate, I...
- Umm...
- Hello, this is Koizumi.
Why are you with
Miss Asahina?
Certain circumstances
came up.
Would it be possible for you
to come join us right now?
I'll be right there!
I'll be ri~ght there!
Miss Asahina!
What in the world happened?
K-Kyon...
I... can't go back to the future...
The... the... the future?
In other words,
this is what's going on.
We are going through an eternal loop
of the same time period.
Even if you can say something as impossible
as that with a smile on your face...
Koizumi, do you realize
what you're saying?
I do. Much more than
I wish I did.
I had just been speaking
with Miss Asahina.
Call me too, when you
have talks with her.
And as a result, what we realized
was that recently,
the flow of time
was a bit strange.
You might want to credit this
to Miss Asahina.
Thanks to her,
I was able to confirm it.
Confirm what?
That we have experienced the same
span of time numerous times.
You said that earlier.
To be precise, we've been repeating
the time from August 17th to the 31 st.
We're in the middle of an
endless summer vacation.
Well, it is
summer vacation, but...
It's a never-ending
endless summer.
This world has lost all time
after September 1 st.
That is why Miss Asahina
cannot go back to the future.
I suppose you could say
that it's natural.
What's natural about there
being no future?
Who'd believe it?
We'd like for you to believe it,
at the very least.
Are we trapped inside one of
those closed spaces?
No, that's not it.
A single portion of time
has been torn away.
At exactly the point when it becomes
midnight on August 31 st,
everything resets, and we go back
to August 17th. That's the process.
So you mean that time does
that thing that you mentioned.
Well, we do have someone from the future
here, I guess it can't be helped.
Oh no, Miss Asahina
isn't involved in this.
Okay then,
what's the culprit?
I would guess
Miss Suzumiya.
I'm sure she doesn't realize it,
but somewhere inside of her...
is a desire to not let
summer vacation end.
What the heck? Do you mean she
feels regret over something?
That's what I believe.
Perhaps she feels that
there's something left...
that she wants to do
during our summer vacation?
So, what are you saying
I should do?
If we knew that, we would
have this problem solved.
You seem awfully cheerful
about this.
It's because we've finally
been able to solve...
the mystery of the frequent feelings
of deja vu that I've had lately.
Is it possible that other people
across the world feel this, too?
It doesn't seem that way.
You and I are a special case.
It appears that the people who
are closest to Miss Suzumiya...
are able to sense
this strangeness.
What about Haruhi? Does she
sense any of this at all?
Not at all, it seems. It would
probably be bad for us if she did.
However, I believe that there is one
person who remembers everything,
more than the deja vu
that we do.
That's an awfully unhappy thought.
And who would that be?
I think you know,
even without my saying.
I believe that the Thought Entity, which
transcends time and space, would.
- Is that right, Nagato?
- It is.
- You remember all of it?
- Right.
So, how many times have we repeated
all of this, this time?
This is the 15,513th time.
15,513?
What do you mean by 15,513?
Nagato, what are you saying?
Are you serious?
I am.
You're saying that we've done the
exact same things that many times?
They're not all guaranteed
to happen.
Which means?
Out of 15,513 repetitions,
there are two occasions,
#2,391 and #11,054, where we
did not go to a Bon festival.
A pattern where we did
go to a Bon festival,
but did not go to a goldfish scooping
stand, occurred 437 times.
We've had a part-time job
9,031 times, and in those instances,
we have done six different
kinds of jobs.
In addition to handing out balloons,
we also worked as movers, cashiers,
handed out flyers, worked as call center-
I got it, that's enough.
Handed out flyers, worked as call center-
15,513 times.
That's what Nagato said.
Times two weeks, hmm,
that's around 594 years.
She alone has memories
of all that time,
repeating it all
over and over...
Nagato, how must it feel to experience that
same period of time over and over again?
I wonder if they exist.
Martians.
I kind of don't
want them to.
They're probably a reserved people,
living underground.
They're probably friendly.
There's no guarantee
of that.
I'm bored of this.
UFOs. Let's look for UFOs.
Exactly what does
she want to do?
Now what could
that be?
If we could figure that out,
this would all be solved...
Oh, how about
trying this out?
Give Miss Suzumiya a sudden
embrace from behind,
then whisper "I love you"
into her ear.
And who would be
doing that?
Is there anyone else who could
fill the role other than you?
I'm exercising my right to veto.
In other words, I'm not going to.
I guess it can't be helped.
All right, how about if I do it?
I'm kidding. I'm lacking a certain
something for the role.
And all that would do is cause unnecessary
confusion in Miss Suzumiya.
Hey, Nagato,
you were aware of this loop before
Miss Asahina said anything, right?
Yes.
If that's the case,
why didn't you say anything?
It's my job
to observe.
I see...
All right!
Look, I got a home run!
Yay! I did it!
We were always
doing something.
We went to a real
fireworks show,
and we even took part in
a goby fishing tournament.
We also did a test of courage,
went to the beach,
went bowling, sang karaoke,
and watched some movies.
Of course, I knew that this wasn't
going to satisfy Haruhi.
Even still, there wasn't anything
I could do about it,
...and the last days of our summer
vacation ticked away.
And so we ended up
at August 30th...
With this, we've finished
everything on our list.
I wonder if this
was good enough.
But, hmm, well...
I guess this works.
Hey, is there anything else
you want to do?
That's fine, then.
We were able to do a lot this summer,
so that's enough, right?
No, it's not.
You're still not satisfied.
Okay, we're done
for today.
I had tomorrow set aside just in case,
but you can just take the day off.
Let's meet again in the clubroom
the day after tomorrow.
Wait...
Wait, Haruhi.
No, I can't let
you go!
If she goes, we'll end up repeating
these past two weeks
for the some-thousandth
time again.
But what should I do?
What should I say?
There must have been a hint
somewhere in what Haruhi said.
But what was it?
What has she said
up to this point?
It's no use.
I don't know...
Wait... wait...
Haruhi!
Thank you very much!
August 31 st. I haven't
touched my homework.
Whatever, it doesn't
matter anymore.
If we're just going to do it all over again,
then there's no point to doing it.
Whether tomorrow comes or not, I'll leave
it to the me at that time to deal with it.
Sora kara ochite kitanda
It fell from the sky
subete no negai wo nosete
With all of the wishes
that were made upon it
hitotsu no hoshi niwa
chotto omokatta kana
Maybe it was a little too heavy
for a single star
yappari nanika henda yo
Something just doesn't
seem right
kokoro no kimi ga kieta
The image of you in my mind
has vanished
tashika ni oboeteru tte
ieruno kai?
Can I say that
I remember you clearly?
Tomare!
Stop!
Kako wa jibun no mono
The past belongs
to me
touzen daretomo torikaetakunai
Of course I don't want to trade it
with anyone else
nazenara
That's because
basudei datta watashitachi niwa
It was my birthday,
and when we saw each other
deai ga umareta toki ni
We could see
the first dream
hajimete no yume ga mieru
That we had when
we were born
doushiyouka tte
nayanda koto mo
Worrying about
"what do I do?"
Ima omoeba waraeru hodo
datta yo ne
Is laughable when I
think about it now
mou wasureteta
I've already forgotten it
kimi wo sagasou
Let's search
for you