Princess?
What is the matter? You're here
alone, and so late at night...
I have an urgent request
to make of you two in secret.
A history of the couple's romance
that starts from the first kiss
You, the one who cast magic on
this destiny, suddenly appeared
The sky where two moons
never fade away
That's an impossibility, right?
This is the first time I've
felt anything like this
I'm feeling more and more
at ease with this place
Even if you trip and
become depressed
I will always hold you
tight with a squeeze
The story where we met that day
stays hot with a sweet kiss
See, you can cast magic, and
the wishes will surely come true
A history of the couple's romance
that starts from the first kiss
You, the one who cast magic on
this destiny, suddenly appeared
A Princess's Request
I have decided to marry
into a family in Germania.
What did you say?!
Of all things, the country of all
those savage upstart nobles?!
It cannot be helped.
To protect our small
country of Tristein,
we need a strong
alliance with Germania.
A marriage of convenience
to the country?
You stay quiet!
Even if it's for our country,
to face such a hardship...
I am the princess of Tristein.
I do not mind sacrificing myself
for the sake of the country.
However...
However, there is one thing
that I must do before that.
Princess!
If there is anything that I can do,
please tell me to do so!
Thank you, Louise Françoise.
I would like you to
retrieve a certain item.
A certain item?
A letter that I sent to
Prince Wales in Albion.
Albion?
If the world finds out
about that letter,
this engagement will be called off.
Princess...
What kind of letter is it,
that would ruin a marriage...
I told you to keep quiet!
Albion is currently politically unstable,
and in a dangerous
situation right now.
I hear the nobles
started a coup d'etat,
and the royal family is about
to fall from their reign.
I'm sorry,
for even asking such a close friend
to do such a thing...
I...
But now, you two are the only ones
I can ask such a thing!
Thank you so much, Princess.
Louise Françoise...
To request me to perform
such an important mission...
I could not be happier.
Louise...
Then, will you go for me?
Who is it?!
Guiche!
I have heard everything.
Weren't you just eavesdropping?!
Please ask me, Guiche de Grammont,
anything you wish...
Don't be so reckless!
Grammont?
Then, you must be
General Grammont's...
I am his son.
You will be of service to me as well?
So Guiche is going to
tag along after all?
He's just going to get in the way.
I think I just heard some noise...
Oh, well.
Um...
Oh, Siesta.
I'm terribly sorry.
That bit about the love potion
really was true.
I was so rude to you, Mr. Saito.
You shouldn't worry about it.
Louise is back to normal too.
If it is Gundolf, it is worth believing.
Gundolf again, huh...
Hey, who at this school has
a detailed knowledge of history?
History, is it?
Originally, there were
five elements of magic,
not just Fire, Water, Air, and Earth.
The five elements are said to have
been the pinnacles of the pentagon.
That lost apex is the element of Void.
Gundolf is the familiar of
the legendary Void mage.
Void mage?
However, in modern times,
no mage has been confirmed
to have Void magic.
The rune that appeared on your hand
closely resembles that of Gundolf.
But...
As long as no Void mage exists,
unfortunately, we cannot be certain
that you really are Gundolf.
The master is far from legendary,
the way she is.
I thought something smelled.
Is this it?
That is the blood of a dragon.
Dragon's blood?
In the past, two dragons
never seen before
appeared in the skies
with a tremendous roar.
One of them disappeared,
and the other fell
somewhere, they say.
I happened to come across blood
that was said to have been
shed at that time.
I am in the middle of replicating it.
This is blood?
I mean, this smell...
Prince Wales of Albion and
our princess are cousins.
Cousins, and childhood friends?
Louise?
I'm not any good at magic.
Can I go through with
such an important job?
What are you doing?
Nothing will get done if you worry.
We got through everything
in the past somehow, right?
Must be nice to be so easy-going.
You know...
What?
If something happens,
I'll protect you.
Of course, that's to be expected!
You're my familiar!
Oh, yeah, yeah.
This is the Ruby of Water, that my
mother has entrusted me with.
Right now, this is the only
reward that I can give you.
Princess...
I will send one of
the guards with you.
Ask him to lead the way to Albion.
The guard...
It's about time he would
show up, I'd think.
What?
Verdande!
Oh, my cute little Verdande!
You thought I would
leave you behind again,
because I went to the lake
without you the other day?
You touch my heart so!
Let me tell you, we can't take
a big mole with us.
What is it?
No!
Wait!
Where do you think you're touching?!
Guiche!
I see, the ring.
The ring?
Verdande loves gems, especially
ones that are valuable.
You've got to be kidding!
I won't stand for a mole eating the
valuable ring the Princess gave me!
Enough of that! Help me out here!
Verdande!
Who is it?!
Up above!
A griffon...
Who are you?
I am Wardes, leader
of the griffon squad,
ordered by Lady Henrietta to
accompany you on this trip.
It's you!
Of the famous Magic Guards?
Louise...
Sorry to surprise you.
I had thought that my
fiancée was in trouble.
Fiancée?
You're kidding!
You are as light as ever!
Just like a feather.
It has been a while, Lord Wardes.
What's the commotion,
so early in the morning?
Who's that good-looking guy?!
Louise... That wench!
The top of the elite, the leader
of the griffon squad,
is going to guard us personally?
I can't feel anything but
impressed by all of this!
Whatever.
I was very surprised.
I had not heard that you would be
coming here, Lord Wardes.
We can't move the entire griffon
squad on a secret mission.
When I was asked by the princess
to do something about the letter,
I requested to guard
you all personally.
You asked to personally?
Of course.
Hearing your name, there's
no way that I could stay put.
Lord Wardes...
What's this "Lord Wardes" thing...
Something wrong?
Oh, nothing...
Hey, aren't we going to the port?
This is in the mountains,
no matter how you look at it.
You really don't know anything.
Are you tired?
No, not at all...
This is a good chance to catch up on
all the time we have spent apart.
Oh, yes...
Well, I won't be surprised at
whatever comes my way.
Oh, it's in sight now.
That is the port village, La Rochelle.
All the buildings here are
carved out of one boulder.
Thanks to Square-class mages
specializing in Earth,
it's a work of art.
We will spend the night here,
and depart tomorrow evening.
Understood?
Understood, Mister Wardes!
Saito, at least answer him.
Don't you think it's rude?
It's all right, Louise.
I don't like to act like nobility.
There we go.
You know, I'll tell you this much.
What?
My parents decided
on this fiancée thing.
Hmm.
What was that "hmm" for?
He's stuck-up,
but he seems to be the most decent
of all the nobles I've met,
so he's a good guy, isn't he?
That's right! I've always looked up
to him, from when I was a child!
He had lost his parents early on,
and went through many hardships to
become leader of the Magic Guards!
Unlike you...
What?
Well, you know...
I guess I didn't have to tag along.
You're a familiar! It's a given
that you're coming with me!
Oh man... I just don't know.
What, you were in love with Louise?
I'm not in love with her!
So savage, so selfish, such
a twisted personality...
Then why are you so depressed?
"I'll protect you!"
I just wish I hadn't said
something that cool.
That's all.
To summon a human familiar...
Nothing less from you, Louise.
Even you would say that,
Lord Wardes?
No, I'm not being sarcastic.
This is an amazing thing, Louise.
I heard that you two had a duel.
That was...
Is it true that the duel was the first
time you wielded a sword, Saito?
Well, yeah.
Is it also true that you used
the Staff of Destruction
to capture Fouquet
the Sculptor as well?
I guess.
You really know the details.
Being where I am, I get all sorts
of detailed information.
Even about a peasant
familiar like him?
That's why I've grown
an interest in you.
I had thought I would like to
ask you for a practice match.
The ship leaves tomorrow night.
It's boring to just
spend idle time, right?
Lord Wardes!
Of course, I won't force you to do so.
I don't mind.
Saito, stop it!
Lord Wardes, this is no time
to be doing such a...
It's okay. I'll go easy
on him, of course.
Now, let's get to our rooms soon.
Come, Louise.
Room?
No, I can't. We're not married yet.
It's all right. We're engaged.
But...
I have something
important to tell you.
A romantic evening.
Not really.
It's pitiful that you're the one
I'm sharing it with.
Same here.
Oh, that's right! I remember now,
I have to do something!
Do something?
I just remembered that
when we were eating,
there was a young lady!
I have to speak with her.
Otherwise I'd be rude, yes?
What's with that logic?
Hey, Derf.
What is it, partner?
Do you know about Gundolf?
What are you talking about,
this late in the game?
What are you, if you're not Gundolf?
My partner has always been Gundolf,
6000 years ago to the present.
Are you crying, mi lady?
Viscount, you were here?
You were scolded again
by your father?
Now, come. I will speak
well to your father.
It's all right. I am at your side.
Your magical powers were always
compared with your older sisters,
and you always pouted
in that small boat.
Geez, Lord Wardes!
But I always felt an aura from you
unlike any other, even back then.
An aura unlike any other?
There is a special power
that only you have.
That's not true.
I've had only failures in magic so far.
Let's get married when this
mission is over, Louise.
We just happened to buy something
from the bargain rack in
the armory, you know?
Even if it was coincidence...
There is no coincidence in this world.
You are my partner, and
that's why I'm here.
Isn't that common sense?
Then why didn't you
tell me until now?
Because you didn't ask.
Well, you have a point.
The power to freely
wield weapons, huh?
I'll tell you this,
it only applies to things
made to be weapons.
It doesn't work at all for things
made to be ornaments,
like that shiny sword
from the other day.
Then if I wielded you, would I win?
Even against that Wardes guy?
Are you stupid? That's all up to you.
I'm only being used.
I don't intend to end as just the
leader of the Magic Guards!
Someday, I would like
to rule a country...
No, I want to be a noble that moves
the entire world of Harkeginia!
But, such a sudden marriage?
I need you, Louise.
But it's so sudden!
Louise...
I will protect you.
If something happens,
I'll protect you.
Saito...
No, that's not it.
Saito came here from another
world, not knowing anything,
and I was the one that summoned
him. I'm responsible...
It looks like someone is starting
to live inside your heart.
It's not like that! That can't be true!
It's all right. I won't ask you to
give me an answer right now.
Listen to me, Lord Wardes!
By the end of this journey, your
heart shall be completely mine.
Let us rent one more room for now.
Lord Wardes...
Good night, Louise.
Good night.
Oh, wait!
Sheesh, I was only trying for a kiss.
These mountain girls
are all so innocent.
Then shall we begin, Saito?
Sure.
Stop this foolishness!
Nobles are troublesome folk.
"Am I strong or weak?"
It gets on your mind and
you can't help but to move.
Saito, this is an order! Stop it!
I can't hold anything back, okay?
No need to hold back.
Come at full strength.
So agile... as I expected.
But you are still a novice,
with many openings.
Del Wil Sol La Winde.
Look out, partner!
Are you all right, Saito?
You can't win against
a real mage with your skills.
In other words, you
can't protect Louise.
As if I were under a real magic spell
A bright smile is burnt onto my heart
But each time I see you, I give you
a pointy, cold shoulder
Why do I act mean towards the one
that I think about the most?
My true feelings, the
shards of loneliness
In the deepest part of my heart,
I'm calling for you
For the day to start from zero
Marriage? It's too sudden
for such a thing.
It's true that, Wardes,
my feelings for you...
But, but, what should I... Saito...
Next Episode: Louise's Marriage
Next episode: Louise's Marriage