Spring is almost here, isn't it?
Yeah, spring...
It's really spring.
When spring approaches,
we tend to mellow out, don't we?
You're always mellow, though.
It's more unusual when you're not mellow.
Now that you mention it, you're right.
"Dear Ai, this year's Carnevale
brought more visitors than usual."
"Things were really lively right up
until yesterday, when it ended."
"During Carnevale, we had many opportunities
to work onboard our mentors' gondolas."
"It gave us the chance to watch them up close
as they worked with all sorts of customers."
"It was a great hands-on
learning experience. But..."
"...on the other hand, it also made me
very aware of my shortcomings."
"I guess I still have a long way to go
before I can become a Prima."
"I'm sure you'll be just fine, Akari."
"In fact, by the next time I visit Neo-Venezia,
you might already be a Prima."
Do you remember that day
Oboeteimasuka ano hi o
When your heart suddenly began to race
Futo kanjita tokimeki o
The rays from the blue sky were pouring over you...
Aoi hizashi abite
...as you cut through the wind
Kaze o kiru kimi ni
I couldn't look away, and when our eyes met
Mitoreru to me ga atte
I couldn't help but smile
Egao koboreta
It's just like a spiral
Marude supiraare
I want to spend my days waving to you
Itsumademo te o furitai hibi
This is my proof that I was here with you
Koko ni tashika ni kimi to ita akashi
An eternal spiral
Zutto supiraare
There's a path which stretches on ahead
Kono saki mo tsuzuiteru michi ga aru
When you climb the next hill,
Tsugi no saka o nobottara
Let's meet again
Mata aimashou
That Imminent Spring Breeze...
Gondola coming through!
Wow, Junior! You're really
projecting your voice today.
That was amazing, Alice!
I had a revelation.
Oh?
While watching Athena work,
I thought about a number of things.
From this day forward, I'm Neo-Alice!
Sounds like you were inspired by
your mentor during Carnevale, too.
Yes.
You too, Aika?
Yeah, I guess so. But...
...I've been working nonstop these
past few days, so I'm really... sleep... y...
Oh, Aika.
You're both really sleepy-heads...
Well, it is spring, after all.
Say, why don't we get some coffee
at the café up ahead?
Agreed!
It's Al.
Huh? Al?
You're right.
I wonder if he's having tea by himself...
No... He's with Pony-boy...
Yay!
Al, Akatsuki!
How nice to see you all! Good morning.
Good morning.
It's unusual to see you both
having tea at this hour.
We're having a study session today.
Indeed.
If I can't defeat this fiendish promotion exam,
I won't be able to complete my training.
But what's with all these
difficult words, one after another?
It's a pain just reading it.
Now, now, don't say that.
It's important for Salamanders to learn
the workings of Aqua, Akatsuki.
I know that!
This doesn't look like a study session...
It's more like Al's just tutoring you.
What did you say, Gachapen?!
Don't call me Gachapen, Pony-boy!
I'll go buy us some coffee.
Sideburns.
Get another cup for us, too.
Okay...
Well then, study hard!
Will do.
Take care.
Promotion exam, huh?
You two will probably have yours soon, too.
Eh? You think so?
Yeah, I do.
I guess... we might?
Why are you being so doubtful?
We're practicing hard like this to prepare
for when that day comes, aren't we?
Yeah.
I can't lose to Pony-boy, that's for sure!
Akari, President Aria, let's have lunch.
Yes!
I heard the involtino from
this shop is really delicious.
Oh?
You're right! They look delicious!
My, my.
Let's eat!
The salmon is delicious!
We don't have any bookings for this afternoon,
so maybe we can call it a day.
There aren't many people around after Carnevale,
so it feels a little lonely, doesn't it?
Oh, no! President Aria!
Oh, my! Water, water!
Here's a glass of water, Akari.
Okay.
Here, President Aria.
Looks like he'll be okay.
Please eat slowly, President Aria.
Delivery for the Aria Company!
Coming!
Woody, thank...
Huh?
Akari!
Spring is almost here in Neo-Venezia.
Spring is?
From the sky, you can see...
...that the city is gradually changing its colors.
Sounds wonderful.
Hmm...
Here you go, this is your package.
Thank you very much!
Well then, see you later.
Yes!
It's addressed to you, Alicia.
My, my. I wonder what it is?
"Bringing you spring a little early."
My, it's from a customer
we had during Carnevale.
Do you remember? It's the lady
who came with her daughter.
Ah, I remember.
They were from the south, right?
It's cherry tea and cherry jam.
Might as well... Why don't we
invite everyone over?
What a great idea!
It's slow this time of year, so Akira
and Athena might be able to join us, too.
I'll try calling them.
My, my.
Seeing Neo-Venezia after Carnevale...
...is like seeing it after it has
taken off its mask, isn't it?
It's the true face of Neo-Venezia.
I see...
If I think of it that way,
it doesn't feel lonely at all.
My, my.
If I think of it that way,
it doesn't feel lonely at all.
My, my.
We're back!
How did it go, President Aria?
Did you catch any fi...
Oh, no!
What happened, President Aria?
Please pull yourself together!
President Aria, could you
help us with this next?
Alicia, I'll make the cookies.
Yes, please do.
Hello!
Coming!
Oh, something smells delicious.
Welcome!
Please come upstairs.
Coming in!
Thank you for inviting us today.
My, my. Welcome.
Athena's still working, but she said
she'd come when she's done.
President Maa, President Aria's
pudgy-wudgy tummy isn't a snack.
Okay everyone, let's have a seat.
Akari, could you bring the tea, please?
Okay!
So that's the cherry jam?
I'm really looking forward to it.
My, my.
We've made a bunch of things,
so have as much as you like.
Yay! Alicia's homemade cooking!
We brought walnut bread, too.
Thank you, Akira!
Smells like spring...
All right! First, we need to
wash our hands and gargle.
For Primas, keeping in good health
is an important part of the job.
Right!
All right, me first!
You're really a cheater!
I can't lose to Pony-boy,
but I can't lose to Junior, either.
Aika...
Yes?
You're so childish.
Wha-?!
It smells great.
It makes it feel like spring, doesn't it?
This is the first time I've had cherry jam.
My, my. Did you want some
more tea, President Aria?
Ah, you'd like more bread, too? Sure.
My, my.
Alicia, what kind of person was the customer
who sent you this cherry tea?
It was a mother and daughter
who were very close.
Right, and also...
The building on your right is Palazzo Ducale.
And straight across is the
Piazzetta of Piazza San Marco.
Once we leave this canal, the wind will
become colder, so please be careful.
Neo-Venezia really is
a wonderful place, isn't it?
You've always wanted to come here, Mother.
But I guess I should have brought you
when the weather was a little warmer.
I chose a bad time to come.
Not at all, I'm happy we came.
We hardly ever see snow back home.
I chose a bad time to come.
Not at all, I'm happy we came.
We hardly ever see snow back home.
Ma'am.
Your daughter and Neo-Venezia
have a wonderful gift for you.
My, what it could be?
Please hold out your hand.
My hand?
Like this?
Oh, my!
Snow!
It's snowing!
It's beautiful.
Yes, it sure is.
What a wonderful gift!
The cold snow brought warmth to our
customers' hearts, as well as our own.
Yes.
No sa... pp... y...
You're too amazing, Alicia.
My, my.
Alicia's amazing, but so is Akira.
Huh? Did something happen?
How do I look? It suits me, right?
Hey, cut it out!
It's not safe!
It's fine, it's fine!
I have good sense of balance!
If Akira wasn't balancing you out,
you'd already be at the bottom of the canal.
Akira should scold him.
Sir, that's a woman's mask.
Oh?
My beloved prince, please marry me!
Ah! I said it, I said it!
I proposed to Himeya's Akira!
Listen, would you just...
Whoa!
Excuse me!
That was close...
Princess, acting like a troublesome
tomboy won't help to win me over.
Y... Yes...
Oh, that.
It's not like I don't understand
wanting to cut loose on vacation.
You're too cool.
My, my.
If I had snapped then, they probably wouldn't
have remembered their vacation as fondly.
Something similar happened
with Athena, as well.
No! I want ice cream!
Honestly...
You can't, it's cold. You'll get a tummy ache.
No, I want some! I want it, I want it!
No! No! Buy me ice cream! Ice cream!
Come now, be a good boy.
No, I want some! I want it, I want it!
No! No! Buy me ice cream! Ice cream!
No, no, no, no!
What's with him all of a sudden?
Even though Athena looked
pretty dopey, it was really cool.
Dopey...
Alice...
Eh? What?
Were you just talking about me, Alice?
Yes, about how you're really clumsy.
Ehh?
Welcome, Athena.
Good work today!
Thank you for having me!
Which clumsy story?
When I put mayonnaise on our pudding?
Or when I slammed into the
glass door in the bathroom?
No.
Actually, we were talking about how
amazing the Three Great Water Fairies are.
Sounds like the three of you realized
that you still have a long way to go.
We sure did. I feel kind of
depressed because of it.
Let's do our best, Aika.
Of course we will.
It's true that the three of you
have a long way to go.
Alicia.
But... so do I.
Akira and Athena, too.
We all have a long way to go.
Right?
Yeah. You're right.
Eh?
That's really a shocker.
You're already so amazing,
we could never catch up to you.
She's right!
So then, when are you going
to be satisfied with yourself, Akira?
Probably... never,
no matter how much better I get.
No matter how long I continue this job.
If you believe you've reached the top and
become complacent, you can't move forward.
That's why I think it's really important
to believe you still have a long way to go.
Yes.
"Tomorrow, I'll shine much
brighter than I did today."
That's something you want to
believe about yourself.
That feeling will probably never change,
even if you become Primas.
Even after you step off your gondolas for the
last time, that feeling will still be there.
Maybe that's how everyone
finds their own brilliance?
Their own brilliance...
In other words, it's only natural
that you still have a long way to go.
That's right.
And that's something very wonderful.
Maybe it's best to just cherish yourself and the
long journey ahead, and have fun along the way?
Yes.
Hey Alicia, pour me another cup
of cherry tea, will you?
Ah! Me, too.
Yes, yes.
I feel so relaxed after today.
Yes.
Alicia and the others will keep on chasing
after their own brilliance, won't they?
I'm really motivated!
Do you remember?
"If you can praise yourself honestly, and make
everything in this world something to enjoy..."
"...then becoming the brightest
star Undine isn't a dream."
Grandma taught us that, didn't she?
I remember it.
It's somehow...
Yeah?
Um...
What is it?
How should I put it?
Our mentors, who we love so much,
teach us many precious things...
...and always watch over us, just like the sky.
Yes.
I was thinking, maybe that's
something really special?
Yeah.
But we can't depend on it.
Someday, we have to become the brightest stars,
so our own apprentices can say the same about us.
Oh!
Yeah... you're right...
What's with that tone?
No being doubtful allowed!
Huh?!
You're Alicia's only apprentice!
Yes...
You need to be more self-conscious
and feel the pressure!
O-Okay.
You're really strict, Aika.
We're definitely going to
become the brightest stars!
Yeah!
I can't hear you! Louder!
We're going to be the brightest stars!
I wonder what kind of Primas they'll become?
I can't hear you! Louder!
We're going to be the brightest stars!
I wonder what kind of Primas they'll become?
Yeah!!
I wonder. But I'm looking forward to that day.
I'm looking forward to it too,
but that'll also be the day they leave us.
It's kind of lonely.
I'm sure Akira will cry.
Wha-?! Who's going to cry?!
My, my.
Good grief.
Though I'm sure each of them will be unique...
...and become a new kind of Prima Undine
that we've never seen before.
That's right.
They'll become fairies, bringing
new wonders to Neo-Venezia.
And then, the torch will be passed, won't it?
Yeah.
"Akari, it seems like spring in Neo-Venezia
helps bring out everyone's true colors."
"But Akari, your true colors are..."
A shore awash in golden waves
Kin no nami kishibe ni
Filled with yearning, I open my eyes and it's morning
Akogare mezameru no asa ni
As my thoughts focus intently on someone,
Dareka no koto o tsuyoku omou toki
Love rests on my palm, held high
Kakageta te no hira ni ai ga tomaru
A future guided by the flow of water and wind
Mizu no yukue to kaze ga shimesu mirai
I gaze at the hope that surrounds this world
Kono hoshi o tsusumu kibou mitsumete
The distant clouds of light are beckoning now
Tooi kumo hikari ga sasou you ni yureru ima
A shore awash in golden waves
Kin no nami kishibe ni
Filled with yearning, I open my eyes and it's morning
Akogare mezameru no asa ni
And my day begins
Hajimaru
Next Episode
A customer booked a tour,
and she specifically requested me!
Next Episode
Wait, isn't that woman?
You might be in a really big pinch!
Next Episode
Huh?!
You might be in a really big pinch!
Next Episode
Huh?!
That Smiling Customer...
Next time, "That Smiling Customer..."
Next Episode
That Smiling Customer...
Now, please take my hand.
Next Episode
That Smiling Customer...