Suioh University
Hooray for spring.
Genshiken
Of course you'd use homing missiles...
However!
W-What a bold assault!
That's f-fast.
Three times faster than usual.
It's n-not that fast.
It's springtime, don't you
have anything else to do?
Right, stupid question.
You can't read this pattern!
S-Says who?
We're back!
Ta-da!
Whoa!
Since it's Ral,
it's gotta be a Goaf!
Pretty much...
Y-You too finally, Ohno?
"Seeing as its fall, it's gotta be an oaf"?
What?
Genshiken
I woke up and as usual forgot
my cell and missed the Express.
My life reflected in
the train window.
I'm sure I have something that
I won't lose to anyone in Japan...
... but it's pretty sad
that no one notices it.
I can't run fast, though.
I'm not that strongly-built.
Here I go, at my dauntless pace.
Pass away, today's
sadness, raining in the sun!
Hesitation, repetition,
dreaming all night, all night.
Farewell sadness,
to outer space you go!
Look to the sky and shout
at the top of your lungs!
At this tempo!
Right now, at this tempo!
Genshiken
Episode 8: Comparative Research
of the Mass Production Process
I figured spring was a
good time get a move on.
We picked up a bunch of HGUCs.
So now you're dabbling in those!
Wow, there's so many parts.
Dare I assume that rather than
a B-3, your choose a B-type...
...for your love of Ral?
Uh, um...
S-Sasahara got a JM?
Is that the kind you go for?
I like the inorganicness of
the mass production models.
Then why not the Zako?
Well, the Zako sticks
out in front too much...
...and I guess I don't like
how it's not symmetrical.
The Cannon too, then?
I'm afraid so.
In a way, that's manly!
Speak Japanese, people!
Kasukabe doesn't have
any interest in models...
Oh, you mean plastic models.
Uh, um...
W-Well, one thing I can
say for the MG series...
...these bundled magazines are killer!
They're cool...
But to be honest, it requires
quite a bit of remodeling...
...to make those poses doable.
Well, these days they have...
...intermediate level courses
on how to build for beginners.
Beginner Upgrade Courses
You went to the trouble
to make this thing?
Actually, spring is the
best time to build models.
In summer and winter the temperature
is fine, but it's hard to control humidity.
Y'know, I don't recall asking that.
You may wonder why fall is no good...
...and that's because it gets cold quickly
and then it's tough to paint them.
No, I don't wonder why...
Let's go ahead and get started.
Okay!
Wow!
It looks so complicated.
If you're overwhelmed by this, maybe
you should steer clear of the PGs.
Tanaka, don't tell me
you've mastered those?
Well, generally.
Models...
Aren't they essentially toys?
I can't let that one go.
Sorry, but models and
toys are different things.
These you have to assemble yourself.
Ah, then they're less than toys.
That's false.
Because a model is
something you have to...
...go to the trouble of
putting together piece by piece...
...it takes on the spirit of the builder.
In other words, the meaningfulness is
completely different from that of a toy.
Right...
So with this type of kit, the personality
of the builder is realistically embod...
H-Hey, did you make that?
Y-Yeah, I did...
Let me see.
Huh?
"Huh" nothing. Let me see it.
Sure, of course.
Hey, some parts move.
U-um, stabilize the
joints when you move it.
Huh?
I mean, that is, move the elbow
after the shoulder and such...
...naturally and without forcing them...
Why?
Well, I guess for safety's sake?
If you say so.
Why?
Why'd you put it on
such an unstable surface?
Was it on purpose? Well?
N-No!
I thought maybe it'd display
better in a high place...
Thank god it's not hurt...
That made me break a sweat.
Some of the parts are flammable.
S-Shall we put them away?
Don't bother.
M-Maybe we said too much...
I sense a culture gap.
Is that the problem here?
You're in for it now!
Sorry about that.
Tanaka really loves his models.
He's being way more
otaku than usual today.
He gets long-winded
about stuff he likes.
You don't build models, Madarame?
Nah, not too often.
Ahh, so you suck at it.
Well, in a way what Tanaka said
is the logic of those who build...
...but that doesn't mean
it's completely correct.
That sounded a little otaku-ish too.
Hey there!
Hey, how'd you do?
I won.
Won what?
A fighting game tournament
at the Manga Club.
Of course...
So Tanaka and the others
have started building models.
Does that mean you do it too?
Hmm, just one.
It was just an MG Zita...
...but it was so hard I gave up and
let Tanaka take over and finish it.
Then, you don't like them very much.
I do, generally.
Want to see it? The Zita Gungal.
I'll pass.
Beginner Upgrade Courses
Step 1: Smooth out the seams
One way or another, let's get
through test fitting today.
Yes sir!
We'll do our best!
Carefully, carefully.
Oh, and also, cut those
pins off on the short side.
It'll make it easier when you
take it apart after test fitting.
Y-Yes sir.
There's no special
technique required as of yet.
Fun, isn't it?
It still makes me kind of tense.
Then you'll never
make it through inking.
You'll be so tense
you'll forget to breathe.
Wow, I wonder if I'll make it.
But the JM looks like
it'll be harder to ink.
I thought so. I'm not that good at it.
Whoa!
Whoa?
Nothing, nothing.
Go on, continue.
Yes sir.
Hey, where's Kohsaka?
I haven't heard.
Oh.
I'm not gonna do anything!
I-I'm sorry, I just...
Beginner Upgrade Courses
Step 3: Even out the Hike
I finished the head!
Oh, nice pace.
You're quick, Ohno.
Ah, but the JM has more head parts.
Let's see it.
Not bad.
Just attach the mono-eye
and it's perfect.
It, it is?
Aren't we all having fun.
Well, um...
The mono-eye... fulfills the
duty of being the main camera...
Was that by any chance for my benefit?
No, I'm just talking to myself.
I see.
...without a fifth person.
Scary story, part 2.
What's with these bad vibes?
Am I some kind of nuisance?
I liked how today's Kujiun was
bursting with minor characters.
Maybe that's why, but Tokino
seemed livelier than usual...
You could say that.
This b-being the second season...
...it's n-nice to be able to
see a filler episode like this.
I agree.
The staff would have their hands full
trying to pull it off in 13 episodes.
Anyone else?
Saki, were you watching it?
Huh?
Uh, that's...
Oh, this?
I was just checking it out.
T-That's still in the
test fitting stage!
I mean, it's easy to
lose track of the parts.
Fine, fine, I'll give it back.
Sorry about your precious head.
No, I'm sorry.
I wonder if K-Kasukabe
wants to make one too...
There's no way.
No chance.
Not a one, no.
But you know, maybe we should ask
her.
W-Well...
I don't know.
She's not interested.
Oh...
Making models is so much fun though.
I think maybe I'll take the
one-shoulder challenge this summer.
One-shoulder?
Outfits that show off
one of your shoulders.
Huh.
Speaking of one-shoulder...
...I like the Zako better than
the Goaf that Ohno's building.
The one with spike armor
just on one shoulder...
Is something wrong?
No, what should we do after this?
What would you like to do?
Let's see...
Sorry, I think I'll split.
I'm kinda tired.
Say what?
Ohno, are you doing a manicure?
A new color?
Pardon?
Of course not...
U-Um...
What?
Would you like to build with me?
I mean, you've been here a lot lately...
I thought maybe you were
interested in models.
Yeah, right.
Try again.
See? There's no way.
A-Anyway, let's continue
smoothing out the seams!
It goes without saying that this
one task yields tremendous results.
Yes sir!
Yes sir...
Hey, Genshiken!
What's up?
Don't give me that!
We've got complaints about
the smell of paint thinner...
...coming from your neck of the woods!
Paint thinner?
Ahhh...
And what does "ahhh" mean?
Well, it is spring, you
get all types showing up.
Huh?
You see that you do whatever it
takes to keep those bozos in line.
Why'd this have to happen now?
I'm worried about any dust.
There's no way to get
rid of it in the end.
You just have to block the wind with
your body as much as possible.
What are you doing?
Well, there were complaints about a
paint thinner smell in the club room...
To be honest I resent this...
...but hey, don't give up until the end!
Yes sir!
Beginner Upgrade Courses
Step 4: Inking
Are you tired?
I don't exercise much, so...
Just one more push.
Yes sir, I'll try.
Beginner Upgrade Courses
Step 5: Affix Decals
Hmm.
How are they?
Good job...
That just leaves the
finishing touch, matte paint.
Yes sir!
This is something where
mistakes are irrevocable...
...so you have to be earnestly
steady and careful with your painting.
Yes sir!
We'll start with Ohno.
Yes, please.
See?
It's a snap of the wrist like this...
So you don't end up with unevenness.
L-Like this?
Ah, nice, that's the way.
All right then...
The wind's messing me up!
You have to time it right.
Uh, for now dry it off!
Then sandpaper it again!
Y-Yes sir!
First carefully strip
it off. Carefully...
Y-Yes sir!
Something's on my JM too!
That Federation peon can wait!
Say what?
They take this stuff so seriously...
Tanaka, you're a Zuon guy?
It came off!
They take this stuff so seriously...
My JM!
Hey!
Genshiken!
I don't know what the hell you're
doing, but don't pollute the courtyard!
No, we're just...
What's that stink?
Clean it up immediately!
That tension.
Huh?
To be frank, it's a drag.
All you do is scream your head off!
And just when have I done that?
You're doing it now!
All I did was give those
three the warning they deserve!
Dammit, that's why it's a drag!
What's a drag?
Here it is, springtime, don't
you have anything else to do?
That's none of your business!
Hey, Ohno.
What's this about?
I finished the Goaf.
Huh?
Wow, you finished it...
It's not that good though...
Oh well, right? I wouldn't really know...
I'm impressed that
you made it to the end!
Yeah, yeah!
Um... can I touch it?
Uh, um, um...
Sure.
Uh, it's okay this time.
If you aren't rough with them,
they don't break so easily, right?
Y-Yes, of course...
Carefully, then.
Hmm, it bends easier than I expected!
Y-Yeah...
Wow, so that's how this works.
It moves pretty well!
Huh?
Oh, hold the joint when you move it?
That's right, as smoothly as possible...
Like this?
Huh?
"Snap?"
S-Sorry! Looks like
the leg came off...
I-It's okay! Chances are
the polycap just came off...
It's broken...
For real?
It was on purpose! I know it!
No it wasn't, I didn't mean to!
But you said "Hnn!"
What the hell was that all about?
They don't usually break this easily!
Huh?
But... Huh?
Tanaka.
Ohno, I'm sorry...
No, it's all right...
I'm okay, totally...
I'm just fine!
What?
What? Huh? This...
Sorry! I'll make it up to you!
We'll go shopping, okay?
No, you don't need to...
Well, there you have it.
It's unfortunate, but making it up
to her won't bring her Goaf back.
That Goaf isn't just a
thing that was bought.
Ohno spent a week putting
it together herself.
The accumulation of each
and every effort involved...
...is the reason behind her tears.
It's not something that can be
healed by buying the same kit.
Do you understand?
Ohno's tears are in and of themselves...
...the difference between a
model and a toy you simply buy.
I'm sorry, Ohno...
No, I'm really alright now.
Then, I'll do any one
thing for you as an apology.
What would you like?
Seriously, anything you say.
Oh, okay...
Please cosplay.
Huh?
B-By the way, how much
was that originally?
About 3000 yen.
3000...
That's not much for full-body cosplay.
How about just one part?
One part...
Then maybe that would work.
T-This, huh?
Isn't it a bit much
compared to last time?
You think so?
I think the maid effect
makes it that much cuter.
Please, meow.
Meow?
I won't let you trick me!
Hey, that's no fair, you promised!
What?
We took no detours or shortcuts...
... and we weren't afraid of
what tomorrow would bring...
... as we kept walking down
Inogashira Street late at night.
Only vivid dreams extended
deep into the shadows.
We aren't quite grown up.
Simple but complicated
glistening like marbles.
The time we could see from there
sparkled, even if nothing big happened.
What we see from the marbles in
our hands now is a little different...
... but they shine faintly nearby.
Kasukabe the cat-eared maid...
I'm sure she'd be uppity at first,
but she'd turn obedient before long...
Oh, I like...
Right now, their
imaginations are running wild!
When a character gets upset,
a huge droplet of water appears.
You mean the sweat drop.
Don't you think it's
gotten a little too old?
Just like blinking lines over their
heads when they realize something.
Or when they're on a cheek.
Sometimes they're even over b-breasts.
I guess even symbols like
those can become fads.
T-The most embarrassing
things these days are...
...split-screens and
trendy theme songs.
Yeah, I like the kind
where you can shout out the...
...name of the robot or its
attacks in the song during karaoke!