Hey, Nana. Do you remember
the first time we met?
I'm the type who believes
in things like fate.
So I think it was fate.
You can laugh if you want.
You have a new message
Unopened messages: 1
Dear God! Great Buddha! Demon Lord!
Shoji
The sakura has blossomed
All right!
E-Excuse me, this...
Nana! What are you shouting for?
Oh, you want to return that?
This man will be happy to help you.
Nana?
From this moment on,
I'll have you know,
I am no longer working here.
You're quitting?
Thank you for all that you have done
for me this past year,
and do give my regards
to the manager.
Oh, and tell him to be sure to transfer
the rest of the pay he owes me
into my bank account.
Well then. Be well.
I'll see you around!
Nana!
It's spring!
Spring has finally come!
After the long wait,
spring has arrived!
I got into my top-choice University!
Yay! Call me.
Oh I can't wait to see you, Shoji.
I got into my top-choice University!
Yay! Call me.
When I was darkness at that time
With trembling lips
In a corner of a room I cry
The more I struggle
The more this wound deepens
The broken promise hurt me
Nobody can save me
God, I have only one request
Stop tearing apart my love
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Sorrow tumbling down is your song
All alone with nowhere to go in my life
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Oh baby, help me from frozen pain
With your smile, your eyes,
and sing me, just for me
I wanna need your love
I'm a broken rose
Well then, in celebration of
Shoji's acceptance into university...
- Cheers!
I am so happy for you.
Wasn't it worth working hard
that extra year after failing the first time?
Stop bringing that up!
No, really. I'm happy for you, too.
I thought for sure you'd fail again.
You too?
What did you say, Koichi Sato?!
Hello? Nana?
What if it isn't her?
Did you get my email?
Thanks.
I guess that's proof
he hasn't been fooling around.
There's no way he could
ever cheat on her. It's not in him.
Yeah. I'm just having a drink with
Kyosuke and Junko at the Junction.
That's right,
the bar I'm always telling you about.
How about you, Nana?
What are you doing?
I was packing.
Nana says she's on her way
to Tokyo.
- Yes?!
To Dad and Mom,
I'm going to Tokyo!
I'll be in touch as soon as I find a place,
so please send me the boxes
in my room.
I'll find new, fancy furniture
in Tokyo,
so just leave the furniture
in my room as is.
I'll be back from time to time!
Say hi to Nao and Nami for me.
See you, Nana
One ticket to Tokyo. One way.
Non-reserved seating!
None of the trains are on schedule
because of the snow.
That's okay.
As long as I get there.
March 519:30
I'll meet your train.
What time are you arriving?
Which train?
Let me know and
I'll wait for you at the platform!
Am I nice or what?
Shoji.
Thank you for using
the Tohoku bullet train today.
- Due to the snow, the train's departure, .,
- What's this? It's packed.
- was delayed by forty minutes.
- I wanna find a seat quickly,
so I can email Shoji.
Um...
Um, excuse...
What? Why did it suddenly stop?
An accident?
Are you all right?
I'm fine. Sorry.
I'm sorry too.
You got flattened by this, didn't you?
I'm fine.
Er... By the way...
Is this seat open?
Go ahead.
What a beautiful person.
More like, so cool.
She has an aura different
from that of a commoner.
She's skinny and has a small face.
Could she be a celebrity?
And such long eyelashes!
I envy how the loud makeup
looks good on her.
Beautiful people look great,
no matter what they do.
Wow, a well-worn Vivienne Westwood ring!
So cool!
Sorry. Is the smoke bothering you?
No, I'm totally fine.
It's not moving.
The train. It's been running like this
for a while now.
Is that so? What am I gonna do?
I'm in a hurry.
Really? That's a problem.
No, it's all right.
I'll send an email.
Okay!
Wow, you're really fast!
I'm amazed at what high school students
can do nowadays.
But I'm twenty years old.
Sorry. Then I guess we're the same age.
She's so cute when she laughs.
What? The same age?
No way, you don't look it. That's fraud!
The way you said
"high school students nowadays"
makes you seem a lot older!
Yeah, it's a habit.
I live in the analog world.
An announcement to our passengers.
Due to the snow, we will be
proceeding at low speeds for a while.
We apologize for the inconvenience
- this delay is causing you.
- No way!
How long is it gonna
take us to get to Tokyo?
What is the purpose of your stay
in Tokyo?
Nothing in particular.
I'm moving there.
I'll look for a job in Tokyo.
Really. Same for me.
What, you're moving there too?
Really? I thought you were
from Tokyo.
So you're not returning home
from a tour around the country.
A tour?
Like concerts.
You have a guitar, after all.
I figured you were
a professional musician.
So, are you in a band?
Back in my hometown I was.
That's so cool!
Where is your hometown?
An email.
Or, no, it's the phone.
Hello, Nana here.
Oh, Shoji? Yeah, that's right.
The train has stopped.
I've got no idea when we'll arrive.
Huh? You sure?
But it could be around midnight.
You sure it's okay?
Thanks.
Then I'll call you again
when I know what time we're arriving.
Bye-bye.
Is your boyfriend from Tokyo?
You sure are lovey-dovey.
I get it. So you're chasing after
a guy who moved to Tokyo.
You're wro--!
Well, I guess you're right about that.
Which is it?
Well, he's not from Tokyo.
We went to the same college
at our hometown.
But he came to Tokyo
a year ago to study art.
Why didn't you go with him then?
I told him that I'd go too.
But Shoji...
He insisted I shouldn't.
Why's that?
Because I have no objective
or money.
He says it's not wise to make
such a move without a plan.
I see.
So I tearfully stayed back and
saved up money to make the move.
We made a promise
that if Shoji passed
the entrance exams to University,
then I'd move to Tokyo!
When I get to Tokyo,
I'm gonna find a job
and give every effort
so he doesn't tell me to go home!
Say... What am I doing telling
all this to a stranger?
A total stranger!
What's wrong with that?
Tell me more.
From the look of things,
we've got lots of time.
Yeah, you have a point.
Then, will you hear me out
so we can kill time together?
To be honest, I was dying to talk
to someone about him.
His name's Shoji,
and he's kind, reliable, and pretty cool.
But when he talks,
he acts like a fool.
Like a fool?
Hey, wanna have some beer?
Sure, I would.
Two beers please!
Okay, then. Let's make a toast.
A toast to what?
Well...
To Shoji passing
the University exams!
No. that has nothing
to do with me.
Then, can we at least drink
to this unique moment?
Hey, I like that.
To two girls, the same age,
arriving in Tokyo at the same time
on the same train.
That's quite a coincidence,
don't you think?
And to one more thing.
My name is Nana too, Nana.
Do you remember
the first time we met?
Before we knew it,
there was a snowstorm outside.
The train was stop and go all the way,
and it took us five hours
to get to Tokyo.
But I wasn't at all bored.
I kept talking about myself
and didn't bother to ask
about you at all.
But knowing you,
you likely would've just changed
the subject or something, anyway.
Nana!
Shoji!
Why are you crying?
You're so mean to be laughing!
You really had a tough time.
Five hours, right?
But you know...
What's the matter?
I became friends with
the girl sitting next to me.
Oh?
But she's not here,
even though we got off the train together.
Has she already left?
I should've given her
my cell number and stuff.
You didn't do that?
Then you can hardly
call yourself friends.
Don't cry. Kyosuke and Junko
are waiting downstairs.
Jun-chan!
There's no snow
on the ground in Tokyo.
So. What do you want to do?
Wanna go have a drink?
But I gotta tell ya,
I'm really tired.
And it's one o'clock
in the morning.
Well then, I guess that means
we'll go home directly.
I'm really sorry.
I mean, you guys came all
the way out here to meet me and all.
Hey, there's no reason
for concern.
We can get together any time
we want to now.
We'll take a rain check
on the party.
It feels so good to be together,
the four of us.
Just like old days back
at our specialty school.
More than just a nostalgic feeling,
a sense of relief.
It's like this is my second family.
Here I am finally, in Tokyo,
with all of you.
See you!
Good night.
Huh?
What are you doing, Nana?
Let's go.
Ah, right.
Shoji Endo
Wait a minute.
Is it all right to be staying over...
- like it's the natural thing to do?
- Come on in.
Though the place is a mess
since you came on sudden notice.
Sorry 'bout that.
Huh?
I'm being a bother by suddenly
coming like this, aren't I?
I was hoping to stay with Jun-chan
until I found my own place.
But that wouldn't be
too considerate, would it?
Those two are living together now.
I had no idea!
Jun-chan never told me!
Since when?!
I wonder.
It was like, before I know it,
Kyosuke had moved to Junko's place.
I see. I never knew.
Hey, you've still got
your shoes on!
Tokyo is not a foreign country,
you know!
They always did have the composure
of a middle-aged couple.
"Middle-aged couple"?
I guess they just bonded more
after moving here.
That's totally great!
What?!
Hey, are you taking
my clothes off already? You pervert!
I wonder, can Shoji and I
gradually become like that too?
I wanna make up for
all the time we were apart.
I'm so happy.
I should be back around 6.
When you go out,
leave the key in the mailbox. Shoji
Damn! I wanted to be sure to
get up early
and make breakfast for him.
I'll make up for it
before Shoji gets back.
Doing stuff like this makes me feel
like a newlywed wife.
Just to imagine how happy I'd be
to help him out like this every day...
I wonder if it would be all right
if I just stayed here.
Shoji would surely appreciate it.
Hi! How was your day?!
Uh... hi.
This is pretty tasty.
What's with that surprised look?
Because you come across as the type
who doesn't do much cooking.
Th-That's not true.
Just joking.
But this is really good.
I'm impressed.
This was worth the three hours
it took me to make it.
By the way, how did it go with
the real estate agent?
Did you find a place?
I didn't have time today,
so I couldn't go.
Why? Oh, of course.
You were looking for a job.
Did you find something?
That's right.
I've gotta look for a job.
Don't tell me you were sleeping
the whole time.
No way! I cleaned the house,
did laundry and stuff,
it was a super productive day!
You serious?
You didn't come all the way
to Tokyo to do that, did you?
You promised me you'd find
a job that would allow you
to make it on your own,
and give it every effort, right?
How can you say such a thing?!
I did this all for you, Shoji!
I shouldn't have talked
to him like that.
It's like I'm trying to
make him feel guilty.
Thanks for the meal.
I'll clean up.
It's all right.
I can take care of myself.
I'm pathetic.
I'm gonna take a bath.
I'll never make it like this.
He's just gonna hate me.
What am I to do?
What can I do to keep him
liking me?
Hey Nana.
Wanna take a bath together?
Not a chance!
Oh, give me a break.
What are you playing Miss Innocent for,
at this point?
Well, it's embarrassing!
What's embarrassing?
I mean like...
Well, being an old couple,
you and Kyosuke may have long forgotten
the embarrassments in a relationship.
An old couple?
The bathroom's brightly lit
and it's small.
He'll be seeing every inch of me.
There's no way!
Keep your voice down.
Maybe living with my boyfriend
isn't for me.
You know,
I started going out with Shoji and
then right away
we became long-distance lovers.
So there's still a bit of uneasiness
and nervousness when we're alone.
What are you talking about?
When you were hanging around
as friends back home,
there was nothing to
be nervous about.
Being friends and being lovers
is different!
I don't want to show
my boyfriend my bad side!
I think it's a bit late for that.
By the way, I gotta go to
the real estate agent by the station.
Could you join me?
Out of the question.
I have to work this afternoon.
Come on. I won't know what
to do by myself, Jun-chan.
Get a hold of yourself!
You are going to start living alone.
You have got to learn
to do things on your own!
She's right. I don't think
I can live with Shoji,
but living alone might
be even harder.
Ando Real Estate
You won't find a nice place for
fifty thousand yen a month or less.
If I work hard,
I might be able to afford
a bit more for the rent,
but can't I get a better deal
on the deposit?
Hmm... if you don't mind living
in an older building.
No deposit!
And it's very reasonable for this space!
I can have pets, too?
Do you wanna go and see it?
Yes!
It's not often you find
a good deal like this!
There it is.
That old brick building.
That mansion,
built long before I was even born,
had such a high-class feel to it.
I fell in love with the elegant
western design the moment I saw it.
The only problem was that
the seven-story building had no elevator.
Being a country girl,
the riverside location and
green environment was an added bonus.
So what do you think?
Do you like it?
The view from the window
is great, isn't it?
It's not often you find
a good deal like this.
You know,
you are a very lucky girl.
Hey, Nana.
Do you remember how we used
to stand side-by-side by the river,
gazing at the lights
that colored the water?
That song you were singing.
Sing it for me again.
I reached into the sky
But I couldn't reach what I wanted
They grew smaller
and disappeared into the sky
Like colorful balloons
I'm alone
My hand had no place to go
And gently you took it
Starless night
I won't look back
at the shadow of my past
I want to feel your warmth
Tears are falling down
Even if I'm unsure I won't let go
Of your hand holding mine