Nana had a red tattoo
on her arm.
It was the lotus flower,
the flower also known as Ren...
What that flower meant to her,
of course, I had no way
of knowing at the time.
When I was darkness at that time
With trembling lips
In a corner of a room I cry
The more I struggle
The more this wound deepens
The broken promise hurt me
Nobody can save me
God, I have only one request
Stop tearing apart my love
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Sorrow tumbling down is your song
All alone with nowhere to go in my life
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Oh baby, help me from frozen pain
With your smile, your eyes,
and sing me, just for me
I wanna need your love
I'm a broken rose
Ohh, that's bright.
I've gotta get curtains.
I've gotta get to work!
What time is it?
What am I gonna do?!
Good morning, Hachiko.
It's a nice day.
Wanna go for a walk?
Why didn't you wake me up?!
- You idiot, idiot, idiot!
- Why should I hafta wake you up?
Because, I have to work!
The shop opens at 11
and I'm late my first day!
Late? It's still early.
You don't have to be at work
until about ten, right?
You got lots of time.
You're kidding.
But my alarm clock said eleven.
The clock you got yesterday
at Mizukoshi's?
You mean it's broken already?
Nana, I don't think
this clock is moving.
It's still at the time it was
when I set it last night.
I'm gonna get that Mizukoshi,
just as soon as I get to work.
The refrigerator better be working.
Oh good. It's nice and cold.
Were you cooling something?
Beer. Want some?
Yay!
No, not "yay!"
You got work, remember?
But I'm thirsty!
No, I'm hungry!
I should have bought something!
By the way,
I ate the hamburger.
It was awesome good! Thanks.
You ate it all by yourself.
Not fair!
Well then, write "do not eat"
on the darn thing next time!
A present for Nana
From Hachi
Well then, write "do not eat"
on the darn thing next time!
I wonder if there's a classy café
or something like that open right now.
At this time of the morning?
What do you expect?
I'll get you some dog food
at the convenience store.
Found a cute bakery!
They all look really good!
I don't know which one to get!
You really do have
a good nose, don't you?
Being a dog.
Let's eat by the riverside.
It looks so refreshing. A mini-picnic.
We need to get a table.
Hey, Nana.
The gas man's coming to
open the valve today, isn't he?
Oh yeah. He said he could come
in the morning.
I'll be at home,
so don't you worry about it.
You go to work.
Your stuff from home is
arriving today too, isn't it?
I'll be there to accept it.
Sorry. I've been leaving everything
to you since yesterday.
No worries.
I got nothing better to do anyway.
But still...
What are you going to do
about work?
Don't you have to find a job?
If you're not particular,
jobs are easy to come by.
I wonder if that's true.
Like, is life that easy?
Bought on impulse
I know it's not for me to say, but...
50's headband
Bought on impulse
70's dress and shoes
I know it's not for me to say, but...
Bought on impulse
50's headband
70's dress and shoes
Hasn't been paid yet.
Hello, how are you today?
Jun-chan!
This place really suits you.
Shoji came over last night,
you know.
Said you were going
to be working here,
so I thought I'd come by
and check it out.
It's good to see you got
a good job.
Oh, so Shoji went over
to your place after that!
Yup. He spent the rest
of the night
drinking with Kyosuke
until morning.
Oh good. I really didn't know
what I would do
if he had gone to Sachiko's.
Who's Sachiko?
She's like an apprentice
of the Demon Lord.
If it makes it easier to understand,
she's kinda like the "Muddy Mistress"?
I have no idea what you're saying.
Nana, is this your friend?
Nice to see you, I'm Mizukoshi.
I run the joint.
Oh, Mr. Mizukoshi,
this is my best friend Jun-chan.
She's an art student.
Thank you for looking after Nana.
Jun-chan?
Not Kyu, Japanese for nine?
Stop that, Mr. Mizukoshi.
By the way, Hachi...
- Hachi?
- About this clock.
Did you fix it?
Well actually, it's natural
it won't move without batteries in it.
Oh of course.
How embarrassing. I'm so sorry.
No, it's my fault.
I guess I forgot to put batteries
in the box.
I'll set it for you later.
Sorry to trouble you. Thank you.
Oh, why don't you go for lunch
with your friend
while business is still slow?
Really? You don't mind?
No problem. I'll watch the shop.
Yay! See you in a bit.
Your disease, it's started again.
You know the Jackson burgers
are really good!
I should've known
there was something going on,
you finding a job so quickly.
Didn't expect such a young boss.
Koichi Sato! Another burger please.
You got it.
Hey, you know I don't care.
As long as you have a job.
Never mind the reasons
for sticking to it.
Just don't give Shoji a hard time.
Like last night, too, he got drunk
and started saying stuff.
Saying stuff?!
"Last night, too"?
Is he always saying stuff about me?
Uh...
So actually,
Shoji really doesn't like me!
Because I'm good for nothing!
It's not like that.
Shoji is so in love with you
he doesn't know what to do
with himself.
You're not going to find a man like that
just anywhere, you know that?
You gotta take better care
of him, man.
Otherwise, that's when heaven'll
get you back.
I know that.
But what do I need to do, and how,
in order to take better care of him?
Actually, I thought I was taking
pretty good care of him.
I wonder if I should have spent
the night with him last night.
Nana, it's eight o'clock,
so I'm going to close up shop now.
Oh, okay!
Thanks for hanging in there.
Must have tired you out being
such a slow business and all.
Not at all.
Just to think that I can work
amongst all this cute stuff
every day from now,
I'm totally happy.
As long as you don't mind.
Are you hungry?
Do you want to go for something
to eat after we close up?
I'll buy.
Really?
- Heaven'll get you back!
- What do you want to have?
Is there anything you don't like?
I'm sorry, Mr. Mizukoshi.
I have other plans for tonight.
It totally slipped my mind.
- A date?
- No! It's not like that!
You don't have to be embarrassed.
You're that age, you're allowed
to have a boyfriend or two.
Tell him to visit the shop.
I'll give him a discount.
Thank you.
I messed up.
No, no, it's fine.
I've got Shoji.
I'd be in trouble if things started
to look good with Mr. Mizukoshi.
Like, these thoughts alone are
totally inconsiderate of Shoji.
No way. It's not like that.
I can't go on living without Shoji!
Why don't I call him?
Oh, Shoji...
Your phone is being re-directed
to the answering service center.
Please leave a message after, .,
Maybe he's still working.
Call me when you get off work.
Just because I'm in Tokyo now
doesn't necessarily mean
Call me when you get off work.
that I can see Shoji any time I want.
Send
That's natural,
but it feels kind of lonely.
I should have stayed over
at Shoji's last night, after all.
Shoji's got his job,
and he's going to start going
to school now too.
He'll be busier than ever.
And I've got work now.
And working is kinda tiring.
Are we not going to be able
to see each other when we want?
I guess life isn't so easy, after all.
I thought that if I at least made it to Tokyo,
I could have everything my way.
In fact, I am getting my way, aren't I?
It's almost scary.
I'm on a roll, even.
But I hardly get the feeling
I've grasped anything in these hands.
I wonder why?
Besides, what is it that I really want?
Time with Shoji...
cute clothes and knick-knacks...
classy apartment and furniture...
Sure they're all important,
but something's missing.
Am I asking for too much?
Oh, hi Hachiko.
How was work?
What are you doing, Nana?
Carpentry.
I'm making a table and some chairs.
Wow! That's awesome!
So elaborate and so cute!
We need a table to eat on, don't we?
I'll be finished in a minute,
so when I'm done, let's eat.
But I didn't buy any groceries.
I'll go get something
at the convenience store!
I've made some stew, if that'll do.
Huh?
And salad.
This looks so good!
This is super!
Oh and your things arrived,
so I stuck them in your room.
I handed your guarantor papers
over to Mr. Ando, too.
I also received your key.
It's over there.
Thank you, Nana!
What's that?
I didn't really do anything.
Stop crying!
Oh, I am so happy.
I guess I am on a good roll.
Nothing's gone wrong
since I got to Tokyo.
In fact, it's Nana.
It's always fun when I'm with Nana.
I always feel so positive.
It's strange,
because we're so different in every way.
I guess this is what they mean
when people say "you just click."
Incredible! It's perfect!
The size is just right for the window!
Something store-bought
just wouldn't work like this.
Right? Do you like it?
Oh, I do! You are so talented!
Hey, this is no big deal.
Besides, I got some scraps from
a nearby construction site,
so it's basically free.
While I was at it,
I got one of the young workers
to help me shave the wood.
Nana, you could be a carpenter!
Cool, a girl carpenter!
Why don't you look for work
in that line?
Might work,
but say I do this every day
and then cut a finger or something.
I won't be able to the play guitar.
Oh, right, your guitar...
Shall we eat?
Hey Nana, are you looking to be
a professional guitarist?
What, are you kidding?
I'm not good enough to make it
as a pro.
But you used to play in a band,
didn't you?
Well yeah, but I wasn't the guitarist,
I was a vocalist.
You were the singer!
Awesome! Cool! Respect!
About what?
Well...
Tell me that after
you hear me sing, man.
Yeah, I think I'd like
to hear her sing.
There's no doubt in my mind
that she'd be cool.
I'll be her greatest fan, for sure.
Hey Nana?
I've been wondering,
that tattoo on your arm.
Is it real?
It's not a sticker?
Ah, yeah.
I knew it!
Wow! I've heard tattooing
is incredibly painful.
You're so brave! I was scared
just getting my ears pierced.
A bit of pain makes it
all worth doing.
You think so?
Kinda like, being aware
that you're alive?
Are you a masochist?
No, actually if I had the choice,
I'm more the sadist.
So true.
But Nana...
That's the flower of the lotus, isn't it?
Why did you choose the lotus?
Actually, it's the ren.
Huh?
Sui-ren?
Just plain ren.
You mean lotus.
I said no.
But that's totally a lotus.
Oh shut up!
But it definitely is a lotus.
Why are you being so stubborn?
Who's the stubborn one?!
Who could it be at this time of night?
Miss Osaki. I have a delivery for you.
It could be the stuff from Yasu!
That man sure works fast.
What a guy.
Good evening.
Nobu! What the heck
are you doing here?!
Oh wonderful!
The exact response I was expecting!
Good!
Wow! This is delicious!
I am so impressed!
- You'll make a good wife, Nana.
- No... Umm...
You have the same name,
but what a difference!
Thanks for the compliment.
I made that.
Figures. I thought it was a bit...
...sal-ty.
If you don't like it, leave it!
What the heck are you
doing here anyway? You!
Wha? I came to bring you your stuff!
It was an eight-hour drive, man!
You could be thankful!
Well done, then.
Now you may go.
- Get outta here. Go home!
- Nana!
Please! Let me stay here
just one night!
No way.
- In fact, I...
- I don't wanna hear!
I ran away from home.
I told you,
I don't wanna hear it!
Nana!
I have no attraction to
my hometown, whatsoever.
Why do you treat him like that?
He's your friend, isn't he?
Um, Nobu, is it?
Are you all right?
You don't have to be polite to me.
I'm totally used to this.
Don't expect any hospitality,
but you can stay here if you like.
Thanks. You're so kind...
I won't have it.
Nana, what are you going on about?
It's for him.
He needs to smarten up!
Now you listen to me, Nobu.
You are to follow your father's footsteps
and run that huge Japanese Inn.
Get it through your head.
I didn't choose to be born
into that family.
Quit being a brat about it!
You are blessed, young man!
Your future is guaranteed!
What's the need to throw away
that happiness?!
I won't regret it in the least bit.
As long as I can play my guitar,
I'm happy.
And I wanna play for you.
Don't make me repeat myself.
Hey Nana. Let's just at least
let him stay tonight.
It's getting late already. Okay?
Oh, a phone?
Oh, it's mine.
Hello. Hey, Yasu.
Yeah, just got here
a few minutes ago.
Hello Yasu? Do something
about this stupid son, will ya?!
Why'd you get him to bring
my stuff anyway?!
Oh sorry,
but he insisted that he'd go.
What do you mean, "but"?!
What are you gonna do about it?!
No smoking
What do you mean, "but"?!
What are you gonna do about it?!
No smoking
There's nothing I can do about it, Nana.
Nobu's serious.
No smoking
Why don't you find some
new band members and start over?
I know you'd prefer
a band to going solo.
Besides, you can write lyrics
but you can't write a tune.
Oh by the way,
did ya listen to the tape?
Tape?
The new number Nobu wrote.
It's good.
If you sing it, in my opinion,
nobody's got a chance over you guys.
This song is the best!
It is so cool!
Did you really write this Nobu?
I am so impressed! Really!
Nana.
Play it for me.
I'd like to try and sing it.
Sure.
Oh, but I left my amp
in the car!
This thing.
No wonder it was so heavy.
What's this? Man, only one guest
in the house tonight?
Pretty shabby if you ask me.
Oh, well, I guess that's how
it is when just starting off.
One's better than none.
Good evening. We're Blast.
Welcome to our very first
Tokyo performance.
Good evening...
I'll make this a night
you'll never forget.
I still can't forget that night.
There weren't any words
to the song yet,
so you just sang
a whole bunch of nonsense.
It was almost as if someone
was putting a spell on me.
I became a prisoner of
that voice of yours.
Our table became the stage,
your phone was the mike
and the crescent moon was your spotlight.
Only you could make magic
like that, Nana.
I still believe it.
The more I close my heart
The more this love tangles up
Nice and gently kiss me
Nobody can save me
Like a frozen rose
I want a peaceful sleep for my tears
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Sorry dying, falling, is my soul
Collapsing in loneliness like a little girl.
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Oh baby, help me from frozen pain
with your smile, your eyes,
and sing me, just for me
I wanna need your love, .,
I'm a broken rose