Genshiken
I woke up and as usual forgot
my cell and missed the Express.
My life reflected in
the train window.
I'm sure I have something that
I won't lose to anyone in Japan...
... but it's pretty sad
that no one notices it.
I can't run fast, though.
I'm not that strongly-built.
Here I go, at my dauntless pace.
Pass away, today's
sadness, raining in the sun!
Hesitation, repetition,
dreaming all night, all night.
Farewell sadness,
to outer space you go!
Look to the sky and shout
at the top of your lungs!
At this tempo!
Right now, at this tempo!
Genshiken
What am I doing in a place like this?
That was the seventh time today.
I can't grasp it no matter
how many times it's said...
...but what I really can't grasp
is why she came along with us...
Better late than never.
I'm sorry...
Hey, isn't Kohsaka here yet?
Didn't he just message us
that he's in the parking lot?
So slow...
Today's the day I make my move!
I have a feeling it's
a waste of effort...
C'mon, let's go.
Episode 10, The Fetishism of Leisure
Spending Taking into Account Economic Effect
It's embarrassing to go
to Comic Fest with a tan.
It sure is...
Well, we put on sunscreen...
There they are.
Let go of me, okay?
Aww, no, I can't...
Hello, could you do something about
her?
Wow, Ohno is, well...
The scary thing is,
she's not even trying...
Kugapee drove us here...
...but why did you guys come too?
Well, it's just how it happened.
One of these things is
not like the others.
So you came for real.
Hello.
Don't get too close.
I wouldn't get too close to you, sistah.
S-Sasahara, p-pull it a
l-little farther that way.
About here?
Look, it's all right.
The hotel back there keeps
a close eye on the beach.
No weirdos are going to hit on
you. It's almost all families here.
You always wear embarrassing
things when you cosplay, you know.
That's different from this...
Besides, look.
If it comes down to it, we have
an entire squad of bodyguards!
In any case, let go of my hand.
Kohsaka and I are going swimming.
That's the way.
Hey, Kohsaka.
Let's go over this again.
Don't come within a ten meter
radius of me and Kohsaka!
I expected this to an extent...
Well, since we're watching the stuff, the
parasols at least can be close together.
What's with this difference
in population density?
Why do I gotta be on this side?
E-Everyone go do their thing.
I have to drive home, so
I'm conserving my energy.
I don't really know how to swim...
Comic Fest is next week, and
I won't be humiliated by a tan.
Well, there you have it.
Is that true?
Come on, let's go.
Yes, it is.
Oh, that was nothing.
M-Monkey...
Who'd help somebody
who calls them "monkey?"
Hey, are you just going
to sit here like this?
Yeah...
While I'm at it, I might as well
look at Comic Fest materials.
What, right here?
Oh, you've chosen your costume.
Which one are you doing?
I thought this might be good...
Ahh, but you'll need a long prop.
Her uniform is cute, though.
Let's go.
W- Wait, wait!
Seriously, please!
Can we hang out?
They're over there starting in on
the "Gungal Word Game" or something!
Hey, I want to play it too.
Come on, please.
I won't make any passes at him.
Fine, whatever...
Yes!
Oh come on, why not?
Amuro wants "Sayla's good
luck charm" in the novels!
Isn't that way too geeky?
Delving into the novels
is kind of abnormal!
How so?
Ahh, geez...
Why not "Sayla Mass?"
No way!
Don't make me checkmate you!
This is a time-honored
Japanese tradition!
Yes, I know that!
I will not yield!
Have it your way.
Then it's the "m" in "charm."
M-M-M-Mass
production model...
I'm kind of tired of this...
S-Since we're here, why
not go out there a bit?
I-I'll watch our things.
Oh, are you sure?
Yeah.
W-Why don't you go play
on the beach too, Ohno?
Okay, just for a bit.
Me too, then.
I'm not going!
Having a tan at Comic Fest is...
We know, it's embarrassing.
Suit yourself.
I-I...
Nice and cold!
If you stand in one place long enough...
If you stand in one place, the sand at
your feet steadily washes away.
Eh?
Oh, yeah it does...
The illusion of the waves help make it
seem like you're going to fall backwards.
O-Ohno?
Was that intentional?
She sure is a clever one...
Aw, I got my bottom wet...
A-Are you okay?
Yes...
Let's play in the sand some.
Good idea.
I can handle that...
I can see why Kasukabe
didn't want to be around us...
Yeah, really.
Kohsaka, how about lunch?
Hmm, what do you suppose we should
eat?
Look at that, you finally came out.
Well, it was inevitable.
After coming all this way...
It would've been a waste not to.
Weren't we supposed to stay
a 10m radius away from you?
Eh?
Oh, that was just a joke.
Kohsaka, would you like
to go get a cold drink?
That sounds good.
It's not a joke in your case.
Darn, maybe this is useless.
Huh? What gives?
Why are you here?
S-Same to you.
So that's how it is, huh?
No, that ain't how it is!
What's that supposed to mean?
It's none of your business.
You think you can talk to me that way?
I told you, you're wrong!
What the hell's with you?
Shouting annoys those around you.
Look buddy, we're friends
of this girl's brother!
He's here with us too.
Over there!
H-Hi...
Yeah, hi...
You didn't come here
alone either, right?
Let's not start any trouble in public.
I'll message you later.
Don't bother.
Damn, I am so fallin' for him.
You can move now!
Are you too stupid to
stay out of trouble?
That guy thinks he's a
bigshot for yelling at people!
Sorry, sorry...
You sure were quick to run.
Because I'm an unreliable bodyguard.
Are you okay?
Yeah...
I'm no match for her...
Don't destroy it, Saki.
Ah, yeah...
I would've already done it
back in grade school...
That's a closed club, there...
Sure is.
That's Cagliostro Castle.
It's true. They've even
built in the clock tower.
You mean The Shepherdess
and the Chimneysweep?
There you go again.
I'm an "originals only"
kind of guy at heart.
But you like Clarisse.
That's different!
I also like The Fuma Conspiracy.
You recognize the Furukawa Lupin?
It's a good movie, though.
For curveballs I'd love to give
the illusory Oshii version as an...
...example if it'd ever been completed.
Was something like that planned?
It was supposed to be the
third theatrical release...
...but that ended up being The
Legend of the Gold of Babylon...
Wish we could have seen that.
Well, no use figuring the
age of a dead child.
That's true.
I've got it!
A way to fight off Kasukabe...
Why'd you come to my place?
Who cares, just let me stay a while.
Huh?
I'm your little sister after all.
Well sure, of course you are.
That's where I have
an advantage, genetics.
So show me some videos, some anime.
But don't you hate them?
Just do it.
And no softy poser stuff,
I want hardcore otaku shows.
No!
If even one of us leaves
we'll be eliminated.
I can't go on.
I'm sorry I'm gutless,
but this is my limit.
Tokino!
Outside, outside, outside, outside.
Just hold out a little longer!
The heat must be getting
to our opponents too.
Let's talk about something,
to take our minds off the heat.
That won't work!
Shouldn't you just go to bed?
Shut up!
I want to go to Comic Fest too!
Ah, lately she's been watching
lots of stuff at my place.
Looks like she's picked up an interest.
Kujiun is such a great show...
Are you trying to become
otaku or something?
I guess it just seems to suit me.
Right, big bro?
Cut that out.
Are you aware of what's sold there?
Manga books, right?
Porn books!
Just a moment!
I know, I know, you're about
to say it's not all porn.
But what is it that you guys buy?
Porn books...
Want me to show you what they're like?
This place is full of them.
Hey, you bet I do!
Would you do the honors, Tanaka?
Me?
I don't want to touch that filthy trash.
No joke, porn manga.
Isn't it?
What a disgrace.
They even have Nekodora porn!
What?
We're talking about a tightly packed
line of dozens of thousands of guys...
...like these who pour into a huge hall.
You talk as if you've been there.
Is everyone there to buy this stuff?
Yes!
No, not everyone is!
Kohsaka buys it too, naturally.
That I do!
Um, if you want titles geared
towards women, we have better ones.
Don't bring those up!
Show me!
Are you for real?
Isn't he... you know?
...and he's the vocalist from...
These don't belong to me personally...
Whoa!
You know, I think I really
am a little interested now.
Y-You suppose her eyes just opened?
I can't wait for Comic Fest!
Why've things turned
out like this, again?
Yeah, why's Sistah here?
You're one to talk!
Needless to say, I don't have one bit
of an inkling to become an otaku.
I'm only here to keep an eye on her.
Do you get that?
You do, right?
Of course we do.
How childish.
Someone has to teach kids
how rough the world is.
Well, we understand that
plenty, but we can't help you.
We'll have our hands full shopping.
Right.
I know, which is why I
won't let her slip away.
As if I'd slip away from Kohsaka.
Don't let it go to your head!
It's not?
She's not slipping away...
Yeah...
Hey...
Yeah?
Why are they lined up in the
middle of this goddamned heat?
How should I know?
Ahh, the ones up front are
finally starting to stand up...
Wonder if they'll move...
I'm about to have a nosebleed...
Oh, okay.
Gotcha.
They say they'll meet up
with us once we've moved some.
Man, their type sure is crafty.
Please keep off the grass.
Huh?
The lawn is all off-limits.
Please come over here at once.
Kohsaka!
Kohsaka?
H-How far are you gonna go?
The lines for the biggest
circles are outside.
Why do they do something like...
Don't you think becoming
an otaku ain't worth it?
No, I'll do it!
I've got what it takes, I know it!
Someone in our group said this...
An otaku isn't something
you try to become...
You just are one before you know it...
That's why you can't quit either.
It's laughable, but
for us it's a tragedy.
You don't really get what it
means to go out with an otaku.
It's not as if it's enough to
say you'll just become one too...
What're you saying?
In my opinion...
Nah, I won't tell you.
That's unfair!
You're my rival, idiot.
Like I'd tell you.
Did you see all those dojinshi
for sale on the way here?
It's an incredible world.
I totally didn't have time to...
Then let's go see.
I totally don't have the willpower...
You don't have a thing.
I totally don't...
Please don't sit on the grass.
Hi.
Oh? What happened to those two?
We got separated so I called them.
They said they'll be at the
restaurant down at that end...
...and for us to call
them when we leave.
Just tell them to go home already.
What the hell'd they come for anyway?
This is a letdown, since
Kasukabe comes here so rarely.
It's a mistake in itself for them
to come when they don't even fit in!
That's true.
But you know...
Now we can admire the booty
to our hearts' content.
How about the new Jam Jam Bullet?
Here it is, I bought it.
We sure bought a lot this time.
You mean you've never thought of
becoming an otaku for Kohsaka's sake?
Never.
Well, I did at least try a video
game with him once, but that bombed.
Then you have tried.
So, do you understand now?
What?
Give me a hint.
No.
Why not?
People sure get crabby
when they get old.
Ow!
It was just a typical Comic
Fest for us, in the end.
That it was.
But maybe we got to buy more this time?
Hey, Keiko.
Huh?
How long are you going
to be at my place?
Oh, I'll leave today.
Oh yeah?
Is that so...
You're a total gimp.
How long have we been related?
You bought a ton of dirty
stuff today, didn't you?
I could do without an
actual little sister...
You think?
There's nothing good about them.
So you do understand.
Understand what?
How to date an otaku.
That's it.
What, you mean like this?
Yup!
Then today, you too...
Yeah, I'll go back
to my place, of course.
Ouch, that's rough.
Well, it's about valuing
your time alone...
Yeah but, I mean, isn't
that like being cheated on?
It is...
You're something else, sistah.
Admiration doesn't make me happy.
In that case let me
stay at your place...
Go home!
What was that for?
I guess they get along now?
That can't be a good thing...
Hey, you don't suppose your sister
will get into our school next year?
No, she's an idiot.
We're in the clear.
Pardon?
We took no detours or shortcuts...
... and we weren't afraid of
what tomorrow would bring...
... as we kept walking down
Inogashira Street late at night.
Only vivid dreams extended
deep into the shadows.
We aren't quite grown up.
Simple but complicated
glistening like marbles.
The time we spied from there sparkled,
even if nothing big happened.
What we see from the marbles in
our hands now is a little different...
... but they shine faintly nearby.
Saki, why do you hate otaku?
Because they're homely.
They're fat, they wear bandanas and
weird gloves, have bags full of junk...
Lately more of them
have been attractive.
I don't know, but you can tell them by
their stench, that super strong smell.
And they're so proud
when they take a bath.
Like that's some extraordinary thing.
It's nothing to be "proud" of.
Um, well...
And what's with their conversations?
Did you know this, did you know that?
That's not conversation, it's just a
bragging fest. What are they, idiots?
Keep your voices down,
stop talking to yourselves...
...don't get so friendly
with me, get lost!
Aww.
Don't say things like that!