Now my life is blooming then falling
I grab destiny tight
There's no more hesitation anymore
Tying our bond
To the sky waiting for the dawn
Holding you, my love, tightly
I present an unbreakable prayer
We all are still in the darkness
Right now I just
Want to touch you deep in your heart
And give you all of my overflowing passion
I spread out my wings
Toward the future of our dreams
On them are engraved
The feeling you gave me that day
The words of our oath
Will make a miracle happen
My pounding heart, take off now!
My wish can fly high, high up
Feather 9:
"The Veil and the Wind"
Water Celebration!
Not so bad.
I'm thrilled!
A strong opponent! A strong opponent!
But how about this?
For Sekireis, there were
no wars of righteousness.
Some were better than
others, but that is all...
Water Dragon!
What?!
Water, perish!
That was dangerous! Who art thou?
I'm just a passerby.
I only didn't like the unfair fight.
Unfair?! The one who
is unfair is that veiled one!
I gave my name properly, and...
But there are two of you.
Musubi!
Yes! Is it my turn?
One-on-one battle is the Sekirei way.
Thou shalt play with that child there.
Ah, that's true.
That should resolve the issue.
Let's continue our battle!
I'm number 88, Musubi.
Pleased to meet you.
Ah, pleased to meet you too.
Um... shall we fight?
It's impossible!
I've already lost in every aspect!
You really are incompetent.
Hey, you.
Yes?
She is number 95, Kuno.
I'm her Ashikabi, Haruka Shigi.
I'm sorry, but we won't fight.
I don't care about the
Sekirei Plan or whatever.
We don't have any intention
of fighting against anybody.
Water Dragon!
This finishes it!
Ah, it's empty already?
Stay out of this!
You don't know how to speak to others.
What a cheeky girl.
All right! I'll stand by her.
How dare thee...
Flower Refuge!
Remember, only number 01 and the
Game Master can talk to me like that.
Thou art... a Sekirei?
Number 03, Kazehana.
Bye, Miss Panty-Flasher!
Bitch! They got away!
Number 03...
Musubi!
Musubi?
Where art thou?
Where hast thou gone?
Musubi!
Why did you save me?
I've seen you before. How's Miya?
Rats!
I could trick Musubi-tan and others well.
You're as good as I'd expect from
Number 03. I could never match you.
Number 10, Uzume.
I hereby formally challenge you.
They're very late.
I wonder if those two are okay.
What are you doing, Mina-tan?
I'm helping with chores. If you have
something to be washed, give it to me.
Helping with chores?
Since the capital became like this,
my job's been shelved too.
A little thing like this is
the only thing even I can do.
It's not a "little thing." And please
stop putting yourself down that way.
I told you before, you should
be more confident in yourself.
Th-Thank you, Matsu-san...
What are you doing?!
You said if I have something
that needs to be washed...
I didn't mean you should
take off your clothes right here!
Oh, come to think of it, Musubi-tan
and others are all out of the house now.
This is a good
opportunity for the experiment.
Mina-tan, surrender nice and easy...
Wa-Wait, Matsu-san!
Matsu? Are you here?
I'm sorry. Am I interrupting?
No, not at all! I'm in the
middle of chores, so, see ya!
You coward!
I can't believe you're dressed like that, Matsu.
I was in the middle of an experiment.
Kagari-tan, would you join me?
I guess you want me to turn
you into ash, you lusty monster.
I was just kidding...
Anyway, can you give me more medicine?
You really shouldn't. My medicine
only lessens the pain for a short time.
I'm really in pain.
Is your body still unstable?
I'm not recovering.
It's the first time I've been like this.
Does that mean...
Maybe...
Never mind. I'll come
to pick the medicine up later.
You should be more confident in yourself.
Confident, huh?
Minato-san!
Mi-na-to-saaaan!
I'm sorry. Are you okay, Minato-san?
I'm alive...
Come with me right now, please!
Now, hurry!
Wha-What's going on all of a sudden?
I would like you to meet somebody!
Me?
This is the apartment I used to live in...
Yes.
Isn't there somebody already here?
This is Musubi.
I'm Minato Sahashi...
I'm the one who used to live here.
Eh? So are you the failed college prep
student the landlord talked about
who brought in women
and had good times?
"Had good times"?
Minato-san, this is Shigi-san.
Number 95, Kuno-san's Ashikabi.
Ashikabi?
Yes. Is this guy your Ashikabi?
Yes. You don't need to worry anymore.
Minato-san can help you somehow.
"Somehow"? Uh... what?
Minato-san, I want to help them.
Musubi! Musubi!
Hasn't Musubi returned yet?
She took Mina-tan and went out again.
What?!
Where did they go?
I have no idea. Did something happen?
The veiled Sekirei?
Yes.
I see...
I have no doubt about it. She is the
perpetrator who has been hunting Sekireis.
Then, you say that number 95
was chased by the Veiled Sekirei
and disappeared with Musubi-tan.
Anyway, it's impossible for her to fight.
You mean number 95?
She's as frail as one can be.
Why did Minaka release
such a girl to the earth?
Even that is one of the
possibilities for the future.
That's what the Sekirei Plan is.
Thou art using sophistry!
What canst thou expect of one
who can't even make a fist to fight?
Physical fights are not the
only way to fight for Sekireis.
Especially in a battle royale,
one must be able to use this too.
I wonder why I feel
abominable when I'm talking with thee.
Oh, sounds like we feel the same way.
No!
No fighting!
W-We understand,
so stop that, Kusano!
We'll make up and take a bath together.
I've lost...
Nobody can win against crying kids.
That landlord is really annoying!
He casually storms in to
complain about every single detail.
I know, I know!
He just comes to annoy
tenants for no reason at all.
Yeah, yeah! And when
I'm a delicate exam-taker too!
You're an entrance exam taker?
This is the second year I failed...
though I'm aiming for the
Shintou Teito University.
My comrade!
No way! You also failed twice?
And aiming for Shintou Teito U?
And also, I'm an Ashikabi like you.
They say even a chance
acquaintance is part of one's destiny.
Musubi-chan...
In addition, you are both Ashikabi-sama,
you've lived in the same room,
and you also both failed
the entrance exams twice!
Do you understand
what you're saying?
The only difference is
that my Sekirei is incompetent...
No, I'm "Kuno"...
Um... so what is your problem?
You don't look like a bad guy,
so I will be honest with you, but...
It's dangerous stuff.
Can you keep it a secret?
Yes, a secret.
To tell you the truth,
we don't want to fight.
No, rather it's impossible to fight.
She's really weak, and her
only weapon is a loud voice.
So that's why we want to drop
out from the Sekirei Plan.
We want to escape from the capital!
Escape from the capital?
Mina-tan and Musubi-tan are late.
That bloody Musubi!
How long will she drag him around?!
Tsukiumi-tan, don't bathe with
other Ashikabis' Sekireis any more.
Why?
Because you'd be defenseless.
Kusano-tan, you too.
No matter where you are,
you must be attentive.
The battle royale has already begun in
this inescapable cage named Shintou Teito.
Escape from the capital?
Yes.
Um... Why don't you leave if you want to?
Don't you know?!
MBI choppers are flying all over day and night.
Tons of soldiers are at the
train stations and airports.
We have actually tried to escape
across the bridge, but there was...
The Discipline Squad?
Yes. According to her, they are dangerously
strong Sekireis following MBI's orders,
and they don't even hesitate to kill
Ashikabis if they decide it's necessary.
Even Ashikabis?!
We are watched by such guys!
MBI is to not going to let
us Sekireis and Ashikabis
get away from the capital no matter what!
The capital will become a battlefield!
So... that's what is going on...
Shit! That must be nice...
Huh?
I'm sure you can be so relaxed
because you have a good Sekirei.
Oh no, that's because
I'm too carefree... I'm sorry.
You kissed me.
You said I was your girl.
Okay, I know. I won't compare anymore.
Dammit, how the hell can
we escape from the capital?
I'm glad I made a
friend in a similar situation.
Yes.
Also, they were tightly bonded.
It was fantastic to see.
Yeah.
But... I wonder if there
really is a way I can be useful?
Minato-san...
"Maison Izumo"
Thou art late, Minato!
We're back!
Hast thou done
anything secret with Musubi?
No, I didn't! I didn't! Right, Musubi-chan?
No, we just had a secret talk.
What was that secret talk?! What?!
Mu-Musubi-chan!
Please explain properly!
I can't walk any longer.
Me either!
We're here!
Huh? Did I leave the bed spread out?
I can't stand anymore. I'm going to sleep.
Wow! Your breasts
are huge! I'm down, too...
U-Uzume-san?!
And... who?
What happened, Minato?!
Minato-san?!
What is it? It's so loud...
Minato! What art thou doing, bastard?!
Oh, no, I don't know
what's going on at all...
I drank too much... Hmm? Where am I?
Number 03?!
Your voice... Turn it down!
Ah, excuse me, but who are you?
Could you be Minato?
You really... resemble... So you are his...
Stay away from that woman!
She was allied with that Veiled...
Landlady?
I told you I would never
forgive any violence here.
You too.
Do you understand, Kazehana?
It's been a long time, Miya...
so I guess I'm in Maison Izumo?
Landlady.
Do you know her?
She used to live here.
Is it you who brought her, Uzume-san?
Probably.
Anyway, do something about your looks.
Sahashi-san will feel a
needless lustful urge again.
Wait, Landlady! What do you
mean, "lustful urge" and "again"?!
Thou... Art thou acquainted with her?
Yeah... we just met
in town by accident. Right?
Yes, right! Completely by accident!
- Right, right!
- Enough, already!
Number 10, Uzume.
I hereby formally challenge you.
No, it's too much trouble.
Aw, I'm sobering up.
I won't let you go!
The fight is over. What will you do now?
I can't... I can't lose yet.
Looks like there's a story behind this.
Well then, let's have a trade.
A trade?
I'll overlook you, so...
Treat me to sake. Sake! Sake!
I've started feeling silly,
being serious all by myself...
What do you mean?!
What?! Those two art attempting
to escape from the capital?
Yes.
Impossible! How can she have
the nerve to escape from the capital
even though she's a Sekirei?
He... Shigi-kun said that his
Sekirei's unbelievably weak,
and that's his only way to protect her.
Is that an elopement?
Lovers hand in hand
on the run! How romantic!
Shut thy mouth!
Number 95 and her Ashikabi
want to escape from the capital?
Yes.
Do you think it's actually possible?
Supposing, just supposing, that all of
your Sekireis join forces at full strength...
Really?
Then, we can help Shigi-kun and...
You don't understand
how formidable MBI is.
An island?
Kamikura Island.
It all began when two students
landed for an investigation
without permission on this island that
suddenly arose out of the ocean near Japan.
They found a ruin on the island.
A ruin?
But "ruin" may be a misnomer...
It was way more advanced
than human civilization.
Life-forms appearing exactly
like humans were sleeping there.
Although their genetic
structures were similar to humans',
their life forces were much stronger,
and not only that, each of
them had a special ability.
Could they be... Sekireis?
Yes. And the student who discovered
them was the future president of MBI,
or Mid Bio Informatics, Hiroto Minaka.
Minaka turned MBI into a colossal
enterprise that can even buy out the capital
by providing just a bit of the ruin's
ultra advanced technology to society.
"Ultra Giant Enterprise!?
MBI became the top of the industry!"
By providing just a bit of the ruin's
ultra advanced technology to society.
"Teito Sports, MBI Conquers the World.
Rapidly grew to a super-giant conglomerate.
Taking over even Shintou Teito."
By providing just a bit of the ruin's
ultra advanced technology to society.
And everything was for this Sekirei Plan.
For the Sekirei Plan?
What's important now is
that Minaka chose the capital,
Shintou Teito, as the battleground.
Retiring from the game without permission
or helping someone to do so is serious
treason for both Sekireis and Ashikabis.
That means... we'd make MBI our enemy.
I just want you to know that, Mina-tan.
Minato-san, lunch is ready to be served.
Maybe...
Yes?
Maybe the escape plan
is too reckless after all...
Wishes will be granted, Minato-san.
I think, as long as we care about
each other, and have strong bonds,
there's no such thing as
"impossible" in this world.
Hey, hey, I heard something interesting.
Blue found a Sekirei and Ashikabi
trying to escape from the capital.
Isn't this unusual?
And? Did Blue kill them?
Nope. She said they were
kinda interesting, so she let them go.
That's pretty good judgment for Blue.
Is that so?
It'll get more and
more interesting, I'm sure.
I see. Then I'm looking forward to it.
Yeah. Me too.
Yo, baby girls! Get ready now!
This is the textbook of love
Don't let it go, don't get upset so
Without false starts, it's show time!
Get the funky beat!
First ones win?
No such thing in this case! No, no!
That's perfect for me
A sudden scramble!
But I'm a woman, I can't lose. No, no!
My feelings grow
No, and then a big bang!
Don't seduce him
Get away from him
My heart is pounding hard, so hard!
Secret, going off by myself
Big success, just two of us
Sweet and dazzling night
To tell you the truth, I want him to
Hold only me, just me
I want to monopolize him so badly
I wonder if I could stick a flag on him?
I knew it, he's so wimpy, what should I do?
He's just too gentle
I love that about him
So we are devoted to him
Dear Sweet Heart!
I'm Yukari Sahashi.
I came to the capital I'd longed for,
but I met a mysterious pretty boy,
and now we're actually living together!
"Super-moe almost R-rated
love comedy, Yukari and Shiina!"
That would've made a better program,
don't you think so, Shiina?
In one sense, it's not that wrong, but...
Feather 10:
"The Night Before the Escape"
In one sense, it's not that wrong, but...
Feather 10:
"The Night Before the Escape"
Episode 10: "The Night Before the Escape."
Feather 10:
"The Night Before the Escape"
Please favor us again next time!