During the two weeks
that Nana was gone,
I took on extra work,
so I'd be busy every day,
and worked until I was
absolutely exhausted.
I did this to keep my mind off
of how lonely I was.
Yet I went to the practice sessions
at the studio without fail.
Then Nobu would always
walk me home.
I hadn't heard from Takumi at all.
Blinking eyes call the wind
A smile clears all the noise away
The angel in your eyes whispers
"Everything begins now"
Can you feel it now
It's like being caught in a wave
Pulling on my heart
Breath held, arms reaching out
Baby this world is
different from yesterday's
You're the only one I can see
Baby my wish on a wing
This sky is torn
By a single overflowing word
I'm thinking about going on a trip.
Hey, that sounds nice.
Buy me a gift from wherever
you're going.
I'm finished.
Where do you wanna go?
Go on your own.
You might have the time,
but I'm busy.
Take some time off work.
We have an important concert
coming up,
so I hafta practice every day.
What's that?
Are you on the pill again?
It's your fault!
If you want a child that badly,
have some other woman
give birth to one for you.
You don't mind if I slept
with another woman?
You're such a cold woman.
You just realized that now?
I'm gonna go write a song.
For the cute Reira.
Oh, Shin. You're awake.
Good morning, Miss Ryoko.
I'll be flying out again tomorrow.
To the States.
So I won't be seeing you for
a while.
But I'll bring back a bunch of gifts.
You can keep your hopes high.
So you'll be going.
I'll be lonely without you,
Miss Ryoko.
Oh, my. You're not only good
with your technique,
you've also improved
your choice of words.
Perhaps it's due to
my great teaching skills.
I am grateful.
Thanks to you, business is thriving.
I've turned an angel into a devil.
Upon a closer look,
I guess you don't look much
like her, after all.
Huh? What?
No. Nothing. Seconds please?
Yasu!
Long time no see.
You haven't changed
one bit. Mhm. Mhm.
Oh, stout beer please.
How are you doing?
I'm glad to finally meet up with you.
That's because you keep
pestering me.
I invited Reira too,
but she's back in her hometown.
She really wanted to come.
Is that so?
By the way, Naoki,
your voice is too loud.
You're a celebrity now,
so you'd be wise to keep
a low profile.
Not to worry.
The customers here are all from
the entertainment industry.
Really?
By the way, Yasu, I heard you came
to Tokyo to go pro.
Reira was complaining that
she's not happy with your decision.
Yeah, I guessed as much.
That's why I don't wanna meet her.
She'll keep on teasing me about it.
Well, of course she'd tease you.
What in the world happened to
make you change your mind?
Let's see.
You could say I feel responsible
for the band like it's my child.
What's that supposed to mean?
You really haven't changed, Yasu.
You need to let it
all out sometimes.
Go wild for a change.
Though I suggest not becoming
as violent as Takumi.
When he loses it,
he becomes a criminal.
Although he's been quite calm
as of late,
perhaps from fear of becoming
the next gossip item.
Back in junior high school,
none of the windows had
glass because of him.
Yeah, I remember that.
Speaking of Takumi,
I can't reach him on his cell phone.
What's he up to?
I don't know, but...
He's probably visiting women,
one after another.
There's no need to worry about him.
Is that so?
Reira, what are you doing?
Visiting my hometown.
Oh right. Of course.
You startled me.
How long have you been here?
Thirty minutes.
Huh?!
I've been here staring at you
like this for thirty minutes,
but you didn't notice me at all, Takumi.
It's got me exhausted.
No, I meant how long have
you been in town.
Anyway, if you've been
staring at me,
the least you could do
is say something!
I've been here for three days.
I was visiting mother's
grave just now.
But your mother is still alive.
Your mother, Takumi.
Due to work, you couldn't be
here for the ceremony
marking seven years after
her passing,
so I prayed that she may
warmly protect her careless son
from the wrath of the gods.
Well, thanks for that.
Is your father doing okay?
Maybe I should go and say hi.
Don't bother.
He's the same as always,
drinking from early in the day.
That's gotta be tough for
your elder sister and her husband.
With a little brother like this
on top of it.
You know, if you're gonna worry
about someone,
worry about your own mother!
Leaving her alone way out here
in the countryside.
But she says
she doesn't wanna go to Tokyo.
She really likes this place.
I don't get it.
What's so good about this place
way out in the country?
Especially given the fact
she lived in New York at one point.
Isn't that why?
Living abroad didn't suit her at all.
I've been telling her Tokyo
isn't a foreign country.
But I kinda miss New York.
It's my birthplace after all.
Why not go there?
Though we only have
two more days off.
You should've gone.
Hmm... But I had a number
of things to do.
Besides, we all should pay
our respects to our parents once in a while.
We came so close on our tour
the other day,
but I couldn't visit because of
our tight schedule.
What about you, Takumi?
As long as I stay in Tokyo,
I end up working.
So I thought I'd wander off
to the country.
Call it an escape.
But I can't keep my mind off work,
so I'll be returning now.
I just stopped by here for a bit.
Huh, you're going back?!
We got to meet here,
so why not have some fun together?
Give me a break.
Give me a chance to be alone
on our off days. See ya.
Oh, Reira...
We've got a photo shoot for
a magazine next week,
so don't get tanned.
I'm aware of that, leader.
What is that guy doing?
Their free time is coming to an end.
But I didn't contact him, either.
Why didn't you?
You've got no reason to hold back.
You should send him a bunch of
emails daily and keep his mind on you.
But I don't wanna contact him
only to be ignored.
He may be in less of a position
to contact you
once they're back to work.
Yes. But it's okay
if that's how it goes.
Yasu! Aren't you worried
about Hachi?!
Don't you get the urge to call Takumi
and give him an earful?!
Sure. But I can't get through
to him on his cell.
Nana!
If he came to see me because someone
around him told him to,
that's not gonna make me too happy!
I really am fine, so don't worry!
The way I said that...
to them it probably sounds like
I'm trying to be strong about this.
But the honest truth is,
if Takumi were to never
call me again,
I'd be fine with that.
Or in fact,
it would be better that way.
Hachi! Buy one for me too!
Buy it yourself.
What should I get?
Thank you.
You know, Nana's singing seems
to be improving day by day,
don't you think?
Maybe because of the sit-ups.
I'm sure we'd be able to go pro, right?
Trapnest will be on their break
for two more days.
If I don't hear from Takumi again,
I can become the poor girl
who was tricked and
dumped by a nasty guy.
I can make it all Takumi's fault,
and move on to a new love.
But if he found out about
my cunning thoughts,
he'll end up hating me.
First of all, I'd be dreaming
to think someone would
make me their girlfriend
because Takumi dumped me.
I don't want Nobu thinking
I'm such an easy woman.
But the fact is,
I am that type of woman.
A black four-wheel drive Mercedes Benz.
Nobu!
Thank you for walking me home.
Huh?
I'll be fine on my own from here on.
I'm almost home.
I'm sorry for having you take
a longer route home
to walk me home every day.
No, I don't mind it.
If you're bothered by it,
I'll have Shin or Yasu walk you home
from tomorrow...
No, it doesn't bother me.
Nana!
If he's gonna come at this stage,
he could've sent me
an email ahead of time.
Such a selfish man who
makes decisions on a whim.
Well, well. It's you.
Where were you this late
at night?
I worry, you know.
I've been waiting for an hour.
Ah, sorry. I was at the studio
to see Nana and her band practice.
Nana's staying with Ren now,
so Nobu walked me home because
I'm afraid to walk home alone.
Is that so?
Well, thank you very much for that.
Okay, then. Thank you, Nobu.
Good night.
I'm the worst.
Sorry for coming like this
outta the blue.
I left my place without my cell phone
and came here before returning,
so I couldn't call you.
This is what happens when
I think cunning thoughts
and take advantage of
someone's kindness
by having him walk me home.
I must've really hurt his feelings.
What am I gonna do?
I can't go to the studio anymore.
I won't be able to look him
in the eye!
Oh, Takumi, want me to
make you something?
Are you hungry?
No.
Then, do you want
something to drink?
There's cold beer.
Sure.
I mustn't let my guard down.
To Takumi, I'm nothing
but a convenient woman
who will sleep with him when
he wants to do it.
It's one thing to get involved
once or twice,
but this is the third time.
If I don't put a stop to this,
this pathetic relationship may
continue on.
If I'm gonna end this,
I've gotta do it now.
Before it's too late.
I just hafta tell him never
to come here again.
But...
am I able to say such a thing?
I can't say it.
Why are you drinking on your own?
Give me some.
I know he's not that great a guy.
So why can't I... end it?
Oh, welcome home, Nobu.
Don't!
What are you watching?!
Erotic videos. I'm studying.
Cut it out. Not at a time like this.
Are you doing it to make fun
of me?
I can't take it anymore.
Take what?
What's the matter?
Nothing! It's none of your business!
Um, sorry. Please leave me alone.
Shin.
A man and a woman are
simply opposing creatures
driven toward each other by lust.
Can they be connected by love?
Sorry, I don't know either.
The truth is, I'm just a girl
who wanted to get close
to Trapnest's Takumi outta curiosity.
I'm not as pure as Nana thinks.
And I'm sure I'm different from
the ideal Nobu pictures me as.
But Takumi understands me...
me who's helplessly empty.
And me too.
I know Takumi
is a pathetic man.
Nana...
It's strange.
He lived in a world
farthest away from mine.
But only Takumi...
will forgive me for who I am.
As if he was the sole accomplice
to my actions.
Thanks for your concerns
about everything.
THANKS FOR YOUR CONCERN
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
TAKUMI CAME BY LAST NIGHT,
AND SAYS HE'LL BE WITH ME
ALL DAY TOMORROW,
UNTIL THE END OF HIS BREAK.
BUT I HAVE WORK.
I SHOULD HAVE TAKEN
THE DAY OFF.
Thanks for your concerns
THANKS FOR YOUR CONCERN
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
TAKUMI CAME BY LAST NIGHT,
AND SAYS HE'LL BE WITH ME
ALL DAY TOMORROW,
UNTIL THE END OF HIS BREAK.
BUT I HAVE WORK.
I SHOULD HAVE TAKEN
THE DAY OFF.
THANKS FOR YOUR CONCERN
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
TAKUMI CAME BY LAST NIGHT,
AND SAYS HE'LL BE WITH ME
ALL DAY TOMORROW,
UNTIL THE END OF HIS BREAK.
BUT I HAVE WORK.
I SHOULD HAVE TAKEN
THE DAY OFF.
Takumi came by last night,
THANKS FOR YOUR CONCERN
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
TAKUMI CAME BY LAST NIGHT,
AND SAYS HE'LL BE WITH ME
ALL DAY TOMORROW,
UNTIL THE END OF HIS BREAK.
BUT I HAVE WORK.
I SHOULD HAVE TAKEN
THE DAY OFF.
and says he'll be with me
THANKS FOR YOUR CONCERN
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
TAKUMI CAME BY LAST NIGHT,
AND SAYS HE'LL BE WITH ME
ALL DAY TOMORROW,
UNTIL THE END OF HIS BREAK.
BUT I HAVE WORK.
I SHOULD HAVE TAKEN
THE DAY OFF.
until the end of his break.
But I have work. I should have
taken the day off.
WHAT TIME DO YOU THINK
YOU CAN MAKE IT HOME, NANA?
WITH THE LIVE CONCERT
COMING UP, I DON'T WANT
TO GET IN THE WAY OF
YOUR PRACTICE, SO I WON'T
BE DROPPING BY THE STUDIO.
GOOD LUCK.
But I have work. I should have
taken the day off.
WHAT TIME DO YOU THINK
YOU CAN MAKE IT HOME, NANA?
WITH THE LIVE CONCERT
COMING UP, I DON'T WANT
TO GET IN THE WAY OF
YOUR PRACTICE, SO I WON'T
BE DROPPING BY THE STUDIO.
GOOD LUCK.
WHAT TIME DO YOU THINK
YOU CAN MAKE IT HOME, NANA?
WITH THE LIVE CONCERT
COMING UP, I DON'T WANT
TO GET IN THE WAY OF
YOUR PRACTICE, SO I WON'T
BE DROPPING BY THE STUDIO.
GOOD LUCK.
What time do you think
you can make it home, Nana?
WHAT TIME DO YOU THINK
YOU CAN MAKE IT HOME, NANA?
WITH THE LIVE CONCERT
COMING UP, I DON'T WANT
TO GET IN THE WAY OF
YOUR PRACTICE, SO I WON'T
BE DROPPING BY THE STUDIO.
GOOD LUCK.
WHAT TIME DO YOU THINK
YOU CAN MAKE IT HOME, NANA?
WITH THE LIVE CONCERT
COMING UP, I DON'T WANT
TO GET IN THE WAY OF
YOUR PRACTICE, SO I WON'T
BE DROPPING BY THE STUDIO.
GOOD LUCK.
With the live concert
coming up,
WHAT TIME DO YOU THINK
YOU CAN MAKE IT HOME, NANA?
WITH THE LIVE CONCERT
COMING UP, I DON'T WANT
TO GET IN THE WAY OF
YOUR PRACTICE, SO I WON'T
BE DROPPING BY THE STUDIO.
GOOD LUCK.
I don't wanna get in the way
of your practice,
WHAT TIME DO YOU THINK
YOU CAN MAKE IT HOME, NANA?
WITH THE LIVE CONCERT
COMING UP, I DON'T WANT
TO GET IN THE WAY OF
YOUR PRACTICE, SO I WON'T
BE DROPPING BY THE STUDIO.
GOOD LUCK.
so I won't be dropping by
the studio. Good luck.
Give my best to everyone. Hachiko.
GIVE MY BEST TO EVERYONE.
HACHIKO.
Give my best to everyone. Hachiko.
Trapnest's time off came
to an end,
but Nana didn't come home.
I simply assumed
she was with Ren.
I wanted to at least drop by
the studio and see Nana.
But I didn't because
I didn't have the guts to see Nobu.
As usual Takumi didn't send me
a single email.
But surprisingly, I accepted that
with an open mind,
casually thinking he'll eventually
come to see me again.
I couldn't tell if that was
a feeling of trust or resignation.
Misato!
Thank you for coming all
the way out to pick me up, Miss Komatsu.
It's not a problem.
And call me Hachiko.
That's such a cute nickname.
We still have time before
the concert,
so why don't we go home first
so you can leave your bags?
I'll carry one.
Thank you so much.
Is it really okay to stay
at your place again?
Mhm. You can stay for as
many nights as you wish.
It's summer vacation,
so you have free time, don't you?
Yes.
To be honest, I would love to spend all
of my summer vacation here,
but I couldn't possibly impose
on you for a full month.
That's totally okay with me!
Then spend your whole
summer vacation here!
Or rather, I want you to stay!
Are you sure? I'm thrilled!
I'm just as glad about it.
- Nana's staying with Ren...
- A train will be arriving on track one.
and shows no sign of returning.
- I was feeling all lonely living alone.
- Please stay inside the yellow line.
You know, I still can't get over
the excitement
after learning that Nana and Ren
are all lovey-dovey.
I carelessly blurted it out.
I assumed you would already know.
But I did secretly find out when
they were back in my hometown
that the two were living together.
I've been wondering what had
happened between them after that,
so this news is such a relief to me.
Please don't tell anyone, okay?
Rest assured.
Please have faith in me, Miss Hachiko.
The concert starts at seven, right?
I can't wait to see
the band members.
I wonder if they're still rehearsing.
Actually, I haven't seen them
for a week.
But I thought you visited the studio
every day to see them practice.
Well, yeah, but...
I didn't wanna bother them
so close to their live performance.
I see. You're right.
Let's hope that BLAST's professional
debut becomes a reality.
Mhm.
If I were to see Nobu today,
what expression should I make?
Nobu may never smile for me again.
That thought almost made me cry.
That other night, when Nana sang
that song that Nobu wrote.
She was wishing for something
as she sang it with such passion...
so her voice would reach me.
Right now, I realize
what she was wishing.
I reached into the sky
But I couldn't reach what I wanted
They grew smaller
and disappeared into the sky
Like colorful balloons
I'm alone
My hand had no place to go
And gently you took it
Starless night
I won't look back
at the shadow of my past
I want to feel your warmth
Tears are falling down
Even if I'm unsure I won't let go
Of your hand holding mine