Say, Nana Komatsu.
We used to spend
so much time together,
but I didn't understand you one bit.
Well, you see... to understand you
is usually impossible!
So give me a break, will you?
Blinking eyes call the wind
A smile clears all the noise away
The angel in your eyes whispers
"Everything begins now"
Can you feel it now
It's like being caught in a wave
Pulling on my heart
Breath held, arms reaching out
Baby this world is
different from yesterday's
You're the only one I can see
Baby my wish on a wing
This sky is torn
By a single overflowing word
Hello! Welcome to Junko's room.
Long time no see. I wonder what
customers we'll have today.
Welcome!
Wow! I've wanted to come here
for so long! "Junko's room"!
Um, who are you?
Ooh, Naoki of Trapnest. Welcome.
Oh, right. Welcome. But wait.
Why is a guy with a bigger role here?!
Could it possibly be,
you're here because...
- Naoki, is your role in jeopardy?!
Papa-rakkyo!
Oh, don't worry about this.
He's like a zashiki warashi or jizo statue
of Junko's room.
Really?
Who are you calling a jizo statue?!
You know,
I'm being treated terribly lately.
In the last "Junko's room," I was here...
- By the way, isn't Hachiko here today?
- but didn't have a single line.
By Hachiko,
do you mean Nana Komatsu?
Yeah. I hear she's quite something.
She's not only a great strategist,
but she's a great cook and great in bed.
In addition, she thinks of Takumi
and Takumi only.
- Um...
- I wonder about that.
Huh?
Why don't we watch the video?
Hey, Hachi...
That Takumi is so annoying.
Hachi is our pet.
Don't talk of her like she's a dog.
But doesn't it piss you off?
Get her back, Nobu.
You like Hachi, don't you?
It may have very well happened
in the heat of the moment,
but knowing Hachi, she may become
more and more serious about him.
But if Takumi continues treating
this relationship in that manner,
Hachi is obviously gonna get hurt.
Are you okay with that, Nobu?
I don't like it one bit.
If you want her, go for it.
I'm sorry about suddenly
coming over last night
and blurting out weird nonsense.
So, now that I've come to
see you like this again,
this time I'm gonna be direct with you.
I love you.
I know that I'm not being fair
by saying this now.
Since I know about you and Takumi.
I'm sorry. You didn't come
to the studio today
even if you wanted to because
of what I said, right?
I'm sorry, that's not it!
I was working today!
I don't mind, so please drop by
like you've been doing.
Everyone feels a bit lonely
without your presence, Hachi.
Actually, it's me who gets sad.
Thank you.
Thank goodness.
That's good enough for me.
Nobu! Thank you for
walking me home.
Huh?
I'll be fine on my own from here on.
I'm almost home.
I'm sorry for having you take
a longer route home
in order to walk me home every day.
No, I don't mind it.
Nana!
Well, well. It's you.
Well, thank you very much for that.
Okay, then. Thank you, Nobu.
Good night.
I can't take it anymore.
What's the matter?
Nothing! It's none of your business!
Um, sorry. Please leave me alone.
Shin.
A man and a woman are
simply opposing creatures
driven toward each other by lust.
Can they be connected by love?
Sorry, I don't know either.
- Yes.
- Takumi, .,
I wanna see you.
Nana...
- Thank you!
- F-For what?
I thought you would
never talk to me again.
So I'm glad that you came tonight.
What are you talking about?
That's nonsense.
Of course I'd talk to you.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
You've done nothing wrong.
That's not true.
The truth is...
I'm a really horrible woman!
What's this about being
a horrible woman?
A really horrible woman?
But it's true.
You're idealizing me for sure, Nobu!
Otherwise there's no way
you'd fall in love with me!
If you knew the real me...
you'd be disappointed.
Then, disappoint me.
I want you to.
Because I don't know what else
I can do to stop loving you.
I'm sorry. I'll break it off with Takumi.
I really didn't want anyone to know
about what happened with Takumi.
I thought, then I could act like
nothing happened
and become your girlfriend.
I had such cunning thoughts.
Lots of them.
Do you hate me now?
Huh?
No. I'm happy.
I can't take you from him by force.
I can't have you do something
that'll make you a horrible woman.
I don't find you cunning.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
It can't be helped that
you're attracted to Takumi.
And no matter how hard I try,
I'll probably never be able
to compete with him.
That's not true! I!
But if you tell me that
you're still gonna break it off with him
and be my woman...
I'll do everything I can
to make you happy.
For the sake of your happiness,
I will do everything within my power.
I mean, with you by my side,
I feel like I can do anything.
When you break it off with Takumi...
and sort out your feelings...
then come to me.
I'll be waiting faithfully.
Sorry, I have to go now.
I'll call you when I have some time.
You don't have to!
In fact, don't ever call me again!
Huh?
Goodbye!
Hi there!
Stop startling me!
I told you yesterday.
Put an end to things first,
and then come to me.
But I did. That's why I came.
Too fast!
Nana...
Hmm?
You know, I... Nobu...
I think I'm head over heels
in love with Nobu.
Isn't it natural?
Huh? Nobu and Takumi?
Um, Nana Osaki and Ren of
our band are back together.
She lives with Hachiko, and...
Lately, the relationships are
becoming so confusing.
Hey, look here!
It's a diagram of the character
relationships in the anime, Nana,
that I made to clarify things.
Wow!
It doesn't really clarify anything.
Huh? Naoki's not connected to anyone.
Huh?
Wh-What are you saying!
I'm Yasu's best friend!
Even now,
he's supposed to be meeting me...
FROM: YASU
I HAVE OTHER PLANS
STOP CALLING ME OVER AND OVER!
Is he really your best friend?
Sure he is!
Come to think of it, he said this.
MR. Y. T. (AGE 23) OF TOKYO
How are you doing?
I'm glad I could finally see you!
Because you were being such a pest.
And there also was this comment.
MR. T. I. (AGE 23) OF TOKYO
Then go home. Our band can make it
without you, Naoki.
Why?! Why do you two
know so much?!
Junko's room is that sorta place.
That's right.
No matter who says what,
Yasu and I are best friends!
- I'm gonna draw one!
- Ahh!
- I'm gonna draw a line here!
- Don't do it!
Now he's completely isolated.
You are pregnant.
This small black circle you see is
the sack that contains your baby.
And the little dot you see inside it
is your baby.
Morning sickness?
I won't keep it, so don't worry!
There's no need for you to
feel responsible, Takumi.
I'm the foolish one.
This child could be my boyfriend's.
Go home.
And don't come back again.
Is your boyfriend Nobu?
Takumi?
What are you doing?
Takumi...
NOBU
Don't tell Nobu!
What is it?
Hey, can you hear me?
Yes.
Nana's pregnant.
I don't know if it's yours or mine,
but regardless,
if Nana wants to keep it,
I intend on becoming its guardian
and raising it as my own.
What do you think?
Nana... Is it true that you're pregnant?
Hey...
I wanna hear it directly from you.
It could be my child.
There's no need to hide it from me.
And I knew that you had just
broken things off with Takumi.
I'm sorry.
Why...
are you apologizing?
Didn't you break it off with him?!
Please make up an excuse.
I don't care if it's a lie. I'll believe you.
I'm sorry!
I wanna have this child and
raise it as your child, Takumi.
If it's okay with you.
Wanna get married?
Huh?
If I marry an ordinary girl, the media
won't go too crazy over this.
No?
Married?
So I'm sorry, but...
could you find a new roommate?
But sure, that's not fair to you
having her move out so suddenly,
so I'll pay half the rent until
you find a new roommate.
I don't need it!
I can't stand the thought of you
doing it with some other man.
Don't you worry about a thing and
just focus on pleasing me.
You're a lot more important
to me than my boyfriend, Nana.
I think I'm head over heels
in love with Nobu.
Could you find a new roommate?
If you don't like it, I don't want it either.
I wanna use it as a set.
Why don't you use
the strawberry glass?
Because there are only two of them.
What if I break one?
But if you don't use them,
what's the point of having them?
Yeah, but still,
it's too sad if one of a set breaks.
You can use it,
but be sure to be careful, okay?
Nana?
Leave her alone.
TO NANA
What's this?
Hachi!
Hachiko, are you here?
I can't count
how many nights
I wished tomorrow
would never come
To live as I am
without being fake
What do I need
If I don't believe in myself,
what can I believe in
The answer is
too close to see
Black tears are
falling down
I have nothing,
only sadness
I can't put it
into words
My whole body
starts to ache
I can't stand it anymore
on my own
So there you have it.
Did you enjoy the third installment
of Junko's room?
Until we meet again some day.
- Bye-bye.
- Huh? Wait a minute.
Good bye.
I-I-I should have more lines.
Huh? Huh? Wait!