Genshiken
I woke up and as usual forgot
my cell and missed the Express.
My life reflected in
the train window.
I'm sure I have something that
I won't lose to anyone in Japan...
... but it's pretty sad
that no one notices it.
I can't run fast, though.
I'm not that strongly-built.
Here I go, at my dauntless pace.
Pass away, today's
sadness, raining in the sun!
Hesitation, repetition,
dreaming all night, all night.
Farewell sadness,
to outer space you go!
Look to the sky and shout
at the top of your lungs!
At this tempo!
Right now, at this tempo!
Genshiken
All right, this is more or
less the financial report.
Since we saved money
on the school festival...
...and had our activities suspended,
we have quite the budget...
Oh?
Look what I found, a sketchbook.
H-Hey, Kasukabe!
Can I look through it?
Wow.
Pretty Menma
Yow, it's full of models and figures.
No touching, okay?
Look, Saki, these are
costumes for you to wear.
Why not try them on, since you're here?
Don't wanna see it, don't wanna hear it.
This is how I live, love it or leave it.
See ya.
12, Problems and Countermeasures Arise When
an Organization Undergoes Reconstruction
No more intruders left.
Yeah, I guess we're in gallery mode now.
Why don't we go?
Ohh, sure.
That's unusual...
Wanna get something to eat?
Let's do that.
What to get...
What's the matter?
That's not a safe place to be.
I figured you'd show up about now.
Oh, really...
I don't suppose you have some
plan to turn all this around?
Eh...
No, sorry, I don't...
Maybe this time you went a bit
too far, starting that fire...
Yeah...
But according to the information I've
procured, the club won't be disbanded.
Information?
A limited suspension of activities...
...with some volunteer work
during that time, I'd say.
Wouldn't it make you happier
to see Genshiken go away?
Uh well yeah, that is true.
It's like, gotten boring lately
having to meet at people's places.
Like it's no fun, not
how the group should be.
I don't think it's something you
should feel so responsible for.
They probably don't blame you
as much as they say they do.
That might be true.
But for all that...
Several days later, a formal
punishment was issued to Genshiken.
For one month from the day of
issue, suspension of club activities...
...no usage of the club office...
...and over 100 combined hours of
volunteer work between all members.
We were allowed to take things
we needed from the club room...
...as long as it didn't
amount to too much.
Should we keep this in someone's room?
Good idea, we can use it for New Year's.
Get some controllers and games too.
I wonder what the volunteer
program will be like.
Who knows!
But it'll probably be welfare-related or
helping out with official events, right?
I guess there's a lot of
that over the holidays.
You're probably right.
Right in the middle
of year-end sale wars!
Not having time for
any of it really stings!
All thanks to someone!
Now, now.
Saki?
What's the matter?
Hey, Saki?
Me?
Was it me?
Did I do that?
Well duh!
I mean, she's really crying?
It's not just an act?
It's for real!
We're sorry.
We didn't realize, did we?
R-Right.
We'll leave the rest to you, Kohsaka!
Everybody out! Hurry!
I-Isn't it a bad idea to
leave them by themselves?
What?
T-That's right, we don't know what'll
happen in a situation like this!
And y-you're the one
with the key, M-Madarame.
Anyway you're the
one who made her cry!
H-Hey, wait a minute.
This is your chance!
If you wait you won't be able to go!
Do it as our chairman!
You know, lately...
Yeah.
I can't smoke.
Smoke?
Cigarettes...
I mean, fire...
It scares me even in my dreams...
W-Well that's just as well!
Cigarettes are bad for you!
Crap, that didn't work.
It's okay, I know you were scared.
Don't worry, just relax.
R-Really, when that happened...
I dropped my cigarette
because Madarame scared me.
Of course, it was
me, it was my fault.
No, it's my fault!
I can see that...
That's why I even cosplayed, but I'm
always having to make it up to everyone.
Of course! Sorry!
I won't talk about it anymore.
Damn, is that the only
way I can talk right now?
But you know, Saki...
I think cosplaying was
the right thing to do.
That became more a way for
us to appeal to other clubs...
...than for you to make things up to us.
After that, the others weren't
so harsh towards Genshiken.
Uh, yeah, that's very true.
The mood around us
changed a bit after that.
The video the manga club shot seems
to have quite the cult following.
So even if it takes time, part of
why Genshiken can pick up the pieces...
...is because we have
that going for us...
Besides, the reason we pick on you...
...is that we all like you.
That sounded so embarrassing, I just...
I'm going to the bathroom.
Okay.
Yeah, she hasn't been smoking lately.
You're right, and she
no longer smells of it.
Well, maybe this is an
unexpected side of her.
I wouldn't call it unexpected...
But it's something we
easily fail to notice.
Saki.
Hold on, I need to fix my face.
Here's the key.
All right, I'll accept
responsibility for it.
This is the volunteer work schedule.
Many thanks.
We're sorry for the trouble.
You should tell that
to your club members.
That's true.
Well, good luck.
Pardon?
Nothing.
Ah, there they are.
Are we done?
Yup, thanks for helping.
Let's call it a day.
Are you sure?
Well, you know...
You're right.
It'd also be better for Saki
to settle down a little more.
Bye.
Yeah.
So, shall we grab some food?
Sure, it'd be a good way to finish up.
Where to?
How about some beef bowl from
Handaya?
Or cabbage fried rice at Soukutsuya.
I'm for kiev style cutlet at Chiruchiru.
W-Want to sing?
No singing!
Ehhh!
Volunteer work schedule
That can't be!
T-This sucks.
So much for Comic Fest.
All three days.
Man...
No.
Just one of us has the 30th free.
I don't suppose you're going
to suggest another penalty game.
No, this is a request.
No!
But even if Kasukabe did that for us,
she'd probably just get
more mainstream dojinshi.
We can always just buy that
kind afterwards at dojin shops.
No, there's also Comic
Fest-specific limited editions!
That's why someone must go in person!
I know better than that.
Your ultimate goal isn't to
buy dojinshi, it's to use them.
You'd make me be your gopher
for something like that?
She's a tough one.
If you understand us that
well, I'll get to the point.
Here it comes.
If I may be so bold!
It's always gotta be
some big production.
A winter break without
new books from Comic Fest...
...is more boring than we can stand!
And when it's that boring, we're of course
going to spend it doing you-know-what!
In other words, nothing but
m- m-m...the whole time!
Wham.
She really punched him.
Like her arm just extended.
This is volunteer work,
and the last time...
I'll go!
So, this is the first Kujiun
series summarization meeting.
Wasn't it the New Year's / Genshiken
is back in business party?
Well, it certainly did take
a long time to come home!
All kinds of volunteer work, forced labor,
working for free, compulsory service!
You can stop making it sound like
all I did was go buy dojinshi.
I worked at a nursery.
So anyway, yes, let's stop
talking about that and cut! Right?
Tokino!
Please come over, Tokino!
We're waiting for you!
Come on!
What can you see from there?
What I can see from here is...
A view I'm sure we've never seen before!
This is it! This is the
quality I wanted to see!
The sale date got pushed
back again and again...
...and some said it
would never be released.
But this changes my
opinion of Yamabata now.
T-These days only a-artist
type directors tend to stand out.
Like Aizawa and Seki.
Yeah, they're a bit over-hyped.
Their tricks are too
obvious and polished.
I'll say.
It shows we need to pay
more respect towards these...
...negotiator-type
professional directors.
It's the same as ever.
Yes, it is.
I've got something I need
to say, if now's a good time.
What is it?
Well, h-how to say this...
Um...
Might I retire as chairman?
Huh?
W-What brought this on?
Well, I guess, this seemed
like a good stopping point.
I'm not too sure.
Oh really?
Just come out and say it...
Someone's been causing too many
problems and you're tired of it!
Uh, no, I was afraid to say it since
I thought you'd take it that way.
Besides.
I have to start job hunting this year.
Job hunting?
Knock off the harmony, you two!
Well, I think it could be good
timing, not really too early.
It's January, after all.
True...
And so, as for my successor...
I'd like Sasahara to do it.
Eh?
W-Why me?
I'm not suited at all, am I?
Hmm, well, you don't look like you've
ever been in charge of anything before.
Of course not!
But, when I look at these faces...
There's no generalized
otaku there but you.
One of them isn't even otaku at all.
Why not?
It was process of
elimination the last time too.
It's a tradition.
N-Not a very good one.
Well, we have Kasukabe's
stamp of approval...
Okay!
So new chairman, tell us your ambitions.
Ah, all right...
Now that I've become chairman...
Kind of like Madarame.
Shut up!
Just once I'd like to see us
participate as a circle at Comic Fest!
Oh?
Ah, he said it.
I'm not involved.
What's the big deal?
Participate as a circle?
It means becoming a
seller at Comic Fest.
Making dojinshi.
Are you thinking
"gaku-man" for a genre?
What's "gaku-man?"
It means a school's manga club.
Is there a series you wanted to parody?
A series I want to do?
If we're going to do this, I want to do a
male-oriented offset-printed Kujiun book!
"Male-oriented?"
Uh, um, umm umm...
Umm, uh, uhhh...
Never mind, I get it.
Suioh University Entrance Exam Site
What?
You're alone.
I'm meeting someone.
I see.
Oh, yes.
Good job on things.
Various things.
You fit in well over there.
Didn't Kugayama draw it?
Why not a sketch of Yamada?
Well, it's my personal preference.
I still don't know what direction
the story will take in the end.
What's up?
Yo.
What's that?
The Comic Fest application.
Really.
If we're accepted,
will you be a salesgirl?
Sounds like fun, but I'll pass.
If you think it sounds like fun...
If I did it, I'm sure I'd take the
money like this, like it's dirty.
Still, really doing the application...
I guess, I've longed vaguely for this...
...but once I came out and said
it, it suddenly felt real...
It's like maybe I really
did want to do this.
Come to think of it, dojinshi were
part of why I joined Genshiken.
Yeah, what a surprise.
And now, here you are
applying to Comic Fest.
Have I gone up or down?
Come on.
Down, obviously!
And oh yeah, that was when
Kasukabe hit me for the first time.
Wow, that takes me back.
You've got a good memory.
I mean, sorry!
You shouldn't hit people
when you first meet them.
No, it's all right.
Well, I'm sure I've turned
out the way I was meant to.
How I joined Genshiken then,
how I'm chairman of it now...
...and even down to how I'm
applying to Comic Fest, everything.
Might as well keep going
until I get there...
Oh, yeah, what should we
do about our circle name?
Hmm, The Society for the Study of
Modern Visual Culture's no good.
Of course not, we're applying
as totally male-oriented.
Guess the abbreviation's out, too.
I wouldn't say it's completely
out, but it's not that good.
Let's think of something weird, then.
How about "Genshiken" in hiragana?
Ahh, good idea.
Yeah, yeah, a subtly dubious
sound might be the ticket.
Hello.
Howdy.
You're just in time
to see a legend born.
Like what?
Kasukabe did the naming.
Don't go nuts on me.
Nice sound.
G-Good sense.
Being told I have good sense for this
kind of thing makes me really nervous.
It's all good, it's all good.
I'll hit you.
That aside, take a look at this.
Let's see.
Oh awesome!
Who did the original?
M-Manta. From Sangakudou.
Ahh, I see.
It's out already?
I could have sworn...
Genshiken
We took no detours or shortcuts...
... and we weren't afraid of
what tomorrow would bring...
... as we kept walking down
Inogashira Street late at night.
Only vivid dreams extended
deep into the shadows.
We aren't quite grown up.
Simple but complicated
glistening like marbles.
The time we spied from there sparkled,
even if nothing big happened.
What we see from the marbles in
our hands now is a little different...
... but they shine faintly nearby.
What was with this episode?
It was boring and ridiculous.
It wasn't even worth watching!
The "light and shadow of youth?"
Who wrote this embarrassing stuff?
But Mistress Renko, you
spoke your part so well.
It moved me!
D-Don't be stupid!
That was just part of the script,
and it wasn't how I really felt.
You really are a fool if
you don't realize that.
Then you really are
mean, Mistress Renko.
What, that again...
Next episode, the long-awaited finale.
Kujibiki Unbalance,
the final tournament.
Mean Mistress Renko is finally
going to be active again!
Stop referring to me that way...