This is... Lord Wales'...
The letter has been taken,
and the Prince's life was taken
in front of my eyes...
The greatest responsibility
for all of this is mine.
I couldn't see the truth
about Wardes...
Now, lift your head, Louise Françoise.
Thank you for his final
memento and will...
Thank you, Louise...
Princess...
A history of the couple's romance
that starts from the first kiss
You, the one who cast magic on
this destiny, suddenly appeared
The sky where two moons
never fade away
That's an impossibility, right?
This is the first time I've
felt anything like this
I'm feeling more and more
at ease with this place
Even if you trip and
become depressed
I will always hold you
tight with a squeeze
The story where we met that day
stays hot with a sweet kiss
See, you can cast magic, and
the wishes will surely come true
A history of the couple's romance
that starts from the first kiss
You, the one who cast magic on
this destiny, suddenly appeared
Zero Treasure
Isn't this another false lead, as usual?
This time, I am sure that
this information is true!
Come in.
Oh, Miss Vallière.
Hello, Mr. Colbert...
Um... I'm here to report...
All right, I'll accept
your vacation notice.
About how many days?
We are heading to the village of Talb,
so I believe that we will be back
by the solar eclipse at the latest.
Then, if you will excuse me...
Mr. Colbert is taking some time off?
Apparently, he has found the
location of the legendary dragon.
Legendary dragon?
He's gone on a search for
a legendary something in the past,
and almost stranded himself
out in the ocean.
Well, I'm not counting on him much.
Now, let's hear the report.
Yes, sir.
The Reconquista?
This looks like it will be
rather troublesome.
Thank you for the hard work.
You should take a nice vacation.
Um, Old Osman?
Do you know about the
descendant of the Void?
My memory is uncertain,
and I don't know who it was
that called me that,
but I'm sure...
Void is the legendary element of
magic that has long been lost.
Legendary?
Such amazing magic...
Or rather, even normal magic
for me is, well, um...
You don't have to go into the details.
I guess Gundolf is for real as well.
Gundolf?
Saito is the legendary familiar?
That's impossible.
Here we go...
I'm back.
What is it?
I can't stay in clothes stained
from such a long journey!
So I was just changing clothes.
Oh, so there was more laundry.
Geez.
If you complain too much,
you can do without food!
Yeah, yeah...
How can you go back
to normal like that?
You kissed me!
You know...
What is it?
How do I put it...
Cheer up, okay?
Well, this is about all I can say.
Saito...
The elastic is broken.
Yeah, it's broken for sure.
What does that mean?
You say that, but...
Oh, well.
You don't suppose, back then...
Back then?
Oh, no, nothing.
I mean, it's not something
I did on purpose!
I'm just disciplining a familiar
that doesn't take good care
of his master's belongings.
I can't possibly be disciplined
over a pair of panties!
It's not that I wanted to do that
when I did it, either!
That's right! You're just a familiar
because you can't help it,
because otherwise you can't eat!
That's right! Looks like
you do understand!
If you hate it that much,
you can get out of here!
Oh, is that so?
This familiar will follow his
master's orders, master!
That hurt!
Geez!
I was looking out for her!
That selfish girl!
Why did I do such a thing?
"Such a thing"?
Siesta!
That outfit...
I was granted vacation,
so I'm going home for a while.
I see, going back home.
It's a rather small village.
At least, you're lucky you have
a place to go back to.
Come to think of it, you said before
that your grandfather
came from another world?
Yes, that would be my
great-grandfather.
Can you tell me the
details of that story?
I was on a desperate journey
for the sake of our country,
but Montmorency thinks that
I went on vacation to cheat on her.
That's all thanks to your
usual everyday behavior.
So can you tell her...
Geez, Saito, are you cheating
with a girl like that again?
Kirche! My favor...
Shut up!
Two dragons?!
Yes.
The first one disappeared
in the solar eclipse,
and my great-grandfather was
aboard the second dragon.
One disappeared from there,
and the other fell
somewhere, they say.
Seriously? And what
happened to that dragon?
Apparently, it is a family heirloom,
and has been enshrined somewhere.
Though I've never seen it.
Siesta!
Yes?
Can you take me to your village?
What?
Did you hear that?
Yeah... A treasure...
Tabitha, what do you think?
Not interested.
I'm super-interested!
Back then, I hated it,
but I couldn't help it...
Geez!
Why can't I get it out of my mind?!
I've said too much. I'm sorry...
No, that doesn't sound
dignified enough as a master.
I'll forgive you. You should be
thankful of it!
Maybe a bit too harsh?
Where did he go?
Someone's trying to apologize here...
Siesta?
She just left, saying she was
going to see her folks back home.
Going home?
Yeah. To the village of Talb.
Anything wrong with Siesta?
No, nothing. Thank you.
Siesta's home, is it?!
That dog is always in heat!
He kissed me, yet... Kissed me, yet...
Kissed me, yet... Kissed me, yet...
He kissed me, yet...
The village of Talb?
I've heard of it somewhere.
It's just a little more.
It's really nice here.
Um, is it all right?
What is?
Coming out here without
permission from Miss Vallière...
It's all right.
Mr. Saito...
I'll wait here.
Here? Please come to our house.
I'd like to properly introduce you
to everyone in the family.
Properly...
Come on, wouldn't that cause
a misunderstanding?
I see.
Oh, well, um... If you
get that depressed...
I'm sorry.
This is important to you,
isn't it, Mr. Saito?
Then I'll look up the location of
the treasure, and be right back.
Thanks. Sorry to be a bother, Siesta.
It's all right.
She's such a good girl.
Yeah,
much more than that selfish girl
that has nothing but pride.
But your real feelings
are over there, after all?
Of course not! You stay quiet!
The village of Talb is right up ahead!
I secretly brought out what was
hidden in the back of the shed.
Is the dragon here?
Apparently, the correct name
for it is the Robe of the Dragon.
Robe?
Yes.
I heard that my great-grandfather
flew from another world using it.
Using?
There they are.
Kirche?
Mole?
That means...
Hey.
You guys... Why...
Or rather, what for?
Of course, it's to look for the treasure!
What?!
It's this cave?
I'm so excited!
You know, I'm not
playing around here.
Neither am I.
I have the fine objective of
finding a hidden treasure,
so that Montmorency will get
a better opinion of me!
What a grand objective!
I'm so looking forward to this.
I couldn't do much back in Albion.
Albion...
I wonder what happened
to them after that incident.
Lord Cromwell!
Finally, the Tudor family
that had been using
this country of Albion for
themselves have all fallen.
Glory to the newly reborn Albion!
Hurray for Albion! Hurray for Albion!
I wonder how far this goes?
I don't know. Not even the
village folk get near here.
It's said to have a nest of orc demons.
Say things like that before we go in!
Someone is coming.
Someone?
Someone other than us...
These are footsteps, right?
From behind us...
Seems that way.
Who is it?!
Who's there?!
Siesta, behind me!
Okay!
That was a warning.
If you value your life, leave now!
Dammit!
Verdande!
Wait, this voice...
You thieves, going after
a valuable historical relic!
Mr. Colbert!
You guys?
Louise?!
I gained information that the
ruins of the dragon was here,
and I came here to excavate,
but to think that all of you would...
So our objectives are the same?
Objective?
Oh... This is...
Then, are you someone who is
of the blood of another world?
To think that such a valuable
piece of research material
was so close at hand!
What an oversight!
It's just a legend,
and I'm not sure whether
that map is correct or not...
I'm here as an aide to our
instructor's research.
It's not that I came chasing
after you or anything.
I didn't say anything.
I didn't want you to misunderstand,
so I just said it first!
And why would I misunderstand?!
You know, lovers' quarrels
are nice and all...
It's not a lover's quarrel!
But you'll be left behind.
This is turning out to be
just like a class.
Watch your step!
Don't get out of line!
It was a fun treasure hunt
in the beginning.
Watch your step!
Don't get out of line!
It was a fun treasure hunt
in the beginning.
No time for small talk!
This is...
Amazing.
How fitting, for a hidden
treasure to rest here.
And the treasure?
According to the map,
it's around here.
That is...
If it's a key of this nature,
it looks like it can be
unlocked with magic.
Tabitha, what are you looking at?
Those are unfamiliar letters.
Okay, it's opening up!
Navy Ensign, Sasaki Takeo,
rests here in another world...
You can read it?
It's Japanese...
The language of my home country.
What?!
Here it is! This is it!
What is this?
I've never seen anything
like this before.
This is the Robe of the Dragon?
You're kidding...
I'm certain.
There's no doubt about it.
A Zero fighter!
It looks like it has been preserved
with stability magic.
To think it really existed...
You know, when I first
saw you, Siesta,
somehow, I got
a feeling of nostalgia...
I see. The black hair and eyes
came from Japanese blood.
Japanese?
Your great-grandfather and I
come from the same world.
Saito!
You might be able to
return to your world!
They appeared together
with the solar eclipse,
and one Robe of the Dragon
disappeared into the eclipse.
Why couldn't the other one, in other
words, this one, return as well?
It is said that my great-grandfather
flew around in the skies even
after the other Robe disappeared,
and in due time landed...
I believe he missed
the right timing for it.
Timing?
The solar eclipse must have
ended while he was flying,
and he couldn't return.
In other words, if you
fly into the solar eclipse
with this Robe of the Dragon,
perhaps you will be able to fly
back into your alternate world?
Then, if Mr. Saito was
to get inside this,
and plunge into the solar eclipse,
he can go back to his world?
Well, that is only an assumption
that I've made,
but that possibility is rather high.
There's a chance that I can go back?
Saito is going to be gone...
Then what of the letter sent to
Wales of Albion, my nephew?
There is no mistake,
Archduchess Marian.
I have received word from Germania
that they would like to
call off the engagement.
My haphazard actions have
caused this situation.
Please, punish me
however much you want.
You have been through
enough pain already,
with the death of your loved one.
That which has passed
cannot be helped.
Let us accept all of it as destiny.
Mother...
Your Highness!
There is a crisis!
To think you'd really find it...
I thought you'd get stranded up
in the mountains this time.
I thank you for your efforts
in transporting and becoming
caretaker of the Robe.
Something of this caliber...
I'm sure I can get permission
to have it at the Institute
as valuable research material
deemed by the Palace.
Now for fuel...
That's right!
Mr. Colbert!
If you can make lots of this,
I'm sure the Robe of
the Dragon will work!
Oh, just as I thought!
I was not mistaken when I thought
that was the blood of the dragon?!
It's not blood, it's gasoline.
Gasoline?
Hup...
This is the rudder...
And this is the pitch lever...
Is this for real? I really know it all!
That's why I told you
you'd know if you got on.
You can freely use all sorts
of arms and weapons.
That's what this is, right?
Yeah, there's no mistake that
this was a weapon of war.
Saito...
Saito is going to be gone...
Louise!
We have a huge problem!
Shut up.
I just heard in the village...
What did you hear?
Another rumor of a cute girl?
Albion...
Albion?!
Albion changed its name to the
New State of the Reconquista...
And declared war on Tristein!
You're kidding, right?
But when is a solar eclipse coming?
All of Albion, nobles
and peasants alike,
are bowing down in servitude
to you, Your Excellency.
What should be feared is the
magical power hidden in this ring.
It was worth the efforts taken in
taking it from the Water Spirit.
But this is only a foothold,
in order to take the
entire continent as mine.
Next, we will take the country
in the center of the
continent, Tristein.
We have already set up for that.
Tristein no longer has
anywhere to escape to.
They're no match for the
esteemed Dragoons of Albion,
as soon as we send them in.
Now, when will this land of Albion
be closest to the continent?
In three days...
On the day of the solar eclipse.
As if I were under a real magic spell
A bright smile is burnt onto my heart
But each time I see you, I give you
a pointy, cold shoulder
Why do I act mean towards the one
that I think about the most?
My true feelings, the
shards of loneliness
In the deepest part of my heart,
I'm calling for you
For the day to start from zero
Since when has there been pain in my
heart when we have an argument?
Since when is it that I can't help
but think of the girl that's
standing next to you?
Farewell, Saito.
Next episode - the final episode:
Louise the Void
Next Episode: Louise the Void
Next episode - the final episode:
Louise the Void
Next Episode: Louise the Void