That far off future was suddenly upon us...
And soon, it too will become a passing memory.
Alicia, the future always has
a worried look on its face.
So let's go greet it with a smile, together.
Akari...
Alicia, good morning.
My, good morning, Akari.
Umm... I put on my uniform.
My, my!
Yes, it looks great on you!
W-What is it?
I'm just happy, that's all.
We heard!
Ah, yeah. I've become a Prima, too.
Ah, yeah, congratulations.
Really congratulations.
Ehh? That's it?
This is no time for that!
Is it true that Alicia's retiring
because she's getting married?
Is it true?
Yeah.
That's not the only reason
for her retirement, though.
Apparently the Gondola Association has wanted
Alicia to be a Managing Director for a while now.
They said they'd like her to work
not only for the future of the Aria Company,
but for the future of the
entire Water Guide Industry.
But regardless of how amazing Alicia is,
it's impossible for her to hold both jobs.
Apparently she asked them
to wait until I became a Prima.
I was really surprised about her marriage, too.
I think she was waiting on that as well,
until I became a Prima.
If only I had been more dependable...
Ah, it's the phone.
Hello, this is the Aria...
Sideburns!!
Akatsuki...
Is A-A-A-Alicia really getting m-m-m-married?
It's not true, right? Please tell me it's not true!
It's true.
We've been getting a storm of inquiries
by phone and email all morning.
I wonder where everyone
is hearing the news from?
Do you remember that day
Oboeteimasuka ano hi o
When your heart suddenly began to race
Futo kanjita tokimeki o
The rays from the blue sky were pouring over you...
Aoi hizashi abite
...as you cut through the wind
Kaze o kiru kimi ni
I couldn't look away, and when our eyes met
Mitoreru to me ga atte
I couldn't help but smile
Egao koboreta
It's just like a spiral
Marude supiraare
As the days begin to swirl in brilliant colors
Azayaka ni mawaridashita hibi
Always and forever, they're filled with love
Itsumo itsudemo ai ga michiteita
Surely, it's a spiral
Kitto supiraare
The days passed by, each one filled with warmth
Atataka na mainichi o kasanetara
And before I knew it, off in the distance...
Itsunomanika tooku ni
...there you were
Kiteita no ne
To That New Beginning...
So?
Are you all right?
Huh?
Ah, yeah.
Alicia said she'd stay until
things calm down at the company.
And the association will be handling
her retirement ceremony, so...
That's not what we mean, Akari.
Are you all right?
We're really worried.
Yeah.
Thank you, Aika, Alice.
I'm sure...
...I'll be fine.
Yes...
I'm sure...
Ever since the day she
told me about her retirement,
I've been really busy with a lot of things.
The days have become really hectic.
But Alicia is always smiling.
Not one thing has changed about our days here.
Time is passing by like it always has.
These are gentle...
...and happy days.
Alicia is here.
President Aria is here.
And I'm here.
That's why I'll be all right.
Huh?
What did this number mean, again?
I'm sorry, Alicia. About this document...
Alicia?
Alicia...
There was something in that document
I didn't understand, so I was looking for you.
A customer had brought me flowers, so...
I see...
Huh?
It's because no one wants you to retire.
Your customers... The people of this city...
Everyone really... really loves you, Alicia!
You're one of the Three Great Water Fairies...
You're always kind...
You're everyone's Snow White...
That's why everyone wants you to stay...
Huh? I'm sorry.
I wonder why?
My tears... They won't stop...
Alicia...
The truth is...
The truth is, you've had the skill to
become a Prima for a long time now.
But I was afraid of losing the
cherished time I've spent with you.
As your mentor, I knew I had to be strong...
...and that I had to make up my mind.
I kept thinking that, but I couldn't do it.
This is all because of my selfishness.
I'm so sorry.
Alicia...
I'm sorry, too.
So many things happened at once...
They're all such wonderful things,
and I should be really happy, but...
Akari.
I've always known that times
and places change, but...
...deep down, that thought has
always made me worried and afraid.
I'm sorry.
As we walked together, it always
felt like we were all on the same path.
But really, we were all on our
own separate paths, weren't we?
I...
I walked down my own path...
...came to Aqua...
...and here I met you, and everyone.
I...
I want to see everyone's wonderful
futures that await them down this path.
That's why...
...I have to see you off with a smile.
Thank you, Akari.
Let's do our best today too, President Aria!
Our first booking today is a Mr. Namihei Anno.
Hey.
Huh?!
So that's your name, Mr. Postman.
Yeah.
Do you have the day off from work today?
Huh?
I've also retired from my post.
From now on, I'll be working
at the office as a supervisor.
I see.
Thank you for your hard work all these years.
It's delicious.
It's buckwheat tea.
Oh!
So your alias is Aquamarine?
Yes.
It's a good name.
I'm really happy that you're a Prima now,
and I can take a ride in your gondola!
Are you lonely at all?
Alicia has stayed on this whole time
while I adjust to running the company.
I see.
But when tomorrow's retirement
ceremony is over, I really will be alone.
You'll be all right.
You have this entire city on your side.
Yes.
It's really delicious.
Thanks to Mr. Postman's recommendation,
I have a booking for tomorrow, as well.
My, my.
Also, the owner of Caffè Florian and
the Campanile caretaker recommended me,
so I received a few bookings from that, as well.
I see.
I feel like...
...I'm being helped in all sorts
of ways, by a lot of people.
Your Aria Company has
already begun, hasn't it?
My...
...Aria Company...
Alicia!
How's it going? Are you
done with the preparations?
I see you gazing up at the endless sky
Dokomademo tsuzuku kono sora nagameteru yokogao
It's time.
I see you gazing up at the endless sky
Dokomademo tsuzuku kono sora nagameteru yokogao
Yeah.
Your long hair brushes your cheeks as it sways in the wind
Hoho ni fureru nagai kami ga yureteiru
Though this heartache can't be expressed with words,
Setsunasa wa kotoba ni naranai keredo
As I always have, both now and forevermore...
Ano koro mo ima mo zutto
...here in this city, overflowing with light,
Hikari afureteru kono machi ni
I'll gather up these feelings that will never change
Itsumademo kawaranu omoi o yosete
Whenever I am blessed with kindness,
Yasashisa ni meguriau toki
I can always feel the wind as it sweeps past
Fukinukeru kaze wa itsudemo
It fades away in the distance, as I gently close my eyes
Haruka tooku tokete yuku sotto me o tojita
Alicia... This can't be true!
Akatsukin, are you crying?
They're tears of joy, right?
Shut up!
Sob
We spoke a little while ago, it was a moment full of smiles
Sakki made futari hanashita hohoemi no hitotoki
These nostalgic, happy days... I'm leaving them behind
Natsukashikute tanoshii hibi nokoshiteku
There's just one thing I'm praying for
Hitotsu dake negai o komete inoru no
A bridge to connect our hearts
Kokoro o tsunagu kake hashi
As you cross that bridge,
Ano sanbashi no mukougawa e
Look around, and you'll see the sun-dappled canal
Furimukeba kirameku komorebi no michi
If you visit here, come with open arms
Kono basho ni otozureta nara ryoute hirogete uketomete
The blue sky and the starry night will be here to greet you
Aoi sora mo hoshizora mo mukaetekureru
Of that I'm certain
Sou kitto
My heart races like the rhythm of the waves
Takanaru kodou wa namima o utau rizumu
As I discover that intangible certainty
Katachi no nai tashika na mono mitsukete
Congratulations on your
promotion to Prima, Alicia!
Whenever I am blessed with kindness,
Yasashisa ni meguriau toki
I can always feel the wind as it sweeps past
Fukinukeru kaze wa itsudemo
It fades away in the distance, as I gently close my eyes
Haruka tooku tokete yuku sotto me o tojita
If you visit here, come with open arms
Kono basho ni otozureta nara ryoute hirogete uketomete
Snow?
If you visit here, come with open arms
Kono basho ni otozureta nara ryoute hirogete uketomete
But it's not the right season yet...
The blue sky and the starry night will be here to greet you
Aoi sora mo hoshizora mo mukaetekureru
But it's not the right season yet...
The blue sky and the starry night will be here to greet you
Aoi sora mo hoshizora mo mukaetekureru
She truly is Snow White, isn't she?
The blue sky and the starry night will be here to greet you
Aoi sora mo hoshizora mo mukaetekureru
Alicia.
The blue sky and the starry night will be here to greet you
Aoi sora mo hoshizora mo mukaetekureru
Thank you... Thank you
very much, for everything!
They'll welcome you
Anata no koto o
Thank you... Thank you
very much, for everything!
They'll welcome you
Anata no koto o
Of that I'm certain
Sou kitto
Good morning, President Aria.
Alicia...
Oh, it's been a while since I've had
hot cocoa with whipped cream!
I want extra cream on mine!
My, my.
You're really like a selfish little kid, Athena.
Okay, here comes the walnut bread!
The cookies are fresh out of the oven, too!
Why?
Everyone's here...
I see.
This place is still filled with
all those fun memories we shared.
Opening this shutter is my first task of the day.
If I open it now, my usual day will begin.
This precious mirage
will vanish in the morning air.
But...
...that's okay.
Because today is a new beginning!
"Dear Ai, shall I tell you
how everyone is doing?"
The gentle wind strokes my cheek
Hoho o naderu yasashii kaze
Good morning!
The gentle wind strokes my cheek
Hoho o naderu yasashii kaze
"Lately, Woody the Sylph has been bringing me
freshly laid eggs before he goes to work."
The gentle wind strokes my cheek
Hoho o naderu yasashii kaze
"Apparently he's started raising
chickens at his home in Ukijima."
I sway among the sound of waves
Namioto ni yurarete
"Apparently he's started raising
chickens at his home in Ukijima."
I sway among the sound of waves
Namioto ni yurarete
Aika?
I sway among the sound of waves
Namioto ni yurarete
"As for Aika, the young Himeya branch manager,"
Aika?
I sway among the sound of waves
Namioto ni yurarete
"As for Aika, the young Himeya branch manager,"
Yes, yes!
I sway among the sound of waves
Namioto ni yurarete
"As for Aika, the young Himeya branch manager,"
I sway among the sound of waves
Namioto ni yurarete
"she's adjusted to her position well,
and has become a very dignified supervisor."
And I can feel my whole body relax
Karada no naka hodoketeyuku yo
"she's adjusted to her position well,
and has become a very dignified supervisor."
And I can feel my whole body relax
Karada no naka hodoketeyuku yo
"But when it's just the two of us..."
And I can feel my whole body relax
Karada no naka hodoketeyuku yo
"...secretly, she's still the same crybaby."
And I can feel my whole body relax
Karada no naka hodoketeyuku yo
"I heard Al was promoted recently,
so he's no longer an apprentice."
I close my eyes, and then I can see...
Me o tojite mietekuru
"I heard Al was promoted recently,
so he's no longer an apprentice."
I close my eyes, and then I can see...
Me o tojite mietekuru
Why yes, thank you.
I close my eyes, and then I can see...
Me o tojite mietekuru
"I haven't seen him for a while,
but Aika keeps me updated constantly."
...the path that the wind takes
Kaze no yuku michi ga
"I haven't seen him for a while,
but Aika keeps me updated constantly."
...the path that the wind takes
Kaze no yuku michi ga
"Apparently, he's grown a bit taller."
...the path that the wind takes
Kaze no yuku michi ga
"Akatsuki was also promoted."
Come, let's paddle away
Saa, kogidasou
"Akatsuki was also promoted."
Come, let's paddle away
Saa, kogidasou
"He often appears out of nowhere
and surprises me at the office."
To the shining waves
Hikaru nami e
"He often appears out of nowhere
and surprises me at the office."
To the shining waves
Hikaru nami e
Oh!
To the shining waves
Hikaru nami e
"I'm sure it's his way of showing he cares."
Soon we'll be overflowing with smiles
Egao ga sugu koboreru
"I'm sure it's his way of showing he cares."
Soon we'll be overflowing with smiles
Egao ga sugu koboreru
You look bored.
Soon we'll be overflowing with smiles
Egao ga sugu koboreru
Oh.
Soon we'll be overflowing with smiles
Egao ga sugu koboreru
You could come visit Ukijima, if you want.
Soon we'll be overflowing with smiles
Egao ga sugu koboreru
Come, let's let others feel...
Nee, tsutaeyou
Thank you.
Come, let's let others feel...
Nee, tsutaeyou
"Alice, the legendary rank-skipping Prima,
is always the focus of everyone's attention."
This excitement in our hearts
Kono tokimeki
"Alice, the legendary rank-skipping Prima,
is always the focus of everyone's attention."
This excitement in our hearts
Kono tokimeki
"The self-imposed rule she's
most passionate about lately is..."
I'll ride the wind to where you are
Kaze ni notte anata no moto e
"The self-imposed rule she's
most passionate about lately is..."
I'll ride the wind to where you are
Kaze ni notte anata no moto e
"...that the three of us
must spend time together."
I'll ride the wind to where you are
Kaze ni notte anata no moto e
If the three of us don't hang out together,
the world will come to an end.
I'm on my way, Undine
Yuku wa, Undine
If the three of us don't hang out together,
the world will come to an end.
I'm on my way, Undine
Yuku wa, Undine
Huh?
I'm on my way, Undine
Yuku wa, Undine
You're such a little kid.
I'm on my way, Undine
Yuku wa, Undine
"Athena, encouraged by those around her,"
"made her debut as an actress
at the opera the other day."
"Alice was angry, saying that it would
affect Athena's work as an Undine, but..."
"...on the day of Athena's debut, Alice was
overcome with emotion at seeing her on stage."
"She was crying... but that's a secret."
The wind falls into a lull, and if you look back
Kaze ga nai de furikaereba
"Himeya's Akira is shining brightly
as the reigning number one Prima."
The wind falls into a lull, and if you look back
Kaze ga nai de furikaereba
"She truly evokes the feeling
of a Crimson Rose in full bloom."
You can see the world shine in the sunset's glow
Yuubae ni terasare
"She truly evokes the feeling
of a Crimson Rose in full bloom."
You can see the world shine in the sunset's glow
Yuubae ni terasare
Geez, she's such a thorn in my side.
You can see the world shine in the sunset's glow
Yuubae ni terasare
I'm going to dethrone her and
make this era mine as soon as possible!
You can see the world shine in the sunset's glow
Yuubae ni terasare
"She says that, but..."
And the sight is dyed deep into your heart
Kokoro made mo somatte yuku yo
"She says that, but..."
And the sight is dyed deep into your heart
Kokoro made mo somatte yuku yo
"...it's easy to tell that she's happy,
and proud of Akira's achievements."
And the sight is dyed deep into your heart
Kokoro made mo somatte yuku yo
"And as for our eternal Snow White, Alicia,"
If you look up, you'll hear it resound
Miagereba hibikidasu
"And as for our eternal Snow White, Alicia,"
If you look up, you'll hear it resound
Miagereba hibikidasu
"she attends various lectures, ceremonies,
meetings, functions, all sorts of things."
The song of the stars
Hoshitachi no uta ga
"she attends various lectures, ceremonies,
meetings, functions, all sorts of things."
The song of the stars
Hoshitachi no uta ga
"She's very busy every day."
The song of the stars
Hoshitachi no uta ga
Come, let's paddle away
Saa, kogidasou
"I even attended a lecture the other day where
Alicia and Grandma were the guest speakers."
To the distant future
Haruka asu e
"I even attended a lecture the other day where
Alicia and Grandma were the guest speakers."
To the distant future
Haruka asu e
As our dreams spread out across the water
Minamo ni yume hirogaru
"But still, whenever she has time..."
As our dreams spread out across the water
Minamo ni yume hirogaru
Hello.
As our dreams spread out across the water
Minamo ni yume hirogaru
Grandma!
As our dreams spread out across the water
Minamo ni yume hirogaru
Alicia!
As our dreams spread out across the water
Minamo ni yume hirogaru
Come, let's find...
Nee mitsukeyou
We're here again.
Come, let's find...
Nee mitsukeyou
...those treasures we have yet to discover
Mada shiranai takaramono o
"...she comes and visits with Grandma,
just like she's doing now..."
...those treasures we have yet to discover
Mada shiranai takaramono o
"...and smiles that wonderful,
unchanging, Water Fairy smile."
You and I, together
Anata to issho ni
"...and smiles that wonderful,
unchanging, Water Fairy smile."
Let's find them, Undine
Sagasou, Undine
"...and smiles that wonderful,
unchanging, Water Fairy smile."
Let's find them, Undine
Sagasou, Undine
"I hope this breeze, which carries happiness
and many new beginnings, reaches you, Ai."
Good morning, President Aria.
Good morning, Akari.
I put on my uniform.
W-What do you think?
Yes, it looks great on you, Ai.
Um, what is it?
I'm just happy, that's all.
Thank You