The moon is beautiful, isn't it?
Yes. It really soothes the heart.
Fidget-fidget-fidget-fidget...
What's the matter, Aika?
Is something bothering you?
Eh?
Anything at all?
Huh? Al?!
I-I'm not thinking of Al! He wasn't even
on my mind! I-It's absolutely nothing!
She's really a young maiden in love.
"Dear Ai, the summer heat has finally passed,"
"and little by little, Neo-Venezia
is being dyed in the colors of autumn."
"Today is Alice's first day working as a Prima!"
"So, Aika suggested we go see how she's
doing before we begin our usual practice..."
Do you remember that day
Oboeteimasuka ano hi o
When your heart suddenly began to race
Futo kanjita tokimeki o
The rays from the blue sky were pouring over you...
Aoi hizashi abite
...as you cut through the wind
Kaze o kiru kimi ni
I couldn't look away, and when our eyes met
Mitoreru to me ga atte
I couldn't help but smile
Egao koboreta
It's just like a spiral
Marude supiraare
As the days begin to swirl in brilliant colors
Azayaka ni mawaridashita hibi
Always and forever, they're filled with love
Itsumo itsudemo ai ga michiteita
Surely, it's a spiral
Kitto supiraare
The days passed by, each one filled with warmth
Atataka na mainichi o kasanetara
And before I knew it, off in the distance...
Itsunomanika tooku ni
...there you were
Kiteita no ne
The Excitement on That Moon-Gazing Night...
Wow, this is so beautiful!
Our Undine is adorable, too!
T-T-Thank you very much.
Hey, hey. Isn't that the Bridge of Sighs?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure it was in the guidebook.
Up ahead is the Bridge of Sighs.
Ah, I knew it!
Because it's so beautiful
it makes you want to sigh!
No, its name actually comes from Manhome,
back when prisoners had to cross this bridge...
...after receiving their sentence at Doge's Palace,
and they would let out a deep sigh when they saw...
It's the sea!
...after receiving their sentence at Doge's Palace,
and they would let out a deep sigh when they saw...
It's the sea!
It's so pretty!
I'm glad we came here.
Definitely!
Geez, could she be any more stiff?
Alice...
It looks like she has a
clothes hanger for shoulders.
I had such a good time.
Me, too. We'll definitely come again!
Thank you very much!
At any rate, it seems like she
was able to satisfy her customers.
Thank goodness.
I'm sorry, President Aria!
President Aria, please hold it in!
Alice will notice we're here!
I really already noticed you.
What are you doing here?
Umm! We just happened to be passing by...
Right! We just happened to see you while
you were working and decided to watch...
You two... watched me... while I was working...
But, you know... You seem to
have managed it okay!
Yeah! It was very thoughtful of you to back up,
so that gentleman could see those cats.
Athena would have done the same...
You've been watching me for that long?
Spying on me is really not allowed!
Right...
But...
...other than that, everything else was bad.
Please tell me honestly what you thought!
Well, my thought was that
you looked like a toy robot.
A robot?
Your shoulders were so tense...
This is how you looked.
That's a zombie.
Wha-?!
Aika...
You know there's no time
to be depressed, right?
You're a Prima now.
I...
I know!
Why don't we have a
moon-gazing party tonight?
Moon-gazing?
Yeah!
It's fall now, and the weather's nice today.
I'm sure the moon will look really beautiful!
Moon-gazing...
This... is the first time
I've ever been moon-gazing.
It's not a tradition we have here on Aqua.
Why are we having dumplings
at our moon-gazing party?
They're supposed to be
symbolic of Manhome's moon.
Well, in that case...
I'll have some, too.
Ah! Eating two at once is no fair!
Wha-?!
Then, I'll have four at once!
You can't beat me!
Don't be so sure!
N-No more dumplings allowed!
You're really a glutton!
Pudgy-wudgy tummy...
President Maa, President Aria's pudgy-wudgy
tummy isn't a moon-gazing dumpling!
This is the brown rice tea that
the postman recommended.
It's delicious.
The season when warm drinks
taste great is finally here, isn't it?
Come to think of it, Al is late, isn't he?
Since when was Al supposed to join us?
Wasn't the moon-gazing party
just for the three of us?
A-An event about the moon and stars
wouldn't be complete without Al, right?
Maybe he could teach us a thing or two.
Oh? Is that so?
W-What's with that face?!
Since you weren't there that night
when we all saw the meteor shower,
I invited Al so you could catch up!
Oh?
I'll go get him.
I bet he's late because of work again.
He might be lost somewhere, too.
See you later!
Aika is really cute.
Akari...
Thank you very much for inviting me today.
Gazing up at the moon like this...
...is somehow calming.
Tomorrow, if I can be like the moon
and keep this sense of tranquility,
I think I'll be able to do much better.
Alice, would you like some more tea?
Yes, please.
Huh? Where's President Maa?
President Maa!
There he is!
Al!
Aika!
You're late.
I'm sorry! I had to stay late and work.
Honestly. No overworking allowed!
Yeah, sorry about that.
Well, if there's one good
thing about me being late...
...it's that now, we have the
still of the night all to ourselves.
Aika, that's dangerous!
It's fine, it's fine!
Are you all right, Aika?!
I-I think so...
Here, grab my hand.
I'm sorry about this.
Huh?
I-I'm sorry...
W-Why are you apologizing?
It's my fault for weighing so much, after all...
It's a good thing the city's wells have
dried up and are no longer in use, but...
...I think we're still in trouble.
What should we do?
A long time ago, before
the city had a water system...
...I heard they used to collect rainwater in the wells
in each plaza, and used that for drinking water.
It must have been lively when housewives gathered
to fetch water in the morning, and again at night.
I bet there were a lot of
"wellside gossip meetings"!
Ow, ow, ow...
It's no use.
Looks that way...
President Maa!
Yay! We're saved!
Hey, President Maa! Go get Junior!
President Maa?
President Maa, are you listening?
Go-get-Jun-ior-and-bring-her-back...
And why did you jump down?
Listen, President Maa!
Go get Junior, on the double!
Go!
What?!
Why'd you come back?!
Now look, President Maa!
It's no use. She's still a kitten, after all.
It's okay! President Maa is a fine Aqua Cat
that can understand human language!
I have no doubt... she'll get...
Junior... to come... for us...
At any rate, you're the only one who can help us!
Please, go!
Yes!
You can do it!
Yes, that's the spirit! Keep it up!
Please do your best!
Keep going, keep going!
Just a little more!
Please do your best!
Almost there!
She did it!
Do you really think we can count on her?
Probably not...
Ah, the moon...
What a strange moon-gazing
this turned out to be...
I wonder why the moon revolves around Aqua?
It's because of the forces
of attraction and repulsion.
As I've explained before,
the force of attraction...
...and the centrifugal force created by the moon's
rotation around Aqua, maintain a perfect balance.
Unable to get closer or move farther away,
the moon just goes around and around.
Sounds like a certain someone...
The outer moon is used as a space station, among
other things, by several different fields of study.
They mine minerals and perform chemical
experiments which can only be done in a vacuum.
Oh, did you know? Back on Manhome, it's said their
moon's craters resemble many different shapes.
For example, some say it looks like a crab
with huge claws, or an old woman knitting,
or a lion, or a woman's profile,
or rabbits pounding rice cakes...
Ah, speaking of rabbits, that reminds me!
I hear the "Rabbit-Pounded Rice Cakes"
sold at the space station are really tasty!
I've been wanting to try them,
so I mail-ordered some the other day.
They also come with a haiku collection book
about the moon, so I'm really looking forward to it!
Not allowed!!
Ehh?! What is?
All of that! It's not allowed!
S-Sorry.
Honestly!
At any rate, it's quite dark in this well, isn't it?
Al...
...by any chance, are you scared?
That can't be, right?
Gnomes are always working in the dark
and can see really well at night, so...
Well...
Since there's no sunlight, the lighting
infrastructure underground is quite advanced...
Al, you're so cute!
It's all right! Big Sis is here with you!
There are two moons now.
The inner moon is approximately
1.8 times bigger than the outer moon,
and it flies around in a
geostationary orbit over Aqua.
The inner moon completes its orbit
around Aqua in under eight hours...
...and revolves in a very close orbit,
only 5,900 kilometers above Aqua's sky.
That distance is just 1165th of the distance
between Manhome and its moon.
It's really close, isn't it?
Yes.
The small moon that got too close...
...will be drawn in by
Aqua's influence, and in time...
...it will surely break into pieces...
Why are you crying?
It's too close...
It may seem like it's just the
moon that's affected by Aqua...
...but the thing closest
to Aqua is that very moon.
So Aqua is under the
influence of the moon, as well.
Al...
It's ruined!!
A-Aika!
What's ruined?
Aika, are you all right?
Ahhhhh!!
I'm so glad we found you, Aika.
I can't believe you fell
down into a well like that.
Well, excuse me!
Is that how you talk to your rescuers?
Sorry.
I'm grateful to President Maa.
As you should be.
By the way, when did you two get there?
Right at the "It's ruined!" part.
So, what was ruined?
It's because of centrifugal force!
If you're afraid of getting close and
just flail around, it makes you hungry!
Huh?
That really makes no sense.
Al...
Yes.
It's the force of attraction.
No sappy lines allowed.
Okay.
Let's eat.
It's delicious!
By the way, what was sappy?
A-AI made a sappy old man joke!
Oh?
What?
So, what was ruined?
Y-You're asking even though you already know...
"Ai, it was an impromptu moon-gazing party..."
"...but it brought out everyone's familiar smiles,
and ended up being a fun autumn evening."
"Akari, if the moon has the force of attraction,
maybe it has other wonderful powers, too?"
"I'd love to join you all next autumn!"
A shore awash in golden waves
Kin no nami kishibe ni
Filled with yearning, I open my eyes and it's morning
Akogare mezameru no asa ni
As my thoughts focus intently on someone,
Dareka no koto o tsuyoku omou toki
Love rests on my palm, held high
Kakageta te no hira ni ai ga tomaru
A future guided by the flow of water and wind
Mizu no yukue to kaze ga shimesu mirai
I gaze at the hope that surrounds this world
Kono hoshi o tsusumu kibou mitsumete
The distant clouds of light are beckoning now
Tooi kumo hikari ga sasou you ni yureru ima
A shore awash in golden waves
Kin no nami kishibe ni
Filled with yearning, I open my eyes and it's morning
Akogare mezameru no asa ni
And my day begins
Hajimaru
Next Episode
I'm all fired up now! Just like Junior!
Huh?
Next Episode
Alice, you're so cheerful!
Huh?
Next Episode
Those Ever-Changing Days...
Next time, "Those Ever-Changing Days..."
Next Episode
Those Ever-Changing Days...
Now, please take my hand.