Every weekday's tightly packed.
Madly dashing around
again since morning.
Rat race? Looks like fun.
But surprisingly death-defying.
What I'd like is a slow lifestyle.
My wish made on a shootin'star.
But there's no mercy, 100÷3.
Full of things you can't divide.
Genshiken
That's why I've carried
this in my hands...
...a limitless dream!
I jam-packed the rest with it...
...or at least I've tried to!
A modest happiness.
A shared joy!
We're about to etch them now
right into our youth.
So Ionely to just walk on by.
So sad to have this frustration!
Let's take a break from today...
...and break into song!
Aren't anime and video game costumes...
...nothing but weird outfits
that embody male desires?
Many of those who create them are women.
Then in other words, warped
male and female desires.
I just can't believe you would wear
such things and pose in front of people.
What you express through
cosplay is the character herself.
That includes inner essence,
not just outward appearance.
You're quibbling. Photos
don't show inner essence.
Yes, they do!
This is embarrassing. Don't
you think you're exaggerating?
Oh? This is no exaggeration.
I can't understand it.
There are people who do, though. Right?
Huh?
Last year, Saki did such an admirablejob
portraying the president through cosplay!
Wha?
Please, speak up!
Don't even go there.
So, in any case, is it
safe to say Ohno's...
...cosplay shoot will be our main
part of this year's school festival?
Sure, why not? It's more
like our only main, though.
Thus making the festival all hers.
Why don't you give it a try too?
I won't do something that embarrassing!
You want to try it,
in reality, don't you?
Episode 15
Then I'll Undress You!
Society for the Study
of Modern Visual Culture
I wish things could be a little
smoother between Ohno and Ogiue.
Maybe getting Ogiue to cosplay
for the photo shoot's a good idea.
Huh? What for?
I mean, you got more well-rounded
after cosplaying last year.
Huh?
I did?
You no longertalk
about smashing Genshiken.
Whoa!
And here you are, even without Kohsaka.
Huh?
Back on topic...
I'll make any number of outfits
if that's all I have to do...
...but who's going to tell Ogiue?
L-let's leave that to Kasukabe...
No way.
Oh... okay.
I'm not against making her cosplay.
Well then!
But I don't like you
capitalizing on my success.
Hmm. What now?
First, we should pass
word along to Ohno.
Th-that's true.
Who'll do that? Tanaka?
Huh?
Well, that's fine.
Y-you two're the c-cosplay
team, so n-naturally.
That decides that, then.
Hm?
What's this?
Gulp!
Is this a Kujiun uniform?
But it's small.
Renko?
Is this Rimururu?
EE Sakura, and Ink Seizuyo?
Tanaka?
Not one of those is a
character geared towards me.
Well, you see. It's not
like I was hiding them.
They weren't hidden anyway.
I always keep costumes in the closet...
Tanaka...
University Ouran Festival
Yakisoba
Karaoke tournament
Bamboo wares
Let's bring that right a little.
Yes, sir! Whoa!
I got it!
So, what? Ohno's ticked off
and not getting anywhere?
That's how it is.
Shames me to say it.
Well, don't look at me.
Keep out
Uh, never mind Ogiue cosplaying.
Could you maybe go placate Ohno?
She's in there in the changing room.
You are too pathetic.
Yeah...
So it's me, after all.
Huh, after all or inevitably?
Sorry about this.
I don't mind playing go-between, but
you do understand what the problem is?
Huh?
Yeah... That I went ahead
and made Ogiue costumes.
Wrong!
Eh?
That doesn't matter. Even
Ohno wanted to make her do it.
But...
You're missing the point.
Look, the focus of Ohno's
discontent isn't Ogiue, it's...
Good morning.
M-morning!
H-hi!
Cosplay photo shoot
The Society for the Study of Modern Visual
Culture
Good morning!
Good morning.
Guten morgen!
What is it?
Nothing.
Yeah, nothing.
Nothing at all!
I'll give it a shot.
Okay...
I don't really mind him
making outfits for Ogiue.
He's made a bunch for you, too.
That part I mind.
They're right there.
What're they thinking?
I mean, it's cosplayer's instinct to
want an appropriate person to wear them.
Instinct, huh?
It's just, he made them
without telling me...
It's not like I'm defending him...
...but maybe he thought you'd
object if he tried asking?
No, I wouldn't.
Really?
Too much arguing would be... you know.
Yeah, well, it's give and take.
Still, though... Take a look at this.
The Ogiue outfits are... this and this.
And then... this and this.
And this.
There's more over there.
Well... I'd get mad too.
You think? This amount! This zeal!
He ran with all these Lolita
characters that I can't do!
Then there's the fact that
he brought them here today.
No, I'm the one who did that.
Oh.
But hey, Tanaka lives
for cosplay in a way.
I say let it go.
I know that.
You do?
So therefore, or maybe nonetheless...
...I thought being a
team meant something else.
Being a team, huh...
Definitely. I mean, here
you are, our go-between.
Yeah, well...
Oh, here she comes.
How'd it go?
I'd say she's okay.
But...
It'd be best if you apologized.
All right.
Properly! Don't leave anything out.
You're totally right.
Oh, I'm sorry. We're not ready yet.
Oh, okay.
But I think now I kinda
want to get Ogiue to cosplay.
Wha!
There's plenty of outfits...
H-here it comes...
Besides, in my experience, doing it
does bring about a certain breakthrough.
I knew it!
But right now?
That could never happen.
We'll see about that.
Remember how she bought that outfit
just because the clerk recommended it?
Aha, she sure did.
I'm a pro at that job!
I'm not sure whatjob you mean.
I think I get the gist.
Just watch.
Ogi! C'mere a sec.
Huh?
That's right.
What is it?
You'll find out.
Tanaka, Ohno! Can I come in?
Huh? Uh, sure. Feel free.
Might I be intruding?
In what way?
Then, Tanaka, could you excuse us?
What's this about?
Wha?
What's up?
Oh, nothing.
Now get a move on.
Huh? What?
No way!
Way, indeed.
Another one bites the dust!
Genshiken
Here you go, Ogi!
What are you doing!
I won't wear that. It's creepy!
Nobody said wear it!
We're just seeing how it looks.
Somebody bothered to make it,
so why not see how it'd look on you?
Someone else made it, not you!
Oh, come on.
Look in the mirror.
Hey, pretty nice!
You have big eyes, so this
kind of thing's nice and cute.
Wha?
So cute!
See, and this.
And this! Wow! Nice!
Or like this. Oh, very nice!
Try letting your hair down.
No thank you.
You don't have to wear
anything. It's just your hair.
But I don't want to.
Doesn't it contrast with these styles?
Just this once, real quick.
Hey, Saki, what's the big idea?
Well, I thought maybe
I'd get her to cosplay.
Huh! What for?
Why not? You won't be a
drag and stop me, will you?
Forcing her to do it
is against the rules.
Like how I was forced
to do it last year!
Very nice! Let's see.
Wow...
Y'know...
...it really works.
Well, I'll admit that much.
They're looking at me!
So there you have it!
Huh?
Thanks, you did great!
Hm?
Okay...
What's up? Did you want
to see a little more?
No.
Why not try one on?
No thank you!
Oh! This is Saki's gift of gab.
Yeah, but...
It's right here!
Never mind! I have no
interest in cosplay!
She almost even had me that time.
Oh, really?
Then look, would you if I wore one?
Huh?
Y-you will?
I will if you wear one.
Wow, that turned around in a hurry.
And Ogiue hasn't realized it.
So, what do you think?
About what?
Will she wear one?
Ogiue?
50-50... no, maybe 60-40 against.
I-it won't happen.
She'll do it.
You're confident enough.
Mhm. It's Saki, after all.
Even Kasukabe has her limits...
Your humble servant Coochy hereby
bets this Kujiun cell strap!
I own one...
Then I'm going with yes, she will.
Huh?
Hey, hey, you're party to this!
All the more reason.
I don't think she will.
Won't.
Will.
We don't really need
to go to this trouble.
It's been downgraded to just trouble.
You can just wear it in here! You
never have to show it to the guys.
Of course! Who'd ever...
Then just for a little!
No thanks.
Really quick, right on then back off!
No, no thanks.
One more push, Saki!
We won't take any pictures!
Uh, pictures...
You're just trying it on,
so come on, change.
Well, I don't know how much to take off.
Then I'll undress you!
No!
I'll undress myself! I'll do it!
Are they okay in there?
Who knows...
Down she goes!
If Saki was a guy, she might
make a good porno scout.
University Ouran Festival
Ouran
Authorized personnel only
All others, entry prohibited
Wow, now that's cosplay!
Yes...
M-maybe you could say it's cute.
Well, Ohno?
She's Renko from Kujiun.
I don't mean that.
Y-yes, well, I guess
she looks cute in it?
Pardon?
Oh, fine. She looks cute. Don't
ask again like you didn't hear me.
She said cute. But then, you really are.
It's k-kind of drafty on my legs.
And the material's cheap.
Huh?
I have no idea about the
character's inner essence.
You can always just get
into it through appearance.
That's news to me.
If you try it and have even a
little fun, that's good enough.
Ah, I'm sorry. We're a little behind.
Ohno!
It's about that time!
Oh, already?
Are you wearing it?
Not yet.
Is there a problem? I'm coming in.
No!
Saki, Ogiue, could you help me?
But I need to...
You can change later!
Just go out like that.
No!
Grab that MOS-KOS headgear.
A booming success.
That's our Cosplayer Youko for you.
There are some who came
here today just forthis.
It w-was advertised online.
Here they come finally.
Hey.
Incredible.
We might have you to thank.
So, what happened?
What do you think happened?
She cosplayed.
She really did?
No way! What character?
The one from Kujiun... uh...
Renko Kamishakujii!
Kamishakujii, huh? Makes sense!
I don't like how natural
it apparently seems!
Oh no, not my first edition Wild Soul!
Yes! Jackpot!
Were you guys betting!
Uh, well...
It was a joke, a joke!
It never ends up as a
joke when you say it!
Kasukabe!
I had high hopes.
We all wanted to see it.
Because Saki looked so good in hers.
So how'd you bet, Kohsaka?
That Ogiue would do it,
of course. So did Tanaka.
Who bet against?
I did!
Idiots.
In the end, Kohsaka's
the only one who gets it.
So what do you get for winning?
Wild Soul.
A Harahoro prize.
Plus! You guys pay for drinks.
Wh-why shouldn't you pay?
Kohsaka's win is my win!
Nice Gianism!
The v-vice president.
Now I really wish I
could've seen Ogiue's Renko.
You should've taken part
in the photo shoot too.
Not on your life.
The highest priority was improving
her relationship with Ohno.
Cosplay was just a means, right?
Well, that's true.
Hey, Ogiue kept complaining,
but she finally did it.
She'll let you see it eventually.
Eventually, huh?
H-how do you feel about cosplay?
It's horrible!
Now I know for sure it's not for me.
Just so long as this
improves the mood a bit...
We took no detours or shortcuts...
...and we weren't afraid of
what tomorrow would bring...
...as we kept walking down
Inogashira Street late at night.
Only vivid dreams extended
deep into the shadows.
We were simple
when we were young...
...with our endlessly
glistening marbles.
The time we spied from there...
...sparkled, even if
nothing big happened.
What is seen from the marbles...
...in our hands now is a little different...
...but they shine faintly nearby.
Next episode preview
Irohagokko
What's wrong, Ohno? You look down.
Kujiun's ended, and now
it's like, what do we do now?
Ahh, that's true. I guess we
can't have Kujiun meetings anymore.
It sure is sad.
I fail to see why
you're so absorbed in it.
Huh? You do?
You guys can breathe easy!
Mourn not, for Ritsuko
Kübel Kettenkrad...
...Chihiro Enomoto, and Tokino
Akiyama live on in your hearts!
Theirjourney's only just begun!
Aha.
Eh, never mind.