Nana!
Shoji!
Hold... me!
What's with that face?
I'm sorry about earlier.
I said stuff I shouldn't have.
Don't worry about it.
That killed the mood!
When I was darkness at that time
With trembling lips
In a corner of a room I cry
The more I struggle
The more this wound deepens
The broken promise hurt me
Nobody can save me
God, I have only one request
Stop tearing apart my love
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Sorrow tumbling down is your song
All alone with nowhere to go in my life
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Oh baby, help me from frozen pain
With your smile, your eyes,
and sing me, just for me
I wanna need your love
I'm a broken rose
Welcome back!
Jun-chan, you've gotta hear this.
You know what Shoji!
Good night.
Room 707? Give me a break!
What are you talking to yourself for?
That's scary.
I'm not talking to myself.
I'm talking to Demon Lord.
That's even scarier!
Damn, I'm tired from running around.
You really are troublesome.
It's your fault for
leaving me all alone!
Why, at a time like this,
must I speak like a bitch?
I wanna always be the cute girl
when with the man I like.
I can't stand this.
Perhaps it's too late now.
I've shown Shoji things about me
that are less attractive,
and here we're in a room together and
there's no longer that sense of nervousness.
He's just gone right off to sleep.
You know, Nana...
The truth is, I really want to bring you
to Tokyo with me.
But, you know, I don't have a job.
I'm not even a University student,
just studying to enter one.
If you were on the verge of life and death,
I could do nothing to help you.
That's hard for a man.
I want you to understand that.
Then...
Then I'll stay back home,
find a job and save up money
to come to Tokyo!
Then, after one year,
you pass the University entrance exam,
I'll come to Tokyo too.
Then I'll find a job here and work hard
so that I can make it on my own!
Would it be okay then?
Then I must pass next year,
no matter what.
Just watch me, Demon Lord!
All right!
Now that we've made up, why don't we
sleep together for a change?
What do you mean by that?!
For a change suggests
we've done this in the past!
We haven't even kissed yet!
It's okay if you don't want to.
I've become used to holding back.
Doesn't it cross his mind that
it might be nice to build the mood?
Never mind.
Don't jump to conclusions
on your own!
Oh? Then why don't you share
your opinion on this subject?
Huh? Well...
Then, if you tell me
that you love me,
I'll sleep with you.
Love?
You've gotta realize
this isn't about who says what!
You can't expect
a Japanese man to say that!
But I have never had anyone say
those words to me in my life.
I'd be happy to hear it just once.
What's the point if
it's said because you asked?
Never mind.
All right, you win.
A man's gotta do
what a man's gotta do. I'll say it.
I'll just think of myself
as an American.
My name's Michael.
Who's that?
Do I hafta sleep with
some mysterious foreigner?
I won't sleep with anyone but Shoji.
I'm gonna make some tea, okay?
So would you prefer
green tea or brown tea, Michael?
Nana.
Shoji, I know you said it...
inside your heart.
You told me that you love me.
So you heard it.
I wanted to have a happy love.
Romantic and dramatic
like in the movies.
But during the summer of seventeen,
I became a woman
and learned that dating men isn't so sweet
like on the big screen.
Or so I thought.
But that evening,
my body was melting away
with the sweet taste of happiness.
I wonder if things are all right
between those two.
I'm a bit worried.
But they can't rely on their friends
to bring them back together.
They're not junior high school kids.
Right?
Don't just leave me here
talking to myself.
Good night.
A woman's life isn't so bad after all,
is it, Jun-chan?
But it's long distance.
Huh?
Nothing. That'll be three hundred yen
for the late return.
Ah, right.
Nana.
Wanna have dinner with me tonight?
Mr. Nakamura.
That would be a problem.
You may have finally woken up
to my beauty,
but it's too late now, Nakamura.
What's the big deal? It's just dinner.
And he's not serious.
Aren't you lonely with your boyfriend
having moved to Tokyo?
And he's a pest.
But you had a crush on me.
You've got the wrong person!
Should I quit that job?
But it pays pretty good.
I hafta hurry and save money,
so that I can move to Tokyo.
I can't wait until next spring!
Yes, this is Nana!
Shoji! I'm doing great!
Nana Komatsu. I'm 19 years old.
I have a boyfriend, but we're in
a long-distance relationship.
I'll show you, Demon Lord!
I don't know where I was born.
I've never seen my father,
and I've long forgotten
what my mother looks like.
I came to this coastal city
when I was four,
where I was raised by my grandmother
who owns a little restaurant.
She had nothing
but sarcastic remarks for me.
Right now, I work long hours while
polishing the shards of my dream.
Good evening!
We're Blast.
Thank you!
It's cold!
It's too cold!
They're coming!
No way!
Everyone was waiting out here
in this freezing cold?
Thanks a lot for today.
Nana! Your performance was the best!
Thank you.
Nana! I have a present for you.
What is it? Vivienne Westwood?
You sure it's okay, Misato?
You...
You remembered my name?
Of course, because you're always there
when we're performing live.
Nana, your birthday was last week, right?
That's a birthday present for you!
Happy eighteenth birthday!
Thank you.
Yay! I got Vivienne Westwood!
Izakaya - Japanese pub
Okay then,
here's to today's successful show.
- Cheers!
We were by far the best
in tonight's battle of the bands, right?
Most of the audience came to see us.
I never imagined
such a day would come
when I'd be so popular with women.
But they all come dressed as Nana.
It's kinda scary, if you ask me.
Wow, it's a jacket. I'm touched!
I'll bet the other fans are strangling
that girl about now.
A significant investment
for one kiss from me.
Demon!
Excuse me, I'll have another!
Nobu, stop it already.
Your graduation is tomorrow, right?
Aren't you attending graduation, Nana?
Well, excuse me for dropping out
of high school!
What's up with that?
I only finished junior high.
Why are you bragging about it?!
The national university student's laughing.
Rub it in, will you?
Still I would've liked to see Nana
in her school uniform.
Did you wear those loose socks, too?
Don't go there, Yassan.
She was one terrifying girl
in school.
I was so scared
I wouldn't dare talk to her.
Liar! You were always
following me around!
You were really annoying!
What's that?
I became your friend
because you were always alone
at school and looked lonely!
You should thank me for that!
Hurray for Blast!
It's no use.
Let's just leave him and go home.
You think he'll die?
Yeah, he'll die.
I'll flag down a taxi
and take him home.
Yassan, you sure have money.
You're not learning law for nothing,
you lawyer-to-be.
Yasu, should Nana get thrown in jail,
make sure and defend her
as her lawyer.
What do you take me for?!
I'll never get caught.
- Did you do something wrong?
- Wait, Ren.
I'll tell Nobu about that thing.
So you tell Nana, okay?
About what?
The truth is,
the reason Yasu became a skinhead
has to do with this bald spot he got.
In the end, those who laugh at the bald,
cry as a bald!
Performing live is the best.
How can I put it... Orgasmic!
I come while on stage.
There's no stopping it.
I'm glad for you.
Yup. It's awesome. It feels sooo good.
Even better than doing it
with a man?
That depends on the man.
Wow, I'm freezing!
I'll catch a cold!
What would you do if I end up
losing my precious voice?
Isn't there a hand warmer
or something?
Those girls need a lesson
on gift buying.
There has to be something we can use,
like a scarf or something.
Found one!
- Awesome!
Ren Honjo
Nana Osaki
Hey, Ren, do you remember?
There was a snowstorm
the first time we met as well.
I remember.
Really?
It was at a Christmas live concert
a few years ago.
Two years and three months ago.
You were wearing a red dress
that day.
Was I? You don't even hafta remember
the clothes I wore.
I couldn't forget it even
if I wanted to.
You were the worst audience ever,
for refusing to get into the mood.
What are you saying?!
You were in the very front
and just stood there with
a cold look on your face.
I was thinking,
"What's up with her?"
It pissed me off.
Then, after the show,
you came backstage with Nobu.
The way you greeted me was pitiful.
All you said was, "I'm Nana."
Without even so much as a smile.
That was it.
Don't you have anything else to say?
Back then, there was so much going on,
I was in a bad state.
Yeah. Because you got kicked
outta school for selling yourself.
I was not! I was framed!
You're the one who took
my virginity!
Sorry about that. Calm down.
But given your short temper,
I'm surprised that
you didn't fight back.
I didn't have the energy
to lose my temper back then.
Yeah. That certainly was
the expression you had.
Besides, I wanted to quit school
and get a job,
so I figured it worked out well.
But wasn't your nasty grandmother
overworking you at the store?
What did you need the extra money for,
to put up with that?
I wanted money.
And Grandma never gave me even
a penny of allowance money.
It's not a laughing matter!
Yeah, yeah.
I told you before.
When I was four, my mother left me
with Grandma and disappeared.
She gave birth to me without knowing
who my father was.
Soon enough, I became a burden to her
so she fled with another man.
Grandma had a habit of telling me
how she didn't want me growing up
to be like my mother.
Therefore, I was never allowed to
wear pink or red girlish clothes.
She said they were provocative colors
that would seduce men.
When Grandma died, I was all alone.
I decided I'd use the money I earned
to buy poor me a Christmas present.
Of all things, I bought myself
a frilly red dress.
I excitedly wore it to
the live concert that evening.
I was hiding the red dress under my coat
and ran in the snowstorm.
He's my senior at school,
two years older than me!
He's really cool!
I'll introduce you to him later.
Really, don't bother.
I just came to have fun.
You'll see what I'm talking about
when you meet and talk to him.
He's more level-headed
than your average grownup.
He grew up in an orphanage,
so I'm sure he's gone through hard times.
Ren was abandoned in
the warehouse district by the harbor,
right after he was born.
It was apparently all over the news.
Nobuo, it's not nice to talk about
such touchy issues of someone else.
It's all right.
Ren boasts about it.
He does?
He brags that
not too many people can say
they were in the news
right after they were born.
On top of that, he actually lives
in that warehouse district.
He says, "This is my origin."
Ren is trying to become
a professional musician.
So he says he's thankful
for his scandalous past
because it attracts attention!
What's that all about?
What a fool.
Why? That's pretty cool!
He's just trying to get sympathy
by selling his unfortunate past.
That's so not cool.
But I was charmed by the man
who appeared on stage.
Ren was abandoned
in the warehouse district by the harbor.
Ren boasts about it.
What name do I give that feeling
that was born that night?
Sweet words like "love" or
"adore" just don't sound right.
Perhaps envy and irritation
mixed in with jealousy.
And moreover desire.
Even now I get anxious.
Because sometimes I feel
that this daily life,
living together with Ren,
is nothing but a dream.
Ren was a bright light that lightened
the boring life I lived until then.
But no matter how hard I try,
he still remains outta my reach.
I wish we could do it in a bigger place.
You're right.
This place is kinda small.
Not that. I mean performing on stage.
We have the fan base now.
Yeah, go for it.
I mean both of us.
By the way,
what was that thing Yasu was talking about
as we were leaving.
He seemed kinda serious.
Was it concerning the band?
Getting a bald spot is a serious matter.
Never mind.
I'll hear about it from Yasu.
More importantly,
I'd better take my medicine.
Can't live without it, huh? Junkie!
No way! It's the pill!
We'd be in trouble
if I don't take it!
Since you won't do anything
for prevention!
What are we going to do
if I have a baby?!
Give birth, and we'll raise it.
I worked hard labor instead
of going to high school,
so I've got lots of money.
One or two kids would be totally fine.
Fine with you, but not with me.
Right now I'd rather perform
than raise kids.
Nana...
I'm going to Tokyo.
You live your life however you like.
I reached into the sky
But I couldn't reach what I wanted
They grew smaller
and disappeared into the sky
Like colorful balloons
I'm alone
My hand had no place to go
And gently you took it
Starless night
I won't look back
at the shadow of my past
I want to feel your warmth
Tears are falling down
Even if I'm unsure I won't let go