Nana!
I thought I might find you here.
He's so cool.
Matsushida the DJ!
Super cool! Super nice!
If you like him,
just tell him so.
If you're lucky,
he may make you his girlfriend.
No way. Matsushida is very popular
with the ladies
and I'll bet he fools around a lot.
Rumors are that he changes women
all the time.
He's so full of himself. I'm sure of it.
An enemy of women.
Then don't fall in love with him.
I like the way you said that.
Your comeback line.
You're starting to sound
a lot like Jun-chan.
Should I call you Sho-chan?
Everyone would become like this
after hanging out with you!
But Jun-chan doesn't talk
to me the same way now.
She's been so preoccupied with Kyosuke,
her personality is softening.
Like she's boneless.
She lacks something now.
But it's all right.
I have you now, Shoji.
So I'm merely Junko's replacement,
I guess.
By the way, Sho-chan, why'd you come
looking for me? Is it something urgent?
Don't call me Sho-chan!
I was at a bar drinking
with Kyosuke and Junko,
and thought I'd invite you.
You may get upset if you thought
we deliberately went drinking without you.
Yes! Let's go, let's go!
Let's drink!
You know, we seem to
always end up drinking.
For once, I'd like to try something
more refreshing, like go to the beach.
The beach?
Hey, summer vacation's coming up.
Why don't the four of us
go on a trip somewhere?
- The beach!
When I was darkness at that time
With trembling lips
In a corner of a room I cry
The more I struggle
The more this wound deepens
The broken promise hurt me
Nobody can save me
God, I have only one request
Stop tearing apart my love
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Sorrow tumbling down is your song
All alone with nowhere to go in my life
I need your love
I'm a broken rose
Oh baby, help me from frozen pain
With your smile, your eyes,
and sing me, just for me
I wanna need your love
I'm a broken rose
The beach is really nice.
This is what youth is all about.
I'm tired of the mountains.
Yeah, I've also grown tired
of watching the mountains.
I'm really sleepy.
Really, Jun-chan?
Then I guess we should get going.
What are you saying, Nana?
You're in this room with Junko.
I'll give my place to Kyosuke.
I'm gonna sleep with Shoji.
Huh?! Wh-What are you saying?
Come on. You've gotta be
more considerate, Shoji?
Hey!
Hurry up, let's go.
Well, I guess there was nothing
to worry about, after all.
You think it'll be that simple?
What are you thinking?
It's really okay.
There are two beds,
and I won't assault you, so don't worry.
I can even sing you a lullaby
like your grandmother.
Never mind! You may be fine with this,
but I'm not!
I might force myself on you!
Why?
Why, she says...
We're friends, right?
Nana, you really have
no clue about men.
A guy can do it with a girl even if
he has no feelings of love for her.
I know that.
But I believed that you weren't
like those types of guys.
Jun-chan even guaranteed it.
I'm afraid that I am like that!
I don't know what
Junko guaranteed you...
Hey, why are you crying?
Because I really like you, Shoji,
but you say things that
make me lose interest in you!
Ah, say, Nana.
When you say you like me,
you mean as a friend, right?
That's right.
You are the most precious
guy friend I have.
I like you not as the male species,
but as a human being!
But you're right.
Since you are a member
of the male species,
it may be dangerous to be sleeping
in the same room.
I was mistaken.
It's hard for a guy and a girl
to be friends, right, Sho-chan?
But we'll do our best.
Well then, I'd better be going back
to my own room.
Wait, Nana!
That's not a good idea!
Huh?
They're probably in the middle of...
you know...
Oh, right! What should I do?
When do you think
they'll be done?
Don't ask me.
We've got a problem.
All right, I've got it, Nana.
Sleep right there!
Huh?
I'll sleep in this bed.
No, Shoji! It's dangerous!
No need to worry!
Why's that?
You said a moment ago
that you lost interest in me, right?
I need to regain that trust that I lost!
For the sake of our friendship!
Good night!
Shoji...
I love you!
Go to sleep, little baby
Go to sleep, my child
You don't have to sing!
It's not a laughing matter.
Man. Thanks to that,
I didn't get any sleep at all.
Very well done, Sho-chan.
Don't call me, Sho-chan.
Take good care of Nana
from now on too, okay?
Yeah, yeah.
Although we're just friends.
Now I can go to Tokyo
without worry.
Jun-chan!
Come in! Let's swim together!
Okay, okay.
If you try to tan too much at once,
you'll regret it later.
Kyosuke, is Junko going
to Tokyo?
Yeah. So you heard.
Why? To do what?
It's not just a trip?
She's going to apply to
an art school in Tokyo next year.
Even if she doesn't get in,
she'll go to prep school.
Junko should be able to get in,
no problem.
But are you okay with this?
Why can you remain so cool?
Why?
Because I'm going too.
No! No! No! No!
Don't go, Jun-chan!
Aren't you gonna stop me?
You're right!
If Kyosuke decides not to go,
Jun-chan won't go either.
Don't go, Kyosuke!
Enough already, Nana!
Even if Kyosuke weren't going,
I'd still go!
I wanna devote myself
to studying art
at an art school in Tokyo!
It's my life!
You cannot tell me what to do!
I'm sorry.
You're right.
It's exactly as you say, Jun-chan.
But I'm gonna be so lonely.
I'll be even sadder than
I was on that snowy day.
You know, Nana...
I wanna go to Tokyo and try
and get into an art school as well.
Why don't you do the same?
Huh?
No way! Awesome!
I never knew there were
so many art schools in Tokyo!
I'm sure I will get accepted
into some place.
Yeah. Why not apply
to all of them?
Even if I don't get in a university
I can go to
a specialty college again.
What do you mean by that?
What meaning would it have
to do such a thing?
It's my life!
You cannot tell me what to do!
Ouch!
But... I wanna go to Tokyo
with everyone else!
Do as you wish.
Why should I care
how your life ends up?
Jun-chan!
I just abandoned you.
Why does that make you happy?
I must do my best!
No more staying out late!
No more clubbing!
Drop dead, Demon Lord!
No alcohol My goal: Tokyo
No more staying out late!
No more clubbing!
Drop dead, Demon Lord!
No alcohol My goal: Tokyo
Farewell, DJ Matsushida!
I have no time to be thinking
about love.
When I get to Tokyo,
I'll see many handsome men
walking the streets...
This is the beginning of
our wonderful Tokyo life, Jun-chan!
I guess life doesn't always
work out as planned.
But why? I studied so hard
and yet I failed them all.
I knew it, it's my cursed fate!
Don't blame your fate for it.
It's fine for you two, Jun-chan.
You got into your university, so you can
play all you want this spring.
I'm not going to university
to have fun!
But Nana, it doesn't hafta be
a university for you, right?
A specialty college will do, right?
My parents tell me
they're only paying tuition
if I were going to university.
Then you'll hafta wait
a full year from spring.
But I don't wanna go to art university
desperately enough to wait a year.
What in heavens should I do?
Hey, shouldn't we be heading back
to the hotel?
I wanna get up early tomorrow
and visit a few real estate agents.
You're right.
Nana, since we've come
all the way here to Tokyo,
wanna try another shop?
Yes!
Which shop would be nice?
Sorry!
Go on ahead without us.
Okay. But don't drink too much.
You never stop worrying, do you?
Tokyo is quite the place.
It's this late at night,
but there are so many people.
I feel like such a country girl.
You are a country girl.
But more importantly, don't you think
the correct choice for you
would be to continue at
the local art school from April?
But I wanna come to Tokyo,
no matter what.
I kinda feel responsible for this.
I brought it up, after all.
But you know,
you're better off staying back home.
Absolutely not!
Do you want to be with Junko
that much?
But...
But you're going to Tokyo too,
aren't you, Shoji?
Actually, I think I'll remain here
and commute to prep school,
and then try to get in again next year.
Then I'm coming to Tokyo
to live here, too!
I don't need my parents to pay
for my living expenses.
I'll work freelance or whatever,
and prove that I can survive
on my own!
You're being ridiculous!
Don't try and overdo things.
I'm not overdoing it. I'll be all right.
I'll show you that I can make it.
Do you have enough money to get by
without getting an allowance from home?
Like I said, I'll get a job!
What about rent money?
You're gonna need
a few hundred thousand yen upfront.
You're not a kid,
so you should know that much.
Think of things
a little more realistically, will ya?!
Then I'll go to prep school too.
That way my parents might
give me money.
What do you mean by that?
You can't go to prep school
for that reason.
What should I do then?
I'm telling you, stay back home.
You're not gonna be lonely
without me, Shoji?
I won't be lonely at all!
I'll be relieved!
What am I to you?!
The way you become all tearful,
say things to make me think
you like me...
Is it so much fun to mess
with my heart?!
All you're looking for is
a guy next to you,
who you can cuddle up
to on your terms!
What male-female friendship?
Give me a break!
I hafta get back to the hotel.
But I don't know my way back.
I've always relied on Shoji,
so I never paid attention
to where we were going.
I've purposely tried not
to watch the road.
It seems that I've fallen into the pits.
Where am I standing now?
Nana.
That's right. I'm in Tokyo.
But... it can't be.
I knew it.
What's the matter?
What are you doing here?
It's over.
Because! She was being so unreasonable!
I got upset!
I can see why.
It's natural for you to get upset.
But to just leave her there?
I'm disappointed in you, Shoji!
Well, the streets are
well lit during night.
She should be able to
get back here alone.
That's not the point! You shut up.
It's come to this,
so I'll tell you.
Shoji, Nana is in love with you.
That's not possible.
Imagine how hurt she'd be,
being told those things
from the man she loves.
Think it through, and act on it!
To be honest, I did sorta suspect that.
But I figured that was
just wishful thinking.
What do you mean?
Hey, if Junko's telling you,
then you know it's true.
See what happens when
you act before you think?
I see. You applied to art schools here.
But I failed to enter all of them.
I'm not sure what to do now.
I had my heart set on coming Tokyo.
But it wasn't like I came
to search you down or anything.
I'm not a stalker,
so don't worry, okay?
You haven't changed, Nana.
What? No way! I did change.
My hairstyle, my clothes...
more like a kid than
when I was in high school.
I'm pretty embarrassed
having you see me like this.
That suits you better, Nana.
Y-You think so too?
But the way you speak
hasn't changed at all.
"I will not cause you trouble, Mr. Asano."
"I won't stalk you." " Don't worry."
You'd say it every time we met.
I felt uneasy every time
you said it.
Why?
You haven't changed at all either.
Every time I'd ask
what's wrong I would get no reply.
I felt uneasy every time that happened.
Is that so? Well, I'm sorry.
It's such a strange feeling.
I thought I really hated this man.
But now that we meet
I have trouble hating him.
I should stop thinking that this was a lie.
I loved him with all my heart.
And at one time,
he gracefully accepted my feelings.
That's good enough.
It's something to be thankful for, isn't it?
I shouldn't be sad about it.
Right. I know now.
I recognize this corner.
Just go straight
and you'll get to your hotel.
Huh? Mr. Asano!
What are you doing here so late?
And alone with a young girl?!
I'm gonna tell your pretty wife.
Then I'd better treat you to something
next time to keep you quiet.
Yes! I'm looking forward to it.
See you.
Shouldn't you be making some excuse?
There's no need to worry.
He was just kidding.
If I tried to defend myself,
that in itself would make him suspicious.
I see. But he dealt with that guy
so calmly and swiftly.
Is he used to this adultery stuff?
But that was your real name, after all.
I'm glad.
Huh?
No, I was just talking to myself.
Well then, I'll be on my way now.
Don't you ever cheat
on your wife again!
I'll be careful.
Very well.
Not that I should be the one telling you.
Goodbye, Mr. Asano.
I really...
loved you.
I'm all right.
There will be no more tears.
What a stupid ring tone?
That ruins the mood.
Yes, Nana here.
What? You're in high spirits.
Kyosuke?
Judging from your cheerfulness,
I guess he found you, did he?
Wh-Who?
So he didn't find you.
Well, it wasn't likely.
Where are you now?
I-I thought he meant Mr. Asano.
I'm right by the hotel.
I'll be there in a bit.
About an hour ago,
Shoji and Junko got all concerned
and went out looking for you.
If they find you,
it would be like some TV drama.
That could be fun.
Is it so much fun to mess
with my heart?!
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean for this to happen.
Well, don't apologize to me.
I...
And don't cry to me.
But, .,!
It's all right.
Shoji is in love with you.
Liar!
You're the one who's lying,
and you know it.
Kyosuke...
Where do you think Shoji is now?
Who knows?
I imagine he's within walking distance.
Anyway, just come back to the hotel...
No luck, Kyosuke! I can't find her!
It would be quicker trying to reach her
on her cell phone!
So you finally realized.
The truth is I always loved him.
From that first time I saw him,
I liked him.
But at that time,
I was battered pretty badly.
I may have selfishly labeled myself
as a victim,
but I was hurting all over,
just the same.
I was afraid.
Afraid that if I got involved,
my scar would spread.
Whenever I'm with you,
Shoji, I always felt healed.
You hugged me gently with
all your heart, didn't you?
Right now, I want you to embrace me
with that warmth,
with all your strength.
Shoji... Shoji!
I reached into the sky
But I couldn't reach what I wanted
They grew smaller
and disappeared into the sky
Like colorful balloons
I'm alone
My hand had no place to go
And gently you took it
Starless night
I won't look back
at the shadow of my past
I want to feel your warmth
Tears are falling down
Even if I'm unsure I won't let go
Of your hand holding mine