Senpai!
Are you okay?
Yeah, thanks.
Kuriyama-san, it's not dead! Destroy its eye!
Its eye?
I'm going after it!
Th-That's the spirit!
What're you doing?! It's gonna get away!
I don't wanna damage the fence!
We can get the Cleaners to fix it later!
I just hate standing out, okay?!
Be careful! This thing isn't holding back.
I know that!
Loneliness makes my cheeks wet
kodoku ga hoho wo nurasu nurasu kedo
But when the dawn emerges in silence
yoake no kehai ga shizuka ni michite
And carries me up into the skies
watashi wo sora e maneku yo
Hope awaits on the other side
kibou ga kanata de matteru
So here I go
sou da yo iku yo
I've been wandering, trying to find you
mayoi nagara mo kimi wo sagasu tabi
We missed each other, but our hands touched
surechigau ishiki te ga fureta yo ne
I'll hold your hand tightly
tsukaemaeru yo shikkari
Our mutual longing is
motomeau kokoro
The first step toward our dream
sore wa yume no akashi
We're drawn closer as we begin to accept each other
tagai wo uketomeru tabi ni hikareteku
We won't need to spend our days in sadness anymore
kanashii hibi wa mou iranai
Because we'll have a great time together
tagai wo uketomete ikiru yorokobi ni
That I'm sure the two of us will
kitto kitto futari
Learn to appreciate
mezameru yo
What matters is that I've finally found you
mayoi nagara mo kimi wo mitsuketa yo
Ultramarine
Too slow!
Where'd it go?
Kuriyama-san, be careful! Especially with your glasses.
You're being unpleasant!
Hiding underground?
There!
Kuriyama-san!
Did you get it?
Yeah.
Wait... Th-The eye can move?!
It's getting away, Kuriyama-san!
Can't we just let it go?
After all that?
It won't bother me any more.
Quit now and you won't get a dime.
Whatever.
But how will you pay for tomorrow's groceries?
And next month's rent?
So unpleasant!
He should be safe down there.
Kuriyama-san!
Stab it!
Hurry! Stab it!
No!
Kuriyama-san, are you all right?
I'm fine. Just a bit lightheaded...
since... this uses my blood.
Let's take this to Ayaka-san tomorrow.
I'll pick you up in the morning.
Ayaka? Who's that?
She purchases demons as an official appraiser for the Exterminator's Society.
All of the Exterminators around here...
You shouldn't get too close.
I normally keep these powers suppressed.
Even you would get hurt by touching my blood now.
Regardless... Blood's still blood, right?
Give me your hand.
I can do it myself.
Come on.
I need to thank you.
You saved me back in your apartment, right?
Kuriyama-san, aren't you going to join a club?
I don't have time for one.
Are you interested in the Literary Club?
Why?
I'd love to have a bespectacled beauty there.
You're so unpleasant!
You see, I'm a member of the club.
There are only two of us, though.
Oh, the other member is an Exterminator as well,
so she could help you out with work as well.
I'll pass.
Huh? Why?
I don't care to interact with others.
A beauty in glasses under the moon...
Kanbara Akihito-sama
This is unpleasant.
I'm the one who finds this unpleasant!
We're here.
A café?
No, a photo studio?
Shindou Photo Studio
Only as a front.
Kanbara-san! Good morning!
Good morning. Is Ayaka-san around?
I'm sorry. She was up late last night, so she's still...
I see.
There was a demon I was hoping she could take a look at.
You got one? That's kind of strange.
H-How can you speak with a demon as if she's a friend?!
Wait!
Don't tell me you never noticed!
She's a demon!
I know she is! But she isn't our enemy.
As you can see, she's no different from a normal person.
Ayaka-san is the same deal.
They're like normal people?
Yep! Demons come in all shapes and sizes!
My name is Shindou Ai.
Demons appraising other demons?
Yep! We're even certified by the Exterminator's Society.
See for yourself!
Authorization to Appraise Demons
Name:
Shindou Ayaka
Authorization Number: 33703
Under the provisions stated in
Legislative Article 21, Section 1,
this testifies that you are authorized
to dispose of and appraise demons.
Exterminator's Society
Demons... dealing with demons?
I get that a lot.
I would imagine!
It's not like humans go around appraising other humans!
You shouldn't lump all the demons together like that!
There are all sorts of us, ranging from insectoids to humanoids.
We're jumbled together sort of the same way mammals are.
For instance, you may both be mammals,
but humans appraise cows and pigs, right?
Well, when you put it that way...
I'm glad you understand!
How come you still seem unconvinced?
Akihito.
Who's that?
Oh, you haven't met before? This is—
You're a pig, Senpai!
Where the hell did that come from?!
Akihito, you're horrible!
And why are you playing along?!
Mitsuki, you know who this is, right?
This is Kuriyama Mirai-san.
Oh, this is her!
So she's real after all.
What's that supposed to mean?
To be blunt, I thought you subconsciously created an imaginary girl
who looks cute in glasses and always ends her sentences with a "meow,"
since you're so pathetic and can only sustain yourself through escapism.
I'm amazed at how you can insult me and be so casual about it.
Oops. Should she end with "glasses!" instead?
If you're making her as quirky as possible, she should always shout, "Yeah, glasses!"
Actually, that doesn't sound half bad.
We really should be on our way.
Ai-chan, have you noticed anything unusual with the demons lately?
No, not in particular.
Did something happen?
Well, I ran into one that was rather aggressive.
Mitsuki, do you know anything?
Don't know, don't care.
You stuck your nose where it didn't belong, didn't you?
Don't make it sound like it's my fault!
Oh, right! Kuriyama-san!
Y-Yes?
About what I said yesterday. What do you think?
I'm inviting you to come visit the Literary Club.
Sound good?
You haven't joined any other clubs,
and there aren't that many Exterminators at our school.
Plus you just got here, so—
I believe I already turned that offer down.
Akihito.
You're a pervert.
What makes you say that?
Cafeteria
Oh, there she is!
Basic Udon Noodles
Basic udon noodles again...
Senpai!
My treat. Eat up.
I-I don't need—whoa!
Need me to hold that?
P-Please do.
Take this back!
But my hands are full.
Like I said!
Are you that against joining the Literary Club?
Huh? Did you give it a try? How was it?
Was it any fun?
I guess there's no other choice. I'll have to ask him first.
How typical of him.
Hiromi!
Don't forget my title.
I'm an upperclassman.
You forgot to put a Cage around the school the other day, didn't you?
Thanks to you, I had to call the Cleaners!
I don't recall promising to keep a Cage around the school constantly.
It's not my job to specifically protect this campus.
There's something I'd like to ask you.
I thought so.
You'd have no reason to see me otherwise, Akkey.
Want me to tell you why I don't care to see your face?
Because demons and Exterminators mix as well as water and oil?
It's because that weird nickname you gave me makes it sound like I'm some washed-up idol!
Akkey, you're so rowdy!
Always so energetic when it comes to that name.
I regret coming to you 30 seconds after you opened your mouth!
You owe me an apology!
So, what did you want to ask?
I ran into a rather aggressive demon yesterday.
Any idea what could have agitated it?
Are you getting involved in things you shouldn't again?
What if I am?
I won't raise a hand against you, Akkey.
In exchange, you aren't supposed to offer anyone support.
That was the promise, huh?
It wasn't a promise. It was a deal. A truce.
Hiromi...
Yes, Akkey?
What are your hands doing there?
Well, my fingers were getting cold.
Akkey, your waist is really something.
Stop it!
You shouldn't freak out over a fellow man wrapping his hands around your waist.
Like hell I won't!
All I'm trying to say is that that your waist is pure and warm.
That doesn't make me the least bit happy!
Let's just get back to the topic at hand!
You mean why girls give you the cold shoulder?
I would like to know why, but not even close!
I'm here about the demon!
Why do you want to know about that?
Did Mitsuki send you?
No, I'm here on my own accord.
In that case...
I'm even less obligated to talk.
In other words, you do know what triggered it.
You bought that?
She's not here, huh?
Shindou Photo Studio
26,000 yen?! Seriously?
I believe I'm giving you quite the deal.
Oh, Kanbara-kun!
Hello.
I keep running into you!
Can you believe it?
After all my hard work, she's only giving me 20,000 yen!
You shouldn't lie.
We both know that demon wasn't all that aggressive, now was it?
As if! It went nuts attacking me!
It's strange for it to be like that.
Oh, dear!
Hello?
Oh, sorry. I'd like to run home and get changed before I head over.
Don't be stupid!
What type of heroine attends a group blind date in wool panties?
She's as lively as ever.
So has a girl named Kuriyama-san dropped by?
Kuriyama-san?
Oh, you mean the case Ai texted me about?
No, she hasn't.
I see.
By the way, have you set up a new barrier to ward people off?
Yeah, the old one was starting to wear off.
But the average Exterminator should be able to see through the new one.
It's hard to say whether or not she counts as "average."
If I remember correctly, the Nase Manor is somewhere near the top of this hill.
Yep! I heard it's really huge!
May I help you?
We're okay.
Goodbye.
I just can't seem to find it.
I'm sure it's around here somewhere.
Kuriyama-san.
Yes!
Oh, Senpai.
Come with me.
Uh, okay...
Um...
What?
Mitsuki-senpai, why...
Why what?
Why are you with Senpai... Kanbara-senpai?
Good question.
To put it simply,
you could say I'm watching him.
Here we are.
Shindou Photo Studio
Kanbara Akihito-sama
It looks like her thoughts are embedded into it.
Care to see them?
Well, this postcard did come from my mother.
AKKUN
Yippee!
Akkun, have you been staying awesome?
It's Yacchan—
AKKUN
Could you pretend that you never saw any of that?
Kanbara-kun, was that your mother just now?
Yes! She's always been in her own world!
On Parents' Day in elementary school, she always sat with the students and raised her hand.
She has such an avant-garde mindset!
Akihito, a strong sense of individuality and uniqueness is a great thing to have.
How long have you been there?
Since you said, "I keep glasses worn by high school girls in vinyl bags,
and I get high huffing the air out of the bags."
I said no such thing!
The girl in glasses is Kuriyama-san, yes?
Y-Yes!
I'm Shindou Ayaka.
I'm a demon, but please don't attack me.
Perfect timing!
You need to appraise Kuriyama-san's demon, so my letter can wait.
I'd just love to hear the rest!
Wouldn't you?
Even I can get embarrassed, you know!
Akane, it's true that cat-type demons aren't too bright,
but you shouldn't be embarrassed of your own mother!
Wait! My mother isn't a demon.
She's an Exterminator.
My father is the demon! We've been over this before!
Then how do you explain those ears?
They're fake.
They looked awfully real.
It's all about the details for her.
The apple doesn't fall far from the tree, huh?
Aw, screw it!
I just can't talk you guys out of it!
Let's just get this over with!
You gotta know when to hold and when to fold, Kanbara-kun.
I have something impurrtant to tell you,
so please be all ears to the end.
I think even the avant-garde community would award her for dancing like that.
Could you please stop
talking about my mother?
Oh, but first off, are you eating right?
If you don't cook for yourself from time to time,
you won't get the nutrients you need.
It's unhealthy!
For the love of God!
Akihito.
Kill yourself now.
Leave me alone!
Moving along...
Now for my important message.
A powerful demon is headed your way, my kitten!
Have mew ever heard of the "Hollow Shadow"?
The Hollow Shadow doesn't possess a physical body.
So no meowtter what, don't try to fight it!
Akkun, you're a good kitten,
so I'm sure you understand,
but make sure to steer clear of it!
Pinky promise that you'll stay away from it, Akkun!
Isn't it wonderful to have a busty mother with a few screws loose?
Just stop.
Anyway, what's this "Hollow Shadow"?
Just as she said, it's a powerful demon that lacks a physical body.
Rumor has it that the last time it appeared,
five Class A Exterminators didn't last even five minutes.
Class A Exterminators...
What are we going to do if that comes here?
We'll just have to wait for it to pass us by.
Could this be related to why the demons were so aggressive yesterday?
It's possible.
Low-level demons are easily influenced by the aura surrounding other demons.
So that's what it is.
Well, now that the show's over,
why don't we take a look at Kuriyama-san's demon?
Wait! All of that was just a show to you?!
You couldn't tell?
Don't make my mother the source of your entertainment!
Where is the demon you caught?
Oh, right!
If you would be so kind...
Let's see...
1,000 yen?!
I worked so hard to take it down, and all I get is 1,000 yen?!
Well, that's just how it goes.
This is seriously unpleasant!
A schoolgirl's complaints!
Well, you can just ignore Akihito.
If you run into trouble, come to me for advice.
You know where our clubroom is, right?
Mitsuki says you're welcome to join, too.
Senpai...
Are you hungry?
Beef Bowl
Open 24 Hours
Thanks for waiting for your medium bowl!
This is my reward?
Right. You helped a bit, so you earned it.
Thank you. May I get some pickled radishes?
Stick with the complementary pickled ginger.
All right, all right.
Well, you are treating me with the money earned from your first job.
I should be honored.
Senpai...
What is it?
This is the last time.
Please don't meddle in my affairs any more.
You and I are different.
I don't want to go through life the way you do.
I'm not allowed to enjoy life with others the same way you do.
Why not?
I... killed someone.
I killed someone. I...
I killed her with my own two hands.
seijaku wo kirisaku you otozureta no wa
Breaking through the silence
hitsuzen toshite no kaikou
We met in an inevitable encounter
bokura no tame ni
For both our sakes
koukai wo nageku me ni
In your mournful eyes
utsuru kimi wa sou
I see a reflection of regrets
urei wo matotte utsukushiku saita
Enveloped in sorrow, you've blossomed beautifully
dare ka no seimei ni tokeru hana
The flower that fuses into someone's life
nee kimi ni mo mieru darou
Hey, do you see it too?
kitto
I'm sure you do
kasaneta ayamachi nurikaeyou
Let's paint over all the mistakes we've made
nando demo ii sa kurikaeshiteiku start line
A new start line will always be there if we want to start over
kako to wa chigau asu wo
Let's make our future different from the past
futari dake no kibou egaku start line
Our small hope will paint a new start line
I never say goodbye
itsu datte sou sa
That's how I always am
As long as people exist, demons will also exist.
Moonlight Purple
And with our ability to see them,
we will continue to smite them.
Don't you think that makes being an Exterminator an undesirable career?
Senpai...