My, my. She's much stronger than I had anticipated.
Honestly, I'm glad we're in the middle of the Calm.
Where do you think you're going?
Even during the Calm, you're this powerful?
Impressive!
But how about this?
Aya-chan...
Loneliness makes my cheeks wet
kodoku ga hoho wo nurasu nurasu kedo
But when the dawn emerges in silence
yoake no kehai ga shizuka ni michite
And carries me up into the skies
watashi wo sora e maneku yo
Hope awaits on the other side
kibou ga kanata de matteru
So here I go
sou da yo iku yo
I've been wandering, trying to find you
mayoi nagara mo kimi wo sagasu tabi
We missed each other, but our hands touched
surechigau ishiki te ga fureta yo ne
I'll hold your hand tightly
tsukaemaeru yo shikkari
Our mutual longing is
motomeau kokoro
The first step toward our dream
sore wa yume no akashi
We're drawn closer as we begin to accept each other
tagai wo uketomeru tabi ni hikareteku
We won't need to spend our days in sadness anymore
kanashii hibi wa mou iranai
Because we'll have a great time together
tagai wo uketomete ikiru yorokobi ni
That I'm sure the two of us will
kitto kitto futari
Learn to appreciate
mezameru yo
What matters is that I've finally found you
mayoi nagara mo kimi wo mitsuketa yo
Senpai!
Senpai, you've finally woken up!
Ai-chan!
It's quite the troublemaker, isn't it?
Big Bro!
I know! You don't need to worry.
Be careful!
Keep your eyes on the darn thing!
Yakiimo!
Silver Bamboo
To think I just had this upgraded to an anti-demon gun...
This puts me in quite a bind.
You seem to be enjoying yourself despite that.
Really? That's good to hear.
I will not let things go as you had hoped!
I see.
I manipulated the light particles.
I've been conducting research on various topics, you see.
Is the Exterminator's Society backing you?
Senpai...
Ayaka-san!
Izumi-san!
Senpai...
Mitsuki!
Start shrinking the Cage! Don't allow any gaps!
Make sure it doesn't waver!
Concentrate! Maintain its current strength!
Got it!
Aren't demons supposed to become weaker during the Calm?
Normally, that demon would have given a Class A Exterminator a hard time.
I bet some Exterminator bit off more than he could chew and attracted it,
thinking he could beat it during the Calm.
Thank you...
Yakiimo.
Izumi-neesama...
The door's locked.
Doesn't look like he's come back yet.
Allow me...
But why did Akihito transform into a demon?
When he was unconscious, Ayaka-san told me
that his human half had grown terribly weak.
Even though his demon half has been weakened by the Calm,
his human half might be even weaker right now!
It seems that his demon half has taken control as a result.
Right.
That would explain why Akihito-kun's demon form was weaker than it had been in the past.
That's why he fled.
Oh, I'm sorry!
Number 135?
“Overall Grade: 83.
Comments: While this photo contains the special mystique that only bespectacled beauties have,
her expression seems too forced.
It simply does not feel natural."
How unpleasant.
Check out those boxes over there.
What a sicko!
It's a shame that the half-demon, one of the rarest kinds of demons, is like this.
I don't think it's fair to criticize him after you've gone through his stuff without his permission.
But this is just too much!
Kuriyama-san
The magazine for everyone who loves glasses
magazine for everyone who loves glasses
who loves glasses
For Kuriyama-san’s
birthday
How unpleasant!
I'll go ahead and set it up so I'll know if anyone comes in.
What was that?!
Another demon?
All three of you, be prepared
to fight at a moment's notice.
He could be nearby.
Right.
Mitsuki, fall back.
You got it!
Did you really expect me to respond like that?
This is serious!
I'll run if I feel like my life is in any danger.
More importantly...
What are you going to do if you wind up having to fight him?
This isn't anything all that new.
I imagine Akkey is also prepared for what's to come.
But remember what Akihito's mother said?
She warned him to be careful during the Calm.
If you fight Akihito like before and injure him like you have in the past, he will...
What the heck is that?
Did Akkey do this?
Probably.
Is he still in the area?
I'm not certain. Hiromi, create a Cage.
On it.
Um... Shouldn't we be searching for Senpai?
I suppose.
This is merely based on my personal deductions.
You do not have to listen to me, and I cannot make you do this.
Regardless, I'm going to say this because I believe it is for the best.
Kuriyama-san, the moment you find Akihito-kun,
kill him.
Mirai?
Y-Yes?
How long are you going to stay in the shower?
I'm sorry.
The Calm has completely upset Akihito-kun's internal balance between his human and demon halves.
If he is still in his current state when the Calm ends,
we can assume that Akihito-kun's demon half will suppress his human half,
considering it has already taken control of his body.
When that happens, he will simply be a powerful demon with the gift of immortality.
Akihito-kun will lose his human half.
He will be despised as a demon forever.
Even so...
Of course, all of this is purely speculation.
There is no guarantee that this will come to pass.
But if what I just described does become reality,
he will be unstoppable.
You must decide now how you're going to act.
During the Calm, he will have lost his immortality.
During the Calm, you can kill Akihito-kun.
This... can't be real.
You're raising the gas bill.
What's wrong with you?!
I finally got you to talk.
Are you hungry?
No.
So something did happen.
What makes you say that?
Why?
Why is it so weird for me to not be hungry?
Don't cry.
Put a shirt on! Disgusting...
The right to barge in and issue demands is reserved for my little sister.
Big Bro, what do you think?
About?
What Izumi-neesama told us.
There's nothing to think about.
But she told Kuriyama-san to kill Akihito!
That's just so...
It's certainly understandable, considering the situation.
Then you should kill him for her!
I would if I could!
But even in the middle of the Calm,
if you wanted to make sure Akkey was killed,
Kuriyama Mirai is your best bet.
Big Bro...
More importantly...
More importantly?
Never mind.
Using these methods,
we should obtain Beyond the
Boundary within a day or two.
I'm counting on it.
Making another report?
Yes. I feel the Nase family has grown too large.
All of them buzzing around gives me a headache.
Now hurry off to bed.
I ran into Fujima Miroku.
I see.
What do you hope to get out of using Kuriyama Mirai?!
I didn't believe him at first,
but I've changed my mind after seeing the way you act around her.
It's obvious that you're just using her...
to kill Akkey!
And then there's Akkey turning into a demon.
There isn't anything pointing to what could have weakened Akkey's human half so much.
Izumi-neesan, did you use a frozen barrier to weaken Akkey's human half?
Izumi-neesan!
Be careful.
The Exterminator's Society is conspiring to topple the Nase family.
About time!
Things are finally starting to get interesting!
You didn't have to force yourself to come.
It's easier to be here than home alone.
What happened?
I'll tell you eventually.
Sakura...
Kuriyama-san.
Hiromi-senpai?
You haven't explained the situation to her?
I haven't.
First of all, I don't really consider her an Exterminator.
Plus, it's easier on me this way.
Look behind you.
Isn't that a...
Supposedly it's part of a demon...
known as "Beyond the Boundary".
Beyond the Boundary...
Don't kill Akkey.
I'd like you to contact me if you find him.
Kuriyama-san, do you...
Never mind.
When I first met Senpai up here, what do you think he told me?
In short, I love girls with glasses!
I thought he was crazy.
I was like, “What's this demon going on about?”
That sounds like Akkey.
I wish I never met him.
If I knew that this was waiting for me,
I wish I had never met Senpai.
I feel like someone has it out for me.
I think that maybe, just maybe...
I really am cursed.
I'm sorry to have called you out here.
It's fine.
I don't have a doubt in my mind
that Izumi-neesan is trying to get Kuriyama Mirai to kill Akkey.
The question is, why?
Would the Nase family somehow profit from killing Akkey?
The elimination of an immortal half-demon...
No, something like that is too simple for this intricate plan.
That phenomenon!
That phenomenon has been described as a part of Beyond the Boundary.
It couldn't be!
Only one piece of Beyond the
Boundary has appeared thus far.
That means the rest of it has to exist somewhere else!
It must be terribly strong,
possessing an overwhelming power!
It would be the ultimate demon, capable of leading the world to its destruction.
If such a demon existed...
He's the only one who fits that description!
As such, I believe that the demon inside of
the half-demon, Kanbara Akihito, is the one known as
Beyond the Boundary
That is a safe assumption to make.
Akkey...
I had a feeling I'd find this here.
You son of a—
Don't you worry.
I merely came to retrieve the Hollow Shadow.
Senpai!
Hello...
Where are you right now?
I'm in front of Senpai.
You're going to kill Akkey, aren't you?
Yes.
That was your plan from the start, wasn't it?
Yes!
Hey! Hello?
Hello?!
He's negating my powers!
Do you think... I look like a normal person?
Kuriyama-san!
...kill him.
You're going to kill Akkey, aren't you?
So...
live!
seijaku wo kirisaku you otozureta no wa
Breaking through the silence
hitsuzen toshite no kaikou
We met in an inevitable encounter
bokura no tame ni
For both our sakes
koukai wo nageku me ni
In your mournful eyes
utsuru kimi wa sou
I see a reflection of regrets
urei wo matotte utsukushiku saita
Enveloped in sorrow, you've blossomed beautifully
dare ka no seimei ni tokeru hana
The flower that fuses into someone's life
nee kimi ni mo mieru darou
Hey, do you see it too?
kitto
I'm sure you do
kasaneta ayamachi nurikaeyou
Let's paint over all the mistakes we've made
nando demo ii sa kurikaeshiteiku start line
A new start line will always be there if we want to start over
kako to wa chigau asu wo
Let's make our future different from the past
futari dake no kibou egaku start line
Our small hope will paint a new start line
I never say goodbye
itsu datte sou sa
That's how I always am
This is Nase Izumi.
White World
I called because there is something I would like to tell you.
Akihito kicked the bucket about two weeks ago.