Why the hell are you empty?!
Taking it out on the shampoo won't get you anywhere.
She's right! Please, just calm down.
Why are you so far away?!
Busted!
I-It's just a coincidence!
R-Right! Just an unfortunate coincidence!
Loneliness makes my cheeks wet
kodoku ga hoho wo nurasu nurasu kedo
But when the dawn emerges in silence
yoake no kehai ga shizuka ni michite
And carries me up into the skies
watashi wo sora e maneku yo
Hope awaits on the other side
kibou ga kanata de matteru
So here I go
sou da yo iku yo
I've been wandering, trying to find you
mayoi nagara mo kimi wo sagasu tabi
We missed each other, but our hands touched
surechigau ishiki te ga fureta yo ne
I'll hold your hand tightly
tsukaemaeru yo shikkari
Our mutual longing is
motomeau kokoro
The first step toward our dream
sore wa yume no akashi
We're drawn closer as we begin to accept each other
tagai wo uketomeru tabi ni hikareteku
We won't need to spend our days in sadness anymore
kanashii hibi wa mou iranai
Because we'll have a great time together
tagai wo uketomete ikiru yorokobi ni
That I'm sure the two of us will
kitto kitto futari
Learn to appreciate
mezameru yo
What matters is that I've finally found you
mayoi nagara mo kimi wo mitsuketa yo
One Week Ago
Kuriyama-san, could you stand there for a moment?
R-Right here?
A petite and demure damsel in glasses...
Shocking Pink
Well then, I can see why boring guys who can't properly express their feelings would find you irresistible.
What are you trying to say?
As an upperclassman, I'd like to help you make your high school debut.
During that festival, I thought to myself, "She could be a diamond in the rough."
Why don't we start by taking off your glasses?
Wait!
That's sacred territory that mankind must never sully!
Akkey, you should put more faith in Mitsuki.
No, I'm not backing down on this one!
A girl without glasses is like a
shortcake without strawberries!
Really? If you're comparing girls to shortcakes like that,
having strawberries would be whether or not she was a little sister.
Could you drop that disturbing conversation already?
Why'd you take them off?!
For the love of... Kuriyama-san, put these on!
Akkey, you're freaking the ladies out.
So are you.
Anyway...
What's with the bonsai trees?
Kuriyama-san, would you happen
to know anything about them?
B-Bonsai?
Wiping your glasses like that is only proving your guilt.
You're so unpleasant!
Impressive! I had no idea you were into bonsai.
You have to handle them with care!
I spent several 10,000 yen bills to grow it that big!
Be gentle! Gentle!
S-Several?!
I think I know why you're always short on cash...
and why your stomach is always growling.
B-But that hardship ends today!
At long last...
I got it back!
Shindou Photo Studio
A demon with a high bounty?
Yes. My rent is due pretty soon.
I only have a few days to come up with the money.
You shouldn't worry about money all the time.
That's where naughty photos comes from.
How much for that one?
Let me think...
You two are the ones acting naughty!
This is the one!
A fruit-type demon...
That's right! Its body is about three meters wide.
Apparently it doesn't really attack people.
On top of that, it's located on the roof of your school.
Really?
A-And the reward?
It depends on a couple things,
but it wouldn't go for less than 500,000 yen.
Five hundred thousand?!
I bet Nino is already on her way to defeat it, though.
After all, it is a rather sweet deal...
or so you'd think.
This one has quite a nasty problem.
Ayaka-san, you did that on purpose!
There it is.
There's its eye... Okay!
Wait, Kuriyama-san!
Huh?
How unpleasant!
That's what I should be saying!
I could have taken it out if you hadn't shown up or said anything!
I had nothing to do with that!
If it senses danger,
that demon covers the threat in that noxious-smelling liquid.
You didn't have a chance to begin with.
Nasty!
Got it.
So basically, all I need to do is defeat the demon before it notices me, right?
Can you?
I can!
That was great!
One of the great things about bespectacled girls is all their various gestures!
Naturally, the way they wipe their glasses melts my heart,
but so does the way they lift up their glasses, like what you did just now!
Or when they're tired and take off their glasses,
massage the bridge of their nose for a second, and then put their glasses back on.
Those are in a whole world of their own!
Huh?
It won't notice me if I'm up here!
You're mine!
Oh, crap!
Like hell that'd work!
I couldn't do it!
It dawned on me back there that you might be just a bit dumb.
Something really stinks, doesn't it?
You're right! What is that?
Senpai, try to be more mindful of everyone around you.
Hey!
What?
Don't give me that!
Are you trying to put all the blame on me?
Not really. I just think you need to be more mindful of others.
Quit messing with me!
And why do you stink so bad?
Did you make sure to wash thoroughly?
I most certainly did!
It's just... I was able to change most of my clothes...
but my underwear...
Are you serious?
I couldn't help it! I'm a girl, after all!
Even if I went commando,
I couldn't possibly go around
without proper upper support.
You couldn't go without...
I couldn't...
All right! They wouldn't jiggle around even if I wasn't wearing anything!
The only way to describe my figure is "cute," "underdeveloped," or "slender."
And why the heck do they have
to be graded A, B, C, and D?!
I think those grades must have hurt a bunch of people!
Okay, I get it! I'm sorry!
What do you guys think?!
People are bound to pick on you if you whine like that!
Isn't tomorrow Sunday?
I swear I'll get it tomorrow.
You're going to try again?
Of course I am!
Laundry doesn't pay for itself.
Shindou Photo Studio
What's this?
That's all I have available at the moment.
You're welcome to take those home.
It's not as embarrassing as your PE uniform, is it?
But these are pajamas!
Right, exactly.
Did you learn anything?
What's with those clothes? Are you spending the night?
Forget about what I'm wearing.
So, what did you learn about the demon?
This type of demon is commonly handled by diverting its attention and defeating it while its guard is down.
Makes sense.
Unfortunately, there's a problem with that whole distraction part.
Apparently it's not your typical demon.
How so?
How should I say this?
It's a bit unusual for a demon.
Kinda weird, even.
It seems to have a thing for human girls.
In other words, it's a pervert!
A-A pervert?!
Yeah, basically.
So if we could get a girl to draw its attention while another person attacked it...
Not happening.
Mitsuki, it's for your cute underclassman!
That has nothing to do with this! Why can't Ai do it?
I'm a demon, so it wouldn't work.
Exactly! Mitsuki, you're our only hope!
Please! For the sake of the Literary Club's bonsai!
You brought those into our clubroom without consulting me.
Please, Mitsuki!
What is that?!
My uniform.
It's soaked with the demon's bodily fluids.
Quit it!
Please help me, Mitsuki-senpai!
Not you too, Kuriyama-san!
Please, Mitsuki!
Mitsuki-senpai!
It's dripping! It's dripping! I-It's dripping!
It's dripping! That goo is dripping!
Next Day: Sunday
Can't we just lock it in a Cage and call it a day?
No. It's very cautious, so it'd pop the moment you tried.
Ai-chan, sorry we're making you help us out.
It's fine! Aya-chan told me to lend you a hand.
Um... Mitsuki-senpai, shouldn't you be the one drawing it's attention?
I don't have to do this.
Right, right!
Kuriyama-san, give it your best shot!
All right...
Um, excuse me! Hello!
Uh, I'm not here to attack you.
Look. I don't have any weapons or anything.
So, um...
It's ogling you, Kuriyama-san!
Right!
Um...
It likes her!
They say that when its eye changes color,
it means that its becoming less alert!
Great! Keep it up.
I think I've waited long enough.
Go, Yakiimo!
Y-Yakiimo?!
It ate too much!
What a disaster.
Same Day: Sunday
I see.
So the liquid it hit Mitsuki with is from what it's previously used.
Right! Put simply, it's like how pollen gets shot toward a pistil.
It marked her with a unique scent so that it wouldn't lose track of where she is.
The person who has been marked is oblivious to the smell!
No matter many times I bathe or change my clothes,
I'm going to smell awful to everyone around me, right?
Correct. The stench will disappear if you defeat the demon,
but that's the only way to get rid of it.
I'm sorry about this.
I think I finally understand why that demon is worth so much.
Same here.
Wouldn't it be better if you earned your income
gradually instead of all at once with large, risky jobs?
Yeah. I think the landlord would give me some extra time to come up with the rent if I asked, too.
Stop right there!
Why do I get the feeling
that you're backing out?
Can you blame us?
That demon is way stronger than it—
You dragged me into this.
Stop! Are you trying to kill me?
What will happen to me?
I've got school tomorrow.
Mitsuki!
Are you all right?
Big Brother!
You okay?
That was the first text my little sister has sent me in roughly a year.
This is horrible!
She's your precious little sister, isn't she? Could you help her out?
That stench...
Was the demon that attacked Mitsuki shaped like a fruit?
You've heard of it?
Yeah. Izumi told me about it.
Exodus!
The fresh air is so nice!
We should have done this from the start!
Ai-chan, where did that come from?
What is this?
It's a mysterious ball.
Aren't you supposed to use it to play in the water?
Have you come up with a way to defeat that demon?
Aya-chan just so happened to have one.
It's true that the demon takes
a strong interest in the ladies,
but it's also interested in one other thing—
Mitsuki!
Wh-What is it?
I just realized that it would be kind of nice if I kept you in this thing.
You feel that way, too?
I was just thinking the exact same thing!
I think a bespectacled beauty would
look surprisingly hot in one of these!
Oh, that's quite the image!
She'd have to be a little sister, but that's not bad!
I wasn't expecting to strike gold today!
We seem to be on the same page today.
This isn't half bad, huh?
Indeed, it's not!
Fresh air tastes good!
That stinks! I mean, that hurt!
It reeks!
Nasty!
Where's that smell coming from?
Do you think we should report it?
My little sister has committed a criminal offense.
Forget about that!
Hurry up and tell me how to defeat that demon!
Songs?
Right. In short, it's said to react strongly if a person sings with a steady pulse,
and moves their body in time with their singing within its range of vision.
So basically, we need to sing and dance for the demon?
Just what I would expect from Ayaka Shindou's little sister!
You're a clever cookie.
Thank you very much.
What an adorable gesture!
She'd be a perfect little sister if she weren't a demon!
Did you just flip the switch on your sister complex?
I wish I had thought of this sooner.
You surrounded yourself in a Cage?
So? Do you know what the song is?
Yeah.
This is the song that was used the last time someone defeated it.
I'd like you two to listen to it.
I-I have to sing and dance to this?
Well? Isn't it a nice song?
Why are you making us use a song you like?
Calm down!
I assure you that this was officially recognized as the song used the last time it was defeated!
Where was it officially recognized?
It's sickeningly sweet... and kinda embarrassing.
I think I actually like it.
According to the data I found,
the demon's eyes gave off a pale light when it listened to this song.
It completely dropped its guard,
and defeating it was as easy as taking candy from a baby.
But, I don't really...
We're doing it.
We're gonna do it.
Okay.
Well, let's go for it!
R-Right!
I'm starting the song!
Hiromi, I just remembered something.
What is it?
If I remember correctly, Kuriyama-san told me that she's a horrible singer.
Akkey...
It's too late.
Th-The promise caught... i-in—
Most unpleasant.
That's what I should be saying!
So what now? It's gonna be dark soon!
Isn't that obvious?
After our showers, we're going to give it another shot!
I don't want to.
Hey! Do you realize what you're saying?!
I'm sick of stinking so much!
Hey! Kuriyama-san!
I mean, it just stinks so bad.
It doesn't even make sense anymore!
There's nothing but non-stop stench!
I'm tired of stinking to high heavens!
Stinking really stinks!
What's gonna happen to me then?!
Please keep your distance!
You stink!
Why you...
It's true...
It may be true that we stink, but that's all the more reason not to give up!
Big Brother!
That demon has humiliated the Nase family for the last time!
I cannot afford to keep quiet and do nothing.
I will defeat it!
Whatever might happen, I will neither  forgive nor forget what it's done to us!
I feel the exact same way.
Why must I get stinky?!
I've never, ever been so pissed over getting stinky.
I swear that I will defeat that demon!
Senpai!
I'm sorry.
Kuriyama-san.
Let's defeat that demon together.
I'll be there to cheer you on!
Okay!
Come on!
O-Okay!
With that all sorted out, let us begin our training!
Okay!
One Week Later
You're set and ready to go!
W-Will this actually work?
We have to believe that it will!
We can't let our week's worth of training go in vain.
That's right! We worked so hard. We can do this!
That's right, we will! We can do it!
I swear on my pride as an Exterminator, we will make this work!
Break a leg, everyone!
Guys, let's do it!
Yeah!
I'm turning on the music!
It'll work out. We can do it! I'm sure we can!
Knowing us, we can pull it off. That's right. We are...
idols!
The promise we hold in our hands is
tenohira ni tsukanda yakusoku wa
A treasure that will never disappear
eien ni kienai takaramono
One day we'll reach beyond the sky that we look up at
itsuka miageta sora no kanata ni
The future star guides us to our future
bokura no asu e to michibiku future star
Sweet! It's working.
Yeah, it's working!
It can't look away from them! What a reaction!
The tears we shed together were
kimi to tomo ni nagashita namida
Just like shooting stars that streak across the night
marude yoru wo kakeru ryuusei ne
If I could make a wish come true
negaigoto ga kanau no naraba
I'd use it to protect the one thing that's so precious to me
hitotsu daiji na mono wo mamoru yo
Miracles don't happen by chance
kiseki wa guuzen ja nai
They're the fruit of hard work
doryoku no kesshou de
Even in the deepest darkness, you can find a beautiful dream
donna kurayami ni mo utsukushii yume wa aru yo
Let's push on with indomitable spirit
motto mae e susumou akiramenai kokoro
You motivate me to never give up
kimi to naraba ganbareru
It's not wasted effort
muda na koto wa nai yo
Look up and smile
ue wo muite waraou
Amazing! The demon's eye is glued to them.
This moment is yours
ichido kimi no toki dakara
I'll never forget your smile
wasurenai yo egao
Even when I take the most painful path
donna tsurai michi mo
You always stick with me
itsumo kimi ga soba ni iru
No matter what awaits at our destination
tadoritsuita saki ni nani ga matteiyou to
The star of the future that lights the way will keep us together
asu wo terasu kizuna wa future star
A hard week's worth of effort!
We can't let it go to waste!
Please! This is...
...our...
...ultimate weapon!
Let's push on with indomitable spirit
motto mae e susumou akiramenai kokoro
You motivate me to never give up
kimi to naraba ganbareru
It's not wasted effort
muda na koto wa nai yo
Look up and smile
ue wo muite waraou
This moment is yours
ichido kimi no toki dakara
I'll never forget your smile
wasurenai yo egao
Even when I take the most painful path
donna tsurai michi mo
You always stick with me
itsumo kimi ga soba ni iru
No matter what awaits at our destination
tadoritusita saki ni nani ga matteiyou to
The star of the future that lights the way will keep us together
asu wo terasu kizuna wa future star
We did it!
Success! We pulled it off!
Now... we can defeat that demon.
So, who's gonna defeat it?
The End
Why the hell are you empty?!
seijaku wo kirisaku you otozureta no wa
Breaking through the silence
hitsuzen toshite no kaikou
We met in an inevitable encounter
bokura no tame ni
For both our sakes
koukai wo nageku me ni
In your mournful eyes
utsuru kimi wa sou
I see a reflection of regrets
urei wo matotte utsukushiku saita
Enveloped in sorrow, you've blossomed beautifully
dare ka no seimei ni tokeru hana
The flower that fuses into someone's life
nee kimi ni mo mieru darou
Hey, do you see it too?
kitto
I'm sure you do
kasaneta ayamachi nurikaeyou
Let's paint over all the mistakes we've made
nando demo ii sa kurikaeshiteiku start line
A new start line will always be there if we want to start over
kako to wa chigau asu wo
Let's make our future different from the past
futari dake no kibou egaku start line
Our small hope will paint a new start line
I never say goodbye
itsu datte sou sa
That's how I always am
I see. Kuriyama-san said that?
More or less.
She wants to hurry and settle things with Sakura.
Color of Clouds
Did something happen?
Sakura!
I should die by your hands...
or so I had thought.