Why are you still alive?
Are you trying to atone?
Sakura!
"Sakura!" Isn't that what you were screaming back there?
That's right.
Inami Sakura.
She's the younger sister of Inami Yui, the girl I murdered.
Cut the revenge crap!
This has nothing to do with you.
Loneliness makes my cheeks wet
kodoku ga hoho wo nurasu nurasu kedo
But when the dawn emerges in silence
yoake no kehai ga shizuka ni michite
And carries me up into the skies
watashi wo sora e maneku yo
Hope awaits on the other side
kibou ga kanata de matteru
So here I go
sou da yo iku yo
I've been wandering, trying to find you
mayoi nagara mo kimi wo sagasu tabi
We missed each other, but our hands touched
surechigau ishiki te ga fureta yo ne
I'll hold your hand tightly
tsukaemaeru yo shikkari
Our mutual longing is
motomeau kokoro
The first step toward our dream
sore wa yume no akashi
We're drawn closer as we begin to accept each other
tagai wo uketomeru tabi ni hikareteku
We won't need to spend our days in sadness anymore
kanashii hibi wa mou iranai
Because we'll have a great time together
tagai wo uketomete ikiru yorokobi ni
That I'm sure the two of us will
kitto kitto futari
Learn to appreciate
mezameru yo
What matters is that I've finally found you
mayoi nagara mo kimi wo mitsuketa yo
Color of Clouds
That was the bell's memory.
The Hollow Shadow is a terrifying demon.
If you aren't a strong Exterminator, it will possess you.
Look.
When you look at the sky, what color do you see?
Mirai-chan and I see purple
because of our power...
as Exterminators.
The bell has lost its memories.
First, I want you to see this.
This was no accident.
No way! Are all of the CDs like this?
I was even warned.
Two nights ago, I felt the urge to listen to music and turned on my MP3 player.
But all of my idol groups' albums had been replaced with...
Naked Salary Men
the Naked Salary Men drama CDs!
That has to be Mitsuki's doing!
I can't think of anyone else who
would do something this drastic!
What did you do?
I only submitted Mitsuki's resume
to HND48 without telling her.
Audition Application
Name
Nase Mitsuki
Why didn't you get her permission first?
"My family sent in my resume without telling me!"
You hear that kind of story all the time!
Picture this:
Surrounded by other cuties,
my little sister takes center stage in an adorable costume, straddling the microphone stand!
C-Can I put everyone in glasses?
I won't argue over such petty details.
It's beautiful.
Isn't it?
Hey, you two perverts.
Where is Kuriyama-san?
Huh? Oh, I dunno.
Today's Udon Day, so she's probably...
Udon Day?
It's a monthly event held by Hachibei, the udon shop.
Kama-age Udon Noodle Festival
Yen
For 150 yen, you can eat as much kama-age udon as you want!
Anyway, it's about time we did something about those bonsai trees.
She brought in a whole bunch of them.
It's good!
Hey!
You lousy kids! Go play baseball somewhere else!
It's her! Let's scram!
She sounds like a grumpy old man.
Outbreak on the Surface of the Mirror
In regard to this incident, my...
How unpleasant!
That branch was the counterweight!
Need any help?
I'm fine—
See what I mean? Udon.
Yeah, I see it.
Y-You're so unpleasant!
As if you have the right to say that now.
This place hasn't changed a bit!
Nino-san, you normally don't come by here.
What's up? Is something wrong?
Akkey, you're lacking in the delicacy department.
Haven't you noticed that Nino-san only drops by when she needs to rant about some guy?
Oh, really?
That's not why I'm here!
It's not?!
You two are better friends than I would have guessed.
I see. You're sure that this is the girl who tried to kill you?
Yes.
I didn't think it was actually her,
but I figured I'd should make sure since you mentioned her before.
So she's an Exterminator from the Inami family?
She's already passed the transfer exam,
so our school has no reason to reject her.
She'll transfer in tomorrow if we leave things alone.
We can't...
What do we do?
It's a bit low, but if you asked Izumi,
she could put a stop to this girl's transfer right now.
The Nase family has a lot of influence in both the local and Exterminator communities.
Kuriyama-san...
Look me in the eyes and say that.
Naked Salary Men
No, I'm not listening to dudes moaning to each other!
Quit it!
Do you think you made the right choice?
Yeah. I don't think keeping her from transferring in will change anything.
She could attack me any time I'm not at school if she really wanted to.
That's true, but...
When I defeated the Hollow Shadow,
I thought that it might have given Sakura some closure, just like it did for me.
That's what I thought.
But as long as I'm around...
As long as the person who killed Yui is around...
things will never be over for Sakura.
Whenever I look at them,
they remind me not to take life too seriously.
What the hell does their company even do?!
Why don't you listen and find out?!
Despite how they act, I think they both take life seriously.
Really?
I'm really bad at this whole...
living thing.
Oh, no! I think I left my
commuter pass at school!
Go ahead without me!
Did something happen?
I'm not sure.
What are you doing out here?!
Hey!
Wh-What is this thing?!
What is that?
Oh, you're awake?
Would you like something to eat?
You're just gonna go back to sleep?!
What are you doing here?
This is my apartment.
Then what am I doing here?
I carried you here!
You abducted me?
I saved you!
It's yours if you want it.
But man, that weapon is something else!
Even I was able to defeat a demon.
You used it?
We were in a tight spot.
Here, this is the demon I defeated.
This sucks.
Then don't eat it!
Sheesh!
There must be something
wrong with your taste buds.
What are you doing?
It grows stronger when you feed it demons.
So that's why you've been going around and defeating demons?
Is it all so you can defeat Kuriyama-san?
What will defeating her accomplish?
If I defeat Kuriyama Mirai...
I will get to keep this.
It isn't yours?
I'm borrowing it...
under the condition that I use it to kill Kuriyama Mirai.
Who gave it to you?
A man?
You don't know?!
My older sister's goal was to become a respectable Exterminator.
For me to realize that goal, I need this power.
Can you handle that?
As that weapon grows stronger,
won't it require more power from the Exterminator who wields it?
When I held it earlier, it drained a massive amount of my energy.
Senpai! It's me, Mirai!
K-Kuriyama-san?
Stop! Do you plan on trashing my home?
I don't care.
Yeah, well I care!
Senpai?
U-Uh, sorry! I was in the bath. Gimme a sec!
Give that back.
Senpai?
Hide in here!
You don't want to fight when you're completely exhausted, do you?
Sorry! Is there a problem?
No, I found this and thought you might have forgotten it.
Oh, I didn't even notice! Thank—
Do you have a guest? Is someone visiting?
No, no one's—
Ah, look, it's not what you think.
Th-Those are...
Senpai, aren't you an only child?
You don't have any little sisters,
little brothers, cousins, or second cousins, do you?
Judging by their size, those shoes
belong to a young lady, don't they?
Don't jump to conclusions!
When a high school boy lives by himself,
it may be normal for him to do stuff like this.
But I still don't think it's appropriate!
I'm really not sure if it's appropriate or not!
You get flamed because you always post without thinking about what you're writing first!
Who is it?
I bet it's Mitsuki-senpai! It is, isn't it?
You two are making fun of me behind my back, right?!
We are not!
There's no way it'd be Mitsuki!
So it's Ayaka-san? Or Ai-chan?
You mustn't! They're demons, you know!
Reel in your imagination and get it under control!
N-Ninomiya-sensei?!
No way!
Then could it be...
H-Hiromi-senpai?!
Akkey, does he think your waist is more than just "warm"?!
How obscene! How unpleasant!
How unpleasantly obscene!
Give me a break.
Then who is it?
It's Sakura.
Sakura?
Two sheep, three sheep, four sheep...
Calm down!
Please don't interrupt me.
Eleven sheep... Um, uh...
She was injured and fell unconscious.
I was just making sure she was okay!
Sakura...
Kuriyama Mirai...
Good morning.
Today I'd like to introduce
our new transfer student.
Inami Sakura
I'm Sakura Inami.
Akkey...
Actually, maybe I should refer to you as "Creepy" instead.
I already told you, I'm just keeping watch!
Besides, I'm not a fan of girls when they're by the pool.
Why not?
Because the bespectacled beauty, Kuriyama-san,
has to take off her glasses, along with all of the other bespectacled first-year beauties!
But they have those water-proof glasses.
Those are goggles!
It truly upsets me whenever I hear people comparing those things to glasses!
An Exterminator gave it to her?
Yeah.
In an attempt to compensate for
her lack of supernatural powers,
I think she decided to use that.
So she's willing to go that far.
Mirai-chan!
Huh? What is it?
Sakura-san seems to be doing okay, doesn't she?
Everyone said that she seemed cold,
but once they tried talking to her,
they found it she wasn't all that bad.
That's how she is.
Sakura!
We're heading out right now.
I'll be waiting. I'll make dinner.
That's all I can do.
Sakura...
It's the things you can do that we can't that make you so great!
I see. Kuriyama-san said that?
Handle
with care
More or less.
She wants to hurry and settle things with Sakura.
You shouldn't get involved.
I know that.
It's raining again.
Market
I've placed human repellents.
These repellents are weak.
I'll evaporate your blood!
You hardened it?
Yes! Now...
I lost my way once.
I should die by your hands...
or so I had thought.
But I came to realize something when I defeated the Hollow Shadow.
My regret will never leave me.
Killing someone...
Pushing someone to the point of death...
It's something you can never take back.
I can't let you dirty your hands like that!
Yui wouldn't want you to, either.
You have no right to say my sister's name!
It grows stronger?
Yeah. She said that by having it absorb demons,
the weapon itself grows stronger.
I've never heard of something like that.
But if someone without any supernatural
powers were to wield such a weapon...
It will eventually...
devour her.
It looks like you've defeated a bunch of demons with that scythe!
But you don't stand a chance!
I was holding back when we fought last time to save some energy for the Hollow Shadow!
I'm going to put this bluntly:
You cannot become an Exterminator!
With just the power you have, it's impossible.
I will live out my life as an Exterminator,
both for you as well as for Yui!
No!
Sakura!
Don't move an inch!
Are you jealous of my power?
I... No.
Yui also mentioned how she was jealous of you.
My sister said that?
So please, continue to be yourself, Sakura.
Yui
Stay the Inami Sakura that we both knew.
Mirai
Let's go home.
That was the bell's memory.
Lost...
Mirai!
Confused...
Losing sight of myself, I grew desperate and struggled.
Every time I heard the sound of the bell, I struggled.
I wondered, "Where is the one who matters the most to me?"
In hindsight, I knew the answer the whole time.
I finally came to that realization after she showed me the way home.
I was able to decide that this is where I would live.
This is one of my precious bell's memories.
Deceiving children really isn't my thing,
but at least it looks like it's devoured enough demons.
Well then, I guess it's about time
I recovered the Hollow Shadow.
Yakiimo, you really ought to lose some weight.
Hide.
Izumi, how unusual.
You're never up this late.
What is that?
The Calm is coming.
The Calm?
A stagnant time when everything comes to a halt.
And then...
Beyond the Boundary.
seijaku wo kirisaku you otozureta no wa
Breaking through the silence
hitsuzen toshite no kaikou
We met in an inevitable encounter
bokura no tame ni
For both our sakes
koukai wo nageku me ni
In your mournful eyes
utsuru kimi wa sou
I see a reflection of regrets
urei wo matotte utsukushiku saita
Enveloped in sorrow, you've blossomed beautifully
dare ka no seimei ni tokeru hana
The flower that fuses into someone's life
nee kimi ni mo mieru darou
Hey, do you see it too?
kitto
I'm sure you do
kasaneta ayamachi nurikaeyou
Let's paint over all the mistakes we've made
nando demo ii sa kurikaeshiteiku start line
A new start line will always be there if we want to start over
kako to wa chigau asu wo
Let's make our future different from the past
futari dake no kibou egaku start line
Our small hope will paint a new start line
I never say goodbye
itsu datte sou sa
That's how I always am
Yup! At long last, the Calm is coming!
Don't take this lightly. Something about it makes me uneasy.
Calming Gold
Do something! Isn't she your older sister?
It's not like I could do anything for him, though.
Rest for a bit longer.