Senpai?
Why? Why did you come?!
What's the point of everything I've done up until now?!
Why have I been—
Shut up!
"Live," huh?
You want me to "live like a normal person" now?
When did I ever say that's what I wanted?!
When did I ever ask for that?!
You're being unpleasant!
So extremely... unpleasant!
I think you're being unpleasant!
I refuse to accept this!
I don't want to live if it means living without you.
A future without you...
means nothing to me!
Are you that oblivious?!
Were you really that oblivious?
I never expected to run into you here, Kanbara Yayoi.
It's been a hip-hoppin' while.
Izumin, you're all grown up now!
I wanna kick her.
What are you after? And what exactly is Kanbara Akihito?
What? Why, Akkun is my wittle babby wabby.
Oh, and I don't mean that in a dirty way—
I can only take so much.
Don't worry. If you hadn't kicked her, I would have.
Give me a real answer!
What exactly is an immortal half-demon?
What are you after?!
For you to ask such boring questions
means you've turned into a snore-fest yourself, Izumi.
And you should never turn into a stoopy-poopy boring adult.
It's not like I wanted to end up like this.
Izumi...
Izumi!
A puppet!
How long do you plan on making these kids wait while you nag at me?
The Exterminator's Society is already on the move.
Hiromi-kun, Mitsuki-chan!
Akihito and Mirai-chan aren't your typical demon and Exterminator.
Those two are something special.
Please look after them.
To be continued!
Wait!
Sis!
For now...
shouldn't we be focusing on whatever that is?
Come on, isn't that thing too strong to be considered a demon?
Gray World
Last Episode
Don't complain to me.
Besides, that thing was originally living inside of you. Remember?
That's the core.
Everything you see here
actually existed inside of it.
That explains why my shoulders have been killing me lately!
This really isn't the time for jokes.
Senpai, do you know anything about it?
Like what?
A weakness, maybe.
I know!
Maybe it's ticklish under its armpits, like you are!
Under its armpits... What armpits?!
Th-Then is there anything it dislikes?
Anything will do!
Something it dislikes...
Fish with roe?
Fish with roe!
Think we pissed it off?
What do you think?!
Kuriyama-san!
Senpai, did you do that?
I think so.
Your hand! Are you transforming into a demon again?!
So that defeated demon was part of Beyond the Boundary?
I can't believe it was part of you!
Yeah.
Senpai, that hand possesses some of Beyond the Boundary's power!
I'm not sure how to use it,
but if you have a power that can hold up against it...
Trying to get close to it might not be a bad idea.
Looks like it still hasn't eaten enough.
Is Beyond the Boundary simply that powerful?
Or is Mirai Kuriyama's will simply that strong?
It's clearly the latter!
Wow, you're pretty hot stuff!
But I'm afraid you're not my type.
It looks like some of my powers have returned
thanks to their hard work up there.
Really, this should be enough to beat—
You're not the one I want.
You're running late today.
I've been waiting for you!
It's grown rather powerful, don't you think?
It finally started to look decent after I stole the Hollow Shadow from your family.
Sorry, but it's my policy to stalk punks like you
who have messed with my little
sister until I'm able to crush them!
So it's three against one?
No, it's four against one.
Mitsuki...
My whole life, I've always been left to
watch the house since I'm the youngest.
It's time you let me graduate from being the house sitter!
Agreed.
I was the one originally entrusted with that scythe.
I am partially responsible for this.
Geez. I see you guys have all buddied up.
Sis!
Crap!
Well, no one can interrupt us now.
How much farther is it?
We're almost there!
Sweet! The key's in the ignition.
Wait! Senpai, do you have a license?
It's not like these are public roads, right?
Kuriyama-san, hurry and get on!
Hey! Geez!
On the handlebars?!
We've got demon up ahead!
And under us?!
Way to go, Kuriyama-san!
Are we going the right way?
I have no idea!
But keep going straight, full throttle!
If you're wondering why...
It's because it's too late to stop now!
Senpai!
No way!
This is so messed up.
Everything that exists here is messed up.
And considering where it came from, it means you're messed up, Senpai.
So it's my fault?!
But we managed to make it here.
We made it?
It's getting nervous, too!
You can tell?!
No, I can't!
But that's the feeling I get.
I'm sure everything will work out somehow!
You don't sound like your usual self, Kuriyama-san.
I don't care how I sound.
But....
Right now... I, Kuriyama Mirai, feel so optimistic, it's unpleasant!
You just had to go and say that!
Do you think it can really hear us?
How the hell am I supposed to know?
Kuriyama-san, go for it!
Kuriyama-san!
Akkey...
It's just about time.
Beyond the Boundary will soon be free of Mirai Kuriyama.
It will devour every last demon and transform into a giant vortex
before destroying the world.
So, what will you do about it, Izumi-san?
Kuriyama-san...
Kuriyama-san!
Please don't kill me.
You make me sick.
You're a monster.
I'm scared!
Don't kill me!
Beat it!
This is my...
Senpai?
Your younger brother and sister are quite persistent.
Almost as much as you are.
Big Bro, go!
Mitsuki!
If we leave everything to Izumi-neesama,
we'll be following the same old routine!
Nothing will change!
All right. You can count on your big brother!
Hiromi-senpai's gross.
Isn't he?
Why are you in such a rush?
That expression...
I've been dying to see that expression.
Trembling with fear and anxiety,
you're struggling to appear calm and collected...
while trying to defeat me!
Shut up!
Are you really that scared?
Oh, by any chance, have you fallen for me?
Or do you want to keep your siblings from learning about your past?
Shut up!
You surrendered to a demon!
What's this?
You do know that you're no different from me, right?
We both harbor demons inside our bodies.
Did you know about that, Little Brother?
Izumi...
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
It's true that we may be the same,
but I haven't cast aside my pride as a human being!
We are not the same.
Don't give me that bullshit!
Sis...
Wh-What's going on?
This is probably similar to what
happened with the Hollow Shadow.
Hiromi-senpai!
Yui!
Kuriyama-san, close your eyes!
Just do it!
Okay!
Don't let it deceive you.
Aren't demons supposed to be the embodiment of the twisted feelings and hatred found in human hearts?
The weakness in our hearts has taken form and appeared before us.
Remember what I said
back when we first met?
"I'm the same way."
Kuriyama-san, you've got me here by your side.
We met each other!
Our worlds changed.
Don't let yourself be consumed by your past.
Kuriyama-san, you aren't alone anymore.
Kuriyama-san, you've got me.
Senpai...
Open your eyes.
Wh-What is this?!
Let's get rid of them.
All of them?!
Have any other ideas?
How unpleasant!
Ayaka-san!
Ai-chan!
You two were okay?
Think we got all of them?
Dunno...
Isn't it pretty?
Yeah...
Why are you so scared?
Relax. Everything about you is also me.
All of it... existed inside of me.
Even your pitch-black jealousy!
And the despair of never being able to become human!
And the sadness of having been abandoned!
And the regret of having hurt someone!
Senpai!
And your selfishness,
your paranoia, your hatred,
your resignation, your deviousness, and your need to save yourself!
I won't let a single one of these emotions run rampant!
They all belong to me!
I'm taking all of them back!
I am the immortal half-demon.
Senpai...
Senpai!
Could you come over here?
I'm sorry, but, um...
Well, I'd like to ask...
for a favor.
What is it?
Um, please... hold out your hand.
My hand?
Yes.
Please pat my head.
I'd like you to pat me on the head.
Huh?
Kuriyama-san?
Please say, "Thank you."
Thank you...
Say it like you mean it!
Thank you!
I'm so happy!
So very happy!
Kuriyama-san!
I'm so happy! So happy!
Kuriyama-san, your feet...
Beyond the Boundary has gone back inside of you.
This dimension will fall apart soon.
I guess that means I'll vanish as well.
Now that Beyond the Boundary has returned to you,
I won't be able to exist anymore.
The real me ceased to exist a long time ago.
I'm truly glad that I got to meet you, Senpai!
Stop it!
I'm truly glad that I fell in love with you, Senpai!
Knock it off! Don't say that!
Thank you so very much!
Kuriyama-san!
This can't be happening! Wait!
I don't know if our fates had been sealed from the very beginning
or if it turned out this way because of everything Kuriyama-san did.
Personally, I like to believe that it's the latter.
At any rate, Beyond the Boundary is back inside of me,
and the world is at peace once more.
Don't tell me that was only worth a measly 100 yen!
I'm heading out!
Oh, good morning!
Good morning!
Be careful!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Gah, she's asleep!
Sakura-chan, wakey-wakey!
Demons are still around, and as always,
Exterminators continue to make a living by defeating them.
Ayaka-san and Ai-chan have returned to their old home.
60% MILK
Banana
au lait
No one knows where Fujima Miroku has gone.
Everything was swept under the rug with the claim
that he had fabricated his relation to the
Society and was acting on his own accord.
Hiromi has taken Izumi-san's position as the one overseeing the Nase family,
but it hasn't had much effect on his daily life.
Sis...
Sooner or later, there will come a day when you will understand.
I'm sorry.
Izumi, I've always looked up to you!
I've wanted to become just like you.
But I've changed my mind.
I'll never become like you.
I get it! A person can work for their ideals.
But if you lose sight of those ideals when things don't work out as planned,
you'll never accomplish anything!
You won't be able to protect
yourself or those dear to you!
You've grown strong, Hiromi.
Listen, Hiromi. You are the Nase family's—
I know!
Don't say another word. Not now.
Literary Club
Mitsuki still spends all of her time in the clubroom, verbally abusing me.
Isn't that a total waste of time if you already know that the bad guys lose in the end?
It's about the journey, not the destination.
Knock it off!
Aren't you supposed to keep your hands warm in the winter?
There's nothing wrong with me burying my hands under your arms.
Believe me, it's bury wrong!
Three points.
But Kuriyama Mirai is not here.
In the end, I lost.
Goal:
50,000 Yen!
There's no point in a future built upon sacrificing her.
Goal:
50,000 Yen!
Despite having yelled that,
here I am, accepting that future as I go through life.
I bet that right about now,
Kuriyama-san is saying,
"Serves you right!"
How unpleasant.
Just as there is some light at night and some darkness during the day,
there will always be darkness in the world.
At the same time, the world will never be completely engulfed by the darkness.
In a mix of blurred colors, everything moves on. Our fates are determined.
Amidst all of that, I...
seijaku wo kirisaku you otozureta no wa
Breaking through the silence
hitsuzen toshite no kaikou
We met in an inevitable encounter
bokura no tame ni
For both our sakes
koukai wo nageku me ni
In your mournful eyes
E-Excuse me!
utsuru kimi wa sou
I see a reflection of regrets
urei wo matotte utsukushiku saita
Enveloped in sorrow, you've blossomed beautifully
Glasses...
In short, I love it when you're
wearing glasses, Kuriyama-san!
dare ka no seimei ni tokeru hana
The flower that fuses into someone's life
nee kimi ni mo mieru darou
Hey, do you see it too?
kitto
I'm sure you do
How unpleasant.
kasaneta ayamachi nurikaeyou
Let's paint over all the mistakes we've made
I don't know if our fates had been sealed from the very beginning
or if it turned out this way because of everything Kuriyama-san did.
nando demo ii sa kurikaeshiteiku start line
A new start line will always be there if we want to start over
Perhaps my feelings for
Kuriyama-san got through to her.
kako to wa chigau asu wo
Let's make our future different from the past
Thus, Kuriyama Mirai and I were reunited.
If our story—if you could call
it one—could've simply ended here,
futari dake no kibou egaku start line
Our small hope will paint a new start line
then all the world's lore would've never come to be.
I never say goodbye
Oh, yeah! Kuriyama-san!
itsu datte sou sa
That's how I always am
You forgot something.
Would you do me the honor of wearing these glasses?
Beyond the Boundary