This is the last time.
Please don't meddle in my affairs any more.
You and I are different.
I don't want to go through life the way you do.
I'm not allowed to enjoy life with others the same way you do.
Why not?
I... killed someone.
Loneliness makes my cheeks wet
kodoku ga hoho wo nurasu nurasu kedo
But when the dawn emerges in silence
yoake no kehai ga shizuka ni michite
And carries me up into the skies
watashi wo sora e maneku yo
Hope awaits on the other side
kibou ga kanata de matteru
So here I go
sou da yo iku yo
I've been wandering, trying to find you
mayoi nagara mo kimi wo sagasu tabi
We missed each other, but our hands touched
surechigau ishiki te ga fureta yo ne
I'll hold your hand tightly
tsukaemaeru yo shikkari
Our mutual longing is
motomeau kokoro
The first step toward our dream
sore wa yume no akashi
We're drawn closer as we begin to accept each other
tagai wo uketomeru tabi ni hikareteku
We won't need to spend our days in sadness anymore
kanashii hibi wa mou iranai
Because we'll have a great time together
tagai wo uketomete ikiru yorokobi ni
That I'm sure the two of us will
kitto kitto futari
Learn to appreciate
mezameru yo
What matters is that I've finally found you
mayoi nagara mo kimi wo mitsuketa yo
Kuriyama-san.
You may have it.
Do you think you can win me over by bribing me?!
You're taking this the wrong way.
I'm not like Senpai!
Moonlight Purple
This is only my first time here,
but this place is pretty damn impressive!
An interrogation officer from the Exterminator's Observation Department?
That's right.
I'm Fujima Miroku, Nase Izumi-san.
What brings the Society here?
The Hollow Shadow.
You don't see demons of that class every day,
so I've come to observe it.
Dreams are a milestone to the underworld.
The deception of dreams,
or demons, are said to be the embodiments of human animosity.
They come from people's twisted hearts, hatred, jealousy, and malice.
As long as people exist, demons will also exist.
And with our ability to see them, we will continue to smite them.
But wouldn't you say that would make being an Exterminator an undesirable career?
The Society has some rather interesting thoughts on the subject.
Meaning?
Being the daughter of an ancient line of Exterminators
whose livelihood has always depended on exterminating demons,
I feel that my job is comparable to a farmer gathering rice, or a fisherman fishing.
I'm not concerned about the semantics.
I see.
Is that a painting of a demon?
That's not a picture frame. It's a frozen barrier.
So that's real?
Come to think of it, weren't frozen barriers your forte, Nase Izumi?
May I ask you something?
What is it?
How do you personally perceive demons?
Isn't that a given?
They are simply monsters.
Kanbara-senpai!
Eating in the cafeteria today?
Uh, yeah.
Say, Ai-chan, how do you have food when you don't even have enough money for plain udon?
That's a good question.
Basic Soba
Kitsune
Fried Gyoza
Basic Udon
Ramen
Curry Udon
Cup Ramen
Oh, so this is where you went.
Senpai!
How may I help you?
Well, I heard that you defeated a demon.
That's none of your business.
Mitsuki left it with me,
so I dropped by Ayaka-san's and traded it in.
T-Ten-thousand yen?!
That demon was worth...
Shoot, my last shrimp!
Take it.
I said I don't want it!
Calm down! Your actions are contradicting your words.
Do you realize how many of these instant ramen cups I could buy with that?!
That's why I said you can have it.
Are you crying?
I can't accept it.
Your words sound way too empty!
I don't really need this, but since you went to the trouble of bringing it here...
Like anyone would believe that one.
Anyway, just forget about it. Why don't you drop by our club today?
I've already told you. Please don't meddle in my affairs any more.
After all the times you used me as your practice dummy?
I'll stop doing that.
First you insist on chasing after me and now you're running away?
So that's Kuriyama Mirai?
Gee, I wonder whose hands these are.
These would be my hands, which I have placed on your waist.
Is there a problem?
Oh, right! I never told you, did I?
I'm a teacher here.
Did you hear about the Hollow Shadow?
Guess not since you just moved in!
It's supposed to enter town this evening.
We aren't allowed to approach it until it leaves.
Is that right?
You could live almost like a king for a good year if you managed to defeat it,
but you'd need more lives than a cat to make it out alive!
Be extra careful to steer clear of it!
Hey! No running in the halls!
A clan that can control their blood at will, huh?
Do you know anything about them?
Like... Did something happen in her past?
Was there an accident?
No clue.
Even if I had some idea, I'm not obligated to tell you.
I truly don't know anything about this, though.
I see.
Did she tell you something?
If you don't want to tell me, you don't have to.
No, I'm just not sure if it's something I should talk about.
But... I'm pretty sure that she's hiding something.
How do you know she isn't just messing with you?
Akkey, it's hard for you to turn a blind eye when you see a busty damsel in distress, isn't it?
Hold on.
You're not completely wrong, but I don't care about them being "busty."
The most important factor bifocal enthusiasts look for in a girl is that they wear glasses!
Akkey, do you enjoy passionately declaring your fetish or something?
Shut up!
You're in no position to be criticizing me when you're what we call a "siscon," Hiromi!
Oh, but isn't my unwavering resolution grand?
As a bifocal whatever-it's-called, you could never comprehend the love I have for my sacred sister.
My love for glasses deserves far more recognition than you're giving it!
I've put glasses on that "sacred sister" of yours.
You've what?!
I had her put some on when we were alone in the clubroom.
Actually, it might be more accurate to say she went nuts putting them on.
Mitsuki started to really enjoy herself somewhere along the line.
She went nuts with them?
How could you do that to my sister?!
Hey, you two sickos.
That crude behavior isn't welcome in our clubroom.
Mitsuki, you really have awoken to the glories of glasses!
I merely wanted to land a critical strike on that lecher I call my brother.
How could you defile the sacred glasses?
Now then, Pervy Bro!
Can't you call me "Big Brother" like I ask you to?
Pervy Big Brother, I would like you to hurry up and remove the Cage.
Okay, no problem.
You admit that you're a pervert?
And since you're technically in the Literary Club,
could you help us out a bit with the screening process?
I wouldn't mind picking a story out.
I'll take any blood-related little sister series, little-sister-in-law series,
or anything that has a little sister in it, really.
If you want, I could go through the ones that only feature little sisters.
There aren't any!
"Love you"?
That was clearly, "Burn in hell," you moron!
Meet me at 5:30
So this is the place?
Are we gonna be okay in a place like this?
I made sure to set up a Cage.
Animal Biscuits
Curry Flavor
Does this mean that it'd be really bad if someone overheard us?
Indeed it would.
It was so critical that we avoid eavesdroppers, I accepted the risks in being alone with a pervert,
and had us rendezvous here.
Wait! There's only one person here this "pervert" could be, right?
Well, if this pervert did his best to attack me with everything he's got,
I can't say with certainty I wouldn't fulfill his desires.
I-I'll pass.
You need to man up.
Wasn't it your goal to confess your feelings for me when you graduate, Akihito?
Since when was that my goal?!
Just get to the point already.
Kuriyama Mirai.
I suspect she's after the Hollow Shadow.
Why?
Dunno. I simply asked an Exterminator who specializes in information to do some digging around.
Ichinomiya Iori.
You've heard of him, haven't you?
Yeah.
Didn't you tell me that he can connect his mind directly to the Internet to obtain information?
That's right. He stumbled upon a rumor that almost sounds like a ghost story.
Care to hear it?
Wow! What a pretty color!
Huh?
It won't show up in a picture.
The Hollow Shadow's influence is merely making the sky appear purple.
It's the same as how Exterminators are the only ones who can see demons.
That means...
It has already entered this town.
A-Aya-chan...
The demons are growing rather restless, I see.
You can relax. I just finished.
Misfortune befalls everyone who becomes involved with those who carry the cursed blood.
An Exterminator, Inami, took in the only living descendant from that clan.
While she was subduing the Hollow Shadow,
she lost her daughter, whom she cared for more than anything.
I believe we can prevent it from hitting the center of town.
Oh?
If an Exterminator lets their guard down
for even a moment while near the Hollow Shadow, it will possess them.
Seeing that you're accustomed to mystery novel plots as a member of the Literary Club,
you can put the pieces together, can't you?
Senpai...
Why are you here?
You're going after the Hollow Shadow, aren't you?
You accidentally killed that Inami girl when the Hollow Shadow possessed her.
That's what happened, isn't it?
You looked into that?
A little, but most of it is speculation.
This is none of your business.
Please go home.
Kuriyama-san!
I can't believe all that is one demon.
Its actual body is only a portion of the central core.
The only reason you're perceiving it this way
is its immense power, which warps the space around it.
Are you going?
You're still here? Please hurry home.
What'll you do after I leave?
Senpai, that doesn't concern you.
Defeating the Hollow Shadow won't change anything.
You can't bring back the dead.
All the Hollow Shadow will bring you is the risk of getting killed, Kuriyama-san.
I know that!
You should stay home and wait for it to pass!
I know that.
Then why?!
The Inami family took me in despite my cursed blood.
They taught me how to suppress these powers, which were too much for me back then,
Their daughter was named Yui.
Wait!
Certainly. How may I help you?
I'll take it up!
Even in the Inami house, I was kept isolated.
Yui was the one who opened the door to the outside world for me.
One, two, three!
Mirai, you're going to be in high school next year, right?
Yeah! I'm going to join the Archery Club!
Really? Good luck!
I'll come cheer you on!
She was my friend.
I'm lucky I know such a cool upperclassman!
But... I...
I'm a murderer.
You're not!
I'm a murderer!
Back then, fear gripped my heart.
"I might lose my own life."
That selfish thought clearly flashed across my mind.
You're wrong!
Senpai, what would you know?!
You said that you're a half-demon.
You said that you're special, just like me.
But you're mistaken!
You have friends.
You've got Hiromi-senpai and Mitsuki-senpai.
You've even got demon friends like Ayaka-san and Ai-chan!
You're wrong.
How am I wrong?!
Ever since I was a baby, I've been treated like a demon.
People are afraid to even touch me.
How could you possibly know how I feel?!
Please don't act like you know what it's like.
Kuriyama-san!
Wait!
Please don't follow me.
It's unpleasant.
We're issuing an announcement that all Exterminators in the district
are prohibited from approaching the Hollow Shadow for their own safety.
We request that those able to set Barriers or Cages
Calling....
Akihito
offer their assistance in guiding the Hollow Shadow out of town.
Is that a type of Barrier?
Hardly! It's nothing that impressive.
It's coming.
If I use my blood, even if it doesn't have a physical body...
Who's there?!
Sakura!
No! Get away from here!
Sakura, at this rate, the Hollow Shadow will—
The demons are filled with malice...
Damn it!
Why are you still alive?
Are you trying to atone?
Sakura!
I won't accept it.
This is...
My blood...
Senpai?
Give it a rest.
You are the one who doesn't get it!
Breaking through the silence
seijaku wo kirisaku you otozureta no wa
We met in an inevitable encounter
hitsuzen toshite no kaikou
For both our sakes
bokura no tame ni
In your mournful eyes
koukai wo nageku me ni
I see a reflection of regrets
utsuru kimi wa sou
Enveloped in sorrow, you've blossomed beautifully
urei wo matotte utsukushiku saita
The flower that fuses into someone's life
dare ka no seimei ni tokeru hana
Hey, do you see it too?
nee kimi ni mo mieru darou
I'm sure you do
kitto
Let's paint over all the mistakes we've made
kasaneta ayamachi nurikaeyou
A new start line will always be there if we want to start over
nando demo ii sa kurikaeshiteiku start line
Let's make our future different from the past
kako to wa chigau asu wo
Our small hope will paint a new start line
futari dake no kibou egaku start line
I never say goodbye
That's how I always am
itsu datte sou sa
Did you think you could defeat the Hollow Shadow without a plan?
Bitter Orange
My plans got skewed!
First you show up when no one asked you to, and now you're complaining?
Man, you're really getting on my nerves!
That's what I should be saying!