Yes, hello?
This is Nase Izumi.
Nase? As in the Nase family?
Yes. I called because there is something I would like to tell you.
Loneliness makes my cheeks wet
kodoku ga hoho wo nurasu nurasu kedo
But when the dawn emerges in silence
yoake no kehai ga shizuka ni michite
And carries me up into the skies
watashi wo sora e maneku yo
Hope awaits on the other side
kibou ga kanata de matteru
So here I go
sou da yo iku yo
I've been wandering, trying to find you
mayoi nagara mo kimi wo sagasu tabi
We missed each other, but our hands touched
surechigau ishiki te ga fureta yo ne
I'll hold your hand tightly
tsukaemaeru yo shikkari
Our mutual longing is
motomeau kokoro
The first step toward our dream
sore wa yume no akashi
We're drawn closer as we begin to accept each other
tagai wo uketomeru tabi ni hikareteku
We won't need to spend our days in sadness anymore
kanashii hibi wa mou iranai
Because we'll have a great time together
tagai wo uketomete ikiru yorokobi ni
That I'm sure the two of us will
kitto kitto futari
Learn to appreciate
mezameru yo
What matters is that I've finally found you
mayoi nagara mo kimi wo mitsuketa yo
GLUCOSE
INTRAVENOUS INFUSION
CALL
White World
Kuriyama-san?
Senpai?
You're awake?
So that's what happened?
Right!
Things got pretty intense after you transformed.
But on the bright side, you didn't hurt anyone.
I see.
I think the Calm has something to do with that.
Your injuries still haven't completely healed.
You know, I was told that you would actually die if I attacked you during the Calm!
I was such a nervous wreck!
Don't go playing with it!
It should heal right up as soon as the Calm passes.
I'm not against trying new things,
but I need to know what they are first.
It's a rice omelette!
A rice omelette?!
Yes. When I asked Mitsuki-senpai what to make, she said that you love rice omelettes.
Where's the egg?
Right here.
Boiled?!
It was that or nothing!
I was down to the very last one!
The last one?
How many did you use?
They're all gone!
Wh-What's that?
It's to celebrate your recovery. Sakura—
Who celebrates with this?!
And you can't just rummage through my fridge just because I'm unconscious!
Or put a pig head in there!
You just focus on getting sleep, Senpai.
I'll run to the store and make you another one.
Why?
"Why?" Well...
What's wrong?
Nothing! It's just...
Are you truly that oblivious?
Sakura?!
When did you get here?
Ever since you fell unconscious,
Mirai has been taking care of you.
She never once left your side.
You still don't get it?
Get what?
Mirai, he may be a lost cause.
What are you trying to say?!
What exactly are you trying to say?!
You should just tell him, plain and simple.
What?! Tell him what?!
What are you two—
It's hot!
Th-That's because it's summer now.
Summer, huh?
Nagatsuki Station
Shindou Photo Studio
Nagatsuki Municipal High School
Literary Club
Good morning, Senpai!
It's pretty cold today, isn't it?
Tow Warning
If you have left your bicycle here,
please move it immediately.
Unattended bicycles will be—
Nagatsuki Station Bicycle Parking Area
Where's Sakura?
She said she was going on ahead.
It's summer vacation, all right.
But when I texted Mitsuki-senpai a minute ago, she said that she was at school.
You brought in more?
Y-You must be imagining things.
Besides, I don't have the money to buy more bonsai stuff.
Oh, I got a text from Sakura.
So this is where you were!
Oh, glasses!
How strange.
I could have sworn I heard Akihito's voice.
Am I hearing things?
This is great!
There is no denying that sunglasses aren't as effective as regular glasses,
but by placing a girl who rarely wears glasses or swimsuits into a situation—
This is one talkative ghost!
Ghost?
Akihito kicked the bucket about two weeks ago.
Looking back, you've gotta feel sorry for the guy.
They say that the more beloved you are, the shorter your life is.
But Akihito didn't fit into that saying at all!
He was hated, scorned, and treated like a nuisance...
all the way to his dying breath.
I'm not dead.
Yup, you're Akihito.
In that case, you'd better make yourself scarce.
Letting you see me in a bikini for free is nothing less than degrading.
I never asked you to put on a swimsuit!
Sheesh...
Akihito.
What now?
Learn from this experience and take a good, hard look at yourself.
I've had all I can take...
of nightmares like that.
Right.
While you're at it, drag that pervert to the clubroom with you.
Hey, pervert.
What is it, pervert?
The snow isn't letting up, is it?
Ow!
Ouch...
Senpai?
Senpai!
Wait!
Please wait, Senpai!
Wait...
Please!
The days keep getting shorter, don't they?
Well, the summer solstice was a while ago.
Wanna read for a bit longer?
I'm fine.
Hiromi and Mitsuki sure are taking their sweet time.
They already went home.
Seriously?!
And here I am, finally back after slipping between life and death.
Don't you think that's exactly why they left?
I bet it feels awkward for them to face you!
What is it?
Uh, it's nothing.
Kuriyama-san, are you free?
See, I was thinking we could go out to eat or something.
Ah, I can cover for you if you're short on cash.
O-Okay.
I mean, I don't know what really happened,
but I'm sure I must have put you through a lot.
I wish you had asked me earlier.
Is that a "No"?
Yes.
This will probably be over once the sun goes down.
What do you mean?
Senpai...
Senpai, why are you always so nice to me?
I feel like the two of us are alike in a few ways.
If I said that, Kuriyama-san, would you get—
You got a problem with that?!
I-I wouldn't say that!
Your disgust is written all over on your face!
D-Did that make you happy?
How would that make me happy?!
Well, Mitsuki-senpai told me that you get immense pleasure
from people stepping all over you.
I'm having a hard time mastering her techniques, though.
You don't need to master that!
Please forget what Mitsuki told you!
No!
I won't forget.
I will not forget.
What's that?
That's you, Senpai.
That's Beyond the Boundary.
It is a collection of people's warped hearts.
It's said that it will destroy the world.
And... it was a demon that resided inside of you.
That was inside of...
I originally came to this town to defeat Beyond the Boundary.
But things didn't go according to plan.
I couldn't bring myself to kill you.
I didn't want to kill you.
That's why...
I was told that if I used the power of my blood during the Calm,
I could force Beyond the Boundary to leave your body.
I desperately wanted to do that.
What happened... to Kuriyama-san?
She vanished.
Th-Then...
Who are you, the Kuriyama-san sitting here in front of me?
Senpai, you still haven't regained consciousness.
This is all part of a dream.
A tiny bit of my blood is still inside of you, causing you have this dream.
But the dream is about to come to an end.
Senpai, you're going to actually wake up soon.
Kuriyama-san...
I thought I could do it since this is a dream.
It really is hard, isn't it?
Farewell.
Just a dream?
Six Months Earlier
Kuriyama Mirai-san?
It is a pleasure to meet you.
I am Nase Izumi.
This is Kuriyama Mirai.
She is the legitimate heir to the cursed blood and an Exterminator.
She's from the clan that is
abhorred by most Exterminators?
Yes.
Kuriyama-san.
She attacks by manipulating her own blood.
She is able to shape and harden her blood.
It is also a potent poison capable of
destroying her opponent's internal organs.
Will that be enough to defeat it?
It is still too soon to say for certain.
However, I believe she stands a good chance.
Isn't her target said to be immortal?
Yes.
It's immortal?
I believe it simply has tremendously fast regenerative capabilities.
"The immortal half-demon."
That is what the local Exterminators call it.
The immortal half-demon?
Here is what it looks like.
Unlike those possessed by a demon,
this dangerous creature is the inconceivable mix of a half-human and a half-demon.
Upon researching it,
I found that its demon half is Beyond the Boundary.
When my younger brother tried to subdue it, the creature retaliated.
His wounds put him on the brink of death.
You are the only person I can turn to.
Please.
That's Beyond the Boundary.
This person must...
Does the Exterminator's Society know about any of this?
It's possible.
I will offer her my full support.
I'm sorry you had to attend that stifling meeting with me back there.
With all the history behind this area,
there are bound to be many customs.
Bonsai?
Yes. Anyway...
Yes?
Where is Beyond the Boundary?
Don't worry.
I'm making sure it's kept under close observation.
In the end, I'm going to have to kill it, right?
If that's the case, I'd like to hurry.
Are you up to it?
How am I supposed to know if I can do it?!
Earlier you said—
No.
I was asking if you are mentally prepared for this.
I heard about what happened with Inami Yui.
My condolences.
After the way the Exterminators persecuted you,
I know I'm asking for a lot.
You don't need to apologize to me.
The half-demon's name is Kanbara Akihito.
It is a second year high school student.
You—
I-I was too much for you.
Uh...
Say...
Do you think you could do something about this?
Pretty please?
Is he really all that dangerous?
Why are you so hung up on me?
Then why don't you quit being an Exterminator?
If I could quit, I would have a long time ago!
But the cursed blood running
through my veins isn't normal!
This power is...
I'm the same way.
Why did you have to say that?
Why?
Five Months Earlier
So as we predicted, his immortality is preventing
you from finishing him off through normal means?
That's correct.
You should watch him for a while.
Attacking at random will get you absolutely nowhere.
But...
Just like when Hiromi faced him,
Beyond the Boundary is sure to overtake the body eventually, even if it is only temporary.
That is when you should strike.
Understood.
Also...
I am saying this as a friendly warning.
You should distance yourself from Akihito-kun.
Oh, right! Kuriyama-san!
Y-Yes?
About what I said yesterday. What do you think?
I'm inviting you to come visit the Literary Club.
Sound good?
You haven't joined any other clubs,
and there aren't all that many Exterminators at our school.
Plus you just got here, so—
I believe I already turned that offer down.
Wait!
Please don't come with me.
Despite what I said...
Why did you follow me, anyway?
Because you're a bespectacled beauty!
...you came after me anyway.
Stab me!
I'm immortal, so...
I was only ever thinking about myself.
"Senpai has friends who are there for him."
So...
That's why I thought you weren't anything like me.
live!
Senpai!
Farewell.
But I didn't know anything about you or your life.
I had no idea how much you had been suffering
or how hard life had been on you.
I have to stop you!
And then, I...
Four Months Earlier
You couldn't kill him?
I believe I told you to distance yourself from Akihito-kun.
The Hollow Shadow's possession had
clearly weakened Beyond the Boundary.
You wasted the perfect opportunity to defeat it.
Are you happy?
If we allow Beyond the Boundary to roam free,
it will use its massive power to destroy the world.
When that happens, there will be no second chances.
Right.
Goodbye.
I've been thinking about it ever since then.
And I realized that being indecisive won't get me anywhere.
I have no choice but to annihilate Senpai—Beyond the Boundary.
But I don't want to kill him!
I do not want to kill him.
Three Months Earlier
The Calm is coming.
The Calm?
I have a plan.
Care to explain?
Very well.
First, I shall place Kanbara Akihito in a frozen barrier
and weaken his human half.
The Calm will have also weakened Beyond the Boundary, which I will draw out.
I will then tell Kuriyama Mirai that if she takes advantage of the Calm,
there is a way to save Kanbara Akihito without killing him.
Kill him.
Considering Kuriyama Mirai's current mental state,
I am certain she will believe me.
However, the Exterminator's Society is bound to come in pursuit of Beyond the Boundary as well.
I swear that we will annihilate it before they do.
Is what you said in the text all true?
Yes. Seeing as it's a demon,
even Beyond the Boundary will be weakened during the Calm.
If you use your body along with all of your blood,
you should be able to remove Beyond the Boundary from the body
without killing Akihito-kun.
However, that means Beyond the
Boundary will violate your entire body.
But Senpai won't have to die that way, right?
You've already made up your mind, haven't you?
I have.
This is where you will find Akihito-kun.
He will awaken sooner or later.
If you truly wish to save Akihito-kun, you had better act quickly.
Kuriyama-san...
Akihito-kun wants you to live.
He wants you to kill him so that you may live.
I'm absolutely sure that's what he would want.
I bet.
Regardless, you're going to rescue Akihito-kun, aren't you?
Yes.
I know that Senpai is going to be angry with me.
When he hears about what I did, he'll say that I didn't understand anything.
Just like he did back then...
Well, he doesn't either!
The snow is starting to pick up.
That must be Beyond the Boundary's core.
Kuriyama-san...
seijaku wo kirisaku you otozureta no wa
Breaking through the silence
hitsuzen toshite no kaikou
We met in an inevitable encounter
bokura no tame ni
For both our sakes
koukai wo nageku me ni
In your mournful eyes
utsuru kimi wa sou
I see a reflection of regrets
urei wo matotte utsukushiku saita
Enveloped in sorrow, you've blossomed beautifully
dare ka no seimei ni tokeru hana
The flower that fuses into someone's life
nee kimi ni mo mieru darou
Hey, do you see it too?
kitto
I'm sure you do
kasaneta ayamachi nurikaeyou
Let's paint over all the mistakes we've made
nando demo ii sa kurikaeshiteiku start line
A new start line will always be there if we want to start over
kako to wa chigau asu wo
Let's make our future different from the past
futari dake no kibou egaku start line
Our small hope will paint a new start line
I never say goodbye
itsu datte sou sa
That's how I always am
Senpai?
I'm glad I was born!
Black World
I'm truly glad that I came to this town and met you!