Give it a rest.
You're the one who doesn't get it!
I-I don't get it?
Don't worry about it! Let's go!
Why did you come? If the Hollow Shadow shows up...
Anemia?
Just hold still!
W-Wait, Senpai!
Who was that back there?
How did you get here? We're pretty deep in.
I'm not sure.
I just jumped in headfirst when I saw you.
That aside—
Let's make a break for it!
Up you go!
Put me down! I can run perfectly fine on my own!
Hey, Senpai!
Loneliness makes my cheeks wet
kodoku ga hoho wo nurasu nurasu kedo
But when the dawn emerges in silence
yoake no kehai ga shizuka ni michite
And carries me up into the skies
watashi wo sora e maneku yo
Hope awaits on the other side
kibou ga kanata de matteru
So here I go
sou da yo iku yo
I've been wandering, trying to find you
mayoi nagara mo kimi wo sagasu tabi
We missed each other, but our hands touched
surechigau ishiki te ga fureta yo ne
I'll hold your hand tightly
tsukaemaeru yo shikkari
Our mutual longing is
motomeau kokoro
The first step toward our dream
sore wa yume no akashi
We're drawn closer as we begin to accept each other
tagai wo uketomeru tabi ni hikareteku
We won't need to spend our days in sadness anymore
kanashii hibi wa mou iranai
Because we'll have a great time together
tagai wo uketomete ikiru yorokobi ni
That I'm sure the two of us will
kitto kitto futari
Learn to appreciate
mezameru yo
What matters is that I've finally found you
mayoi nagara mo kimi wo mitsuketa yo
Bitter Orange
Big Brother, I love you. Big Brother, I love you.
Hello?
Change your ringtone this instant.
How did you know?
It's the sort of thing you'd do.
What do you want?
Do you know where Akihito is?
No. Did you share information with Akkey?
Just a bit...
Without telling me?
I can't let that slide, you know?
I know!
Please, Big Brother!
All right.
Now then...
It looks like it's passed.
I certainly hope it has.
It's making a labyrinth based on our memories?
Right. Ayaka-san warned me about this.
She said that it usually possesses people,
but it can also create labyrinths to trap us.
Okay...
So, where are we headed?
Dunno.
What?
How should I know?
If either of us knew where to go, it would be you.
How am I supposed to know?
You came to fight without a plan?
O-Of course not!
Yup, you didn't have a plan.
That's none of your concern!
Why did you follow me, anyway?
Because you're a bespectacled beauty!
That's unpleasant.
Sakura!
Did you think you could defeat
the Hollow Shadow without a plan?
My plans got skewed!
First you show up when no one asked you to, and now you're complaining?
No one asked me?!
Then you should have kept that story to yourself and come alone!
I never asked you to look into my past or wait for me outside of my apartment, did I?!
Who do you think enticed me into all that?!
Besides, you came after me first, Kuriyama-san!
That's because...
Man, you're really getting on my nerves!
That's what I should be saying!
I'm going to make this perfectly clear!
You said that I've got friends,
but that's the farthest thing from the truth!
But it's obvious that you do!
I'm telling you that I don't!
You're the one who doesn't know anything, Kuriyama-san!
You're so stubborn!
Please don't look!
Kuriyama-san, I'm sorry, but I don't
have the energy to carry you.
Kuriyama-san, take off
your shoes and tights!
I-I was already—
Kuriyama-san, hurry!
I know!
There's the exit!
It's one of the oldest tricks in the book,
but if she falls for it...
Why... did we leave... my tights?
You didn't have anything else handy.
So who the heck was that?
"Sakura!"
Isn't that what you were screaming back there?
That's right.
Inami Sakura.
She's the younger sister of Inami Yui, the girl I murdered.
And she's trying to kill you?
It looks like it.
But unlike Yui, Sakura's powers as an Exterminator should be near nonexistent.
So why...
Wh-What's going on?
The trains...
Yui!
What?
She's gone?
What's that?
Damn it!
Kuriyama-san!
Inami Sakura!
I won't let you interfere.
Cut the revenge crap!
This has nothing to do with you.
Yui...
Don't let it deceive you! That isn't the real Yui-san!
Kuriyama-san, get out of there! Hurry!
Kuriyama-san!
Run! Hurry! Kuriyama-san!
Damn it!
Yui...
Yui is...
Yui is gone!
No...
This is the Hollow Shadow's main body.
We're back.
Kuriyama-san!
Huh? What is it?
Blood?
This is the power of her cursed blood.
Simply touching her blood will erode your flesh, and that will be the death of you.
She's like a reaper.
Do you—
Do I...
look like...
a normal person?
In my eyes,
you are nothing more than
a bespectacled beauty.
What... is that?
The Hollow Shadow!
Wow! It's so pretty!
Ai, you're so excited, you've changed forms.
I'm going out for a quick walk.
Play with this.
Kuriyama-san, hurry...
Hurry and stab me!
It's weak right now, isn't it?
If you chase it out of my body, knowing you...
But, Senpai, you'll...
I won't die. I'm immortal.
I can't hold it in much longer. Hurry!
B-But...!
Isn't this... why you're here?
You're here because... you have do you this, right?
Th-That's right, but...
Then just do it already!
Defeating it won't change anything.
It won't change the blood flowing in your veins or the position your in!
It won't change a damn thing!
But... despite that, you're here!
Follow through with what you set out to do!
Don't surrender to the Hollow Shadow!
If you give up now, everything will have been a waste of time!
Stab me!
I'm immortal, so...
So...
live!
Senpai!
Spray your blood.
Senpai...
Stop.
Get back.
Why? You were up against
the Hollow Shadow.
Didn't think this would happen?
I'm sorry.
I can't guarantee that you'll survive.
I know.
Wh-What are you guys doing?
You've know that Kanbara-kun is a half-demon, haven't you?
When his body is in an extremely perilous state,
his demonic instincts awaken.
Basically, dealing with him is a real headache.
Senpai...
The Cage!
He's negating our supernatural powers.
Ayaka-san!
I know!
I'm doing my best to regenerate the Cage.
If he starts to break it faster than I can regenerate it,
we won't be able to stop him.
If it gets to that point,
I'll eliminate him.
Eliminate?
He'll eliminate the space encompassing
his physical tissues.
It may not be enough to kill him,
but he can't exist that way.
You can't.
You can't!
No!
This won't last much longer! Where is your big sister?
She's probably on her way right now!
No way!
Nino-san!
Don't expect this to do much!
Now!
He's stronger than last time!
I can't hold him! He's gonna break free!
Izumi-neesama?
Isn't this...?
Do I...
look like...
a normal person?
How could you possibly know how I feel?!
You're the one who doesn't know anything, Kuriyama-san!
I'm the same way.
I'm sorry!
Senpai, I didn't know
anything about you,
but...
I have to stop you!
Kuriyama-san?
I... did it again.
Senpai...
Sorry...
I'm sorry!
I see.
No wonder the Society is concerned.
I suppose I'll have to withdraw for now.
Thank you for the food!
King of Chinese Cuisine
You can take your time, you know.
I'm feeling seriously lightheaded! I need to replenish my iron.
And I can't believe that thing wasn't the Hollow Shadow!
To think what I got was only worth a measly 200 yen!
I don't think Ayaka-san would lie to us though.
Then what's going on here?
How am I supposed to know?
Senpai, aren't you going to eat that?
Nope.
Where are you going?
To the restroom.
Hey.
Yes?
Do you think... I look like a normal person?
I think so.
To me, you look like a creepy
upperclassman with a thing for glasses.
How flattering.
seijaku wo kirisaku you otozureta no wa
Breaking through the silence
hitsuzen toshite no kaikou
We met in an inevitable encounter
bokura no tame ni
For both our sakes
koukai wo nageku me ni
In your mournful eyes
utsuru kimi wa sou
I see a reflection of regrets
urei wo matotte utsukushiku saita
Enveloped in sorrow, you've blossomed beautifully
dare ka no seimei ni tokeru hana
The flower that fuses into someone's life
nee kimi ni mo mieru darou
Hey, do you see it too?
kitto
I'm sure you do
kasaneta ayamachi nurikaeyou
Let's paint over all the mistakes we've made
nando demo ii sa kurikaeshiteiku start line
A new start line will always be there if we want to start over
kako to wa chigau asu wo
Let's make our future different from the past
futari dake no kibou egaku start line
Our small hope will paint a new start line
I never say goodbye
itsu datte sou sa
That's how I always am
Is that it?
Yes. I have recovered the Hollow Shadow.
This should stall the Exterminator's Society for the time being.
You have done well.
You are dismissed.
Sir.
Chartreuse Light
Do you miss it every year?
That is none of your concern.
If you stop and think about it, we're all alone.