I apologize for summoning you on such short notice.
To be frank, I'd like to ask you for a favor.
Yes ma'am, how may I be of service?
I'd like to practice on you.
I haven't used this on humans in quite some time.
Wh-What are you...
I'll set you free in just a minute.
Wha—
No!
Help me!
You may rest at ease.
Due to the coming of the Calm,
I believe that the situation will change.
Are you certain of this?
I have a plan.
And I swear on my family's name, I will carry it out.
The Calm is coming.
It is a stagnant time, when everything comes to a halt.
And...
Loneliness makes my cheeks wet
kodoku ga hoho wo nurasu nurasu kedo
But when the dawn emerges in silence
yoake no kehai ga shizuka ni michite
And carries me up into the skies
watashi wo sora e maneku yo
Hope awaits on the other side
kibou ga kanata de matteru
So here I go
sou da yo iku yo
I've been wandering, trying to find you
mayoi nagara mo kimi wo sagasu tabi
We missed each other, but our hands touched
surechigau ishiki te ga fureta yo ne
I'll hold your hand tightly
tsukaemaeru yo shikkari
Our mutual longing is
motomeau kokoro
The first step toward our dream
sore wa yume no akashi
We're drawn closer as we begin to accept each other
tagai wo uketomeru tabi ni hikareteku
We won't need to spend our days in sadness anymore
kanashii hibi wa mou iranai
Because we'll have a great time together
tagai wo uketomete ikiru yorokobi ni
That I'm sure the two of us will
kitto kitto futari
Learn to appreciate
mezameru yo
What matters is that I've finally found you
mayoi nagara mo kimi wo mitsuketa yo
Calming Gold
Come on! Please get up.
You're going to be late.
Sakura!
I don't need to.
Jeez! Get out of bed already!
Now go get dressed!
I only transferred to this school so I'd have more opportunities to attack you, Mirai.
With that reason no longer valid, I see no need to—
Here! Your uniform.
Listen!
We don't have time to talk.
Look at this! Your hair is such a mess!
Mirai, you have no room to talk.
And look down.
How unpleasant.
Good night!
No going back to sleep!
And that's why you're late?
Yes... It was by no means my fault!
If Sakura had gotten out of bed faster—
Ow, ow, ow!
It's surprisingly stubborn.
Please stop trying to force the knot out!
Hey!
Senpai?
Taking a morning nap?
A-Are you all right?
Yeah... Sorry.
What the heck do you think you're doing?!
An accident.
Do you think that those are magic words that can get you out of anything?!
That hurts.
And look.
Senpai?
Oh, I fell right back asleep.
Is something wrong?
Were you up all night?
Well...
To be honest, I spent seven hours debating whether you would look better in green-framed or rimless glasses.
What a way to spent seven hours...
Sparkle!
Whoa! You took me completely by surprise!
The train is here.
Finals are just around the corner.
So it's obvious why we're reviewing this page in class, isn't it?
Sakura! Sakura!
Sakura!
Here I am, going out of my way to help you,
but every now and then some people don't show any appreciation for...
Sakura!
...my goodwill!
Oh, I'll be taking a week off for personal reasons starting tomorrow.
If you have any questions, you'd better ask them today!
Personal reasons? Are you getting married?
Die! Then revive and die a million times!
That's brutal!
You do realize that's verbal abuse, don't you?
Then I'll claim sexual harassment!
Don't think I'll go easy on you just because you're a high schooler!
She's taking it way too seriously.
The Calm is coming.
That's what's happening.
The Calm...
Yup! At long last, the Calm is coming!
But there's, like, something more important right now.
Akkun, I heard that you, like, broke your promise with me and approached the Hollow Shadow.
I'm, like, steaming mad!
I was, like, so upset that I couldn't even eat my sunflower seeds!
It's amazing that she has a new character to play with every postcard she sends.
They're all kind of the same, though.
Quit calmly analyzing her!
And Kuriyama-san, why are you dressed up like that?
I-I was in the middle of work!
I never thought I'd ever have to wear something like this.
Thank goodness I had Sakura head home without me.
How unpleasant.
So unpleasant!
So Akkun, when did you, like, turn into such a little delinquent?
When I borrowed a dirty magazine from a friend, you went behind my back
and tore out the page that had a nude model wearing glasses.
It became your treasure!
Where has my pure-hearted, darling Akkun gone?
I'm, like, devastated.
She isn't making the right sound!
It's the small things like this that show her age.
Like I said, quit calmly analyzing her!
I-I'm gonna run out of time if I keep this up!
Now, to get to the heart of this letter.
The Calm is coming!
The Calm is, like, coming!
The Calm is, like, totally coming!
Where do you draw the line between "genius" and "insane"?
Please! Not another word!
Be sure to be, like, extra careful!
Promise Yacchan you'll, like, be careful, Akkun!
That's all you had to say?!
In short, the Calm refers to a period during which our demon powers are weakened.
Your powers are weakened?
Yup! I don't know the details, but according to the records,
our innate vitality apparently drops dramatically.
As such, Exterminators are able to defeat demons
that are normally out of their league, so they're thrilled.
But in that case, why do I need to be careful?
Have you forgotten?
Kanbara-kun, you are a half-demon.
If your demon powers weaken, what do you think would happen to you?
What would happen?
Half-demons are too rare for me to know for certain,
but your immortality is one trait that you could temporarily lose.
I see.
And if an Exterminator found him in that vulnerable state,
there is a chance Akkey would be attacked.
Exactly. Isn't that why you escorted him here?
To be precise, she said that the Calm does not start until midnight.
Perhaps it's just me, but I think the air feels somewhat heavy.
I wouldn't say it's heavy. It feels very still.
The Calm...
What an appropriate name.
At times like this, I think my little sister and I...
should walk home side by side.
But she's already gone.
Why?!
Because she doesn't want to walk home with you.
Why not?!
Because she hates you.
Why?!
Because you're always acting like that!
Senpai, I'm going to miss the sale on frozen dinners if I don't hurry, so I've gotta run!
Oh, okay. Later!
Akkey!
Don't take this lightly.
I can feel it in my chest.
Falling in love?
Would you like a lift?
I'll drop you off.
The Calm, huh?
What do you want?
Well, I figured we could have a
talk while going out for a drive.
I want to tell you about what you saw.
Is that a demon?
Right. Just like the Hollow Shadow,
many of the more powerful demons lack a physical body.
It's said that it takes years for these demons to come into physical being.
Supposedly, they are born from the resentment and twisted hearts of countless people
fusing together before eventually taking form.
If left alone, they could lead the world to ruin.
It is said that these demons are the origin of disease, natural disasters, and war.
They are collectively referred to as "Beyond the Boundary".
Beyond the...
However, we're fortunate that only a fragment of this one has shown up.
It hasn't started to spread its influence yet.
Why are you telling me all of this?
The Exterminator's Society has been keeping their eye on it for ages.
I was made to believe that the tight-lipped Nase family has more information on it.
I thought I would be able to get you to talk,
but it looks like the baby of the
family has been kept in the dark.
Yakiimo.
But it's true!
Keep going.
What is the plan for subduing the demon you refer to as "Beyond the Boundary"?
Is the Nase family going to annihilate it in secret?
I couldn't get any info on that, either!
Your sister is way too scary!
But...
"But"?
Do you wanna know?
Yakiimo!
Oh, I'm sorry!
I found some intriguing information regarding Kuriyama Mirai.
About Kuriyama-san?
While I was digging around,
I found that the Inami family tried to kill Kuriyama Mirai
for murdering their daughter, Yui.
Apparently, the one who stopped them...
was Nase Izumi.
Do you think that is somehow linked to this "Beyond the Boundary"?
I can't say.
But wouldn't you find it fascinating if it was?
Big Bro!
What a hassle.
The way you followed your little sister all of the way out here...
It sure looks like you've got a sister complex.
That hurt.
I don't just look like I do!
What are you after?
You should go ask your little sister!
Big Brother!
Thank you for that delicious little outburst.
Wh-What's going on?!
Akihito-kun, you were hit by a car, so why...
Where did your injuries go?!
Oh, this—
Don't kill me!
Please! Don't kill me!
Wh-What makes you think I would do that?
I-Izumi-san?
You must be exhausted.
What are you doing here?
Rest for just a little longer.
Thank you for riding with us.
Hananodera. This is Hananodera.
Please make sure to take all of your belongings.
It's only natural to assume that the
Calm had something to do with this.
However, I get the feeling that his human half has been greatly weakened along with his demon half.
Is there anything we can do to help him get better?
There are ways to help humans
and ways to help demons to some extent,
but Kanbara-kun is a half-demon.
To be perfectly honest, half-demons are so rare,
I don't really know what would help them recover.
Senpai...
At any rate, he's suffering from a
fever, so I brought some cool water.
I can take care of that!
You two should head home for now.
But...
For the duration of the Calm, we can't go out in the open anyway.
Sitting and watching Kanbara-kun sleep won't help him get better, now will it?
That may be true, but...
Don't you have school tomorrow as well?
When did Kanbara-senpai and Mirai meet?
I'm not sure. I don't know the details,
but I think they met shortly after Mirai-chan moved here.
It's almost time.
Ai, make sure to stay on your guard.
Yeah.
I planted the seeds.
I suspect that they should be ripe by now.
This is what I've been chasing
after since everything started.
I know. I won't let the Nase family claim it.
Full
It's...
...showtime!
I never expected that to make so many pop out!
Here I go!
You stole my prey!
I had my eye on that one!
I screwed up!
You may have it.
You're here, too?!
That's Nase Izumi!
What a beast!
Do your best to stay out of her way.
In this area, the Nase family's authority is absolute.
In an attempt to create internal rifts,
enemy powers have tried to stir up trouble more than once.
Then you're saying everything
Fujima Miroku told me is a lie?
Shindou Photo Studio
That's not what I said.
However, I cannot deny that is a distinct possibility.
Izumi once warned me to be wary of the Exterminator's Society.
I suspect that the organization isn't on good terms with the Nase family.
And you didn't say anything when Kuriyama-san was gossiping about the Society a while back!
I can't just tell everyone about that!
Besides, I haven't been told the full story myself.
I'm going to see Izumi-neesan!
She's going to play dumb, and that will be the end of it.
Do something! She's your older sister, isn't she?
I could say the exact same thing to you.
It's from Kuriyama-san.
How about you, Big Bro?
Akkey is...
A demon?!
One item for 280 yen,
Message Sent
one for 350 yen, and another for 10 yen.
Thank You Very Much
Yen
Your total comes out to 1,870 yen.
That much?!
Thank you very much.
I was lost in thought and wasn't paying attention.
It's fine. More importantly, about Kanbara-senpai...
If you ask again,
I'm sure they'll let you stay with him.
But it's not like I could really do anything for him.
Even so, you want to stay by his side.
You're being unpleasant!
You don't mean it when you call someone unpleasant like that.
That's what my sister told me a long time ago.
You're being unpleasant!
This time you truly meant it.
How could you tell?
No one would stop you.
Not if you want to be with Kanbara-senpai.
I-I don't really want to be with him or anything like that.
It's just, I...
Kanbara-senpai loves glasses.
It doesn't have anything to do with that!
It's just...
He's normal around me.
Even though I'm from a cursed clan...
Even though I possess such abnormal powers...
He treats me like a normal person.
And always he has...
It must make you happy...
that you two met.
You're being unpleasant!
You didn't mean it that time, either.
All trains are out of service today.
Aya-chan...
Ai, go inside.
How may I help a member of the Exterminator's Society?
I never thought you'd find me.
I guess I should've expected it from a demon that can stand amongst Exterminators.
You don't intend to subdue me, do you?
Of course not!
I simply came to check on the situation here.
But now that it's come to this,
I don't have a choice!
I am taking custody of Kanbara Akihito.
Please hand him over without any trouble.
I'd like to hear your reason why first.
You see, I promised to look after Kanbara-kun.
I don't have time to explain myself.
Besides, I doubt you'd believe me even if I did.
Did you truly believe I'd hand him over after hearing that?
My, my.
She's much stronger than I had anticipated.
Honestly, I'm glad we're in the middle of the Calm.
Where do you think you're going?
Even during the Calm, you're this powerful?
Impressive!
But how about this?
You're here early.
Do you prefer girls who keep you waiting?
Aya-chan...
Senpai!
seijaku wo kirisaku you otozureta no wa
Breaking through the silence
hitsuzen toshite no kaikou
We met in an inevitable encounter
bokura no tame ni
For both our sakes
koukai wo nageku me ni
In your mournful eyes
utsuru kimi wa sou
I see a reflection of regrets
urei wo matotte utsukushiku saita
Enveloped in sorrow, you've blossomed beautifully
dare ka no seimei ni tokeru hana
The flower that fuses into someone's life
nee kimi ni mo mieru darou
Hey, do you see it too?
kitto
I'm sure you do
kasaneta ayamachi nurikaeyou
Let's paint over all the mistakes we've made
nando demo ii sa kurikaeshiteiku start line
A new start line will always be there if we want to start over
kako to wa chigau asu wo
Let's make our future different from the past
futari dake no kibou egaku start line
Our small hope will paint a new start line
I never say goodbye
itsu datte sou sa
That's how I always am
I wish I never met him.
Where are you right now?
Silver Bamboo
I'm in front of Senpai.
Kill him.
I think that maybe, just maybe, I really am cursed.