This is Kuriyama Mirai-san.
Chartreuse Light
When I told her about our club,
she said she wanted to check it out, so I brought her over.
Huh? D-Did I? Wait, no I didn't!
Literary Club
Constantly Reading
Quasi-meeting Reading
You pressured me into coming!
Now, now.
Anyway, she's not here yet,
but our president is Nase Mitsuki.
You met her the other day. Remember?
This is third-year student and the prince of ditching, Nase Hiromi.
There are two other nobles of ditching who didn't grace us with their presence today.
I see.
So, welcome to the club!
You're being unpleasant.
Please! We're in desperate need of new members!
That doesn't mean I have to...
H-How.. How did you get this?!
Gardening Encyclopedia
Our advisor, an upperclassman, donated all of the books on that bookshelf.
As such, we cannot lend them out.
However, Literary Club members may—
I'll join!
That was fast!
You're acting like an autumn maiden who has fallen in love!
And I'm just wondering, but are you interested in gardening?
Um, a little bit.
Mitsuki sure is taking her sweet time.
I know! I can't wait.
It's that time already?
Loneliness makes my cheeks wet
kodoku ga hoho wo nurasu nurasu kedo
But when the dawn emerges in silence
yoake no kehai ga shizuka ni michite
And carries me up into the skies
watashi wo sora e maneku yo
Hope awaits on the other side
kibou ga kanata de matteru
So here I go
sou da yo iku yo
I've been wandering, trying to find you
mayoi nagara mo kimi wo sagasu tabi
We missed each other, but our hands touched
surechigau ishiki te ga fureta yo ne
I'll hold your hand tightly
tsukaemaeru yo shikkari
Our mutual longing is
motomeau kokoro
The first step toward our dream
sore wa yume no akashi
We're drawn closer as we begin to accept each other
tagai wo uketomeru tabi ni hikareteku
We won't need to spend our days in sadness anymore
kanashii hibi wa mou iranai
Because we'll have a great time together
tagai wo uketomete ikiru yorokobi ni
That I'm sure the two of us will
kitto kitto futari
Learn to appreciate
mezameru yo
What matters is that I've finally found you
mayoi nagara mo kimi wo mitsuketa yo
This is the Literary Club's quarterly magazine?
Shibahime?
Yeah.
The next one will be a commemorative issue, a compilation of our best pieces.
We're having a hard time deciding what will be included.
Is that so?
I'll admit, red does look good on her.
The frames, I mean.
So you can see the beauty if you try!
As of today, you're a fellow glasses enthusiast!
She possesses "little sister" characteristics as well, just like you said.
Doesn't she?
Soft and fluffy hair...
An innocent face...
A bosom that hasn't fully matured...
Thighs that have yet to be tainted...
A petite and delicate frame!
She is truly the ideal little sister!
A-A little sister?
To top it off, she looks stunning in glasses!
And these aren't decorative
glasses that are just for show.
That perfect nose of hers practically screams, "Place glasses here!"
You're being unpleasant!
You shouldn't let those two bother you.
Perverts will be perverts.
Mitsuki, why couldn't you come straight to our precious club meeting?
Big Bro, you're the last person I want to hear that from.
E-Excuse me!
I've decided to join your club.
I look forward to working with you!
Okay.
D-Did I do something wrong?
Not really.
Glad to have you.
Thanks!
Thank you for having me!
Oh, yeah. Kuriyama-san.
Yes?
We need to take care of something important. Are you free after this?
Kuriyama-san, Is this your first time visiting Hiromi's house?
Yeah.
Everyone around these parts has heard of the Nase family.
They've always owned a ton of land.
They also manage this area's Exterminators.
It'd be wise to stay out of their way.
I can hear you.
Am I wrong?
Perfect timing!
You're Nase Hiromi-san and Mitsuki-san, right?
And you are?
I'm Miroku Fujima from the Exterminator's Society.
It's nice to meet you!
I was staying here while I observed the Hollow Shadow.
You caught me on my way out.
Exterminator's Society?
I wanted to say goodbye to Izumi-san, but I'm running short on time.
Please give her my regards. Bye!
I've never seen someone from the Society before.
Until now, I had only heard rumors about them.
Like what?
Anyone who tries to dig up information on the Society's leaders... gets killed!
Those are urban legends.
In reality, they primarily manage identification for Exterminators.
They also single-handedly gather and compile data on Exterminators,
which is obviously kept confidential.
You can think of their office as a city hall for Exterminators.
Is that so?
Well, I shall be keeping this.
No way!
We broke the rules and went after the Hollow Shadow.
Don't hold it against her.
You should be grateful that she's only confiscating it for a month.
A whole flipping month! How will I pay my rent?
And eat?!
I-I could help you out a bit.
Is she in that dire of financial straits?
Yes. She's poor.
She always has a monstrous appetite as well.
You're being unpleasant!
I eat so much because my powers use my blood.
Indeed, they do.
So please be careful.
You do belong to a clan from a cursed bloodline.
Izumi-san?
I have something to say to you as well, Akihito-kun.
I cannot believe you intentionally went after the Hollow Shadow.
I was under the impression that you had a better understanding of yourself.
That is all I wanted to say.
Kuriyama-san, I would like to discuss your future, so please stick around for a bit.
Goodbye.
Don't let it get you down!
If Izumi-san felt like it, she could have exiled you.
But she didn't, so you can take it easy for now.
Isn't that right, Hiromi?
Well, I guess you could look at it that way.
Come on man, just back me up!
Mitsuki!
Huh?
Are you working part-time again this year?
Huh? W-Well, I haven't thought about it yet.
Could you introduce Kuriyama-san to your boss?
Surely you understand. She might starve if you don't!
Sure, I don't mind.
It's a simple job as a shop assistant. Anyone can do it.
Really?
But I get offers for one other job as well.
I always turn it down, but you could rake in the cash if you take it.
What is it?
Have them tell you about it when we get there.
Okay.
Welcome!
Um, is there anything else?
That's all I had to say.
Th-That's it?
Thank you for waiting.
Uh, what's...
This is Yakiimo.
He's a demon, so normal people can't see him.
Want some?
No, I didn't mean to stare!
Well?
I'll take a bite.
It's so good!
Is something the matter?
Not really.
I was just thinking about how much you've changed.
How so?
Remember how you insisted that you didn't
want to interact with others or join any clubs?
Right. I did feel that way, but...
Some time ago, I had decided that I can't interact with others,
and that I had no choice but to be alone, but...
I wouldn't be so hasty.
It isn't wise to suddenly convince yourself that you aren't alone.
Akihito is a half-demon and nearly killed my brother.
That may be true, but...
Everyone knows precisely how dangerous Akihito can be,
so the Nase family observes and handles him as we see fit.
I've told you before. I'm only keeping an eye on him.
I believe I understand, but...
Regardless, it's so much better than what I've known.
I'm sorry.
I said too much.
What's that?
He's possessed by a demon.
What should we do?
Won't it consume that man if we leave him be?
Excuse me!
Uh...
Ex-Excuse me!
It's out!
Wait a second!
What's this?
Thank you.
I see you don't hesitate anymore.
Nothing will change if I'm always lost and floundering.
Crap! You defeated it?
I rushed over when I saw the Cage.
Nino-san...
I've had my eye on that demon for quite some time.
You can have it.
My license is currently suspended anyway,
so I couldn't do anything with it even if I kept it.
Really? But that demon is worth at least fifty thousand yen.
F-Fifty... Fifty thousand yen?!
I just can't catch a break! All I can do is whine on my blog!
That's why you're such an easy target for flamers.
I'd feel bad if I didn't give you something in return, so...
Cheers!
If you want a meal for adults, you gotta have grilled meat!
Don't hold back! Go on, dig in!
Waiter, gimme another beer!
Sure thing!
Mitsuki-senpai, please look!
At your drool?
That's not what I meant! Behold the meat! The meat!
There's so much!
Look! See?
Yeah.
That's all you have to say?!
Man, this is the life!
September Lantern Festival
This is one of those moments that make you happy to be alive, isn't it?
What's that?
September Lantern Festival
What?
Oh, I guess Kuriyama-san hasn't heard about it yet.
It's a local festival that's held every year.
But it's pretty much a couples-only thing.
Single people probably wouldn't have much fun there.
Mitsuki-senpai, have you ever gone?
No. I'm part of the Nase family.
I see...
But doesn't it look nice?
Thanks for waiting!
You took too long! Gimme another on the house!
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
Sorry for the inconvenience.
We are working to repair
damages.
Safety
First
What? Mitsuki-chan, you can't come?
No, I'm sorry.
Mitsuki.
Izumi-neesama!
Remember this well:
As long as someone is an Exterminator, they will always be alone.
I understand!
Ueyama!
Here!
Obayashi!
Kanbara!
Kanbara Akihito!
This is where you work?!
I couldn't possibly appraise demons!
If someone comes, all you need to do is hold on to the demon they bring in.
Everyone had to take off because of the Hollow Shadow fiasco,
so there shouldn't be that many people bringing in demons anyway.
That's right!
Aya-chan!
Where's my obi?
Wasn't it in your dresser's second drawer?
Oh, right! I moved it there the other day.
Hello!
Kuriyama-san said that she would like to start working here.
Oh, really? Including the other job?
What other job?
Oh, I haven't brought that one up—
Please accept! You're perfect for the job!
How unpleasant!
Okay, now smile!
I can't! Why am I stuck doing this?!
Shouldn't you be grateful?
You're getting paid to stand there.
Kuriyama-san, we've had our eyes on you for a while.
We were hoping you'd model for us.
M-Me?
Why me?
Lately, one of our regulars has been willing to pay a fortune for photos of pretty girls in glasses.
So we've been looking for someone who'd look good in glasses.
By the way, we can't disclose personal information such as that customer's name.
But his initials are A. K.
Akihito Kanbara...
Just what I'd expect from an Exterminator.
That has nothing to do with it!
It would have been obvious to anyone!
Next, lift up your dress and
slant your glasses to one side.
What a seductive pose!
Why...
Suck it up! At least they aren't asking you to do any nudes.
However, if you are willing to go that route,
this is the minimum we'd be looking at for your modeling fees.
Gulp!
You said that out loud.
Aya-chan takes the nudes for her personal collection,
so you don't have to worry about them getting passed around.
They're fun to look back on, too.
Here!
Shindou Photo Studio
What's in here?
The nudes Aya-chan took of me!
Shindou Photo Studio
Of you?
Yup!
A cat?
See? Isn't that a great shot of me?
Ai is able to take on that form.
Any in your human form?
Yep. They're under that.
Hiya!
What do you think?
You're hiding...
Hiding?
huge melons?!
How unpleasant!
You're all set.
I'll go get my purse!
Pick out a small one!
Okay!
So, is Kanbara-kun holding up all right?
He's skipping school.
He must have caught a cold or something.
I hope that's all it is.
Despite how Kanbara-kun acts, it really eats away at him.
He always gets really moody after he transforms into a demon and loses control of himself.
He was just like this after that incident with Hiromi, remember?
Well, could you handle things until we get back?
Shindou Photo Studio
Certainly!
Are you sure about this?
Shindou Photo Studio
We could just close up for the day and go together.
You're always so stubborn when it comes to this.
I doubt anyone would mind if you went.
Are you going to the festival together?
You're always so flashy!
Ma'am, are you attending the festival?
I nabbed myself a guy!
I'm on my way to met up with him.
I can still catch a guy or two when I put my mind to it.
Later!
Well, shall we get going?
Yeah!
Do you miss it every year?
Isn't that what Ayaka-san said?
That you firmly refuse to go every year.
Not really. That is none of your concern.
Could you tell me why you won't go?
Why should I?
Because...
Akihito isn't any different.
He didn't tell us why he was missing school.
When you get down to it, we're all alone.
I'm going to lock up.
Senpai, look!
We can have our own festival and...
Mitsuki-senpai, look at them all! Isn't this amazing?
Why are you so excited?
Why not? This is a festival!
Aren't they pretty?
Aren't you glad you decided to cave in and come?
You little brat!
Ah, you just called me a brat.
Huh?
Stop it! Why the hell do I have to come dressed up like this?!
Senpai?
Kuriyama-san? Mitsuki? Why are you here?
Why? I came to cheer up the guy who spends his days eating in a bathroom stall.
I keep telling you. I don't need anyone to—
Senpai...
It's because we're all alone.
We're all... alone.
Look at that!
Sorry.
Couldn't make it after all.
Hey, Big Bro.
I want a candy apple.
seijaku wo kirisaku you otozureta no wa
Breaking through the silence
hitsuzen toshite no kaikou
We met in an inevitable encounter
bokura no tame ni
For both our sakes
koukai wo nageku me ni
In your mournful eyes
utsuru kimi wa sou
I see a reflection of regrets
urei wo matotte utsukushiku saita
Enveloped in sorrow, you've blossomed beautifully
dare ka no seimei ni tokeru hana
The flower that fuses into someone's life
nee kimi ni mo mieru darou
Hey, do you see it too?
kitto
I'm sure you do
kasaneta ayamachi nurikaeyou
Let's paint over all the mistakes we've made
nando demo ii sa kurikaeshiteiku start line
A new start line will always be there if we want to start over
kako to wa chigau asu wo
Let's make our future different from the past
futari dake no kibou egaku start line
Our small hope will paint a new start line
I never say goodbye
itsu datte sou sa
That's how I always am
Izumi-san?
A fruit-type demon...
That's inviolable territory that mankind must never sully!
Shocking Pink
Why the hell are you empty?!
Taking it out on the shampoo won't get you anywhere.