You're my dad?
Let go of me, Chief!
I promised myself that I'd give him a good punch!
My name's Ivica.
Your wife, Eureka, saved my life once.
How would you describe the state she's currently in?
Are you familiar with the anthropic principle?
The sci-fi idea that reality changes based on who the observer is?
The Scub Coral is an intelligent unit.
To escape the Limit of Questions, they found a means to travel between universes.
That's what you call the Quartz.
Different universes?
You mean, not the future, but an entirely different universe?
As a Coralian, Eureka must've turned herself into Quartz,
and took the dangerous Quartz with her to somewhere else.
She must've only desired to be
transported to a different time and place.
That's why she couldn't arrive or
materialize at a particular destination.
Can't you do something? Isn't that what you're here for?
You came here to save Mom, right?
You destroyed the Scub for that, didn't you?
It's been reported that the Quartz Gun's power could alter the course of events.
But...
As you can see,
the Quartz Gun is a large collection of Quartz that has taken the form of a weapon.
Yeah, it can change time and the world.
There should be one more shot left in it.
You've been looking for it, haven't you?
So Eureka gave birth to Ao on this island?
Thank you very much.
It's been ten years since Mom disappeared.
What were you doing this entire time?
Ten years? Oh, right!
You've grown so much.
For me, it was just a short while ago that she left.
A short while ago?
Mr. Thurston, what does that—
Ao!
Do you like soccer?
That man who just appeared might be another threat.
We should strengthen our surveillance.
He's Ao's father and Eureka's husband.
Eureka and the Gekko arrived here before, right?
That's how we discovered that the Scub that came to this universe went back in time.
It traveled from the distant future of this Earth to countless pasts.
The Quartz opened the door to parallel worlds.
This world considered that as a danger, and as a result, Secrets emerged naturally.
In order to survive, the Scub desired to go somewhere without Secrets:
the past of this planet.
However, the Secrets chased them through the holes in time that the Scub opened.
Thus came the history of Scub Bursts.
In the future, mankind became extinct due to Scub Bursts.
Hence, the Secrets considered us enemies as well and attacked us.
Don't let your guard down, Eureka!
Renton?
You should go to another time through the Scub's pillar of light!
Somewhere with less trapar.
What are you going to do, Renton?
I'll destroy all the Scub here. Otherwise...
I'm coming with you!
I don't want to make you destroy Scub!
Go!
Renton... Renton!
Renton! Renton! Renton! Renton! Renton!
RENTON!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
In the distant past, Eureka gave birth to you and tried to protect you.
Renton... I mean, Dad...
Why are you trying so hard to destroy the Scub?
It's our responsibility as adults.
Responsibility as adults?
There was a time when we fought to protect the Scub Coral.
I see... Naru said Mom's the same as the Scub.
But then why?
It's because we protected it that this
universe has to suffer from Scub Bursts.
That's why!
Ao!
Mr. Thurston!
I'm going back!
Back to ten thousand years in the future!
Wait! Hey!
Why? Are you going to abandon Mom?!
Gramps?
Let's go, Nirvash!
Let's end all of this!
Gramps, I must go after all.
What?
Because I still think Dad's wrong.
Ao...
You can fly well.
I'm sorry, Ao.
Don't apologize.
Adults shouldn't do stuff that they'd have to apologize to kids for!
I'll use the Gun.
I'll shoot the first Scub Coral in this universe with it.
The Scub Coral will then be erased from all past and future.
Ao, I want to return this universe to its correct form!
You can only fire it once!
What about Mom then?!
Eureka's prepared for it as well.
God dammit! I can't lose them!
Are you ready, Ao?
We're fighting back!
That movement...
No way! The Neo should have no Archetype!
Good, Ao! Follow him!
Why the hell am I hearing Truth's voice?!
What are you talking about? I've been with you this entire time.
We Archetypes wish to help LFO pilots that need us.
I'm awaiting your orders, Ao.
An Archetype... I see.
Truth was once a Secret, but in this world changed by the Quartz Gun, he exists as an Archetype.
Truth, is this the one and only truth? Or the truth you desired?
What are you mumbling about, Ao?
He's coming.
Why?! Why's there an Archetype in that machine?
Ao, get out of it!
One Nirvash with an Archetype is enough!
The original's enough!
What the hell? Says who?!
Shit!
The Quartz Gun!
This is bad!
Don't interfere, Ao!
Gramps told me...
What?!
about my sister!
You asked before if you had a sister.
Why are you bringing that up now?
Eureka told me about her.
She turned into stone right after she was born and passed away.
In a high trapar density environment, the different types of cells in a child of a human and a Coralian reject each other.
Just like how corals die, the child turns into rock.
That's why you chose this world... this
Earth that Mom discovered by accident.
You wanted to raise your second child in a traparless world.
But there's Scub Coral here too, so you tried to erase it.
Thank you, Dad...
You went so far to keep me alive...
Thank you...
Fleur!
But you can't do this!
I have a dear friend... A dear friend who's also a Coral Carrier!
She lives in symbiosis with the Scub!
If the Scub gets erased from this world, what is going to happen to all of them?
Tell me!
If they've merged with the Scub, they might disappear along with it.
But Ao!
Erasing something that's wrong doesn't make it right!
A man called Blanc told me to look for what's right.
I thought he meant the right enemies that aren't Secrets.
I was wrong.
Looking for an enemy means we still have to fight in the end!
Ao, listen to me!
You can't live on this planet with the way your body—
I grew up on this planet!
Even though a child's life is young, it's still life!
I don't want to negate that.
I don't want to fake it just because it's more convenient to do so!
Ao!
The Okinawan pole light...
Dad arrived from there.
Ao, what do you think you're doing?!
Ao!
Don't tell me he wants to enter the pole light!
You want to go save your mom, right?
But why?! You said we're family!
You still want your real family then?!
Ao, so you were lying to us?!
No, Fleur.
I'll bring an end to all of this.
I'll save Mom, then...
Then?
Then...
You're stupid!
You don't have to shoulder this alone!
You're so stupid!
Ao, you're so stupid!
The emotions of intelligent creatures make the Quartz resonate.
I see.
Quartz!
Take me to the burst ten years ago! Take me to where my Mom is!
It won't do. I have to take them away.
Ao, I'm so sorry!
Ao...
Ao! Is that you?
How do you know it's me?
At this point in time, I should be only two years old...
Stupid, you told me!
When I accidentally arrived here in the Gekko,
you showed up in your Nirvash and helped me return.
I was piloting that Nirvash?!
You came for me, Renton!
Mom...
Ao?
What's going on? You were over there just then!
And why "Mom"?
Because you're my mother.
I'm your son.
Thank you. And goodbye.
I'm back...
Thank you, Ao!
I then understood that I'll be giving birth to you someday.
A boy named Ao.
That's why Dad knew my name?
Why didn't you tell me?
Even if I did, you wouldn't have believed me.
And you were pregnant with my sister.
You know that as well?
Renton!
Go with Dad, Mom.
I can't just leave the Quartz here!
It must've been hard for you.
You had to fight and kill the Scub, your own kin.
All for me!
No!
Someone once told me that I was selfish to have fallen in love with Renton and have a child.
That's why we must take responsibility...
Something or someone must be sacrificed for that.
Break free from that curse already!
I guess that's the reason why I was born.
Ao...
If it's for you, I don't care how much hardship I must endure.
Renton, don't cry in front of Ao!
Thank you, Dad, Mom...
I... We'll somehow manage in this world.
That's why at the very least I want to send you back...
to your homeland.
No one knows how long my body will last.
But I'll believe in the future my parents chose...
The future that we, the people of this time and this planet, chose and worked for!
You're kidding me, right?
That's so embarrassing.
So these are my parents?
But I'm so glad both of you made it back home.
Episode Twenty Four
Gates of Summer
Truth, where are we this time around?
I don't know. I'm investigating right now.
Thanks.
There we go. It's year 2027.
Year 2027.
We're back then?
Back? What are you talking about?
You changed the world three times with the Quartz Gun.
Sign: Japanese Ministry of Foreign Affairs,
Vice-Minister Nakamura Yasumochi
This isn't the world you know anymore.
Sign: Okinawan Allience State Department
Vice-Minister Kinjou Jirou
Fukai Ao may not even
exist in this world.
If that's the case, no one will remember you.
You saved your mother, then said goodbye to her forever,
and wandered in time for a long while,
so that might not be a big deal for you.
That's fine.
She had to live in a place she didn't know,
gave birth to me all alone,
and had to endure solitude just to keep me alive.
Compared to what she had to go through, this much is nothing.
What are you gonna do, Truth?
Looks like it's not over for me yet in this world.
I see. You're leaving?
Yes. Goodbye.
One day, we'll meet again somewhere.
Thanks for watching!