Kokoro
masshiro PAGE mekuru
I walk through the white pages of my storybook
Incoming Text
tobidasu irodoru hajikeru
just waiting to be painted
mangekyou no fuukei
with a kaleidoscope of my experiences.
From
Me
To
You
kizukeba STORY wa mada
This story has only
gikochinaku hajimatta bakkari
just barely begun
shinkokyuu wo mou ikkai
I take a deep breath
tabi suru kaze tsutsumikomu you ni senaka wo osu
and the wind wraps around me and urges me forward
aa yawarakakute atatakai kimi no te
Your hand is so warm held within mine;
nigiri shimete sono kokoro no oku made todoku you ni
it reaches all the way to my heart.
hohoenmi de kureta nara nigirikaeshite kuretara
I can't see a brighter future
boku wa tada mae wo miteru
than you smiling and taking my hand as well
Thank goodness you knew where Kazehaya was.
Yeah, we were just talking earlier.
About what?
Secret.
What? Tell me!
I think she's still being misunderstood,
and that she's keeping more things to herself than she says out loud.
But she's trying her best, and I love that about her.
I don't want to give up either.
I like her.
I want my feelings to reach him.
Please...
Please,
Confession
reach him!
Ryu?
Kuronuma.
I can't stop shaking…
It's time to tell him how I...
...feel.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I made you cry.
I'm sorry I put you through so much trouble.
I'm sorry for saying whatever I wanted.
If you have a response to what I said though, please tell me.
I want to know, no matter what it is.
My feelings for you won't change.
Okay…
But your like is different from mine.
If you're looking for Yoshida and Yano, they're probably outside.
No! I came to find you!
I came because I wanted to talk to you.
Not them…
Is that okay?
Is this okay?
It's okay just like this, so please listen.
'kay.
Kazehaya…
No matter what I did, people have always apologized to me.
That's why I was so happy when we first met and you smiled and thanked me instead.
I've never treated you the same as everyone else.
But, even so, I was still happy.
It was as if everything suddenly had color to it.
You changed my world.
Every second of every day was different because of you.
But even though it meant so much to me,
I did the exact opposite of what you did.
So this time, instead of apologizing to you, I want to say…
Thank you for your smiles.
Thank you for talking to me.
Thank you for your kindness.
Thank you for telling me your hidden feelings.
I…
Kuronuma—
I like you!
I like you.
It's so hard to put all of these feelings into words…
I don't know how to say them.
I just… Like you.
I like you.
No!
Don't open it!
I'm—
I don't want you to see me right now!
I wonder if Sawako was able to tell him.
I suppose we should let them be and go home.
Kazehaya!
Hey, Kazehaya!
If you're here, raise your hand!
Will this really be okay?!
It should be fine. Ryu's still here.
Ryu! Have you see Kazehaya?
Where is he?
Hehe...
Have you seen him?
Really?
Ryu doesn't really lie though.
It's Joe he's talking to.
Should be fine!
Do you guys know where Kuronuma is?
N-No!
What? You guys are no help.
What do you want with her? We'll take a message for you.
I can't tell you guys.
I've thought of something really good.
So good!
Definitely something bad!
Guess I'll go check around the classroom.
Oh right, she went home already!
Yeah, she went home!
Then why didn't you just say that earlier?
We forgot!
We just remembered!
Sawako went home already!
Yeah!
Oh right, the classroom…
K-Kuronuma.
I-I-I!
Wait! Don't turn away.
Look at me.
I feel like I've never had the chance to look at you face-to-face like this before.
Oh there you are, Kazehaya!
Huh? And Sadako?
Pin was looking for you.
Seemed important.
What were you guys doing?
What were we doing?
Seriously, I—
Kuro—!
Th-The teacher's looking for me!
What was I doing?!
Kuronuma!
Kazehaya! What were you doing? I looked all over for you!
What do you mean "what"?
Man…
What?
That was important!
Well, whatever.
About our snacks for later,
what do you think of having maybe seven salty and three sweet? Or maybe eight—
I don't care!
What?
What?!
You failed?!
Girls, if you're going to make a mistake, do it on the boys' costumes!
Got it!
We'll do it on Joe's!
But you confessed, right?
Pretty much…
Pretty much? What does pretty much mean?
I wasn't able to tell him a tenth of my feelings…
What did Kazehaya do?
What did he…
Wh-What is it?
Um…!
Working hard?
What are you doing here?
That's our line!
What are you doing here?!
I'm just a caring homeroom teacher.
I wanted to go over details for tomorrow's performance with Kuronuma.
I-I forgot about him!
Do it tomorrow!
Who let you in here...
I've come up with something good! We'll definitely get points for this!
Come here for a sec, Kuronuma.
Okay!
Shouldn't that be a bag of snacks for us that you're holding?
He's definitely trying to pull something again.
Look at his eyes, full of hidden desires!
Hidden desires?!
So about tomorrow's costume parade:
During the solo performance,
use this!
I…
I can't look at Kazehaya without hidden desires anymore!
I-I'm glad.
No, that's not good!
He said his feelings wouldn't change but I just don't know what to do anymore!
I keep thinking what if!
If there's a chance!
If-If…!
Do you really think Shota and the others don't have hidden desires as well?
We all have a heart.
It's normal to have hidden desires!
So yeah…
Tomorrow, put one of these on each judge's plate.
Okay!
You got it? Everyone has hidden desires!
Yes!
And also, tomorrow, tell him everything you just said right now.
All of these mix-ups are annoying.
See ya.
Right!
I just…
said something amazing, didn't I?
Now I need to go find Shota!
I think you need more paint on that side.
Got it.
Will we make it?
Won't we make it?
We're pulling an all-niter for it.
Pin was supposedly just at the girls' place!
At Yoshida's?
Yeah. She said there's a Pin-vasion warning!
More like a disaster warning.
Yeah, no kidding.
He really doesn't need to come.
He's lonely!
I'm gonna use the bathroom real fast.
Sure.
Yo!
Hey Kaze-filled-with-hidden-desires-ya!
Go away!
What did you say?
You know, hidden desires are part of the heart!
I got it, now leave!
What are you doing?!
Listen up in there!
Shota's mind is filled with nothing but hidden desires!
That's Pin, isn't it?
Yeah, it's Pin.
Kazehaya?
Hidden desires?
Hey! Shota! I came all the way over here just to give you advice!
You should be grateful and thank me!
Damn it—!
Will we finish on time?
We can do it!
Pin showed up at the guys' place too!
No way!
He's like yelling outside or something.
The sooner he leaves, the more help he'll be!
I'm so nervous...
Sawako.
When are you going to talk to him?
I-I'll try to before the parade!
and excited…
Good luck!
and exhilarated.
I can't remember the last time I looked forward to tomorrow this much.
Kazehaya, what did he mean by "hidden desires"?
That's what I'd like to know!
Seriously, Pin's messing with your business.
Joe's just been eating all night.
And when is Ryu gonna get up?
Sawako Kuronuma
Tomorrow
I want to talk to you again.
Sawako Kuronuma
Tomorrow
I want to talk to you again.
I can't wait…
to see you again.
douka ima dake wa furimukanaide
Please don't look at me right now
yuugure sawagu kaze
The sun's set, the wind's blowing,
furesouna kyouri
and we're so close that we can almost touch
kimi wo mitsumeteru zutto
My gaze has always been fixed on you
kimi ga suki de
I like you
I've always liked you
kono omoi koi demo ii
I don't mind if this emotion is what they call love,
kizu tsuitemo ii
and I don't care if I get hurt by it
nando demo tsutaetai
I just want to tell you, over and over again
kimi ni todoke
I want to reach you
Preview
From Now On
If we're together, I'm sure we'll…
If we're together, we'll be even more…
Next time: From Now On.