Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
namida wo nose
take away your tears
kareru made supiido agete
Speed up until they dry
tobikoete yukeru
I can overcome this
kitto kotae wa
The answer is
harukana ano sora no mukou
waiting beyond the distant sky
kotae ga mitsukaranai koko de wa
There's no answer here,
tameiki wo tsuite sora wo miru
so I sigh and look up at the sky
aoku somerareta hitomi no oku de kagayaiteru no wa
Shining deep within my eyes, reflecting its blue,
doko de mo yukeru, yume wo miteru
is a dreamer who can overcome anything
jibun na no sa
It's me, myself
Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
negai wo nosete
carry your dreams
nobashita te wa asu wo egaku
My hands willl draw tomorrow
mou kowaku nado nai
I'm not scared anymore
namida no ato
The memory of my tears
nijiiro ni somatte tondeyuku
are dyed by rainbows and fly
ano sora no mukou
far away beyond the sky
Ao, how's it going?
Caught anything?
Not yet.
Got something!
Be careful!
I'll be fine.
I was raised on an island after all!
The fishing rod...
That was close.
Are you hurt?
No... um, is your baby okay?
Oh, you noticed?
Well...
I'm at six months now. The baby's doing well!
She's a Rainbow
Thanks for the food.
Table manners.
Good boy.
You make it sound like I'm a kid.
Huh? How old are you?
I'm 13, and I should be in seventh grade,
but stuff happened on the day of the entrance ceremony.
This is so good!
So good! So good! So good!
What is this? It's all so good!
Isn't this wonderful?
These are just emergency rations...
But Generation Bleu is overseeing a food supply chain as well, so...
Um... You really should ask for protection.
From Generati... You mentioned them earlier.
Is that the name of this country?
No, it's not a country...
Ah, right. This is Earth after all.
But it's entirely different from the one I come from.
Mo—
Eureka, what was your Earth like?
Have you heard of the Scub Coral?
Yeah. We have it here too.
No, there's a lot more of it.
It covers the entire planet.
People were living on the top of it.
Humans and the Scub Coral lived together.
If you don't have authority on this matter, just say so.
I'll contact the Secretary of Defense directly.
She's back! Eureka! The one that disappeared 10 years ago!
Not to mention she has a new Mark I,
no, a Mark II with her now!
This time we won't—
Well, yes, it's in Japanese waters.
But we can't just let the Japanese take it...
Sorry for causing you all this trouble.
Not at all.
I'm a reserve, so I've always been prepared to stand on the frontline.
Especially with Japan being as it is...
I'm really grateful.
But... is it true?
Generation Bleu is denying it,
but from our surveillance photographs...
I can hardly believe my eyes.
This is why I asked you to come.
In the Japanese army, you're the only one who survived the Scub Burst 10 years ago.
If you negotiate with Eureka,
you could very possibly convince her to cooperate with our country.
Colonel Endo, it's my honor to welcome you on board of my vessel.
She's a good ship, captain.
Agent Nakamura, what exactly is the meaning of that?
Huh?
She got on board without asking a question.
Are you seriously going on a mission with your lover?
Oh, I'm so scared!
What are you doing here, Truth?
I dropped the Nirvash here.
I'll take that woman for myself as well.
Don't forget that this ship is just on lookout.
The government isn't determined enough yet to face off against Generation Bleu.
I can't have you causing trouble.
Oh? I thought you liked trouble.
Come on, we're so late!
I'm sure you know we reentered the atmosphere as fast as we could.
But it's still weird that a woman came out of the Scub Coral!
Ao hasn't been keeping in contact either...
Don't worry about it. Here, have this.
Who's this Eureka person anyway? Everyone acts weird whenever her name is mentioned.
Chief Hannah even left space for her.
She's a woman beyond common sense.
I don't know what you're misunderstanding...
I'm not misunderstanding!
Eureka is Ao's mother.
Yeah, I heard that, but I can't believe it!
I know she saved your life ten years ago.
Right?
But what we have right now is a mysterious being that emerged along the Scub Coral.
I'm well aware, Mama Hannah.
She's back... She's back... The birth...
How long has it been since Mama last went down to Earth?
Who's this Eureka anyway?
In the past, when a Scub Coral appears, a Secret emerges and a Scub Burst happens.
That's the natural order. At least it was.
But ten years ago in Okinawa,
for the first time, mankind fought back against the Secrets.
We were taught that Scub Bursts can be stopped.
It was....
Eureka?
That was when Generation Bleu was founded.
This is bad.
Not only is the Japanese Navy heading there, the Okinawan Allied Forces are making an appearance too.
It's still not too late to command Fukai Ao
to bring back the woman that looks like Eureka.
Then we would have to abandon that huge ship.
We can't let Japan or America have it.
Such a complete sample is unprecedented.
Ao is also on highest alert.
Is it really a good idea to leave it to a kid
instead of dispatching team Goldilocks?
We lost that blue haired girl once already.
We don't know when she's going to vanish again.
I don't want to lose her due to any hasty actions.
The Gekko?
Yeah, it's the name of this ship.
I traveled on it with many other people a long time ago.
We were all on a journey together.
Was your, uh...
Baby?
Yeah. Was his father traveling with you too?
How did you know! Oh, no!
But at first it wasn't like that.
We were pretty much like children back then.
He was a crybaby as well,
and kind of useless...
You didn't love him?
Nope...
I did. Every bit of him.
Um, and was Dad...
Do you want to go back?
Yeah. I think Renton will come for me though.
But I don't really know where I am.
Renton?
To research the cause of the disappearing Scub Coral,
we purposely allowed the Scub Coral to consume this ruined ship.
But while we were conducting the experiment, we were both caught up in this.
Both? The other Nirvash?
You're piloting a Nirvash too, right?
It's so weird.
It looks just like the one Renton is building now.
Don't worry.
We got a call earlier, right?
It's my chief and sub-chief. And...
It's been such a long time.
My name is Ivica Tanovic.
Mr. Ivica Tanovic, was it?
Huh?
Mr Ivica...
My name is Ivica, but...
Shut up!
I've met you before.
But I heard you fell to Okinawa two years ago.
No, it was way before that.
I've came here once before.
You're Mr. Endou, right?
G-Monster, closing in!
This is impossible! We should leave it to the air force!
No!
If the calculations are correct,
then a Scub Burst here could erase the entire main island of Okinawa!
We need to stay here!
Are you telling me to trust that woman?
And believe what she said about that Quartz?
This won't work...
I'll have to take it... with me.
Nirvash, stop it!
Ao, I'm so sorry!
Come here!
What is that?!
The sea giant!
She left, didn't she?
I heard she has a son.
We took his mother away from him.
But thanks to her, we now know how to fight back.
Even if we can't defeat the Secrets,
we can prevent the Scub Burst by retrieving the Quartz.
I'm Christophe Blanc. If you'd like, please join the organization I'm plannin—
I must return to my country.
Many sons are close to losing their mothers there.
Well, after that then.
I'm sorry, but I think this is the first time we've met.
But... Chief, you said you knew Mom.
Eureka from the past?
She hasn't given birth to you yet.
She came from a time before she showed up at Iwato island 13 years ago.
What do you mean?
Could it be that... her baby is... me?!
I have managed to link some data to that ship.
However, I could only identify the numbers.
The date of the data is 12005 AD.
So that ship is from the distant future?
Then Eureka isn't an alien? She's from the future?
Ten thousand years and two thousand more...
This isn't the time for jokes...
After all...
I can see the cause of your concern.
And even if all goes well and I give birth to him, wouldn't he just hate me?
Stop there if you really think so.
You fell in love with someone
and you're bearing his child.
It's all because you wanted to.
Are you're just starting to worry about the child now?
Shouldn't you just focus on how to overcome the difficulties?
Am I right?
But the doctors said that inside of areas with high trapar concentration,
the child of a human and a Coralian would be...
Why are you here?!
Blanc, huh?
The Gazelle Corps is an independent contractor under direct control of the president.
Um, he somehow ended up with us.
Jeez. How did you find us in the first place?
Where's your mom, Ao?
Answer my question!
Don't fight.
We're surrounded by the JAF and the Allied Forces.
We can use the Triton as a decoy
and use the GenBlu transporter, which is standing by, to retreat...
But Mom doesn't want to leave here!
We'll return her to her world.
Return her?!
But if we have her, the research on Scub Coral and Secrets will progress a lot faster!
She's fated to come here again.
Thirteen years ago.
What are you talking about?
Do you know of a way to return her?
You just don't want Generation Bleu to take her—Eureka—away from you.
Did you fall for her, ten years ago?
Huh? Am I right?
Stop being retarded, Gazelle!
Why are you always pretending to know it all
and get in our way all the freaking time?!
What the hell do you know?!
Gazelle!
Ao!
The smell of gunpowder!
Don't tell me—!
It really is you, Eureka.
There's no mistake.
What do you want?
Where is Hannah?
The woman who was with you is unhurt.
Hannah!
How could you...
What's wrong?! What happened?!
You! You're Endo from the ground forces!
Endo?
Keep them cornered!
Now, this way.
Wait! Please!
Return fire?
We can't while they have her!
I don't know!
I don't know, but it can't stay as it is!
Mom's gonna stay with me! I won't let anyone take her!
Is that...
Mom!
No way... Is that Eureka?
Mom, let's escape together?
Where to?
The Chief said he'll send you back,
but I don't want to say goodbye!
But if the child you're carrying is me
then this way I won't get... born...
You're slow, Eureka's child.
Truth!
Who are you?
Sorry for being so rough.
But in this world you can't trust the Allied Forces nor Generation Bleu.
We, the Japanese, are the only ones truly wishing for peace.
Please...
Truth...
Naru...
Ao... My Ao...
Mom...
Mom!
Ao! Return to where I belong... to Renton.
You're the only one who can do that.
I don't want to!
I finally get to meet you!
I've been looking for you all this time!
Please. A terrible thing is about to happen.
A terrible thing?
The Secrets aren't your enemies.
What?
What did you just say?
What do you mean the Secrets aren't our enemies?!
Oh? He protected you?
Who are you?
What a rude greeting.
But it doesn't matter.
You are mine.
Get away from her!
Step away, Truth!
Get lost.
Now then.
Stop!
IFO?
That's... Ao!
Fukai Ao! You can't change this world!
Ao!
A... o...
Thank you very much.
I have a child.
Two years old. A real troublemaker.
Oh... really?
If something happens to me, please take care of him.
Take care of Ao.
Ao?
You bastard...
She asked me!
She asked me to protect her child!
You're not getting away!
In here!
Damn Nirvash!
Can you fly?
I don't know where am I or who those people are, but I only know...
That I have to protect this planet!
Nirvash!
Is that...
The Nirvash!
Go!
Ao!
Eureka!
Let's go, Nirvash!
To be continued.
Preview
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
Truth and the two Nirvash face off in a wild battle.
The Secret that appears in the middle of the fight
cracks the walls of the world.
The revealed truth pulls Ao into despair.
Eureka Seven AO, episode 14: Starfire.
Listen to the voices of the children of the stars.