Kokoro
masshiro PAGE mekuru
I walk through the white pages of my storybook
Incoming Text
tobidasu irodoru hajikeru
just waiting to be painted
mangekyou no fuukei
with a kaleidoscope of my experiences.
From
Me
To
You
kizukeba STORY wa mada
This story has only
gikochinaku hajimatta bakkari
just barely begun
shinkokyuu wo mou ikkai
I take a deep breath
tabi suru kaze tsutsumikomu you ni senaka wo osu
and the wind wraps around me and urges me forward
aa yawarakakute atatakai kimi no te
Your hand is so warm held within mine;
nigiri shimete sono kokoro no oku made todoku you ni
it reaches all the way to my heart.
hohoenmi de kureta nara nigirikaeshite kuretara
I can't see a brighter future
boku wa tada mae wo miteru
than you smiling and taking my hand as well
Why are you crying?
Was it Miura?
…I'm sorry.
I'm sorry you had to look out for me so much.
I'm sorry I caused you so much trouble.
I'm sorry!
I did those things 'cause I like you.
Because you're an idiot!
Wasn't Kazehaya the only one who never looked at you out of pity?
Even though even Chizu and Ayane did!
Open your eyes!
What…?
To You
Kuronuma!
How's the school festival prep coming along?
Making progress?
The costume and accessories groups are both doing really well.
I think they'll be able to finish on time.
The news poster group is moving along well too.
When they're finished, they'll be able to help out the other groups.
The mural and parade float groups are a little bit behind right now.
I see.
Tell those slowpokes to get a move
on! Overworking is required in youth!
The circumstances have changed.
Beat the seniors.
Be the overall champs!
Oh high class sushi…
You're betting on us, aren't you?
Oh right, also!
I think you're misunderstanding something.
More misunderstandings?!
Shota's really not as great as you think he is.
Just give up on him!
As great as I…?
Hello lowly workers! Working hard?
What a terrible teacher.
Seriously, the worst.
Let's see, all of the varieties of herbal tea are ready to go.
The shift schedule for the café is just about done too.
Yano-chin!
What do you think of having herbal ramen?
No.
But why?
Where am I attaching this again?
Here.
Oh right! Hold down that end!
Got it.
But I do think he's great.
What have you been holding all this time?
Information for the Black Magic Café.
Books on black magic, huh?
Try to contain yourself.
What did he mean by give up?
Give up on trying to go out with Kuronuma?
On liking her?
Wow, that's a lot of books!
They look heavy! What did you get so many books about?
On herbal teas and snacks and such.
Oh, for the Black Magic Café!
Let me see!
Introduction to Herbal Teas
But why do you have so many?
Well, because... Since it's a café, I want
people to be able to relax and enjoy themselves.
You're so into this!
Look, this one's cute!
It looks so yummy!
Which one?
Wow, it really is!
Really?
I'm so glad!
…You already have trouble with yourself.
He's right.
I always just think of myself…
I…
Open your eyes!
Did I fall in love with him because I think he's great?
I don't want you to think I'm lively, or fair, or whatever.
10 days until the
School Festival
I walk through the white pages of my storybook
just waiting to be painted
with a kaleidoscope of my experiences.
This story has only
just barely begun.
I take a deep breath.
And the wind wraps around me and urges me forward.
Your hand is so warm held within mine;
it reaches all the way to my heart.
I can't see a brighter future
than you smiling and taking my hand as well.
5 days until the
School Festival
Happy Birthday Chizu!
I suddenly realize
School Festival in 3 days!! Last push!!
how deep my whirlpool of hidden emotions is.
I'm so embarrassed.
And the wind now says it can't wait any longer and runs ahead.
My memories play before my eyes like a revolving lantern,
endlessly, innocently, and oh so brightly.
My fear, my weaknesses, all transform into the high-flying wind.
Forward—
Your hand is warmer and gentler than any other,
and it reaches all the way to my heart.
If you'll smile and take my hand as well,
then I'll never let you go.
Excellent Luck
Why did I fall in love with Kazehaya?
I'm pleased to announce the beginning of
the 43rd Kitahoro High School Festival!
43rd Kitahoro High School Festival
Fairy Café this way!
Come see the Astronomy Club's planetarium!
We have fortune telling!
Cult fortune telling!
Sadako's Black Magic Cafe
[Mystery] Black Magic Consultations Happening Now [Dark Arts]
- Herbal Teas - Herbal Sweets
I hate it.
The guy I like has a girlfriend and I hate it.
I'll do anything to make him mine and make his girlfriend fall.
I-It's said that to curse someone is to curse yourself.
It's possible that you may end up causing
yourself harm as well, so I suggest…
What is this?
What's with this evil aura?
Rumors about Kuronuma set off more rumors,
Sadako's Black Magic Cafe
End of the Line
and a bunch of people who want to cast black magic showed up.
This is because of her?!
Thank you!
I'll try my best to compete with his girlfriend fairly!
I won't hate her even if I lose!
For some reason, they all leave cured of their malice.
S-She's impressive.
Next guest, please!
No, I'm sorry, we don't play "super cute rock-paper-scissors" here.
Here's your Perilla tea.
It smells so good!
What is this tea good for?
It's effective against constipation.
I'm here!
Chigusa! It's been awhile.
Hey, so do you have herbal ramen here?
Rejected.
I'll take one of these.
The Black Magic Café is going on a ten minute break!
The person she likes has a girlfriend…
There are more love troubles than anything else.
If Kazehaya didn't like someone,
was there something I could've done?
Love
Dedication to love
will bring happiness
Would things be different now?
They wouldn't, would they?
Sadako!
Good work.
I brought this for you.
Did you think I was Kazehaya?
Ayane will give me hell for interfering
again, but I just can't leave this alone.
Can I tell you what I really think?
I thought it was impossible to make Kazehaya fall for you.
I thought that you two were too
different and wouldn't make a good couple.
I thought that if Kazehaya actually
fell for someone, it wouldn't be you.
And even though you said that you don't feel a wall between you two,
I see a wall between you and him and no one else.
A wall that you don't have with anyone else.
Only with Kazehaya?
Do I?
But you're actually pretty cute.
So I thought you should give up on Kazehaya, try
to fit in with the class, and choose someone else.
Along that line of thought, I figured why not me?
Sadako?
I think you look much better when you're smiling.
But I guess now, the only one who can make you upset,
make you cry,
and make you laugh
is Kazehaya, right?
I support you.
Good luck.
A wall with Kazehaya?
I-I'm sorry!
Thanks!
Feeling embarrassed,
not wanting him to hate me,
being unable to laugh normally,
unable to say what's on my mind…
When did I create this wall
between the two of us?
When I said what I really thought, Kazehaya
always answered me with full honesty.
Hey, Kazehaya…
I'm sorry.
Sadako… It's a misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
I…
Yeah, I think Kuronuma has the wrong idea about me.
What?
But I think Kuronuma has had to deal with people
having the wrong idea about her for much longer.
Yet, she's never given up.
I know I'm the exact opposite of her,
quick to get angry, with a jealous streak.
I'm definitely not the amazing person she thinks I am,
and definitely not someone worth admiring.
Kuronuma always says "It's all thanks to you, Kazehaya!",
but she's always trying her best all on her own,
always trying to make things better.
I'm the one who admires her.
Kazehaya…
Kazehaya!
We came to check out your Black Magic Café!
We've heard it really works!
That Sadako Kuronuma is a natural!
Sawako.
It's Sawako Kuronuma.
I thought he was like a god.
Bright, lively, and always the center of attention.
The Black Magic Café was a great success!
I respected him, admired him,
but when did he change from a god to just an ordinary guy?
We're done!
Not yet.
The costume parade.
It might take all night to get ready.
Sawako!
Good work today!
Go home, eat, take a bath, then come meet up at my place!
Hey, have you seen Kazehaya?
Nope.
Why, you can't find him?
Kazehaya!
It's okay.
It's okay now.
What's okay?
You can't possibly—
It doesn't matter
who Kazehaya likes anymore.
Go on without me!
Kuronuma, he's in the classroom!
Those things don't matter anymore.
Is it okay to for you to let her go?
It doesn't matter if things are scary,
if I'm embarrassed,
or what he thinks of me.
Why was I hesitating?
There are so many things I want to say to him.
His back,
how he looks when he blushes,
when he's anxious,
when he's angry,
when he's serious,
when he's sad,
when he has a big sparkling smile on his face…
If I told him I wanted all of that,
What sort of face he would make then?
I want to break it.
I want to break the wall I built between us.
I want to tell him.
I want to tell him how I feel.
I want my feelings to reach him.
Please,
please,
please reach him.
douka ima dake wa furimukanaide
Please don't look at me right now
yuugure sawagu kaze
The sun's set, the wind's blowing,
furesouna kyouri
and we're so close that we can almost touch
kimi wo mitsumeteru zutto
My gaze has always been fixed on you
kimi ga suki de
I like you
I've always liked you
kono omoi koi demo ii
I don't mind if this emotion is what they call love,
kizu tsuitemo ii
and I don't care if I get hurt by it
nando demo tsutaetai
I just want to tell you, over and over again
kimi ni todoke
I want to reach you
Preview
Confession
I like you.
Next time: Confession.