Any girl that goes to Altair either dies or transforms into a man.
And that means Mix?
We found her, but it wasn't Mix anymore.
She'd lost her memories.
Are Zessica and Yunoha all right?
We're all right now.
The checkups didn't find anything wrong.
But if we'd been there just a little longer...
Did Mikono come back yet?
No, she's still searching for High Commander Fudo.
How's Shrade?
He's all right for now, but they don't know if it'll take.
So the High Commander is missing and Shrade's tapped out?
Neo-Deava is good as dead!
We might as well surrender now!
It's not over yet.
We should regroup and head back up to Altair!
Andy?
I will save Mix.
Andy...
Andy! Are you okay?
I'm fine!
I'm not giving up. I'll get Mix back if it's the last thing I do!
zetsubouteki ni kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful it's depressing
hanten suru sekai no kattou ni aishiaou
Let's love one another amidst the chaos in this backwards world
bokura ga miteru sekai wa itsudemo sakasama de
This world of ours moves in reverse
A
doushiyou mo nai koto de taigai kimatteku
controlled by forces we can't even touch
A
namida suru hodo kizu tsuku hitomi
There is pain in your eyes so deep I want to cry
A
kokoro de sakebi nagara
Screaming from my heart
A
tada atteitai saigo no futari masarenai mama
The last couple who desire each other cannot be together
A
byouyomi ga kikoetekuru
And time is running out
A
zetsubouteki ni kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful it's depressing
A
sutareyuku doubutsu mitai ni aishiaou
Let's love one another like abandoned animals
A
nakitai kurai kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful I want to cry
A
hanten suru sekai no kattou ni kanjitai yo
Let's love one another amidst the chaos in this backwards world
A
Kiss
I was so close. I almost saw it.
The perfect melody of love echoing between two worlds.
Don't talk.
You have to rest.
Will I finish composing it before my life runs out?
Can you tell me with your Prophecy of Despair?
You really want to hear your dark future?
Sorrow makes some songs all the more beautiful.
Shrade...
If I finish the song, will you play it with me, my friend?
When will High Commander Fudo come back?
We haven't heard anything from Mikono either.
Please have one, Miss Suomi.
No, thank you. I avoid high calorie foods late at night.
I see.
Please don't worry.
Fudo will return to us.
And he'll bring back the legend of Genesis.
Girl with hair the color of grass.
I regret that even though I opened the gate for you...
You!
Don't forget to keep your promise.
What promise? I didn't promise you anything...
Even if you don't remember what it was,
you will keep it for me when the time comes.
Mix...
I actually saw her big bangs.
But they weren't big bangs at all.
Andy, what are you doing here?
I've got to sit right here or I'll sink.
That's one of the holes Mix filled.
Yep. There are absolutely no weak points in the material she fills with.
I can't sink into it even if my power overloads.
Andy...
Amata...
Say we actually got Mix back.
Would I...
I mean, now that she's a boy,
would I still love her the same?
Well, well. I didn't smell anyone, but there you are.
Let go of me!
What are you running away from me for?
We're finally one!
Apollo...
Here I am, Apollo..
I've been waiting to see you again.
You came for me!
Mikono...
Wrong, wench.
We're not Apollon.
We're Amagura!
Mikono, wait!
Hold it right there, wench!
Let go of her!
Shut up!
Join us, wench.
Help!
Amata, stop!
Mikono...
Thank you.
When you clap your hands, what remains between them?
A right hand and a left. Angel and human.
Man and woman. Plus and minus.
What is in the gap between them?
What's in the gap between my right hand and my left?
Nothing.
There's nothing there, but it feels warm.
Haven't I heard this somewhere before?
Long ago, just after the heavens and earth were separated,
the world was bathed in a glorious light.
The flowers sang, while the creatures and insects whispered of love.
and the angels loved, up among the stars.
But the angels were hunters, and mankind was their prey.
In this war, there fought an Angel of Slaughter named Apollonius,
and he met a girl named Celiane, and they fell in love.
Apollonius betrayed his kind and joined with the humans.
He, the traitor, cast off his wings and gave unto the humans a great weapon.
He piloted a machine Angel and fought against the angels.
This is the legend written in the Book of Genesis.
And that's what really happened 12,000 years ago?
No.
This is the previous story, the story of 24,000 years ago.
The wheel of Fate has turned again, and the legend is about to be told once more.
Once more...
Amata Sora! Explain yourself!
I do not recall ordering a sortie!
I'm going after Mikono.
You were not given permission to move out!
She's calling me.
Mikono is calling for help.
I have to move fast!
Mikono...
I can't let someone I love leave me again...
Yes, go to the one you love.
And go also to the Wings of the Sun.
And you, fragmented one, wake up now.
Amata...
Vector Z's transmitter is off. We can't track it.
Cayenne, can you see where it is with the Prophecy of Despair?
I'll try.
No...
This is the city where Mikono and I first met.
What happened here?
Where is this?
The gap between light and darkness, as written in the Book of Genesis.
Cockpit's empty.
Where did Amata go?
The city where Amata and I first met.
And where we had our first Union.
No one's here.
Where did they all go?
I'd heard it was locked down after that fight,
but I didn't know it was like this.
Is Mikono here too?
That's what my power says.
So you did come after Mikono, Amata...
Let's split up and search.
Sir?
What are these?
They aren't mine. Whose are they?
What am I supposed to do?
Why did Mikage send me here?
But it smells...
I'm sure I was here, a long time ago.
Amata...
You've finally unlocked those suppressed memories.
"Skies of Aquaria"?
Mikono...
Mikono!
Amata!
Zessica? What are you doing here?
I came to get you, Amata.
I mean, Chairman Crea ordered us.
Me and Cayenne.
Sorry. It's my fault for going against orders.
This whole town is locked down, so everyone was evacuated.
So that's why there's no one left.
How come you had to come here so badly? You even disobeyed orders.
I don't know... but...
But what?
I felt like Mikono was calling for me.
I'll be waiting for you.
Even if I have to wait for 12,000 years.
Amata, you used to work in this theater, right?
And this is where you met Mikono?
Zessica?
Amata...
Next time...
After the next 12,000 years... I...
It is not the place of you humans to write your own false tales.
Not when a true legend is about to come to pass again!
Zessica!
Run! This way!
What's the matter? Come on!
Run, little beasts of love, run.
Run to the promised land!
Amata!
Zessica!
Ugh!
Stop. I'm not getting out.
You don't know that!
Forget about me! Just go!
Never! I won't leave you behind!
Amata...
Thank you, Amata.
Zessica! No!
Zessica!
We've been looking for you, Amata!
We're here, Cayenne!
Sazanka!
Vector Y... who's in it?
You said when I finished the piece, you would play it with me, my friend.
Cut it out! You can't Union in your condition!
There's no time for that!
Come!
Risky Union!
Go, Aquarion!
Shrade, why...
Thank you, my friend.
This is so rotten!
Aquarion Spada!
Found you, Amata, you pathetic wimp.
Your...
The Wings of the Sun are soon to awaken.
I have to say I'm sorry...
What I did to you... please, forgive me...
You... you saw it.
Yeah. I didn't think it was real.
And I saw Amata, pathetically unable to do a thing about it.
So you're...
Yeah.
You're me.
kimi he tsuzuku sakamichi ni
There were white flowers growing
shiroi hana ga saiteta
on the road on the hill that leads to you
yume kara sameta ato mo kanashii sora miteta
When I woke from the dream, the sky still looked sad
kono kimochi happa no ue ni susunderu
My feelings drift on a leaf in the wind
asatsuyu wo ochiru oto ni mimi wo sumaseteru no
I'm straining my ears for the sound of the dew falling
kamisama anata ga tsukutta sekai wa kanpeki ja nai
God in Heaven, this world You made is far from perfect
koko de wa mainichi koi ga boroboro shindeku
Down here, love is shattered day by day
hajimete suki ni natta no wo anata wa shiranai deshou
You don't know what it's like to fall in love for the first time
chikyuu no uragawa de ii kara soba ni ite hoshikatta
Let it be on the other end of the world, but I wanted to be with him
watashi wo wasuretemo ii kara soba ni ite hoshikatta
Even if You were to forget me, I wanted to be with him
I think maybe Kagura is a little wrong about girls.
Loving someone is supposed to be more kind and gentle.
Next Time
Wings of Rebirth
Oh, no!