nanpeeji mo tsuiyashite
Upon pages and pages of entries
We still don't
know the name
of the flower
we saw that day.
tuzurareta bokura no kibun
We've put down all our emotions
doushiteka ichigyou no
But now I've hit a writer's block
kuuhaku wo umerarenai
I don't know how to finish this page anymore
oshibana no shiori hasande
Putting a bookmark in my diary
kimi to korogasu tsukaisute no jitensha
You and I go out to ride the bike we found in the dumpster
wasurekake no renga wo
Let's go to our secret place
tsumiageta basho ni yukou
Where we piled up our bricks of memories
umi wo miwatasu saka wo kakenobotte
Run up the hill, where we can see the horizon
kowaikurai ni aoi sora to
Where we can see the sky so fearfully blue
migite ni saidaa hidarite wa
With cider in my right hand
zutto kimi wo sagashiteiru
My other hand helps me search for you
souyatte ima wa boku no hou e
You used to come find me way back when
toitsumeru koto mo nakute
You used to demand me of so much more
mada futari wa sugu soko ni irunoni
You're both still standing right by my side
douka mata aemasuyouni nante
Yet why do I pray to see you both again?
douka shiteru mitai
There must be something off with me
Be careful out there, Jintan!
Yadomi?
I'm fine!
Yukiatsu...
That dress...
It looks like the one Menma used to wear.
Wh-Why are you wearing that?
Hey... are you okay?
Do I look okay?
Take a good look at me!
Hey, Yukiatsu!
Please. Let them work this out.
But...
This is the perfect chance. If he doesn't take advantage of it, there may not be another.
Tsuruko...
Hey, I look like Menma, right? I do, right?!
Don't I look like her?
Yukiats—
Can't you see her?!
It's my fault.
It's my fault Menma died that day.
What are you talking about? It couldn't possibly be your fault.
If anything, it was my—
I'm telling you that it's my fault!
If I hadn't that to Menma, she wouldn't have died.
I made her die!
If Menma were to reappear to anyone, it should be me.
To haunt or to curse me.
Either way, it should be me!
But she never showed herself.
Not to me.
Yukiatsu...
That's how I know she doesn't exist anymore.
She doesn't exist anywhere!
I'm right here.
Menma says she's right here.
You're still saying that...?
She says thank you for the hairpin.
And that she's sorry.
Look, I don't really understand it myself, but...
Yukiatsu...
Are you satisfied?
Hey!
Are you sure we should let him go?
It itches...
Well, I'm done for today.
Did you already know about this?
You could say I caught on.
He'd been asking me to hang out with him after school for a while.
He'd pretend he was buying presents for his inexistent girlfriend.
It was women's clothing. A white one-piece dress with a ribbon.
Should we really have done that?
Yeah. I figure you should squeeze all the pus out of a wound.
But because he's rotten to the core, if you squeeze it all out, then there might not be anything left.
Thank you.
"Thanks for the hairpin... And, I'm sorry."
Menma...
Wait up, Jintan!
Jintan!
Wait!
Hold on, Menma!
Why? I can't! Jintan's gonna—
Just let him go.
You're not ugly at all, you're...
Here.
I thought it would suit you...
I thought so because I like you!
I'm sorry! Jintan is gonna get away, so...
So I have to go chase him!
We'll talk about this later!
Maybe it doesn't go well with my glasses.
Now I can't see.
Hey, Me—
Menma...
Do you want something to eat?
Uh...
I want Ken-chan Ramen!
We don't have any.
And you can't find it anywhere nowadays.
What should I do now?
Let me think...
I'll go buy some.
You don't have to; anything else you have is fine.
Jintan?
Menma died,
but now, she's here.
She came to me, not Yukiatsu.
I didn't care whether she was a ghost or a hallucination,
but I avoided thinking about it.
It's fun when we're all together.
It's fun being with Jintan.
That's why I felt that it's okay not to think about it.
Why is Menma here?
You're way too popular.
They didn't have Ken-chan Ramen. So, instead, I got this.
You got all of this instead?
Yeah.
Just hurry up and sit down...
Jintan, I need to talk to you.
About what? Anyway, the popsicle is going to melt.
I want you to grant my wish.
Why bring that up all of a sudden?
I'm doing the best I can, you know...
In a lot of ways...
Yeah.
And, of course, I haven't been as obsessed as Yukiatsu,
but in my own way...
Yeah.
I have a lot of things going on, too, you know!
I don't have the time to babysit you.
Jintan...
I'm home!
Oh, man, I'm exhausted.
What's all this? Are you having a party?
Is that a popsicle? How cute!
Mind if I have it?
That's not cute.
What's with me?
What did I mean by that?
What do I have going on?
I eat, browse the web,
sleep, play videogames,
sleep, and then eat.
I just repeat that cycle.
And yet...
Episode 5
Tunnel
So, I'll take the train on the way home.
I'll be done with work at around 7, so after that...
Gee, it's great that you decided to tag along, Naruko.
Huh?
I was counting on you being there when I made plans,
so I was pretty worried when you told me you wouldn't come.
That's right. Ryou would be pissed at you, otherwise.
Ryou has nothing to do with it.
Hey, actually...
You've been really unsociable lately, you know?
We were even wondering if you still wanted to be friends or not.
Geez, Haruna. Your jokes are too harsh. Don't you think so, Naruko?
Damn. The next one doesn't come for another 30 minutes.
You're the same as always.
In fact, it's creepy how much you haven't changed.
How do you want me to act, then?
Huh?
Do you want me taunt you can call you a femboy?
Yeah. I might prefer that.
I'd appreciate it if you didn't try to use me to restore balance to your self-esteem.
Thanks to you, I managed to put an end to a few things. Thank you.
So then he texts me, saying he loves me!
For real? Sounds like a dream come true.
She got a train and rode it all the way to the city.
And she's lugging around a huge shopping bag.
It's a costume. You'd know all about that.
Huh?
There are certain things you can't manage unless you change your costume.
You were great! Awesome! Awesome! Awesome!
Stick the next one in, Ryou. Hurry up!
Don't talk like a slutty schoolgirl.
I don't care what it is, just hurry up, Ryou!
What you gonna do schoolgirl?
Having fun?
Calm down, Haruna!
You look like you're forcing yourself to stay.
I'm not forcing myself...
Hey, wanna get out of here?
Sorry, guys. Naruko and I are gonna call it quits.
Wait a sec...
I think she's not feeling well, and I have to get up early tomorrow, too.
I gotta catch One Piece, y'know.
Doesn't One Piece air the day after tomorrow?
Does it?
You guys are no fun!
Tell all about it later, Naruko.
Alright, let's get going.
Oh, right.
U-Um...
Is the train station really this way?
I thought we'd just walk to the station together...
Oh, come on. That's not what "get out of here" means.
And I'm a bit buzzed, so I wanna "rest" for a bit.
That's the truth.
I-I'm really not feeling well, so...
Shouldn't you get some rest, too, then?
You're talking about a different kind of rest, though!
Oh, yeah! What about One Piece?
One Piece airs the day after tomorrow.
What? Why don't you just go by yourself?
Wouldn't it be a waste though?
Huh?
They're black aren't they?
Wai— Get off of me! I said I don't want to!
Yeah, sure.
No, not, "Yeah, sure."
Let me go!
Let me go you bastard!
Huh? Is that you, Anjou?
I'm hanging out with Yadomi right now. You want in?
Who the hell are you?
Hey, guys! I found her!
This is such bullshit.
I just rescued a girl from the arms of a man.
That was the most clichéd thing I've ever done.
You call that a rescue?
Wouldn't a rescue involve throwing a punch or two and tearing me away?
I'm hot and I'm smart, but unfortunately I'm a bit lacking in the strength department.
What the heck?
That aside, you're gorgeous.
I don't want to be told that by a tranny.
S-Sorry.
I thought so. Hearing that makes it easier.
Are you a virgin?
Wh-What's wrong with that?
Wanna go out with me?
Don't you like Menma?
Yeah, and?
I... can't. I just can't.
Because...
Is it Yadomi?
What do you see in that guy?
What do I see in him?
Don't act like you've figured it out! I never said I liked him...
He was a leader, smart, and athletic.
But that was all in the past.
That's true, but he's kind in unexpected ways...
And I think if he fixed his hair, he'd look a bit like Yama from Hey! Say! JUMP.
I see.
I don't even know if I like him.
I just can't stop thinking about him.
Thinking about him?
Menma died, then his mother died.
It became tough to talk to him.
I was actually a bit happy that we'd be going to the same school.
But Yadomi can't forget about Menma.
You can't forget the Yadomi that can't forget about Menma.
Back then...
What?
Back then you said Yadomi's name.
You said you'd been hanging out together.
We're letting an express train pass. Please wait for a moment.
We've been left behind.
There we go.
Ding-dong.
This is delicious!
So why are you eating at my house?
Didn't I bring you some wild plants in exchange?
Tempura was the right choice.
He looks like he's really enjoying it.
You've got dirt above your nose.
Oh, yeah. Is Menma here?
Yes! I'm here!
Menma should eat some tempura too.
Do you seriously believe in her?
Didn't I already say so?
But...
I've thought it over once more.
And?
I'm not sure about this, but Menma being here probably isn't a good thing, right?
It means she couldn't go to heaven.
So that must be why she's here.
Go to heaven?
I don't know. I just don't...
Jintan?
I...
Is Menma over there?
Um... well...
Alrighty.
What? Hey...
Hey Menma, how about giving us a little hint?
I'll grant it quicker than you can ring a bell.
There's something you want right?
You can rely on me a bit, too, you know?
I want to let you go to heaven.
Hey, Hisakawa...
Come on, Menma! Please, tell me.
And let me see you, too.
No good? Come on!
But...
I want to talk with everyone else!
But I just don't know...
How about we all think about it together, Menma?
I don't know about my wish, or about going to heaven.
I just don't know!
Can't we? Let's think about it together.
I don't know...
And then you can...
Poppo.
Could you let it go?
deai wa futtoshita shunkan
We met in an unexpected moment
kaerimichi no kousaten de koe wo kaketekureta ne
when you called out to me at the crosswalk,
Please, just let it go.
"issho ni kaerou"
"Let's walk home together."
aa hanabi ga yozora kirei ni saite chotto setsunaku
The fireworks blossomed heartrendingly beautiful across the night sky,
I don't get it.
aa kaze ga jikan to tomo ni nagareru
and time passed as swiftly as the wind.
I don't get it at all.
ureshikute tanoshikute bouken mo iro iro shita ne
We shared so many happy times and thrilling adventures
futari no himitsu no kichi no naka
together in our secret base.
kimi to natsu no owari shourai no yume ookina kibou wasurenai
I will never forget the hopes and dreams we shared during that one summer's end.
jyuunen no ato hachigatsu mata deaeru no wo shinjite
I'm sure we will meet again in another August, in maybe ten years time.
kimi ga saigo made kokoro kara "arigatou" sakendeita koto shitetayo
I could feel your heartfelt thanks all the way until the end.
namida wo koraete egao
And I know it must've been painful
de sayounara setsunai yo ne
to hold back your tears and say goodbye with a smile.
saikou no omoide wo
But those are my best memories.