Goodbye, Menma
Thank you for doing this for me today.
I'm going to heaven tomorrow.
I want to be friends with everyone until the very end. Thank you all.
Super Peace Busters
Fireworks
We still don't
know the name
of
the flower
we saw that day.
nanpeeji mo tsuiyashite
Upon pages and pages of entries
tuzurareta bokura no kibun
We've put down all our emotions
doushiteka ichigyou no
But now I've hit a writer's block
kuuhaku wo umerarenai
I don't know how to finish this page anymore
oshibana no shiori hasande
Putting a bookmark in my diary
kimi to korogasu tsukaisute no jitensha
You and I go out to ride the bike we found in the dumpster
wasurekake no renga wo
Let's go to our secret place
tsumiageta basho ni yukou
Where we piled up our bricks of memories
umi wo miwatasu saka wo kakenobotte
Run up the hill, where we can see the horizon
kowaikurai ni aoi sora to
Where we can see the sky so fearfully blue
migite ni saidaa hidarite wa
With cider in my right hand
zutto kimi wo sagashiteiru
My other hand helps me search for you
souyatte ima wa boku no hou e
You used to come find me way back when
toitsumeru koto mo nakute
You used to demand me of so much more
mada futari wa sugu soko ni irunoni
You're both still standing right by my side
douka mata aemasuyouni nante
Yet why do I pray to see you both again?
douka shiteru mitai
There must be something off with me
It's tomorrow.
Just look at you.
You've finally come home but all you do is dilly-dally around the house and skip school.
Leave me alone. I'll clean up on my own, so just go away.
Whatever.
She's so annoying.
I'm sorry.
Hello?
Hi, Yukiatsu.
Poppo wants to meet up to make the final arrangements tonight.
Are you coming?
I don't know.
That's understandable.
Anyway, let's meet up in front of the subway station...
By the way, is Tsurumi still the same as always?
She acts like she's the only one who understands you.
He's 181 cm tall and weighs 68 kilos.
His favorite food is a bean paste pastry.
His hobby is cross-dressing.
Cross-dressing?
Wait Tsurumi, we still haven't asked what we wanted to.
Hey.
That hurts.
You agreed not to talk about that.
It could really affect...
That hurts.
Tsurumi?
Alright, let's get to it!
Let's start our grand preparations for Menma's ascent to heaven tomorrow!
Let's make some decorations, partner!
I'm going to make flowers out of tissues!
You're the guest of honor. Why are you getting involved in the preparations?
Because it's fun.
That looks good, Menma.
Don't space out Jintan. Make a garbage can out of those papers.
Wha...? Oh, right.
A garbage can?
Back in the day I was a little dork.
I acted like an idiot so people would pay attention to me.
But Jintan and everyone else became my friends, and in the end...
Even though all I could do was watch everyone else from the sidelines...
All I could do was watch...
Poppo?
Anyway, that's why I'm taking care of everything this time.
I'll send you off in style, Menma.
I'm looking forward to it.
You're so nice, Poppo!
What do you plan to do about that?
There's no way I could go.
How much will those kids torment me before they're satisfied?
How much...
I'm going.
Why?
Why would you do that, Saa?
Hey, calm down.
Do you even know how tall I am?
I've grown a lot this past year.
It must have been lonesome, for both you and Satoshi.
There's no way you can forget about Meiko, and that's fine.
But I think we're all lonely.
You, Satoshi, and myself, the three of us are together.
I wonder what'll happen.
You mean if they launch the fireworks?
If Menma disappears...
I used to think about it all the time.
If Menma disappeared, Jintan and I would be able to get along well.
But I was wrong.
When Menma really disappeared, Jintan and I only became more distant.
We've grown closer again, but that's only because Menma came back.
That's something to be grateful for.
Huh?
Nothing.
It's Tsurumi.
Yes?
Are you going to the secret base today?
Well actually...
You're with Anjou, right?
Huh?
Yeah, that's right.
You coward.
Tsuruko?
You pushed so hard for making her go to heaven, but now that it really comes down to it you're afraid.
That's not it.
It's really pathetic.
You're afraid, so you run away from Menma and stay with Anjou.
You want to know you're not the only one who's miserable, don't you?
I remembered about that time when Menma called us.
About what she said.
She wanted to ask us to do something for Jintan.
What happened? What did Tsuruko say?
I have a request for you.
It's something only you can do, Anaru.
Why aren't they here?
Goodbye, Menma
It's fine, I'll see them tomorrow anyway.
Let's get started.
I'll go call them.
Wait, Poppo...
Good job setting up.
Tsuruko!
I brought some snacks.
I expected no less from you.
And I brought juice.
I love you, Yukiatsu!
It's a party!
I believed in you guys!
Party, party!
I knew you'd show up!
I'm so happy.
Oh, I love this stuff.
So they've all shown up.
Huh?
I mean...
I feel like the end is drawing closer.
Ahem. We, the founders of the Super Peace Busters, together with Menma...
Skip the introductions.
Sure.
Well then, please come forward Menma, our guest of honor.
Okay. Here.
Thank you for doing this for me today.
And then this!
I'm going to heaven tomorrow.
I want to be friends with everyone
until the very end. Thank you all.
What a fine speech.
Super Peace Busters
Hey Menma, want some of this?
It's all red!
I hate spicy stuff because it hurts.
Let's see, s-pi-cy...
It's really not.
Come on, just try some.
Ew ew ew, my mouth is burning!
Don't you have games or something prepared?
Huh?
All we're doing is eating and drinking.
This is supposed to be our final rally.
We've all come together, so let's do something.
Yay!
What kind of game did you have in mind?
Let's see...
How about we go through that day again?
Huh?
Let's recreate how we met here on that day.
You don't mean...
Yukiatsu.
Don't screw around! What do you want to accomplish by...
Anaru.
Hey Jintan.
Stop!
You like Menma, don't you?
You guys...
Say it.
Menma's here right? Say it clearly.
Yukiatsu.
Say it.
This is too much. You're going that far?
I like her.
Menma, I...
If you run away now it'll all be the same!
Menma didn't make a sound.
She just let out a torrent of tears.
Episode 10
Fireworks
Stop crying already. It's shameful.
I'm a disgrace either way.
That's an idea Yukiatsu instilled in you, isn't it?
Hey. Let's not do this.
I mean, I already know what he would have answered that day.
You'll stay lost without resolving anything even after Menma goes to heaven.
You'll keep losing to a Menma that shouldn't even be there.
Are you fine with that?
You can't understand...
How it feels like to never have the person you like take notice of you...
I do understand.
Because I like Yukiatsu.
Yukiatsu has always been chasing after Menma.
That's the only side of him...
Tsuruko.
I don't know about 'never'.
Once Menma goes to heaven, Yadomi will...
How can you say that?
But Yukiatsu definitely won't choose me.
Because even if Menma goes to heaven, you're the replacement for him.
No way!
That's not the way it is! A replacement? Yukiatsu doesn't think of me that way.
And besides, no matter how rough it is for me I'd never date Yukiatsu.
I like Jintan! I'm not some replacement!
That's right, there's no replacement.
That's why we have to make Menma go to heaven.
Sorry, Jintan.
I really put you on the spot there.
Poppo.
It's just that everything seemed to wind back in time again.
Wind back.
Hey.
Is what you said earlier true?
Huh?
It... it's true.
I like you too.
When I said I liked you, it's not just the kind of liking between friends.
I know. It's the kind of liking that means you want to marry me right?
If I had kept growing up normally like this, I wonder if I would have become your bride.
Even if it wasn't normally...
Huh?
Can't you just stay here instead of going to heaven?
Jintan.
I've gone and said it.
I'm going to heaven.
You know about reincarnation?
If I don't go to heaven I can't do it.
And I won't be able to talk with everyone properly.
But if I come back as a caterpillar...
With everyone... properly...
So Menma, when Jintan said he liked you, how did you answer him?
No.
She wanted to ask us to do something for Jintan.
I already know her answer.
Menma, I...
It's obvious.
Yeah, forget about it.
Let's go to heaven, okay Menma?
Am I not enough for you?
Say Menma, do you know about reincarnation?
Reincarnation?
That's right. Even if your life ends, you can come back as a baby again.
And it may not be as a human. It could be as a baby kitten, or a baby flower.
That's why it's not scary.
That's amazing!
But there's just one thing...
Just one thing...
Wait just a little longer, auntie.
Everyone's going to send up fireworks.
Wait a little longer.
Well then, let's start by outfitting the launch cylinder.
Outfitting!
Menma.
Sorry I'm late.
What? Tsurumi?
You're so cute! You look like you did when you were little.
What's up with that?
I had a change of mood.
That's a lie.
Yeah, it is.
Jintan.
Grab a hold of that.
Like this?
Heave-ho!
Good afternoon.
Oh, you really came.
What the?
Is something wrong?
It's just that I caught a familiar scent.
You called Saa for me, Jintan?
Yeah.
Thank you, Jintan.
Jintan?
It's nothing.
So this is really the end.
Heave-ho.
Here we go.
It's fine like this right?
Our interests are the same as Menma's.
I'll make sure she goes to heaven.
But right now I can still stop her.
Yadomi?
Menma must be happy.
Yeah, right.
I won't let him stop her.
Right now I can stop her.
I can stop her, but...
I'm going to heaven.
Heave-ho!
Wow! You're so strong, Saa!
Yadomi?
Now all that's left is the launch.
This was a job well done.
Hey, does anyone have any last words or something...
Her brother is here.
Oh yeah.
Then I'll just let it out.
It was really fun!
Thanks for everything!
Poppo.
You go too, Jintan.
Let's get this thing going. If it gets too late, it'll bother the neighborhood.
Right.
Jintan?
Is this all right? I can still stop this.
I can stop it.
Wait...
The firework went up.
Wow! A flower blossomed in the sky!
Huh?
Umm... Huh?
Menma?
Is she there?
Hey, is she still there?
Huh?
Hey, the fireworks...
I'm sorry, Menma.
What happened?
Huh? What's going on?
I couldn't help but think this at the time:
"I'm glad you didn't disappear."
aa hanabi ga yozora kirei ni saite chotto setsunaku
The fireworks blossomed heartrendingly beautiful across the night sky,
aa kaze ga jikan to tomo ni nagareru
and time passed as swiftly as the wind.
ureshikute tanoshikute bouken mo iro iro shita ne
We shared so many happy times and trilling adventures
futari no himitsu no kichi no naka
together in our secret base.
I will never forget the hopes and dreams we shared during that one summer's end.
kimi to natsu no owari shourai no yume ookina kibou wasurenai
jyuunen no ato hachigatsu mata deaeru no wo shinjite
I'm sure we will meet again in another August, in maybe ten years time.
kimi ga saigo made kokoro kara "arigatou" sakendeita koto shitetayo
I could feel your heartfelt thanks all the way until the end.
namida wo koraete egao de sayounara setsunai yo ne
And I know it must've been painful to hold back your tears and say goodbye with a smile.
saikou no omoide wo
But those are my best memories.