Kokoro
masshiro PAGE mekuru
I walk through the white pages of my storybook
Incoming Text
tobidasu irodoru hajikeru
that's just waiting to be painted
mangekyou no fuukei
with a kaleidoscope of my experiences
From
Me
To
You
kizukeba STORY wa mada
This story has only
gikochinaku hajimatta bakkari
just barely begun
shinkokyuu wo mou ikkai
I take a deep breath
tabi suru kaze tsutsumikomu you ni senaka wo osu
and the wind wraps around me and urges me forward
aa yawarakakute atatakai kimi no te
Your hand is so warm held within mine
nigiri shimete sono kokoro no oku made todoku you ni
It reaches all the way into my heart
hohoenmi de kumeta nara nigirikaeshite kuretara
I can't see a brighter future
boku wa tada mae wo miteru
than you smiling and taking my hand as well
...Like me.
I wouldn't mind...
if you liked me.
Affection and Annoyance
What the hell are you doing?!
Wh-What?
What did you do to make her cry?
I'm sorry, Sadako.
No, you didn't do anything wrong .
You tried to cheer me up…
No one did anything wrong!
Then why are you crying?
Calm down, calm down!
Let's just leave it at that.
Sadako was finally able to compliment you with open eyes.
With open eyes?
It's Kazehaya.
'Sup!
What are you up—
Kazehaya
(Angry?)
Flamboyant
Dude?
Sadako!!
(Crying)
Wow, this scene!
What, are you both trying to pick her up, Kazehaya?
Wow Sadako, you're so popular having both of them after you!
Th-That's not funny…
Yeah.
What is it, Kazehaya?
Do you like Sadako?
I do.
I like you, Kuronuma.
Problem?
I-I mean…
It's just that…
Are you for real?
He's got to be kidding.
You can't say it like that…
If you say it like that,
it could be taken the wrong way!
What?
Are you saying we would take it the wrong way, Sadako?
No one would make that sort of mistake!
You're overthinking it!
Of course he just means it as a friend!
Duh!
It'll make me want to take it the wrong way.
What's so funny?
Kuronuma.
If it bothers you, you can take it that way.
Kazeha…
Kazehaya!
Come on, let's go, that was the bell!
Oh no!
We have gym next!
Pin's gonna yell at us.
Right, break it up!
Time to go!
Hey, Kazehaya was really angry, wasn't he?
Why did we get involved in that?
Who did?
Was he…serious?
Aw, lunch break is over already?
We'll have to wait until after school then.
Sawako's not here yet.
Neither is Kazehaya…
I ran after him…
but what should I do now?
What should I say to him?
I don't know!
If it bothers you, you can take it that way.
Bother?
Kazehaya has someone he likes.
You don't want to be a bother to him, right?
I was already a bother to him, wasn't I?
I didn't even know he liked someone, yet I wanted to keep him for myself…
I like you, Kuronuma.
I made him say something that could've been taken the wrong way by accident.
Why are you crying?
Was it Miura?
He was just trying to comfort me to be nice…
Then it's because of me?
I-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry you had to look out for me so much.
I'm sorry I caused you so much trouble.
I'm sorry!
Look out for you?
You think Miura does what he does out of affection,
and that I find what I do troublesome?
I did those things 'cause I like you.
I'm not who you think I am.
I don't want you to think I'm lively or fair or whatever.
I've never treated you the same as everyone else.
I like you, Kuronuma.
Do you like me?
But your like is different from mine.
Yeah.
I knew it was like this from the beginning.
You only told me what I already knew.
I knew it, but I still…
Kazehaya and Kuronuma are absent?
What happened?
I like you.
Kazehaya did?
Yeah!
I couldn't believe what I was seeing!
With that flashy guy from class D?
Yeah, the three of them were there.
Sadako was crying.
Kazehaya looked kind of pissed off.
He said that he liked Sadako.
What?
Was he confessing to her?
No way!
But the way you described it, that's what it sounds like!
It does!
There's no way!
I wonder if Sawako's with Kazehaya.
That'd be nice.
Kent!
Do you know where Sawako is?
I…don't know if she's still there, but the last I saw her, she was outside…
Outside?
Yeah, I saw her by the benches during lunch break…
You didn't do something you shouldn't have, did you?
Yano-chin, let's go.
Thanks, for now.
Wait up, I'll come too—
Kurumi!
It's been a while.
I heard it was a huge scene, whatever happened between Kazehaya and Sawako.
Wow, that was fast.
What happened?
Tell me.
I may have done something I shouldn't have.
This is
freaking heavy!
I skipped class.
And school's already over now.
I need to snap out of it.
There's the school festival preparations, too.
I can't be the one slacking off.
But can I really show myself to people right now?
Are you trying to kill me?!
I-I'm sorry!
What are you doing sitting on the ground in the dark?!
I'm sorry!
I was wondering what happened when both you and Shota didn't show up in homeroom.
It's because of love, isn't it?!
How's that? Jackpot?
I was rejected.
I-I was rejected.
What?!
So he went and asked me where you were for that?
What a jerk…
It's okay, don't worry about it.
Forget him, forget him!
What are you doing?!
Ow!
How could you kick your amazing homeroom teacher?!
Why are you sticking your nose where it doesn't belong?
Go away!
What the heck! I was trying to cheer her up!
We were looking for you.
I'm sorry.
What was that all about just now?
What did I hear about finding you and getting rejected?
And…your face.
What did you say?!
We took our eyes off you for one second and what happened?!
I-I'm sorry! I didn't mean to get rejected all of sudden!
That jerk!
What the hell does he think he's doing?!
Hi!
Sawako, you've got it all wrong.
It's kind of too late for me to say this but…
I…
think I thought too much of myself.
I thought Kazehaya treated me just like he treated everyone else,
but was I wrong.
I was overconfident.
I've never treated you the same as everyone else.
I think I've always forced him to look after me.
I started falling for him more and more,
and wanted even more of his attention.
I think he could tell.
Because he went out of his way to tell me I was wrong, that it wasn't like that.
No, that's not it, Sawako—
That's not right.
What? I know, but wait a sec, Chizu. It's not like Kazehaya meant to—
I don't care!
That's just not right, Sawako.
You don't think that we're friends with you just to be nice or something do you?
I-I didn't think of that!
I-Is that true?
No!
If you think that, then it's your fault that Kazehaya's so angry!
What do you mean, of course things are this way?
You have us!
How long do you plan on putting yourself down?
Don't be stupid!
Wait, Chizu!
She's been put down and avoided for so long that she thinks it's normal.
That's really sad, isn't it?
She's a really nice girl.
Chizu snaps when she gets too upset or frustrated.
She's worried about you.
Hey, Sawako.
In the beginning, we thought you were gloomy and strange too.
But now, we know how nice and cute you are.
We love you.
We're able to feel this way because you were brave enough to tell us.
There's nothing different about you, or us, or Kazehaya.
You just need to believe that.
I'm kind of worried about Chizu, so I'm going to go after her.
Wash up and come find us.
Did I…Did I make a mistake?
Chizu!
I can't believe I did that! I'm so dumb!!
It's okay.
I'm sorry, Yano-chin.
You were trying to tell me something but I cut you off.
What was it?
That the girl Kazehaya likes is Sawako.
With things the way they are now, I thought I might as well.
Why didn't you?!
'Cause I thought you said everything that needed to be said.
What you said was the main problem, and maybe things will change now that it's out in the open.
Sawako will do something about this herself.
She's been able to do so herself so far!
It'll definitely be okay.
Yeah, it will.
We're able to feel this way because you were brave enough to tell us.
I guess I should've tried harder then.
Have I been trying my best with Kazehaya up until now?
What about now?
Am I trying my best now?
I…
douka ima dake wa furimukanaide
Please don't look at me right now
yuugure sawagu kaze
The sun's set, the wind's blowing,
furesouna kyouri
and we're so close that we can almost touch
kimi wo mitsumeteru zutto
My gaze has always been fixed on you
kimi ga suki de
I like you
I've always liked you
kono omoi koi demo ii
I don't mind if this emotion is what they call love,
kizu tsuitemo ii
and I don't care if I get hurt by it
nando demo tsutaetai
I just want to tell you, over and over again
kimi ni todoke
I want to reach you
Preview
Just Give Up
Thickheaded.
Cowardly.
Nothing to say.
Next time: Just Give Up.