You still don't know if Jin is alive?
We can't say anything for certain,
but we have faith that he is all right.
Jin was the last child to be born on Altair.
If we have the power to do so, let's avoid losing him.
That aside...
Look at the combat data he sent back from Vega.
Mikage may have been right all along.
About what?
The most powerful Rare Igura we're looking for...
is probably close to the Machine Angel.
I won't stand for this!
We're not authorized to sortie?
They said to stand by until Jin's safety was confirmed.
Well, I'm not going to sit tight and wait.
We're going to Vega, even if we have to go alone!
Yeah!
How beautiful.
I'm a bit envious of Jin.
I didn't think he was so loved by his men.
Who are you?
Brave and loyal soldiers, may you always have hope...
osore
Even if you're scared
living your life   don't give up now   keep moving on
Just live your life, don't give up now, keep moving on
kimi wo dakishimeru nandomo nandomo nandomo
And I'll come for you over and over and over again
ashita boku wa kimi ni deau darou
We'll find each other soon enough
wazukana hoshiakari wo tayori ni
By the faintest glimmer of starlight
boku ni wa kimi ga wakaru yo wakaru yo
I know you, I know you
sen'oku no toki wo koe futari hiraku densetsu no tobira
It's been billions of years, but now we can open the door to our legend
naraku no ao tobikoete
I crossed over the deep blue void
kimi to hai ni naru tame
so I could burn to ash along with you
nagaki rinne wo kanashimi tsurete tabi shitekitanda
I've had a long journey on the vast wheel of fate, gathering sorrows along the way
zenryoku de mikansei kimi no tonari de
I'm not perfect, but I'm giving all I have
kawaita kokoro hodoke chi wo nagasu kedo
If I open my fragile heart to you, I know I'll bleed...
soba ni iru yo zutto yorisotte zutto
But I'll always be with you, always be in your arms
futari hikari no fune ni noru
We'll get on a shining ship of light
kaze no hajimari no oto kanadeyou
And call forth the wind with our voices
My holes!
Someone's filled them again.
You think this was all one person?
Turn Man and Woman
into a Hole New Word
So cold and hard...
I'll find that lonely girl and dig a tunnel into her heart!
You still don't know if it's a girl.
A luxurious restaurant with a breathtaking night view!
Wow!
You're going on a date, Sazanka?
Not me.
But Shrade and Cayenne, ooh...
What about Cayenne?
Oh, nothing.
I just don't have a partner like you do, so...
I have a partner?
Amata.
Amata isn't my partner!
I'll take him if you don't want him.
Neo-Kowloon has some really
charming little hole in the wall places.
That's filthy!
That's a magazine for dirty boys with no standards and inappropriate goals!
Seriously?
"Hole in the wall"? Disgusting!
I never want to see you reading about such pollution again!
Did I strike a nerve?
Maybe...
You didn't find anything in the Abductor wreck?
Correct. We're certain that the machine was piloted, but...
We'll continue our investigation.
Don't take that chocolate donut. I want it.
I'm sorry.
Oh...
It's Shrade.
His tone is getting brighter.
But darkness continues growing in his heart.
You can come in.
You want to tell me something?
Don't be shy.
We can't find any traces of the pilot from that wrecked Abductor robot.
Do you sense anything?
I'm sorry. No, I don't.
But I'm glad you came to ask me.
Just use your power to sense those tones of yours.
Don't go out into battle again.
Are you worried about me?
I just don't need any thrill seekers on my team.
All your dark visions are making you jaded.
You won't be able to hear the sound of your sister's heart.
Mikono?
She's making a lovely sound.
It's expanding in harmony.
The Berlin's gone, though. Why are you still digging?
Digging is my life.
If I stop digging, I'll die.
What are you, a shark?
But seriously, what do you see in holes?
A new world awaits on the other side.
Dig a tunnel through a mountain,
and you encounter new places, new cultures.
And so our world expands.
Dig down to water and make a well,
and people will gather. And so we find prosperity.
That's the story of mankind's progress.
Wow, Andy.
I didn't know this digging stuff was so deep.
So where's the new world this hole is leading to?
The public bath in the girls' dorms.
What?
You could call that a new world, I guess.
It was you!
Of all the girls, it had to be you.
No, perhaps this, too, is destiny!
Our powers are complete opposites,
so they attract with the force of a black hole!
Your big bangs are just waiting to make my universe!
What are you talking about?!
Do you have any idea what you're doing?
Of course I do!
I'm digging a hole! For you!
For me?
YES! A hole to connect you and me!
Stay at least a meter away from me!
I don't want to be dirtied by your taint!
What?
What are you digging all these holes for?
I always have to fill them up!
And just who asked you to fill them?
Those are my holes! I like my holes!
I think there's a hole in your head!
Go away! Get out of my sight!
Go fall into a landfill hole!
How dare you! My holes are my life!
Can you guys stop fighting and help me?
Andy and Mix?
But their teamwork would be full of holes.
What do you hope to achieve with this?
A hole...
A hole?
They say many things about holes.
No holes ventured, no things gained.
Whoso diggeth a pit shall fall therein.
Birds of a feather occupy the same hole together.
Crea is thinking of the Japanese saying "hana yori dango" (boys
before flowers) but replaces "hana" (flowers) with "ana" (holes).
Bros before holes.
No one says that...
So you see, holes can be different things to different people.
And why are you including Mikono?
Her Element power is still unknown.
The donut is an empty space surrounded by a ring.
That's what you said, Fudo.
And Mikono Suzushiro forms the ring
where the donut surrounds emptiness.
The emptiness is not merely nothing.
Within it is all things, even existence itself.
We will see what meaning they can impart to holes.
Why did they pick me?
I'm not like the other pilots. I don't have a power.
But you did okay in the last battle.
I'm sure Commander Fudo and the instructors have their reasons.
NEVER! I won't do it!
Mix!
I'll never Union with him!
Come on, Mix! Everyone has a first time!
Don't be shy. You shouldn't be shy...
I'd rather Union with that green cat than him!
Never! Don't make me do this!
What's the matter with you, Andy?
Union with a girl is your dream, isn't it?
I don't think I trust their reasons.
Andy! Mix! Let's Union!
Let me out! I'm not doing Union with a pathetic hole dweller!
Hey! Take back what you said about holes!
Shut up! There's a hole where your brain should be!
Say what?!
I said shut up!
Everybody calm down!
Aborting the simulation!
I can't do it!
I'm so useless I can't even get them to Union!
Why do I have to be the hole puncher?
It's our punishment for refusing to Union.
It's not my fault! It's their fault for
trying to set me up with the likes of you!
You think I like this? Let me tell you—
Quiet! Just don't talk to me anymore!
Why do I have to deal with men who
might as well have crawled out of a hole?
Come on, do you hate holes or dudes?
I hate both of them! I hate holes and I hate men!
You wouldn't be here if it wasn't for men!
Where would you be if your dad didn't exist, huh?
Don't mention him.
Don't let them get you down, Mikono.
But I could have done better...
I don't think anyone could have gotten those two to work together.
But how come Mix hates guys so much?
Zessica told us something about that...
Hm?
Her dad... was a writer for a magazine?
He wrote reviews and guides about sightseeing attractions.
He met a woman at a little hole-in-
the-wall bath house, fell in love, and...
I see... So that's why she hates holes.
But everyone's been through stuff.
We all get over it and bury our problems.
I suppose, but...
There's a hole in that girl's heart.
And she's been trying to fill it...
Whoa!
Ow! Hey, who put this hole here?
Oh wait, it was me.
Machine Angel, I'll get you and avenge Master Jin!
Mikage! You've manipulated their minds!
Your words hurt me.
I just gave them a little gift.
What did you give them?
A dream.
What are you after?
Do you want the true Eve for yourself?
If everyone admires a single flower,
there's no reason for a whole garden to bloom.
Abductors detected!
All Elements please report to phase one battle stations!
Repeat: All Elements please report to phase one battle stations!
Based on the behavior of the recent Abductors,
it seems that their goals have changed.
They've been appearing closer to the Neo-Kowloon area, too.
There are only three enemy machines.
We should send out a solid, reliable team.
Deploy...
Andy W. Hol as the head.
Roger! Wait, what?
Finally!
With Mix and Mikono.
Wait a sec! I refuse to go with a boy!
Mix! This is a real battle!
Now isn't the time to be selfish!
Go get 'em, Mikono.
Vector X, launching!
Vector Y, launching!
Vector Z, launching!
I've waited a long time for this!
Come on, let's make it a rousing Union!
No!
What?
I won't do it! I won't Union with a boy!
Mix!
I can handle them by myself!
Take this!
Oh no!
Mix!
Andy?
Get over yourself!
I don't blame you for trying to fill that hole in your heart!
But you can't just push away anything that has to do with guys!
It's like you're...
I know! It's like you're in a pit!
What does that even mean?
It means you're not filling the hole, just closing yourself inside it!
You can throw as much dirt as you can, but you'll never fill it!
Because if you want to fill the hole, you have to dig yourself out first!
Let me fill the hole in your heart with the dirt from mine!
Listen up, Mix!
My very first coed Union...
can't be with anyone else but you!
Andy...
Mix, let's Union.
Believe in Andy.
The aura levels of all Elements are rising!
80... 85... they keep going up!
The holes I have to fill are the ones in my heart...
Let's do it, Mix, Mikono!
Roger!
Big Bang Union! Go, Aquarion!
What is this? It's not like doing it with girls at all!
My heart is beating really hard too...
I'm going to make it! I'm tunneling through!
I'm going to expand my world!
I won't let you finish!
Mix!
Out of the way!
Andy!
Fudo!
Element Change!
Amata Sora!
Yes, sir!
Andy!
Are you okay, Andy?
He took the hit for me...
We have to Union right now, Mix!
What? Amata?
Why do you look so disappointed?
Mix, don't let Andy's sacrifice go to waste.
Can't you feel it? The feelings he left behind?
He's still waiting to fill those holes within you.
Mikono...
All right!
Big Bang Union Redux!
Go, Aquarion!
We're connected!
We're connected, and my world is expanding!
This is what Union really is...
Andy?
See? Andy is still with us!
I can't believe it!
But they repulsed each other so violently before!
Is this Mikono's power, Fudo?
Exactly. The power to connect.
The power to connect...
The emotions Andy left behind...
are filling me.
Aquarion Evol!
Union is a type of magic that connects people together!
Of course! It takes the relationships between the Elements...
and creates new powers from their connections!
The Machine Angel!
We'll destroy it right here!
All weapons, ready!
I'm filling Andy's holes!
Absolute Clam!
What happened?
What is this? What is happening?
It's filling in all the openings!
The machine can't handle it!
Whoa...
This is Mix's Element power.
Filling the barrels causes the enemy's weapons to backfire,
dealing damage proportionate to the strength of the attack.
In one move, she fills their holes and digs their graves.
Humans are born from holes, and to holes they return.
This is the power of the living grave!
Jin!
I told you, I was digging holes to dump trash in for the principal!
I said I'm sorry, all right?
I just see a hole and I have to fill it in!
They say the more they fight...
You helped them, Mikono.
Huh?
I think your connection power is incredible.
They were attracted to each other first.
My power doesn't do anything by itself.
Your power isn't for a single person. It's for sharing with everyone.
I think it really fits you.
Ow ow ow!
Amata!
Love is forbidden.
So that's the island where the Rare Iguras are.
kaze ni ubawareta wake janai
We weren't spirited away on the wind
katamichi bun no yuuki de bokura
We knew we could never return, and found the courage
higeki wo ukeireru
to accept the hardship
kokoro ga koko ni atta hazu no kuudou
There's an emptiness where my heart used to be
motto boku ga ookikereba
If only I was stronger
kimi wo mirai wo sukueta darou ka
I could have saved you, and our future...
taisetsu na hito wo mamoru sube ga tatta hitotsu shika motanai
I only know of one way to keep the people I love
sonna anata ga haguretadayou sora
And you left me and disappeared into the sky
anata ijou no hito ni deaenai
I'll never find anyone like you again
tsuki ni aragau nagai furea
A long flare reaches out against the moon
hajimaru mo sezu owaru monogatari
The story ends before it could even begin
kizutsukiuru yawarakasa
So soft, so fragile
tojikometa senritsu kanaderu hodo
I will call up the melody locked away
utau hodo kowareru hodo ni
And sing it until I destroy myself
anata ga koishii
That's how much I love you
Are you kidding? We're getting another new student?
I can't wait to see him!
I can't decide if Amata's top or bottom with him, though...
Next time on Aquarion Evol: The One-Eyed Transfer Student.
Next Time
The One-Eyed Transfer Student