The controls aren't working!
We're being washed away!
This is the rift between the dimensions...
I can hear the moaning of twisted space.
It's the dissonance of despair.
It's only a matter of time before we're...
Shrade!
We have to Union again!
We can't! Your body can't handle it!
Once we Union, I'll be able to hear the scale that the dimensions play on.
Shrade!
Let the flow carry you!
Harmonize with the sounds around you!
Can you feel it, my friend?
This will be my last Union.
Resounding Union!
Go, Aquarion!
Song of Legend
Is everyone here?
We have something very important to tell you.
This is a story of 12,000 years ago,
and of another 12,000 years before that.
An eternal saga.
This is ridiculous!
We don't have time to listen to stories when we could be helping Amata-
What?
What's going on?
We're on top of a book!
This book was always with you.
It has come to us from ages past,
yet too, it has never moved.
It is called the Book of Twin Stars.
Now, at long last...
It shall be opened!
The story begins 24,000 long years ago.
These visions are more lifelike than my Prophecies of Despair!
Let this sword be like a tuning fork...
Its resonance will point me to the exit...
What are those images?
The tuning fork is calling out the memories etched into the dimensions...
Shrade!
Keep watching!
The Dark Angels were humanity's great enemies.
They brought immeasurable
destruction and took innumerable lives.
The footsteps of doom were approaching...
and their owner's name was Apollonius, the Angel of Slaughter.
But by some strange trick of fate, he found love.
Apollonius fell in love with a human woman, Celiane, though she was his enemy.
That's...
The Legendary Aquarion!
Apollonius piloted a Machine Angel to drive away the Dark Angels
and protect Celiane and her world.
But for every light, there is a shadow.
Apollonius' betrothed, the Dark Angel Toma,
both loved him still and hated him for his betrayal.
And there was another.
A small one who sought light from the shadows.
A dog?
It's adorable!
This was the Winged Hound Pollon, Apollonius' companion.
He bore an unrequited love for Celiane, who loved his master.
The sorrowful Pollon made a wish to the night.
"If we were to be reborn, may Celiane and I be reunited."
Many emotions, including Toma's hatred and Pollon's wishes, were left as time flowed on.
The void left by the dead. The sorrow felt by the living.
Joy in the shadows, and madness in the light.
Let us bring them all together,
and wrap them up with beautiful lace.
The noon sun is life, and the nighttime moon is death.
They blur together, until...
Listen closely!
The second chapter is beginning.
These visions again!
They're the same as the ones we saw before.
The Dark Angels returned from their long absence,
and plagued humanity once more.
But humanity still remembered the legend of their salvation.
High Commander?
Why is High Commander Fudo there?
I thought we were seeing what happened 12,000 years ago!
Watch! This is the very center of the legend!
The humans followed their legends, unearthed the Machine Angel,
and used it to fight back.
In Apollonius' place, Aquarion had a new pilot:
a boy named Apollo.
Of course! He was Apollonius!
So he was the reincarnation...
No.
He was actually the reincarnation of...
Kagura! Taking the true Eve for yourself is an act of outright treason!
You no longer have the right to call yourself a citizen of Altair!
Damn it!
I won't let anyone have Silvie!
Forgive me, Apollo...
Apollo was the reincarnation of the Winged Hound Pollon.
Apollon from the legend...
is the reincarnation of a winged dog?
His love, Celiane, was reincarnated as Silvia.
The two were brought together by a twist of fate,
and an attraction formed between them on the battlefield.
But fate can also be cruel.
For the Dark Angel Toma was also reborn into that age.
Toma still bore love and hatred for Apollonius,
and he schemed to destroy the humanity that Apollonius fought for.
But his twisted love brought about the destruction of his own kind.
The Tree of Life meant to restore the Dark Angels
did not bear fruit, but withered and fell back into the earth.
Let's meet again in 12,000 years.
Apollo!
Come, my friends!
Let human and Angel join hands...
and forge a new Genesis for this world!
The poor Winged Hound, Pollon.
For before his love of 12,000 years could be realized,
he would have to be separated once again.
That was the day the world began.
Here, the legend lept forward another 12,000 years,
into the third chapter.
The third chapter?
Does that mean...?
Precisely.
The third chapter takes place now.
The world split!
When the Tree of Life withered, the world fell out of balance,
and the planet was divided in two.
Dark and light. Positive and negative. Male and female.
Two opposite worlds.
The two lover stars separated by the Milky Way, Vega and Altair.
The Earth, and the other Earth beyond the Dimension Gate.
Our Earth...
and its opposite world...
They were originally one?
Perhaps it was God playing dice,
or perhaps some form of quantum entanglement.
The two worlds' fates were linked, despite their separation.
Two worlds that are fragments. Two souls ripped away from one another.
This is the story in the Book of Twin Stars.
Their world wants ours, just like I wanted Amata.
Two worlds bound by fate...
Shrade!
I'm all right.
In fact, I feel good.
I think I can almost hear it.
The final melody I've been searching for.
The two worlds that long for one another sing two melodies.
They're both lonely...
Just like me.
Shrade is lonely?
That's why they're trying to reach each other.
They want to fill the gaps in each others' hearts...
Over the eons, Pollon became Apollo, then a new form.
He was born to a songstress of Vega, Alicia.
However!
Another had reached this age first.
Carrying all his memories from all the ages.
Donar!
This pain...
Apollo was never Apollonius.
He lied to me.
I must have revenge...
I must have my revenge!
He divided the soul of Alicia's child in two,
plotting to use it to take his revenge.
Amata, is that...?
And though Apollo's soul was so divided,
the part of Celiane that loved and became Silvia was reborn into just one life.
Would that be...?
The one who has inherited Silvia's soul.
She is...
Mikono!
Zessica?
Amata really is part of Apollo's soul.
That makes me the intruder.
A world divided into two worlds.
Apollo's soul divided into two lives.
This is a legend of tragedy.
The tragedy has a director.
A soul haunted by his terribly deep love for 24,000 years.
The darkness from the soul that was once Toma.
In this age, his name is...
Mikage.
If there is hope for a bright end to this tragic legend,
it lies with you alone!
That's all I can tell you.
Wait, though!
Isn't the next part written in the Book of Twin Stars?
The end to this war! Something even my Prophecy can't tell!
I will show you.
What?
It's blank!
You must write the rest of the pages yourself!
It's you...
You're finally awake.
I was getting worried.
What's up? You hurt?
No...
Then why are you crying?
I can finally say I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I never realized how you felt.
I'm truly sorry.
I've found it at last.
It took far too long...
but the scales the two worlds play on have come together,
and they exude a brilliant white radiance.
Is it a void in their hearts... or a new world altogether?
Like a pure white score of music...
Listen...
Shrade!
This melody!
This is my final song!
Aquarion's true melody, come forth from nothing!
The song of all beginnings!
To live is to engrave your life.
To hammer the melody of your life into the world!
I will open your path.
I would never have imagined this was possible...
That I could play out my life to help someone...
Shrade!
Could you hear it?
My song...
What's wrong, Cayenne?
Nothing...
I don't know why, but...
I know just how you feel right now.
Legends are written using spilled blood as ink.
No...
Another page of the next legend has just been written.
Amata?
Amata, where are you?
Amata!
I've been waiting for this.
You...
Good girl.
A physical body is such a wonderful thing.
Wait! That's not my voice!
Did you take my body?
You will make a fine vessel.
At last, I can realize my dream.
Give me back my body!
You have to keep your promise.
You...
My name is Mikage.
My domain is the shadows of love.
You should be grateful.
For a Wingless to host an angel is a rare gift.
Reverse!
You can't run anymore, Kagura.
Surrender and hand over the true Eve.
Damn you, Izumo! You're not getting my wench!
This is my smelly wench and no one else's!
Mikono!
Zessica!
I figured it out!
This planet's leader is crazy! We have to beat him or the fighting will never stop!
Zessica?
Call the Wings of the Sun, Solar Aquarion!
Who, me?
You've got Apollo's soul! You can do it!
You can do it...
Aquarion!
It actually came!
The Wings of the Sun!
You dare oppose me?
Now, let's begin telling...
a real legend.
masatsu wo shiranai yasashisa de
With a compassion that never knew conflict
kiri fukai mori ni mayou
The two got lost in the mist-covered forest
futari sennen toozakaru
and drifted apart a thousand years
haiiro no haamonii
An ash-grey harmony
ai to jiyuu wa
Why must love and freedom
naze deau koto dekinai
be fated to never come together
itsuka areno no tsuyu ni naru made
until the day they are but dew in the wilds
kokoro no omosa ai no omosa
A soul is heavy, and love is heavy
zenshin de kiiteita
I listened with all my being
urei kedakai ushiro sugata
As you walked away, sad yet proud
anata no yume wo mamorinuketa nara
If only I had been able to defend your dreams
tsuki ni aragau nagai furea
A long flare reaches out against the moon
hajimaru mo sezu owaru monogatari
The story ends before it could even begin
sotto sora ni oku namida wa
The tears I shed quietly up to the sky
mikan no symphonia
form an incomplete symphony
anata dake ni kimi dake ni hoshi no yuigon
They are the will I leave in the stars to you, only to you
anata ni aitai
I want to see you
All you have to do is close your eyes
to go back to a warm, peaceful morning.
But I have to keep my eyes open.
Life may be a struggle, but I'm holding onto mine.
Next Time