Are you looking for something, Ivica?
Is that all you have to say after making me wait for you, Blanc?
Sorry.
The government is still trying to haggle with us.
They're afraid of us foreigners.
We're just a private company.
But this is terrible.
The sites have always looked like this.
It's the fate of the survivors.
Are you waiting for the girl with turquoise hair to return?
Who else could stop this tragedy?
It's pointless to count the dead in this city.
That's exactly why we—
Why the hell are they flying so low?!
They're going to be in trouble when we get back.
Anyway, let's go. We have our own duties to take care of.
That's true. We don't have time to wait.
Still, it's human nature to keep waiting...
Waiting for the dove to return with a branch of hope in its beak.
Incoming call
Naru
Born Slippy
I had a weird dream.
It felt like the world was going to change!
Change? How?
I don't know if it's for better or worse, but...
I'm sorry.
Naru? Are you all right?
Do you have your inhaler?
Keep your eyes on the road!
Could my body be anymore inconvenient?
Are you're having these dreams because of your spiritual powers?
How would I know?
If you're not even sure that it's going to happen,
why bother taking Noah to a safer spot?
There's going to be a fire! How can I watch him die?!
He barely settled in the forest.
He has no friends or family. I can't leave him alone.
Ao, you understand that feeling, right?
Sorry... Are you mad at me?
Look.
He's there.
Noah!
Are you leaving now?
I haven't gathered all the sea mangoes for Mr. Wong yet.
But poaching is still poaching!
Whatever. Just don't pass out, or the leeches are going to suck you dry!
I know!
If you don't come back on time, I'll call the police!
Oh, come on...
Such a drag.
But you know,
a hundred thousand for delivering the IFO's ECU is easy money.
But Gazelle, are you sure it's a good idea to trust the Japanese army?
And they gave you that weird gadget as well.
Aren't they just playing you for a fool?
Oh, shut up.
We went over this already!
It's the newest beacon controller.
As long as this is online, the Japanese army will lead us safely and soundly to them.
That's what they said.
I'm more concerned with what they didn't tell us.
If you guys aren't interested, feel free to go home.
I'll keep all the money.
Gazelle!
What's wrong? What happened, Gazelle?
I'm okay, but something's on fire.
Looks like my generator's blown.
I need to land. Keep a lookout for me.
Roger!
What was that?
God dammit!
You brat!
The fuck are you doing here, brat?!
What? You nearly killed me because you can't drive!
Try saying that again!
You're a terrible driver!
Wait, Gazelle!
We don't have time to deal with kids!
Pippo!
What the hell are you doing?!
But...
What are we gonna do if the cargo gets damaged?
We won't even see a cent of our money!
Oh, come on...
What's this?
Anyway, just hurry!
If there's a transmitter on the case, the Japanese army will wonder why we opened it!
The Japanese army?
Come on, Pippo. We should hurry.
You're lucky. If we weren't in a hurry...
No luck here, Gazelle.
I've never seen an ECU act like this. I can't do anything about it!
It's your job to do something about it!
Easier said than done...
I've never seen something like this before.
What should we do?
We don't have time.
Hey, where do you think you're going?
You're the kid who lives at Fukai's, right?
You mind lending me an FP?
He must have some spares laying around.
I mean, since he has the money to
raise some random foreign kid and all.
What?
What happened?
The ECU!
The ECU suddenly—
Don't just stare at it!
What the hell are you doing?!
What do you mean "what"?!
You should've learned about this in school!
It's a Scub Burst!
We can't do anything about it. Our FPs—
Where are you going?!
Gazelle! Hey, Gazelle!
What are you doing! We should run away!
This is bad...
This could turn into an ugly mess!
This may have been an ugly mess all along.
I'm already done with today's data...
Sorry, it's time to scramble.
Why can't you call on another team?
We should let the kids rest.
There was a Scub Coral signal.
That happens all the time, Rebecka!
That's true, but take a look at the location.
The Scub Coral signal that we detected 30 minutes ago
grew rapidly in the past five minutes.
We're still analyzing the data,
but it's telling us that the probability of a Secret emerging is 98%.
And this is probably where it will appear.
Don't tell me...
Oh, yes. An area claimed by both the United Okinawan Archipelago and China-Japan.
A problematic place.
You understand now? Will you go if there's a dispatch order?
Naru!
Get a hold of yourself, Naru!
Tell me everything's fine...
Tell me I'm all right!
Calm down, Naru!
That's... the Scub Coral.
We should hurry while we can!
We won't be able to meet up with the Japanese army if we get caught up in this!
I'm afraid that light was emitted by a Scub emergence.
What should we do?
We should withdraw for now.
We should wait.
But...
I understand the risk.
But who would be happy with a giant that can't be used?
We should believe in the people of Okinawa.
We have no choice but to wait.
Hang on tight!
What the heck was that?
Naru, pull yourself together.
Ao...
Where's Noah?
I'm glad!
Ao, what's going on?
I don't know.
But a feeling of sadness is plaguing me.
I repeat. All residents in the Osaki area of Iwato Island must evacuate immediately.
Stay tuned for further updates.
So that thing earlier was really a G-Monster?
This is bad. What should I tell Grandpa?
Iwato Central Hospital
Fukai Clinic
You're late.
I'm back.
The Central Hospital called. I have to go.
I won't be back until tomorrow morning, so go to sleep.
Tomorrow is your entrance ceremony.
So that's all?
You don't have to take care of me.
I can work too.
Don't be foolish.
It's the responsibility of a parent to send their children to school.
Even if they are not bound by blood.
Gramps, will you take my FP?
How is an old man like me going to drive that thing?
It turned into a real mess, so I was worried.
We believed you will deliver it as agreed.
Of course.
Unlike Japs, we keep our words.
Your prickly words.
By the way, there seems to be something missing.
Whatever.
Come on, this is stuff you'd eat at a bar.
All that's changing about me is this uniform...
So why does it feel like something is coming to an end?
You're not going to eat your words, right?
If we get back within six hours, the money's ours!
We never lie!
Yeah, right.
Oh? You sound like you're fine.
You should've nursed me yourself if you were so worried.
Shut up.
Your old man wouldn't give me a break if I went over to your place.
That's always your excuse.
I don't know what your mom did,
but it has nothing to do with you.
You're Ao. It's pointless to worry about all that stuff.
But I'm different...
Sure, you're a foreigner, but nobody's going to die because of that.
That's true...
Just think about how much better you are compared to me.
But...
No "buts".
I've had enough. I'm going to bed.
Naru?
Good night!
Oh, please. I can never win an argument against her since she's sick.
I hope she'll cheer up when I give her this tomorrow.
So? What are we gonna do?
It's not like we have much of a chance.
There's a freaking huge hole in the
ground where it's supposed to be.
That reminds me.
The kid was here, right? Fukai's kid.
That's right.
What if that foreigner kid picked it up?
Should we check it out?
This is really weird.
Something's off.
What's gotten into you?
We were delivering the cargo. Nothing more.
But then the Scub popped up along with a G-Monster.
Now the Japs deployed their army FPs.
What are you talking about?
I think we got up caught in something big.
Yeah, right.
I hope so.
Try listening to the sounds around us.
You can't hear a single bird or even a bug.
Yeah, like that! Everyone smile!
Hey, Naru! What's that?
Yuu, be a good girl and look at the camera!
Look, what's that?
What?
The same thing happened yesterday!
No way!
The Scub shouldn't show up twice at the same place!
Wait, look!
There's more than one pillar!
This is why I told you to leave the first one alone.
This was most certainly unexpected.
I don't mind.
Protecting mankind from emerging unknown creatures
is the job of our company, Generation Blue and our team Pied Piper.
You'll dispatch your team of aces for us?
This is quite the exceptional case.
But because of that, I would like to discuss the price as well...
We've yet to sign a contract and he's moving in?
What's the chief thinking?
And even if we rushed there now, we
wouldn't make it to the Secret in time.
Don't be so edgy.
I can't!
What are you going to do if something
happens to the kids in a pointless fight?
At the moment, I'm more worried
about the children of Iwato Island.
That's true...
Oh God!
Grandpa! Naru!
All circuits are busy now.
I can't get through.
What about the internet?
Connection Error
The internet doesn't work?
Don't just stand there! Run!
Hurry up and run!
Where to?
Just get away from the Scub! Can't you see it?
A G-Monster could show up any second!
G-Monster?
That's the same one from yesterday!
No way... No way...
No way... This can't be...
No way... This can't be true!
Right? Right, Grandpa?
Naru!
We couldn't make up, after all.
That thing... That damned thing!
What the hell's wrong with this thing?
Wait, why is this... glowing?
This is...
Mama...
We've been looking for you.
You had it after all, foreigner.
Give it back.
That's ours.
Let it go!
You little...
You can't have it.
What?
I made a promise.
I don't know what this is, but I'm not handing it over.
Not a chance!
I'm not handing it over to anyone!
To be continued!
takanaru shinzou no koe wa
My heart is racing and beating loud
itsu shika kokochi yoku najinde ite
But that feels cozily familliar
But that feels cozily familiar
kaze ga tsuyoku fuiteite mo
Even if the wind is blowing hard
me wo tsumuranaide itsu datte mae wo muku yo
Don't close your eyes and always look on ahead
nakitaku nattara omoidashite
If you feel like crying, remember
damatte chikaiatta yakusoku wo
The promise we made together
the promise we made together
tabidatsu hinadori no uta
The young birds in the sky sing
ima mo mada umaku tobenai keredo
Though they still can't fly well
though they still can't fly well
meguri meguru toki wo koe
Even if we go beyond the edge of time
hitazura ni tsunaida te wo tadotte
I'll only follow you as we hold hands
kotoba wa
"So I never let you go!" My words
sora ni kieteku bakari da toshite mo
may get lost in the infinity of the sky,
chirabaru hikari no naka de
but among the glittering light
mayowazu ni kimi wo sagashidaseru kara
I can still find you without hesitation
Preview
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
Within the light he discovered through fate,
he found the feelings his mother left for him.
When Ao finds himself in the midst of a battle,
he encounters an anthropomorphic weapon.
What does he see in this vibrating storm of destruction?
Eureka Seven AO episode 2:
Call It What You Want.
Listen to the voice of the children of the stars.