I'll kill you!
Amata!
Cut it out, Andy!
Let me at him!
Why didn't you save Mix?
Don't say that!
Amata was busy saving Zessica!
Zessica!
Now's not the time for arguing!
Focus on getting Mix back!
Get her back?
You think I'd be here if I knew how to do that?
I can't...
After the Gate closed, we couldn't
detect any trace of spatial distortion.
Then how do we save Mix?
Where's the High Commander when we need him?
He sees something.
The fate of our two worlds...
and where to find the seed of destiny that can change it.
Ants...
and their antsy antics.
zetsubouteki ni kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful it's depressing
hanten suru sekai no kattou ni aishiaou
Let's love one another amidst the chaos in this backwards world
bokura ga miteru sekai wa itsudemo sakasama de
This world of ours moves in reverse
A
doushiyou mo nai koto de taigai kimatteku
controlled by forces we can't even touch
A
namida suru hodo kizu tsuku hitomi
There is pain in your eyes so deep I want to cry
A
kokoro de sakebi nagara
Screaming from my heart
A
tada atteitai saigo no futari masarenai mama
The last couple who desire each other cannot be together
A
byouyomi ga kikoetekuru
And time is running out
A
zetsubouteki ni kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful it's depressing
A
sutareyuku doubutsu mitai ni aishiaou
Let's love one another like abandoned animals
A
nakitai kurai kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful I want to cry
A
hanten suru sekai no kattou ni kanjitai yo
Let's love one another amidst the chaos in this backwards world
A
First  Reunion
Mix...
Why did it have to turn out like this?
I never got to hold you in my arms.
I never got to take those big bangs and...
What the hell am I thinking?
I'm such an idiot! I should die! Damn it! Damn it!
Did you eat, Andy?
He's sent back yesterday's, too.
What else can I do for him?
Yunoha...
I've lost someone special. I don't want Andy to go through the same thing.
Yunoha?
Let me take care of it.
It's been a week.
I hope Mix is all right.
How about Zessica?
Taking another day off.
She's really broken up.
I'm so pathetic. I'm an idiot.
Why did you save me, Amata?
I know you won't choose me, so all there is for me here is pain.
That vision again?
Don't be afraid...
What the... what's going on?
Don't cry.
We're the same, you and I. The unchosen.
What do you mean?
You, the unchosen, must know how it feels.
To carelessly take the offered hand, only for it to be snatched away.
I can rip off that hand and give it to you.
I will give you what you desire. I will open the Dimension Gate.
In exchange, I want a promise from you.
Mikono!
Why are you going by yourself to search for the High Commander?
I don't really understand myself.
But he told me...
Mikono Suzushiro, your power is to connect those who are so divided once more.
You connect all the fragmented souls together.
And you're the one who said now's the time for everyone to work together.
Connecting people together is my job.
But that's got...
...nothing to do with this? Maybe.
But I can't just sit and be useless while we lose Mix!
Then I'll go with you!
You're needed here if Altair attacks.
I'm the only one without a combat Element power.
But...
There's something I've had to tell you.
I haven't all this time because I was scared.
But when I come back...
When I come back, I'll say it.
Wait! Mikono!
You don't give Amata a break, do you?
It seems to like that boy, Kagura,
but it growls at the rest of us.
You think it doesn't like me or Amata?
I don't think so.
It's just jealous.
That's just how it is.
If I get to like anyone, it growls at them.
So you do like Amata, Mikono!
I didn't want to get hurt.
But that hurt Amata and Zessica.
I have to tell him.
First I have to connect everybody and save Mix.
After that...
A Dimension Gate has opened above the academy!
What?
So they've finally come out!
That's...
This is unusual.
What?
We've not detected any enemy machines!
That's a Gate!
Andy!
We can go to Altair and take Mix back!
Cool it! This could be a trap!
A trap?
Mr. Donar is completely right.
The enemy is inviting us in.
I will give you what you desire.
Zessica?
With Fudo gone, we can't send Aquarion, our main force, to Altair.
So you're just going to abandon Mix?
I understand how you feel, Andy, but...
So we can't do anything for her?
Excuse me.
Commander! I mean, Principal!
Chairman Crea, this is for you from High Commander Fudo.
A donut?
Eek! Ants!
What?
They're gone?
No.
This must be a message from Fudo.
Perhaps he is telling us, "Don't hesitate! Leap into the ring!"
Into the ring?
"Else you will never get the sweet within."
The sweet... that's Mix!
Orders from the High Commander!
Deploy Aquarion at once!
Roger!
For you, all for you.
I granted your desire and opened the gate for you.
Girl with hair the color of grass,
you will fulfill your promise in time.
And then your turn will come, Kagura.
Vector Y, all green.
Ready to deploy any time!
I'm deeply sorry.
But I will have this seat, my friend.
Cayenne?
But then who's in the Vector?
Shrade Elan deploying!
Shrade!?
I must reach the unknown world and hear its sounds...
to perfect my final melody.
I can't do a coed Union yet. No, I won't.
I'm saving my first time for you, Mix!
Infiltration Union! Go, Aquarion!
Aquarion Evol!
It will take time for that soldier's mind to stabilize.
But the final steps are already complete.
And those piloting talents are extraordinary.
It may not be the result I was hoping for,
but now that we've lost Jin, we could use an extra fighter.
Sir Izumo, the Dimensional Gate has opened!
What? Did Mikage make another move?
It takes an enormous amount of
energy to open the Dimension Road.
Each activation drains the precious little energy left to Altair.
Mikage knows that, and yet...
Something came over! Where are they?
We... we can't detect them, sir!
No mass or heat readings at all!
What?
Is there an error in the Gate?
Just a little longer, Yunoha!
Okay...
This is Altair?
What's up with this place?
The whole surface is covered with metal.
Looks like we can get in from there.
Are those graves? There are so many...
Yunoha!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
But I can only keep them transparent for half a day at best.
We have to find Mix quickly.
The sound of this world is an old woman's rasping wail of grief.
Slow down, Andy!
Hold on, Mix! I'm coming to save you!
Yunoha, you should have stayed with the Vectors.
I wanted to come.
I wanted to see Jin's world with Tama.
Is that Alicia? That's the Skies of Aquaria!
Why are they showing a movie from Earth on Altair?
It's not that weird.
Jin's device had an image of Alicia in it.
Mom... you're somewhere on this planet...
Hey, it's an iVision of Alicia!
Don't see that every day.
Hey, what's the matter with you? You look funny.
Get away, Yunoha!
You almost look like Iguras.
Hey, what are these bags?
Don't touch me!
Zessica!
Creep.
Our Element Suits will attract unwanted attention.
We had best find a change.
This place stinks.
Just keep going, Andy.
There's something else weird about this place.
It appears this city is populated only by men.
Or perhaps this entire planet.
Wait, you think that's why they're kidnapping girls?
Are you all right, Zessica?
My throat's been feeling weird since we got on this planet.
Now that you mention it, mine too.
Maybe there's something in the air.
I can feel it too.
That building over there...
Definitely.
According to the data Jin left for us...
that's the enemy's command center.
Well? We don't know if Mix is in there.
Then let's go and see!
Right.
Wow.
Andy's hole digging power is definitely stronger now.
Andy, wait!
Intruders detected in the hangar block!
All units, phase one battle stations!
We have reports that they are infiltrators from Vega!
We must assume they have Gnis!
Your training may not have prepared you for this type of combat,
so stay hidden and stay alert!
Don't move a muscle!
I said don't move!
Holes?
You'd better watch it.
I don't know if I can control myself.
Now, you're going to be our guide.
Do as I say, or...
I'll put a hole in your body.
There they are!
Damn it!
Andy, Amata! We'll hold them off here!
You two search for Mix!
Be careful, Amata. Don't get into trouble.
Thanks, guys.
Amata...
A crude, ugly dissonance.
I will not allow you to interrupt the melody of love!
Contrary Twister!
They're gone.
Good. Get up.
That wound...
Have you found them yet?
No, sir!
Damn it! Go search area 83!
Yes, sir!
Andy, now.
Stop moving.
Why would you treat my wound?
Shut it. I don't want them tracking us by your blood trail.
Now!
It's a dead end!
This elevator is the only way up the tower.
Then open the lock.
Please, we just want to save our friend!
And I'll do anything to save that friend, understand?
Hurry it up!
Why you...
I figured it out.
I'm not sure why, but you can't kill me.
Amata, get out of here!
But...
If we both get caught, there won't be anyone left to save Mix!
Mix?
I've got this! I'm the immortal Andy!
Fly!
Andy...
What?
The suspected Vega infiltrator is headed into the upper block!
The boy with wings!
The Skies of Aquaria?
That's...
Mom!
Let me go! Give me back my Mix!
Mix...
kimi he tsuzuku sakamichi ni
There were white flowers growing
shiroi hana ga saiteta
on the road on the hill that leads to you
yume kara sameta ato mo kanashii sora miteta
When I woke from the dream, the sky still looked sad
kono kimochi happa no ue ni susunderu
My feelings drift on a leaf in the wind
asatsuyu wo ochiru oto ni mimi wo sumaseteru no
I'm straining my ears for the sound of the dew falling
kamisama anata ga tsukutta sekai wa kanpeki ja nai
God in Heaven, this world You made is far from perfect
koko de wa mainichi koi ga boroboro shindeku
Down here, love is shattered day by day
hajimete suki ni natta no wo anata wa shiranai deshou
You don't know what it's like to fall in love for the first time
chikyuu no uragawa de ii kara soba ni ite hoshikatta
Let it be on the other end of the world, but I wanted to be with him
watashi wo wasuretemo ii kara soba ni ite hoshikatta
Even if You were to forget me, I wanted to be with him
Mix, I want you to fill my holes!
My nostrils long to smell you,
there's a bad feeling in my pores,
and you've left a gaping hole in my heart.
Next Time