Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
namida wo nose
take away your tears
kareru made supiido agete
Speed up until they dry
tobikoete yukeru
I can overcome this
kitto kotae wa
The answer is
harukana ano sora no mukou
waiting beyond the distant sky
kotae ga mitsukaranai koko de wa
There's no answer here,
tameiki wo tsuite sora wo miru
so I sigh and look up at the sky
aoku somerareta hitomi no oku de kagayaiteru no wa
Shining deep within my eyes, reflecting its blue,
doko de mo yukeru, yume wo miteru
is a dreamer who can overcome anything
jibun na no sa
It's me, myself
Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
negai wo nosete
carry your dreams
nobashita te wa asu wo egaku
My hands willl draw tomorrow
mou kowaku nado nai
I'm not scared anymore
namida no ato
The memory of my tears
nijiiro ni somatte tondeyuku
are dyed by rainbows and fly
ano sora no mukou
far away beyond the sky
I hope Noah is okay...
If only we had a space suit for him, then he could tag along too!
This isn't a cartoon. There's no budget for that kind of stuff in real life.
Says the company president's daughter.
Seriously, cut it out.
I wonder if Noah's lonely...
It's been ages since we've seen Naru.
Thank you. I can breathe painlessly now.
Come here.
This is so weird.
When I'm with you, it feels like a weight is lifted off my chest.
You aren't sick.
A part of the Scub Coral is merely growing inside you.
Why are you only kind to me?
Kind? You mean me?
You listen to everything I have to say, and you're always by my side.
I haven't even done anything in return.
You and I are parts of the same being.
We seek truth together and reject this world.
You really are kind.
Because you haven't killed Ao either.
Fukai Ao...
He too will see the truth eventually.
Step into a World
Amazing...
Wh-What is this place?
Below the Headquarters is a facility that processed and reused various materials that are found left inside the Scub Coral.
I believe you have been briefed on this.
OPD...
The Gazelle Corps are an independent and free contractor unit.
I believe we are free to go wherever we want.
However, 100% of your assets belongs to the company,
and we demand complete reports on your activities.
I'm hurt.
We are merely investigating what that USA agent was sniffing about.
As a precaution, of course.
This place is just the ruins of an old experiment area.
It's sealed in fear of contamination.
Contamination?!
And here I was thinking the Quartz would be stockpiled here.
Quartz? There's none of that here.
And you expect us to believe that?
The teams are retrieving them every mission.
And yet there's none here.
I just can't get used to space.
Well then, later.
Huh?
She's bringing the Quartz in.
The stuff from the Scub Coral? Is it all held here?
Silicon?
It's a strategy to look after those who get space sick.
What do you mean, strategy?
Looks like you made it right on time.
A butler? Is that a butler?
This is Chief Hannah from the team Harlequin.
You're Ao, right? I knew it the moment I saw you.
Not hard with his hair.
Uh, Chief...
Just call me Mama.
Everyone calls me that here.
Mama...
Heh, a real alien.
Alien?
Let's have some tea then.
Well, we should have our meeting first.
Hold your horses.
Yuuin...
Okay...
Ivica, you're having coffee, right?
This is why I hate space.
This computer has a Georg too.
I am one and the same, Fukai Ao.
That's because I'm not a computer but an operating sys—
Yep, he's the same.
Ao, come here and help yourself.
That plan pretty much sounds like interplanetary war.
It would appear so.
You think it's that easy to get authorization for something that can intercept ballistic missiles in outer space?
Authorization? There's no need for that.
I've already hacked the connection.
The Fire Cracker, huh?
I'm just reporting. Later.
J. Johansson.
Professor Johansson committed suicide a few years ago.
The Johansson Book he left behind is considered a prophecy by many.
He had an adopted son.
That son is you, isn't it?
Truth.
Johansson said... this world is mistaken.
Even if a fusion explosion were to take place in space as a result of a Scub Burst,
It's started.
it would have no effect on us on the surface.
However, the Scub Coral has materialized in low orbit,
an altitude with a great number of satellites.
A fusion explosion there would result in large amounts of debris.
Because of this, the UN has requested
Generation Bleu to eliminate the Secret.
Hurray! This is nice indeed!
We can deploy with the eyes of the whole world on us.
A real international rescue.
And if we fail, our sponsors will be all gone in a flash.
Why us? They are here too.
The Harlequin are special.
You mean like you—
The official line is that Team Harlequin is our backup.
But the truth is...
They are the protectors of the Quartz!
The Quartz?
Even if the Seven Days of Fire came and the world was burnt to ashes,
they would stay alive.
That's why several families live here.
Seven days of what?
That's not the part you should worry about.
There are really rumors like that.
Even if we all died, they would stay alive?
Just hurry up already!
Our units have limited mobility in space.
We only have one shot to take it out.
Ao, are you okay? Ao?
It's strange... Why...?
This is the first time...
I can't see the path of the wind.
As I thought.
What's the meaning of this?
Ao, return immediately!
Fleur and Elena, stay on standby.
Be good kids.
But the ETA of the Secret is—
Mama's words are absolute here.
What's this path of the wind?
I've seen it all my life.
Ever since I'd first flown when I was little.
Seen what?
You've always piloted FPs following it, right?
Um... everybody can see it, right?
This is probably how Ao sees the world.
What he sees is not wind, it's trapar.
He can see trapar?
It's been revealed that parts of the DNA in his optic nerves are different from ours, right?
But trapar are just particles, only...
25 nanometer in diameter. No human can see them with the naked eye.
But he can see them.
That's why he could play such an active role.
Why?
Why do you know so much about me?
Because you're an alien.
Hey, Elena. Have you ever seen trapar?
Well, my ears can discern who the VA is for an anime character!
That means he sees the world differently from us.
That sounds like a line from an anime.
Not that I know of.
Thirteen years ago, on the 12th April, Japanese time...
12th of April?
Haven't you heard?
Nirvash!
The Americans stationed in Okinawa scrambled instantly.
They recorded this footage.
Mom!
Showing him this out of the blue...
We should've told you earlier.
As you can see, the Mark I, AKA Nirvash, emerged from the pillar of light.
Just like the Scub Coral and the Secrets.
From another world.
Another world?
Where?
According to Johansson...
Don't quote that quack scientist!
Wh-Where is my mother now?
We've told you before. No one has seen her in over a decade...
Why are you keeping it a secret?
After the Scub Burst near Okinawa, just the Nirvash was found without its pilot.
The alien you call Eureka is probably—
As there is close to no trapar in space,
it's inadvisable to dispatch Ao here.
It would be dangerous to make him take part in the action.
As I have suggested previously, he should stay on board of the Protheus
under our custody and assist us in our research.
So even though this battle is in space, you went out of your way to request aid from Pied Piper
just so you can take Ao away from us?
Take away?
That's what you're doing.
I'm opposed to having Ao take part in the fighting.
He might be fighting his own kin!
Mama... Chief...
As long as you're here, you're one of my children too. Okay?
I'm going.
Ao!
I'll show you I can fly.
Ao, I'll guide you.
I bet he's just going to go for a direct attack with a rocket punch anyway.
Thanks, both of you.
Kyrie and Alleluiah will restrain the Secret's attacks.
Nirvash will take that chance to attack the Secret,
destroy it at close range,
and use its recoil to change its trajectory.
He will make contact, or rather, slam into the gigantic Scub Coral,
drop speed, change course, and meet up with the Triton.
Is that all he can do with a full tank?
If he misses the Scub, he'll be headed straight home.
If that happens, we'll bail him out with the Triton.
Is that the Secret?
It's approaching the Scub with the same vector ever since it emerged.
I detect no propelling features, so we can presume it won't change course.
We can't count on trapar in space.
It appears the Secret has detected us already.
Be very careful.
It's like a jack in the box.
I'll draw its attention with some July 4th fireworks!
Please!
Stage two rockets, active!
Go, Ao!
Am I really an alien?
If Mom was one, then I'm also...
Where am I from?
Tell me, Secret!
Ao!
No! We're nearly out of fuel as well!
Please change your vector to rendezvous with the Scub.
I know!
Okay! Pick up Alleluiah and Kyrie, and move to the rendezvous point with Nirvash!
Wait!
What's that?
A railgun?
It's a Japanese satellite!
A malfunction? Now they've done it...
This is bad indeed.
Why?
The Scub changed course and started falling.
Its speed vector is the same direction as the Nirvash's.
So what does that mean?!
My course didn't change.
Because we were moving in the same direction,
Nirvash, the smaller mass of the two, merely slowed down.
The course of the two objects won't change.
Now the gravity of the Earth will pull us down together.
It's simply the conservation of momentum.
What?!
Nirvash won't stop falling!
Ao, get away from the Scub!
Ao!
He's falling...
Fukai Ao...
Am I kind?
We've got the course computed!
They're falling into the atmosphere...
The Scub Coral will burn away
and thank goodness there are no satellites in the way.
We don't need to worry about the debris.
But the Nirvash won't be able to endure the high temperature and will burn away.
I don't want that! Do something, Papa!
Fleur, wait for the Triton to pick you up.
You two can do nothing.
Are you giving up on Ao?!
Because he's an alien?
Fleur!
I'm sorry.
It was impossible after all.
It's not your fault, Mama.
Ao, when you enter the stratosphere, there will be trapar.
You may be able to use that to decelerate.
But if I burn away first...
Don't give up!
You're...
Mom isn't around anymore.
You are all kind to me but Mom's already gone!
And you kept that a secret from me!
So what?
I'm not going to let you die.
Even if I have to burn the Triton away, I'll save you.
We're coming for you! Just wait!
I... I am...
Ao...
Hurry, Ao! Inside!
What's that?
A ship?!
Is it telling me to use the ship as a board?
Let's fly!
My name is Eureka.
Nice to meet you.
Huh? Your hair is...
M... Mom...
To be continued.
takanaru shinzou no koe wa
My heart is racing and beating loud
itsu shika kokochi yoku najinde ite
But that feels cozily familiar
kaze ga tsuyoku fuiteite mo
Even if the wind is blowing hard
me wo tsumuranaide itsu datte mae wo muku yo
Don't close your eyes and always look on ahead
nakitaku nattara omoidashite
If you feel like crying, remember
damatte chikaiatta yakusoku wo
the promise we made together
tabidatsu hinadori no uta
The young birds in the sky sing
ima mo mada umaku tobenai keredo
though they still can't fly well
meguri meguru toki wo koe
Even if we go beyond the edge of time
hitazura ni tsunaida te wo tadotte
I'll only follow you as we hold hands
kotoba wa
"So I never let you go!" My words
sora ni kieteku bakari da toshite mo
may get lost in the infinity of the sky,
chirabaru hikari no naka de
but among the glittering light
mayowazu ni kimi wo sagashidaseru kara
I can still find you without hesitation
Preview
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
Ao unexpectedly gets to spend time with his mother on the Gekko.
Ao is confused by her eccentricity.
The truth she tells wakes a storm that shakes this world.
Eureka Seven AO, episode 13: She's a Rainbow.
Listen to the voices of the children of the stars.