Kokoro
masshiro PAGE mekuru
I walk through the white pages of my storybook
Incoming Text
tobidasu irodoru hajikeru
that's just waiting to be painted
mangekyou no fuukei
with a kaleidoscope of my experiences
From
Me
To
You
kizukeba STORY wa mada
This story has only
gikochinaku hajimatta bakkari
just barely begun
shinkokyuu wo mou ikkai
I take a deep breath
tabi suru kaze tsutsumikomu you ni senaka wo osu
and the wind wraps around me and urges me forward
aa yawarakakute atatakai kimi no te
Your hand is so warm held within mine
nigiri shimete sono kokoro no oku made todoku you ni
It reaches all the way into my heart
hohoenmi de kumeta nara nigirikaeshite kuretara
I can't see a brighter future
boku wa tada mae wo miteru
than you smiling and taking my hand as well
Misunderstood
About what I said that day...
You don't need to worry about it.
Forget it.
What did he mean by that?
That what he said before wasn't important?
I guess he must've meant that.
I guess that much should have been obvious.
It should have been obvious, but...
I considered myself the closest to you out of all of the guys.
But that's not necessarily true.
I can't stop thinking about what he said,
and how I should've answered him.
I still don't know.
Forget it.
I shouldn't be this upset.
It makes no sense for me to be this upset.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm the only one who thought it meant something else...
I was only thinking of myself.
I'm so embarrassed.
What is it?
What did we have to come all the way out here to talk about?
Don't be like that!
I'm finally in the same class as the popular
Kazehaya. It's only normal to want to talk to you!
Come, come. Have a seat.
What do you want me to say to that?
Oh come on. Just sit down!
So how many times have you been
confessed to? Do you have a girlfriend?
No.
Don't be like that!
I really don't. What do you want?
Sadako's been sort of an outcast since freshmen year, hasn't she?
Don't you think it'd be better to leave her alone?
I've heard that you can't stop helping people like her,
but don't you think you're actually doing more harm than good?
What are you trying to say?
You call Kuronuma an outcast and then
say that I can't leave outcasts alone.
That has nothing to do with anything.
Sorry. Did I hit a nerve?
Don't be so angry!
Let's see a Mr. Lively Smile! Smile!
Irritated
Whatever, I don't want to hear it from you.
I feel sorry for her.
You shouldn't involve yourself with her so much.
She's finally being accepted in class.
But if the girls start getting jealous of her
because you pay so much attention to her,
she'll become an outcast again.
That would defeat your purpose too.
You shouldn't do that to her.
Why are you telling me that?
Even if that happened, I would take care of it!
There's a reason why I do the things I do!
What do you know?!
But you know,
the more you do, the more she'll stand out as a target of jealousy.
She has all these false expectations. I feel sorry for her.
You keep saying that. Why do you feel sorry for her?
She's trying her best.
When has she ever had false expectations?
You just don't understand.
You and Sadako have wildly different expectations.
But you're not close enough to her to see that.
What do you mea—
I can't say any more than that.
Otherwise I'd be giving away a girl's deepest secrets.
You don't want to make things difficult for her, do you?
She's trying so hard.
I don't need you to tell me!
As long as you know.
Thanks in advance then.
Hey! You're so popular, yet you don't have a
girlfriend. Does that mean you like someone?
I do!
You should go out with her!
Should I help you get her?
No!
Absolutely not!
What the heck was that?!
But you're not close enough to her to see that.
What don't I understand?
I'm not close enough to her?
What the hell?
Wh-What do you think?
It looks good.
Seriously?
Seriously!
Score!
Really, really?
Yes!
So it's like a relatives-only ceremony?
Yeah. They're not even inviting their coworkers,
so I assumed that I wouldn't be invited either.
What? No way.
But then Toru called me and told me that I had to go.
You're like one of the family!
Were you happy he called?
Of course.
But if I'm going to go, I have to look good!
That's important.
Don't worry. You'll look great in that.
Thanks.
Hey!
Yoshida?
Look what I have!
I went shopping and couldn't help myself.
Yano has great taste. I wish I could've shown Sawako too!
Did Sawako go home yet?
Yeah... I think.
What kind of answer is that?
Hey, do you think Kuronuma and I are really that different?
Do I really not understand her?
No, I don't really think you do.
He doesn't even know that Sawako likes him!
Why are you asking all of a sudden?
It's nothing.
Just something someone said to me.
Your shoelace is untied.
I didn't think that at all.
I actually thought I understood her better than just about everyone.
It's like...
Like, people have had the wrong idea about Yano-chin and I before.
We've dealt with our share of gossip and lies,
but maybe not as much as Sawako has.
And Ryu too. He's always been fourth to
bat... always the clean up guy, right?
The upperclassmen on the team are really tough on him sometimes.
Yeah.
In that respect, in terms of experience,
you're probably the most different from her.
See you.
What's up with him?
Did something happen with him and Sawako?
Honestly.
Wow, Sawako ran a review session?
Yeah, supposedly she was really good at explaining things!
It's just like Kazehaya to plan something like that.
Actually, he didn't.
That loud, flamboyant guy did it!
His name's Kent!
Yeah, Kent supposedly volunteered her
for it right in the middle of class!
Miura...
G-Good morning!
Don't over think, don't over think!
Impossible.
Morning.
Joe!
Morning, Kazehaya!
I messed up again.
This is how it used to be.
It used to be like this, but...
Just now, I kind of felt like he was avoiding me.
What am I thinking?
What the heck was that?
Entry Prohibited
What's going on?
What did you and Kazehaya talk about
yesterday that made things today so awkward?!
If anyone else saw this, they'd
definitely think Sawako's being bullied.
So basically, you spoke with him twice, and the first time...
First Time
I considered myself the closest to you out of all of the guys.
Second Time
Forget about what I said that day.
And the second was like that. Correct?
Correct.
He's getting impatient...
And you! Why did you give
chocolates to everyone but him?
That was such a good chance!
You two even went to the shrine together on New Year's!
You could've just said it was in thanks, like you always do!
He gave you his contact info, didn't he? Didn't he?!
Hey, Yano-chin!
It's not that hard to meet up with him! Or to give
him chocolates! Any excuse to do it would've worked!
Oh...
I-I'm sorry. I went too far.
No, it's not that. I just don't know what to do anymore.
I couldn't bring myself to give him chocolates just in thanks.
I can't bring myself to contact him either.
I'm so nervous when I'm around him that I can't even greet him.
I'm scared.
I'm so embarrassed...
I don't want him to hate me.
I can't stop myself from being selfish.
You aren't the only one who's scared.
Sawako, would you really like things to stay the way they are now?
If you decide not to do anything just because
you're scared, things will stay this way forever.
If you don't want that, then you need to do something about it.
Ayane...
Chizu...
Th-Thank you...
It's not something that you can do in an instant.
So just calm down and think about it for a bit.
Yes.
Whoever's on duty today for year 2 class
D, report to the office immediately!
Duty?
I didn't know what we were going to do when Sawako started crying.
But you knew exactly what to say.
... Nakamura from the class next door?
That hurt! What's your problem?!
That's my line!
Drop your act. Stop avoiding Sawako.
What?
What's going on?
No idea.
I'm not avoiding her!
Then make it seem like you're not!
She's used to people avoiding her so
stop giving her reason to suspect it.
Bye.
Yano-chin!
Darn it! Everyone just keeps saying whatever they please! Jeez!
Poor guy.
What's wrong? You seem to be in a pretty bad mood.
Yeah, well...
That's bad. I lost my temper.
Lost your temper?
I just felt kind of bad for Kazehaya too.
Why do you feel bad for Kazehaya?
'Cause... I mean, the girl he likes
acts like she's super scared of him...
What?! Kazehaya likes someone?!
What about Sawako? This is bad.
But Yano-chin, Kazehaya cares about Sawako too!
Like yesterday!
Yesterday he—
Wait, Chizu.
Kazehaya likes—!
Your voice is too loud!
What was that?
Then what's the problem?!
There isn't one! That's what I've been saying!
Then this is great, isn't it?
Let's just tell him!
Kazehaya!
Wait!
Do you think Kazehaya's the type who
likes people interfering in his business?
Oh right...
In middle school...
Hey Kazehaya, Eri says she likes you.
Are you making fun of me?
No, for real!
Then why are you the one telling me and not her?
Totally
Serious
Wow, he said that?
This is bad. If we tell Kazehaya and he thinks she
asked us to do it, it'll make things worse for her!
Wait! We can tell Sawako and get her to confess to Kazehaya!
Wait!
If we tell Sawako and force her to
confess, they might start going out.
But would that really be for the best?
If Sawako's still afraid of him?
They'd be a couple in name only.
Their actual situation wouldn't change.
But...
I don't want Sawako to date him while still feeling inferior to him.
I want her to come up with the strength to confess to him on her own.
They both like each other. It'd be wrong for her to
feel like he's just dating her out of pity or kindness.
Yeah.
Now that I think about it, even if we did tell
Sawako, she probably wouldn't believe us.
You guys are so nice to me!
That too.
But wait, yesterday...
No, I don't really think you understand her.
You're probably the most different from her.
Different... Different... Different... Different...
I'm the one who didn't understand.
Oh right. You were saying something about Kazehaya?
What? Kazehaya? No, not at all!
Oh no! If I don't fix this, Yano-chin'll kill me!
What? You went to the cursed review session?
How was it?
It was amazing!
Just like the rumors said!
Like...
Losing five kilograms in three days!
Amazing?
What?
Th-That can't be healthy...
Wow Sadako!
They're complimenting you!
Sada—
Wow...
You're amazing, Sadako!
Will you hold one today too?
See? You've got to be more confident!
Sadako, thanks for yesterday.
Oh no, don't thank me!
Where did you get that plant from?
That's a medicinal herb I'm growing in the garden.
Medicinal herb?
Garden?
Yes!
You really helped me back there.
... the more you do, the more she'll
stand out as a target of jealousy.
What... should I do?
douka ima dake wa furimukanaide
Please don't look at me right now
yuugure sawagu kaze
The sun's set, the wind's blowing,
furesouna kyouri
and we're so close that we can almost touch
kimi wo mitsumeteru zutto
My gaze has always been fixed on you
kimi ga suki de
I like you
I've always liked you
kono omoi koi demo ii
I don't mind if this emotion is what they call love,
kizu tsuitemo ii
and I don't care if I get hurt by it
nando demo tsutaetai
I just want to tell you, over and over again
kimi ni todoke
I want to reach you
Preview
The Person I Like
He's the one person whose eyes I can never meet.
Next time: The Person I Like.