I can't stand that noise.
That flying power...
I'm sure I know who he is.
He who?
Mikage! What are you doing here?
Don't change the subject, Izumo.
Who is "he"?
Fine, I'll say it for you.
He's the pilot of the Machine Angel who unsealed the forbidden Union.
With golden eyes and amber hair that flutters in the breeze.
A young boy who resembles our sleeping Eve.
osore
Even if you're scared
living your life   don't give up now   keep moving on
Just live your life, don't give up now, keep moving on
kimi wo dakishimeru nandomo nandomo nandomo
And I'll come for you over and over and over again
ashita boku wa kimi ni deau darou
We'll find each other soon enough
wazukana hoshiakari wo tayori ni
By the faintest glimmer of starlight
boku ni wa kimi ga wakaru yo wakaru yo
I know you, I know you
sen'oku no toki wo koe futari hiraku densetsu no tobira
It's been billions of years, but now we can open the door to our legend
naraku no ao tobikoete
I crossed over the deep blue void
kimi to hai ni naru tame
so I could burn to ash along with you
nagaki rinne wo kanashimi tsurete tabi shitekitanda
I've had a long journey on the vast wheel of fate, gathering sorrows along the way
zenryoku de mikansei kimi no tonari de
I'm not perfect, but I'm giving all I have
kawaita kokoro hodoke chi wo nagasu kedo
If I open my fragile heart to you, I know I'll bleed...
soba ni iru yo zutto yorisotte zutto
But I'll always be with you, always be in your arms
futari hikari no fune ni noru
We'll get on a shining ship of light
kaze no hajimari no oto kanadeyou
And call forth the wind with our voices
Call of the Wild
Altair has lost all its women.
We, its denizens, are on our way to extinction.
We began investigating Vega, hoping to find the solution.
And so,
we formed a plan to capture Rare Iguras,
women who could withstand Altair's environment,
and use them as Eves to bear the future of our world.
One of the candidates was that same sleeping Eve: Alisia.
But when subjected to dimensional
travel, she fell into a deathlike sleep,
and hasn't awakened since.
Now she's just used trash.
While we returned to Altair, she bore a child,
and left it on Vega when we came back for her.
But that's not important.
She couldn't be our True Eve.
She'll just sleep in there forever.
Nothing but a doll for you to gaze at for comfort.
A wingless butterfly.
For comfort?
How sad, Izumo.
The scales of a wingless butterfly
are nothing but a mirage.
So we might as well...
put an end to this long dream.
Mikage!
You will not lay a hand on Alisia!
Then tell me, Izumo.
How would you make this dream end?
Jin has infiltrated the Machine Angel's nest!
We can choose from the Rare Iguras who pilot it!
Did you know, Izumo?
On Vega, butterflies are a symbol of rebirth.
Thus, forbidden love shall be reborn.
Oh, Kagura.
You're such a beast.
Wonderful, Kagura. More.
I can feel it roaring within you.
Soon your past will be unleashed.
Every bit of it, not a drop left behind.
Yes, those memories of Apollon and Silvie sleeping inside you.
Silvie is so close to your heart.
She sighs delicately, and her voice is so sweet...
She could bring bliss to the heavens themselves.
Following her warmth, a love has been reborn countless times.
You want that love, don't you?
You want to have the forbidden Union, don't you?
Kagura!
More. Want it more.
Even more!
Perfect.
You are a hungry beast, howling for love.
Go, beast of love.
Go out and find your love, and sate your hunger.
An animal?
Izumo...
I don't care about the revival of the Rare Igura that will bear Altair's future.
I want the rebirth of the Machine
Angel of Genesis slumbering in Vega.
Who are you?
Just remember this.
I will never trust you.
And if you ever try anything again,
I'll get you.
What was that power?
Will Akbarjin Batbayar please come out?
Now, no more trying to sneak into the girls' dorms.
Cayenne, you pointed a gun at your classmates.
Stay in there a bit longer and think about what you've done.
What is that?
I... I thought you liked Alisia, so...
That's supposed to be Alisia?
It's not perfect, but...
But at least the face?
I'm sorry!
Where are his manners?
Akbarjin Batbayar...
is an impostor!
I see no problem here.
He did pass Neo-Deava's final tests.
But...
What we need is—
The power to isolate.
Didn't Yunoha say she understands how Jin feels?
Yeah. There's a lot we don't know about him,
but at least he doesn't seem like a bad guy.
If we got to know him better, we could ask him,
and get to understand him better.
Yeah, understand...
Mikono, I have to...
I want to know...
I have to ask...
About him...
About that man...
His eyes looked so lonely.
Forgive him? For what?
Like a stray dog.
Sorry we're late!
You would not believe the lines!
Hey, what's with you two sitting together and moping?
Nothing...
I forgot my juice!
Can I have a sip?
Public indecency!
Hey, that's an indirect kiss!
An indirect kiss?
Can I try some of yours too?
Fine.
Man, Zessica, you're really thirsty, huh?
Are you all right?
Yeah, but...
Something's in the hangar!
Kagura?
Close the gate!
Yes sir!
Don't let Kagura get to Vega!
Kagura...
Let me give you a flower for your journey.
I pray that the fire of love in your eyes
sheds light on the Machine Angel of Genesis.
So the time has come.
I don't care how thirsty you are!
Don't do things like that when people can see!
Why don't you leave a pot of barley tea brewed?
I don't like barley tea.
Fine, then black. Or Oolong.
It doesn't matter, just don't do that again.
Hey, where are you going?
Back to the dorms.
Don't you have afternoon classes?
Hey, Zessica!
I tried to stitch the inside of the hem evenly,
but it didn't work very well...
So bittersweet...
I think it's great.
I hope Jin opens up to her.
You think this isn't going to affect you?
Listen, the ladies are always thirsty for love.
Remember Zessica at lunch?
What does that mean?
If you want it, you gotta dig.
Dig to the well down in Mikono's heart.
You see?
Mikono's...
But I can't. You know love is forbidden.
It shouldn't be an issue when this war with the Abductors is over.
But you'd better reserve her for then.
Reserve?
Mikono's a cutie.
If you stall, someone else is going to take her from you.
Mikono, can I talk to you?
You're gonna do it right now?
Well, he is the second hole digging bro.
He's standing up for himself.
What?
Kagura!
You've lost your senses. I can't let you go to Vega.
Who dares?
Kagura! Get out of the Mithra and go back to Izumo!
Damn you!
Stay out of our way!
Yo, Izumo, you old fart.
You want Ianthe to get smashed, or you want to open the gate for me?
Make your choice!
How can this be? Kagura's combat abilities have increased by an order of magnitude!
Blooms out of season, but falls in a blink.
Such a flower is the Kagura camellia.
Do you understand, Izumo?
All I do, I do for love!
What?
All units are out of the line of fire!
We're clear!
Open fire!
Give me...
my wench!
Kagura...
Let me awaken your love!
What's she have that I don't?
That Mikono...
Apollon...
Silvie...
What's the matter, Mikono?
Nothing.
So what did you want to talk about?
Um... it's about that guy...
Someone else is going to take her from you.
No, wait! It's not like that?
It's not?
Wait, that's not what I meant!
Um... so...
Oh no!
Amata?
C-Can you look that way for a second?
Please!
Um... I... not right now, but...
Yes?
After the war with the Abductors is over,
would you...
Scream for me, Kagura.
Your love may not be with you now,
but you can change everything with a mere scream.
You can reverse everything.
It's cold.
Their blows... feel cold.
Hold still, Kagura!
It stinks.
I want to kill that wench.
I want to kill her,
then take her in my arms...
and crush her!
My...
Silvie!
Magnificent!
Will you...
Mikono?
What is that power?
Mikage! Is this your doing?
You wound me.
Kagura is merely answering the call of the wild.
Now go, Kagura.
To the holy land of love!
kaze ni ubawareta wake janai
We weren't spirited away on the wind
katamichi bun no yuuki de bokura
We knew we could never return, and found the courage
higeki wo ukeireru
to accept the hardship
kokoro ga koko ni atta hazu no kuudou
There's an emptiness where my heart used to be
motto boku ga ookikereba
If only I was stronger
kimi wo mirai wo sukueta darou ka
I could have saved you, and our future...
taisetsu na hito wo mamoru sube ga tatta hitotsu shika motanai
I only know of one way to keep the people I love
sonna anata ga haguretadayou sora
And you left me and disappeared into the sky
anata ijou no hito ni deaenai
I'll never find anyone like you again
tsuki ni aragau nagai furea
A long flare reaches out against the moon
hajimaru mo sezu owaru monogatari
The story ends before it could even begin
kizutsukiuru yawarakasa
So soft, so fragile
tojikometa senritsu kanaderu hodo
I will call up the melody locked away
utau hodo kowareru hodo ni
And sing it until I destroy myself
anata ga koishii
That's how much I love you
That day at the movies was when we first met.
I've constantly been in flight ever since then.
I'm so embarrassed!
Next Time
Skies of Aquaria
Next time on Aquarion Evol: Skies of Aquaria.