Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
namida wo nose
take away your tears
kareru made supiido agete
Speed up until they dry
tobikoete yukeru
I can overcome this
kitto kotae wa
The answer is
harukana ano sora no mukou
waiting beyond the distant sky
kotae ga mitsukaranai koko de wa
There's no answer here,
tameiki wo tsuite sora wo miru
so I sigh and look up at the sky
aoku somerareta hitomi no oku de kagayaiteru no wa
Shining deep within my eyes, reflecting its blue,
doko de mo yukeru, yume wo miteru
is a dreamer who can overcome anything
jibun na no sa
It's me, myself
Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
negai wo nosete
carry your dreams
nobashita te wa asu wo egaku
My hands willl draw tomorrow
mou kowaku nado nai
I'm not scared anymore
namida no ato
The memory of my tears
nijiiro ni somatte tondeyuku
are dyed by rainbows and fly
ano sora no mukou
far away beyond the sky
Everything has finally calmed down.
What's going on?
Is he out of his mind?!
Chasing terrorists isn't our job.
Destroy the Secrets before a fusion explosion.
That's the mission of IFO teams.
We don't have any spare time to take on extra tasks.
That much should be enough for him, don't you think?
What is his punishment?
This is unprecedented, but we're considering something serious.
How about a verbal warning?
That's not even a punishment!
You agree?
We mustn't forget about what happened with team Goldilocks either.
It's decided then.
We'll trust you and we won't persecute this any further.
IFO pilots are like my children.
A father should trust his children.
Father, huh?
You have no right to say that.
One Nation Under a Groove
What is that guy doing?
Weirdo.
Sign: Fleur Blanc's Official Blog — First Contact
Hey, Ao!
Shopping?
Hey, miss, give me a large cup of hot generation coffee!
What do you want?
Why are you guys following me?
I wonder why...
Anyway, just stay away from me.
Was that supposed to be threatening?
Are you keeping Ao under surveillance?
You should be more discrete about it. It's pretty obvious.
We've been ordered to do it like this.
You're putting pressure on him by being obvious?
That's not something you guys could come up with.
The president's orders, isn't it?
I heard you're not getting along well with your dad.
Ao too.
He's not a big fan of his dad.
We received an official request.
You're to mobilize immediately.
Understood.
Faisal Arabia, huh?
It showed up at a troublesome spot again.
The Allied Forces is contacting you, President.
Speak of the devil.
I'll take it in my office. Forward it there.
You lost a team in Columbia.
Then there was a terrorist attack.
You're piling up losses, Cristophe.
I'm sorry for the trouble caused, Secretary of State.
I don't even want to think of what's coming.
What do you mean?
That Nirvash of yours.
Some of the senators are complaining that it's the lost Mark I,
which was built with our precious tax dollars.
They are trying to pressure the President by using the mass media.
It's election season. They won't be picky with methods.
I see.
However, Nirvash and the Mark I are two different things.
I know.
But will the US government believe what you say?
So Faisal Arabia, huh?
It's still quite far away.
Should we prioritize Quartz recovery?
And what would we do if the enemy accelerated?
Well...
The moment the Secret showed up, our possible courses of action became limited to one.
Wait, so they were tailing me by the President's orders?
Seems so.
I see.
And he went on about fatherly trust and all that.
He doesn't mean what he says!
Oh, he said that to you too?
IFO pilots are like my children.
Is it a good idea to say that in front of his daughter?
His daughter?
Huh? We didn't tell you?
Fleur is the President's daughter.
Enough chatter.
We've confirmed the Secret.
This Secret is very similar to the one spotted in 1752 in Philadelphia, America.
At that time, lightning caused serious
damages to places the Secret passed by.
The phenomenon we call "lightning" is the result of the difference in ionic charge exceeding a certain—
The operation is cancelled. The Triton is to return immediately.
What's going on?
The President's orders.
The President? What kind of an order is this?
Turn the ship around!
Chief! You can't do this!
Chief! Chief!
Chief!
Understood.
It's me.
He made some sort of deal in the background.
That's the only explanation.
If that's the case, the only one who can put
pressure on the President is the US government.
Why would America...
Faisal Arabia, the location where the Scub appeared, is the most prominent anti-US country in the Middle East.
America, on the other hand, antagonized Faisal Arabia as a supporter of terrorism,
making the two countries being constantly on the verge of war.
In the background of Faisal Arabia's anti-US
position is the internal opposition of royal—
If a fusion explosion occurred, it would seriously damage the enemy country,
and, at the same time, prevent the establishment of a plant coral.
That's why...
Are you kidding me?!
Why would the President agree to such a thing?!
The deal must somehow be beneficial to the company.
That's not it! The President must be—
Rebecka.
Telling us to turn back here...
is telling us to watch them all die!
Fleur?
Elopement?!
I hate my father.
You're the same, right, Ao?
I heard about it from Gazelle.
We're similar, I guess.
That's weird.
Why do you work for your father's company if you hate him?
Five years ago, Maman and I got into a traffic accident.
If one of us donated our internal organs to the other, the other could survive.
When the doctors told my father that,
he chose me... and killed Maman.
I loved Maman.
If he had made the other choice back then, Maman would still be...
I hate my father for making me live with this burden.
So I do what annoys him the most.
Chief...
Let us take a look at inside Faisal Arabia.
These are footages of the Abuha region where the G-Monster first appeared.
The governments of Britain, France, China and other countries
Return to the Triton immediately.
After seeing these footages, the public
demanded that Faisal Arabia must be helped.
have voiced intent of immediate aid to the stricken country.
The Allied Forces had no choice but to agree.
That means...
Our return order was revoked.
We are resuming the operation.
They won't have it their way!
Let's show it to America and our stupid President!
"Stupid President"...
This has to be a complete victory, right, Miss Fleur?
Right, Ao!
So passionate!
You two should gattai!
180 seconds until we reach the combat area.
We've got visual on the target.
Putting it on screen now.
The lightning is merely a side effect of the
expulsion of ionized particles from the Secret.
A Secret normally doesn't attack IFOs as the trapar field shields them.
However, the lightning is an electric discharge
independent of the Secret's intent, so be careful.
The lightning can strike outside of the ZOA.
The IFOs are equipped with electricity
discharge shields for immediate protection,
but if you get hit directly, the lightning may cause system errors.
Be careful of this as well.
You're just telling us to be careful, but what exactly are we supposed to do?
Dodge them.
He makes it sound so simple.
Leave your complaints back in the ship.
Let's get this done.
You're outside of the Zone there.
A hot day in Little Russia...
full power!
Next!
The amount of charged particles is increasing by 250% per second.
The charged area is likewise growing.
All units, retreat!
No way!
Elena, respond! Elena!
Nirvash and Alleluia, wait for my orders.
But...
Our strategy won't work without Kyrie!
Chief, the Secret!
The Secret has emitted all charged particles it had stored up, and has started lifting.
It is expected to stop in 75 seconds.
A drop is expected. The destination of its trajectory is...
The Scub Coral!
Is it going for a direct impact?!
Operation cancelled! Return immediately!
But!
The situation has changed. We can't help it.
We can help it!
We lose if we retreat!
We can't lose to them!
Listen! Calm down!
But...
Miss Fleur! Fleur!
Fleur, come back! Fleur!
T-minus 115 seconds until fusion explosion.
Miss Fleur, please respond!
Miss Fleur!
Alleluia is too lightly armed for this!
I don't want to lose this fight.
I absolutely cannot lose this fight.
I don't care about what happens to me.
The Secret has reached 7500 feet above Faisal Arabia.
It has lost its thrust and is beginning its descent.
I don't like that.
I hate my father too.
But I won't risk my life for him.
I'll stay alive no matter what and give him a good beating.
So you mustn't die either, Fleur!
We've got no time.
Let's do this, Fleur.
Nirvash and Alleliua have reached the Secret.
T-minus 25 seconds until fusion explosion.
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
six, five, four, three,
two, one...
Georg, how's Alleluia and Nirvash?
Alleluia and Nirvash are both intact.
Life signals have been detected, so it is safe to assume the pilots are unhurt.
Fleur, you okay?
Yeah...
I'm alive.
Yeah, we're alive.
Where are you two going?
To see the stupid President.
We must report our victory to him.
I wonder what face he's making...
Maybe the Americans spanked him and he's crying!
How is the stupid President going to welcome us?
Ouch! Don't pull so hard!
Look at this.
Oh, look who we've got there.
Hey, guys! We look awesome, right?
Those costumes...
Both of you have left your designated locations without permission during an operation.
I'd like to talk about that.
When we broadcasted that video,
there were immediate reports that we're not there despite an official request.
The Americans called of course.
They thought we're the source of such reports.
And what did you say?
Of course I told them I didn't know anything about it.
By the way, why did you stay despite receiving the return order?
Engine troubles. We had some difficulties fixing it.
Where are you headed?
The children are waiting.
The President was behind those footages...
He lied to the whole world.
But we were able to go back because of that.
We saved lots of lives.
Fleur, did we really win?
Wait a second, when did you start dropping the "Miss"?
To be continued!
takanaru shinzou no koe wa
My heart is racing and beating loud
itsu shika kokochi yoku najinde ite
But that feels cozily familiar
kaze ga tsuyoku fuiteite mo
Even if the wind is blowing hard
me wo tsumuranaide itsu datte mae wo muku yo
Don't close your eyes and always look on ahead
nakitaku nattara omoidashite
If you feel like crying, remember
damatte chikaiatta yakusoku wo
the promise we made together
tabidatsu hinadori no uta
The young birds in the sky sing
ima mo mada umaku tobenai keredo
though they still can't fly well
meguri meguru toki wo koe
Even if we go beyond the edge of time
hitazura ni tsunaida te wo tadotte
I'll only follow you as we hold hands
kotoba wa
"So I never let you go!" My words
sora ni kieteku bakari da toshite mo
may get lost in the infinity of the sky,
chirabaru hikari no naka de
but among the glittering light
mayowazu ni kimi wo sagashidaseru kara
I can still find you without hesitation
Preview
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
The man wishing for change to create something new summons melancholic memories from the past.
What does the one from the jet black depth offer to the man,
and what does it show to the boy?
Eureka Seven AO, episode nine: In The Dark We Live.
Listen to the voices of the children of the stars.