Don't shoot!
Please, forgive him!
You're not to leave the dorm until we decide how to proceed.
Is that it?
You're not going to lock me up like Cayenne?
Or is this just more training?
Mikono Suzushiro.
What have I done?
zetsubouteki ni kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful it's depressing
hanten suru sekai no kattou ni aishiaou
Let's love one another amidst the chaos in this backwards world
bokura ga miteru sekai wa itsudemo sakasama de
This world of ours moves in reverse
A
doushiyou mo nai koto de taigai kimatteku
controlled by forces we can't even touch
A
namida suru hodo kizu tsuku hitomi
There is pain in your eyes so deep I want to cry
A
kokoro de sakebi nagara
Screaming from my heart
A
tada atteitai saigo no futari masarenai mama
The last couple who desire each other cannot be together
A
byouyomi ga kikoetekuru
And time is running out
A
zetsubouteki ni kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful it's depressing
A
sutareyuku doubutsu mitai ni aishiaou
Let's love one another like abandoned animals
A
nakitai kurai kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful I want to cry
A
hanten suru sekai no kattou ni kanjitai yo
Let's love one another amidst the chaos in this backwards world
A
Confession
from the Soul
Mikono, do you remember what Jin said to us when we were buried?
Yeah?
When I heard it, I thought...
As long as I don't forget Jin, he'll always be with me.
I'll keep his memories with me and live as well as I can.
Yunoha... I guess there was something to that training after all.
You're the one who made me realize that, Mikono.
You told me I was precious to you.
So now, in return, I'm going to support you.
You're precious to me too, Mikono.
Yunoha...
Thank you.
Mikono...
Hey, it ended well, didn't it?
I mean, you still didn't do it, but...
Why did I do that? I don't know.
I don't even understand myself anymore.
That's okay. No one ever really understands you completely.
But I feel like I don't understand anything.
And that...
Are you saying Mikono is Silvie?
Yes. And that guy is Apollon.
What's the matter?
It's nothing.
Speaking of strange things...
Shush has never liked anyone but me,
but it really took a liking to him.
That means he can't be too bad.
Whoa!
It's even worse with Amata.
Shush scratched his face.
Now that I think about it, Shush hated me ever since we met.
Does that mean I'm not meant to be with Mikono?
Could be.
Maybe you're just not fated for one another.
Like how Mix and I were brought together by holes!
It's your destiny to be hated by Shush
and lose your love to that wolf guy.
Is that what you're thinking?
Was this all predestined 12,000 years ago?
Don't get so down, Amata!
They say if you want to shoot down the captain, first aim for his horse.
Try getting Shush to like you first.
That'll be 3450 kowloons, please.
Okay.
Well, I bought stuff I think Shush will like,
but I don't think it'll really help.
There I go again.
Go what?
Nothing!
Can I ask you something?
Let's say I told someone something that I shouldn't have told them.
How do I handle it?
Don't "handle" it.
Skip the drama and just tell him.
That's better for him, too.
A-Are you sure?
No point being polite. Just say it!
"I don't like you!"
What?
When it comes to men, you have to be firm!
Oops! I'm supposed to meet Andy!
Bye!
"Bye"?
That doesn't help at all!
Damn it!
Area 337 again?
Get on it immediately.
Obviously, rescuing civilians should be your top priority.
Roger.
Ianthe was created by my mother, Oriza.
It maintained order and prosperity for this world.
But it's suffering a mysterious drop in power.
Its control systems are failing.
There have even been explosions.
I know that no machine can last forever.
But this is still too quick.
Jin...
Is this the beginning of the end for Altair?
Or is it my punishment?
A practice duel?
Yes. It was Fudo's suggestion.
Making the Aquarion's fight each other is too dangerous!
Life and death are two sides of one coin.
They have completed the Special Training of the Grave.
They will learn from danger and reach the next level of potential.
The fights are only going to get worse.
They must be able to overcome greater challenges.
That's why they must go through this special training.
Roger.
Who are the Elements in the fight?
They've already been decided.
Cayenne Suzushiro.
Never thought I'd fight a mock battle with another Aquarion.
Sazanka Bianca.
I'm gonna Union with Cayenne!
I hope the other pilot is Shrade!
Malloy Dorezza.
Sorry. It's just me.
Against Amata, Zessica, and Mikono.
Is everything just predestined?
How could that be?
All Vectors have entered the battlefield.
Cayenne's team will form Aquarion Gepard!
Roger!
Amata's team will form Aquarion Evol!
Training Union!
Go! Aquarion!
Aquarion Gepard!
Aquarion Evol!
No restrictions on Element powers on either team!
Treat your opponent an enemy!
Fight with all you've got!
Amata, do you have what it takes to protect Mikono?
Show me what you've got!
Amata!
They've got a range advantage on us!
We'll close in using the buildings as cover!
Crumble...
How?
That building fell apart like a sand castle!
That's my Element power. It got an upgrade from the Special Training of the Grave.
This is the first time I've really gotten to use it!
The Curse of Malloy.
It destroys the stability of any material,
making it shatter at even the slightest impact.
Unfortunately for you...
there's nothing you can use for cover!
Go, Mikono!
Amata! Let's get away!
That's exactly what Gepard wants us to do!
If we can just get over there...
Amata, we can't win if we keep running away!
Amata knows that! But just for now-
Both of you stop talking!
Gepard excels at ranged combat.
They're not going to chase us down.
Amata!
Amata, behind you!
Wrong again, Amata!
Digging holes is trivial when you add my curse to gunfire!
Damn it, Malloy! You know holes are my thing!
Infinity Punch!
The machine's balance is off!
Look!
Evol's feet! They're rusting!
Ha ha ha! My Element power is corrosion!
I can make any object rot away!
This is over!
Infinity Punch!
Keep running away. That works great for Gepard.
The rusting stopped, but we won't be able to close in like this.
Give up already, Amata.
You never had a chance of winning this mock battle.
This was your fate from the start.
My fate?
Just accept your defeat.
What?
Is he predicting my moves?
Well, Amata?
If these were real bullets, your Evol would be swiss cheese by now.
It's Cayenne's Prophecy of Despair!
It's been enhanced so that he can see just a moment into the future!
Thanks to the Special Training of the Grave, their base aura levels have also increased.
Combining Cayenne's Instant Prophecy with Gepard's weapon targeting...
He can aim his fire right where the enemy is about to move!
Seriously?
Jin, please protect Mikono and the others...
Where are you going to come from?
Right? Left? Maybe from above?
Wherever it is, I'll read it...
and predict the defeat you're destined to suffer!
No.
I refuse to lose to fate.
I won't take it!
Amata!
Even if it was predestined 12,000 years ago...
I... I...
I'll fight fate for it!
Amata, you're right.
Zessica?
The vision in the mirror I told you about...
I thought it was fate.
But I forgot that there was something more important.
Fate's not what matters.
It's our truth, right here and now!
What we're feeling this instant!
Skip the drama and say it!
I think I can say it!
Say what, Zessica?
Amata...
Yes?
I... I lo...
Looks like they're done fighting.
Then let's put them out of their misery!
Fire!
I lo...
I love you!
That was close.
What did you say, Zessica?
I couldn't hear you over the explosions.
What?
It's really important to you.
Say it again.
I'm listening now!
I...
love...
you.
I love you, Amata!
L...
Love?
LOVE!
I...
I said it!
Z-Zessica?
What's going on?
The Evol!
It's glowing!
Evol's emotional gauge is going way up!
That's...
Zessica's strong unrequited love!
So Aquarion can go berserk for unrequited love, not just mutual love!
What should I say?
I'm flattered, but...
Amata!
Evol's moving on its own!
The Infinity Punch!
It vanished into thin air!
Fudo, what's going on?
It's begun.
When they take the final step into forbidden love,
the power that Aquarion unleashes will cross time and space.
Love goes out of control.
What is this?
Images are coming in through the punch!
I've never seen this place before!
Where is it?
Who's that?
He's like an animal!
Are those two...
That's Aquarion!
But it's a little different from our Aquarion.
This is...
Genesis Union!
High Commander Fudo?
He kind of looks like him, but...
How beautiful.
The light of my beloved Wings of the Sun.
The light of hope that will restore us!
That man...
I've seen him somewhere...
But I can't remember where.
Aquarion!
It's growing wings!
Wait, is that...
the legendary Aquarion?
Apollo!
Thank you, Silvia.
Apollo?
Silvia?
Not Silvie?
I'll never forget how lovely you smell.
Apollo!
Let's meet again.
In 12,000 years.
Apollo!
Is this...
Could it be...
The true story of 12,000 years ago!
What?
What happened?
How is the island?
The signal's clearing up!
We're getting video!
Are you serious?
The island's almost gone!
We've confirmed signs of all the Elements!
Gepard and Evol are intact!
A heart that searches for the truth.
And a heart that searches for true love.
The two have become one in harmony,
and the forbidden power has been awakened.
Help! Someone get me out of here!
The Infinity Punch flew through time itself.
That's not all.
I couldn't predict it with my Instant Prophecy.
Could it have traveled through time itself?
Just how powerful is Aquarion?
Good, Cayenne's team is okay!
But what did we do?
It was my fault.
I'm the one who came out and said I loved you.
That's why the forbidden power awakened
and Evol went out of control.
If I'd messed up, I could have killed everybody.
But that guy we saw...
If that was really what happened 12,000 years ago,
Apollo acted like an animal.
Just like that guy who's after Mikono.
Can I really fight against fate?
kimi he tsuzuku sakamichi ni
There were white flowers growing
shiroi hana ga saiteta
on the road on the hill that leads to you
yume kara sameta ato mo kanashii sora miteta
When I woke from the dream, the sky still looked sad
kono kimochi happa no ue ni susunderu
My feelings drift on a leaf in the wind
asatsuyu wo ochiru oto ni mimi wo sumaseteru no
I'm straining my ears for the sound of the dew falling
kamisama anata ga tsukutta sekai wa kanpeki ja nai
God in Heaven, this world You made is far from perfect
koko de wa mainichi koi ga boroboro shindeku
Down here, love is shattered day by day
hajimete suki ni natta no wo anata wa shiranai deshou
You don't know what it's like to fall in love for the first time
chikyuu no uragawa de ii kara soba ni ite hoshikatta
Let it be on the other end of the world, but I wanted to be with him
watashi wo wasuretemo ii kara soba ni ite hoshikatta
Even if You were to forget me, I wanted to be with him
Are you serious? Next week's the swimsuit episode?
Cayenne in red!
Shrade in a wet shirt!
I'm definitely going to record this!
Next time on Aquarion Evol: Rise Up, Life.
Next Time
Rise Up, Life