Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
namida wo nose
take away your tears
kareru made supiido agete
Speed up until they dry
tobikoete yukeru
I can overcome this
kitto kotae wa
The answer is
harukana ano sora no mukou
waiting beyond the distant sky
kotae ga mitsukaranai koko de wa
There's no answer here,
tameiki wo tsuite sora wo miru
so I sigh and look up at the sky
aoku somerareta hitomi no oku de kagayaiteru no wa
Shining deep within my eyes, reflecting its blue,
doko de mo yukeru, yume wo miteru
is a dreamer who can overcome anything
jibun na no sa
It's me, myself
Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
negai wo nosete
carry your dreams
nobashita te wa asu wo egaku
My hands willl draw tomorrow
mou kowaku nado nai
I'm not scared anymore
namida no ato
The memory of my tears
nijiiro ni somatte tondeyuku
are dyed by rainbows and fly
ano sora no mukou
far away beyond the sky
There was a Scub Burst in Phoenix, Arizona eight hours ago.
Although the United States Army brought its full force to intercept the Secret,
they still failed.
Isn't this the first time a Scub showed up in America?
Really?
Scub Bursts have, in fact, occurred in the US a couple of times.
However, no Secrets have ever emerged in any of those cases.
Even though they failed to stop the Secret...
Would they still request our help?
The last Scub Burst in America...
I can't imagine them requesting help from us.
Well, it's not entirely out of the question either.
Release Yourself
At the moment, team Pied Piper is standing by on the Mexican side of the Arizona border.
Yout just need to officially request our help using your power as the governor of the state.
It's relatively simple.
Precisely because it's simple, there are bound to be many in opposition.
This is a matter I want to take my time to thoroughly consider.
We've already had to wait this long! You can't be serious!
What do you think, Rebecka?
I'm glad to see you're alive and well.
Thanks.
Hey, what's the meaning of this?
I'd assume you knew since you take orders directly from the company president.
She's dispatched from above.
So what?
As you know, the mother company of Generation Bleu
is the largest PR company in the US.
The truth is, I worked there too until I switched to a political career.
Our relationship is that of a mentor to a protégée.
We were the best partners.
Our greatest achievement was silently erasing an entire country from the face of Earth.
The smoldering ethnic conflicts of the Balkan Peninsula
turned into a civil war after a Scub Burst.
As they were on the losing side, the state as an institution was destroyed.
And not a single country offered to help.
I've heard that story.
That country was preparing for ethnic cleansing.
Why would anyone offer help?
The genocide was just an illusion that we, the PR company, created.
What?
There was no good or evil in that conflict.
Eh?
But the world does not move unless a distinction between good and evil is made.
And you made a profit off of that?
You'll never change.
And what about you?
I hope I do.
That isn't possible.
You're doing the same thing now as you have been all along.
Aren't you secretly trying to get me to do your bidding this very moment?
Noah?
You shouldn't come in here.
The Pied Piper of Hamelin?
The story about the violinist?
Wrong.
The Pied Piper of Harmelin...
is a story based on a historical incident in Germany.
Why is our team named after the Pied Piper of Hamelin?
A piper was hired to rid the town of mice,
The name who named it...
but he was denied payment after completing his job.
...was the Chief, right?
Thus, he led away the children of the town.
Why?
Who knows?
Continuing on!
Let me explain the possible meaning of the legend.
One is that the piper was a harbinger of death,
and the story symbolizes the death of countless children due to plague and other reasons.
A different explanation suggests that the children were led away
on a pilgrimage or to join an army such as the Children's Crusade.
Furthermore, in the 20th century, there were explanations
that claimed the children left the town by their own free will.
In many East European villages and towns,
there are historical remains related to the children of Hamelin.
You're still going on about that...
It is thought that—
The United States Army has made a move.
They are sending in a second wave of attacks.
A direct infantry attack?
The ZOA generated by this Secret is
considered to be exceptionally large.
The participants in the first wave of attack approached carelessly and was completely annihilated.
They are not used to fighting against Secrets,
so they want to avoid losing anymore IFO units.
So they thought:
Since the Secret reacts to flying IFOs, they'll move in with infantry.
We are going.
Where to?
To meet up with the American forces and assist them.
Hey, it's not the time for jokes.
You are still our employee, remember?
I act by my own judgment. Sorry.
Wait, Ivica!
After we cross the border, refuse identification requests and avoid border examination.
That is possible, but we will be violating laws.
The United States Immigration Law—
Keep that information for yourself.
Yessir.
I'm sorry.
I volunteered, and you'd need someone to pilot it anyway.
Also...
What?
I was thinking that this isn't like you.
You don't usually go against orders issued by the president.
The Americans aren't that stupid to engage in such a strategy on a whim.
They must have considered using infantry against Secrets for a while.
So they have experiment results to support it?
I have a bad feeling about this.
You too, don't you?
Chief, over there!
We are from Generation Bleu.
An evacuation order was issued for this area.
What are you doing here?
Chief, something's wrong.
Something's wrong with him!
He threatened us into gathering here!
Why are you doing this?
By your sacrifice, the truth of the Secrets will be revealed.
Truth...
Give back Naru!
Ao!
The second wave of attack has failed as well.
All units were annihilated by unexpected attacks.
So do you feel like acting a bit more serious now?
What unexpected attacks?
I don't know the details yet.
Now then...
The right to request emergency mobilization from Generation Bleu is still in my hands.
Are you still going on about that?
Truth!
This is unbelievable!
What the...
Chief, where is—
What's this?
Did he do this?
Hurry up and hide inside the building!
Everyone, hurry to the building!
Shoot!
The Secret only reacts to machinery and IFOs!
Not humans!
We can do this!
What are you doing?! Get a hold of yourself!
Secrets aren't what you think they are.
They are still looking for us.
Call for help, quick!
We can't contact the army unless we return to the choppers.
Everything will be fine. Don't worry.
Whatever happens, Mommy is gonna protect you.
A direct attack using humans?!
Yes. When the infantry attacked the Secret,
it reacted by directly annihilating the troops.
It annihilated everyone in its way, no matter if they were armed or not.
Is this the unexpected attack he talked about?
What about Ao and the Chief?
No contact from them.
Expedite negotiations with the governor.
You have free hand in deciding our conditions.
Conditions?
This isn't like you. What are you so scared about?
I'm not scared.
Is it about Ivica?
I've heard about what happened to his home country.
I've brought you to a dreadful place. I'm sorry.
I chose the name "Pied Piper" for the team.
My home country doesn't exist anymore.
They made light of some information, and by the time they realized, the whole world turned against them.
My wife and child died when we got dragged into the fight.
Many others have died as well.
But I have no right to hate the enemy.
We've done the same thing.
I agreed to join Generation Bleu to repent for my sins.
But only children can pilot IFOs.
The Pied Piper is me myself.
I lead you to the battlefield as I play my flute.
But the Piper won't let you die no matter what.
I'll distract them!
Use that time to escape!
But then you will...
Ao!
I've done it!
What's the meaning of this?!
It was an experiment.
Experiment?
On a higher floor, I saw some mannequins shot to pieces.
Mannequin?
Are you telling me they identify humans by our form?
That's what I thought too, which is why I conducted an experiment.
You're too reckless!
But...
I don't want to see people die anymore.
Everyone, I ask you to believe in and follow us!
The Chief and I are going to lead all of you to safety!
We're the Pied Piper after all!
Everyone follow me.
Leave me alone with him.
What?
Please.
We once had the power to erase an entire country from existence.
I won't let you say you've changed since then.
This time, we're going to make the world move ourselves.
I might as well request emergency mobilization from Generation Bleu.
However, I have conditions.
Generation Bleu must hereafter support—
What were your conditions again?
The Governor of Arizona requested emergency mobilization.
The Triton is to launch immediately.
First, retrieve Ivica, Ao, and Rebecka, then destroy the Secret.
Let's get away from here quickly and get somewhere safe!
Roger.
Again, we thank you for your help.
The Triton is confirmed to be closing in.
Have they gotten the mobilization request?
We must hurry and destroy the Secret quickly.
If it makes it to a city, there will be disaster.
I have an idea.
The ZOA reaches all this way?
Are we at the meeting point yet?
Just a little more!
There it is!
I knew it!
It recognized the human form Nirvash as an enemy.
Damn! I can't reach the Secret!
He can't get close.
But there is a way.
Can you both hear me?
Our chance comes when it opens its mouth to let out its Options!
When it does, shoot it with all you've got!
But how?
Leave that to me!
Chief, don't tell me!
Chief!
All right! Now!
Chief...
Don't carelessly mention her past ever again.
Not even to Rebecka herself.
Have you seen through it all?
People change. That's all.
Don't regret it.
She's only dedicated to you because of her sense of guilt!
What are you talking about?
What's wrong?
These children need a piper to lead them.
Please don't be careless.
The Pied Piper, huh?
Actually it might have been the children playing the pipe.
To be continued!
takanaru shinzou no koe wa
My heart is racing and beating loud
itsu shika kokochi yoku najinde ite
But that feels cozily familiar
kaze ga tsuyoku fuiteite mo
Even if the wind is blowing hard
me wo tsumuranaide itsu datte mae wo muku yo
Don't close your eyes and always look on ahead
nakitaku nattara omoidashite
If you feel like crying, remember
damatte chikaiatta yakusoku wo
the promise we made together
tabidatsu hinadori no uta
The young birds in the sky sing
ima mo mada umaku tobenai keredo
though they still can't fly well
meguri meguru toki wo koe
Even if we go beyond the edge of time
hitazura ni tsunaida te wo tadotte
I'll only follow you as we hold hands
kotoba wa
"So I never let you go!" My words
sora ni kieteku bakari da toshite mo
may get lost in the infinity of the sky,
chirabaru hikari no naka de
but among the glittering light
mayowazu ni kimi wo sagashidaseru kara
I can still find you without hesitation
Preview
Next time in Eureka Seven AO.
A small intruder makes the girl's past resurface.
The other self-reflected image in the mirror starts moving again.
Who will find the truth, as her true self quivers?
Eureka Seven AO, episode eleven: Plateau of Mirrors.
Listen to the voices of the children of the stars.