Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
namida wo nose
take away your tears
kareru made supiido agete
Speed up until they dry
tobikoete yukeru
I can overcome this
kitto kotae wa
The answer is
harukana ano sora no mukou
waiting beyond the distant sky
kotae ga mitsukaranai koko de wa
There's no answer here,
tameiki wo tsuite sora wo miru
so I sigh and look up at the sky
aoku somerareta hitomi no oku de kagayaiteru no wa
Shining deep within my eyes, reflecting its blue,
doko de mo yukeru, yume wo miteru
is a dreamer who can overcome anything
jibun na no sa
It's me, myself
Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
negai wo nosete
carry your dreams
nobashita te wa asu wo egaku
My hands willl draw tomorrow
mou kowaku nado nai
I'm not scared anymore
namida no ato
The memory of my tears
nijiiro ni somatte tondeyuku
are dyed by rainbows and fly
ano sora no mukou
far away beyond the sky
Agent Nakamura, you still haven't given up?
You failed to retrieve the Mark I four months ago, didn't you?
The IFO plan has been cancelled.
But our country is under an international embargo
and we're in an explosive situation with both Okinawa and the Allies.
If we acquired a form of absolute defense,
Sign: Revised budget estimates for pseudo Scub Burst simulations
we would have a chance to become the strongest economy in the world!
Listen here, Nakamura.
Japan got this far precisely because we've avoided fishy business like this.
Why stir up unnecessary military tensions and worsen the situation?
The people are allergic to these Scub and trapar stuff.
So you're saying that, no matter what, our budget plan won't be approved by the Ministry of Interior.
Please give it up.
No luck?
They just want their coward's peace until they die.
They don't give a damn about our country's future!
Now we've got no choice but to prove our point
and make them give an ex post facto approval.
I'm sending over the data I received from the Fire Crackers.
Are you sure it's okay to trust them?
Aren't they considered cyber terrorists?
Should we really interact with them as representatives of a country?
I'd say the Fire Crackers are taking pity on Japan,
since we've been ostracized from the rest of the world in terms of information.
Isn't this the data the Americans kept refusing to hand over?
How on Earth...
For now, I don't care how they did it.
Our generation needs this...
in order to destroy this country once.
In The Dark We Live
Hey, we've gotta train!
Stop fooling around.
But this is training.
Why don't you jump in and join us?
But we really need to have proper training!
Yeah, yeah, I understand you want to get your girlfriend back.
She isn't my girlfriend...
Oh? Are you frustrated?
Ao, you can't swim? Or just afraid your worries would pull you down?
Oh, please...
Oh, so you can't swim?
Then I won't help you if you're about to drown, even if you cry for help.
Of course I know how to swim.
We've got some new intel from a mole inside the Ministry of Defense.
You even have people in the Japanese government?
Results notwithstanding, supposedly they will be conducting simulations of artificial Scub Bursts.
To preserve the power balance of the world,
we absolutely can't allow Japan, in their misguided state, to get their hands on a plant coral.
And that's where our company's ace, team Pied Piper comes into the picture.
You mean we should secretly retrieve the Quartz?
But it's same order as usual.
Hurry up.
Anyway, I'll leave it in your hands.
I'll have one of our accomplished employees to brief you on the specifics.
Understood...
Sideseeing!
My mother re-marry in Switzerland.
My Japanese, very good! Have a tad ov an accent though.
So this is Japan, huh...
Now an Okinawan counts as a foreigner here.
Such a bureaucratic immigration procedure...
It's like we've gone back in time.
And now?
We're taking that. Heading east.
They call it the Shinkansen.
So Tokyo used to be there a long time ago.
Yeah, the Scub Burst that happened 70 years ago
dealt the final blow to Japan after their defeat in the war,
and caused the reconstructions to be pushed back.
Light emission confirmed. Water temperature rising.
The damaged Quartz seem to have started fusing.
Great! The reactivation is successful!
Our country has got a plant coral now.
Reactivation is the first step in the plan.
Huh?
It means the fun starts now.
They're saying the experiment was successful.
Light emission detected. The spectrum matches that of Quartz.
A Scub has materialized?
Contact team Pied Piper.
How long do we have to be on standby here?
It's an island country, so access by sea is more effective than by air.
We are sitting just outside Japanese territorial waters.
If we move any closer, we'll get caught in the net of the Japanese army.
Their patrolling battleships will likely—
Just now the Japanese apparently succeeded with their experiment.
If there is a Scub Burst, then a Secret will...
Emergence confirmed.
What just happened?
Emergency alert from the experiment area.
A Secret has been sighted on the sea!
Commence operation to capture the Secret.
Request an area check of the experiment area.
What on Earth...
Secrets have a much higher potential as weapons in real battles than IFOs.
It's all right. The Secret targets the Scub Coral.
Which means we're safe as long as we're—
Damage confirmed in the battleships standing by.
We're under attack by the Secret!
Eh, you won't take the bait?
For this operation, you have been dispatched
to the seabed south of Tokyo Bay near the mouth of the Sagami river.
For most of its area, the Tokyo Bay is around 20 meters deep,
but this area is exceptional in that it reaches as deep as 500 meters.
Taking the water pressure at that depth into consideration,
there is a risk of the IFO's frame suffering damage, primarily the limbs.
To prevent this, all units are advised to stay in flyer form as long as possible,
and only convert to human form when the conditions are fitting.
Which means, don't transform until the very last moment.
That's crazy!
It'd be nice if the enemy is kind enough to wait until we complete our transformation sequences.
But then why are we attacking underwater?
We could just go and fight above the water.
Our target this time isn't the Secret but the Scub Coral underwater.
Retrieving the Quartz takes top priority.
The Secret is moving towards the JAF base.
We'll take that chance to move into where the Scub Coral materialized,
destroy the Scub, retrieve the Quartz, and retreat immediately.
Roger.
What is that Quartz thing?
It's a crystal inside the Scub Coral that the Secrets are targeting.
The Quartz is that thing they had us transport?
Yeah. The Generation Bleu folks think that the Secrets are going for those.
They're hiding the all the Quartz they've retrieved from the Scub somewhere in the HQ.
Why?
Who knows...
So Generation Bleu's top priority has always been retrieving the Quartz?
This time in particular.
To prevent a dangerous incident with Japan, we must destroy the Scub as well.
And what about rescuing the victims?
If we suppress the Scub Burst by retrieving the Quartz, damages can be kept to a minimum.
Oh, please.
It's pointless to talk back, Ao.
They are the type of people who look away if there's something they don't want to see.
Fighting is heartless.
We can't allow Japan to emerge as a trapar superpower.
You're Okinawan so you should understand!
What are you talking about?!
I don't care if they're Japanese or
Okinawan, people are dying out there!
Stop, Ao!
Alleluia, Kyrie, prioritize retrieving the Quartz.
Understood.
Roger.
Fuck... Fuck...
We would've been better off if we had just infiltrated their base!
I get that, but don't drive so recklessly!
Cars are so last century!
If there's an explosion in the military harbor, that means the Secret is in the water over there!
Hey, isn't that...
our Mark I?!
What's wrong?! Why did you stop?
That's my Nirvash.
Who are you?
Thank you for using my present so well.
You're a member of the Fire Cracker?
My name is Truth.
You're that guy from the toilet...
Is this mess all your doing?
This... isn't a Scub Coral!
Damaged Quartz...
Why is there so much? And this light...
It's been reactivated.
Damaged Quartz is a side product of a Scub Burst. Look at how much there is left.
Taking all this into consideration with other data...
It's the remains from the Scub Burst 70 years ago.
If you gather enough damaged Quartz in one spot, it's gonna go bang again.
I guessed a Secret would show up then.
And I was right.
Fake Quartz?
Then that time...
Where is it?
Dammit!
This is bad! The pressure will crush Nirvash!
Where is it? Where's the Secret?
At least call for help!
Fleur?
Fleur!
What is it doing?
That's...
I see!
What are you doing?!
Ao, what was that for?!
Come!
No way... Tell me this isn't happening...
But...
Huh?
I thought you weren't going to help him if he was going to drown.
Shut up!
Answer me! Were you the one who gave us that?
You can't see the truth.
What did you say?
The truth only shows itself to the ones who try to see it.
Hey, how did you know that the Secret was going for the trapar?
I saw it.
Saw what?
Something we can't see?
Is that your special ability? Like clairvoyance?
I don't know...
I just saw it when I tried to...
That's all I can say.
I hope you can understand now. Japan needs no overwhelming military power.
Even meager peace is better than none.
You...
What do you want?
You got in my way!
You said you want to destroy this country.
Would you really be satisfied with just destroying this tiny nation?
To be continued!
takanaru shinzou no koe wa
My heart is racing and beating loud
itsu shika kokochi yoku najinde ite
But that feels cozily familiar
kaze ga tsuyoku fuiteite mo
Even if the wind is blowing hard
me wo tsumuranaide itsu datte mae wo muku yo
Don't close your eyes and always look on ahead
nakitaku nattara omoidashite
If you feel like crying, remember
damatte chikaiatta yakusoku wo
the promise we made together
tabidatsu hinadori no uta
The young birds in the sky sing
ima mo mada umaku tobenai keredo
though they still can't fly well
meguri meguru toki wo koe
Even if we go beyond the edge of time
hitazura ni tsunaida te wo tadotte
I'll only follow you as we hold hands
kotoba wa
"So I never let you go!" My words
sora ni kieteku bakari da toshite mo
may get lost in the infinity of the sky,
chirabaru hikari no naka de
but among the glittering light
mayowazu ni kimi wo sagashidaseru kara
I can still find you without hesitation
Preview
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
In the land of the great power America, mankind's choice triggers
a fearful evolution in the Secrets, fueled by the sacrifice Truth prepared.
Can Ao's team overcome this difficult situation and resolve the crisis?
Eureka Seven AO, episode ten: Release Yourself.
Listen to the voices of the children of the stars.