-OP-
-ED-
Jinta
No, that's not true.
Yeah, I know it's not.
But really, your tits have gotten bigger.
You're being kind of creepy.
But...
Die.
Die, die, die!
Die, die, die, die!
Don't leave any of your recessive genes behind.
You damned sex addict.
Huh?
Is that Building Builder?
No way.
Women are so brainless.
Really? But he looks so much like him.
Look at his lips; see how they're so puffy?
If that's the only criteria, then even the old guy from Abacus Tutor looks like Building Builder.
Yeah, but Jintan...
Huh? Jintan?
Jintan?
Summer's beast is fierce indeed.
Hey, no fair! I want salty ramen, too!
Ooh, an egg!
I want egg soup, egg soup!
Hey.
The egg.
It's gonna be lumpy.
Stir the egg, stir it, stir it!
What's that? Ramen?
Oh, it's your dad.
That looks good. Make some for me, too.
Thanks for having me over.
Jinta?
Yeah, fine.
Awesome! How cute.
Why are you making it for your dad but not for me?
How about you quit that habit of calling everything cute?
What? But it's such a great word. You can use it in any situation.
Wow, your dad just said the way I talk is cute! What part is cute, exactly?
Except normally you wouldn't.
Do you want an egg in it?
Throw one in,
but don't break it apart.
OK.
Ah! Even your dad likes it that way!
Favorites, favorites, old people's flavors!
So that's how it is.
Time for some TV.
Hey everyone, today...
Oh, a cat. How cute.
My dad's acting completely normal.
So that must mean...
Hey, Jintan!
Here you go.
Yay!
Let's dig in.
Pepper, pepper, and more pepper.
More pepper... there!
I'm going to eat too.
Jinta?
Uh, oh, it's no-
Chopsticks. Where are the chopsticks?
The chopsticks!
Uh-oh.
What? What's wrong with you? Did you get a heatstroke from sitting in the house?
That's cute, but that's also serious!
Jintan?
That summer back then...
Be careful, Jintan.
I'm fine.
Wow! Jintan's is the biggest one for sure.
That's right.
Yeah, it's really huge.
Jintan's so cool.
Who I was back then...
Jintan.
Huh?
What's up, Menma?
Actually...
I have a wish.
nanpeeji mo tsuiyashite
Upon pages and pages of entries
We still don't
know the name
of the flower
we saw that day.
tuzurareta bokura no kibun
We've put down all our emotions
doushiteka ichigyou no
But now I've hit a writer's block
kuuhaku wo umerarenai
I don't know how to finish this page anymore
oshibana no shiori hasande
Putting a bookmark in my diary
kimi to korogasu tsukaisute no jitensha
You and I go out to ride the bike we found in the dumpster
wasurekake no renga wo
Let's go to our secret place
tsumiageta basho ni yukou
Where we piled up our bricks of memories
umi wo miwatasu saka wo kakenobotte
Run up the hill, where we can see the horizon
kowaikurai ni aoi sora to
Where we can see the sky so fearfully blue
migite ni saidaa hidarite wa
With cider in my right hand
zutto kimi wo sagashiteiru
My other hand helps me search for you
souyatte ima wa boku no hou e
You used to come find me way back when
toitsumeru koto mo nakute
You used to demand me of so much more
mada futari wa sugu soko ni irunoni
You're both still standing right by my side
douka mata aemasuyouni nante
Yet why do I pray to see you both again?
douka shiteru mitai
There must be something off with me
What happened?
I'm sick. Without a doubt.
All of the stress and trauma I've accumulated until now have become corporeal due to the summer heat...
Even my pubescent sexual urges have been thrown into the mix.
Good morning.
Jintan.
For now...
Let's say that you're here as the embodiment of my stress.
But...
Why did you appear now?
And on top of that,
why did you appear as a mature version of yourself?
Ummm... let me think...
I have no idea!
I can't believe you...
But.
I think I want to have my wish come true. That's it!
Your wish? What are you talking about?
Actually...
I have no idea!
How can you get a wish fulfilled when you don't even know what it is?!
But I really do get that feeling that's the reason.
What could it be?
How would I know?
Eewww, you spat on me!
Barrier!
She is the summer beast.
She is my stress.
She is my trauma.
For now, just try to remember what your wish was.
Oh yeah, about that! It was a wish that could only come true if everyone was together.
Everyone? You mean...
Coming!
Wait! I told you to wait.
But someone's at the door.
What would happen if you opened the door?
Just be quiet and wait...
What are you doing?
Wow, it's Anaru!
Hey, calm down!
Calm down? I'm not exactly worked up.
Oh, yeah.
I feel like there's a weight on my neck.
Anaru, you can't see me?
So what's up?
Here.
The teacher asked me to bring you your homework for summer break.
Now? There are only two days of summer break left you know.
Unlike you, I have a lot going on.
Then you should have tossed this away somewhere.
Besides, I don't feel like going to that school for retards any more.
I don't care whether you come to school or not.
But you should be ashamed of yourself.
Bye.
Ana...
Jinta, you big dummy!
Why didn't you ask her?
Just say, 'Let's grant her wish together, Anaru!'
First of all, don't call her Anaru.
Pick either Anjou or Naruko and stick with it.
Why should I? Anaru is Anaru.
She's nice to everyone, and has lots of video games and manga.
That's what I mean.
She's not the Anaru she was back then anymore.
That rotten bitch wouldn't help me even if I asked her.
'Rotten bitch?'
It means, 'stupid woman.'
Anyway, she's not my friend anymore.
I hate that!
I hate it!
I don't like it when you say bad things about Anaru.
Menma.
Come on, let's go talk to her again! Let's ask her, Jintan!
Jintan?
Alright already.
Now that you've seen Anjou you should
understand what it means for your wish.
And it's not just Anjou, everything has changed since back then.
Are you ready yet?
Yeah, yeah, I'm coming.
You're wearing a hat and glasses?
Don't worry about it.
Come on, let's go.
Yeah.
Oh?
Hello there. Going shopping?
Yes. Say, did you hear...
Jinta?
I know.
What's wrong?
Hello there.
What a funny expression.
Hey, you have a piece of green onion from the ramen stuck to your teeth!
Shut up!
Dammit.
Wait up!
Anaru's house isn't this way.
We're taking a walk since we're outside anyway.
This used to be Bomu-Bomu! Now it's a WcDonald's!
Awesome! But I...
Did you see that one movie?
Those guys went to my middle school.
Which one?
You know, the one with the girl that uses
nun-chucks to fight aliens that show up at school.
What the hell?
You haven't seen it?
Were those your friends?
Nope.
That's the way it is.
Those grannies really got me worked up,
but no one gives me a second thought.
Even Anaru said as much.
She doesn't give a damn about me.
'Snap!' goes your neck!
It smells like summer!
You haven't changed.
Huh?
Never mind.
It's not really a surprise.
She's just a hallucination, after all.
'Please grant my wish,' huh?
This must be, without a doubt, because of my relationship with her...
Jinta!
Look at me!
What are you doing? That's dangerous.
Jinta.
Menma has...
Ji...
Jintan?
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
Ouch...
Yadomi?
What are you doing?
Episode 1
Super Peace Busters
Hey, Naruko.
Did you go to Jin's house?
Knock first!
I thought I did. Well anyway....
I only stopped by for a bit. And it's none of your business.
Yes it is. I wanted you to take them some steamed buns.
Just take them by yourself!
Oho, someones going through puberty.
I'm the one...
...who should be ashamed.
Here.
Thanks.
We're on our way home from summer classes.
Did you know? We're going to a college-prep high school.
That's the high school uniform
that I was going to wear.
We want to support you!
No matter how small
the issue, please talk to us!
A
I was going to.
Yadomi?
Are you alright?
Huh? Yeah.
Well then...
Eh? Hey...
That's Yukiatsu and Tsuruko!
Let's go.
Oh, I mean, Menma is...
That's not it, I mean...
What about Menma?
You see...
Are you still talking about that?
Yukiatsu?
I've heard about you.
Yukiatsu.
Apparently you're not going to school.
You failed the entrance exams and ended up going to a low-tier school around here.
You're not going to school, and you're blurting out Meiko Honma's name.
Is there something wrong with your head?
Jintan!
Yukiatsu, you idiot!
What are you getting so worked up over?
Even you change when you talk about Meiko Honma.
Isn't that right, Yukiatsu?
Whatever.
You're such a pathetic guy.
But you do have your looks going for you.
I also have my brains.
Sure you do.
Jintan.
Wait.
Do you get it now?
Everyone has changed.
That's not it. The one who's changed the most is me.
Jintan.
Hey.
Hey, my stress. Give me a break already.
When I'm with you, I remember...
I remember things I don't want to.
And I get pissed off.
Jintan.
Back then.
That summer back then.
It wasn't like this.
I've got it!
What?
We'll be the Super Peace Busters!
Wow! That's so cool!
What's 'busters?'
It's like a group of strong people.
We'll protect the peace!
Awesome!
What peace are we going to protect?
The peace here, there, and everywhere!
Then Jintan will be the leader, right?
Yeah!
Everyone followed me.
That's right.
On that day.
Even on that day.
Hey, Jintan.
Huh?
You like Menma, don't you?
What are you talking about?
Be honest about it.
There aren't any secrets among the Super Peace Busters.
Yukiatsu.
Say it, say it, say it!
Just let it go already.
Who...
Who'd like an ugly girl like...
I thought she'd cry.
Because she's such a crybaby.
But...
Wait, Jintan!
Jintan!
Oh, you're back already?
I'm going to see your mom for a bit.
Wash and
dry your
hands before
you eat.
- Dad
A
Microwave the food I left you before you eat it.
That smile tore at my heart.
I thought I should just apologize tomorrow.
Gross.
But that tomorrow...
...never came.
Curry.
The door's open.
Then you should close it.
Wow, it's Saa! You've gotten so big.
And dad's got lots of gray hair.
Mama.
Just stop doing that already.
Saa?
You always offer a bowl to Sis whenever we have curry.
It's an eyesore.
That's because it was her favorite food.
Dead people don't eat.
Don't say that.
Your sister was a bit of an airhead, so maybe she hasn't even realized that she died.
I know.
I know that I died.
What the heck are you doing?
I don't know. The cup moved on its own.
Menma?
Just clean it up.
I didn't even do it.
Completely empty.
Dang it, dad.
And then...
...all of us who busted peace...
...just drifted apart.
I want egg soup, egg soup!
That girl...
I will never forget the hopes and dreams we shared during that one summer's end.
I've always wanted...
I'm sure we will meet again in another August, in maybe ten years time.
Where could she have gone?
But those are my best memories.
I've always wanted...
...the tomorrow after that day...
...the tomorrow when I could apologize to Menma...
...to arrive!
We met in an unexpected moment
when you called out to me at the crosswalk,
Menma.
"Let's walk home together."
My stress.
I might've hidden shyly behind my bag,
My trauma.
but the truth is, I was really, really happy.
That's right. I'm sure of it.
I conjured Menma up so that I could apologize to her.
The fireworks blossomed heartrendingly beautiful across the night sky,
If that's the case, then I have to...
and time passed as swiftly as the wind.
We shared so many happy times and trilling adventures
Men...
together in our secret base.
I will never forget the hopes and dreams we shared during that one summer's end.
What's all this?
Mourning Gown Housewives
This is one specific fetish.
I'm sure we will meet again in another August, in maybe ten years time.
You fool!
The romance lies in the impossibility!
I could feel your heartfelt thanks all the way until the end.
What? You're Jintan, right?
Poppo?
Let's carve our name here.
And I know it must've been painful to hold back your tears and say goodbye with a smile.
How do you write 'super?'
You haven't learned it yet?
Write the radical for 'run' to the left...
So how do you write 'run?'
But those are my best memories.
What are you doing here?
Super Peace Busters
The time that stopped on that day has started moving again.
Where should I go?