Kokoro
masshiro PAGE mekuru
I walk through the white pages of my storybook
Incoming Text
tobidasu irodoru hajikeru
that's just waiting to be painted
mangekyou no fuukei
with a kaleidoscope of my experiences
From
Me
To
You
kizukeba STORY wa mada
This story has only
gikochinaku hajimatta bakkari
just barely begun
shinkokyuu wo mou ikkai
I take a deep breath
tabi suru kaze tsutsumikomu you ni senaka wo osu
and the wind wraps around me and urges me forward
aa yawarakakute atatakai kimi no te
Your hand is so warm held within mine
nigiri shimete sono kokoro no oku made todoku you ni
It reaches all the way into my heart
hohoenmi de kumeta nara nigirikaeshite kuretara
I can't see a brighter future
boku wa tada mae wo miteru
than you smiling and taking my hand as well
Valentine's Day
This is freaking amazing!
Freaking?
Would you like some too, Ayane?
Thanks.
You have one too.
Thank you.
Have you gotten used to the new seating arrangements yet?
I have!
Winter break ended in January and we had another seating change.
It could just be my imagination, but the girl who sits behind me, Takahashi,
jokes with me even during class,
and the boy next to me, Yagi, starts conversations with me.
I often get sleep paralysis.
Do you think that's normal?
Yes, perfectly normal.
Growth spurt
Thank goodness.
I feel like people aren't avoiding me as much.
That's great!
It's thanks to all of you.
That's our Sawako, always too grateful.
We might not be sitting next to each other now,
but it's not like things have gone back to the way they were before we became friends.
In fact, things only seem to be getting better.
What do you think, Sawako?
Delicious!
Isn't it?
No way, really?
Seriously, it just like this!
Though, it'd be a lie if I said things were perfect.
Tickle, tickle!
Giggle, giggle?
Sadako?
She's become a lot brighter lately, hasn't she?
Yeah.
No small thanks to Shota here, no doubt.
True.
I felt like I had gotten a little bit closer to Kazehaya.
But ever since we switched seats,
I feel like we've grown a little bit farther apart again.
And now, it's February.
I don't really eat sweets, but if you want to give me something, I won't say no.
February 13th
1. English
2. Math
3. Japanese
And tomorrow is Valentine's Day.
Are you making yours, Sawako? Or buying?
What?
Your chocolates.
What are you acting all surprised for?
You give chocolates to your Dad every year, don't you?
Daddy...
What about you, Chizu?
I'm going to give some to Ryu.
What about you, Yano-chin?
Maybe as a bribe...
What? A bribe?
I didn't want to say anything,
but I was already prepared to make chocolates.
This one's for Ayane.
To Tomo
To Ayane
To Chizu
and Sanada
And this one is for Chizu and Sanada.
And this one is for Tomo.
And one for Ekko.
Oh, and this one for Daddy.
Kaz
And this one...
A-Actually maybe I shouldn't write him a card.
Wait, why does Kazehaya's bag seem to have more pieces with nuts than everyone else's?
And those pieces with hearts!
Why are there so many hearts?
W-Was I favoring him subconsciously?!
And these are handmade, too...
I really wanted to give him handmade chocolates...
But maybe this is too much.
But I....
really want to
give them to him.
Good morning!
G-Good morning!
He just took chocolate out of his locker, didn't he?
Well, of course he did!
I-I'll see you later!
O-Okay!
I couldn't do it.
These are so good!
Share them with Sanada, okay?
Okay!
Thank you!
Thanks, Sadako!
You're really good at this.
I'm so happy you like them.
I have just one left.
Kazehaya!
I have chocolates for you.
Wow!
Thanks.
Obligatory chocolates.
Nothing more, nothing less.
Look how happy that dork is though.
I-I need to use the restroom!
What?
Sawako?
Oh my gosh, I'm so nervous.
Kazehaya's been getting chocolates all morning!
If I give him mine too, he'd have way too much chocolate.
But even if he can't finish eating all of them today, he can refrigerate them!
If I just give them to him casually and happily like she did,
I'm sure he would be happy to take them too!
Kazehaya, chocolates for you!
Thank you.
T-That's somehow even more awkward and unnatural.
I know!
I can just give them to him normally, like I did with Ayane and Chizu.
Wait, normally?
No!
I can't do this.
I just keep over-thinking things when it comes to Kazehaya.
You got chocolates too, Ryu?
Want one?
Yes, please!
This chocolate tastes different than the previous ones.
Are you sure it was okay for me to have one?
Were these more than just obligatory chocolates?
No.
Chizuru—
Yoshida made these?
To Ryu
No way.
Kuronuma made them.
So they're obligatory chocolates through Chizuru.
Huh?
S-She has the same chocolates!
What is it? Do you want one?
I guess you can have one.
No, I'm fine!
Shota!
She's asking for you.
I'm definitely over-thinking this.
If we were still sitting where we were before,
would I have been able to hand them out naturally?
Did you see that?
It looked like he turned her down.
Man, such a waste.
Turned her down?
Turned down her chocolates?
So those weren't... obligatory chocolates.
In the beginning, it was only selfishness and misunderstanding.
So maybe the only reason he accepted the other chocolates so easily
was because they were just obligatory chocolates.
Mine are out of thanks,
but does that make them obligatory chocolates?
February 14th
Friendship chocolates?
Huh.
I don't want to use them to confess to him!
But I can't deny that I like him.
What kind of chocolates are these?
It looked like he turned her down.
That really woke me up.
I want to give them to him so badly.
But I need to hurry up, or else...
Wait, s-school's over already?!
I'm hooked on this drama rerun right now.
Which one? A foreign drama?
No, a trendy drama!
Did that girl ever manage to give him her chocolates?!
It doesn't look like it...
Let's go home, Yano-chin, Sawako.
What do you wanna do?
Wanna stop somewhere before going home?
I have to meet my girlfriend.
H-He's going to leave!
Shota!
Have I got a job for you.
Come with me.
Kazehaya!
You guys go on home!
Kazehaya.
Why me?
Because only you can do it.
He still hasn't left.
This could be...
my last chance.
Sorry... I really...
C-Could you guys go on without me?
I want to stay here for a little longer.
Then we'll stay with—
No, no, it's okay.
We can go ahead. See you tomorrow!
If you say so.
Hey, have you noticed that he's been staring at you the whole time?
Shh! Don't look at him.
I did it. I'm here alone.
But now what?
I'm scared!
My shoulders have been really stiff lately.
Give me a strong one, okay?
You've gotta be kidding me.
That's why you asked me to come here?
You should be honored.
It's fine if you don't want to though.
Do you remember when you came to me crying in the middle of a storm?
Eight year old
Kazehaya
Daddy said to bring this to you.
Were you afraid of the storm?
Remember when you said you wanted to sleep over at my house
Six year old
Kazehaya
and you ended up wetting my bed?
Yay...
Damn kid!
Maybe I should take a picture.
Maybe I should broadcast all of these super interesting things over the school—
Alright, alright, I got it!
That's it.
My left shoulder and the back of my neck are especially sore.
Darn him.
What're those?
Those chocolates?
When you're as awesome as I am, your fans just never leave you alone.
He's so egotistical.
Thank you for all
your hard work.
Wait, those chocolates aren't from Kuronuma, are they?
Idiot.
As if I'd break the girl's heart by telling you who they were from!
You're pitiful.
That hurts!
That's a bone you're hitting!
Don't you think the pain in your left shoulder and back of your neck are some sort of punishment?
I read in a manga once that problems from the neck and and above are caused by God.
God?
Maybe I'm being punished for messing with sacred trees at shrines,
or being stingy with offerings.
I'll purify myself with her chocolates!
What?!
He choked.
W-Water! Water!
If I want to give these to him,
I need to do it now!
Kaze—
Kazehaya.
Kurumi?
Hey Kurumizawa.
Won't you accept some chocolates from me since it's Valentine's Day?
Please?
It'll be the first and last time I ever give you any.
Thank you.
Spying on us?
How terrible.
I-I-I'm sorry!
I just got so caught up watching you two that I forgot to turn away.
She admitted to it.
Kazehaya doesn't accept homemade chocolates.
What did you just give him?
It's different. I'm special.
He's already rejected me.
So I'm very special. Don't you agree?
Are those for Kazehaya?
They're a thank you.
Are they really just a thank you?
They don't have any hidden meaning to them?
If those are just obligatory chocolates, I'm sure Kazehaya will gladly accept them.
Don't regret it now.
See you.
She has no one to blame but herself if she backs off after being teased a little.
Kurumi!
I haven't gotten any chocolates from you yet, Kurumi.
Really now?
She treats me like that even though we're in the same class.
She's really changed lately, hasn't she?
She was much cuter before.
I think I like her better now.
Definitely not.
You're terrible.
You just like them cute.
Girls are all cute, aren't they?
Not all of them.
That girl is from class D, isn't she?
Yeah. Sadako, right?
Oh right.
Even a girl like her
wants to give out chocolates on Valentine's Day.
Saying these are in thanks is just an excuse.
I didn't mean to,
but I guess I was really hoping for something today.
I'm afraid because there's something I'm secretly hoping for.
If those are just obligatory chocolates, I'm sure Kazehaya would gladly accept them.
They aren't obligatory chocolates.
They definitely aren't.
I say they're a thank you,
but what I'm really thinking is...
What if they could bring us closer?
Kazehaya doesn't accept homemade chocolates.
I can't do it.
I can't give them to him and pretend they're obligatory chocolates.
I mean it. I mean it too much to give these to him.
Don't regret it now.
Those chocolates meant so much to me
that I couldn't give them to him.
douka ima dake wa furimukanaide
Please don't look at me right now
yuugure sawagu kaze
The sun's set, the wind's blowing,
furesouna kyouri
and we're so close that we can almost touch
kimi wo mitsumeteru zutto
My gaze has always been fixed on you
kimi ga suki de
I like you
I've always liked you
kono omoi koi demo ii
I don't mind if this emotion is what they call love,
kizu tsuitemo ii
and I don't care if I get hurt by it
nando demo tsutaetai
I just want to tell you, over and over again
kimi ni todoke
I want to reach you
Preview
2nd Years
New seasons.
New meetings.
Next time: 2nd Years.