We weren't able to make Mikono
Suzushiro manifest an Element power.
I see.
We'll be sending her home, as we expected.
I think beef bowls are better with
raw ginger instead of pickled ginger.
I see.
About the Aquarion disaster...
Welcome back to Earth.
I did some investigation.
The forbidden Aquarion was last sent out nine years ago.
The head pilot was Donar Dantes.
What is Aquarion?
And what was the disaster you were—
I can't say it any better than this.
That mock battle yesterday was incredible!
I know, right? Wow!
I'd never seen anything like that before!
I'm never going to see Amata again.
He's one of Aquarion's Elements now.
Just like Cayenne.
I'm not part of their world anymore.
Really? You're just gonna go?
And leave your boyfriend?
Boyfriend?
I think his name was Amata.
You know, the one you were in Aquarion with?
That...
Haven't you forgiven him yet?
He even bowed in the mock battle.
I'm pretty sure he was saying sorry to you.
That's none of your business.
That's just how it is with you, isn't it?
"Ooh, I'm so useless." "Boo, it's none of your business."
You're so negative all the time.
Whatever.
C'mon, let's shake before you leave.
Good-bye.
osore
Even if you're scared
living your life   don't give up now   keep moving on
Just live your life, don't give up now, keep moving on
kimi wo dakishimeru nandomo nandomo nandomo
And I'll come for you over and over and over again
ashita boku wa kimi ni deau darou
We'll find each other soon enough
wazukana hoshiakari wo tayori ni
By the faintest glimmer of starlight
boku ni wa kimi ga wakaru yo wakaru yo
I know you, I know you
sen'oku no toki wo koe futari hiraku densetsu no tobira
It's been billions of years, but now we can open the door to our legend
naraku no ao tobikoete
I crossed over the deep blue void
kimi to hai ni naru tame
so I could burn to ash along with you
nagaki rinne wo kanashimi tsurete tabi shitekitanda
I've had a long journey on the vast wheel of fate, gathering sorrows along the way
zenryoku de mikansei kimi no tonari de
I'm not perfect, but I'm giving all I have
kawaita kokoro hodoke chi wo nagasu kedo
If I open my fragile heart to you, I know I'll bleed...
soba ni iru yo zutto yorisotte zutto
But I'll always be with you, always be in your arms
futari hikari no fune ni noru
We'll get on a shining ship of light
kaze no hajimari no oto kanadeyou
And call forth the wind with our voices
Wall
I hope Mikono understood what I was bowing for.
Nooooooo!
My hole! My path to hope!
Andy?
Impossible!
This material has absolutely no weak points!
Is that the hole from yesterday?
Did someone fill it?
They didn't just fill it! They filled it with an Element power!
Whoever filled this hole is on the other side of that wall.
It's one of the girls!
A girl?
I can feel it...
An impenetrably hard heart of stone!
But I can feel something else...
The cutie who filled this hole is waiting for someone to dig in and reach her!
Just you wait, gorgeous, I'm on my way!
You're not even considering that a boy could've done it.
Hey, that song...
Oh, that's Shrade.
Who's Shrade?
He's the top student here at Holy Angel Academy.
He's got some kind of Element scholarship.
He gets to sit out of training and he's never been deployed.
But word on the street is that girls are buying up way more of his pics than any other guy's.
Hey, where are you going?
Sorry about that.
Dude, wait up!
Come in.
Hey, Shrade. Sorry if we're interrupting something.
Don't worry about it, Andy.
The simulator played a lovely tone in yesterday's mock battle.
That was you, wasn't it?
How can you even tell?
It was a unique tone. Very honest.
Even silence can carry emotion.
It can change the course of a heart.
Hello. My name is Amata Sora.
I'm Shrade Elan.
THERE YOU ARE!
Cayenne!
How unlike you, my friend.
What brings you here?
Shut it! I'm not here for you!
You! What the hell was that in the mock battle?
I think you're asking for a beating!
Cayenne!
What're you doing?!
Please don't fight here.
I do dislike having to bring you down.
Quit struggling!
S-Shrade! You...
Farewell, Amata.
And farewell, Cayenne.
Farewell.
Mikono!
Mikono!!
Are you all right?
How does Shrade look so calm while he's doing that?
That's Shrade's Element power.
He uses sound to manipulate peoples' emotions.
Your mind is in chaos.
You said "Mikono", didn't you?
Have you been worried about your sister?
And so angry.
You started it!
I suppose.
A dissonant strain is near.
Abductors have appeared around the Neo-Kowloon area!
Neo-Kowloon?
That's right next to the Academy!
Deploying Elements are Cayenne, Andy, and Amata!
Sweet!
What?
Repeat: Deploying Elements are Cayenne, Andy, and Amata!
Me?
That's us!
Let's go!
But why me?
Vector X launching!
Vector Y launching!
Vector Z launching!
This isn't just practice. These are real enemies!
I can't believe this.
You're going to send me into battle with this newbie again?
Aquarion's power is coming online.
It looks like he has the ability to draw it out.
We're going to face stronger enemies from here on out.
If there is anything we can do to ensure our victory,
we must seize it.
The humanoid isn't there.
Guess it's just the cannon fodder.
Let's finish this!
Go! Aquarion!
Aquarion Gepard!
Aquarion is fighting.
Cayenne... Amata might be inside too...
My chest feels funny... Bad...
We're surrounded!
They're really strong! They're unmanned, aren't they?
They're acting like they're organized!
They've never done that before!
There must be a commander somewhere.
Showtime in the shadows.
They're not going to make it!
Commander! Element Change! We have to send out Shrade! He's our ace in the hole!
But his body can't...
Where is he? Where's the boss?
I'll awaken your power, my friend.
We're caught!
I can't move!
What?
Piano music!
Shrade, what are you doing?
I'm getting a vision...
There you are!
Aw man, they found me.
But it's too late!
The enemy was on the Three Fortunes!
Blast! He can evade all of our attacks!
They're gonna lose!
We can't land now!
Cayenne...
Sorry about this!
So sorry!
The boat's turning around!
Sorry... for taking the wheel of destiny!
Goddamn it! I'm gonna die without getting to Union with a girl even once!
Andy's spirit level is falling!
The Union is going to collapse!
Principal! I mean Commander! Someone has to Element Change!
I'll do it!
Change out everybody! The girls can handle this!
Hey!
Commander, give us your orders!
Commander! Send us out!
Principal!
Commander!
Element Change!
Call back Andy W. Hol!
Change him out for Mikono Suzushiro!
What?
Who are you?
B-But I...
Get out! We don't take orders from outsiders!
W-Who is this clown?
C-C-Could you be?
Fudo Zen!
Fudo?
We have awaited your arrival, High Commander Fudo.
High Commander?
Mikono Suzushiro, you will be one of Aquarion's pilots.
I can't! I'm useless!
I'm not even an Element!
Look over there.
Those boys are fools.
They only know of one way to protect what they love.
They only know how to be hurt.
You shut up!
Get away from him, Mikono!
Mikono! Get up and let's go!
They've been protecting me.
Cayenne and Amata let themselves get hurt for me.
I'd rather my body get hurt... than my heart...
They're still protecting me right now...
Mikono!
I can't... that's it for me...
The Union has collapsed!
I'll do it!
Really? But aren't you useless?
I'm completely useless. I know.
But I... want to hold their hands one more time!
Then go!
Element Change!
Mikono?
Mikono! What are you doing here?
Amata! Let's Union!
But—
I forgive you! Just do it!
Really?
Great!
Now shout, Amata Sora!
Snow Melting Union!
Go! Aquarion!
Aquarion Evol!
That's the form they used to fight Kagura.
Too bad we already know what it can do.
Mikono! Why are you in Aquarion?
I never wanted you on the battlefield!
Cayenne!
I've been having the same Prophecy of Despair ever since we were children.
Mikono, you approach Aquarion, and...
If only I'd never had that vision.
Mikono, I wanted to protect you.
I don't care if you hate me.
I'll protect you!
You've always protected me.
Thank you.
But I don't want to sit around and let you protect me any more.
You're my brother. I want to protect you too.
I want to get hurt too.
Mikono!
You too, Amata.
Don't hurt yourself for me anymore.
All right...
When Mikono's with me... I feel like...
I can do anything!
The resonance between the Elements in Aquarion is strengthening!
What?
What does this mean?
What is this?
Aquarion's heart is beating.
I'll tell you what's in Aquarion's chest.
It's the pulse of youth.
I feel... like I'm flying...
My heart is pounding.
We join hands, we join hearts, and it only pounds harder...
Our feelings will reach the sky.
And to infinity!
Aquarion's arm!
It can't be!
The legend of the Infinity Punch is reborn.
You've broken another seal, Fudo.
That's some attack.
But I doubt Izumo will mind since I got all of this data.
How far does that fist go?
Wait! It's coming back towards the Neo-Deava base!
What?!
The Berlin!
Whoa, girls!
Oh no, boys!
Silence!
The barrier between men and women is shattered!
But I hereby declare...
Love Forbidden
love to be forbidden!
What?!
Good morning, Kagura.
kaze ni ubawareta wake janai
We weren't spirited away on the wind
katamichi bun no yuuki de bokura
We knew we could never return, and found the courage
higeki wo ukeireru
to accept the hardship
kokoro ga koko ni atta hazu no kuudou
There's an emptiness where my heart used to be
motto boku ga ookikereba
If only I was stronger
kimi wo mirai wo sukueta darou ka
I could have saved you, and our future...
taisetsu na hito wo mamoru sube ga tatta hitotsu shika motenai
I only know of one way to keep the people I love
sonna anata ga haguretadayou sora
And you left me and disappeared into the sky
anata ijou no hito ni deaenai
I'll never find anyone like you again
tsuki ni aragau nagai furea
A long flare reaches out against the moon
hajimaru mo sezu owaru monogatari
The story ends before it could even begin
kizutsukiuru yawarakasa
So soft, so fragile
tojikometa senritsu kanaderu hodo
I will call up the melody locked away
utau hodo kowareru hodo ni
And sing it until I destroy myself
anata ga koishii
That's how much I love you
Love blossoms by the poolside.
You come running to me, cocktail in hand.
It's romance beneath the summer sky!
Next Time
The Order Against Love
Next time on Aquarion Evol: The Order Against Love.