No!
Fate doesn't matter.
Focus on us, right now...
Zessica?
Man!
I was late to lunch, and they were all out of yakisoba sandwiches...
Zessica...
Um...
What you said before Aquarion went out of control...
I love you.
I... I can't...
Right now, Mikono-
Okay! Fine!
It's all right.
I knew it would turn out like this anyway.
Bye!
Zessica, wait!
Mikono...
I'm sorry for butting in.
Wait! Mikono! It's not like that!
Mikono!
They've had the Special Training of the Grave and that mock battle.
It appears that they're ripening.
It may be time to dig it up.
zetsubouteki ni kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful it's depressing
hanten suru sekai no kattou ni aishiaou
Let's love one another amidst the chaos in this backwards world
bokura ga miteru sekai wa itsudemo sakasama de
This world of ours moves in reverse
A
doushiyou mo nai koto de taigai kimatteku
controlled by forces we can't even touch
A
namida suru hodo kizu tsuku hitomi
There is pain in your eyes so deep I want to cry
A
kokoro de sakebi nagara
Screaming from my heart
A
tada atteitai saigo no futari masarenai mama
The last couple who desire each other cannot be together
A
byouyomi ga kikoetekuru
And time is running out
A
zetsubouteki ni kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful it's depressing
A
sutareyuku doubutsu mitai ni aishiaou
Let's love one another like abandoned animals
A
nakitai kurai kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful I want to cry
A
hanten suru sekai no kattou ni kanjitai yo
Let's love one another amidst the chaos in this backwards world
A
Rise Up, Life
Yep, I got rejected.
So, today at lunch, I think you got the wrong...
Never mind. Forget I said anything.
What's the matter with you? Love is forbidden, remember?
People could have died in that battle!
Get love off of your minds!
Guess so.
On the other hand, when we're all fighting side by side,
that's the perfect time for passionate love to grow.
It's a human instinct.
You want to persist your genetic information before putting your life on the line.
Genetic information?
That's a mere physical Union!
I'm talking about pure love here!
But if I really wanted to die...
I guess I'd want to leave my genes.
Emergency meeting?
Everyone is here, I see.
I would like to entrust you with a mission of utmost secrecy.
But did you have to notify us like this?
So what's this top secret mission?
You must go to a place, and dig up an item.
What's the item?
Top secret.
Where's the place?
And we get to dig?
Top secret.
You'll be leaving tomorrow.
All you need to know and have prepared
is detailed in this strategic handbook.
Remember, this is completely secret.
Do not let anyone else know.
Excuse me, High Commander?
I'm sure you're all concerned after seeing this obviously handmade book,
but you must keep this in mind:
The bananas are not snacks!
It's beautiful!
Keep it down. This isn't just a field trip.
What?
So these are our supplies?
Kind of weird for bananas, aren't they?
The hell?
Seeds?
These must be an old type of banana.
Bananas aside, where are we going?
He wouldn't say, and the Vectors are preprogrammed.
We're just along for the ride.
Do you know, Professor?
All I know is that I have to lead.
Not even Professor Donar was told about this operation.
This really is top secret!
What does the High Commander want us to dig up?
What if it's...
the mythical Legendary Aquarion?
The Legendary Aquarion?
But even if the legend is real...
What's going to happen if we dig it up?
So they've finally started...
searching for the Wings of the Sun.
The Legendary Aquarion is supposed to be here?
It would be a good place to hide it, I suppose.
This is a lake! How does the High Commander expect us to dig in a lake?
Wait there for a while.
You're all free until ordered otherwise.
You heard him.
We have free time?
That's what he said.
So that's what these are for!
Check it out!
Things to bring... swimsuits?
If you have forgotten your swimsuit, there are some in the transport.
Forget the war for now and let your souls be cleansed.
W-What are you staring at?
Hidden beneath Professor Suomi's normal tough, strict shell...
is a beautiful lady!
Zessica's normal clothes may seem risque,
(ﾉゝ∀・)~キラッ☆
but she's got a new air to her with that swimsuit!
But the star of today's show...
Even in a swimsuit with a mature design, those big bangs are making universes left and right!
Mix...
(ﾉゝ∀・)~キラッ☆
Of course, Mikono's swimsuit is cute,
but Yunoha...
Unbelievably adorable!
Are you ignoring me on purpose?
Mikono...
The wind blowing over the lake plays a melody.
Doesn't it feel wonderful, my friend?
Should we be doing this?
We can't do anything else until the High Commander gives us instructions.
Let's enjoy this. Consider it part of our training.
Training?
Are we still not good enough?
Here I go!
This isn't really about the swimsuit, but...
Mix is really pretty.
Yeah...
Mikono sure is pretty.
Damn it! My genes are going nuts!
What am I doing watching this opportunity go by?
Ready, aim, fire!
Andy!
Ow!
Sorry. Are you okay?
I'm fine. It's just a bruise.
It's nothing compared to the pounding pain in my heart!
Did you get hit in the chest, too?
That's not what I meant...
Well, I'm done.
Huh?
But I'd advise you to rest for a bit.
Mix!
Stay with me just a little longer.
I want to talk to you... alone.
They've been in there for a while.
What are Andy and Mix doing, anyway?
Let's bring them some of these.
I think we should leave them alone.
By the way, where's Mikono?
She...
Zessica's missing too.
I'm so stupid.
Mikono!
I just wanted to be away from everyone.
It looks like we're on the same wavelength today.
Put this on or you'll catch a cold.
So, Mix...
I know there's that "love is forbidden" thing...
But if I don't say this now, I'll hate myself forever.
Hate yourself? Whatever for?
Andy?
Mix! After the war with the Abductors is over...
Damn it, I'll be triggering my own death flag if I say this, huh?
Screw it! I'm not going to die!
Please, after this war is all over...
Um...
Say it! Just say it, Andy!
Say, "I know I'm all about digging holes, but let me fill the hole in your heart!"
Andy...
Mix!
"Let me fill the hole in your heart!"
"Let me... fill the hole..."
Mix!
Yes!?
Let me fill your hole!
My... hole?
Your hole!
No, wait! Not that hole! The one in your heart! I meant the...
Did you guys just hear a really loud sound?
I hate you!
In your heart...
I think I envied you all this time, Zessica.
What?
You can be open and honest with your feelings all the time.
You were able to tell Amata how you felt.
A lot happened before I could, though.
I envy you too, Mikono.
You're sweet, and you always do your best.
I'm sure all the boys want girls like you.
You're wrong!
Zessica, you're way more popular with the boys!
Nah.
They'll pick girls like you in the end.
Girls who they can fight for and protect.
Zessica?
The sky!
Is that a...
It's a Dimensional Gate!
Amata, let's boot up the Vectors!
Yeah!
What are the Abductors doing out here?
Wait, Andy!
I screwed up.
She totally hates me now.
I'm such a moron.
I want to crawl in a hole...
Dimensional Gate opening at the Lakeside area, zone ANH!
The regular Elements are out?
What's going on here?
Relax, Donar.
Chairman Crea! High Commander! What's happening?
What is that Abductor?
Let's get out of here, Mikono!
Andy!
Andy, what are you doing?
It's dangerous in this weather!
Get out of that hole!
Why? Leave me alone.
What?
Winter Union! Go, Aquarion!
Aquarion Gepard!
We'll handle this weird Abductor.
Shrade, take care of everyone left above ground!
Of course, my friend!
It's so cold!
I'm from the south, so this cold is extra intense for me!
Take shelter in this hole Andy dug!
You'll be protected from the cold underground!
Did the Abductor cause this blizzard?
We'll be okay. Amata will save us.
Damn it! Without our Element suits...
The heat isn't working?
Cold... so cold...
How deep did Andy dig?
Andy!
Andy...
It's over...
It's all over for me...
Andy's aura level is almost at minimum!
Then it's time.
Time to dig it up!
Do it, Andy W. Hol!
What is this?
This sound...
is resonating across dimensions.
What the...
It's finally begun, Fudo.
The seed that fell into the earth is sprouting.
In time, it bears fruit year after year.
Thus does it bestow life upon the next generation!
It's cold...
Water? No, wait, is that milk?
It's warm...
This is a hot spring? It smells funny.
What are you doing here?
I'm back!
Sorry!
Zessica?
Mikono?
Amata!
Mixed Bath Union! Go, Aquarion!
I can feel it rising up!
From the depths of the earth!
The energy of life itself!
Aquarion Evol!
In ancient alchemy, men and women boiling in one pot
represented each working together and covering for the weaknesses of the other.
The Elements are coming together in the bath,
fighting as one and covering each others' weaknesses.
Is that what you wanted from this special training, High Commander Fudo?
So that's why we're bathing together. But why the bananas?
A bunch of bananas are a bunch of fruits that represent ripening!
In the Garden of Atlandia, the Serpent that tempted Eve hid itself in a banana tree.
The banana is the fruit of Paradise, and the fruit of the Sun.
As it ripens, the banana rises up and faces the Sun!
This feels wonderful!
I feel warmth all through my body!
Let's warm up!
Aquarion...
has shed its peel.
Cluster Infinity Punch!
Break him!
They did it!
Fill the hole... in your heart...
I've found a fragment of the Wings of the Sun.
But the better part of them are elsewhere.
You can have as many fruits of the Sun as you wish.
But as for the Wings of the Sun...
Morning, Amata!
Morning...
Um, Zessica?
Zessica, what are you wearing?
What happened?
I just had a change of heart.
Oh, I forgot to tell you...
Amata rejected me.
But that's okay.
If love ripens, Aquarion goes nuts, you know.
I'll keep loving Amata, even if he never loves me back.
kimi he tsuzuku sakamichi ni
There were white flowers growing
shiroi hana ga saiteta
on the road on the hill that leads to you
yume kara sameta ato mo kanashii sora miteta
When I woke from the dream, the sky still looked sad
kono kimochi happa no ue ni susunderu
My feelings drift on a leaf in the wind
asatsuyu wo ochiru oto ni mimi wo sumaseteru no
I'm straining my ears for the sound of the dew falling
kamisama anata ga tsukutta sekai wa kanpeki ja nai
God in Heaven, this world You made is far from perfect
koko de wa mainichi koi ga boroboro shindeku
Down here, love is shattered day by day
hajimete suki ni natta no wo anata wa shiranai deshou
You don't know what it's like to fall in love for the first time
chikyuu no uragawa de ii kara soba ni ite hoshikatta
Let it be on the other end of the world, but I wanted to be with him
watashi wo wasuretemo ii kara soba ni ite hoshikatta
Even if You were to forget me, I wanted to be with him
Who was I back then?
A strong-willed and confident fighter!
A strong-willed...
I don't know! I don't understand!
Next Time
Rare  Igura