Do you feel better now?
I do! Thank you!
Mikono!
Mikono's on the tower!
Calling all Elements.
Abductors detected in the Neo-Kowloon area.
Training has been suspended.
Cayenne, Zessica, and Andy, please
return to the Academy immediately.
I'll take care of it for you, my friend.
Head back to the Academy.
You too, Sazanka.
But Mikono is in danger!
Do you think your sister is more
important than your duty as an Element?
Hey, wait for me!
You go well together.
Your Union will be the greatest and most beautiful of all.
If only I could give it to you.
osore
Even if you're scared
living your life   don't give up now   keep moving on
Just live your life, don't give up now, keep moving on
kimi wo dakishimeru nandomo nandomo nandomo
And I'll come for you over and over and over again
ashita boku wa kimi ni deau darou
We'll find each other soon enough
wazukana hoshiakari wo tayori ni
By the faintest glimmer of starlight
boku ni wa kimi ga wakaru yo wakaru yo
I know you, I know you
sen'oku no toki wo koe futari hiraku densetsu no tobira
It's been billions of years, but now we can open the door to our legend
naraku no ao tobikoete
I crossed over the deep blue void
kimi to hai ni naru tame
so I could burn to ash along with you
nagaki rinne wo kanashimi tsurete tabi shitekitanda
I've had a long journey on the vast wheel of fate, gathering sorrows along the way
zenryoku de mikansei kimi no tonari de
I'm not perfect, but I'm giving all I have
kawaita kokoro hodoke chi wo nagasu kedo
If I open my fragile heart to you, I know I'll bleed...
soba ni iru yo zutto yorisotte zutto
But I'll always be with you, always be in your arms
futari hikari no fune ni noru
We'll get on a shining ship of light
kaze no hajimari no oto kanadeyou
And call forth the wind with our voices
Found you.
You stink.
You stink deliciously.
Mikono!
This is...
It's not love.
a forbidden meeting.
The Agitato of Life
Mikono!
What a delicate little thing.
Let Mikono go!
Where's your smell?
You don't. You don't smell at all.
Why the hell don't you have a smell?
Hey.
Mind if I kill you?
I'd really prefer you didn't...
Huh.
Wait!
Buzz off.
This is my wench.
No...
I won't let you...
I won't let you have Mikono!
Asshole!
His wings!
What the hell's that noise?
Kagura has gone to Vega again.
Who opened the gate for him?
Kagura's Gnis was supposed to be locked out.
It's been a long time, Izumo.
You've grown up, Jin.
Mikage!
I had a feeling you were behind this.
When did you awaken?
When?
I was awakened by a kiss.
From the Machine Angel's forbidden power.
Why did you help Kagura?
I merely saw him off.
The chosen one, blazing a trail into a new world of love.
"New world of love"?
The Machine Angel unleashed its forbidden powers.
And so, the Rare Igura within it is guiding Kagura.
Aren't you a little curious about the Rare Igura he follows so doggedly?
One that can leash the Machine Angel, at that.
She may be the true Eve for us of Altair.
Continue the reconnaissance of Vega.
If another irregularity occurs, take back the Mithra Gnis by force.
Yes, sir.
Alisia...
Hey, mind if I kill you?
Sure.
If you can play me.
You smell real faint.
And you kinda smell like her.
Damn it!
You would play a lovely sound.
Shrade stayed in Neo-Kowloon, didn't he?
Fine.
Deploy as soon as Cayenne, Zessica, and Andy return.
Roger.
Uhm... I've been wondering this for a while.
How come Shrade's never been deployed?
He always has the best record for the mock battles.
So the girls have been curious as to why...
Boys and girls Union together now,
so we should know about Elements we might do it with sometime.
Shrade Elan had a great gift with music from a young age.
But a strong, dark Element power infused the music from his piano.
They said his music could reach into
people's minds and play on their pain.
So rumors spread, and eventually he became a terrible weapon.
This sound!
Neo-Deava?
So Shrade got pulled in by the chairman kid?
Wait, how old is the chairman anyway?
But the Element aptitude test revealed something terrible.
Piloting Aquarion would shorten Shrade's life.
Aquarion amplifies the power within its Elements.
That power feeds back into the Elements, each strengthening the other.
Shrade's Element power is too strong.
His sick body can't handle channeling Aquarion's power.
I'm so sorry.
It took a little damage.
But it has a lovely sound.
I would die happy hearing its voice.
Mikono!
I'm sorry...
I have to tell him I'm sorry...
You're sorry? Him?
What are you talking about, Mikono?
The Abductor alarm!
Vectors!
Goddamn it! Why can't anyone leave us alone?
My wench...
Where is she?!
It's him!
It's that beastial Abductor again!
Mithra Gnis.
Is that the name of the robot, High Commander?
I can smell better from in here.
Cayenne!
Not this one.
Must be that one!
Look out, Zessica!
I can tell...
He's looking for Mikono.
Mikono! You're awake!
Amata...
Where am I?
Mikono, you were saying that you have to apologize to him.
Apologize?
I don't know.
I was so scared when he grabbed me.
But I felt like he really cared about me.
And then I thought, I'd felt that before...
I can't shake him!
Found you.
My wench!
Are you all right, my friend?
Shrade?
Let me take over.
But your body can't take it!
Give me my wench!
Mikono! Why, that...
Don't worry about me! Amata!
I felt it too.
I think I know him.
And I know I can't let him take you.
Cayenne!
That's not him! Wait...
Shrade!
Why is he in a Vector?
You can't do this!
Our enemy is not playing with us.
You need me for this fight.
But your body...
Element Change!
Call back Andy W. Hol!
What? But I was finally about to Union with a girl!
Get over here, wench!
What are you doing?
Vector Z!
Mikono, get out of here.
Amata!
Chairman Crea, requesting permission for Union.
Shrade! You can't!
I'm ready to die.
If I can't play Aquarion, I may as well be dead.
Union authorized! Shrade Elan, you're the head!
I've been waiting for this.
For when I could finally play Aquarion!
Melodic Union! Go, Aquarion!
A powerful sound is resonating inside my chest!
But why does it feel so comfortable?
This is the sound of life itself!
The first sound we made when we came out of the womb!
Aquarion Spada!
A Union with Vector Y as the head!
Shrade's power has given Aquarion a new form.
Aquarion.
The moment I first laid eyes upon it,
my still heart began to beat once more in a powerful staccato.
That is...
the melody of my soul.
Damn you, Machine Angel! I'll get you out of my way for good!
Amata. Zessica.
To live is to engrave your life.
To make the melody of your life resonate with the world!
Help me! Help me play out the melody of my life!
You got it!
If you're going to beat him, I'm with you!
Now let us play out our souls a arpeggio!
Damn it!
Amata's Element power is rocketing!
Add Zessica's force...
And when you combine those two with Shrade's power...
Set the moon in the sky with vibrato,
and the moon on the water in allegro vivace.
What are you talking about?
Then I will play the moon within us in the agitato of life!
Moonlight Requiem!
What?
Did he win?
I'm not done...
I'm not done fighting yet!
Sorry. I'm taking back the Mithra Gnis.
Stop messing up our Vega reconnaissance.
You're just making my job harder.
Damn you, Jin...
He's getting away!
Shrade, let's go after him!
Shrade?
Wait, Shrade is...
Shrade! Are you okay?
Shrade!
Mikono?
What's the matter, Mikono?
I don't know.
I don't know, but...
It hurts that I don't know.
kaze ni ubawareta wake janai
We weren't spirited away on the wind
katamichi bun no yuuki de bokura
We knew we could never return, and found the courage
higeki wo ukeireru
to accept the hardship
kokoro ga koko ni atta hazu no kuudou
There's an emptiness where my heart used to be
motto boku ga ookikereba
If only I was stronger
kimi wo mirai wo sukueta darou ka
I could have saved you, and our future...
taisetsu na hito wo mamoru sube ga tatta hitotsu shika motenai
I only know of one way to keep the people I love
sonna anata ga haguretadayou sora
And you left me and disappeared into the sky
anata ijou no hito ni deaenai
I'll never find anyone like you again
tsuki ni aragau nagai furea
A long flare reaches out against the moon
hajimaru mo sezu owaru monogatari
The story ends before it could even begin
kizutsukiuru yawarakasa
So soft, so fragile
tojikometa senritsu kanaderu hodo
I will call up the melody locked away
utau hodo kowareru hodo ni
And sing it until I destroy myself
anata ga koishii
That's how much I love you
I hear the Academy is haunted by the ghost of a missing Element.
You'll be so scared you can't even take a leak at night!
I'll dig a hole out, just in case.
Next time on Aquarion Evol: The Midnight Girl.
Next Time
The Midnight Girl