hikaru suiheisen
Just over the bright horizon,
s
t
r
U
hajimari to owari no
where the beginning and the end
s
t
r
U
tokeau soko wa
melt into one,
s
t
r
U
namida no furusato na no
lies the homeland of tears
s
t
r
U
furueteru te de
I've already pocketed
s
t
r
U
shinjirareru mono
my trembling hand
s
t
r
U
poketto ni tsumekonda
which holds my beliefs
s
t
r
U
kanata de yurameiteru shinkirou
A mirage shimmers in the distance
s
t
r
U
sora miagereba
I look to the sky
s
t
r
U
michibiitekureru you na
hoping it will show me the way
s
t
r
U
natsukashikute atsui hikari wo kureru
And it gives off a familiar, warm light
s
t
r
U
anata wa chiisaku te wo furu yo
You wave at me faintly
s
t
r
U
ikanakucha
I must go
s
t
r
U
mou nakanai yo shangurira
Don't cry anymore because Shangri-La,
s
t
r
U
aratana sekai he to daibu shiyou
a new world, is waiting for us
s
t
r
U
aoiro ni dakareta boku wa
As I'm embraced by its blue...
s
t
r
U
kono mune no takanari to tomo ni
My heart beats loudly
s
t
r
U
Naru?
Naru... Naru!
Naru... why?
Why did you choose Truth?
Don't leave!
Don't leave, Naru!
What's this...?
Naru! Naru!
What's going...
Naru... Naru...
Naru...!
Naru!!
Ao... Ao!
Goodness, I'm certainly not impressed.
I'm so sorry.
I'll run through today's flight data again.
That's not what I meant.
I was referring to you being up so late.
Regaining stamina is also a part of being a pilot, you know.
I know... but...
With Alleluia and Kyrie's Third Engines inoperative,
I must be strong enough by myself.
I have to... become stronger.
What was that for?!
That's enough! Get some rest.
My IFOs aren't meant to be piloted by sleep-deprived kids!
Mr. Alex...
Hey! Ao!
The new parts have come in!
We've been getting by with Kyrie's spare parts up till now,
but Nirvash will be back in top shape for the next mission!
We'll be counting on you, Ace!
Warhead
You're still up working, Chief?
Well, something was bothering me.
Doesn't it bother you too? Secrets, that is.
Indeed. Since the battle near Ogasawara,
emergences have been becoming more frequent.
That's not all.
Since the battle at Arizona, Secrets have started to resemble humans more and more.
Then there's the signal Georg had observed.
That was—
The unknown signal I had detected during the battle of Ogasawara
has been detected in seven further incidents since then.
The analysis is not yet complete.
However, according to measurements, the signal gain is increasing.
What's your opinion, Christophe? The Japanese Government's—
That nonsense?
That the Scub is an invader of our universe,
and Secrets are the immune system that eradicates foreign objects?
It might be rubbish, but the fact is that they've pricked the ears of many countries around the world.
It's all currently under investigation.
I'll keep you informed of any developments.
I'll be counting on you.
In any case, be it Scub or Secret, we'll be the ones dictating which one represents justice.
I have one more question for you.
Where do you stockpile all the Quartz that you gather?
So you haven't discovered anything...
Even after sending an agent in to infiltrate and investigate us.
You are aware that we can pressure people even higher than you, right?
The Big Blue World is merely one of our stockholders.
I don't recall ever taking orders from them.
We are currently undergoing medical screenings.
All staff: please confirm your schedules and follow your superiors' directions.
Anything wrong with your body? Vertigo? Nausea?
Nothing really...
Umm...
Mama Hannah, it's time for the shuttle.
I got it.
Send me the data once you're done.
Yes ma'am.
What's wrong?
No...
It's nothing.
It's pretty rare for Mama Hannah to come all the way down from space.
Well, you know, it must be true.
We've heard all the rumors.
All his abnormalities are a result of the genes inherited from his mother.
Eureka must be really pretty.
I wonder if Ao's taking after her.
Ao's been acting all strange since she came along.
By the way, Elena, weren't you acting weird the other day when Eureka appeared?
What was that all about?
That's classified information.
I'm done.
You're next, Chloe.
I know what you're doing.
You called for company-wide medical
screening, but your goal was just Ao, right?
I don't know what you're talking about.
What did you talk about with Eureka?
Was it something about the effects of trapar on the human body?
Even if...
Even if she irreversibly changed his world,
all mothers in the world will still sympathize with her.
Don't you think so?
Well...
Does that mean she's...
Have you got what I asked for?
Sleeping pills, right?
It doesn't have any side effects, but don't overdose on them.
How much do I owe you?
Forget it.
You're my pal from the same island.
Thanks.
I would've had to go get a prescription—
It's not your body that's keeping you awake, right?
Eureka said it too.
She said that the Secrets are not the enemy.
Aren't you just worried about that?
Don't get the wrong ideas.
Well then, let me make the introductions once again.
We secured this on Japanese territory.
This is a Secret.
A real one?
Is it some sort of a life form? Or...
Both organic and inorganic matter are present in its body.
Not even infrared or x-rays allow us to peek at its inner structure.
We're unable to tell if it's a machine or a life form.
However, unlike Secrets we have seen before,
this one is emitting radio waves of a certain frequency.
We've determined that this is some form of a signal.
Thus, we returned a signal of the same wavelength.
Is that according to the IAA's first contact protocol?
What's that?
International Aerospace Association.
Starting from odd numbers, prime numbers,
and other forms of information that occur naturally,
we've managed, step by step, to teach it human speech patterns.
As a result...
Ask it if it can comprehend this signal.
I didn't expect the Japanese government to publicize its discoveries of the Secret.
How about we figure out what trick they're using?
But if the Secrets are truly the protectors of this universe, just as they claimed...
Don't be silly.
That's impossible.
Excuse me.
It's me.
What's the matter?
What?
If I'm not mistaken, you must be Han Juno.
I've had the pleasure of meeting your father on a few occasions.
Why is the Japan government undergoing negotiations with a trapar company?
Our country is solely dependent on its economy.
I didn't realize that we're not supposed to contact your father's company.
On the mainland of America?
We most certainly retrieved the Quartz from that Scub and forced it to calm down.
Why would it return?
There are no documented instances of a Scub reactivating.
According to the database—
We received a report that a Secret has already emerged.
I just have to deal with it, right?
We are outside the ZOA, but we have visual on the Secret.
Wait, a humanoid?!
Fleur, let's get it over with!
Mark!
Set!
Sensation!
Got it!
Wait...
No way! It's undamaged?
It's still in one piece? It should've been blown to smithereens!
Girls, cover me!
Wait, Ao!
Long range assaults are useless against Secrets!
I'll go into close quarter combat with Nirvash.
You're kidding!
Those aren't even missiles! Why are they following him?!
Run, Ao!
I'm running already!
I can't die here!
Ao was shot down?
His life is not in danger.
We can leave the rescue to team Pied Piper.
I can't believe it.
How could a plant reactivate?
Prioritize defending the plant.
Rescuing the wounded can wait.
What are you doing here?!
Unauthorized personnel are not allowed here!
Ao was shot down, wasn't he?
Assuming you don't have enough men for the rescue mission,
the Gazelle Inc is more than willing to subcontract it.
We really don't have enough men.
Take the offer, Stanley.
What should we do?
That's it?
Don't get too close carelessly!
Once it locks on to you, there's no way of escaping it!
Lock on?
She's right!
So that's what hit Nirvash?
Ao! Ao! Respond to me!
Ao!
We've rescued the pilot.
The machine is yours to retrieve!
This voice...
Why is he here?
You're such a great pilot.
Shut up!
So we're only able to take it down in a 5v1?
Incoming calls from different countries.
Plants all around the world have been reactivated.
No way!
Our plant!
Is this true?!
We're doomed!
We have requested a priority line.
Please calm down and wait for your turn.
We're being flooded by requests from all around the world.
If any Secrets are to appear, we will separate into groups and deal with them.
Deal with those giants?
The children won't be able to take it!
We're trying our best to deal with it.
But the fact is that the Quartz have
mysteriously reappeared in all those Scubs.
So eventually...
This is...
Chloe.
We've switched places.
How is Nirvash?
Did I do it again?
Kinda.
You turned this into quite a mess.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Ao...
Secrets are our enemy, right?
What do you think?
Honestly, I have no clue...
What are you girls doing here?
Look.
The plant coral...
is glowing?
This is in the Vesterålen islands, Norway.
Maeve and I are from there.
We all moved there from Ireland to work at the plant.
I wasn't even one years old back then.
Where are your parents?
They still live there.
I don't want to lose anyone anymore...
Like how I lost Bruno...
I'll protect everyone, no matter what the enemy is.
Sorry, you've been ordered to scramble.
Can you go?
Say, isn't Eureka behind all this?
Ever since two or three of your mothers showed up, weird things keep happening!
Even Naru went nuts.
That can't be the case.
But...
But that's not possible, right?
There it comes.
We have no choice now.
If we could gather them in one place...
I'll be the decoy.
They targeted Nirvash the last time as well.
Ao!
But there were two Nirvashes back then!
Eureka isn't here.
Ao, Elena, Fleur.
Standby in your cockpits until we decide on a strategy.
But—
We're going.
I still—
Let's go.
But—
Come on, Ao.
We've arrived.
Using my automatic translation algorithm,
it's likely that I will be able to analyze the radio waves
that the Secrets are emitting and send the results to HQ.
Do it, Georg!
What the hell are you guys doing here?!
You were...
You were in the inspection team.
What's that?
Signal caught.
Connected... Signal...
Analyzing...
Hey, are you all right?
Yes, I am. And you are?
I am Han Juno from Generation Bleu.
I am what you call a Secret.
We're being hacked?
Secret, what are you?
Where do you come from?
Who made you?
I am created to rid this space of alien substances.
Where? By whom?
It is all a natural process.
Explain what's going on!
If you're really a Secret, tell us why the Scub is reactivating all around the globe!
Ten years ago...
In the place you call Okinawa, a huge Quartz disappeared from the Scub.
Ten years later, that Quartz is now—
I get it. Leave the Scub to us.
I cannot do that.
Our goal is to eliminate the Scub Coral.
As long as Scub exists in this space, we will be pursuing it.
I see...
If what he says about Secrets reacting automatically to alien matter is true...
You don't want to do that, Blanc!
The Big Blue World won't keep quiet.
Connect me to the American Secretary of State.
This is an emergency.
Can't we do anything else?
What are you talking about?
Do you want to disobey our orders?
And what do you want to talk about, Christophe?
We have no time.
Let's cut to the chase.
The Scub is reactivating all around the world.
This is due to the material called Quartz you asked about the other day.
Papa...
What is he talking about?
Disconnect him right now!
All Secrets emerge to destroy the Quartz.
In order to gather all the Secrets,
we just need to gather more Quartz in one place than there is in all the Scub around the world.
And where would you get such an amount of Quartz?
Stop, Blanc!
We, Generation Bleu, have collected the Quartz from every Scub we calmed.
We are storing them all in space.
We are going to them to destroy all the Secrets that have emerged around the world!
To be continued.
futashikana*
s
*T/L Note: I'm so uncertain
boku
no sekai
ga ima*
v
*T/L Note: In the blink of an eye,
mabataku
ma ni
kawari-
hajimete
hirogaru*
A
*T/L Note: my whole world started changing and opening up.
ano hi mitsuketa yume no tsuzuki wa doko*
A
*T/L Note: That day, I found out where my dream continues
sugu ni
sagashite
miseru yo*
A
*T/L Note: I'll show you its sequel now
ima mo boku
dake wa
oboeteirun da*
N
*T/L Note: Right now, I'm the only one who still remembers
natsukashii
nukumori*
.
*T/L Note: that familiar warmth
saa
mou
ikou
ka*
A
*T/L Note: Now let's get going
machiu-
keteru
unmei ni*
)
*T/L Note: I was frozen with fear
tachisukumi
obieteta*
H
*T/L Note: thinking of the fate that awaited me
mou
kess-
hite
mayo-
wanai
you ni*
A
*T/L Note: I'll become so strong that I won't
tsuyoku
natte
yuku yo*
Z
*T/L Note: be uncertain ever again
nido to modorenai kako mo ashita kara kate ni shite*
A
*T/L Note: The past that can't be written will support me from tomorrow on
sou
yatte
noriko-
ete yuku
no sa*
q
*T/L Note: I'll overcome it all
sou shite boku
wa boku ni naru*
A
*T/L Note: and I'll become myself
sou shite boku
wa boku ni naru*
Don't repost to any manga readers!
You have to sign up for our forum to download!
Preview
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
Ao is determined to fight even if he has to deny himself.
The Polaris Plan is executed with him in the center.
The Secrets are closing in on the capsule with mankind's fate in it.
What path will the boy choose in the face of chaos?
Eureka Seven, episode 16: Guardians Hammer.
Listen to the voices of the children of the stars.