Kokoro
masshiro PAGE mekuru
I walk through the white pages of my storybook
Incoming Text
tobidasu irodoru hajikeru
just waiting to be painted
mangekyou no fuukei
with a kaleidoscope of my experiences.
From
Me
To
You
kizukeba STORY wa mada
This story has only
gikochinaku hajimatta bakkari
just barely begun
shinkokyuu wo mou ikkai
I take a deep breath
tabi suru kaze tsutsumikomu you ni senaka wo osu
and the wind wraps around me and urges me forward
aa yawarakakute atatakai kimi no te
Your hand is so warm held within mine;
nigiri shimete sono kokoro no oku made todoku you ni
it reaches all the way to my heart.
hohoenmi de kureta nara nigirikaeshite kuretara
I can't see a brighter future
boku wa tada mae wo miteru
than you smiling and taking my hand as well
Where's Sawako?
She's at the festival after party.
Oh...
Sawako goes out a lot now, doesn't she?
If she gets a boyfriend, she'll be out even more than this!
Here.
Th-That's right. When Sawako gets married, she'll...!
We're not talking about some far off event like marriage.
After the Festival
I wonder if they're on their way yet.
I wonder!
Until they get to the party, it's just the two of them! All by themselves...
"Did you wait long?"
"I just got here."
That's probably exactly what they said!
I can't wait to make fun of them.
What if the two of them don't show up??
Oh, man. I would so punch Kazehaya.
I meant to take a peek at him in secret but he totally looked at me!!
W-Why are you so upset? That hurts!
I-I'm sorry!
I'm just so nervous, I—
Yeah, it's really nerve wracking.
And embarrassing.
He feels the same way!
I like you!
You feel the same way too, right?
I want all of you!
It's like a dream!
Sawako!
No, he only touched her with his hand!
No way, he didn't hug her?
No, barely touched her!
I see!
No way!
I wish I had seen that!
Wow...
No, still wrong! You guys are too close!
Kazehaya!
Oh Kazehaya!
Some people weren't lucky enough to see so we were reenacting it for them!
Oh right! Yesterday, in the classroom—
Joe...
Can I punch you now?
Was what we just saw real?
Do you really like Sadako, Kazehaya?
What did you mean by "same here"?
When you said it was like a dream, did you mean a good dream? A bad dream?
Wait, did you two just come together?
Are you two dating?
Where should I start from? Oh gosh!
In a word,
yes.
Are you serious?
Why?
You mean it?
How did Sadako manage to get with Kazehaya?
Magic?
No!
I fell for her.
What?!
What??
You didn't know either?! Poor Kazehaya.
You understand, don't you?
Y-Yes.
This is really okay, right?
Man, you make me so nervous!
Thank goodness.
They look like they're for real!
It's not just looks!
Wow!
Sadako, you're amazing!
I can't believe you managed to win over Kazehaya!
You weren't just faking it.
Where do we pray?
I want to pray too!
Please let us get significant others too!
Don't say that!
Why did things turn out like this?
It's okay, they both look pretty happy.
I can't do magic!
Second year, class D, congratulations on sixth place in the school festival!
Cheers!
I still can't believe it...
No,
I want to believe it.
Sawako!
It's okay.
No one...
thinks I'm an annoyance.
Dammit! Women!
So cute!
What do we have here?
What? Aren't you Miura?
It's Pin!
What are you doing here? And with girls from another class!
Isn't our class having their party right now?
I was going to go, but these girls invited me out first.
Aren't you lonely, drinking all the way out here by yourself?
So lonely!
Shut up!
Oh, it's our class.
What?
Strawberry time?
Now he's a "confessed and successful" Kazehaya!
Sadako!
This is just wonderful!
Teacher!
Kazehaya, come here a sec.
What?
Just come on.
Why?
Let's go!
What's with them?
Were they really such good friends?
Kuronuma.
Don't make Sadako cry anymore, now.
Did you hear why Sadako was crying outside that day?
Cause she thought you liked someone!
Why would she think that?
Cause she heard it.
From who?
From me.
I knew that was your fault!
Oops!
And it's Sawako, not Sadako!
Are you sure it's okay for me to call her Sawako?
It's okay. I'm just using Sadako as a cute nickname for her.
Did you manage to tell him?
What we talked about yesterday?
What we...
Oh right!
You're too loud!
Pin!
Shota!
Come here for a sec.
What?
Are you two dating?
Yeah.
Really?
You sure you aren't the only one who thinks that?
Did you actually ask her "Kuronuma, go out with me"?
No, but she under—
What!
Does she really look like someone who would just somehow understand things?
Ask her right now!
Yeah... Asking "Do you understand?" isn't the right way to do it.
Kuronuma.
Yes?
Will you marry me?
Get...
Marr
...Married?
iage
Just kidding.
Leave!
Go away!!
Who do you think helped you two get this far?
Let...
Let?
Let me think about it.
What?!
Wait, Kuronuma.
Please let me think about it!
Kuronuma!
Are you sure it's okay to not go after her and explain?
What do you think you're doing?!
Whose fault is it that things are like this?
That's true... Worst case scenario, she might say yes.
She doesn't understand jokes.
She thinks you're serious, and when you tell her you're not,
she'll be so upset.
So upset...
Now it's not a question of asking her out anymore.
She might turn you down.
Good luck!
Hello? Dad?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'll try not to stay out too late.
Yeah.
I wanted to ask—
No, never mind.
What is it? It's okay.
If I were to get married, how would you feel?
Never mind! Forget I asked!
What's wrong?
Kuronuma.
Kazehaya.
You've got it wrong.
I didn't mean that.
About... Getting married, I mean.
Kazehaya, are you saying that was a misunderstanding?
Yeah.
You can hit me.
No, wait.
Even I didn't really take that seriously.
I knew it was Mr. Arai who said that.
What?
Yes.
What?!
Let me think about it.
Let me fantasize about it.
Hide... I need to find a hole and hide...
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to make you misunderstand things.
I wanted to imagine it.
The idea was so beautiful that I couldn't help myself.
I'm sorry for being so selfish.
I shouldn't have asked if you understood.
What?
This is too important not to say straight out.
We'll never move forward otherwise.
Please go out with me!
I'll always take care of you.
Always...
Yes.
I also have something important to say to you.
What is it?
Don't hate me, okay?
No matter what you say, I'll never hate you.
I can't look at you without hidden desires anymore.
There's no way I could hate you for that!
I guess we had nothing to worry about.
Lucky them!
We can see what you want.
Nah, I just think they look really good together.
Yeah. I feel bad for saying that he's the most distant from her.
Who'd you say that to?
Who?
K-Kazehaya.
When?
Just before they started being really awkward with each other.
It was you?!
I-I'm sorry!
Forgive her.
Everything turned out okay in the end!
You too!
Go back to the girls from the other class!
Yano-chin!
Chigusa!
Class C extended their party too?
Yup.
Where's Sadako?
Strawberry time?
You guessed it.
Good job, Sadako!
It wasn't a dream
Not a dream
Read
your diary!!
Read me
Note
This diary is not a dream.
It looked very
good on him.
I made it.
He was wearing
regular clothes
at the party.
It seems like it wasn't a dream!
Sleeping made it seem like it was nothing but a dream.
But all of these reminders I left for myself before bed...
Dad's going to be—!!
It's real
They're real.
I like you!
Please go out with me!
I'm so happy.
It all really happened.
What?
What is all this?
Something about my advice—
With black magic?
Sadako got Kazehaya?
Kazehaya's eyes supposedly turned red while he was confessing to her!
I like you. Like like like you!
So scary!
She's totally controlling him!
I believe it.
Wow.
Sadako.
No pushing! Form a line!
You guys!
What are you lining up for?
Supposedly everyone who got advice at the Black Magic Café were able to confess and are now dating!
N-No way.
To be feared...
and worshiped...
she's already a god.
Charge them for it already!
F-Feels like I'm swindling them!
Seriously, if she had that sort of skill the two of us would already have amazing boyfriends.
Totally! There are only idiots, losers, and baldies here though!
But I'm glad she doesn't have to worry about being bullied.
Yeah, nothing to worry about.
Please let me borrow a good luck charm!
Like one of your spirit summons!
Don't tell me Kazehaya believes I have magic too!
You're still saying that?
I don't even want to get involved.
I said it wasn't like that! I've always liked her.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
He's blushing so it's got to be true!
That means...
G-
Good morning.
Kazehaya says he's always liked you!
Yeah, he said it was like a dream come true!
Hey! What do you know about—
Since we have such a large audience, even from other classes,
why don't you make it crystal clear for everyone?
What is Sawako to you?
Poke, poke.
My girlfriend.
Girlfriend?!
So blunt!
He used such a real, direct word.
My dreams really did come true, but it's really overwhelming.
Just leave me alone for a while.
To sum it up, please look this way.
Yes, that's it exactly.
Dream Come True
Wish
Dream
K
S
Boyfriend
Girlfriend
Strawberry Time
in love with
Always liked
Wants all of
Now everyone, please be sure to spread the good news!
Didn't I say to leave me alone?!
They're so lovey-dovey.
Yeah, they were like that at the party too... Especially Kazehaya.
Looking at them now, I can't believe I didn't see how perfect
they were for each other until now.
Really?
This is how it should be.
But really...
No one thought Kurumi would be the heartbroken one,
and Sadako the winner.
douka ima dake wa furimukanaide
Please don't look at me right now
yuugure sawagu kaze
The sun's set, the wind's blowing,
furesouna kyouri
and we're so close that we can almost touch
kimi wo mitsumeteru zutto
My gaze has always been fixed on you
kimi ga suki de
I like you
I've always liked you
kono omoi koi demo ii
I don't mind if this emotion is what they call love,
kizu tsuitemo ii
and I don't care if I get hurt by it
nando demo tsutaetai
I just want to tell you, over and over again
kimi ni todoke
I want to reach you
Preview
An Important Person
My story has only just begun.
Next time: An Important Person.