-OP-
The wind whispers to me...
It's delicious. It's beyond delicious!
First of all, I have to make sense of everything.
Why is Menma here?
Divine Wrath!
The ghost of a mother-in-law tortured to death by her inhuman family strikes back!
Maybe she can't go to heaven because she's clinging to some worldly regret.
That sounds about right.
I don't get it.
Because...
The Menma I know is always...
smiling.
Who could like that ugly...
I've always wanted to apologize to her.
And it goes beyond ordinary contrition.
I know that much for sure.
Oh yeah! Maybe that's my wish: to have you go to school.
School.
nanpeeji mo tsuiyashite
Upon pages and pages of entries
We still don't
know the name
of the flower
we saw that day.
tuzurareta bokura no kibun
We've put down all our emotions
doushiteka ichigyou no
But now I've hit a writer's block
kuuhaku wo umerarenai
I don't know how to finish this page anymore
oshibana no shiori hasande
Putting a bookmark in my diary
kimi to korogasu tsukaisute no jitensha
You and I go out to ride the bike we found in the dumpster
wasurekake no renga wo
Let's go to our secret place
tsumiageta basho ni yukou
Where we piled up our bricks of memories
umi wo miwatasu saka wo kakenobotte
Run up the hill, where we can see the horizon
kowaikurai ni aoi sora to
Where we can see the sky so fearfully blue
migite ni saidaa hidarite wa
With cider in my right hand
zutto kimi wo sagashiteiru
My other hand helps me search for you
souyatte ima wa boku no hou e
You used to come find me way back when
toitsumeru koto mo nakute
You used to demand me of so much more
mada futari wa sugu soko ni irunoni
You're both still standing right by my side
douka mata aemasuyouni nante
Yet why do I pray to see you both again?
douka shiteru mitai
There must be something off with me
What? Why are you going to school?
I shouldn't have to explain.
You don't have to force yourself.
What's up with that?
Before this you were yelling at me to go.
Before is before,
but now go forth before you!
Jintan.
Don't worry about me.
But you look so grim...
Now I'm all set!
Jintan?
There's something you want right?
You can rely on me a bit too you know.
I want to let you go to heaven.
Has Jintan's mom gone to heaven?
I wonder what going to heaven is like.
I'm in control.
I'm in control of myself.
That's right. My heart is empty...
Empty... empty...
It's impressive how someone can act like it's no big deal coming to school after that.
I know right. Are you talking about that first year from class 3?
Yeah. Her name's Naruko Anjou.
Look.
Anjou.
See? Looks like it was true after all.
Anjou?
Looks like it.
No way. Anjou?
That's awful...
This has been really anticlimactic.
There are a few people who have noticed me...
Who's he?
Maybe he's that guy who's never showed up before.
No way! She was called to the principal's office?
Naruko really screwed up.
But I don't think going to a love hotel is such a big deal.
But Anjou's got me beat by a long shot.
Now that it's come to this I feel like I psyched myself up for nothing.
But...
Someone from the PTA saw her.
Apparently she was with some old guy.
You think he was paying her?
But...
Everyone back to their seat.
Class is starting.
You can take a seat too Anjou.
Open up your books...
You messed up bad.
Let's see, the sentiment of this story's narrator
is on several occasions tinged with rage.
First and foremost is his anger at that man and his wife's betrayal.
I'm amazed she's taking notes at a time like this.
She's always been that way.
She's not smart. She learns slowly.
Try as she might...
Anjou's really out there.
Maybe she'll let you do her if you ask.
"...Sense of self-respect as a man has been gravely injured."
I didn't do
it damn it!
...bullshit!
Shut up
already! Die!
Anjou.
Help me.
Coming up
with whatever...
Second is his anger at himself.
The contents of the letter allude to this fact.
"To assert my dominance as both a man and a husband before him..."
Maybe she'll let you do her.
Did he pay her?
Hey guys...
Look at me.
I'm the guy who hasn't showed up to school in a while.
I haven't been to school except for the opening ceremony and the first week of classes.
How do I look to you? Ain't I a sight to see?
"Ain't I?"
What language is that?
Umm... Uh... What? Could you be...
Yadomi?
Jintan...
This girl...
I can give her a booty call any time, anywhere.
Are you all really making a big deal out of some love hotel?
Shouldn't it be obvious looking at her that she's been to one a time or two?
She's got that love hotel look to her!
Hey...
That's why...
I'll only say this once.
She'd never take money for sex.
And besides, she's a Capricorn and has blood-type A.
She's never gone out on a limb, she's serious to a fault, and had this pissed off look when she wore glasses.
She's got tons of stuff and she's a neat freak...
She's collected tiny things since she was little.
And her glasses... Damn, what a lame chick....
That's enough already!
Get your bag.
Lets get out of here.
Wait.
Naruko.
"Look at me."
You sounded like an exhibitionist.
Shut up.
But... Thank you.
You covered for me.
I didn't really...
But...
I don't have "that love hotel look"!
I've really never gone to a love hotel.
I've never even been inside one.
Yeah, sure thing.
What do you mean "Yeah, sure"?
Don't worry about it, just head home. Your mom's probably worried about you too.
Hey, where are you going? Your house is this way.
I'm not going home.
The school has probably already called my home.
She'll be angry at me.
She'd never let something like this go.
Hey, Anjou.
No. That's not right...
Episode 6
Forget, Don't Forget.
Hey, what do you mean you're staying over?
It'll only be until things calm down.
Until things calm down?
I'll have you know that this place is my castle,
and it's soaked up various manly fluids including but not limited to sweat and tears.
We all built it together.
Look, there's proof. I carved out that Hamtaro.
Hamtaro?
It looks more like a sausage than a ham.
I'll start off by cleaning up since that man juice stinks so much.
H-h-h-hey, don't touch those!
What the? This is rotten!
What are we going to do about her?
Even if she stays over she should tell her mom about it.
Otherwise there'll be an uproar.
She's so timid.
She always huddled in Menma's shadow.
Hey Jintan.
Where's Menma now?
She's not around.
Really?
Then how about we go check out her house?
We might get an idea about her wish that way.
You...
I want you to grant my wish.
Jintan?
Oh, right.
Wouldn't it be better if Menma came with us?
Yeah but, wouldn't it be kind of awkward to say
"Hey, let's go to Menma's house", when she's right there?
I didn't think you were that good at reading people's feelings.
Yeah, well, I did become a level 5 Shaman while I was in Vietnam.
Those exist?
Great, now that that's settled, let's text Yukiatsu.
Let's see, what's his number...
From Yukiatsu
About Today
We have exams coming up.
I'll be held up at school so I can't go.
Tsurumi's in the same situation.
What's up with that? He's so cold.
That's how college-prep schools are.
I guess. I'd thought that no one had changed at all after I saw everyone again.
But that's not the case. People do change, little by little.
Hey, maybe we shouldn't go to Menma's house after all.
Huh? Why?
Think about it, we've never even gone to her house to play before.
Yeah, Menma's dad was one scary guy.
But maybe this is a good opportunity.
I mean, I want to light an incense stick for Menma.
Yadomi?
I can't help but think about how Menma's mom will react when she sees us.
I can't believe everyone came here. Meiko would be so happy too.
Now come in, come in.
Could you say hello to Meiko?
Sure.
What's bothering me?
Menma's dead.
I've known that all along.
This is Meiko's room. Go ahead.
Hey, Tsurumi.
Minako wants you to give this to Matsuyuki.
This is embarrassing.
We're all in the same class. She should just give it to him herself.
Wait a sec.
Don't act so high and mighty.
You can't look down on me just because you're always by his side.
I know all about it! You like Matsuyuki.
What are you...
Tsurumi?
Is something wrong?
Let's go.
Right.
Heading home? Be careful.
There have been shady people around these parts lately.
People always get envious of you like that.
Sorry for causing you trouble.
I'm sure I'd be freed of all my worries the instant I sent out photos of you cross-dressing.
That's true.
Oh yeah, apparently Yadomi and the others are going to Menma's house.
Wow, so they're all taking what Yadomi said seriously.
Nobody can leave the past behind them.
You least of all.
I won't deny that.
You're finally being honest.
I couldn't get anything past you if I tried anyway.
He pisses me off.
Yadomi?
Be it the school I go to, or my overall standing,
right now I'm far above him in every way.
But I'm still getting caught up in his pace like back then.
He even spoke Menma's name.
How long does he plan to make a fool out of everyone?
On that day..
If only he hadn't told everyone to gather at the secret fort.
Didn't Menma call us that day?
That's right, Menma gave me a call.
She called?
Wait, that's right. She wanted to talk about something that day.
Yeah, she said she had something she wanted to talk about, so...
I didn't think she'd hand over Menma's diary that easily.
What a great mom.
But wasn't that depressing?
My husband told me I couldn't stay obsessed with Meiko forever, so he cleaned up this room.
Meiko's things are in here.
What else can they do? Seeing her things will only make it harder for them.
If they see...
I don't really know how a mother feels,
but I think having a child must be an extremely heavy burden in a lot of way.
You can say that with a straight face?
Maybe I should head home.
It's not like I'm worried about my parents or anything.
I just remembered something I had to do.
See ya!
She's not being honest with herself.
But anyway, we got the diary so let's head back to the secret fort and read it.
Could that wait a bit?
I'm in charge of cooking dinner tonight,
and I haven't washed the plates from this morning, so...
See ya!
Then I'll go ahead and...
No, don't read it without me. Don't do it!
I'm... all alone.
Seeing will only make it harder.
Then would it have been better not to have seen Menma?
No.
But...
Welcome back, Jintan! How was school?
I've already seen her.
Only harder...
So you know, I sort of went with the flow and went to see your mom today...
Confiscated!
Huh?
Confiscated! Confiscated!
CONFISCATED!
Hey!
Why...
Did you do something like that?
What do you mean why?
Menma?
If you do that my mom will remember me.
I'm putting my mom
through lots and lots of sadness.
I don't want to make her any more sad.
I don't want to make her remember me anymore.
You may not want her to remember you, but that's impossible.
Because...
I don't care that it's impossible!
Even if it's only a little bit,
I want my mom to forget about me.
Yeah right. You said yourself that you'd be happy if we all remembered you.
But...
Cut it out already!
You're always worrying about others like that.
Think about yourself a little more!
Your attitude pisses me off!
You laugh it off even when you're hurt.
When you cry it's only for other people.
Why am I yelling like this?
Jintan.
I'm...
Jintan!
You have a nosebleed!
Oh no! Umm, umm...
Here, stuff this tissue inside.
Wait a sec...
Tissue!
And then lie down facing up!
That way it'll get better.
Jintan?
Sorry.
I'm going out for a bit.
This late?
Jintan?
What the hell am I doing?
Really. What am I doing?
Yadomi? What are you doing here so late?
What about you? Didn't you go home?
And what about the way you're dressed?
It's not what you think!
I had some blood backed up in my nose already.
I swear it's not because you were turning me on...
Hey, calm down...
Get out! Pervert!
Pervy-scurvy one-touchy!
Now I have no doubts. She's definitely a virgin.
deai wa futtoshita shunkan
We met in an unexpected moment
kaerimichi no kousaten de koe wo kaketekureta ne
when you called out to me at the crosswalk,
"issho ni kaerou"
"Let's walk home together."
aa hanabi ga yozora kirei ni saite chotto setsunaku
The fireworks blossomed heartrendingly beautiful across the night sky,
aa kaze ga jikan to tomo ni nagareru
and time passed as swiftly as the wind.
ureshikute tanoshikute bouken mo iro iro shita ne
We shared so many happy times and thrilling adventures
futari no himitsu no kichi no naka
together in our secret base.
kimi to natsu no owari shourai no yume ookina kibou wasurenai
I will never forget the hopes and dreams we shared during that one summer's end.
jyuunen no ato hachigatsu mata deaeru no wo shinjite
I'm sure we will meet again in another August, in maybe ten years time.
kimi ga saigo made kokoro kara "arigatou" sakendeita koto shitetayo
I could feel your heartfelt thanks all the way until the end.
namida wo koraete egao
And I know it must've been painful
de sayounara setsunai yo ne
to hold back your tears and say goodbye with a smile.
saikou no omoide wo
But those are my best memories.
The ghost of a mother-in-law tortured to death by her inhuman family strikes back!