hikaru suiheisen
Just over the bright horizon,
s
t
r
U
hajimari to owari no
where the beginning and the end
s
t
r
U
tokeau soko wa
melt into one,
s
t
r
U
namida no furusato na no
lies the homeland of tears
s
t
r
U
furueteru te de
I've already pocketed
s
t
r
U
shinjirareru mono
my trembling hand
s
t
r
U
poketto ni tsumekonda
which holds my beliefs
s
t
r
U
kanata de yurameiteru shinkirou
A mirage shimmers in the distance
s
t
r
U
sora miagereba
I look to the sky
s
t
r
U
michibiitekureru you na
hoping it will show me the way
s
t
r
U
natsukashikute atsui hikari wo kureru
And it gives off a familiar, warm light
s
t
r
U
anata wa chiisaku te wo furu yo
You wave at me faintly
s
t
r
U
ikanakucha
I must go
s
t
r
U
mou nakanai yo shangurira
Don't cry anymore because Shangri-La,
s
t
r
U
aratana sekai he to daibu shiyou
a new world, is waiting for us
s
t
r
U
aoiro ni dakareta boku wa
As I'm embraced by its blue...
s
t
r
U
kono mune no takanari to tomo ni
My heart beats loudly
s
t
r
U
I knew it...
I loved you because I could never reach you...
No matter how far I go... It's still the same sky...
What's going on?!
Where's the attack coming from?!
This world is mistaken.
Truth!
Don't tell me that... you've been hiding in the Abe all this time!
I'm omnipresent.
But this world isn't mine.
You're just a Secret!
I came from a distant place.
A place where neither Scub Coral or Secrets are present.
A world where humans create energy and everything shines in a brilliant light.
Fire! Open fire!
Did we get him?
Galaxy 2 Galaxy
All's well that ends well.
Now, how do I report this to Colonel Tanaka?
Do something! Quick!
Me? Sorry!
The Abe...
What?! Where did he come from?!
Truth!
Why is he still alive?!
Maggie! Elena! Get out of here!
Maggie!
Elena!
Is this what you want?
Papa told me with his final words that Truth was a Secret.
Didn't you use to corporate with Truth?
That was all Nakamura from the Defense Department.
That doesn't matter now.
What does Truth want?
He was indeed once a Secret.
Really? Not Johansson's son?
Johansson?
But he's lost himself.
Truth, just what do you want?!
Are you an ally of the Japanese?
Then you're on our side now.
Are you an ally of the Secrets?
Then you're still on our side!
But, still, you killed the President...
What the hell?
I don't get it!
I'm your enemy.
Oh really?!
What?
Truth has abnormally high trapar density surrounding himself.
You could call it a trapar storm or perhaps whirlpool.
No one can overcome it.
But Ao can see the waves of trapar.
It is not possible with his Nirvash.
It has no soul.
A machine having a soul?
What's going on? I can't move...
Elena!
Damn! I can't read the flow of the trapar!
Naru...
Naru? What's wrong?
Is it her body?
This Plant Coral shouldn't have been reactivated...
A giant!
Very good!
The Quartz don't matter.
Just destroy the Scub Coral!
That's perfect, Truth!
Calculate an interception course!
We're going for him.
That's...
Are you telling me that the Scub Corals are all interconnected?
Or is it because Ao is Eureka's son?
Hey, are you hungry?
Thank you for assisting us with the rescue effort.
Don't mention it. We're glad to know you're all safe.
What does that report even mean?
What the hell is happening with our IFO pilots?
Um...
I have returned, disgraced and ashamed! I guess...
The acting president has approved of your return.
I won't say a word.
And Ao?
He showed up on Iwato Island.
Iwato Island...?
That's where his girlfriend is.
She's not his girlfriend! He said they're just childhood friends!
Truth is heading for the Okinawan Plant Coral.
The largest Quartz in the world...
He really can't change the fact that he's a Secret.
No, he's going for a different reason.
Wait, wait, wait, what the hell did you do?!
Sup, Elena!
How do you like the new gear?
Take it off! Take it off right away!
Or what? Are we going to have a threesome with Nirvash and Alleluia next?
Come on, you may as well give it a lion's chest and a tiger's head!
Truth is no longer a Secret.
It's been that way for more than a decade now.
Are you ignoring me?!
You said he's not himself anymore.
But aren't Secrets just antibodies that emerge automatically
to erase anything that doesn't belong in this world?
Consider the antibody itself becoming infected.
Coral Carriers...
What?
The Allied Forces trained pilots who have the coral implanted in them.
Is that what Hannah Mama reported about earlier?
Stanley knew about this all along, didn't he?
The Scub Coral is a colony of small life forms much like real corals.
When the Scub Coral encounters an intelligent life form,
it might assimilate the life form in an attempt to communicate.
Assimilate? Does that mean they cease to be humans?
Ten years ago, Truth emerged to create a confluence explosion.
But the Quartz suddenly disappeared and the Secret became confused.
He emerged to destroy the Quartz, but his target disappeared.
He would've kept on rampaging.
The Scub Coral merged with the Secret and helped him stay alive.
That's why that child thinks that a world without the Scub is a right one.
He wanted to create that world himself.
We don't have time for this!
Don't fight with Truth.
What are they talking about?
The people around Naru are dangerous elements because they're infected by the Scub.
Naru is just sick!
The people downstairs said that her disease is spreading.
The Scub infects people.
Before you targeted Ao as a foreigner...
Now you've moved on to Naru?
But it's true.
The people infected by the Scub are camping at the Plant Coral.
They claim they can hear the Scub's voice.
Isn't that creepy?
And that's how you draw the line between you and those who are different from you?
Naru, are you...
What?
Um, well...
You changed, right?
I mean, you've grown those things on your head.
These?
They're just some accessories?
Or is that Truth's fetish?
Well, they say girls wear different stuff for guys...
So if you like Truth...
So that's what you've been thinking the whole time?!
That's how you looked at me?
Well, you know, I met Mom and talked with her...
And you see, I might've had a sister!
So I thought that because you've protected me since we were little,
you're like my sister...
Sister? Your sister?!
What are you so mad about?
Oh, Hannah Mama!
Mama? Now I'm your mom?!
That's not it.
Ao, we're going after Truth.
We'll work together with the Triton.
But I thought Team Harlequin was our enemy.
We had to say so at that point.
Ao, what are you going to do?
Of course I'm going!
Wait, Ao!
You were born from a human and the Scub Coral.
Truth is the same!
This is weird... This shouldn't be happening!
The Big Blue World guaranteed that it's safe!
We couldn't produce any abnormalities in the Coral Carriers from our experiments.
This is Truth's fault!
What did he do then?
Our observations suggest that the IFO Blanc called Canon, which has now merged with Truth,
is creating a space of extremely high trapar density around itself.
As the trapar density rises, the coral in the Carriers go berserk,
and the Scub kills its host.
That can't be...
There are many Okinawans who are unaware that they're Coral Carriers.
A carrier like you.
They'll all die if Truth's IFO gets close.
No! The Scub enters us to make us humans better!
Naru...
I thought it was a sickness all along.
But I was wrong.
The Scub granted me invisible wings that are inside of me.
So that when the day the world is filled with trapar comes...
you and I would become equals, Ao... And our wings...
Humans and Scub Coral are different.
Are you drawing that line?
Though you're not a carrier,
we're not sure how it'll affect your body.
But...
Leave it to us and Ivica.
The Secrets say they'll help too.
We'll stop him no matter what.
Naru, you haven't changed at all, have you?
What are you talking about?
You protected me from the people who treated me as a foreigner.
If the Scub Coral populates the world, no one will think I'm different anymore.
I'm sure you understand that I haven't changed either.
I must go.
You can't win against Truth.
Your Nirvash doesn't have an Archetype.
What's that? It doesn't sound like equipment upgrades.
Stupid.
When are they gonna kiss?
Will they?
A special emergency warning has been issued.
I repeat. The Okinawan government has issued a special emergency warning.
The Allied Forces will commence operations in the area,
so take refuge immediately.
Refrain from using FPs and other trapar powered devices temporarily.
I repeat. The Okinawan government has issued a special emergency warning.
Come! Come, Truth!
A decade ago, the Japanese government
considered trapar mining to be too dangerous,
and tried to seal the Scub away by taking it under direct interior control.
But Okinawa resisted,
and used the help from the Americans to forcibly gain independence.
Look at the results now.
This is the apocalypse you guys chose.
Isn't it wrong?
IFOs?
Team Harlequin!
Liu! Lerato! Rajkumar! Don't let him get any closer!
He might want to trigger a confluence explosion!
So we can't just let him take the Quartz, huh?
If there's an explosion here, the whole area from Okinawa to Taiwan will be affected.
Truth was reborn below the Generation Bleu HQ.
Even if he triggers a confluence explosion,
he might be able to heal himself using the Scub Coral's power.
But then...
We have no choice but to trust him.
Give him a good scolding, Daddy!
Not funny.
No matter how mad you become...
No matter how you change your form...
You are still a Secret.
I'm a Secret?
Are you not?
I'm not. I don't care about the Scub Coral.
I want to destroy the entire world.
Then are you the Scub Coral that invaded this world?
No I'm not.
Then are you a human? The son of Johansson?
No, not that either...
I'm nothing!
Then what are you?
Body blow successful...
Elena, pull back!
I can't...
Now I must...
Prepare the main cannon!
Chief!
Truth...
You'll...
I'm... I'm nothing...
I'm the only Truth!
It's no more over here too...
It's the same wherever I go...
The Scub Coral encountered the defenses and the planet died.
Seven pillars...
The Seventh Swell!
Nirvash!
Let's go, Nirvash.
Eureka's calling us.
It'll be over... I can finally end it all now.
Right, Eureka?