Mom...
What are you doing here?
Why do you look just like you did when you left me?
Why? Why?
Mom, give me an answer!
zetsubouteki ni kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful it's depressing
hanten suru sekai no kattou ni aishiaou
Let's love one another amidst the chaos in this backwards world
bokura ga miteru sekai wa itsudemo sakasama de
This world of ours moves in reverse
A
doushiyou mo nai koto de taigai kimatteku
controlled by forces we can't even touch
A
namida suru hodo kizu tsuku hitomi
There is pain in your eyes so deep I want to cry
A
kokoro de sakebi nagara
Screaming from my heart
A
tada atteitai saigo no futari masarenai mama
The last couple who desire each other cannot be together
A
byouyomi ga kikoetekuru
And time is running out
A
zetsubouteki ni kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful it's depressing
A
sutareyuku doubutsu mitai ni aishiaou
Let's love one another like abandoned animals
A
nakitai kurai kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful I want to cry
A
hanten suru sekai no kattou ni kanjitai yo
Let's love one another amidst the chaos in this backwards world
A
Intruder in the Alicia Room!
Only one target!
Block off the halls!
Don't move a muscle!
Stop.
It's dangerous here, Sir Izumo! Please, leave at once!
Izumo?
You!
No, you leave.
Wait outside until I say otherwise.
But...
Just do as I say.
Be careful, sir.
Boy with wings.
I did not expect us to meet again so soon.
What is my mom... what is this woman doing here?
Answer me!
Do you know of the curse of Eve laid upon Altair?
The curse of Eve?
We should be safe for a bit longer now.
Thanks.
How do you feel?
My throat's still feels a little strange.
Mine too.
Do you think the guys are okay?
They're fine. I made them promise not to be stupid.
That's true.
They promised...
In exchange, I want a promise from you.
Zessica?
I'm okay! Nothing wrong here!
Most of the sky is covered up on this planet.
Weird, right?
Maybe everyone on the planet longs for the sky,
and that's why they fantasize about the Skies of Aquaria.
Like Jin...
Yunoha!
Damn, we were almost toast!
What?
What am I saying?
We're not safe here.
Great time for Shrade to be taking a walk.
I know, right? What a freaking flake.
I understand now.
At last I know the melody this world dances to.
What an ugly sky.
The life of this land is waning away.
Ha, how strange.
This land and I are much alike.
Awaiting a death not far off.
And so I understand you.
I can feel your power flowing,
and I can see the nexus of that power.
Let me out, assholes!
You can't keep me here! I said, let me out!
What am I saying? I should thank them for bringing me here.
Hold on, Mix. I'm gonna find you...
I'm going to find him. I have to find High Commander Fudo...
That's why I've come this far.
He really stands out, so it wasn't hard to track him here.
This is all I can do to help.
I'm done running away.
I'll find High Commander Fudo and take him back to the academy.
Right, Shush?
High Commander Fudo!
You certainly took your time.
What do you mean? I've been looking as hard as I could!
Looking?
Yes!
Why did you have to look?
I've been with you the entire time.
At the market, on the trolley, and all through this town.
I did not move for but an instant.
What?
Though my body journeys across Creation, I move not.
Though my soul lives throughout Eternity, I change not.
Change not? Move not?
You're "Fudo"...
Exactly. Fudo, Achala, the Immovable.
This is the meaning of the name, Fudo ZEN!
High Commander Fudo, do you mean you've been alive for 12,000 years?
Not quite. You should say 24,000 years.
Mikono Suzushiro, do you wish to know the whole truth?
I'm sure of it. I swore to myself I wouldn't run away.
No matter how hard it would be to take.
That will do.
The truth...
can be truly cruel.
Fourteen years ago, all of the Igura, the women of Altair, died out.
That's... Jin!
Jin Muso was the last child born on Altair.
Do you understand now? A planet without Iguras is doomed to a slow death.
That's why you've been abducting women from our planet?
All we want is a mother, to bear Altair's future.
You think that gives you the right?
Hear the whole story, boy.
There is more to the truth you need to hear.
And the rest is only more cruel.
Just wait, Mix!
Where am I?
Who are you?
Damn you!
Now, tell me! Where's Mix?
Mix?
The girl with gigantic big bangs! Your boss brought her a while ago!
A girl? Oh, you mean...
Hold it right there!
Don't even move!
Or the next hole's going to be bigger, and...
Wait! I'll tell you!
Where is she?
What's going on here?
Damn you!
I guess I'll let you off easy this time.
Okay, my power just doesn't work on living things, but still!
He got away.
The prisoner has escaped!
I'll find you and hold you in my arms, Mix!
Where are we going now?
Mikono Suzushiro.
When you see this donut, what do you think?
Um... I think it looks tasty?
I hold this donut still in my hand.
But in reality, it is crossing the waters as quickly as this boat.
What?
You find nothing wondrous about a donut crossing the sea?
And now the donut has vanished.
Here is the secret:
Paradoxically, it is so close to you that you cannot see it.
And now it's in your stomach, High Commander.
Are you certain?
The donut will be decomposed into its molecules, yet it will not truly disappear.
It will be incorporated into my body, and from a certain point of view, become Immovable.
You're talking in Zen koans.
What did you mean by the "whole truth"?
There is an entity that has been "immovably" sustaining this world for 12,000 years.
Immovably?
The Legendary Aquarion of myth.
It lies sleeping at the end of this journey.
This is pointless! I'm digging blind here!
There he is!
Intruder sighted in block X33! Get him!
Damn! Stay away from me!
Take that!
I warned you. Keep out of my way.
Izumo's in the Alicia Room!
He's with the Vegan intruder!
Amata!
The curse of Eve did not end with the extinction of Iguras on Altair.
It also affected the Iguras we took from your planet.
But at last we found Iguras powerful enough to resist the curse.
Rare Iguras.
Rare Iguras?
But the most powerful of the Rare Iguras, Alicia, was still not enough to be our true Eve.
So what did you accomplish by taking away my mom?
All I have done has been for Altair's future.
Because of some curse? And what about all the other women you took?
What's going on?
Our radar and infrared sensors aren't picking anything up!
The only one pinging is the graviton sensor!
How far?
Distance of 90!
What?
Distance... 0!
Zessica, Yunoha! Are you all right?
I'm fine, but Yunoha's drained her power...
My body feels hot... what's going on?
What the hell is this shit?
My chest...
What's happening to their bodies?
Shrade, do you read?
Andy! Are you all right? Where are you?
Right under you! I'm in the tower!
A fine entrance you made.
Isn't Amata... with you?
I think he's in something called the Alicia Room.
It can't be true...
It is.
Now you see the magnitude of the curse of Eve laid on Altair.
I can't believe that!
At first, neither could we.
But when it happened before our very eyes...
That's Spada's sword!
The Machine Angel!
Amata! Get on!
Shrade?
Don't forget me!
Andy!
Hurry! Zessica and Yunoha don't have much time!
Amata... so that's your name.
I have one more thing I absolutely have to tell you.
Your father...
Sir Izumo!
Please retreat!
There he is! Fire!
Mom...
I've called the other Vectors!
Andy, Amata, take the seats!
All right!
Roger!
Yunoha, Zessica! Fly up and stay there!
Sorry...
Don't screw it up, assholes...
Yunoha, you sound...
Talk later! We've got incoming!
It seems we cannot play the forbidden melody
without first fighting in a glorious concerto...
Come!
Right!
Boys' Union! Go, Aquarion!
Aquarion Spada!
I'm sorry we can't stay for long.
We'll break through in as rapid a toccata as we can play!
Upon a boys' moon, Moonlight Rhapsody!
Spatial Augmentation!
What happened?
Something's filled the thruster exhausts!
Did you say filled?
That power... but it can't be!
That's Mix!
What?
But that's that soldier that led us into a trap!
Don't yank my chain like that!
I'm not... I'm not kidding, Andy!
What do you mean by that?
The curse of Eve is...
Even those few Iguras lucky enough to survive here on Altair
transform into men in body and mind.
Transform into men?
This is Altair's doom.
The planet can never bear new life.
That is the curse of Eve!
That's Mix! She's just had her memories altered by the Altairian military!
That can't be...
If that's Mix, then I...
I'll never make it with a girl...
And I found her and didn't even know it...
I'm about to crap out, you guys...
Yunoha!
I'm losing consciousness too...
Shrade, we have to get out of here!
They can't hold on much longer!
But even if we can break through the roof,
they'll remain in danger unless we can escape the planet!
MIX!
Andy!
What do you want from me?!
His Element power is out of control!
He's opening a hole in space!
It's a nano-black hole!
Andy, stop! Please!
No! I can conduct the scale of darkness!
Find the note where the scales meet,
the nexus of power to pierce the dimensions...
Andy, focus your power into my arrow!
Black Hole Arrow!
The gate's open!
Amata, the rest is up to you.
Yunoha, Zessica!
Mix!
Mix!!
Wrong.
My name... is Mixy!
Splendid, absolutely splendid.
The puzzle was in pieces, and now it's becoming whole.
The slumbering wings awaken...
Perhaps it means the Wings of the Sun will be reborn.
So the used trash Eve was good for something after all.
Your awakening will come soon, little puzzle piece.
Return to where everything began,
and the last puzzle will be complete.
kimi he tsuzuku sakamichi ni
There were white flowers growing
shiroi hana ga saiteta
on the road on the hill that leads to you
yume kara sameta ato mo kanashii sora miteta
When I woke from the dream, the sky still looked sad
kono kimochi happa no ue ni susunderu
My feelings drift on a leaf in the wind
asatsuyu wo ochiru oto ni mimi wo sumaseteru no
I'm straining my ears for the sound of the dew falling
kamisama anata ga tsukutta sekai wa kanpeki ja nai
God in Heaven, this world You made is far from perfect
koko de wa mainichi koi ga boroboro shindeku
Down here, love is shattered day by day
hajimete suki ni natta no wo anata wa shiranai deshou
You don't know what it's like to fall in love for the first time
chikyuu no uragawa de ii kara soba ni ite hoshikatta
Let it be on the other end of the world, but I wanted to be with him
watashi wo wasuretemo ii kara soba ni ite hoshikatta
Even if You were to forget me, I wanted to be with him
If you could go back to where everything began
and rewind it all like it never happened...
There's so much I've lost, so much I'm going to lose.
I can't take it.
Next Time
Kiss
Next time: Kiss.