The sound is just slightly impure.
But this piano should be perfectly tuned.
This is your new classmate.
Akbarjin Batbayar.
Nice to meet you.
Mr. Akba... Akbarjin scored excellently in the Meso-Asiatic training program.
He is an Element candidate, and we expect him to be a reserve pilot.
Be nice to him.
Is he from there?
I hope he'll pull his weight.
A-Are these...
real live...
Rare Iguras?
You think he likes holes? I hope so!
I guess.
Huh. He's pretty cute.
He's a bottom. I'm sure of it.
Wait, what if he's a top and just looks like a bottom?
Ooh!
It's just a new boy. Don't lose your head over it.
What are you staring at?
You're interested in boys like him?
That's not it. I just remembered...
I was a transfer student too.
osore
Even if you're scared
living your life   don't give up now   keep moving on
Just live your life, don't give up now, keep moving on
kimi wo dakishimeru nandomo nandomo nandomo
And I'll come for you over and over and over again
ashita boku wa kimi ni deau darou
We'll find each other soon enough
wazukana hoshiakari wo tayori ni
By the faintest glimmer of starlight
boku ni wa kimi ga wakaru yo wakaru yo
I know you, I know you
sen'oku no toki wo koe futari hiraku densetsu no tobira
It's been billions of years, but now we can open the door to our legend
naraku no ao tobikoete
I crossed over the deep blue void
kimi to hai ni naru tame
so I could burn to ash along with you
nagaki rinne wo kanashimi tsurete tabi shitekitanda
I've had a long journey on the vast wheel of fate, gathering sorrows along the way
zenryoku de mikansei kimi no tonari de
I'm not perfect, but I'm giving all I have
kawaita kokoro hodoke chi wo nagasu kedo
If I open my fragile heart to you, I know I'll bleed...
soba ni iru yo zutto yorisotte zutto
But I'll always be with you, always be in your arms
futari hikari no fune ni noru
We'll get on a shining ship of light
kaze no hajimari no oto kanadeyou
And call forth the wind with our voices
The One-Eyed
Transfer Student
Was your training site coed?
Oh, cut it out. You can look that up.
So, what kind of music do you listen to?
What's with him?
What a creep.
What am I supposed to do?
I have to observe.
Have you checked out the school?
We'll show you around if you want.
Observe... observe...
Observe...
Eww!
I'm going to show you around the school.
Follow me.
That's the Berlin.
For a long time, the wall separated Neo-Deava Academy into two areas based on gender.
But part of the wall was broken—
Can you at least look? I'm trying to tell you something.
Can you even see? Your hair's all over your face.
Don't touch me!
I can see. Really.
This place is the center of Neo-Deava.
It stores all the data on the Elements' powers,
and commands Aquarion's strategies and tactics.
What's Aquarion?
Look as much as you wish.
If you bear no insincerity, you will see things as they truly are.
You said "Aquarion"? What is that?
You don't know? I thought you passed training.
It's the new name for the Aquaria.
The Machine Angel?
That's Aquarion right there.
If you're going to be a guide, you have to be nice.
I am being nice.
So nice I want to puke.
Shut it!
Hey, no need to get violent!
You think I'd get violent just because this kid mouthed off a little?
You grabbed me by the collar when you were my guide!
Because you were making a move on Mikono!
No, I wasn't! Well, before, I—
Before? So you are now?
That's not what I meant!
Hey...
Where did that kid go?
A hangar?
So those are the machines that form the Machine Angel.
Steal the Machine Angel?
You don't have to bring back the whole thing.
At least get us one of the component machines.
This might be a little over my head.
Only do it if you can.
Your top priority is to investigate \Rare Iguras that could serve as the true Eve.
We're celebrating the news of your survival.
Finish your mission and get back as soon as you can.
You could just come and get me if you're so worried.
What?
Nothing.
Just establish yourself in Neo-Deava.
We'll talk more after that.
Understood. I'll do it.
It may be Alisia's birthplace, but I don't plan to stay here forever.
A computer terminal in the dead of night.
My program connected to the internet.
It was so simple to overwrite the history file of a student who was supposed to transfer in.
I'll find the most powerful Reaigler soon enough.
Yeah, that's right. Get out of my way.
That way I can investigate without being bothered.
But why are you digging there?
Because this spot is begging me to dig!
I won't let anybody stop me!
Ugh.
Hey! My arms are stuck!
That's your punishment for disobeying me.
That's a Rare Igura?
You don't feel discipline at the school is slipping a little lately?
I don't know what you mean by that.
I wish you'd take this seriously!
You take the wall away, that stuff's going to happen.
You of all people should be most worried
about the Elements falling in love.
If that's the way it is, let's just never approve a Union again.
We can't lose sight of our actual goals.
But!
You'll get wrinkles that way.
I'm trying to be serious!
Ahh! No! Eugh!
I can't believe it! Rare Iguras are really dangerous!
Come on! Faster!
Melon bread for a limited time only!
I'll take one!
Me too!
I had that one first!
Reaiglers... women...
These ones aren't like Silvie at all!
Who's there?
He's trying to peep on us! Get him out of here!
The new kid? No way!
Really?
What a creep.
Don't let him escape! Lock the doors!
So what brings you here?
Bet he was trying to see us naked.
Crucify him!
Excuse me...
I don't think he did it on purpose.
I got lost a lot back when I first came here.
One time I wandered into the boys' bathroom...
I'm so embarrassed!
Who is that?
Is that right?
You didn't know you were entering into the girls' locker room?
Exactly! I got lost! Honest!
It's the truth!
Yo. We've been waiting on you, Akb... umm...
Somethingjin.
Hey, Ak... Ack... what was it?
Can we just call you Jin?
My name's Andy. Nice to meetcha.
Hey!
Jin? Seriously?
Hey bro, do you like holes?
Holes?
Yep! Holes!
Can't I get any peace?
Do they not know what privacy means on this planet?
So he was like, man, it's really bad!
And I was like, how bad, and he was like, so bad I don't even know!
I know, right? You wait the whole
time and never actually get anywhere.
It's awful! I can't take it!
Is this some kind of code? How can they understand each other?
Perhaps I'll never understand Rare Iguras.
Is anyone sitting here?
No.
Mikono! And Amata!
You looked like you were about to vanish.
I'm all right now.
Is something the matter?
I've been wanting to tell you this, but...
I'm really sorry for what I did!
That's ancient history now.
Yeah, Mikono just totally misunderstood.
Are you saying it's my fault?
No! Sorry!
Oh, Amata...
I suppose I did...
You two really like each other.
You think so?
Maybe...
Hey, Jin!
Jin?
His name is really hard to say, so Andy started calling him Jin.
I guess he's not very good with people.
I'm really worried about him!
N-Not like that.
I remember when I was in his spot.
Huh?
I didn't always know how to disappear.
When I came here, everyone wanted to talk to me,
but I was too shy to have a conversation.
I ended up all alone.
I felt like no one could even see me.
Then I thought, it would be nice...
if no one really could see me.
I felt like that all the time.
And so...
So that's how it happened.
It was all my fault.
They were just trying to be nice to me.
But I didn't even try to respond.
I'm worried that Jin might be the same.
It's the voice of the girl from the locker room!
What's troubling you, my friend?
I should ask you. You don't come out very often.
You're not looking well. Did you have another nightmare?
The wedding in mourning clothes again?
A one-eyed giant.
A one-eyed giant? What could it mean?
If I knew, it wouldn't be bothering me so much.
So what do you want to ask me?
There's a noise I'm curious about.
I wanted to let you know.
What noise?
A little noise that came to school a few days ago.
It might have to do with that
vanished Abductor you've been chasing.
A few days ago?
I don't understand this!
Looking at these isn't helping.
Rare Iguras truly are a mystery.
Ow!
I'm sorry!
That's mine!
Oh, Jin!
She disappeared!
Here you go.
Thank you.
Is your device still working?
What do you mean?
I'm sorry.
I don't think it's wrong, though.
Anyway, you really surprised me.
You have the power to just disappear.
That's fantastic!
It is?
You can be alone whenever you want!
I suppose...
I think that would be awesome!
No one would ever bother you!
I don't think it's good to be alone.
Why?
Why? Well, I'd get lonely.
But it'd be so much nicer!
It's not right. It's just not.
All those other people reached out...
I had so many chances to make friends with them...
So why... why did I...
I'm embarrassed!
A noise that came to the school a few days ago.
And a one-eyed giant.
If he's the giant... the Abductor's pilot...
Mix.
Element power: Spatial augmentation.
So basically, filling holes?
Element index 112.
Aura level increase pattern A.
Hey, Jin! Wanna go out and dig holes with us?
Hey, it won't open.
These things do have locks, you know.
Digging holes? Give me a break.
Yunoha?
Yunoha Thrul.
Element power: Optical fluoroscopy.
I looked over your data.
Well done.
Thanks.
So far, the data is consistent with our predictions.
There's a high probability that one of these Rare Iguras
has the right qualities to be the True Eve.
But Rare Iguras are not to be taken lightly.
They look perfectly harmless, but they can get males in the palms of their hands.
And they have a very powerful weapon.
A weapon? What is it?
Tears.
Tears?
Did something happen to you?
I... the one that shot me down... and...
You were defeated again?
Not exactly.
If you find a dangerous Rare Igura, bring her back.
What?
Our goal is to obtain a Rare Igura who can be the True Eve.
You want to dig a hole?
Yes! You finally came around!
You might not want to. It's pretty intense.
Jealous, Amata? You want to dig with just me?
Jealous?
Right!
We are now the three digging bros!
Why did I come?
Nice! Good job!
Behold, Jin. The new world we have blazed a trail into.
The forbidden girls' dorms!
Amata! You're holding us back!
Where have you been? Jin's already—
Where'd he go?
Dunno.
Jin! Where are you!
Shh!
Don't yell so loud,
or they'll find the hole.
You're worried about the hole?
So that's Yunoha's room.
She's the Rare Igura who defeated me...
Jin!
Um, I... can we continue that conservation we had earlier?
About it being wrong to be alone?
Oh no! What should I do?
But Jin wants to hear what I have to say.
Does that mean he's ready to make friends?
Guess the answer's no.
I won't take that!
Did you hear that?
Ttat was a stun ray gun!
What do you intend to do to Yunoha?
I'm not doing anything to her.
I just want to talk.
Stop lying!
Why did you really come to Neo-Deava?
Stop, Cayenne!
Let me go! I'm not going to kill him!
Of course not!
Not so fast!
Don't do it! Jin hasn't done anything!
Yunoha!
Was that a barrier? Did he stop it with a barrier?
Is that his Element power?
Did... Did I do that?
The noise has not disappeared.
But perhaps it's beginning to get clearer.
The power to isolate.
But there will be things in life you cannot wall yourself away from.
What will you do then, boy?
masatsu wo shiranai yasashisa de
With a compassion that never knew conflict
kiri fukai mori ni mayou
The two got lost in the mist-covered forest
futari sennen toozakaru
and drifted apart a thousand years
haiiro no haamonii
An ash-grey harmony
ai to jiyuu wa
Why must love and freedom
naze deau koto dekinai
be fated to never come together
itsuka areno no tsuyu ni naru made
until the day they are but dew in the wilds
kokoro no omosa ai no omosa
A soul is heavy, and love is heavy
zenshin de kiiteita
I listened with all my being
urei kedakai ushiro sugata
As you walked away, sad yet proud
anata no yume wo mamorinuketa nara
If only I had been able to defend your dreams
tsuki ni aragau nagai furea
A long flare reaches out against the moon
hajimaru mo sezu owaru monogatari
The story ends before it could even begin
sotto sora ni oku namida wa
The tears I shed quietly up to the sky
mikan no symphonia
form an incomplete symphony
anata dake ni kimi dake ni hoshi no yuigon
They are the will I leave in the stars to you, only to you
anata ni aitai
I want to see you
Why?
Why does my heart race when I think of her?
This is just like when Alisia was wearing white bloomers
in her new downloadable music video!
Next time on Aquarion Evol: Call of the Wild.
Next Time
Call of the Wild