hikaru suiheisen
Just over the bright horizon,
s
t
r
U
hajimari to owari no
where the beginning and the end
s
t
r
U
tokeau soko wa
melt into one,
s
t
r
U
namida no furusato na no
lies the homeland of tears
s
t
r
U
furueteru te de
I've already pocketed
s
t
r
U
shinjirareru mono
my trembling hand
s
t
r
U
poketto ni tsumekonda
which holds my beliefs
s
t
r
U
kanata de yurameiteru shinkirou
A mirage shimmers in the distance
s
t
r
U
sora miagereba
I look to the sky
s
t
r
U
michibiitekureru you na
hoping it will show me the way
s
t
r
U
natsukashikute atsui hikari wo kureru
And it gives off a familiar, warm light
s
t
r
U
anata wa chiisaku te wo furu yo
You wave at me faintly
s
t
r
U
ikanakucha
I must go
s
t
r
U
mou nakanai yo shangurira
Don't cry anymore because Shangri-La,
s
t
r
U
aratana sekai he to daibu shiyou
a new world, is waiting for us
s
t
r
U
aoiro ni dakareta boku wa
As I'm embraced by its blue...
s
t
r
U
kono mune no takanari to tomo ni
My heart beats loudly
s
t
r
U
Colonel Tanaka...
Just call me Nick.
I'm half Japanese, half Hawaiian.
Shall we begin?
Don't Look Down
A present for you!
What's your guy so mad about?
Huh? He's happy.
Sergei?
Sergei!
And what's your guy doing?
Shut up!
Sign: Drink up, boys!
To all personnel. Third Engine activation test starts as soon as you're ready.
I'm ready.
Third Engine...
Attempting connection!
Fleur, lift the hind leg.
Roger!
Elena, release the stabilizer.
Okie!
No way!
We'll get scolded for this!
If Ao can do it,
I can do it.
A flower bloomed.
Gosh, don't scare me like that!
Are you seriously diving in my bathtub?
First of all, why are you even in my bathtub?
Say, Fleur...
If you could live the remainder of your life under the sea with dolphins, would you?
With dolphins?
That sounds like fun, but I'd end up coming back soon.
We're land creatures, after all.
That's the USA version.
Is that another comic reference?
Ao's choice was the EU version.
He won't return to the human world ever again.
I don't understand what you're talking about.
Otaku knowledge is really just a circlejerk.
I don't know.
Hey, let me wash it for you!
S-Stop!
Come on!
H-Hey, Elena!
It'll be quick!
Stop it!
Stop!
I've told you before I hate that.
What's that?
I just wanted you to do a final check over the contract for us.
It's freaky, isn't it?
I bet you never had anything like that with Generation Bleu.
That's how cunning Cristophe Blanc is.
He tells the world, and even you, that your job is international rescue,
but amidst all of that, he got his hands on highly destructive assault weapons.
Do you mean...
Only the Allied Forces are qualified to manage such weapons.
Both you and Nirvash belong to the Allied Forces.
Are you fine with that?
Hey!
You know, you really do look like her.
Do you mean my mom?
Of course. She was one of us too.
It was thirteen years ago.
Your mother showed up in this world alongside the Mk I.
We tracked it down, but by the time we found it, she wasn't in it anymore.
Then ten years ago...
The greatest Scub Burst in history occurred in Okinawa.
We needed someone to pilot the Mk I to stop it.
Then we found your mother living with you on Iwato island.
She gladly agreed to help and fought alongside us.
Mom...
Cristophe Blanc would have to answer for concealing the Quartz until now.
However, if that weapon is in our hands, then there's no problem.
If you have no objections to that draft,
let's prepare the official document.
You're one of us starting from tomorrow!
Both you and Nirvash belong to the Allied Forces.
Are you fine with that?
I'll send this to them.
Babysitting's such a pain.
The American carrier should be around San Diego by now.
You running some simulation?
On how to take Ao back.
But up against Eisenhowers, not even our IFOs would stand a chance.
Not with these numbers, anyway.
We've received funding from American companies too,
so if we gave them a good spanking, those companies wouldn't just watch quietly.
But seriously, man,
what the hell is Ao thinking?
Is that you, Ao?
Chief... I'm sorry I did this without saying a word.
I saw the video they sent.
Um, I...
What?
I... did something horrible.
If if had went on, I would have ended up doing even worse things.
So... everyone's better off without me at the company.
Can't you trust us?!
Dammit!
What else could I have done?!
If the gun's there, bad things would happen to the company.
But... But... I can't throw it away!
I need it for my mom.
There's no other way!
Fleur?
Ao won't be coming back.
Why?
I don't know.
I guess he has his own reasons.
He's been acting weird since Operation Polaris.
Anyway, let's just forget about him and—
Say, Fleur...
Have you even tried to find out the truth?
You're always like this.
Are you afraid of asking questions?
Or do you really think that ignorance is bliss?
What are you talking...
It's the same for your father, the accident,
and even me who's right in front of you!
Elena, that's...
Why didn't you ask me about this grave?
You've been curious about it all this time.
Because I...
You never even tried to find out!
I killed Miller!
I killed the singer and became Miller myself!
There's no real me!
Well, here I was thinking we were saving the world this whole time.
Look how happy someone is.
Oh?
So Gazelle Co. jokes now?
Jokes? Nope, I'm totally serious!
About the future of the two of us, that is.
Is that really so urgent?
I have to answer questions about the Quartz soon.
Just thinking about it—
It's about Ao. Is it really okay this way?
I know that America's being forceful.
But our enemy isn't America.
That's Stanley's opinion, isn't it?
What about you?
Hallström!
It's about time.
What's up?
Could we...
speak in private, if that's okay with you?
We're going anyway.
Looks like she wants you to comfort her.
You get my drift?
Sure, but I might get a call from Rebecca.
Gazelle...
It's her, after all! Even just her voice—
Elena?
Are you really so worried about it?
Don't worry, your boobs will get bigger.
Idiot.
I wanted to ask, but...
Fleur!
Sorry for barging in while you're changing, but Elena is...
I told you I'm going!
You'll never make it to America with the trapar in Kyrie!
Stop!
I don't care! Just open the gate!
What?!
Elena, what are you doing?!
I've come to a conclusion!
I'm going for Ao!
What are you saying?! Ao isn't...
Isn't coming back?
Then we'll have to take him back!
Do you even get it? He's on an American carrier!
Why are you stopping me? You don't even care, do you?
I...
I didn't ask because you're my friend!
I thought you wanted that!
No!
I wanted you to ask!
Fleur! Elena!
Can you hear me?
Go and bring Ao back.
You want to know how he really feels, don't you?
Then go and ask yourselves.
You can fly now.
I'm going.
I...
You're thirteen now.
As a man living in society, you must think for yourself and fulfill your duties.
Mr. Tanaka...
The Quartz Gun belongs to the world. It's not something a single person should wield.
I...
Warning! Two IFOs approaching.
What?
I repeat: Warning! Two IFOs approaching.
She's locked on to us?
If we take off, they're gonna take us down!
What the...
Come out, Ao!
If you don't, we're blowing everything to smithereens.
Hey, don't make threats!
Fleur! And Elena!
Ao, tell us!
Fleur!
Go back! The president will get mad at you!
You don't want to come back?
Or do you want to stay here forever?
We came all the way here to ask you this!
Give us an answer, Ao!
What are you saying?
I did it for the sake of the company's and everyone—
I don't want to hear about your reasons, Ao!
Just tell us how you feel!
Elena?
I...
want to...
go back...
And be together with all of you!
See, he wants to come back, after all!
I was the one who told you that.
So you get along so well that you fight?
No!
Did you do that to Mom as well?
Generation Bleu is done for.
I...
I don't care.
Fleur! Elena! Let's go!
Crap! The Third Engine is down!
Due to the power of love, it was working fine a moment ago!
You!
You admitted it!
At this rate, we'll run out of fuel...
Should I carry the both of you back?
Not a chance!
Chief...
Is it true that the Generation Bleu made a surprise attack on the US carrier, USS Ronald Reagan?
It is.
Due to this, the questioning of Cristophe Blanc by the UN has been called off.
The United States considers Generation Bleu terrorists,
and demand a UN decision to restrain them, using force if necessary!
Would you look at this!
I never thought I'd ever see Fleur taking Ao back.
It's not funny!
You raised a hand at the American army.
The Big Blue World can't support you anymore!
Blanc...
Just follow the company's orders for once.
Ivica said that
the ones blowing the pipe and leading the way aren't us,
but the children.
I agree with him now.
What's going on? Where are all the adults?
Gazelle?
I made you take Ao back.
What do you mean?
The times where Secrets were our only enemies are over.
Well, it might've been over for a while.
Since the day Eureka showed up.
I knew it would come to this, so I provoked you.
What do you mean?
We've crossed the line.
It's started.
Starting from today, the whole world is against us.
To be continued.
futashikana*
s
*T/L Note: I'm so uncertain
boku
no sekai
ga ima*
v
*T/L Note: In the blink of an eye,
mabataku
ma ni
kawari-
hajimete
hirogaru*
A
*T/L Note: my whole world started changing and opening up.
ano hi mitsuketa yume no tsuzuki wa doko*
A
*T/L Note: That day, I found out where my dream continues
sugu ni
sagashite
miseru yo*
A
*T/L Note: I'll show you its sequel now
ima mo boku
dake wa
oboeteirun da*
N
*T/L Note: Right now, I'm the only one who still remembers
natsukashii
nukumori*
.
*T/L Note: that familiar warmth
saa
mou
ikou
ka*
A
*T/L Note: Now let's get going
machiu-
keteru
unmei ni*
)
*T/L Note: I was frozen with fear
tachisukumi
obieteta*
H
*T/L Note: thinking of the fate that awaited me
mou
kess-
hite
mayo-
wanai
you ni*
A
*T/L Note: I'll become so strong that I won't
tsuyoku
natte
yuku yo*
Z
*T/L Note: be uncertain ever again
nido to modorenai kako mo ashita kara kate ni shite*
A
*T/L Note: The past that can't be written will support me from tomorrow on
sou
yatte
noriko-
ete yuku
no sa*
q
*T/L Note: I'll overcome it all
sou shite boku
wa boku ni naru*
A
*T/L Note: and I'll become myself
sou shite boku
wa boku ni naru*
Don't repost to any manga readers!
You have to sign up for our forum to download!
Preview
Maybe
Tomorrow