Another unusable batch retrieved from Vega.
The warp transport deteriorated the Rare Iguras. They're completely ruined.
Our motherworld, Altair.
It still refuses to accept them.
This is stupid...
We will investigate the power Vega has at its disposal.
Jin, you're in command.
Me?
Fine...
Kagura's gonna be a pain, though.
Control him!
It's his fault the Machine Angel's true power has been awakened.
osore
Even if you're scared
living your life   don't give up now   keep moving on
Just live your life, don't give up now, keep moving on
kimi wo dakishimeru nandomo nandomo nandomo
And I'll come for you over and over and over again
ashita boku wa kimi ni deau darou
We'll find each other soon enough
wazukana hoshiakari wo tayori ni
By the faintest glimmer of starlight
boku ni wa kimi ga wakaru yo wakaru yo
I know you, I know you
sen'oku no toki wo koe futari hiraku densetsu no tobira
It's been billions of years, but now we can open the door to our legend
naraku no ao tobikoete
I crossed over the deep blue void
kimi to hai ni naru tame
so I could burn to ash along with you
nagaki rinne wo kanashimi tsurete tabi shitekitanda
I've had a long journey on the vast wheel of fate, gathering sorrows along the way
zenryoku de mikansei kimi no tonari des
I'm not perfect, but I'm giving all I have
zenryoku de mikansei kimi no tonari de
kawaita kokoro hodoke chi wo nagasu kedo
If I open my fragile heart to you, I know I'll bleed...
soba ni iru yo zutto yorisotte zutto
But I'll always be with you, always be in your arms
futari hikari no fune ni noru
We'll get on a shining ship of light
kaze no hajimari no oto kanadeyou
And call forth the wind with our voices
Measure of Excitement ★ Rapid Rise
Where am I?
Mikono!
Sorry. Just Cayenne.
You!
I'm supposed to show you around.
Follow me.
Hold on a minute!
What am I doing here?
Where's Mikono?
I can simultaneously answer all those questions
and explain what will happen to you.
This is Neo-Deava's Holy Angel Academy.
Here, we are trained as Elements to pilot the Aquarias.
Mikono was telling me about this.
People with the potential to be Elements come here from all over the world.
Our mission is to destroy the Abductors as they attack from their homeworld.
This is the hallway. The bathroom's right here.
You're walking too fast!
And this is the classroom.
Huh?
Look, it's him!
The civilian who hijacked an Aquaria!
So he's got an Element power?
Dude, he did Union with a girl!
Lucky bastard!
Get used to it.
You're a civilian who managed to pilot an Aquaria,
and even did a mixed-gender Union.
Everyone's gonna be talking about you, even up in Neo-Deava.
And, of course, the girl who was with you.
Mikono!
That's the Berlin.
Unions between boys and girls are strictly forbidden,
so at Neo-Deava, male and female Elements are always kept apart.
Mikono is being examined on the other side of the Berlin.
This is the cafeteria.
Hold on!
What do you mean by examined?
That's all I have to tell you.
Now, how about you answer my question.
What?
What's going on between you and Mikono?
Huh?
Between us?
I mean, we just met yesterday, so we're not—
If you just met yesterday, how come she was in there with you?
What does that mean? You think you know how she thinks?
Wait, are you and Mikono...
You bet we are!
Goodbye, my first love...
Of course she would...
She's so pretty, there's no way she'd be single.
She's been timid since we were children.
Since you were children.
I bet you're engaged or something. That's so romantic...
Almost everyone in the Suzushiro bloodline is an Element.
I am. Our parents were.
And a noble bloodline! You're perfect for each other.
But only my sister, Mikono, never developed any powers.
And your sister, to b—
Your SISTER?
Her lack of power made her timid and shy.
She was so afraid of the Abductors, she
wouldn't even leave the house without me.
You're kidding. But she told me...
I can't stand being cooped up at home.
I have to get some sun!
Mikono wouldn't get into an Aquaria on her own.
She's been a coward since birth.
I realize I haven't known her for very long,
but I think she's changed since then.
What?
Mikono is really trying to change herself!
I mean, that's... what I think... kinda?
How's it sound to you, Mr. Mikono's Older Brother?
How dare you!
Hey!
Keep the noise down on school grounds,
or I'll twist you like spaghetti.
Professor Donar!
Professor?!
Listen, redhead.
We're gonna be testing you this afternoon.
You'd better eat up.
This test is going to determine
whether we're keeping you here or not.
As an Element pilot.
You're making me an Element pilot for one of the Aquarias?
No. Not an Aquaria.
You've gone and undone the seal.
You're gonna pilot Aquarion.
Currently, there's nothing particularly wrong with his body.
It looks like his Element power is antigravity.
Whenever he experiences a sudden surge in emotion, his body floats upwards.
Toooo muuuuch!
So you could say he's anything but down to earth.
But flying doesn't explain how he broke the Guize Stones' barrier.
There must be a reason other than his Element power.
It doesn't matter.
That forbidden Aquarion is all we have to combat such powerful foes.
I'm afraid I can't agree, Principal.
We would only cause the disaster to repeat itself!
What disaster?
Excuse me, but what is this?
Just relax and accept whatever you see.
He called out Aquarion's true name,
controlled Evol, an unknown machine, in his first combat,
and defeated an enemy.
Memories of Aquarion sleep deep inside him.
Light level falling to 20000 and stabilizing.
Confirmed.
The waveform is going from magenta to cyan.
No! Wait! Don't leave me behind!
No! Stop! Don't be scared!
No!
Don't go away!
Oh no! Emergency halt!
What just happened?
It looks like something is interfering with the scanner!
As a result, further mental probing is impossible!
Interfering?
Did you hear about the Union between boys and girls?!
Yeah! Zessica was in it!
But only the skirts are short.
You're amazing, Zessica!
You got to Union with boys! I'm so jealous!
And with Cayenne, too!
I know Cayenne's always number two in everything,
but he's so cool!
I'm a Shrade fan, but they never let him into the mock battles.
Don't worry, we'll get to leave soon.
They'll examine me and discover I don't have any Element powers.
All the other girls here have Element powers.
So how did Union with a boy feel?
It was definitely more... intense?
I knew it! Totally called it!
I wanna do Union with a boy too!
No wait, I'd settle for just meeting Cayenne!
If only the Berlin would fall down!
Enough!
The Berlin is very important! It's there to protect us!
We need it! We couldn't possibly be without it!
Aww...
Come on, Mix, lighten up a—
Quiet!
You've been tainted by those boys!
What?
Tainted? Are you saying Cayenne is tainted?
You fools.
Mikono Suzushiro!
Did she say Suzushiro?
She's Cayenne Suzushiro's sister?
No way!
Mikono! Tell them how even your brother is tainted!
Maybe he keeps porn mags under his bed, or...
I don't know.
I don't live with Cayenne anymore.
What do you mean?
You're a Suzushiro. You have an Element power, don't you?
Sibling Elements usually have a
naturally high telepathic resonance.
Even if you're apart, you should be able to tell through—
I can't!
I can't tell.
I'm not like Cayenne.
I'm just useless.
A Serenade of Regret.
Mikono's on the other side of that wall.
She's so close, but they won't even let me see her.
A piano?
It's coming from over there.
Who's there?
Well, well. You're the new kid everyone's talking about.
Dig in.
Nothing like sharing a meal in a hole.
Uh, thanks.
So why is there a hole here?
It's the road to hope!
Hope? Uh, okay... did you dig this by yourself?
There it is.
Did you just... feel the earth?
Yep. That's my Element power.
Your Element power?
Not just dirt, either.
Whatever it's made of, it has a weak point.
Just begging somebody to dig a hole in it!
My power is to find those spots and grant them their desire!
So it's not just me here.
Come on! Let's dig and dig until we've got ourselves a tunnel!
And then we'll thrust our way into the girls' side!
The girls' side? That's where this hole goes?
Ha! You wanna help me dig my hole to bliss?
I do... I think.
I'm so glad someone's with me on this!
My name is Andy W. Hol.
We are now officially digging bros!
Digging bros?
Come on, Bro! Let's dig!
I... I want to see Mikono!
What a beautiful song.
Amata... I hope he's somewhere here.
He must be.
It felt so natural to talk to him.
I've never felt so close to anyone before.
But I was wrong.
Amata was chosen.
And I...
And so we thrust our way in!
We did it, Bro!
Amata?
Mikono.
No! Let me down!
Mikono! Stop squirming!
Let go! Let go!
I didn't expect you to dig that deep.
You're something else, man.
That's not what I...
Amata, you creep!
Mikono!
Hey, don't let it get you down. It happens to everybody.
You get your head stuck in a skirt, and you fly around a...
...waitaminute, that doesn't happen to anybody.
Damn! Let's split, Bro!
It's time for our monthly public exhibition mock battle!
The Elements will be Andy W. Hol...
Cayenne Suzushiro...
And as the head, new student Amata Sora!
Not Cayenne?
What's going on?
I can't believe I did that to Mikono.
But it wasn't on purpose.
I have to apologize and clear things up.
Simulation start!
Time for Union, Amata!
Amata Sora's spirit level is failing to rise!
Union will be impossible!
Union, damn you!
Come on, Amata!
I know you want to Union with girls again, but now's not the time!
That's not what I—
You imbecile! If you keep flying from the enemy, we'll never even Union!
Pathetic.
It's hard to believe that's the boy
who broke the Guize Stones' seal.
What's the matter, Amata Sora?
Goddamn it! This is my first time in three months and I can't do so much as wave to the crowd?
What crowd?
You realize the girls are watching our mock battle, right?
What are they doing?
This is boring.
Can we go yet?
Everyone, quiet!
It's just like I said. The boys can't do a thing.
If Cayenne goes down, it's his fault!
Mikono's watching us.
Stay focused!
I want to tell Mikono!
Amata Sora's spirit level is rising rapidly!
He's finally in the game!
Spiritual Union!
Go! Aquarion!
Whoa!
But how's he going to recover after all that?
Show us, Amata Sora.
Show us how deep your power goes!
Mikono.
Mikono!
Mikonooooooo!
This is his flight power!
Such rapid acceleration!
That Aquaria is flying!
Amata...
Let's show 'em!
Don't forget to impress the crowd, Amata!
Mikono! Please...
Accept my feelings!
What did he do?
A defensive stance that reflects all incoming attacks!
Not quite.
He's...
Bowing his head.
The program's throwing errors because of Amata's unexpected move!
Killing the simulation!
It's over already?
That wasn't a good show at all!
I'm going to have a word with you later!
He... He... I don't even...
Amata Sora...
Time for a pilgrimage to the holy land.
It's been two years since we took over the warp roads.
He has to wake up soon.
He may have served us well before, but now he sleeps,
and the world turns without him.
That geezer Izumo is getting serious.
You should probably wake up soon, Mikage.
kaze ni ubawareta wake janai
We weren't spirited away on the wind
katamichi bun no yuuki de bokura
We knew we could never return, and found the courage
higeki wo ukeireru
to accept the hardship
kokoro ga koko ni atta hazu no kuudou
There's an emptiness where my heart used to be
motto boku ga ookikereba
If only I was stronger
kimi wo mirai wo sukueta darou ka
I could have saved you, and our future...
taisetsu na hito wo mamoru sube ga tatta hitotsu shika motenai
I only know of one way to keep the people I love
sonna anata ga haguretadayou sora
And you left me and disappeared into the sky
anata ijou no hito ni deaenai
I'll never find anyone like you again
tsuki ni aragau nagai furea
A long flare reaches out against the moon
hajimaru mo sezu owaru monogatari
The story ends before it could even begin
kizutsukiuru yawarakasa
So soft, so fragile
tojikometa senritsu kanaderu hodo
I will call up the melody locked away
utau hodo kowareru hodo ni
And sing it until I destroy myself
anata ga koishii
That's how much I love you
The men ripped away. The women kept apart.
A great wall to separate men and women.
Do you have the courage to cross it?
Next Time
Wall
Next time on Aquarion Evol: Wall ~ Conquer Oneself ~.