Phantom pains.
My arm may be gone, but I can still feel it hurting.
That's a sign that something bad's going to happen today.
It's never wrong.
Suomi! We have to evacuate the students and prepare to counterattack!
Right!
Nothing but boring smells!
None of you are the smell I want to destroy!
It's him!
Watch out!
I didn't want to believe it...
Jin, you're one of them...
What?
I'm sorry. I overheard...
a message for you.
What are you two doing?
Hurry and get to the shelter!
Mix! Are you okay?
Andy!
Mix!
Noooo!
Yunoha!
osore
Even if you're scared
living your life   don't give up now   keep moving on
Just live your life, don't give up now, keep moving on
kimi wo dakishimeru nandomo nandomo nandomo
And I'll come for you over and over and over again
ashita boku wa kimi ni deau darou
We'll find each other soon enough
wazukana hoshiakari wo tayori ni
By the faintest glimmer of starlight
boku ni wa kimi ga wakaru yo wakaru yo
I know you, I know you
sen'oku no toki wo koe futari hiraku densetsu no tobira
It's been billions of years, but now we can open the door to our legend
naraku no ao tobikoete
I crossed over the deep blue void
kimi to hai ni naru tame
so I could burn to ash along with you
nagaki rinne wo kanashimi tsurete tabi shitekitanda
I've had a long journey on the vast wheel of fate, gathering sorrows along the way
zenryoku de mikansei kimi no tonari de
I'm not perfect, but I'm giving all I have
kawaita kokoro hodoke chi wo nagasu kedo
If I open my fragile heart to you, I know I'll bleed...
soba ni iru yo zutto yorisotte zutto
But I'll always be with you, always be in your arms
futari hikari no fune ni noru
We'll get on a shining ship of light
kaze no hajimari no oto kanadeyou
And call forth the wind with our voices
The Fallen Giant
The Mithra Gnis is destroying our autocannons!
72% of them have been destroyed!
Most of the students have been safely evacuated,
but there are still over 20 unaccounted for.
Damn!
Launch gate standing by! Launch gate standing by!
There's no mistaking that Abductor.
The pilot...
Mikono!
I swear I'll protect you, no matter what happens out there.
Amata!
Thank you. I believe in you.
Mikono...
You guys remember love is forbidden, right?
Here we go!
Roger!
We're going to stop him from destroying our base!
Counterattack Union!
Go!
Aquarion!
Aquarion Evol!
There's the smell.
Finally, you've come... my...
My...
Silvie!
He's in our communication line!
Did he say Silvie?
Why does my chest hurt?
Infinity Punch!
Nice try!
The Infinity Punch!
He turned it back on them!
What the...
Detecting high aura levels from the Mithra Gnis!
Are those Element signs?
Are you saying the Abductor is an Element?
Impossible!
The power of reversal.
Reversal?
As his love turns into hate,
flames freeze into ice, and light is swallowed by dark.
You mean, he can reverse the laws of physics...
There.
Jin?
You're awake.
Where are we?
You're coming with me.
To the planet of Altair.
The world where I live.
Jin?
I can't. We can't go.
They're out there fighting. Our friends, the ones who accepted us.
Too bad. I need you.
But...
I planned all of this.
My job is to take the most powerful Rare Igura.
They'd never accept me if they knew that!
Let go of me, Jin!
We have an emergency alarm!
One of the Vectors in the hangar is trying to make an unauthorized launch!
What?
Who's the pilot?
Akbarjin Batbayar! I knew it!
He's an enemy spy?
No way!
I can't believe it!
Called it! He had a dark secret!
I'll go stop him.
Authorized.
Zessica! Help me!
You got it!
Pathetic!
What's with this Abductor?
It's not just that new power of his!
He's way stronger than the last time we fought...
What's that?
Something's coming through the Dimension Gate!
Highly concentrated energy is being shaped into a tube and funneled into the Mithra Gnis!
So we have to close the Dimension Gate?
If only we could cut off that tube...
The red strand of fate.
The red strand?
Of fate?
Who dares weave such a sorrowful fate...
Show yourself!
So you already found me. I knew you would.
Flower petals?
He teleported?
You!
Jin... you've become so much happier since you came here.
Was that just part of your plan too?
Shut up!
But I think you really do need them.
And they all need you too.
That's...
That's impossible!
I didn't make it in time.
The last son is alive, and has fulfilled his mission.
Who are you?
He's so pretty!
I'll thank you to stop right now!
Donar! Are you okay?
Donar!
It's been a very long time.
Ten thousand and two thousand years, I believe.
Or was that twenty and four thousand years?
Fudo?
At last you show yourself.
And in such an ugly form, too.
Where did you leave your real body?
What the eyes can see is but an enchantment, a delusion chaining one to the past.
You yourself are still bound to your old form.
Oh well. Let us dispense with pleasantries.
Apollonius' wings, which glow with amber radiance.
The true Wings of the Sun. Tell me where they are.
Aquarion!
Jin, let me down!
They're in trouble!
Jin, please...
Yunoha...
I...
That's the smell.
Reverse!
Amata...
Oh, my...
My Silvie!
Silvie?
I hate you!
I've hated you since the day we met!
My Silvie!
No! Let me go!
Silvie?
Mikono!
I hate you! I'm going to kill you!
I'll crush you in my arms forever.
No! No!
Let her go!
Asshole!
Mikono!
I know you.
The weird guy who doesn't smell.
What are you talking about?
If you don't smell, you don't really exist.
So I guess you won't mind if I kill you.
Let's see what happens...
if I reverse the blood flow in your heart.
Magnificent. You're out of options.
Your last hope has vanished into the void.
Now, tell me.
The love of twenty and four thousand years.
The Solar Wings.
Where are they?
Oh yes. I remember now.
I'm sorry for forgetting about you, Donar Dantes.
Let's meet again sometime.
That was a spiritual body made of pure thought.
Miss Suomi, raise the Element Jammer in the command room.
Right.
Please, no...
Die.
What?
Amata!
Are you all right?
Andy! Mix!
I'm glad you're all right!
What a shock, though.
I was just trying to dig our way out, and he fell right on top of us.
Damn you!
I'll reverse your very life!
You can try!
What the...
Mikono!
Cayenne!
And Shrade, too!
Aquarion, re-Union immediately!
Roger!
We've still got to do something about that Dimension Gate!
My power to isolate!
I'll use it!
You traitor!
Akbarjin Batbayar, you're...
Wrong!
My name is Jin Muso!
What are you gonna do, spy?
You have to trust him!
Jin is one of us now!
He's playing with you, Yunoha!
You don't have to trust me. I don't care.
This power to isolate is something I found by coming here.
And without it, you won't be able to seal Altair's Dimension Gate!
But...
Union with me!
A love that crosses worlds...
Mikage!
The price of treacherous love is steep.
Stop!
Yunoha!
Jin!
I'm fine.
It's just a psychic projection. It's not going to kill me.
Jin!
Hurry up and Union!
Have it your way, Jin! Let's Union!
Amata, Mikono! Piano Four Hands Union!
Go!
Aquarion!
Artillery Union!
Go!
Aquarion!
We can really understand each other!
This is... two sounds in harmony!
This power rising up from inside me...
across the border between worlds!
This is...
our...
Union!
Aquarion Gepard!
Aquarion Spada!
Wow!
That was a beautiful sound, my friend!
Playtime's over!
What a powerful tone!
We can't take this much longer!
Yunoha!
The Elements' aura levels are falling!
Vital signs unstable!
Their lives are in danger!
Kagura!
Jin, you're still bleeding!
I don't care!
I never want to see them again!
Your tears, that is.
Jin!
Yunoha!
We'll do it together.
Jin.
Jin...
Jin!
Thanks, you guys!
We're connected!
What?
What is that light?
Infinite energy that crosses the boundary between worlds!
Incredible! Gepard is creating new weaponry!
Gepard is evolving!
This is Jin's...
We'll pin him down with Spada! Come, my friend!
Roger!
Right now...
We'll seal away...
that dark power...
FIRE!
It formed an isolation field!
Now, Amata, Mikono!
Got it!
Play with me!
The interruzione in his song!
Reverse!
Mikono!
Now! The final refrain!
What?
The Dimension Gate is shut!
Both Spada and Gepard are fine!
We did it, Jin!
Jin?
Yunoha.
When I met you, I felt like it was a miracle,
and it took my breath away.
When I take your hand, it makes me feel a little bit stronger.
So please...
kaze ni ubawareta wake janai
We weren't spirited away on the wind
katamichi bun no yuuki de bokura
We knew we could never return, and found the courage
higeki wo ukeireru
to accept the hardship
kokoro ga koko ni atta hazu no kuudou
There's an emptiness where my heart used to be
motto boku ga ookikereba
If only I was stronger
kimi wo mirai wo sukueta darou ka
I could have saved you, and our future...
taisetsu na hito wo mamoru sube ga tatta hitotsu shika motanai
I only know of one way to keep the people I love
sonna anata ga haguretadayou sora
And you left me and disappeared into the sky
anata ijou no hito ni deaenai
I'll never find anyone like you again
tsuki ni aragau nagai furea
A long flare reaches out against the moon
hajimaru mo sezu owaru monogatari
The story ends before it could even begin
kizutsukiuru yawarakasa
So soft, so fragile
tojikometa senritsu kanaderu hodo
I will call up the melody locked away
utau hodo kowareru hodo ni
And sing it until I destroy myself
anata ga koishii
That's how much I love you
I want to blow away on the spring breeze
and scatter away into the summer night.
I see your face in the autumn moon,
but then it's hidden by the winter snow.
Next Time
Separate
Paths
The seasons without you...