What?
Here...
"Why do you dig?"
When legendary tunnel engineer Alejandro
Vedernikov was asked that question, he responded:
"Because a new world awaits on the other side."
I will get to that new world!
Here I come, girls' locker room!
The girls' locker room!
What's this?
osore
Even if you're scared
living your life   don't give up now   keep moving on
Just live your life, don't give up now, keep moving on
kimi wo dakishimeru nandomo nandomo nandomo
And I'll come for you over and over and over again
ashita boku wa kimi ni deau darou
We'll find each other soon enough
wazukana hoshiakari wo tayori ni
By the faintest glimmer of starlight
boku ni wa kimi ga wakaru yo wakaru yo
I know you, I know you
sen'oku no toki wo koe futari hiraku densetsu no tobira
It's been billions of years, but now we can open the door to our legend
naraku no ao tobikoete
I crossed over the deep blue void
kimi to hai ni naru tame
so I could burn to ash along with you
nagaki rinne wo kanashimi tsurete tabi shitekitanda
I've had a long journey on the vast wheel of fate, gathering sorrows along the way
zenryoku de mikansei kimi no tonari de
I'm not perfect, but I'm giving all I have
kawaita kokoro hodoke chi wo nagasu kedo
If I open my fragile heart to you, I know I'll bleed...
soba ni iru yo zutto yorisotte zutto
But I'll always be with you, always be in your arms
futari hikari no fune ni noru
We'll get on a shining ship of light
kaze no hajimari no oto kanadeyou
And call forth the wind with our voices
Revelations
Here they are, get 'em while they're hot!
Hey, pictures from the field observation trip!
When did you take these, anyway?
Let's just say I mix business with pleasure.
I'll take one of Shrade!
Here you go.
Man, I look awful in this one.
Hey, here's a good one of you.
Yep, that's a good one.
You buying that one, Amata?
Wouldn't you rather have a real live girl instead of a picture?
H-Hey!
Amata, you'll really fly for anyone!
No!
Um, go ahead and take it.
They're all over you, stud.
Cut that out.
Can I have this photo?
That one?
I guess. That'll be 500 kowloons.
Thanks.
Huh? Who's that of?
Um...
Just let me see!
Amata?
Amata and Andy?
I wouldn't have thought of that...
Yo, my hole digging bro!
You'll never guess what I just found!
Unless I'm very much mistaken, this is the Book of Twin Stars!
The Book of Twin Stars?
I've heard of it.
According to the legend, whoever holds that book can take full control of the forbidden Aquarion.
The green cat is right.
Neo-Deava has been looking for this thing since it was founded.
How did you find it, then?
Yeah, where was it?
You see, I was digging a hole to—
Look, that's not important right now.
Chairman Crea!
Isn't it time you told us the truth?
What do you mean?
You must have found something important if you've returned from your journey.
Important?
Oh, I forgot!
This is for everyone to share.
That's not what we mean!
Don't you like it?
That's not the issue here!
They cannot see it with their eyes.
The book will only open for eyes that cannot see.
So if the verb is conjugated like so...
R, ry... ribbit ribbit? What does that mean?
Damn it, why didn't I pay attention in lit class?
Dude, Amata, help me out here.
Kay.
Um, d... dig... digging?
I have to tell him I'm sorry.
Mikono's sorry for what?
This is how it's done!
What are you doing?
"Socks must be white"!
What?
It's the first line. He spent all night on it.
This is Chapter 23, verse 1 of the way to unlocking Aquarion's full potential.
What do socks have to do with Aquarion?
Well, this is just my hypothesis, but...
The wisdom of ancient wrestlers states that fighters who lost their shoes were at a disadvantage.
This shows us that feet are one of the most important things that regulate our bodies.
The color of the cloth that wraps such an vital center of the body is a deep matter.
Cloth wrapping vital parts, you say?
It's got a teal border.
What color do you think I'm wearing?
Come on, you guys, this is serious!
We're talking about ancient documents here!
Huh?
What do people see in her?
What's this about ancient documents?
Andy says he found one.
Let me see it.
Mix, can you read that?
Ancient literature is my thing.
Um... "Top buttons must be buttoned."
What?
Top buttons?
"No hair that grows past the eyebrows."
Hair?
"No dyed hair." "Skirts must reach at least 5cm below the knee." "No running in the halls."
Wait, aren't these...
Ancient school rules. This could be some student's handbook.
What's the matter with him?
To find the most powerful Rare Igura.
We must go to Vega once more.
We have found many Rare Iguras thus far, but the dimensional transference
has either killed them or made them useless to us.
I'd be happy with just Alisia.
Jin, this is about the fate of all Altair.
At first, baby girls quit being born on our planet.
Then our women began dying due to an unknown disease.
Eventually, only men remained on Altair.
This is not an invasion of Vega.
We mean only to ensure the survival of our species.
We must find the most powerful Rare Igura, strong enough to survive interdimensional travel intact,
and make her into our true Eve,
the bride who will bear the next generation of Altair.
There's a good chance that the strongest of the Rare Iguras pilots the Machine Angel.
I understand, High Commander Izumo.
I'll go down there myself this time instead of piloting by remote.
Go, Jin.
Last son of Altair.
I'll dial up the optical sensors...
and I'll focus on solid ammo so I don't end up like last time.
Better take some infiltrator ammo too.
Add some heavy armor on top, and...
I've got a perfect, flawless shield of iron.
Man, I made a total ass of myself.
I dunno, an ancient school handbook is a pretty big find itself.
We can donate it to the Neo-Kowloon Museum!
Those old guys sure sweat the small stuff.
Rules for the length of your hair and skirt?
You're wrong! We can learn from the lessons of history!
Neo-Deava should take the wisdom of the ancients and strengthen its own rules!
What?
I've always thought that your clothes are too revealing, Zessica!
Have you not thought about guarding yourself from the gaze of those boys?
Really? You think so?
To begin with, what do you think the
scriptures say about showing your belly?
You may as well be walking around in just your underwear!
Just her underwear...
Let's try and fix what we can with a few quick rules.
Zessica, there will be no more exposing yourself from now on!
You're treating me like some kind of creep!
Amata, do you think it's bad that you can see my belly?
Well, I mean, not your...
Never have to guess what he's thinking.
Shush?
Do you think guys like girls who wear flashy clothes?
Oh, so you do have clothes like that.
Zessica!
Let me see.
You could show off more.
I think this would look good on you.
I'm not like you!
Abductors detected in the Neo-Kowloon area.
Come and get me, Machine Angel.
He'll start attacking Neo-Kowloon if we make him wait.
He's not here to abduct people this time.
Fudo, what do you think their goal is?
Heavy Armor Radius Gniss.
Send out Aquarion!
The head is Amata! With Zessica and Mikono!
Mikono?
But she...
I... I can't!
Here I go!
Vector Z, launching!
Vector Y, launching!
Vector X, launching!
Approaching the enemy Abductor!
Get ready, Mikono!
Defensive Union! Go, Aquarion!
Aquarion Evol!
W-What should I do?
Mikono...
This ends right here, Abductor!
Infinity Punch!
He's tough!
You hit me with that before.
I'm not falling for the same thing again.
These are the Rare Iguras?
Pff. They're light years below Silvie.
Stop it, Jin! Get back here!
Keep your hands off her! That's my wench!
Your voice is so ugly.
I know you can cry out more beautifully.
Feel the jealousy, Kagura. Feel it harder.
Feel the pain of having the one you love stolen away.
Drink it deeply.
Let's see how powerful you Rare Iguras are.
No damage to Aquarion's external armor!
But it's having an effect on the Elements!
He's using infiltrator ammunition?
He's creating shockwaves that resonate through
Aquarion, thus dealing damage directly within it...
Mikono!
Their Union rate is plummeting rapidly!
The Union is breaking!
Don't look away. Watch closely.
Jin is violating your very own Rare Igura.
Stop!
Stop iiiit!!
Pathetic.
There's no way one of those weaklings could possibly be our true Eve.
The Element suits have been heavily damaged!
We have to do something or the shock is going to go right to their bodies!
Mikono!
I can't watch this! Element Change me!
Let me go, High Commander!
Zessica, dodge it!
What just happened?
I can feel the missiles in the air!
I felt them on my skin!
How is Zessica's machine doing that?
Fudo, what does this mean?
As people get naked, their senses get sharper.
Rip off your clothes, let down your guard,
and you will sense your enemy's moves with perfect precision.
So the less I'm wearing, the better I'll be able to dodge?
But we can't possibly do that!
This isn't the time to be modest!
Zessica!
I can do it too!
Mikono, not you too!
Mikono and Zessica's mind levels are rising!
They're at a Union-capable level!
Right now! Union!
The head is Zessica Wong!
Unguarded Union! Go, Aquarion!
My skin feels so sensitive...
I can feel it all over my body...
So intense!
Aquarion Spada!
I can feel Amata looking at me...
I'm so embarrassed!
Mikono's mind level is still rising!
But why?
She knows someone is looking at her, so her body is hot and bothered.
I understand.
It's okay. You don't have to be embarrassed.
Doesn't matter if you've Unioned.
Just admit defeat already!
Here they come!
My senses are incredibly keen now...
I can feel them all perfectly!
They dodged?
More!
Zessica's spirit level is at an all-time high!
I'll do it too!
I'm embarrassed... but!
Their sonata is so powerful
that I can't possibly play it.
A heart-pounding battle unbound from the chains of modesty!
Let your skin heat up! Let your body burst forth!
Take this!
No Guard!
Attack!
It's game over for me.
But how could I lose to something as stupid as that?
Yes!
Sorry!
But why am I embarrassed?
The best defense is a good offense.
Dropping your guard is the ultimate weapon.
That's a disgusting and perverted strategy! I won't stand for it!
Humans are all born naked.
But that strategy is a double-edged sword.
In exchange for perfect senses, the
Elements sacrifice all of their defense.
I think it'd be best if we all just covered up for now.
How? When did you take these?
Here's 500 kowloons.
Thanks so much!
Put me down for one!
Me too!
Stop it! Don't sell any more of those!
Zessica.
What are you doing all the way over here?
Nothing! I'm not doing anything!
kaze ni ubawareta wake janai
We weren't spirited away on the wind
katamichi bun no yuuki de bokura
We knew we could never return, and found the courage
higeki wo ukeireru
to accept the hardship
kokoro ga koko ni atta hazu no kuudou
There's an emptiness where my heart used to be
motto boku ga ookikereba
If only I was stronger
kimi wo mirai wo sukueta darou ka
I could have saved you, and our future...
taisetsu na hito wo mamoru sube ga tatta hitotsu shika motanai
I only know of one way to keep the people I love
sonna anata ga haguretadayou sora
And you left me and disappeared into the sky
anata ijou no hito ni deaenai
I'll never find anyone like you again
tsuki ni aragau nagai furea
A long flare reaches out against the moon
hajimaru mo sezu owaru monogatari
The story ends before it could even begin
kizutsukiuru yawarakasa
So soft, so fragile
tojikometa senritsu kanaderu hodo
I will call up the melody locked away
utau hodo kowareru hodo ni
And sing it until I destroy myself
anata ga koishii
That's how much I love you
Try saying "horrible" ten times fast.
Horrible horrible horble hobble holeble hole hole...
I hate holes! I'm going to fill them all!
Next time on Aquarion Evol: Turn Man and Woman into a Hole New Word.
Next Time
into a Hole New Word
Turn Man and Woman