Mikono...
The circle of life turns.
Our souls are born over and over.
They experience grief over and over.
And that grief goes to the arms of God in Heaven.
This is...
That is the beautiful law of the world.
Unfortunately, his soul has left the realm of law for something higher.
For we do not have the last son's body.
I say to you that Altair must not die
without seeing even a glimpse of its future.
We have nothing to fear.
The last son has shown us the way.
He has shown us that we live in a time of miracles!
That's ridiculous.
Altair has no future. Its days are numbered.
And Ianthe's power is becoming unstable.
You can't keep them in the dark forever.
Mikage! What do you think you're doing?
Just spreading the great news to the flock.
You sacrificed Jin for this?
He gave much to the world of Altair.
His life was a fair price to pay.
What do you mean?
We were able to deal a great blow to the Rare Iguras' nest.
We obtained a great deal of direct data on the true Eve candidates.
And the reborn Wings of the Sun finally revealed itself.
Jin's soul would be filled with joy if it knew what it brought us.
Perhaps it will be reborn in the first of Altair's new generation.
So that's what you really wanted.
Jin, what I... what Altair has done can never be forgiven.
Separate Paths
We'll be taking them to the graveyard in Neo-Stanley.
The boat will arrive at 2:00. I want everyone there.
Where's Yunoha?
She won't come out of her room.
Or turn visible.
Oh...
Is she going to shut herself in forever?
I know how she feels, though.
If I lost someone I loved, I'd...
Yunoha...
Mikono Suzushiro.
High Commander Fudo?
I don't like him at all...
Bring Yunoha Thrul out of her room.
I want to leave her alone for now.
This school's duty is to foster Union, a positive bond that connects people together.
None can be allowed to drown selfishly alone in their own sorrow.
How can you call that selfish?
Have you forgotten Yunoha's Element power? The power to disappear.
In the wake of Jin Muso's death, her power may go out of control...
and she could erase herself.
You haven't changed.
Yunoha, may I come in?
Mikono...
I thought you might need something to drink.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to if you don't want to.
I'll just leave it here.
Yunoha's aura is getting fainter.
But what can I possibly say?
Jin asked me...
He asked me to go with him.
If only I'd gone, Jin wouldn't...
Oh no... it's getting even fainter now...
She's really going to disappear.
Come, Yunoha.
Come with us.
I can't! I don't want to!
I don't want to... to say goodbye to Jin!
Then don't say goodbye.
I don't want to say goodbye to you, or to Jin either!
I love you, Yunoha. You're a precious friend to me.
Please...
Jin...
Mother, you're on Jin's world?
I... want to...
At last.
At last the students are learning how grateful they
should be to the place we put our lives on the line for,
and the classmates we've lost.
What the hell! We're talking about peoples' lives-
I'm sorry.
Are you...
Sorry.
We've decided to quit school and go back home.
Is that how much you care about your duty?
We Elements have been chosen to fight for this planet!
How could you forget what an honor that-
Mix, stop.
How can you stand this?!
We've been through so much training and...
Andy, not you too!
Naw, I'm staying.
Someone has to stick around or we're all doomed.
We'll all be sucked into that big hole in the sky.
I'm not gonna fall into someone else's hole.
I won't let it happen.
Andy...
Andy W. Hol.
Dig holes.
This is a nightmare!
All these holes...
Thank you, Andy.
What are these holes for?
The planet Altair...
Jin Muso came from another planet called Altair.
Altair...
From the data Jin left us, we have ascertained Altair's intentions.
They are kidnapping female Elements.
The war with Altair will only become more intense.
As it goes on, more may find themselves buried beneath this earth.
In order to prepare you to stand up to the challenge of this war,
you will be buried!
We'll be buried? Are you serious?
I name it...
Special Training of the Grave!
But why? We just
buried our classmates!
I wouldn't want to
be buried in any hole!
And a grave, of all holes!
Hey...
Commander, isn't this...
This is terrible!
Mikono!
How can you say such things when we're all still in pain?!
Each of you is bound by your lives.
As you sleep with the dead, the force of your lives will expand.
Attachment, wickedness, love, stubbornness, hatred.
These thoughts form the links of a chain that shackles each of your souls.
Here, just once, you must experience death.
This character means death.
Death?
You will journey to the very edge of life, then return.
What will you discover in your temporary death?
You must find out for yourselves!
This sounds fascinating.
Shrade!
I'm already on my way there myself.
If my death is soon to come, I may as well rehearse.
Wait, Shrade!
Yunoha!
I want to be with him.
I want to be with Jin, just for a little while.
This is a deep hole. I'll have to fill it myself.
Filling a hole I worked so hard on feels like dying anyway.
I'll never do it!
For you, that's all right.
Your eye looks like it can see through everything.
I hate it!
That's also all right.
Mikono...
Amata!
It's dark. I can't see a thing.
It's so quiet. It's like complete silence.
Wrong.
There is sound here.
The sound of the bugs crawling through the earth.
The creatures that squirm through the dirt.
I can feel the worms creeping at me, trying to get me...
I'm going to... I'm going to...
I'm going to turn into dust and break apart...
My body is rotting away...
Rot away... and return to the earth...
Where I'll be one with Jin again...
I'm so scared... I'm going to go back to the earth...
At this rate, I'll never see the surface again...
Don't be afraid!
I am afraid!
Don't be afraid of this hole.
I can't!
I can't do it.
This is impossible!
High Commander!
This is too much!
Silence!
Well, well. The little Wingless are struggling in the darkness.
Kagura, you want to join them, don't you?
To take the same journey to Hades?
Rest in peace, Kagura...
Rest in peace.
No matter how hard it gets, I can't leave!
Andy dug this hole.
I dug this hole.
If I remember that, I won't be scared.
Even if I can't see...
I can't see anything.
Not even through my Prophecy of Despair.
Why did I see that?
If Mikono is the reincarnation of Sylvie...
then she's not going to choose you, Amata.
I wasn't chosen.
She left me behind, and I wanted to die.
I think I want to die.
If Jin's not in this world anymore...
then I don't want to be in it!
Yunoha!
Yunoha's aura is vanishing!
Amata's power of flight.
Zessica's power of distortion.
Shrade's sound. Cayenne's despair.
And Yunoha's power of erasure.
Their thoughts are going out of control.
If it continues...
No! Yunoha!
Don't do it, Mikono!
We finally became friends! We finally connected!
So why?
Come back! Please!
I can't.
Amata?
If I'm born again, I'll be abandoned again.
I don't want to be abandoned by anyone ever again.
Amata... Amata is going to be abandoned...
I've had enough. I don't want to live anymore.
I want to stay here.
I want to stay here with Jin.
I don't want to be born again.
Never again.
Being alive and alone is...
It hurts.
To live.
No! Stop!
You're all being stupid!
What just happened?
Mikono Suzushiro, this is your power.
The ending of life isn't the only death humans experience.
Just like how we shed hair and lose teeth,
the cells in our body, heart, and soul are always dying.
Moment by moment by moment.
Moment by moment?
This character means old. Note the shape.
But if we are bound to our old, dead selves, if we keep them with us,
個 means separate. The character in the previous scene, 古 (old), is part of 個.
we are divided and cut off from the universe.
Mikono Suzushiro, your power is to connect those who are so divided once more.
My power is to connect?
Yes. To reach out to those who are attached to their old selves
and transform their dead into nourishment.
Like the tendrils of a mushroom,
hidden within the earth.
You connect all the fragmented souls together as they dangle between life and death.
All this time, these twelve thousand years, I've loved you.
No way!
Eight thousand years from the time that I met you, my love will be stronger than ever before.
That voice!
I was always alone.
I didn't care about anyone else.
Jin, it's you!
Yunoha, when I met you, for the first time I wanted to connect with someone.
Please, don't stop living.
Yunoha...
And the rest of you too.
The rest of us?
I realized that I'm not alone.
Our lives...
aren't just our own.
aren't just our own...
He's right!
Our lives can go beyond life and death...
and connect!
The earth is so warm!
We're being cradled by the dead!
I feel like I'm a baby being held at my mom's breast again!
If I'd never been born, I wouldn't be here to experience this!
If I'd never been born, I wouldn't have met anyone here. I wouldn't have met Jin.
There's nothing scary outside of this hole!
There'll be danger, all right.
But there'll be the same warmth I feel in this hole!
That warmth will always come with pain and suffering.
But I still...
There are sounds that must be played from the edge of death and rebirth!
Exactly!
Don't be scared!
I'll be here, waiting for you!
All of you are going to be born again!
And I'll be waiting for you!
As time flows on, we are all being born moment by moment and reborn moment by moment.
The instant that nothing becomes something...
is now!
Now?
And when a heart is there to experience the instant of now...
今 (now) when stacked on top of 心 (heart) make 念 (thought).
That is when thoughts are truly in Union.
The 念 (thought) from the last scene is the first character in the phrase Fudo uses here: 念真合体 (nenshin gattai).
What happened?
Mikono?
Happy birthday!
No way!
kaze ni ubawareta wake janai
We weren't spirited away on the wind
katamichi bun no yuuki de bokura
We knew we could never return, and found the courage
higeki wo ukeireru
to accept the hardship
kokoro ga koko ni atta hazu no kuudou
There's an emptiness where my heart used to be
motto boku ga ookikereba
If only I was stronger
kimi wo mirai wo sukueta darou ka
I could have saved you, and our future...
taisetsu na hito wo mamoru sube ga tatta hitotsu shika motanai
I only know of one way to keep the people I love
sonna anata ga haguretadayou sora
And you left me and disappeared into the sky
anata ijou no hito ni deaenai
I'll never find anyone like you again
tsuki ni aragau nagai furea
A long flare reaches out against the moon
hajimaru mo sezu owaru monogatari
The story ends before it could even begin
kizutsukiuru yawarakasa
So soft, so fragile
tojikometa senritsu kanaderu hodo
I will call up the melody locked away
utau hodo kowareru hodo ni
And sing it until I destroy myself
anata ga koishii
That's how much I love you
Being reborn from the earth gave those kids quite a power up.
I'd better step up my game!
Looks like my old taser is due for an upgrade!
Next Time
Beasts of Love
Next time on Aquarion Evol: The Beasts of Love.