Kokoro
masshiro PAGE mekuru
I walk through the white pages of my storybook
Incoming Text
tobidasu irodoru hajikeru
that's just waiting to be painted
mangekyou no fuukei
with a kaleidoscope of my experiences
From
Me
To
You
kizukeba STORY wa mada
This story has only
gikochinaku hajimatta bakkari
just barely begun
shinkokyuu wo mou ikkai
I take a deep breath
tabi suru kaze tsutsumikomu you ni senaka wo osu
and the wind wraps around me and urges me forward
aa yawarakakute atatakai kimi no te
Your hand is so warm held within mine
nigiri shimete sono kokoro no oku made todoku you ni
It reaches all the way into my heart
hohoenmi de kumeta nara nigirikaeshite kuretara
I can't see a brighter future
boku wa tada mae wo miteru
than you smiling and taking my hand as well
The Person I Like
The first semester midterms have ended...
I get it!
Me too!
Thanks to Sadako's review session!
Thank you so much, Sadako!
...and it's almost time for the school festival.
What is that?
Constipation? Diuresis?
That's so creepy!
Supposedly that junior Sadako Kuronuma grows them.
Sadako?
Oh her! I've seen her before!
There have been stories about her curses since freshmen year!
No way!
The theme for this year's school festival is Fantasy!
School Festival Theme
Fantasy!!
Any suggestions for what our class should do?
School Festival Theme
Fantasy!!
I hope I can participate too.
Whatever's fine, just hurry up and pick.
Me, me! I have one!
What about "Sadako's Black Magic Café"?
Black magic?
Sadako's famous among the freshmen too.
We can use those weird herbs she grows and make tea.
We could make an "Ask Sadako" booth!
But make it more like a fortune-teller's tent!
She's doing well for herself.
Yeah.
That's a great idea!
Alright, let's take a vote!
Class Exhibit
Sadako's Black Magic Cafe: 26
Haunted House: 7
Costume Parade
Midnight Monster Parade
What's this?
That's Vap Ca.
Oh right, there's a Vap Ca tea, isn't there?
What about this one?
That's perilla.
Wow, you're growing perilla?
I thought it might be helpful to have some on hand.
Here come the guys.
Kazehaya!
Look at this!
Sadako's growing a bunch of medicinal herbs!
Hey, do you think we could use perilla in the café?
Sadako?
Huh? Oh, yeah!
We could make tea with it.
That's true. As long as you steep it in hot water, you can make tea with just about anything.
Normally you use rosemary.
Rosemary?
I wanted to talk to him, but I didn't know what to say.
Maybe it's my imagination,
but it feels like we've drifted even further apart now.
Am I the one who's drifting away from him?
Sawako is trying to talk to him but
Kazehaya's just been so difficult lately...
I wonder if something happened.
You're probably the most different from her.
This is bad. I'm screwed if I don't fix this.
That's it! I could get Ryu to—
Ryu's
going with you this Sunday, right?
To the wedding?
Oh that!
Yeah, we're going together in his dad's car.
When are you guys leaving?
Around 7.
Take your gel eyeliner and draw a line right on your lash line.
Make the portion right above your irises the thickest.
Extend the line past the outer corner of your eye…
Eyeshadow
Eyeliner
Done
Huh?
Oh, wow. What are you doing?
Y-Yano-chin!
Please!
I had a doll like this once.
No matter what style you're trying to do, foundation is crucial.
Yano-chin…
Thank you for coming over so early in the morning.
Don't worry about it. I got a good laugh out of it too.
Hey Chizu?
You know, it's not all about making your eyes look big or whatever…
Can I try?
Great.
The almond shape of your eyes is what makes them beautiful.
Really?
You have to leverage that to show off your beauty.
Today's an important day for you too.
And afterwards, let's highlight your eyes in a pale pink to soften the look.
Does it look okay?
Amazing. Like a completely different person!
What do you think?
Not bad.
Hurry up and get in the car!
I'll see you later!
Chi!
You and I will be even closer now.
What? You mean it?
I mean it!
Toru, Haruka,
congratulations.
What's up?
That was a beautiful wedding, wasn't it?
Yeah.
Oh yeah, it's almost time for your summer tournament, right?
Yeah, it's right after the school festival.
Good luck! You guys better win this time!
So what is it?
What?
What did you want to talk about?
There's something, isn't there?
Please!
No.
Why not??
I said I don't want to.
Why not?! You just have to tell him what he wants to hear!
You can say that he totally understands Sawako, 100%!
No, I don't think that works.
I don't want to say it.
You don't understand!
No!
I'll ask him what's wrong though.
But not for your sake. It's 'cause I'm worried about him too.
And that doesn't mean I'm going to tell you anything if he tells me.
Thanks for this.
What? Ryu!
Shota, you're not going to the cafeteria?
You go on ahead.
I'm gonna drop off this toolbox first then head over.
Thanks, Kazehaya!
No problem.
I'm so excited for the Black Magic Café!
There's the Ask Sawako fortune-telling booth too.
What's wrong?
I-I don't actually have any supernatural powers…
Will I really be able to help people with their problems?
Don't worry about it. Just tell them what you see.
Yeah, you're really good at that!
I-I'll do my best!
I could make tea with a blend of perilla and Thunberg's geranium…
Sadako.
Teacher!
I want to have a talk with you. Are you free now?
I am an amazing man~
I'm not letting you sleep tonight either!
Shota!
Here.
Coming!
I'll keep what Chizuru said in mind.
So in the end, did you decide to confront her or not?
Your soup…
Where'd that come from?!
I was just wondering what's wrong.
I don't know how I should treat her anymore.
I've always acted however I liked around her.
I can't say I did that for her sake.
Some of the things I did probably bothered her.
And when I think of that, I just don't know what to do anymore.
Then I think I could just ask her…
You're not going to?
Do you think she'd actually say something's bothering her?
Probably not.
See?
Well, looky here. It's Shota!
Sitting all the way over here, calmly eating his lunch.
Is there something wrong with that?
Is it really okay?
Your lover's cheating on you at the moment!
With Kent Miura.
You've got it wrong.
That's not cheating and we're not together.
What?
Then that means…
Y-You were rejected?
You were rejected!
I was not!
Then you haven't even confessed to her yet, is that it?
You should just tell her how you feel!
Sing out your love to her under the majestic sun.
Work up your small, insect-like courage and confess your love from the top of the jungle gym!
Why does this guy know so much?!
That was delicious.
Time for lunch.
What, you're already done, Ryu?
Especially when Kuronuma probably knows nothing at all.
Or wait. It's possible that she does know but just finds it annoying.
I really don't understand her.
So what? Of course you don't.
Who do you think you are?
Yeah…
Where did you say they were?
What?
Where's Kuronuma?
She's by that weird garden—
Hey!
It seems like you're fitting in really well. I'm so glad, Sadako.
Fitting in? Me?
Seeing
her life
flash
before
her eyes
A
I-Is this what fitting in is like?
I've only ever seen it in my dreams!
Did you just notice?
You're no longer an outcast.
See, even without Kazehaya's help, you're totally fine!
Aren't you happy?
Or did you always want to be an outcast so that Kazehaya would help you?
No…
It's always been my goal...
Can I play too?
...to be able to fit in with everyone.
Good morning.
It's something I've always longed for.
But…
Kuronuma.
Because he's always treated me so normally,
I forgot all about it.
He only cares about you because you look so depressed all the time!
He just cared about me because I seemed depressed.
I guess that's true.
I'm happy but I'm also… shocked.
I always looked up to that part of Kazehaya.
It's an easy mistake to make.
With Kazehaya always paying special attention to you and all.
What?! Does he know?
Amazing! He really is a psychic!
I'm sure Kazehaya didn't mean to do any harm.
He's just kind of insensitive I guess.
Th-That's not true!
Kazehaya's always fair and kind and friendly, no matter who he's dealing with!
He's always greeted even me with a smile!
When I told him how I felt, he believed me.
He's the first person I could talk to without feeling like there was a wall between us.
It's because he's always like that that I fell in love with him.
And yet, that wasn't enough anymore.
I couldn't believe how greedy I was becoming.
I interpreted things wrong…
You knew you were wrong?
Ah, stop! It's hard to admit stuff like this, even to myself.
I understand.
That insensitive jerk!
Don't you think it'd be a good idea to avoid Kazehaya from now on?
For both of your sakes!
Both our sakes?
Yeah! You should live your own life, enjoy your youth!
And Kazehaya's "mission" would be completed so he could—
Sadako, Kazehaya has someone he likes.
He's already rejected me.
I didn't want to tell you,
but now don't you think you can leave him alone?
You don't want to be a bother to him, right?
You should start over.
Have other crushes!
Experience a lot of fun—
Sadako?
There was someone.
There really was someone.
Hey!
You were that serious about him?!
I'm sorry!
I'm sure there's someone better for you out there though!
It's okay!
Sadako, you're much cuter when you smile! Smile!
I can't stop crying…
There was nothing I could do…
I really was too naive.
It's okay, it's okay!
Have some confidence in yourself!
There are tons of guys out there!
Like me.
I wouldn't mind...
if you liked me.
douka ima dake wa furimukanaide
Please don't look at me right now
yuugure sawagu kaze
The sun's set, the wind's blowing,
furesouna kyouri
and we're so close that we can almost touch
kimi wo mitsumeteru zutto
My gaze has always been fixed on you
kimi ga suki de
I like you
I've always liked you
kono omoi koi demo ii
I don't mind if this emotion is what they call love,
kizu tsuitemo ii
and I don't care if I get hurt by it
nando demo tsutaetai
I just want to tell you, over and over again
kimi ni todoke
I want to reach you
Preview
Affection and Annoyance
In the beginning, I thought it was only natural…
Next time: Affection and Annoyance.