Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
namida wo nose
take away your tears
kareru made supiido agete
Speed up until they dry
tobikoete yukeru
I can overcome this
kitto kotae wa
The answer is
harukana ano sora no mukou
waiting beyond the distant sky
kotae ga mitsukaranai koko de wa
There's no answer here,
tameiki wo tsuite sora wo miru
so I sigh and look up at the sky
aoku somerareta hitomi no oku de kagayaiteru no wa
Shining deep within my eyes, reflecting its blue,
doko de mo yukeru, yume wo miteru
is a dreamer who can overcome anything
jibun na no sa
It's me, myself
Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
negai wo nosete
carry your dreams
nobashita te wa asu wo egaku
My hands willl draw tomorrow
mou kowaku nado nai
I'm not scared anymore
namida no ato
The memory of my tears
nijiiro ni somatte tondeyuku
are dyed by rainbows and fly
ano sora no mukou
far away beyond the sky
Wow, it's old school superhero shading!
Um, who...
Elena Peoples.
I like the color of your hair.
It looks like a blue crystal.
Make a contract with me and become a member of Pied Piper!
Huh?
Don't mind her.
She's always like that.
Don't talk to me before the playback ends.
Is that Generation Bleu HQ?
Wow... But why does it look like that?
It's cool, isn't it?
It's built from stuff found inside the Scub Coral.
Tighten Up
This is control speaking.
Triton locked in.
This is the Triton.
Lock in confirmed.
Beginning transport to deck number three.
Roger. All systems connecting.
Connection confirmed.
Beginning complete system check.
Complete system check startup confirmed.
Triton's system check is complete.
Stopping Triton's engines.
Stopping engines.
Transportation of the Triston to deck number three is complete.
Maintenance crew, you may begin your jobs.
I repeat. Transportation of the Triston to deck number three is complete.
Are you the Mark I's pilot?
I'm the technical director, Alexander Boyd.
I'd like to talk to you.
Oh, I'm sorry about the left arm.
Don't worry about it.
We'll finish adjusting the new parts within four hours.
I see you like to oversteer.
Over...?
We'll be doing it over here.
Section chiefs, gather over here.
Sorry for making you wait, Ao.
This way.
But Noah is still...
I'll get someone to look for him.
Don't worry about it.
Lifting the looker!
So warm...
We're saved...
Stowaways, huh?
And your clothes...
Don't tell me you guys snuck on in Okinawa?
T-Take us to your leader...
Take us to your leader!
I see. It matches the data Fleur gathered.
But there is one point where his genome map is very different from ours.
What?
His retina. Especially the positions of his optic nerves.
Is there anything wrong?
His range of perception might be much wider.
He may be able to see electromagnetic waves beyond human limits, such as infrared or ultraviolet light.
Then this world might look very different to him.
I wonder what they're talking about...
No significant abnormalities.
You're a perfectly normal twelve year old.
Normal? But my hair...
It's not a problem.
It's a part of you, and something that you inherited from your mother.
Yessir!
Fleur, where are we going?
Miss Fleur. I'm your superior.
Miss Fleur.
Will do.
A few thousand people work here at the Swiss HQ.
We are at the top of the tower now, the base of the IFO teams.
The tower continues underground as well.
I think all together it's about the size of a city.
Ahead of here are our quarters.
He's the newbie we just recruited.
He has an ID already, I assume?
Whoops, I forgot to ask the Chief!
Come on, it doesn't really matter!
Rules are rules.
Come on!
Next order of business.
Moments ago, a peculiar intruder was spotted at headquarters.
We assume it's a sloth. So far, it has escaped capture.
Noah!
Hey, wait!
If something happened to him, Naru would get mad at me!
Oh, is that so important?
Is that girl on the island your girlfriend?
No, she's not.
Anyway, I have to look for him!
Wait!
Welcome to this distant land.
I am the president of Generation Bleu, Christophe Blanc.
Do you have something interesting for me?
Han.
When your IFOs took something out of the Scub,
it turned gray and the bursts calmed down.
So this is how you do your hyper-rescues?
No one knows this little secret, I guess.
Our company focuses on studying the Scub Coral.
There's nothing weird about this.
The interesting part comes now.
I've seen that kind of shiny thing before.
I got something like that planted on my FP,
but then some Scub appeared from it, and bursted.
Is your company really an innocent volunteer organization as you portray yourselves to be?
I see.
You boys piqued my interest.
Not here either.
Miss... Elena?
Sorry. I'll search seriously now.
Do you really mean it?
Oh look, a sloth!
Where did you come from?
Here, have some!
Look, he likes it!
Chloe, be careful!
Something wrong?
What are you doing, Maev?
But...
Stay still, Maggie!
They're Goldilocks, another IFO team just like us.
Their attitudes are totally different.
Isn't the Fukai kid with you?
She's in Pied Piper!
Rebecca? Who are they?
Stowaways.
Don't say it like that!
Later, Fleur.
See you.
Who was that?
Rebecca, huh? And your surname?
Do I have to answer?
We'll be colleagues from now on!
The president has a screw loose.
What's wrong?
Most likely a Scub Burst.
Fukai Ao, huh?
I heard you entered the Zone and defeated a Secret.
No way!
Didn't you hear? He piloted the Mark I.
The Mark I?
I didn't know that still worked!
You can't have any! It's all mine!
Are you going to eat all that?
Yeah.
But...
You didn't tell her she's tiny.
And you shouldn't!
You may be on the ace team, but we are still your superiors!
You've got cream on your nose.
Anyway, nice to meet you, Ao.
If you've got any questions about life here, feel free to ask.
Thank you!
He's cute for sure,
but the Generation Bleu's fluffy mascot is obviously Bruno! Right?
Pied Piper guys can't have any!
I could live without it too...
Welcome to Generation Bleu.
But you should go back home right now.
If you stay here, you would upset those who care about you.
Now, let's get going.
What's up?
They're mobilized? Shouldn't we...
We shouldn't.
The order was for Goldilocks, not Pied Piper.
It's huge! Any sign of the G-Monster?
You mean Secret.
But none at the moment.
However, there's a mid-sized hurricane closing in on the location.
A typhoon?
You boys?
Let me introduce you.
They have joined the company.
I'm Gazelle. These guys are Pippo and Han.
It's the duty of us elders to give the young ones a chance.
I don't like to involve civilians on a whim.
The Medon is now in suborbital flight.
We're here!
I don't have my ID yet. Are you sure this is okay?
Don't worry about it!
Shower, shower, hey!
Here, some fanservice!
He said I'd make people dear to me sad.
People dear to me...?
What are you doing here? This is the girls' dorm.
But Elena...
Elena? When did you two become best friends?
Ao, why did you come here?
Sorry, I just...
Any Secrets?
Yessir. No reports as of now.
This is a very rare case. According to the records...
1952, Tashkent. '67, Quebec.
'95, the Strait of Malacca.
There are plenty of examples where it took a while for the Secret to emerge.
Don't let your guard down!
Then shouldn't we just collect the Quartz now?
Chloe... Girls, don't go too far ahead.
We know.
If there's any danger, we'll contain it.
Yep, yep.
Maev and I always keep an eye out for Chloe.
Don't worry, Bruno.
I'm not a kid!
My body is small and I'm just 11 years old,
but I'm not a kid anymore!
What?
It's an Eisenhower?
What are the Allied Forces doing here?
This isn't their airspace!
Maggie!
No way! Secrets?!
What about the Credo?
It's on the radar, but there's no response!
Request reinforcements from HQ!
Emergency!
The Secrets were hiding inside the hurricane?!
The seawater, lifted by the Secret's high velocity rotation, prevented visual detection.
It's currently within a 100km radius off the coast of Punta Gallinas.
Stanley.
Just to make sure, Pied Piper is to prepare for mobilization!
The children just returned from action!
So in this case, Kyrie could stand by above the clouds...
Um, what should I do?
Who knows?
You think you're gonna fly with us?
I'm not?
They just wanted to get the Mark I. It's the old fart president after all.
You're so mean.
That's the way he thinks.
But... then why did I...
Hey, where are you going?
I'll ask you again.
Ao, what have you come here for?
Requiem, Gloria, Credo... none of them are responding.
Medon!
We are now going to start rescue operations.
We need assistance!
Team Pied Piper, hurry with your preparations!
S-Sorry!
Where do you think you're going?
That's yours and yours only.
Change.
Hold still.
Hurry.
Yes.
Here.
What is this?
The key to Nirvash.
Um...
We've adjusted Nirvash.
The left arm works fine as well.
Isn't it called the Mark I?
As per the president's orders, the craft is registered under the name "Nirvash".
Shouldn't you say something to him?
Ao? He joined us on his own. There's no need for that.
Triton: start engines and prepare for launch.
Catapult gate: open.
Moving the Triton to the catapult.
Catapult deck, all clear.
Setting the Triton onto the catapult.
Prepare for take off.
Path all clear.
We've got clearance from control.
Engines at maximum.
Ready for takeoff.
Triton, launch!
To be continued!
takanaru shinzou no koe wa
My heart is racing and beating loud
itsu shika kokochi yoku najinde ite
But that feels cozily familiar
kaze ga tsuyoku fuiteite mo
Even if the wind is blowing hard
me wo tsumuranaide itsu datte mae wo muku yo
Don't close your eyes and always look on ahead
nakitaku nattara omoidashite
If you feel like crying, remember
damatte chikaiatta yakusoku wo
the promise we made together
tabidatsu hinadori no uta
The young birds in the sky sing
ima mo mada umaku tobenai keredo
though they still can't fly well
meguri meguru toki wo koe
Even if we go beyond the edge of time
hitazura ni tsunaida te wo tadotte
I'll only follow you as we hold hands
kotoba wa
"So I never let you go!" My words
sora ni kieteku bakari da toshite mo
may get lost in the infinity of the sky,
chirabaru hikari no naka de
but among the glittering light
mayowazu ni kimi wo sagashidaseru kara
I can still find you without hesitation
Preview
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
Lacking any certainty, Ao sets out on a journey with Nirvash.
Beyond the dark clouds that hide a dreadful sight,
a ray of light gives birth to the shadow of a seeker of truth.
Eureka Seven AO, episode six: Light My Fire.
Listen to the voices of the children of the stars.