Kokoro
masshiro PAGE mekuru
I walk through the white pages of my storybook
Incoming Text
tobidasu irodoru hajikeru
that's just waiting to be painted
mangekyou no fuukei
with a kaleidoscope of my experiences
From
Me
To
You
kizukeba STORY wa mada
This story has only
gikochinaku hajimatta bakkari
just barely begun
shinkokyuu wo mou ikkai
I take a deep breath
tabi suru kaze tsutsumikomu you ni senaka wo osu
and the wind wraps around me and urges me forward
aa yawarakakute atatakai kimi no te
Your hand is so warm held within mine
nigiri shimete sono kokoro no oku made todoku you ni
It reaches all the way into my heart
hohoenmi de kumeta nara nigirikaeshite kuretara
I can't see a brighter future
boku wa tada mae wo miteru
than you smiling and taking my hand as well
Forget About It
Now it's May.
Everything is bright and green.
I considered myself the closest to you out of all of the guys.
But that's not necessarily true.
What did he mean by that?
How should I have responded to that?
I still can't stop thinking about it.
K-Kazehaya only said that to me out of kindness,
but I overreacted and responded to him with...
That was so rude of me!
Man, he's so thick. He didn't even wait for you!
Seriously. Maybe it's all in my head.
It must be because of how he compliments you!
Maybe I really am... creepy.
I want to have a natural relationship
with Kazehaya...  Like before.
But now I don't remember what that was like.
Hey, Kazehaya!
Are you doing anything during lunch break today?
It's so nice out I thought I'd go play soccer.
I'll show you my bicycle kick!
Kazehaya and his buddies are going out to play soccer again?
Hey Nakai, Negishi. Why don't you guys play with us?
What?
Really? You sure?
You guys are on the soccer team!
I bet you guys are really good.
Teach us how to head the ball!
Sure, of course!
Awesome!
Morning, Kuronuma.
Okay, be nice and friendly, natural...
M-Morning.
Kazehaya?
What's up?
Kazehaya treated me the same way he treats everyone...
Wow. I guess that's why he's known as Mr. Lively.
It's hard not to stare after being
greeted with such a beaming smile.
What are you talking about?
Good morning, Sadako.
H-He's being so nice and friendly and normal this morning too!
G-Good mo—
No good, no good. You look so tense.
Morning~
Mor~ning~?
Your forehead!
MORNING!
No, more like this.
Morninggg!
Okay, your turn.
MoRn—
Morninggg!!!
They're at it again.
Morning~~~
He just doesn't quit.
Morning~!
MORNING!
Mooorning!
MorninG!
What a pair.
What is it?
Nothing.
Even if we think of it as kindness,
that "kindness" means something completely different to Kazehaya than it does to me.
Ow, my stomach hurts...
I've been kind of constipated lately...
That sucks.
Huh?
Where'd Sawako go?
Maybe the bathroom?
This is good for constipation...
That plant?
What should I do with that?
There she goes again.
Shota?
Ready?
Did something happen?
You've been kinda down lately.
Have I?
Yeah.
Alright, next!
We're in a new class now.
I thought maybe it was normal to say something like that to help her get used to the new class.
But I made her even more uncomfortable instead.
Who?
Kuronuma.
"Something like that"...
What exactly did you—
I don't wanna talk about it.
So selfish.
That's right.
Deep down, I'm pretty selfish,
possessive, and like things my way.
And quick tempered.
That's why I'm just about out of patience.
I know it'll be difficult for her, but I really want to stop beating around the bush.
This...
is your idea of patience?
But it's not like I want to make things difficult for her.
I've tried so hard to get this far.
But doesn't she like you too?
Well, she doesn't dislike me.
He didn't
He got
(courtesy)
chocolate
Kazehaya is just so lively!
I admire him so much!
And respect him!
But that's it!
What part of me is lively? Jeez!
No one said that.
Are you in some sort of rush?
Yeah.
Someone else might have their eyes on her too.
When I think of someone else being with her...
It bothers me.
Is she really that attractive?
She looks like a traditional Japanese doll to me...
I don't really get it, but hang in there.
That isn't very comforting.
Sawako, where are you going?
Would you mind coming with me?
Welcome to my medicinal plant corner!
Detox
Insomnia
What are these signs for?
I thought it might be helpful to let everyone know what they do!
Detox
Constipation
Diarrhea
I-I see. Don't you normally write the name of the plant?
Detox
I thought it'd be easier to understand if I wrote what they're used for.
Hair Loss
It seems more like these plants will cause what's written!
Huh?
Plants and signs from "The Curse"!
What if I wrote "affects" or "for" on them?
Diuresis
For
That's so small.
"For diuresis"?
Kent!
Wow, you all called me by first name!
I'm so happy.
Kazehaya suddenly came to mind.
I was hoping—
You were hoping someone would visit you, right, Sadako?
Someone you like?
I'm such a psychic.
A p-psychic!
Not only does he act natural,
not only is he friendly,
but he's a psychic too!
Your face looks strained!
I told you that girls shouldn't make faces like that!
I'm a philanthropist, so when a girl looks like she's abandoning everything that makes girls happy,
I just can't ignore her.
Wh-Who does he think he is?
Abandoning?
Let's see...
Alright! When I do this, you smile!
Wh-What was that? Did I really just see that?
And she has such a great role model like you to look up to, right, Ayane?
Thanks. Now get out of my face.
And you, Yoshida, have a fine pair of legs.
Right, Sadako?
Wow, it looks like she's straining her face.
Hey, can you stop forcing her to smile?
It's scary.
Strained
Scary
I... I... want to become friendly, Teacher!
Teacher?!
Teacher, huh?
That has a nice ring to it.
I'll do my best, Psychic Teacher!
Your forehead again!
Let's split up the psychic and teacher parts.
What does this guy want?
Kent!
Hey, it's been a while.
How's your new class?
Are there any cute girls?
I don't know if I'd call her cute, but there's someone who interests me.
Really? Tell us about her!
She's dark and super tense!
What?
What's your deal?
Hey Ayane.
What are you planning?
Planning?
Me? What makes you think that?
You sure are making a lot of passes at Sawako.
But doesn't Sawako like Kazehaya?
So she does.
Hey, don't do something uncalled-for, got it?
This is a really crucial time for her.
Crucial time?
It's okay. I'm a good guy.
See you.
Is it really "okay"?
This will be on the midterm!
Man, midterms already?
That was fast.
I heard that Sadako's cursed notes were passed around freshman year in class D!
They weren't cursed. Our class average was really high thanks to those notes.
What, seriously?
Yeah, seriously!
What was that?
On the midterm, Sadako's cursed notes
cursed you into getting a high score!
No, no, that's not it—
Boys! This will be on the midterm!
What are you guys talking about?
Sadako's notes really helped us on last year's midterm.
Wow, you're really good at academics!
Good?
This is kind of important...
Hey guys, Sadako said that she'd hold a crash course for the midterm after school today!
C-Crash course?!
I-I'm going to do something that crazy?
You'll do it, right, Sadako?
We're in the middle of class at the moment...
If you don't mind me doing it...
I can even tell around three ghost stories now!
I wonder if I can live up to their expectations?
I don't think anyone's expecting you to tell ghost stories.
Wow, four people came!
Sawako, you...
I'm really need this crash course!
Yeah!
Kent ain't coming even though he announced it?
Have you guys started already?
We're just about to.
Oh good. I just made it!
Kazehaya came too.
We're here!
We just finished cleaning.
Thanks, Sadako!
N-No, thank you!
You're really doing it?
Takahashi!
I asked Kazehaya about it earlier.
Where's Ryu?
Baseball practice.
Kazehaya told her...
Hey, Sadako?
I don't know if I can help,
but I'll do my best.
Wow, that's a pretty big group.
Yeah. Kazehaya was telling people about it earlier.
Mr. Lively?
They say he can't ignore people who need help fitting in.
So that's it.
You'll come too, right, Tsuru?
First, for this section, what you need to do is remember the formula.
What was that? I can't see!
Sadako, use the blackboard.
B-Black—
Great idea!
That'll make taking notes much easier.
You heard them. Get going!
O-Okay!
I-I got it!
The answer is...
2 root 5!
The dunce duo got it!
Because it's easy to get now!
You're amazing, Sadako!
It's time, Sadako!
I've never seen her smile before!
Even Sadako smiles!
When Sadako smiles, it means good fortune is on the way!
I've seen it before!
I've seen it countless times before!
This is a competition?
Wow, that was great.
And we understand the problems now too.
I'm so glad we came to this review!
Bye!
Thanks, Sadako!
Teach us again, okay?
Thank you!
Th-Thanks for coming!
Thanks!
Sadako.
You worked really hard to do
something outside of your comfort zone.
Thank you very much, Teacher!
What is this?
It ain't impossible. Definitely ain't.
Ant?
Sorry. Think you can go without me?
I have something important to take care of.
Kuronuma.
Do you have a moment?
Sawako, we're in a bit of a hurry.
You said you wanted to do a safety inspection, right?
Oh yeah!
We're gonna take off, Sawako.
Today, I'll thank him more naturally and like a friend.
U-Um!
I interrupted him!
It's okay. You go first.
I'm sorry.
I-I just... wanted to say thank you for today.
I want to be able to thank him better, but I just can't do it.
Even though he made me so happy...
I don't think standing up there in
front of people is my thing, but I—
I do.
Huh?
I think you have a knack for teaching.
I never, ever want Kazehaya to hate me.
Oh, and about what I said that day...
You don't need to worry about it.
Forget about it.
Hey.
I was waiting for you.
douka ima dake wa furimukanaide
Please don't look at me right now
yuugure sawagu kaze
The sun's set, the wind's blowing,
furesouna kyouri
and we're so close that we can almost touch
kimi wo mitsumeteru zutto
My gaze has always been fixed on you
kimi ga suki de
I like you
I've always liked you
kono omoi koi demo ii
I don't mind if this emotion is what they call love,
kizu tsuitemo ii
and I don't care if I get hurt by it
nando demo tsutaetai
I just want to tell you, over and over again
kimi ni todoke
I want to reach you
Preview
Misunderstood
Unconsciously sensitive and always over thinking.
The more I try, the more things...
Next time: Misunderstood.