Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
namida wo nose
take away your tears
kareru made supiido agete
Speed up until they dry
tobikoete yukeru
I can overcome this
kitto kotae wa
The answer is
harukana ano sora no mukou
waiting beyond the distant sky
kotae ga mitsukaranai koko de wa
There's no answer here,
tameiki wo tsuite sora wo miru
so I sigh and look up at the sky
aoku somerareta hitomi no oku de kagayaiteru no wa
Shining deep within my eyes, reflecting its blue,
doko de mo yukeru, yume wo miteru
is a dreamer who can overcome anything
jibun na no sa
It's me, myself
Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
negai wo nosete
carry your dreams
nobashita te wa asu wo egaku
My hands willl draw tomorrow
mou kowaku nado nai
I'm not scared anymore
namida no ato
The memory of my tears
nijiiro ni somatte tondeyuku
are dyed by rainbows and fly
ano sora no mukou
far away beyond the sky
Are you still going to pilot it?
No, I don't think so.
Why?
People will just hate me even more.
I've never done anything wrong,
but people have always treated me like a foreigner and hated me.
I accepted it and thought it made sense.
But I've had enough.
Ao...
I'm already in junior high, after all.
Oh! Rotten Tuna uploaded a new song!
Hold your horses! I'm coming!
Fleur, don't just sit there!
I update my blog where I please!
Chief, please answer if it's ringing.
I poured too much coffee, so I don't have a free hand.
This is the Triton. What is it?
I'm sorry...
But I got myself into some trouble.
STILL FIGHTING
Found it!
My dad hates Noah, so I hid him here.
What are you doing, Noah?!
What are you going to do now, Ao?
I don't know.
No matter where I go, I'll stand out because of my hair.
Quick!
Get him!
Naru?
Dad?
Mister?
I told you to stay away from him!
Hey!
Dad! Make them stop!
Naru!
Naru! You need to go back to the hospital!
It's true!
It's his fault that our island ended up like this—
Hitoga, take him to my training room.
Noah...
Ao...
He's pretty smart to think of this place. No outsiders will be able to find it.
But the islanders all know about it.
We all played here when we were kids.
No luck. It won't budge.
Does it have some special Japanese military lock?
The Japs didn't engineer it by themselves.
They bought the other parts from the Americans and the French.
That means this thing is fat, surrenders when possible, and has terrible teeth.
Get out, Pippo.
You're not going to magically make it work—
How the hell did that foreigner kid pilot it?
But that kid could fly an FP before elementary school. He learned all by himself.
Where are you going?
To get the person who can pilot this.
But he said he's not going to pilot it...
He will. Oh yes, he will.
We see you often in the news, but now we've got the real thing here.
Genere... Generan...
Generation Bleu.
We are the blue generation.
Yeah, that! You're like the Ghostbusters for G-Monsters, right?
I mean, you've even got a cartoon about you.
You're Pied Piper, right? You help people in trouble, right?
Yeah.
Help Mommy!
She's in there!
Young lady, these people have already done their parts.
Go!
Chief?!
We'll be fine with negotiations without you.
Hang on, I'm bringing Allelujah.
Allelujah?
My IFO!
So it's true that only children can pilot IFOs.
Like Ao yesterday...
Oh, Ao?
He's the pilot of the IFO yesterday?
It's just a rumor...
I see. That's so fascinating.
Chief! What about the meeting with the SDF?
There will be more drinking than talking anyway.
I'll leave the decision making to you.
Sign: Jasmine Tea
This is the second Scub Coral that the Okinawa and Ryukyu Alliance have acquired.
Chivalry
We cannot allow research to be conducted on something so precious by outsiders.
The Scub Coral hasn't been completely destroyed!
If it's not dealt with, another Secret will emerge!
Secret?
Oh, so that's what you scientists call G-Monsters.
Secret, huh?
I've never in my life heard of Secrets showing up at the same place twice.
We wish you a safe trip home.
Have you finished negotiating with the SDF?
I'm here for our team's Elena Peoples.
Join Fleur. Keep an eye on Scub Coral from a distance.
Roger.
And you, Miss Rebecca?
I'll...
sing a song.
As long as the Quartz is still intact, Secrets will show up again.
You alien kid! Are you a spy for the Japs?!
My giant?
I only know about the sea giant.
It's a big rock.
We're not asking you about a rock! We're talking about the giant you pilo—
Long time no see, Ao.
Have we met before?
You don't remember me?
Well, I frequented old Fukai's place ten years ago.
Your mother was still around at that time.
I have a question.
Why do you hate me?
I told them many times.
Don't get involved with a woman from the sky.
That's right... It was thirteen years ago.
Back then... Mitsuo saw it as well.
Ao's mother fell out of the empty sky.
Signs: Alien! Foreigner! Get lost!
Let's get out of here!
It was before our Independence.
The Americans came looking for her, but Fukai Toshio hid her.
When Ao was born, everyone thought he was an alien...
And he's hated because of that?!
That's so mean!
No!
That woman and his son brought disaster upon us.
They angered the sea giant!
Sea giant?
When you were around three, a Scub Burst happened nearby.
You know, at that place.
That's also when the Americans found your mother.
She was taken away and the Burst left with her.
We gossiped about it.
"It all happened because she angered the sea giant."
"She summoned the Scub Coral."
How could that be my... or my mother's fault?!
At the time, a few families who were on an excursion got caught up in the burst,
and the only one who survived was Arata's child, Naru.
So that's why I'm hated?
Then tell me, what should I have done instead?
What could I have done?!
Nothing.
But we can't forgive you or your mother.
I'm sorry.
So a trapar bubble emerged with the Scub Coral?
Isn't that good a good thing?
That whole profiteering was crazy.
We even lost fishing rights to China during the negotiations.
The island was a total mess back then.
The island has changed.
The previous generation wanted to find someone to blame.
Let's do some fucking justice.
What does Generation Bleu want from him?
I once knew a girl with turquoise hair.
I want to know what color the boy's mother's hair was.
S-Stop!
How did you start that IFO? The Nirvash.
Nirvash?
There was a girl who called it that. Nirvash.
You're crazy!
Hurry!
Get in! Don't just stand there! Move!
Jiro! What the hell are you doing?!
Jiro?
That's Gazelle's name.
That's Gazelle's dad?!
I don't know nothing about Jiro!
My name's Gazelle!
That's my real name!
Real my ass, stupid son!
Get out, you fool!
I'm sorry, dad!
This guy too?!
We'll use him to negotiate with the Japs!
It's for the sake of Okinawa's true independence!
Are you out of your mind?!
Jiro?
We bullied him for being a foreigner when we were kids.
Know why?
It's because our parents... the adults said so!
"He's a foreigner!"
"He's an alien!"
"It's all his and his mother's fault!"
We can't fish? Our independence is half-assed?
We blamed it all on Ao!
But did you refuse the security money for the Scub?
You children don't understand! Listen!
Don't you want independence?
From Japan? From America? From China?
Then do it!
Don't just talk about it! Do something!
I see.
Watch. We'll do it.
We will.
Hey, what the heck is that?!
It's a G-Monster?
Holy shit, it's huge!
Will Dad and the others be able to get away in time?
They can all burn in hell.
You told me to protect the island yesterday!
Shut up! Aren't you on our side?
If so, keep your mouth shut.
Your side?
Pilot that IFO again!
We'll go to war with the Japs and the Yankees!
I don't wanna.
What?
I don't wanna pilot it.
I ended up like this because I did!
Put me down at my grandpa's place.
You're kidding...
Grandpa!
You're... Ao...
Don't hate them. You mustn't do that.
But they set our house on fire!
Even so, you cannot hate them.
The adults were all born on this island and they will die on this island.
They have nowhere else to go.
They love this island. They just want to protect it.
Understand that.
"Sorry..." So that's why he apologized...
That's the reason?
Grandpa, run.
To the sea, if you can!
Hey! Ao!
Ao!
I... I have every right to love this island too!
It's huge! Aim wherever you want! Just hit it!
Captain!
What?
It's Generation Bleu. They're offering us some advice.
Put them through.
Pardon our earlier actions.
No worries. We are going to open fire at the G-Monster now.
Don't do that.
What?
The Secret will unleash a powerful electromagnetic burst in the area, rendering your electronics useless.
Conventional projectiles will cause it to react and be countered.
Conventional weaponry is useless.
We've been telling everyone this for at least a decade, and they don't get it! Jeez.
Then what should we do?
The Secrets' reactions are slow compared to FP's and IFO's.
The only IFOs in the area are the two of ours...
There's three.
Our headquarters are negotiating a new contract with the Okinawan government.
But our analysis shows that the signals from the Scub Burst earlier are still present.
Therefore, our team Pied Piper will now engage and annihilate the Secret.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
Zone mapping complete.
Some parts are always outside of the zones. Be careful.
Kyrie, let's go.
Support cannons: full power.
Don't worry. It can't see you.
I'm at the feet of the Scub, after all.
Let's try this again.
Dammit!
Sorry! You've got two!
I got it.
I'm going to take them out, so watch out for the shots.
Sorry! You okay?
This is nothing.
I wonder what's next.
Here it comes.
Yeah.
It's an entire army.
Didn't you say you're not going to pilot it? What's up with you?
I'll fight the G-Monster.
It's too big!
If you consider yesterday's one to be a
fighter, then this one's the mothership!
Are you going to protect them? The retarded adults who treated you like shit?
I don't want to pilot it.
If I do, I'll be an alien.
But if I don't, I'll regret it later.
Like your dad did.
Ao...
I don't want to apologize to a child!
Mama?
Don't move, Ao.
This will make Nirvash remember you.
Nirvash?
I see... you remembered me this entire time...
To be continued!
takanaru shinzou no koe wa
My heart is racing and beating loud
itsu shika kokochi yoku najinde ite
But that feels cozily familiar
kaze ga tsuyoku fuiteite mo
Even if the wind is blowing hard
me wo tsumuranaide itsu datte mae wo muku yo
Don't close your eyes and always look on ahead
nakitaku nattara omoidashite
If you feel like crying, remember
damatte chikaiatta yakusoku wo
the promise we made together
tabidatsu hinadori no uta
The young birds in the sky sing
ima mo mada umaku tobenai keredo
though they still can't fly well
meguri meguru toki wo koe
Even if we go beyond the edge of time
hitazura ni tsunaida te wo tadotte
I'll only follow you as we hold hands
kotoba wa
"So I never let you go!" My words
sora ni kieteku bakari da toshite mo
may get lost in the infinity of the sky,
chirabaru hikari no naka de
but among the glittering light
mayowazu ni kimi wo sagashidaseru kara
I can still find you without hesitation
PREVIEW
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
To protect the island, Ao throws himself in the battle to win.
His determination shakes people one after another.
What will the boy do as beyond hope and despair, he loses a place to return to?
Eureka Seven AO, episode 4: Walk This Way.
Listen the voice of the children of the stars.