Kokoro
masshiro PAGE mekuru
I walk through the white pages of my storybook
Incoming Text
tobidasu irodoru hajikeru
that's just waiting to be painted
mangekyou no fuukei
with a kaleidoscope of my experiences
From
Me
To
You
kizukeba STORY wa mada
This story has only
gikochinaku hajimatta bakkari
just barely begun
shinkokyuu wo mou ikkai
I take a deep breath
tabi suru kaze tsutsumikomu you ni senaka wo osu
and the wind wraps around me and urges me forward
aa yawarakakute atatakai kimi no te
Your hand is so warm held within mine
nigiri shimete sono kokoro no oku made todoku you ni
It reaches all the way into my heart
hohoenmi de kumeta nara nigirikaeshite kuretara
I can't see a brighter future
boku wa tada mae wo miteru
than you smiling and taking my hand as well
I'm off to school now!
Have a good day!
Now it's April.
And I'm a 2nd year student.
2nd Years
Homeroom Teacher   Kazuichi Arai
Tomoko Endo
Sawako Kuronuma
What class are Chizu and Ayane in?
Sawako!
We still have two years until graduation. Let's make the most of them!
That was more nerve wracking than I thought it'd be.
Yeah! We were really lucky, weren't we?
Yeah!
Tomo and Ekko are in our class too.
And so is Joe!
Yeah...
Had enough of him?
I would've been really lonely if we weren't in the same class...
I feel like I'm dreaming right now!
I'll bring a CD tomorrow.
Go for it!
Good morning!
Good morning.
Hey guys! This girl's name is Sawako Kuronuma.
You guys can call her Sadako if you'd like!
Seems like things are still the same.
Line up in the hallway! It's time for the opening ceremony.
Ryu, let's make this a good year!
I dreamt that I was going out with her!
Seriously?
Akihiko's concert was so amazing!
Really?
You're too spread out! Compact yourselves!
Chigusa is in class C.
I see.
I can't believe we're all in the same class again!
Funny how that works.
Why do you look like you know something I don't?
Onto more important business...
What? You didn't give the chocolates to him?
But you spent all that time making them! Why not?
Well...
Something definitely happened on Valentine's Day.
Things have been so awkward and strained since then.
It could be that she's finally come
to realize how she feels about him...
But then again...
What are those two doing?!
We had spring break and holidays and everything!
Ya-Yano-chin?
Sawako, love is all about timing.
Kurumi...
He's already rejected me.
It's been bothering me since that day...
Does that mean that Kazehaya doesn't like dating?
Please work hard at both your academics
and your extracurricular activities.
Or could it possibly be that he already has someone he likes?
I feel like I can understand
what Kurumi meant now when she said that she wished
Kazehaya could just remain everyone's beloved Kazehaya
instead of being someone's.
They don't have any hidden meaning to them?
We're in the same class,
and he even said good morning to me.
All of that is like a dream come true, and yet...
And yet...
I just can't forget what it was like when it was just the two of us.
It'd be greedy
to want more of that, wouldn't it?
I would have hidden intentions then, wouldn't I?
Akihiko's final costume was amazing!
It made everyone go crazy!
Sadako! Right?
You know me?
Wow, we're sitting next to each other!
Nice to meet you!
I'm Kento Miura.
N-Nice to meet you!
Hi! A-OK!
So people like this really exist.
So you do have eyebrows!
He's so close!
You look kinda scary now.
That's no good!
You'll give yourself wrinkles!
Poke, poke.
S-S-Scary.
Alright, let's hurry up and pick our committee members.
Starting with class rep...
Should I pick?
Eeny, meeny, miny, mo. With whom should I go?
But this isn't the time for me to be scared!
No one wants to do it...
I could do it.
Oh my gosh, that was close.
I almost took away someone's fun!
You sure, Kento?
Won't I get lots of attention that way?
Don't worry. You'll never get as much attention as me.
Wow, that guy next to Sawako's pretty bold.
A new student, huh.
I nominate Kuronuma for class life rep.
Kuronuma's really good at taking care of the flowers.
Tomo...
You're always taking care of the flowerbeds for us!
You knew?
I'm so happy...
Thank you!
Huh.
What's up?
She can smile.
If it's too much, I'll help too!
Thanks!
Next, the atmosphere rep will be...
Jonochi! Congrats!
Everyone, rise!
Bow!
Good work!
That might be good too—
Hey Miura!
Yes?
Come with me.
I'll tell you all you need to know about being
class rep and respecting your homeroom teacher.
Coming!
What a hassle. That's why I told you not to do that.
Hassles can be fun, don't you think?
Always with that positive attitude.
Hatsure.
You can go on without me.
Who said I was gonna wait?
I'll see you guys tomorrow!
Bye bye!
I'm off to the library. Good luck, Sawako!
Okay.
Really!
It was hilarious!
Kazehaya.
Are you going home now, Kuronuma?
No. I'm going to stay for a bit and
plant some seeds in the flowerbeds.
I see.
Kazehaya?
Coming!
Then I'll see you around.
O-Okay!
Bye bye.
Sorry.
You guys go on ahead.
Hey Ryu!
Today was just the opening ceremony and you already have practice?
Yeah.
Hey, has the date been decided yet?
Databin?
The date for Toru's wedding!
Oh right.
When was it again?
It's probably soon.
I'll go ask your dad next time I see him.
Excuse us!
Good luck!
Oh yeah, you guys have a tournament coming up?
The spring tournament is soon.
Will you go to Koshien if you win?
That's summer.
The spring tournament is more of a practice run.
Well, it's still good if you win, right?
Yeah.
See you.
See you!
I'll come over for ramen tonight!
Thanks for that.
What?
For what?
What do you mean for what? Dividing the classes!
Remember what I said to you?
Sawako can
perform
exorcisms
for you.
I can get all
of them to
work together!
Having Ryu and
Kazehaya in
the class will
make things
convenient
for you.
Chizu will
be helpful
during the
sports festival.
Oh, and chocolate
for you cause I
respect you so much!
As if I bothered listening to all of your requests.
Respect, huh?
Can't argue with that.
You didn't?
A lot of things happen 2nd and 3rd year, right?
Best time of your life.
It's basic human kindness not to want to separate good friends.
Kindness?
So some handsome teacher suggested.
Handsome?
After 1st year, it's easy to tell who the
good friends and not so good friends are.
You weren't even homeroom teacher for the whole—
That handsome teacher's name was Kazuichi Arai.
The man who will one day become president!
I'm going home.
What a waste of time and chocolate.
You guys are good friends.
Have a good time together while you're here.
His existence is a miracle.
It's weird to hear that after hearing him brag about himself first.
Kazehaya?
You're still here.
Yeah.
Kazehaya.
Why don't you get a girlfriend?
You're quite popular after all.
Or wait! Do you already have someone you like?
You do, don't you?
Right?
Do you know anything about personal privacy?!
Who is it?
If it's someone I know, I'll help you.
This isn't like you, Yano.
I don't need help.
And besides...
I can't tell you, Yano. I'd want to tell the person
who I like first before I tell anyone else.
That didn't work at all.
Seems like he's the type who doesn't
like it when others try to interfere.
Well, I suppose it is something that the parties
in question should take care of themselves.
I guess I have to hold myself back
unless the timing doesn't work out.
This corner will be for medicinal plants!
A-A witch?
All done.
I didn't think that he'd still be here.
You planted a lot of seeds.
Yeah.
I thought that he'd already gone home.
What should I do?
It's hard to breathe.
It's been so long since it was just the two of us.
Wait, what am I supposed to do when this happens?
We're in the same class.
That makes me happy.
He laughed.
But we can't talk as much because our seats are farther apart now.
Y-Yeah.
Was he... worried about me?
We'll be together until graduation now.
Yeah.
It makes me even happier.
It makes me so happy that Kazehaya and I
can be in the same class until graduation.
And it makes me want to be with him even more.
W-Were you waiting for someone?
Yeah.
Kuronuma.
I was waiting for you, Kuronuma.
I considered myself the closest to you out of all of the guys.
But that's not necessarily true.
I was too conceited.
Closest...
Th-That...
Um...
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to put you in an awkward
position by saying that suddenly.
No...
Bye bye.
No, that's not true!
You're wrong!
It's just that there was nothing I could
say that wouldn't mean something special.
That's an unexpected combination.
douka ima dake wa furimukanaide
Please don't look at me right now
yuugure sawagu kaze
The sun's set, the wind's blowing,
furesouna kyouri
and we're so close that we can almost touch
kimi wo mitsumeteru zutto
My gaze has always been fixed on you
kimi ga suki de
I like you
I've always liked you
kono omoi koi demo ii
I don't mind if this emotion is what they call love,
kizu tsuitemo ii
and I don't care if I get hurt by it
nando demo tsutaetai
I just want to tell you, over and over again
kimi ni todoke
I want to reach you
Preview
Forget
A smile that captured everyone's attention.
The way it was before.
Next time: Forget.