hikaru suiheisen
Just over the bright horizon,
s
t
r
U
hajimari to owari no
where the beginning and the end
s
t
r
U
tokeau soko wa
melt into one,
s
t
r
U
namida no furusato na no
lies the homeland of tears
s
t
r
U
furueteru te de
I've already pocketed
s
t
r
U
shinjirareru mono
my trembling hand
s
t
r
U
poketto ni tsumekonda
which holds my beliefs
s
t
r
U
kanata de yurameiteru shinkirou
A mirage shimmers in the distance
s
t
r
U
sora miagereba
I look to the sky
s
t
r
U
michibiitekureru you na
hoping it will show me the way
s
t
r
U
natsukashikute atsui hikari wo kureru
And it gives off a familiar, warm light
s
t
r
U
anata wa chiisaku te wo furu yo
You wave at me faintly
s
t
r
U
ikanakucha
I must go
s
t
r
U
mou nakanai yo shangurira
Don't cry anymore because Shangri-La,
s
t
r
U
aratana sekai he to daibu shiyou
a new world, is waiting for us
s
t
r
U
aoiro ni dakareta boku wa
As I'm embraced by its blue...
s
t
r
U
kono mune no takanari to tomo ni
My heart beats loudly
s
t
r
U
Earth? Is that Earth?
It's so beautiful...
I see! So that's what you guys are!
But you're dying...
Amazing! You're all so amazing!
I get it...
I understand it all now, Ao!
Where am I?
Are... Are you Naru?!
Starfire
Is it true that Colonel Endo was taken down?
It seems so.
They assaulted a Japanese Army officer with an IFO?
And it happened in our territorial waters.
What do we do now, captain?
Will we still just stand by and watch, sitting on our hands?
I will inquire about the commander's decision again.
But until then...
All units to battle stations!
But the enemy is Generation Bleu.
What's wrong is wrong!
Georg, did a Scub Coral emerge?
No, there's no sign of that yet.
A Secret?
It went through!
Eureka!
Ao?
It's that pillar of light.
Both the Secret and the Scub come from there!
If you fly in there...
I can return home?
You're not going anywhere!
Shoot!
He looks like an ordinary human, but...
Truth, what exactly are you?!
Elena, open fire as well! Elena!
Eureka... Eureka!
You're not getting away this time!
Elena?!
Elena, are you okay? Elena!
Thanks, Fleur, Elena!
That was not intended!
Hurry, Eureka!
Ao, what do you want to do?
I'll send her home.
I'll send Mom home.
Send her home? But how?
Through the pillar of light!
Ao...
But you finally got to meet her!
If she stays here, people like the president and Truth will be after her.
She's only going to suffer!
Gazelle, we need to stop Ao!
He wants to send her home despite finally getting to meet her...
Leave him be.
He's actually quite mature.
If I go home and see my mother,
I'd just hug her and never let her go.
Over there!
Eureka, if you fly into there—
Why are they all hurting us?
Eureka!
Nirvash, what's wrong? Nirvash!
Nirvash, what are you...
Nirvash!
Eureka!
Ao!
Gosh!
Why did you do that?
It wasn't me! Nirvash just...
Nirvash?
Are you telling me the machine moved on its own?
Of course! Because inside Nirvash, there's...
Something like me.
Two Mark I's? Two Third Engines?
Don't tell me...
Why? What's inside of you?
What is it inside of you that hates me?!
Nirvash.
Let's go to the pillar of light.
Is that... a Secret?!
But... Secrets only show up after the Scub Coral emerges.
That's what's supposed to happen...
What's going on, Elena?
Are you going to leave again?
Eureka.
He was right! Johansson was right!
The Secrets aren't here for the Scub Coral.
It was never the case!
Dammit!
If it stays there, we'll never get close to the pillar!
Ao, perhaps...
Those are the extra locks that Alex couldn't open.
Shoot, Ao!
Okay!
Eureka, now's the chance!
Hey, Ao...
Yeah?
Why did you call me Mom?
That's... Well...
Please give birth to a healthy boy!
My baby's a girl!
That's what the doctors told me.
Wait a moment.
She'll be a healthy girl!
Eureka!
What do you mean your baby's a girl?!
Is that...
Nirvash?
We had no choice but to scuttle the vessel.
The JAF attacked us first.
But this is Japanese territory.
Hey, Ivica.
Did you know that Endo person?
Yeah, like that!
Carefully! Gently!
Firmly!
You want to pick up a Secret?
There's no need to worry.
The Secrets appear to destroy their target.
But its target has already disappeared.
This Secret came not for the Scub Coral,
but to destroy the two Mark Is.
Have you had breakfast yet?
It's not going to be bar food, right?
Why did you suddenly come back?
You know, I thought Mom was abandoned by Dad.
Who told you that?
But she gave birth to me alone.
She had to be abandoned.
Eureka said...
That he's...
He's fighting.
For our child...
For us...
So I must...!
Why didn't you tell me?
You didn't want to hear about it.
You said you don't care about the guy who abandoned you and your mother.
Well, that's true...
And do you know anything about my older sister?
What did you say?!
Have you heard anything about whether I have an older sister?
You met Eureka?
Why are you angry?
Let's go.
Naru?
She suddenly appeared?
What do you mean?
I thought you came to visit her after hearing about it.
Not exactly...
Don't tell Naru that.
You came to see me.
Yeah.
I just happened by on the island for some other stuff.
I dreamed about you, Naru.
There was this weird guy and me in the dream.
You chose him and left.
He's not a weird guy.
He's Truth.
But that happened in my dream.
Truth told me that your consciousness was here.
Then did you really leave with Truth?!
I had a dream as well.
A dream about the Coralians.
Coralians?
It's likely that in the distant future,
they come to Earth and fuse with a coral reef to stay alive.
And also to communicate with Earth.
You see, trapar originates from their metabolism.
Then, after a while, the humans who ran away returned to Earth.
To communicate with those humans, the Coralians created beings similar to them.
That's...
But that's just a dream.
The corals of the future?
Wait, future...?
They found a way to come to our time,
and they want to communicate with us.
My Mom came from the future too...
A coral monster... and I'm its child?
It's not a monster.
Ao, the Scub Coral is spreading all over the world.
But if you take the Quartz—
So that means the Scub Coral is an exceedingly dangerous thing.
Doctor, who's that?
Your doctor is against the independence, so he's been cooperating with us for a while now.
A Jap? Why?
Our government has constantly claimed that Iwato Island
does not belong to the United Okinawa and Ryukyu Archipelago,
or any other countries, as it is our territory.
Arata Naru.
Your lungs, heart, and even your spine,
all contain the same material as the Scub Coral.
The Scub Coral is a dangerous material that infects the human body.
To stop the infection from spreading, you will be quarantined,
and the plant coral will be destroyed!
The Allied Forces control Iwato Island.
Why would they allow the Japanese to land?
This was sent to all foreign embassies by the Japanese government.
As you can see, we have successfully established communication
Signs: Cabinet Office
with the creatures known as G-Monsters or Secrets.
We learned that they mean us no harm.
The Secrets emerge naturally as a defensive reaction to
the invasion of creatures from another dimension, the Scub Coral.
They are the immune system of this dimension.
Unlike the Scub Coral, which contains particles not present in this world,
the Secrets are composed entirely of known materials.
The Scub Coral is an invader and the Secrets are the allies of humankind?
Of course the foreign governments have their doubts as well.
But it's something they must consider.
The Japanese took that opportunity to land on the debated territory of Iwato Island in the midst of the confusion.
But Ao is an employee of our company!
They claim that Ao invaded their territory and killed one of their officers.
Nirvash?
Hey!
I received landing permission from the Okinawan SDF! So why?!
We handed it over as evidence. Sorry.
Sorry? But why?
The Allied Force... no, the American government contacted us.
They said that sheltering you is against the law.
Against the law?
It means that you're no human child.
You admitted it too, didn't you?
We are only here to quarantine a victim of Scub Coral infection,
and to arrest the criminal who invaded our territory and murdered a JAF officer.
That's you, by the way.
That's all we're here for.
We've already contacted America and all other countries.
If the Allied Forces intervenes, they'd become involved in the territorial debate as well.
You didn't want things to escalate, since you wanted to avoid another war.
So you'd rather hand Ao and me over instead.
But that doesn't explain what's changed.
What happened?
The Japanese government announced that the Scub Coral is an invader.
They are no enemy!
It's ruining your body right now.
No! It's helping me!
It wants to be friends with me.
I wouldn't want a friend like that.
Watch, Ao.
Naru!
A Scub Coral?!
No! It's just regular coral!
Since when does coral move like that?!
Naru!
Hey! What are you all standing around looking at?!
What are you trying to do?!
Don't you point a gun at a kid!
This is a matter of internationa—
Let go!
I applaud you, Naru.
Your timing is perfect too.
Looks like you've become a lot more perceptive while I was away.
Yeah. I understand you as well.
It's just like in my dream.
Naru...
You're Eureka?
Please help Ao.
He's on a mission to destroy the Scub Coral.
Eureka...
You're in the way.
It won't go as you want it.
That Mark I...
Is that the one from earlier on?
Eureka?
No...
Ao, come with me!
Naru, what are you doing?!
That's not yours!
I can fly IFOs as well.
You don't have to strain yourself!
I'll protect you.
Ao...
I wanted to fly together with you.
Not to be embraced by you.
Truth!
Why...
Why are you doing this, Naru?
futashikana*
s
*T/L Note: I'm so uncertain
boku
no sekai
ga ima*
v
*T/L Note: In the blink of an eye,
mabataku
ma ni
kawari-
hajimete
hirogaru*
A
*T/L Note: my whole world started changing and opening up.
ano hi mitsuketa yume no tsuzuki wa doko*
A
*T/L Note: That day, I found out where my dream continues
sugu ni
sagashite
miseru yo*
A
*T/L Note: I'll show you its sequel now
ima mo boku
dake wa
oboeteirun da*
N
*T/L Note: Right now, I'm the only one who still remembers
natsukashii
nukumori*
.
*T/L Note: that familiar warmth
saa
mou
ikou
ka*
A
*T/L Note: Now let's get going
machiu-
keteru
unmei ni*
)
*T/L Note: I was frozen with fear
tachisukumi
obieteta*
H
*T/L Note: thinking of the fate that awaited me
mou
kess-
hite
mayo-
wanai
you ni*
A
*T/L Note: I'll become so strong that I won't
tsuyoku
natte
yuku yo*
Z
*T/L Note: be uncertain ever again
nido to modorenai kako mo ashita kara kate ni shite*
A
*T/L Note: The past that can't be written will support me from tomorrow on
sou
yatte
noriko-
ete yuku
no sa*
q
*T/L Note: I'll overcome it all
sou shite boku
wa boku ni naru*
A
*T/L Note: and I'll become myself
sou shite boku
wa boku ni naru*
Don't repost to any manga readers!
You have to sign up for our forum to download!
Preview
Next time in Eureka Seven AO.
Ao suffers as the words his mother left behind toss him about.
But as the balance breaks, the world accelerates,
throwing the children into a fierce battle,
and forcing the adults to make cruel decisions.
Eureka Seven AO, episode fifteen: Warhead.
Listen to the voices of the children of the stars.