Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
namida wo nose
take away your tears
kareru made supiido agete
Speed up until they dry
tobikoete yukeru
I can overcome this
kitto kotae wa
The answer is
harukana ano sora no mukou
waiting beyond the distant sky
kotae ga mitsukaranai koko de wa
There's no answer here,
tameiki wo tsuite sora wo miru
so I sigh and look up at the sky
aoku somerareta hitomi no oku de kagayaiteru no wa
Shining deep within my eyes, reflecting its blue,
doko de mo yukeru, yume wo miteru
is a dreamer who can overcome anything
jibun na no sa
It's me, myself
Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
negai wo nosete
carry your dreams
nobashita te wa asu wo egaku
My hands willl draw tomorrow
mou kowaku nado nai
I'm not scared anymore
namida no ato
The memory of my tears
nijiiro ni somatte tondeyuku
are dyed by rainbows and fly
ano sora no mukou
far away beyond the sky
I told them it's too early for the Mark I to go to the Smithsonian.
Now, let's see...
Which one is stronger?
Walk This Way
The Mark I has appeared.
Mark I?
I've tried contacting it using the JAF, Allied Forces, and public circuits,
but I've gotten no responses.
It means the pilot's ignoring us.
What is he trying to do?
Nothing, I presume.
I think he just doesn't know how to use the radio.
Huh?
That is definitely a logical explanation.
Nirvash, this beeping is annoying the heck out of me.
Can you do something about it?
Easy mode?
Whatever.
What about weapons? Do you have any?
I can't understand any of this technical jargon.
I guess it's not as easy as it looks in a cartoon.
That was...
Call the captain!
The Japanese Armed Forces asserts ownership of that machine!
The Okinawan SDF's...
Conventional weaponry is useless!
The Secret can clearly see them if they use weapons like that.
Elena.
Got it.
I'm sending it over!
Elena—Musou gauge full.
Just kidding.
Impacts of all Goliath missiles have been confirmed.
Prepare for second rou—
You just squealed, didn't you?!
Was that on purpose?
Did you do that on purpose?
Fleur, withdraw for now.
I have to withdraw from the fight again?
No.
You're becoming a babysitter.
Children shouldn't die.
Huh?
I see how it is...
I think I get it.
All right.
A giant has to look like a human!
Oops, I forgot about that.
Mark I entered the Zone.
This isn't good.
Fleur!
Jeez... We have to get out of the Zone quickly!
Ow...
I knew it!
You're the one piloting this thing.
Fukai Ao.
Are Generation Bleu the only ones that are allowed to fight G-Monsters?
The Secrets can't detect IFOs that are outside the ZOA.
ZOA?
Zone Out of Action.
Within the Zone, Secrets can catch IFOs in the matter of seconds.
You wanted to fight without even knowing that?
Oh, crap!
Please move! The G-Monsters are...
It's okay.
We're outside the Zone.
As long as we don't initiate on them, we're safe.
Stay right here.
We need to talk afterwards.
And don't hide again!
Are you going to fight? Can you win?
I have no choice.
It's not like I can leave my friend behind.
Then I'm coming along as well.
Huh?!
If the G-Monsters destroy this island, it'll be a disaster.
The size of a Scub Burst is usually four times the size of the Coral and Secret put together—
I'll protect the island.
Then I'll...
Oh, right.
I can't do that.
I can't stay here anymore...
Fleur, I'm starting to get a bad feeling.
I'm coming. Wait for me.
Lure them all away.
While you do that, I'll get to the big one and take it down.
I told you, inside the Zone...
I've got at least a few dozen seconds, right?
What a surprise.
His strategy is plausible.
Who's speaking?
The Mark I's strength lies in the machine itself,
so the closer it gets, the more effective it is.
The problem is whether or not it can do anything significant with just one arm.
That's crazy!
We can't entrust our fates to a newbie piloting a damaged machine.
Fleur, listen to my orders.
Ivica!
I won't let children die.
If all else fails, we'll use the Triton to shield them.
Fleur, input the course and countdown for him.
Now you can use your radio.
We'll be able to hear what you say.
Okay...
I have to be the decoy and babysit him?
I want a pay raise!
Ao, I'm sending data over to you.
80 seconds...
I can do it...
right?
Elena, are you ready?
I can be replaced.
Stop quoting comic books!
I'm not quoting comic books... I'm quoting cartoo—
He can use Kyrie's cannon?
All IFO designs are derived from the Mark I's.
They couldn't do anything but mimic it.
Shoot, Nirvash!
They realized.
But it's too late!
Ao...
Don't tell me this explosion is...
Naru! Naru!
Naru...
Ao!
There is a possibility that the Scub Coral is emitting harmful particles.
Until we can confirm that it is safe,
civilians may not enter a 3km radius of the Coral.
Hear? There are harmful particles!
But Generation Bleu people weren't wearing any masks.
But...
Time for the Italian stallion to join the race!
Leo?
Papa!
I'm sorry!
Wait!
The Burst calmed down?
It looks just like the real plant.
We can't let them take Ao away!
A long time ago, a woman saved my life.
She had blue hair.
Fukai Ao is Eureka's son, right?
Our company runs a program to raise children like him.
He's in junior high already. Let him decide by himself.
Are you sure about that?
Do you know where Ao is? Please take me to him!
And you are...
Naru! I'm Arata Naru!
Ao is hopeless without me!
If you meet Ao, would you please tell him...
what I'm about to say?
Is Nirvash safe?
Don't worry.
Not even children can reach that beach now.
You rescued me from the sea and now you're doing this... Why?
Why not? I've always wanted to come here.
It's been just ten years since one could gather trapars here.
The development has been amazing.
Okinawa's FP ownership count is the highest in the world!
Get rid of the Allied Forces!
Let's get our independence!
Give us back the trapars!
Get rid of the Allied Forces!
We want Okinawan control over the Scub Coral!
Johanson is the answer if you're seeking the truth of the world!
What are the
Johanson
scriptures?
Let's go.
It's like that every day.
We're independent on paper, but the Allied Forces have their way.
On top of that, our tourism and fishing industry are both dead.
So that means things aren't going that well.
He's got no place to stay? What are you going to do about him?
He can sleep in my company's dorm.
I also wanted him to taste your cooking, Sis.
It's delicious.
What a beautiful dye-job. It's really cute!
You'd get popular with girls if you had a nice dye-job like his.
Your sister is a nice person.
A guy I met recently works for the intelligence agency.
Are you selling Ao out to the Allied Forces?
You saw it with your own eyes.
He piloted that IFO and now both the JAF and the Allied Forces want him!
If we hand him over, we'd get—
Sis, the food was good.
I had a chance to go to America, but now it's gone thanks to you!
Sending
Sent
No trapar trade!
Remove all Allied Forces bases!
Abolish trapar trade!
Why are you helping me?
When I was still a kid, a G-Monster attacked us.
Did you get hurt?
A giant saved me.
It looked similar...
It's like the one you're piloting now.
We're landing soon.
We're here at your workplace?
Yeah. This is the world's largest trapar mine.
Stupid!
I have a message for you from your grandfather.
That giant belongs to your mother.
Ten years ago, she piloted the giant to the Scub Burst and never returned.
If you pilot the giant, you'll end up like her.
Don't die, Ao.
Even we...
Even we don't know anything about what happened to your mother, Eureka.
But if I continue piloting the Nirvash...
Perhaps one day...
Perhaps one day, I'll find the path that she followed.
Ao...
Will you let me join Generation Bleu?
The targets are the plant coral...
as well as the boy and Mark I!
So you've always had wings.
Wings that will carry you away from the island.
I don't get it.
But if Mom's alive, I want to meet her.
I mean, if I neglected her, Grandpa would get mad at me.
Ao, I want to come with—
Naru, you should stay and take care of your granny and Miyu.
And don't fight too much with your dad.
I'll ask them if they know of a way to cure your illness.
Them?
Generation Bleu?
They're G-Monster specialists, after all.
They have to know something about your sickness.
Take him with you!
He seems to like them.
Naru...
I don't have anything else to give to you.
What's that?
They're...
Allied Forces IFOs?!
Why is the Allied Forces here?
For the same reason as us.
They probably hacked the taxi company and used the car cameras to track him.
So they came up with the same idea as us.
Where's the Mark I?
It's being prepared for launch.
He made it on time.
Thanks for hiding it.
I was saved by it.
There are others who also think the same.
Naru, stand back.
I'll be back.
Meet up with the Triton right away.
We're not going to fight?
It's the Allied Forces!
And IFOs have no problem detecting each other!
You won't even last for a minute.
What?
Generation Bleu, huh?
I'll file an official request for them.
Have you seen Noah?
He was here just then.
I'm cold...
Shut up. If you didn't run away from that Doberman, we wouldn't be here!
Found a blanket!
It stinks!
To be continued.
takanaru shinzou no koe wa
My heart is racing and beating loud
itsu shika kokochi yoku najinde ite
But that feels cozily familiar
kaze ga tsuyoku fuiteite mo
Even if the wind is blowing hard
me wo tsumuranaide itsu datte mae wo muku yo
Don't close your eyes and always look on ahead
nakitaku nattara omoidashite
If you feel like crying, remember
damatte chikaiatta yakusoku wo
the promise we made together
tabidatsu hinadori no uta
The young birds in the sky sing
ima mo mada umaku tobenai keredo
though they still can't fly well
meguri meguru toki wo koe
Even if we go beyond the edge of time
hitazura ni tsunaida te wo tadotte
I'll only follow you as we hold hands
kotoba wa
"So I never let you go!" My words
sora ni kieteku bakari da toshite mo
may get lost in the infinity of the sky,
chirabaru hikari no naka de
but among the glittering light
mayowazu ni kimi wo sagashidaseru kara
I can still find you without hesitation
Preview
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
Beyond the mist, the boy sees a black tower slicing the clouds.
The new world he faces grants him new encounters as well as doubts,
making him wonder the meaning of his life.
Eureka Seven AO, episode five: Tighten up.
Listen to the voices of the children of the stars.