World to World
hikaru suiheisen
Just over the bright horizon,
s
t
r
U
hajimari to owari no
where the beginning and the end
s
t
r
U
tokeau soko wa
melt into one,
s
t
r
U
namida no furusato na no
lies the homeland of tears
s
t
r
U
furueteru te de
I've already pocketed
s
t
r
U
shinjirareru mono
my trembling hand
s
t
r
U
poketto ni tsumekonda
which holds my beliefs
s
t
r
U
kanata de yurameiteru shinkirou
A mirage shimmers in the distance
s
t
r
U
sora miagereba
I look to the sky
s
t
r
U
michibiitekureru you na
hoping it will show me the way
s
t
r
U
natsukashikute atsui hikari wo kureru
And it gives off a familiar, warm light
s
t
r
U
anata wa chiisaku te wo furu yo
You wave at me faintly
s
t
r
U
ikanakucha
I must go
s
t
r
U
mou nakanai yo shangurira
Don't cry anymore because Shangri-La,
s
t
r
U
aratana sekai he to daibu shiyou
a new world, is waiting for us
s
t
r
U
aoiro ni dakareta boku wa
As I'm embraced by its blue...
s
t
r
U
kono mune no takanari to tomo ni
My heart beats loudly
s
t
r
U
It's coming from beneath?
Don't tell me it's Blanc...
Hey, Sergei!
Hey, Elena! Neither Kyrie nor Alleluia can fly just ye—
What are those?
Prototypes.
Requiem, Gloria, and Credo.
Credo...
Better Days Ahead
Papa! Papa! Answer me, Papa!
Fleur...
It's trapar...
There must have been a confluence explosion.
Georg?
No, the Secret?
What do you mean there must have been a confluence explosion?!
Cristophe Blanc hit Truth with all the remaining Quartz.
Truth was a Secret, after all.
And Papa? What happened to him?!
To completely destroy the invaders from another dimension known as Quartz,
Secrets erase the surrounding space itself.
Don't screw with me!
Didn't they say that Georg has gone all weird because of a Secret?
It must be his fault!
But your dad said
that the Secrets may not be our enemies.
Nothing is absolute.
Let's hurry. We don't know when the power will go out.
Commander, we're still not going in?
I'd prefer a peaceful resolution.
Let's just wait for them to surrender.
Isn't that what the silence is implying?
We can't locate Blanc's ID signal. But—
He was our stupid president until the very end. That's all.
With the condition that we're in, looking for him would be—
The Allied Forces' attack will be over in a flash.
They only want the Quartz Gun.
We just need to hand it over.
The Quartz Gun is undamaged.
It's still sealed in the deepest level.
What do we do? Are we going to hand the cannon over?
Any further discussion is—
I don't want that.
I went over to their side once, so my words might not hold any weight...
But the President told us this!
He was sure that we could find what the right thing to do is!
In the situation we're in, what would be
more of a right choice than staying alive?
I still haven't found out what the right thing to do is.
But I believe if we surrender now, we'll never have a chance to find out!
That's how terrorists think!
Says the person who erased Georg on some retarded orders!
I had to do that to protect everyone.
Fighting has never been one of our choices, Fukai Ao.
You know what this is, right?
What?! But I completely erased him from the main system!
The pilots' terminals have high-security restrictions on them.
If we copied you into our system, the Triton could fly, right?
Ivica?!
You can reach the lowest level through the central shaft.
I'm going.
I can't leave the cannon there.
Ao...
Don't worry.
Even without Georg, Nirvash can—
Fire the cannon, Ao.
I can't do that.
As soon as Georg is reinstalled on the Triton,
connect it to the catapult system.
Preparing for takeoff and arming the IFOs are top priorities!
Focus!
Alex, we need volunteer mechanics.
If you ask for volunteers, you'd have to put everyone on board.
Mr. Alex, why won't it open?
The area beyond the 20th gate is sealed.
We can't open it remotely.
Okay, I'm gonna break it open then!
They still won't surrender?
Maggie, look!
They finally surrendered?
No, it seems that they're releasing civilians based on their residential areas.
I hate this so much...
Now it's like we're the bad guys.
Are you returning to the Big Blue World?
I was originally sent here by people from above.
So that the company could control Generation Bleu.
Big Blue World is the largest PR company in the world.
If they say the Secrets are evil, the world will believe them.
That's how they marketed trapar as something mankind needs—
Rebecca, I...
You know full well the burden I have to carry!
I can't throw it away so easily!
This is the phone we can use.
We can restore the Triton's systems using Ao's phone.
How long would that take for you?
Chief... I...
The children chose the battlefield. I want to at least protect them until the very end.
Could you lend me a hand?
It's our responsibility.
You... need me?
Give me seven minutes.
Not half bad.
What are you guys going to do?
The very least we can do is to watch over him.
Do we have a response from Cristophe Blanc?
No, sir.
Civilians and defectors have all been secured.
Even though there's a limit to how many people they can evacuate in such a short period of time...
Commence attack!
Technical director, do we have the cannon yet?!
Of course not!
He has to break through armored gates to get there!
What's the status of the defense systems?
They're booting up. But they won't be able to keep up with the Allied IFOs' speed.
He moves so well even though he's not a child?
You can't do that unless you see trapar!
Don't tell me he does?!
I can... I can see the trapar waves!
The catapult's power source is unstable!
Chief, give permission to launch!
We won't make it—
No! We must wait for Ao to return!
But—
This is the Nirvash.
The Triton should launch!
What do you mean?
Breaking out from the lowest level with Nirvash
won't take as long as launching Triton with the catapult!
Hurry!
Launch the Triton.
Ao, don't overdo it.
Roger.
Ao...
We can't confirm the Mark I's location?
Yes, we lost the signal from the tracker a few minutes ago.
Have they found out? Or...
There is an energy signal from under the Generation Bleu HQ!
What?!
It's growing exponentially and it's reaching for the surface!
This is...
President...
I've never seen the Third Engine's signal glow in that color!
Nirvash, what does this mean?
Is it the Quartz Gun?!
T-The Generation Bleu HQ is self-destructing!
Wait, is that what I think it is?
Quartz?!
Launch the Triton!
No matter how dreadful you are,
I won't be afraid of you anymore!
What... What happened?
Is that the power of the Quartz Gun?
What's this?
What's going on, Elena?!
Fukai Ao...
If you shoot us, the world will turn against you...
What did you mean by fixing the mistake?
Ao! Respond, Ao!
What's the right thing to do?!
A new enemy?
Calm down, Ao.
Is that you, Hannah Mama?
We escaped in the Great Protheus right before the explosion.
But we lost over 200 crew members.
I'm sorry.
Anyway, join us!
We'll have to—
Ivica.
We've already talked with the Big Blue World.
Team Harlequin is joining the Allied Forces.
Hannah Mama!
What are you saying?!
The Harlequin IFOs can operate outside the atmosphere!
With you on our side—
Blanc isn't here anymore.
What could we do by ourselves?
Don't you agree, Ivica?
I see.
So that's how it goes.
Team Harlequin will be our enemies?
Ao, we're pulling out.
Chief...
We're moving to a sub-orbital trajectory right away.
Come back.
Roger.
Now we've got a little time.
Rajkumar, what about that signal?
It's still present.
You sure know how to cause trouble...
Fleur?
Ao!
Elena's weird!
She won't come out of Kyrie!
Elena?
Elena, what's wrong?!
I'm opening it!
Elena!
Elena...
Elena Peoples, was it?
That's the name of the identity I picked up in this world.
I know.
You even helped us with intel gathering, didn't you?
What's wrong? You were late escaping?
Do you want me?
Yeah, we do.
You can have me then.
But why are you wearing a mask all of a sudden?
Is that her way of expressing betrayal?
Then should we put on a mask too?
Wait, there's another signal too!
What? What's this signal?
We don't know.
But something is emerging from the HQ ruins!
What? What's that?!
See? There's something hidden under every HQ.
No way! Is that the IFO Zero?!
Blanc was really hiding it!
The three of you retreat!
What is that, Mama?
Codename Canon.
Canon?
A machine very similar to an IFO found in the aftermath of a Soviet Scub Burst.
But no one could control it.
The vast area between Siberia and northern China was erased by it in a flash.
Wasn't that due to a series of Scub Bursts?
No.
But it won't activate without trapar,
so Blanc locked it away underground.
But who would...
My form...
My consciousness...
Who are you?
The Archetype? That's inside you?
Who cares?
Now you and I are one!
Faisal Arabia has offered us asylum.
There are still people on our side?
They aren't in good terms with America, so they just want weapons.
But we'll eventually have to land somewhere and refill our supplies.
We can't fly forever, huh?
We received official messages from China and Australia too.
They'll attack if we trespass their airspace.
That works even in space?
Yeah, it uses an internet line,
so since it's connected to the Triton—
Wait, what?
She had nowhere to run away to.
Greetings.
I am Yamaoka from the Japanese Ministry of Interior.
As per our contract with Cristophe Blanc,
we will provide you with food and other supplies,
and allow your use of Japanese Air Force bases.
The Japanese?!
What are you talking about?
You were doing all you could against us!
Don't misunderstand, please.
Cristophe Blanc negotiated with us.
The Secrets?!
But we're not used to the human way of doing things,
so we got the Japanese government to cover our end of the bargain.
What bargain?
The condition is that Nirvash and all IFO teams remaining
will focus their efforts on destroying the Scub Coral Quartz.
Secrets will cease to emerge when that's done,
which means there won't be any more Scub Bursts.
The Quartz aggregate you call the Quartz Gun is an extremely dangerous thing.
We know.
But if you don't accept our conditions,
we are going to use the Quartz Gun.
Very well.
We will proceed our negations with the Japanese government and return to you with a conclusion.
If I'm not alive when the contract takes effect,
my daughter, Fleur Blanc, will inherit it.
See, he's done it again!
I took everything away from her.
A normal life... Her loving mother...
All I can leave with her is this...
The future.
In order for humankind to never be
exposed to the threat of Scub Bursts,
we will destroy all the Quartz and ally ourselves with the Secrets.
To achieve that, we will sponsor Team Pied Piper!
To be continued.
futashikana*
s
*T/L Note: I'm so uncertain
boku
no sekai
ga ima*
v
*T/L Note: In the blink of an eye,
mabataku
ma ni
kawari-
hajimete
hirogaru*
A
*T/L Note: my whole world started changing and opening up.
ano hi mitsuketa yume no tsuzuki wa doko*
A
*T/L Note: That day, I found out where my dream continues
sugu ni
sagashite
miseru yo*
A
*T/L Note: I'll show you its sequel now
ima mo boku
dake wa
oboeteirun da*
N
*T/L Note: Right now, I'm the only one who still remembers
natsukashii
nukumori*
.
*T/L Note: that familiar warmth
saa
mou
ikou
ka*
A
*T/L Note: Now let's get going
machiu-
keteru
unmei ni*
)
*T/L Note: I was frozen with fear
tachisukumi
obieteta*
H
*T/L Note: thinking of the fate that awaited me
mou
kess-
hite
mayo-
wanai
you ni*
A
*T/L Note: I'll become so strong that I won't
tsuyoku
natte
yuku yo*
Z
*T/L Note: be uncertain ever again
nido to modorenai kako mo ashita kara kate ni shite*
A
*T/L Note: The past that can't be written will support me from tomorrow on
sou
yatte
noriko-
ete yuku
no sa*
q
*T/L Note: I'll overcome it all
sou shite boku
wa boku ni naru*
A
*T/L Note: and I'll become myself
sou shite boku
wa boku ni naru*
Don't repost to any manga readers!
You have to sign up for our forum to download!
Preview
World
To World