hikaru suiheisen
Just over the bright horizon,
s
t
r
U
hajimari to owari no
where the beginning and the end
s
t
r
U
tokeau soko wa
melt into one,
s
t
r
U
namida no furusato na no
lies the homeland of tears
s
t
r
U
furueteru te de
I've already pocketed
s
t
r
U
shinjirareru mono
my trembling hand
s
t
r
U
poketto ni tsumekonda
which holds my beliefs
s
t
r
U
kanata de yurameiteru shinkirou
A mirage shimmers in the distance
s
t
r
U
sora miagereba
I look to the sky
s
t
r
U
michibiitekureru you na
hoping it will show me the way
s
t
r
U
natsukashikute atsui hikari wo kureru
And it gives off a familiar, warm light
s
t
r
U
anata wa chiisaku te wo furu yo
You wave at me faintly
s
t
r
U
ikanakucha
I must go
s
t
r
U
mou nakanai yo shangurira
Don't cry anymore because Shangri-La,
s
t
r
U
aratana sekai he to daibu shiyou
a new world, is waiting for us
s
t
r
U
aoiro ni dakareta boku wa
As I'm embraced by its blue...
s
t
r
U
kono mune no takanari to tomo ni
My heart beats loudly
s
t
r
U
Episode Twenty Three
The Final Frontier
We need to make it to the harbor!
A world supported by trapar is so fragile...
What are you doing?!
How does it feel?
What are you guys doing here?
I'm asking you how does it feel?!
Let me make it clear.
I hated the adults for being so obsessed with the trapar business,
but I had never wished for something like this.
What's independence? To become Japanese?
Or is it to ally with the Secrets?
Or is it to protect the Scub Coral?
The independence you wanted is just as insane as what Truth wanted!
It's never going to happen!
Gazelle... You're talking about yourself, man.
Shut up! It's the same thing.
Listen!
In the business world, even if a common enemy appears,
it's naive to change the implemented strategy immediately.
If we tell the people that Truth is the kin of the Secrets, they would—
You're calling us naive?
Sorry, but we soldiers are the biggest romantics in the world.
Nobody desires world peace more than we do.
Just because there were minor problems with the Coral Carrier experiments,
you're going to act in panic and surrender to the Secrets?
And that's strange, Stanley Fry?
What are you so surprised about?
You didn't expect negotiations with the US to go this easily?
Secret... I thought you were destroyed!
My conscience has already fused with
Georg and exists in countless instances.
Dammit!
Ao!
Fleur...
What are you doing, Ao?! Hurry up already!
Elena?
Dammit... So I have to use this, after all?
What was that?
Elena, take care of Truth! I'll deal with this white one.
Who are you?
What are you to Ao?!
Elena?
Dammit!
Stop!
Naru, why? Why are you helping him?
Because you can't win against Truth.
You can't even hold your ground against my Nirvash.
And that's because you don't have your Archetype.
What's an Archetype?
The trapar's...
This Nirvash is alive.
Just like Coralians, there's an Archetype inside of it.
Yours is nothing more than a machine!
Naru!
The Scub Coral will spread and a new age will begin...
A new world where no one will have to suffer.
That will be our world, Ao!
The Scub or the Secrets... Are there no other options?!
Fleur, behind you!
What?
That's...
No way... Didn't the Harlequin join the Allied Forces?
Peace negotiations have begun between the JAF and the Allied Forces.
The Coral Carriers have been hospitalized because they were displaying severe symptoms of illness.
Some countries have even blockaded areas around their Plants.
Coral Carriers? What about Naru? What's going to happen to her?
She might be in danger too.
And you too.
Naru!
Ao?!
But even so, you're the only one that the world can rely on.
If Nirvash defeats Truth, the world will have to accept that our side is the right one.
Even falsified peace is better than war.
I understand how you feel.
You've been exiled by the Secrets...
Only I can really understand who you are.
You're infected by the Scub Coral, just like me.
You're a Secret,
but the Scub entered you and became half of your existence.
Do you remember the time we first met?
Our breathing became easier because of each other's trapar.
We've been fighting for the Scub Coral since then.
Truth, your power as a Secret should become our power.
1945, the Manhattan Project. Hiroshima. Nagasaki.
That's the correct history!
That's the world I saw...
Over there...
No! No! No!
You're wrong, Naru!
Ao?
It's okay, Ao! Truth is a friend of the Scub!
Get away from there, Naru!
Truth... But why?
It's wrong.
Mankind tames the power of atoms and advances forward.
The military powers of America and Russia struggle with each other.
There's no way Okinawa could ever become independent.
That's the correct version of the world!
There's no Scub Coral there. Or Secrets.
That means this power should be used to reach the correct world!
Naru?
Naru!
Naru...
Truth!
Come at me, Fukai Ao!
Trapar density is rising rapidly.
Rajkumar, take Naru and get away from there.
Is Ao going to be all right?
It had bad effects on Coral Carriers, didn't it?
If you have to face it either way, shouldn't you try to overcome it?
Answer her!
You're the omniscient Hannah Mama, aren't you?
That's...
Liu... Lerato...
Fire the cannon, Ao!
We don't mind! We've been...
...waiting for this.
I can't!
If I did that, both of you would be hit as well!
Truth destroyed the Poseidon!
He must pay for that.
He took away people who were dear to you as well.
But I can't shoot knowing that I'll hit the both of you...
I just can't fire it!
You're naive, Fukai Ao.
Liu! Lerato!
Are you afraid of learning the truth?
I can't let a coward like you wield that power!
We thought the Secrets were our enemies, but they weren't.
Then the Scub became the villain. Now Truth is the ultimate evil.
What is all this crap? Is it the truth?
Was I just looking for an enemy to fight against?
Because you're neither a Secret nor a part of the Scub, you can't stay in this world?
What the hell? Who's there to decide that?!
There's no clear line between that!
You're hoping that by erasing all the contradictions that exist,
everything will sort itself out, Truth?!
It won't solve anything... Not a single thing.
I told you you're naive. Don't make me repeat myself.
Truth?
Dammit!
I ended up learning about the correct world.
I can't pretend that it doesn't exist.
He wants to disappear from this world that forced him to come into existence.
The correct world? The one and only one truth?
What the hell is that?
How much are you going to sacrifice for it?!
Will I die here?
Or will I have to lose even more?
This is...
You did it, Ao!
I did it?
You shot it down with the Quartz Gun!
It?
I shot down Truth?
Truth? What are you talking about?
We've confirmed the destruction of the coral relic IFO that the Allied Forces stole.
Rate of operation at 23...
So this is the world after shooting the Quartz Gun?
It's our victory, Ao.
Mankind won't be divided anymore by Secrets and Scub!
Arata Naru's Nirvash is not operational as well.
Huh?
Are you... Naru?
Isn't it a bit too late for jokes?
I'm sorry... I shot Truth.
Truth? Is that your new girlfriend?
Finish me already!
You have one more shot, right?
What are you talking about?
The Quartz Gun releases the power of the Quartz directly.
It'll run out soon.
If you won't shoot, I will!
Huh? I won?
Huh? Wait!
Naru!
Naru! Where's Naru?!
She's in the base infirmary.
The military personnel who attacked the GenBlu HQ and stole the prototype IFO
and the eco-terrorists who tried to protect the Scub Coral will all face thorough investigation.
But you Americans made her do it!
But the world finally understands that the Scub Coral is dangerous.
However, there's a signal inside Naru's body that's identical to that of the Quartz...
Take a break, man!
How long is that gonna take?
With the first shot,
the plant in Norway was erased as if it had never existed,
and Team Goldilocks disappeared too.
With the second shot,
Truth was erased as if he had never existed.
The Allied Forces stole the relic and
teamed up with Naru to fight the Secrets.
History has been rewritten again.
The trapar industry will be reassessed.
What's going to happen to the Quartz?
It's inside Naru and other patients as well...
What's that?!
Please watch over Naru for me!
Did something happen?
Nothing! We don't have to fight again!
Cheer up! This is the world you wanted!
But Japan's still a small country.
Did something happen?
The Okinawan Plant Coral?
But the plan is to destroy its Quartz tomorrow.
Don't tell me it's a Secret!
No, it's him. He's here.
That's...
Mr. Soga, there shouldn't be any more Secrets, right?
That's what they promised.
But that's not a known unit from any country.
The Scub Coral is here in this time as well?
Ao! What happened, Ao?!
We're going too!
Eureka!
She's Eureka?
He's here.
The charge is at 48%?
The gun loaded the Quartz by itself again...
It's too close!
Who's that?
Why does he know the passcode?!
So you pilot the Nirvash Neo?
Where's its real pilot?
A woman called Eureka should be piloting it.
Huh? Your eyes are...
Ao, can you hear me? Ao!
Eureka showed up on the Triton!
Mom did?!
I see... So you're...
Understood. I'll get this sorted then—
Let's go, Ao.
Bring me to Eureka.
You vanished in Okinawa alongside the Quartz.
She's been wandering through time ever since.
Right?
I can't stay at the same time and place for long.
So I see children grow old in a flash.
Hey!
I'm sorry, he somehow opened the lock...
Eureka...
Eureka!
Wait.
I'm like this...
Eureka... You had no other choice?
I'm sorry.
I should be the one apologizing.
You finally met Ao.
He's such a good boy. He grew up well.
He's much more upfront than you are.
He has what you're looking for.
It's also what called you here.
Mom!
Are you who I think you are?
No way...
My name's Renton Thurston. I'm Eureka's husband.
To be continued.
futashikana*
s
*T/L Note: I'm so uncertain
boku
no sekai
ga ima*
v
*T/L Note: In the blink of an eye,
mabataku
ma ni
kawari-
hajimete
hirogaru*
A
*T/L Note: my whole world started changing and opening up.
ano hi mitsuketa yume no tsuzuki wa doko*
A
*T/L Note: That day, I found out where my dream continues
sugu ni
sagashite
miseru yo*
A
*T/L Note: I'll show you its sequel now
ima mo boku
dake wa
oboeteirun da*
N
*T/L Note: Right now, I'm the only one who still remembers
natsukashii
nukumori*
.
*T/L Note: that familiar warmth
saa
mou
ikou
ka*
A
*T/L Note: Now let's get going
machiu-
keteru
unmei ni*
)
*T/L Note: I was frozen with fear
tachisukumi
obieteta*
H
*T/L Note: thinking of the fate that awaited me
mou
kess-
hite
mayo-
wanai
you ni*
A
*T/L Note: I'll become so strong that I won't
tsuyoku
natte
yuku yo*
Z
*T/L Note: be uncertain ever again
nido to modorenai kako mo ashita kara kate ni shite*
A
*T/L Note: The past that can't be written will support me from tomorrow on
sou
yatte
noriko-
ete yuku
no sa*
q
*T/L Note: I'll overcome it all
sou shite boku
wa boku ni naru*
A
*T/L Note: and I'll become myself
sou shite boku
wa boku ni naru*
Don't repost to any manga readers!
You have to sign up for our forum to download!
Continuing right away!