Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
namida wo nose
take away your tears
kareru made supiido agete
Speed up until they dry
tobikoete yukeru
I can overcome this
kitto kotae wa
The answer is
harukana ano sora no mukou
waiting beyond the distant sky
kotae ga mitsukaranai koko de wa
There's no answer here,
tameiki wo tsuite sora wo miru
so I sigh and look up at the sky
aoku somerareta hitomi no oku de kagayaiteru no wa
Shining deep within my eyes, reflecting its blue,
doko de mo yukeru, yume wo miteru
is a dreamer who can overcome anything
jibun na no sa
It's me, myself
Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
negai wo nosete
carry your dreams
nobashita te wa asu wo egaku
My hands willl draw tomorrow
mou kowaku nado nai
I'm not scared anymore
namida no ato
The memory of my tears
nijiiro ni somatte tondeyuku
are dyed by rainbows and fly
ano sora no mukou
far away beyond the sky
This is good stuff.
I don't expect anything less from our dear president.
Take a look at this beautiful sight.
You should enjoy it with the best of the best.
You won't see it ever again.
You took quite a bite out of my country.
How did you like the taste of that?
What... What are you doing?
Don't tell me that's a...
A transmitter.
He's a government dog pretending to be our customer.
Shit!
The government forces will be here soon!
Hide it all! Hide everything!
We are the anti-drug squad of the Allied Forces.
Put down your weapons and surrender!
I repeat! Put down your weapons and surrender!
Shoot!
The government can't put its hands on what we have!
Fight!
Fight them! Fight!
What are you doing?!
Shoot! Shoot them down!
Shoot already!
Financial instrument consulting, huh?
It's your fault that our economy is on the verge of collapse!
My fault, is it?
The promise of money blinded you.
You sold so much of it even though you knew how dangerous that was.
Who are you?
A spy for another country?
A con artist? Or...
That's right. I would like to know who I am as well.
Those will be your last words!
Tango 20 to HQ.
The target was supposed to be an Asian man...
Is this some sort of a mistake?
Boss...
Why would you give such an order?
I was hiding!
No matter how much blood we spill...
No matter how much wealth we return to oblivion,
we cannot find the way to fix this world.
Why won't the world answer us?
Welcome to this mistaken world.
Light My Fire
We have returned to level flight.
IFO launch space secured.
Launching IFOs.
Roger.
Launching IFOs. Release the catapults!
Fukai Ao!
Yessir!
If you need help with anything, ask Georg.
Georg?
Hi! Nice to meet you, Fukai Ao.
Hello, Georg...
All right.
First of all, here's information on the current situation.
We are currently above the Caribbean Sea,
120 kilometers from Punta Gallinas of the Colombian Republic.
The Secret is moving at 22km/h.
Contact was lost with the three IFOs of team Goldilocks.
Goldi... it's them?
The mission is to destroy the Secret and rescue team Goldilocks.
You can do that, right?
We'll do it.
That's why Nirvash and I joined Generation Bleu.
Path clear.
Nirvash, you're free to take off.
This is Nirvash and Fukai Ao. Launching!
Team Pied Piper, could you hurry with dispatching your IFOs?
We are in a hurry already!
The situation has changed.
The Medon is ignoring our orders and flying straight toward the Secret.
What the hell is going on in their minds?!
Can you all hear me?
I can.
Me too!
I hear you.
You are entering the combat area very soon.
Pay attention to temporary ZOAs and provide cover for the Medon.
However, in the case of an emergency, leave the area immediately!
Aren't we supposed to rescue team Goldilocks?
The main body of the Secret hasn't been revealed yet.
Main body?
Chief Bruno is trying to stop its movements.
Stop its movements?
Wait a moment!
Medon's colliding with the Secret?
Thermal radiation detected.
The Medon exploded!
You're kidding me...
We didn't make it in time?
That is confirmed to be the Secret's main body.
Georg, confirm the situation.
Nothing has changed except for lowering trapar levels.
The reason for that is unclear, but it may cause difficulties for IFO flight.
All units, retreat!
Roger.
The air current is really bad.
Hurry!
Wait a moment!
What was that?
Eisenhower?
The Secret started moving...
Was that Eisenhower our ally?
The Secret changed course to north-northeast. Its speed is unchanged.
Trapar levels back to normal.
All units full speed ahead!
Team Pied Piper, continue searching for team Goldilocks.
Roger!
That's...
The Medon?
But you should go back home right now.
If you stay here, you would upset those who care about you.
Credon found. Requiem found as well.
Mr. Bruno...
Gloria found.
Roger. Hurry with recovering the remains of the IFOs.
Don't leave any parts behind.
Roger.
Isn't rescuing the pilots our top priority?
Yes. The longer the recovery takes the later they get to the hospital.
But—
That's...
Pilots transported to medical facilities.
We don't have any countermeasures.
To contain our losses, we should retreat.
If we lose the Triton as well...
But if that fusion explosion was the result of a mistake...
What?
I think it would cast a bad light on the company, Stanley.
So?
We'll do what we can.
Excuse me, where are the other two?
The older sister is in the ICU.
You can visit the younger sister.
Everyone!
You're awake...
Newbie...
Where's everyone else?
Are you okay?
They are fine.
Your sister and Maggie are fine.
The bear-like chief as well...
Really?
Just sleep. I'll stay here.
Finally!
Ao, where are you?
This is Chloe from team Goldilocks.
Chloe? Are you all right?
Yes, I'm...
Chloe, where is Ao?
No way... The Medon...
Chloe, I'm sorry.
I'm fine.
Anyway, should I wake him up?
You mean Ao?
Yes.
He was dispatched right after arriving from Okinawa.
He hasn't slept for days. We can't blame him.
But the operation must start soon!
It's okay.
He's not going to be of much use this time, so just let him sleep.
Just leave it to Alleluia and Kyrie! We got it!
Are you trying to kill me?!
You snore really loudly.
But I don't even snore!
Alleluia, arrived at operation area.
Starting area scan.
Kyrie, all cannons standby.
What? An operation?
They said you don't have to go this time.
You could at least sleep, right?
They really don't need me.
I don't know anything, and even Mr. Bruno and his crew...
I heard.
I'm sorry...
Don't say that!
Don't say that, newbie!
Bruno did his best to protect us!
Just like what Ivica and your team are doing now!
A newbie lacking sleep is just a sitting duck!
They're just protecting you.
And you still think they don't need you?!
Not to mention your piloting style wouldn't work on that Secret.
To attack it in that hurricane, we needed to enter the Zone and cling on to its main body.
After doing so, we decided to fire at it.
We thought that would work.
Sis!
I came up with the plan.
I wanted to show that you're not the only one who can enter the Zone.
But because of that, the Medon...
I'm going.
Are you listening at all? Even if you go—
I thought...
I thought Grandpa was the only adult who cared about me.
But I was wrong. So I'll do what I can.
And what can you do?
I haven't figured it all out yet, but your plan inspired me.
I'm sure you were right.
I'll go and prove that.
If I don't do that...
I'd upset people who are dear to me...
Just as Mr. Bruno said.
Ready to fire.
Firing main cannon!
Mark!
Shoot!
Fire!
Geez...
Long range attacks won't cut it.
We should really go into the Zone and cling on to it!
No! You'd end up the same as team Goldilocks!
Then what should we do?
The Secret is already within 10km of the Scub!
Shoot once more!
Ao?!
What are you doing?!
Fall back!
Its shield regenerates after being attacked, right?
But it takes time to do so!
Don't tell me...
Strategy analyzed.
It's worth trying.
Prepare heavy cannon for fire.
Let Georg calculate the timing.
Georg, you can do that, right?
No problem.
Fleur and Elena, provide cover for Nirvash.
Roger!
Georg, sync complete!
Understood, Fukai Ao.
Then we're counting on you.
The Nirvash crossed the storm zone and entered the vicinity of the Secret.
Landing on an Option soon.
Jump, Nirvash!
Ao.
You did well.
I see! I get it now!
I've been waiting for you!
If you defeat Secrets, then I...
I'm happy to hear that everything's okay now.
Yes. Maggie and my sister are both making a speedy recovery.
I sent you a little present. Keep it a secret from the doctor.
Has it arrived yet?
Well, then.
I'm waiting for all three of you to return.
Is that all you bought for moving in?
Yeah. It's not enough?
It'd be more efficient to get over with the shopping in one go.
But...
Someone's moving.
Who else would be moving—
That's Mr. Bruno's place.
Never let children die...
Upsetting people dear to us is a part of life...
takanaru shinzou no koe wa
My heart is racing and beating loud
itsu shika kokochi yoku najinde ite
But that feels cozily familiar
kaze ga tsuyoku fuiteite mo
Even if the wind is blowing hard
me wo tsumuranaide itsu datte mae wo muku yo
Don't close your eyes and always look on ahead
nakitaku nattara omoidashite
If you feel like crying, remember
damatte chikaiatta yakusoku wo
the promise we made together
tabidatsu hinadori no uta
The young birds in the sky sing
ima mo mada umaku tobenai keredo
though they still can't fly well
meguri meguru toki wo koe
Even if we go beyond the edge of time
hitazura ni tsunaida te wo tadotte
I'll only follow you as we hold hands
kotoba wa
"So I never let you go!" My words
sora ni kieteku bakari da toshite mo
may get lost in the infinity of the sky,
chirabaru hikari no naka de
but among the glittering light
mayowazu ni kimi wo sagashidaseru kara
I can still find you without hesitation
Hey, look!
A child is down there!
Who the hell are you...
Who's there?!
Who am I?
If I have to introduce myself...
From this moment onward...
My name is Truth.
To be continued!
Preview
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
Generation Bleu is pushed around by the attacks of an unseen foe.
People can change themselves as reality assaults them.
As the echoes of destruction die off, the boy faces the inescapable truth.
Eureka Seven AO, episode seven: No One Is Innocent.
Listen to the voices of the children of the stars.