Yo! Over here.
Sorry for calling you out on such short notice.
I didn't expect Menma's father would get in the way.
That's exactly why we're going there now.
We can corner Menma's mom while her dad is away.
Her mom will definitely side with us.
You're right.
She even gave us Menma's diary. I'm sure she'd do anything for Menma.
Menma.
If she knew I went to her house again without telling her anything...
I'm sure she'd be angry.
nanpeeji mo tsuiyashite
Upon pages and pages of entries
We still don't
know the name
of
the flower
we saw that day.
tuzurareta bokura no kibun
We've put down all our emotions
doushiteka ichigyou no
But now I've hit a writer's block
kuuhaku wo umerarenai
I don't know how to finish this page anymore
oshibana no shiori hasande
Putting a bookmark in my diary
kimi to korogasu tsukaisute no jitensha
You and I go out to ride the bike we found in the dumpster
wasurekake no renga wo
Let's go to our secret place
tsumiageta basho ni yukou
Where we piled up our bricks of memories
umi wo miwatasu saka wo kakenobotte
Run up the hill, where we can see the horizon
kowaikurai ni aoi sora to
Where we can see the sky so fearfully blue
migite ni saidaa hidarite wa
With cider in my right hand
zutto kimi wo sagashiteiru
My other hand helps me search for you
souyatte ima wa boku no hou e
You used to come find me way back when
toitsumeru koto mo nakute
You used to demand me of so much more
mada futari wa sugu soko ni irunoni
You're both still standing right by my side
douka mata aemasuyouni nante
Yet why do I pray to see you both again?
douka shiteru mitai
There must be something off with me
Welcome.
Wow, Atsumu and Chiriko came too this time. I'm so happy to see you.
Come right in.
Please excuse us.
I've got a good feeling about this.
Excuse me.
Yeah
So is this about the rocket firework?
Oh, yes. About that...
I was surprised when my husband first told me about it.
But I think it's great.
Your friends all gather together.
And you come up with fun ideas.
It's the same as when you were little.
Yeah, when we were kids we actually planned to make fireworks with Menma.
Oh really. Meiko was involved...
Umm...
If we could launch fireworks, I think that Menm... I mean, Meiko would also be happy.
So we'd like you to ask your husband...
You all sure do get along well.
I wouldn't say that.
Meiko must be so envious.
She was left out by her friends.
You may talk about what Meiko would enjoy, but really you're just having fun yourselves.
You're using Meiko.
Ma'am...
No, we're really...
Meiko's not here anymore.
And yet you all go on the same as always...
Actually...
Why?
Weren't you playing with Meiko on that day?
Tsurumi.
You read her diary didn't you?
Time has stopped.
She's the only one who hasn't changed since then.
But why have you all grown up?
Why is Meiko the only one... Meiko.
Only her...
I'm home.
What are you doing?
We should get going.
Yeah.
Is your hand okay, Tsurumi?
It's nothing serious.
Menma's mom was super scary.
Yeah. Maybe she's resented us all this time.
This might be the first time someone has hated me this strongly since I was born.
She's a parent after all.
Yeah. She's a parent.
Let's stop this.
Let's drop this foolishness about Menma's wish already.
Wait a second. If we do that we don't know what will happen to Menm...
Open your eyes already.
Everyone has been playing along with poor pitiful you.
Yukiatsu.
I took it too far myself, so I can't exactly judge others in that regard.
But unlike you, I don't force my own pain onto others.
My own pain...
Isn't that the right way to put it?
You're obsessed with the past, and even Menma's parents are like that...
Everyone is in pain.
He was talking about himself wasn't he?
The one who's in pain is Yukiatsu.
I believe you Jintan. I believe that Menma's around.
Jintan.
It's alright.
I'll grant it on my own.
Jintan.
But you said that all of us together have to...
You know...
I had thought that everyone had changed.
Huh?
But once I spoke to everyone, I was surprised that no one had changed all that much.
But no matter how little we change, we're not all together anymore.
We never were from the start.
Because Menma is missing.
Jintan.
Since all of us together don't exist anymore, it's all the same if I grant the wish on my own.
Wait Jintan! I'll keep helping like I have been, so we can...
Welcome home!
That was dangerous.
I was taking my shoes off.
I can grant it even if I'm alone.
Even if I'm alone.
What? You signed up for even more hours?
Yeah. Construction pays well.
You look pale.
That's because I haven't slept.
Hey...
All I did with my life until now was sleep and eat.
I've built up a big sleep surplus.
How?
How can he put so much energy into it?
Does he care about Menma that much?
Hey... Wh.. Jintan?
Have some water.
Thanks.
And take this multivitamin too.
Drink it up.
I feel better now.
Good.
Jintan.
Huh?
Let's end this already.
You must be in a lot of pain too.
Let's stop this.
What do you mean by 'this'?
Huh?
I still have work to do.
Don't go.
Huh?
Don't.
I didn't want you to go back then either.
Back then?
I'm going to tell you something terrible about myself now.
Huh?
Back then, I was actually relieved.
You said that you didn't like Menma.
It's horrible of me, but I was actually kind of happy.
But...
When you left like that...
It was the same as you saying you loved her.
That moment has pained me ever since.
I couldn't forgive myself for being happy then.
Or for hurting Menma, and for how it all ended.
And I... I couldn't forgive myself for liking you.
But it turns out that I... I really...
You're still going?
You're being strange!
Say that Menma really is at your house, if you grant her wish, won't she disappear?
Are you fine with her disappearing, even though you like her?
Welcome!
Jintan you're an...
Idiot!
I'm such an idiot.
I'm home.
Was she waiting for me?
Your nails are pitch black!
I'll clean them off with toothpicks!
You really don't have to.
I'll clean them!
I know. Once I grant her wish, Menma will...
Ouch.
Sorry about that, bear it for just a bit more.
But if that's what Menma wants...
If that's the way it is, I'll...
Jintan?
What's wrong? Did it hurt that much?
No I... I remembered The Dog of Flanders.
Huh?
I was thinking about Patrasche.
Patrasche?
They were showing a rebroadcast of The Dog of Flanders a while back...
What am I saying? This is such a crappy lie.
But...
Jintan.
Jintan!        I'm sure that Patrasche was happy!
Yeah.
Because Nello was really, really nice to him.
They were friends. So it's fine right?
Yeah. Yeah.
Menma.
Episode 8
Menma's mother continues to hate us because she lost Menma.
Anaru continues blame herself.
And Yukiatsu too.
And probably Tsuruko as well.
And even Poppo.
No one is being saved from their sense of guilt.
I can see Menma.
I'm the only being saved by Menma.
That's so...
That's so unfair.
Good morning.
It's this late?
I have to get to work...
I mean, school...
Oh, you're going to school?
Today is your mother's...
Yeah. I'll go.
Wait for me.
I'll be downstairs.
If I'm the only one who can see Menma,
then I have a duty to fulfill her wish.
It's rusted over.
There we go.
Good morning.
Let's go.
Dad.
He didn't say a thing about me not going to school.
I thought that maybe he'd gotten fed up with me.
But..
But a parent...
Hey.
I'm sorry.
About what?
Oh, if it's about your job then don't worry.
You knew about that?
Oh, no way, what is it then?
Oh, about going to the Honmas? Which one is it? Neither of those?
You know about everything.
I don't know anything.
After all, I couldn't tell what you were apologizing about.
So what is it?
It's nothing.
Bring that incense over here.
Sure.
You can't underestimate a parent.
I can't believe Jintan left without even saying good morning.
That's Poppo's!
Good afternoon!
No matter how Menma's mom reacted, we can't leave Jintan to do everything on his own.
And here I'd thought the Super Peace Busters had finally gotten back together.
Hey Poppo.
Did you have a fight? About what?
So I believe in Menma.
Even if Jintan is the only one who can see her, and even if no one else believes in her, I'll...
What's up?
What? You're getting silent phone calls?
Yeah.
Hey, Yadomi is at work right?
I don't know. You don't think he is?
The caller ID showed Yadomi's home phone number.
Yadomi is making prank calls?
There was a kind of scraping, sandy noise.
This might sound silly, but what if it wasn't Yadomi...
Huh?
Yukiatsu?
I wish Anjou wouldn't take days off without saying anything.
Yeah.
Did she say anything to you?
No, sorry.
Really? Dang.
I had plans for muscle party with everyone from the gym today.
I wonder how I should act towards Anaru.
When I see her next time.
Umm...
Welcome!
I'm sorry about what happened.
No, I'm the one who should be sorry for intruding on your home...
My parents are abnormal.
My mom usually doesn't leave the house.
I think she doesn't want to see other people.
I think it's hard for her because my sister passed away.
But it's creepy.
Or how could I put it... it's embarrassing to have a mother like that.
What in the world are parents thinking.
Huh?
But I think it's hardest for them.
Because parents are, you know...
Anyway, you don't have to tell me all this.
They still have another child left.
I was still a little kid, so I don't really remember my sister.
But there are a few things I do remember.
I'm going!
Me too!
Huh?
I'm going too!
You can't come.
I'm going!
But you know, I'm in the Super Peace Busters!
I'm going to protect world peace! So you stay here and protect the house.
Got it?
Yeah!
She told me to protect the house.
But who'd want something from that stingy dump.
Hey listen.
A-Anjou.
Oh, Jintan showed up too.
Yadomi.
Why is everyone...
What have you been doing today?
What? I've been at work.
Have you been calling us?
Calling?
I got a silent phone call around 5 o'clock.
Silent?
What about it? Are you going to say it was Menma again?
Menma?
My dad and I were both out of the house then, so maybe Menma really did...
What's wrong with you? You keep blabbering "Menma, Menma".
Well?
Hey... Yo!
Yukiatsu.
Why don't you show her to me too. Menma is there right?
Show her to me if she is!
Stop it Yukiatsu.
Are you alright?
Calm down.
She's right. Chill out.
Menma.
Not that again....
Stop doing that.
You're the worst. You're keeping this act about seeing Menma's ghost even now.
That's not it.
I'm sorry, everyone.
Why are you apologizing?
Yadomi!
Is Menma there Jintan?
You stop it too Poppo!
Calm down Yukiatsu!
Jintan, time out.
Menm...
I'm begging you. I'm begging.
Please, stop it already.
The things we did to Menma won't fade for the rest of our lives.
Menma apologizing to us is a lie.
There's no way that Menma could forgive us.
Yukiatsu.
The diary?
Why? There's no wind.
Stop it guys.
Really, why did it...
What's wrong Popo?
Today I played at the secret fort with everyone who had grown up.
You shouldn't fight.
The Super Peace Busters should always get along.
Let me see that.
This is Menma's handwriting.
It's Menma's?
That's right.
Menma... Why did you...
Hey Jintan.
Is it really Menma?
Yeah.
futari no himitsu no kichi no naka
...together in our secret base.
kimi to natsu no owari shourai no yume ookina kibou wasurenai
I will never forget the hopes and dreams
we shared during that one summer's end.
jyuunen no ato hachigatsu mata deaeru no wo shinjite
I'm sure we will meet again in another
August, in maybe ten years time.
kimi ga saigo made kokoro kara "arigatou" sakendeita koto shitetayo
I could feel your heartfelt thanks all the way until the end.
namida wo koraete egao
And I know it must've been painful
de sayounara setsunai yo ne
to hold back your tears and say goodbye with a smile.
saikou no omoide wo
But those are my best memories.