We have reports of crustal movement and abnormal weather all over the world!
The breaking of the seal on the Legendary Aquarion is affecting the whole planet.
And we can't contact the Elements, either!
Our only option is sending the machines we have left to Altair!
But how? The Dimension Gate is closed!
I'll open a hole through the dimensions.
I know last time was an accident, and Shrade was there to help...
But... it worked!
Can you do it, Andy?
If I don't, all the holes I've ever dug were pointless!
Let me go, Chairman!
Andy W. Hol...
We will take a risk using your power.
You dare oppose me, Wings of the Sun?
Our goal is to secure the true Eve.
Avoid the core units! Disable their weapons!
You really think that'll work, Izumo?
This is the power of the Wings of the Sun?
But...
This is enough power to wipe out a Gnis platoon all at once.
I'll send it back at you amplified!
He's firing it back!
Then I'll just reverse it!
His power of reversal is canceling out my counter!
Izumo! You can't have my wench! Not even over my dead body!
What's the matter with you, Kagura?
Why do you care about that Rare Igura so much?
She's my smelly wench! Only mine!
So childish!
Sir Izumo, I'll fight with you!
That Abductor...
No way! Mix?!
Sir Izumo is Altair's future!
Please, be safe...
Been a while since it was just us guys in a Union!
We're about to reach the target!
Let's get this done! With a manly Brutal Union!
That's not how we Union!
We're doing a hot-blooded Warrior's Union!
Go!
Aquarion!
Aquarion Gepard!
Mix!
It doesn't matter what your body's turned into!
I'll always come for you!
Remember what I used to say, Mix?
Holes are dug to bring the world together.
This hole's to bring us to that world you're on!
And I'll open another great big hole into your heart!
Big enough to bury myself in!
The artificial Dimension Gate has formed!
Go get 'em, boys!
Wait for me, Mix!
I heard someone calling my name!
No! My name is Mixy!
Outta my way!
Stop!
Mix is the pilot of that robot!
She's my friend!
Your friend?
Here he comes.
Damn you, Izumo.
Amata!
Amata...
Who's there?
Amata!
Where is this?
Amata...
Cut it out!
Reverse!
Sir Izumo!
Go reverse out of my sight!
I'll crush you!
Stop!
That robot!
You!
Aquarion Gepard!
Looks like we butted right into a fight.
Two Abductors and the Legendary Aquarion...
Who are the pilots?
Cayenne! Is that you, Cayenne?
Mikono! What are you doing with him?
Mix!
That's Mix's machine!
What the hell's going on?
Those two Abductors are trying to get Mikono!
Where are Amata and Shrade?
We lost Amata.
Shrade... is dead.
He played out his final song in the dimensional rift.
So that's what it was...
Shrade...
You dare oppose Sir Izumo as well?
Wrong, Mix! I'm only here to take you back!
Take me back where?
Don't you remember, Andy?
It's me! Andy W. Hol!
Stop! I can't stand it!
Mix!
Can't you see, Kagura? Don't you care about Altair?
Not a bit!
This planet can go to hell. I just want my smelly wench!
I'll fight the whole world before I give her up!
Mix! Mix!
All for a single Igura, a single woman...
Alicia...
This is where that voice is calling me from.
Amata...
Mom!
Amata.
The planet. The land. The life sleeping within.
All are about to awaken.
The rebirth of the Wings of the Sun was a double-edged sword.
Will it divide the world, or reunite it?
Come back to me, Mix!
Spatial Augmentation!
Not again!
How long are you going to keep this up?
I'll do this for as long as it takes!
I'll make the holes, and Mix'll fill them!
That's how we came to know each other!
Why does he keep doing the same pointless move?
And why does it feel so familiar?
Amata, I've been waiting so long to see you again.
You've grown.
It's too late for that now! After you left me behind!
Do you know how I've felt all these years?
And after all this time, you call me...
Amata...
I can't ask you to forgive me.
But I have to tell you...
Why I had to leave you.
And about your father.
Your father isn't an Earthling.
He's Izumo Kamurogi, the commander of Altair.
Him?
I cannot afford to lose.
I must put an end to the curse of Eve! The Rare Igura's tragedy!
Your father came to Earth on a mission to find a
woman who could withstand interdimensional travel.
He arrived back when I was an actress.
My machine malfunctioned and I
crashed on Vega. She saved my life.
It didn't take me long to realize
Alicia was the Rare Igura we wanted.
But...
It took even less time for us to fall in love.
I'm in no position to judge Kagura.
I almost betrayed Altair once myself, for a single woman.
I kept her a secret from command, and we returned to Altair.
But I couldn't keep it from Mikage.
He came back some years later. By then, I had you.
But when he told me about the curse of Eve...
I'll come.
Are you sure? We don't know what will happen to a Rare Igura there.
If it'll help you, I'm sure.
Alicia...
It was hard to decide whether I should take you or not.
In the end, I was more worried that you would be in danger on a strange, unknown world.
I never thought we would be apart for so long.
No, that's just an excuse. I abandoned you.
I wanted to help save my love's world.
It was all for the man I loved, the things I loved.
I've resented you all this time.
But not anymore.
I just hate myself from back then, when all I could do was watch you leave.
You were brave enough to go after your love. I wasn't.
That's all there is to it, Mom.
Amata...
Just give it up already, Izumo!
I cannot lose! I will not let Alicia's sacrifice go to waste!
The Legendary Aquarion is fighting!
That's Izumo and the other you.
Kagura?
Ianthe, created by my mother Oriza!
What?
Red strings?
He's focusing all of Altair's power into the Ahura Gnis!
Altair Cannon.
Fire.
What the?
That was the power of the planet Altair itself.
Damn you, Izumo.
That was a warning shot.
Give me the true Eve...
or I'll shoot for real.
Zessica?
What?
That's...
Mom!
No...
KAGURA!
Alicia!
What the...
Now.
Feel the power of the Genesis Infinity Punch!
Farewell, Izumo.
That power...
So this was all your doing, Mikage!
What?
Silvie!
Alicia...
Hang on!
I talked to Mom.
She told me about you.
I see.
Take me to Alicia.
I can't ask you for forgiveness.
I took your mother from you.
What're those?
Mayflies.
I've only seen them once, when I was a boy.
I thought they went extinct a long time ago when the females died off.
Why are they back now?
We're in Area 337.
This is where Ianthe has had the most malfunctions.
Was Ianthe...
Mother Earth. The goddess of the fertile land.
The land that brings forth the blessing of the harvest is symbolized by a feminine figure.
Male and female. Positive and negative.
All of creation is ordered along these dualities.
From people to lands. From worlds to the universe itself.
Ianthe functioned by drawing energy from the earth.
Perhaps it took away the mothering power of the land as well.
If so...
All of this was because of Ianthe.
And all I have ever done...
was for naught.
Hold on! Not when we just met!
Dad! Dad!
It wasn't for naught.
Mom!
Alicia!
Your life meant something.
There's still Amata.
He is the hope for the two worlds.
Amata...
You are the symbol of our love.
Amata, you need to love too.
Love the one person more precious to you than anyone else.
Mom!
My destined smelly wench.
I know your real name.
I love you.
I love you, Silvie!
Next Time
Pieces of Adam
I want to take all of you and hold you.