Come in.
How do you feel?
I finally found the melody of Aquarion.
The perfect melody I've been searching for.
Just a little more...
Don't push yourself.
Shrade, you know your body—
I don't care.
I have to play that melody with my own hands.
Let the fiery depths of Hell take my body.
This is a special permission waiver.
But this quest of yours can only end with death.
Keep that in mind.
We can only hear the melody of life because death comes with it.
osore
Even if you're scared
living your life   don't give up now   keep moving on
Just live your life, don't give up now, keep moving on
kimi wo dakishimeru nandomo nandomo nandomo
And I'll come for you over and over and over again
ashita boku wa kimi ni deau darou
We'll find each other soon enough
wazukana hoshiakari wo tayori ni
By the faintest glimmer of starlight
boku ni wa kimi ga wakaru yo wakaru yo
I know you, I know you
sen'oku no toki wo koe futari hiraku densetsu no tobira
It's been billions of years, but now we can open the door to our legend
naraku no ao tobikoete
I crossed over the deep blue void
kimi to hai ni naru tame
so I could burn to ash along with you
nagaki rinne wo kanashimi tsurete tabi shitekitanda
I've had a long journey on the vast wheel of fate, gathering sorrows along the way
zenryoku de mikansei kimi no tonari de
I'm not perfect, but I'm giving all I have
kawaita kokoro hodoke chi wo nagasu kedo
If I open my fragile heart to you, I know I'll bleed...
soba ni iru yo zutto yorisotte zutto
But I'll always be with you, always be in your arms
futari hikari no fune ni noru
We'll get on a shining ship of light
kaze no hajimari no oto kanadeyou
And call forth the wind with our voices
The Midnight Girl
Are you satisfied, my classmates?
It has been one full week since the Berlin fell,
yet we men and women are still separated by unseen walls!
We must tear down the walls between us and share ourselves with one another!
What's going on?
Dunno, he just got up there and started making some dumb speech.
Andy, I think that's enough—
Fool!
My classmates, I motion for an emergency seating change!
All this just to switch seats?
Objection!
Changing seats is out of the question!
If men and women mix any further,
the taint will be impossible to cleanse!
Changing seats?
I like it.
I second the motion!
This'll be fun! I call next to Cayenne!
Why, you...
I think it's going well.
You're all impure! Unclean! Tainted!
So how do we pick seats?
I guess we can draw for it.
I'll draw for Cayenne and Shrade, since they're out!
It's all sunshine and holes... I mean roses for me from here!
My name's Malloy. Nice to meet you.
You were in the mock battle!
My name's Ei Chan. It's a pleasure.
Really?
I know, right?
Why me?
Of all the people to sit next to...
Those big bangs...
Huh?
Hi, Amata!
H-Hi.
Hey!
Looks like it's going to get hot around here.
And I don't mean out in combat.
Let me down!
Amata!
Reserved
Cayenne and Shrade are sitting next to each other!
This must be God's gift to me!
Ooh, I just can't stand it!
This is the first time we've sat by each other, isn't it?
It'll be the last if I can help it.
Thanks for coming for me, my friend.
I didn't come to get you.
I was investigating the Abductors, and while I was here—
Eyes on the road.
What's the matter? Your sound is clumsy and depressed.
Shut it!
I was making a joke, my friend.
Damn it, why does everyone look so happy?
And who just left this cat doll here, anyway?
A doll, huh? I got it!
Gaaaah! There it is!
The doll of dread, right here with us!
What?
What's going on?
What about the doll?
Have you heard the story?
It's about an Element who disappeared in Neo-Deava.
What are you talking about?
It happened a few years ago...
A girl transferred into the Academy.
But she was timid and shy, and couldn't make any friends.
Finally, she couldn't stand to be alone,
and one day, she vanished from the Academy.
You mean, she...
She must have been so sad...
The girl had just one friend, her doll.
The doll appears at night, wandering around campus.
Sometimes you can hear its sad, lonely voice,
singing of the girl's tragedy...
That's stupid.
I've actually heard that story.
Ever since the Berlin fell, that doll has
even been spotted in the boys' dorms.
Malloy believes it too!
It must be true!
No!
I'm scared!
Gaaaah!
The doll just moved!
Andy!
Will you cut the crap already?
I mean it! It actually moved!
Mission complete.
Well done, Jin.
Thanks.
But you know the simulation is to prepare you for real combat.
How's Kagura?
This time, he's not getting out for a while.
An invisible door, a door to the future.
Fly to the end of the world.
I'm gonna check what's on the other side of the door again.
Go ahead.
Last son of Altair...
Finally done.
Hey, uh... Zessica?
Evening! Cleaning duty?
Just heading back.
Really? What a coincidence! I'm going back to my dorm too!
Huh.
Let's walk together!
Don't be shy! I'm accompanying you!
Huh.
Oh no! It's locked?
Guess we have to sneak in.
We're going in opposite ways now, so...
H-Hey, wait!
Why don't you come in from the girls' side?
Um, okay, but why?
Zessica...
I can't walk if you're doing that.
I'm sorry!
Hey, are you scared?
Don't be stupid!
There's no way!
I'm not scared of moving dolls or singing ghosts!
They're not even real!
What was that?
It's that doll!
What is it doing there?
No way!
It's just some stupid story!
This is someone's idea of a joke!
You stink deliciously.
I was scared... but that wasn't all.
I still can't stop thinking about him.
Why do you think that is?
Stop grabbing me there!
Don't leave me!
No... not Zessica and Amata...
Get back here, Jin!
Keep your hands off my smelly wench!
Now let's see...
if you can lead us to our true Eve.
I saw it, really!
What, the cat doll?
Yeah! In the hall, in the middle of the night!
Amata, you saw it too, right?
Yeah. Definitely.
Dude, it was a joke.
Are you taking it seriously?
It was your story in the first place!
It was even walking!
And we heard it singing!
Sure you did.
You're at the age where you start seeing things.
You're the same age as us!
I have a more important question.
What were you two doing together so late at night?
Oh, that? Zessica was—
What?
Don't tell them I was scared! You're embarrassing me!
What are you two whispering to each other about?
Well, I, we, it—
Why can't you tell us?
You're filthy!
Don't tell me you sullied our holy Academy's grounds by—
No, we didn't!
I saw it!
You saw the walking doll?
No, but I saw Zessica and Amata running
across the courtyard in each other's arms!
And Zessica was screaming at Amata, "Don't leave me!"
So they were having a lovers' spat?
I knew it!
You've got it all wrong! Come on, Mikono!
Abductors detected in the Neo-Kowloon area!
All Elements report to phase one battle stations immediately!
Repeat, all Elements report to phase one battle stations immediately!
Analysis complete. Pattern B.
Proceeding just like in the simulation.
The Abductor has taken down all of the wall structures!
It's moving at 60 kph!
Strange. It's not trying to capture anyone.
We can't let it do any more damage.
Zessica, you're the head!
Roger!
You're with Cayenne and Amata. Get going!
Mikono's really mad at me.
We don't know the range or accuracy of the enemy's laser fire.
Be careful out there.
Roger!
We're being ambushed!
But from where?
Its aiming error is 0.0003%.
Impossible! He can aim a laser through atmosphere that precisely?
Radius Gnis.
Fudo?
He can spot a coin from a thousand villages away,
fire an unerring arrow,
strike true, and pierce straight through!
How do you know that?
I can see.
Union now! A Vector wouldn't survive one hit from that!
Fly low and close in!
Emergency Union! Go, Aquarion!
Aquarion Gepard!
That area has already been cleared.
You're allowed to use the buildings for cover.
Roger!
It's still out of range of our attacks.
But there's only one!
We'll stay in cover and close the distance!
I can read your movements like a book.
I'll just overwhelm you and pin you down.
The enemy is releasing small flying objects!
Missiles?
What are those?
No way!
Damn it! Now we're screwed!
Those floating objects are reflecting the lasers!
The enemy's lasers can attack from all directions!
This is bad.
They can no longer use their surroundings as cover.
It's like we're up against a whole army!
Zessica! Behind you!
Amata!
Vector Z is taking the brunt of the laser fire!
Amata Sora's spirit level is falling!
Amata!
It's hit the limit! The Union is breaking!
This is my fault!
I'm not good enough at controlling Aquarion!
Zessica's spirit level is falling!
It's below 40, now 30%!
But Amata's the one taking damage!
Zessica...
Peoples' hearts cannot be seen with the naked eye.
And so they misunderstand one another and drive each other apart.
However, Mikono Suzushiro, there is a purpose for things unseen.
Now we shall find strength in those hearts that we cannot see!
Element Change!
Switch out Zessica Wong for Yunoha Thrul!
Yunoha?
Who's that?
What?
A doll?
Um, uh...
Hello.
It talked!
Amata, Zessica, I'm really sorry for surprising you last night.
And I'm sorry that Mikono made a mistake because of me.
Just a big mistake.
If you saw something like that late at night, you'd freak out too.
I'm really sorry!
But please, you have to trust me and let me fight with you.
You're an Element?
Can we do this later?
Amata, will you still... Union with me?
Yeah. I trust you.
Spectral Union! Go, Aquarion!
No! They'll see me! They'll all see me!
I can see her! I can really see her!
So that's what you really look like...
No! I don't want them to see me!
But it feels nice...
Aquarion Evol!
It's the Machine Angel's other form.
That was in the simulation too.
It's the student who disappeared! She rematerialized!
And she's cute!
Stop looking at me! I...
Did I miss?
What?
Aquarion vanished!
The lasers went right through us!
Her shyness expands to cover her, making her transparent to light.
That's Yunoha Thrul's Element power.
This is what the soul of a beautifully shy young lady can accomplish.
Be careful. I can't keep all of Aquarion transparent for very long at once.
Works for me!
Yunoha, you're amazing!
Please, if you compliment me like that, I'll get shy...
My lasers don't hit, and it's vanished from all my sensors!
This wasn't in the simulation at all!
We're only 800m from the enemy!
Just keep closing in on him!
Right!
Oh, of course.
You're just invisible to light.
I can't see you, but you're still there.
So I can still shoot you with solid bullets!
Is it gone yet?
I'm getting overwhelmed! Pinned down!
Now!
Hit him with a fist he can't see!
Subliminal Punch!
We beat him!
They won!
Did the ghost do that?
I guess that's the best I can do with this transdimensional remote control.
But hey, I got data on a new Rare Igura.
Invisibility...
Amata!
Mikono!
Zessica told me everything.
I guess I jumped to conclusions.
I'm sorry!
Don't worry about it.
This is the new member of our team.
Yes. My name is Yunoha.
You're the ghost of that dead Element, right?
Huh?
Don't worry, I'm not scared of you anymore.
Let's fight together.
Hold on!
What are you talking about, Amata?
There seems to be a misunderstanding.
I'm sorry, but I'm alive.
Yunoha Thrul is an Element student, just like you.
I'm so sorry!
Oh god! Let me down!
Oh, Amata...
He'll fly for anyone.
kaze ni ubawareta wake janai
We weren't spirited away on the wind
katamichi bun no yuuki de bokura
We knew we could never return, and found the courage
higeki wo ukeireru
to accept the hardship
kokoro ga koko ni atta hazu no kuudou
There's an emptiness where my heart used to be
motto boku ga ookikereba
If only I was stronger
kimi wo mirai wo sukueta darou ka
I could have saved you, and our future...
taisetsu na hito wo mamoru sube ga tatta hitotsu shika motanai
I only know of one way to keep the people I love
sonna anata ga haguretadayou sora
And you left me and disappeared into the sky
anata ijou no hito ni deaenai
I'll never find anyone like you again
tsuki ni aragau nagai furea
A long flare reaches out against the moon
hajimaru mo sezu owaru monogatari
The story ends before it could even begin
kizutsukiuru yawarakasa
So soft, so fragile
tojikometa senritsu kanaderu hodo
I will call up the melody locked away
utau hodo kowareru hodo ni
And sing it until I destroy myself
anata ga koishii
That's how much I love you
My name's Zessica Wong!
I'm pretty famous for a 17 year old,
because they say I expose way too much!
Well, the depths of my cleavage may be open for all to see,
but not a soul knows the depths of my heart.
Next Time
Revelations
Next time on Aquarion Evol: Revelations.