I finally found...
the peace I lost so long ago.
the peace so long denied to me.
And then he came and shattered it...
KAGURA!
You...
You'll pay for this!
zetsubouteki ni kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful it's depressing
hanten suru sekai no kattou ni aishiaou
Let's love one another amidst the chaos in this backwards world
bokura ga miteru sekai wa itsudemo sakasama de
This world of ours moves in reverse
A
doushiyou mo nai koto de taigai kimatteku
controlled by forces we can't even touch
A
namida suru hodo kizu tsuku hitomi
There is pain in your eyes so deep I want to cry
A
kokoro de sakebi nagara
Screaming from my heart
A
tada atteitai saigo no futari masarenai mama
The last couple who desire each other cannot be together
A
byouyomi ga kikoetekuru
And time is running out
A
zetsubouteki ni kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful it's depressing
A
sutareyuku doubutsu mitai ni aishiaou
Let's love one another like abandoned animals
A
nakitai kurai kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful I want to cry
A
hanten suru sekai no kattou ni kanjitai yo
Let's love one another amidst the chaos in this backwards world
A
Shards of Adam
Dammit, Izumo...
Silvie?
Silvie, my terrible smelly wench.
I'm not going to lose you.
The world can burn first!
What?
Has the reaper come for me?
You think I'm the Grim Reaper?
Sorry, the only reaper here...
is you!
It's part of their Machine Angel!
Why do I hear the pilot's voice?
Why do you think?
Because I'm you, and you're me!
And that's exactly why I'm going to make you pay for this!
What?
You killed our father!
Our father? Who?
Izumo, the commander of Altair!
It's your fault!
You took everything from me!
Shut up, Amata, you worthless wimp.
You think you're so cool because you can Union by yourself?
Well, I can do anything you can do!
You can't escape from me!
What?
Now we're even.
Two pieces of a divided soul.
Two pieces of the Machine Angel coming together.
The red dream is about to meet the blue reality.
Chairman Crea, what is happening?
A red planet!
Is that...?
Altair.
We're detecting Gepard!
It's engaged with an Abductor!
What?
Mix!
Let me in, Mix!
Spatial Augmentation!
Andy, you're not going to get through to him!
And if you keep using up your power at this rate, you're dead meat!
I can't give up and leave Mix!
I'm staying right here, Mix!
Until I have you in my arms!
Mix!
Why can't you leave me alone?
Let me fill your hole.
I hate holes!
And I absolutely hate you!
Mix!
Andy!
Get back, Andy!
You want to die here?
I'm not leaving her now!
Mix! I'm going to fill that gaping hole in your heart!
The hole... in my heart?
Mix!
You're finally in my arms.
My Mix.
The holes in my memories are filling up!
The memories of when I was a girl...
And he's all over them...
Andy!
Your memories are back?
Andy.. Andy...
Mix! Thank-
No!
Don't look at me!
I can't face you looking like this!
Mix...
I'm not a girl anymore!
Doesn't bother me.
I don't care if you're a boy or a girl.
The one I love is Mix.
Andy!
Can we Union?
Yeah.
Are you sure?
I am.
You guys are gonna Union right here?
Did you forget what we're here for?
I've been saving my purity all this time!
But now it's time to let that chastity burst open!
Long-Awaited Union!
Go!
Aquarion!
Um...
I'm sorry to butt in.
Welcome home, Andy.
You too, Mix.
Kagura! You had Mom and Dad with you this whole time, right here on Altair!
Everything I didn't have, you had within your reach!
And what did you do?
I was never raised by a father or a mother!
What?
I was raised by that evil bastard Mikage.
Living with him was horrible.
Being with Mikage was even lonelier than being by myself.
I couldn't trust anyone.
But the instant I smelled Silvie, my smelly wench, I knew.
That in all the world, only she would accept me.
That we were destined for each other!
I'm going to kill Silvie.
We're going to kill each other in love.
I'll give up my worthless parents for that!
Kagura!
You're the weak part of me.
You're weak. Even your love is weak.
You're the reason we were separated from Silvie 12,000 years ago!
No!
And even in this life, you let our mother slip away too!
No, no!
And now you're going to lose Silvie!
No! No!
You're wrong!
Altair is still approaching! It's actually accelerating!
They're going to collide. It's like the worlds are following Amata's fight.
Chairman?
This is the next page being written in the Book of Twin Stars.
As two fragments of one soul call to one another,
the two worlds are drawn together until they collide.
The old will die, and a new world will be born in their place.
In this new world, Mikage will be a god.
Is that the ending you wanted?
You've been watching this world silently,
and I've been watching you the same way.
You've been Immovable through the worst of times.
But what about this?
Everything that lives will be sacrificed to the new world.
Even the students of our school.
All because it was foretold in the Book of Twin Stars.
Are you going to silently allow all those deaths?
Is this truly what you want?
Fudo Zen!
Fudo!
When I met Mikono, I felt it was destiny too!
Someone who shared my pain, who understood me!
But that's not all about her!
She's shy, she has a short temper,
and she gets jealous for no reason!
Don't you praise her like that!
But always she does her best, and she can take in peoples' pain!
She can connect peoples' feelings together!
That's the Mikono I love!
Not Silvie! Mikono, right now!
Don't fuck with me!
I love her!
Fate is on my side!
I'll fly over my fate and live for the present!
Mikono!
Silvie!
It's Amata, and...
Stop fighting! Amata, Kagura!
Why should they stop fighting?
Zessica?
Refusing to fight is refusing to live.
You're not going to Union with them.
You're doing it with me, Mikono Suzushiro.
You're not Zessica! Who are you?
I am... the Defeated in Love.
24,000 years ago, I was betrayed by my betrothed.
You...
It was with such hatred in my heart that I fought Apollo, the rebirth of Apollonius.
But though my love was faint, it was not fully extinguished.
Apollo wished to unite with me to save this world, and I accepted.
I was at the height of ecstasy. To become one with my love!
And that instant, I knew.
The very instant our souls touched.
That Apollo was not the reincarnation of Apollonius.
The real Apollonius was...
Not just once, but twice, Apollonius trampled my love.
I will unite the worlds as one, and become the god of the new world.
And as the Defeated, I will trample out love.
That is the Legend I will write.
Now, let us unite.
I won't be satisfied no matter how many times I kill you.
You harlot!
What's happening?
This is the wedding of revenge!
No! Noo!
Mikono!
That was Silvie!
That robot!
Mikono! Mikono's in there!
More power...
Ianthe, give me the power of the motherworld!
Mikage! Are you going to drain the whole planet?
Amata! Are you okay?
Cayenne!
Yunoha and Malloy!
Take my spot!
They need your Element power to stand a chance!
Amata, let's Union!
Thanks!
Final Battle Union!
Go, Aquarion!
Aquarion Evol!
Give Mikono back!
Give her back!
Punish them, Ianthe.
A dog with wings dare oppose a weapon of a god?
Oh, and Kagura.
Kagura.
You can't oppose me either, Kagura.
Violation Union.
Go, Aquarion.
Ahh, beautiful.
But empty...
Mikono!
A Dark Aquarion...
kimi he tsuzuku sakamichi ni
There were white flowers growing
shiroi hana ga saiteta
on the road on the hill that leads to you
yume kara sameta ato mo kanashii sora miteta
When I woke from the dream, the sky still looked sad
kono kimochi happa no ue ni susunderu
My feelings drift on a leaf in the wind
asatsuyu wo ochiru oto ni mimi wo sumaseteru no
I'm straining my ears for the sound of the dew falling
kamisama anata ga tsukutta sekai wa kanpeki ja nai
God in Heaven, this world You made is far from perfect
koko de wa mainichi koi ga boroboro shindeku
Down here, love is shattered day by day
hajimete suki ni natta no wo anata wa shiranai deshou
You don't know what it's like to fall in love for the first time
chikyuu no uragawa de ii kara soba ni ite hoshikatta
Let it be on the other end of the world, but I wanted to be with him
watashi wo wasuretemo ii kara soba ni ite hoshikatta
Even if You were to forget me, I wanted to be with him
It was a miracle that we met.
And a miracle that we could be together.
Let's remember it forever.
Let's pray over its joy.
Let's become one.