Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
namida wo nose
take away your tears
kareru made supiido agete
Speed up until they dry
tobikoete yukeru
I can overcome this
kitto kotae wa
The answer is
harukana ano sora no mukou
waiting beyond the distant sky
kotae ga mitsukaranai koko de wa
There's no answer here,
tameiki wo tsuite sora wo miru
so I sigh and look up at the sky
aoku somerareta hitomi no oku de kagayaiteru no wa
Shining deep within my eyes, reflecting its blue,
doko de mo yukeru, yume wo miteru
is a dreamer who can overcome anything
jibun na no sa
It's me, myself
Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
negai wo nosete
carry your dreams
nobashita te wa asu wo egaku
My hands willl draw tomorrow
mou kowaku nado nai
I'm not scared anymore
namida no ato
The memory of my tears
nijiiro ni somatte tondeyuku
are dyed by rainbows and fly
ano sora no mukou
far away beyond the sky
Distance between the Secret and the Scub Coral is 4km.
Georg, what type is it?
Working on it, Miss Hallstrom.
I am currently retrieving data from HQ's database,
but it's very similar to the one that
appeared in South America in the 1940s.
However, there are very few photographs from that time,
so the records are mostly based on the descriptions of survivors.
Estimated time of arrival?
Eleven minutes.
The Secret will reach the Scub Coral in eight minutes.
After that, there will be a humongous Scub Burst.
We won't make it!
It'll be too late if we dispatch after we arrive!
Let us go now!
You heard Fleur.
What do you think, Elena?
I'll go too.
Ok—
No!
What?!
The Okinawan SDF is scrambling. We can't contact them.
Oh, come on!
We've got no choice because we don't have a contract yet.
Of all countries, they should know best.
But I'm not handing it over.
Not a chance!
I'm not handing it over to anyone!
Not a single chance!
Then you're coming with us.
What?
I'm not trying to take advantage of you in the confusion of the moment.
You were born on this island like us, weren't you?
Are you going to just stand there and watch the island get destroyed?
CALL IT WHAT YOU WANT
This is a message to the Japanese Army carrier.
You are trespassing on the territory of the United Okinawan Archipelago.
This is a warning!
No answer... Fucking Japs.
Captain!
We just received orders to oversee the arrival of Generation Bleu.
The international rescue team, huh?
They're telling us to let the Japs go?
Ten years later, a Scub Burst happens.
The Japs choose this time to trespass.
Are you telling me this is just a coincidence?
You don't have time to bother with us, do you now?
But if the Secret makes contact with the Scub Coral,
we're not going to get away unharmed.
I hope you have no objections. We are leaving these waters.
Look! The G-Monster is leaving!
It's the key of an army FP?
Yeah. The Japs are looking for that.
This...
That's why I want to get their help.
But they are from the enemy nation!
If they're not going to help, jack the FP and get rid of the monster.
Look!
Scub Coral?
It's the first time I've seen it myself.
It's huge.
We have to do something about it.
What do you mean?
What are they teaching you in school?
G-Monsters emerge from Scub Bursts.
They're demons that will destroy everything!
But the international rescue team will do something about it!
And what if they don't come?
Then what do you have in mind?!
I honestly don't know.
But if we don't do anything, the island will be gone.
As I thought, the Japs are gone.
No surprise there.
Han! How's it going?
Going well.
I've estimated their course with help from the Okinawan ships' that turned back.
I'm sending it over.
Here it is!
All righty!
What's going on?!
The Secret should be moving toward the Scub Coral!
Why is it coming after us?!
I wouldn't know.
Captain! Two unknown FPs are closing in.
They are the smugglers!
Don't tell me you want to land on a moving ship!
The difference in velocity is too big!
Watch and learn. This is how you do it.
What?!
Wow! I didn't know you could use the FP's anchors like this!
How was that?
Hey, guys... I think they're aiming something at us...
Stop! They have the key!
Can't you tell?
They were just warning shots!
The Secret has stopped.
What?
However, it seems to be pointing its main cannon at us.
Shit! Shit! Shit!
Shit! Holy shit! Holy shit! Holy fucking shit!
God dammit!
Break the glass!
Huh?
Just do it!
Okay!
An FP?
Ouch!
Get in it! Get in it!
That's the Jap FP! Get in it!
But...
Stop whining! You have the key, right?
Who's gonna do it if you—
Hey!
But...
It has power and it's running. I've got no choice.
I have to do it.
The controls are pretty much the same.
Everything will be fine. It'll work out.
It's okay. I must protect the island.
Ao!
The Arata family...
Naru!
Come, sir!
Thanks.
But I have to say, our country is shit out of luck.
I should hurry or I'll end up sinking before I could even—
They're synchronizing?
Where am I?
Welcome... Welcome home...
Welcome home, Eureka?!
What's going on? Why did it suddenly activate?
What's happening?
What's this tremor... The Mark I?!
He did it! The brat did it!
Who's gonna save us then?
Maybe I will.
I'll give you a discount.
Shut up, dammit!
The Secret's not accelerating or changing its direction.
The Okinawan SDF is not responding either.
We'll have to wait.
Miss Halstrom, there seems to be an error in detection.
An error? What error?
The identification code of the IFO that is rapidly nearing in on the Secret
is identical to the Mark I, which was withdrawn from action last year.
What did you say?
It has shoulders?  Wait, this is an IFO?!
I can do this... I can do this... I can do this...
I'm doing this!
Thank you for helping...
You haven't even found Ao yet.
I told Ao that I'll be at the Central Hospital.
I can't imagine you'd be helping us...
I'm a doctor!
But you helped that woman.
The island changed when she came here.
She brought misfortune and pain upon this island.
Don't involve the children in this any further.
The son of that woman, Ao, is also a child of this island.
I must do something... I must do something... I must do something...
That's...
Could that be...
Have you returned? Or...
Help them! There's Japanese blood inside all of us!
Captain! They're here!
You're late, Generation Bleu!
That's the Mark I, the first ever IFO.
I thought it was withdrawn from action because it couldn't be used anymore.
Is a UOA pilot piloting it?
But he's a total newbie!
He's leading the Secret to the Scub Coral!
Scub Coral?
What the hell am I doing?!
If that thing destroys this, the island will be no more!
Ao, don't cry...
I dodged it?
No, that's not it.
It can't see me.
Trapar levels at 17mmol.
Could it be that it can't see me because of trapar interference?
This is Alleluia. I've got visual on the Scub Coral.
What's with this trapar storm?
The third engine's working!
It's the only function that the Mark I's researchers couldn't get working!
The third engine is working?!
No way!
The IFO has two legs! It's standing!
I can feel it! I feel it!
I feel the trapar wind!
It's not lost! Pick it up!
The Mark I was last confirmed to function 10 years ago.
Okinawa was not yet independent at the time.
The largest Scub Burst in history...
Look at the pilot of the giant!
You're right! His hair is turquoise!
What now?
IFO! Do you hear me?
You are not broadcasting an international identification code.
Confirm your nationality and association.
Crap!
I repeat.
You are not broadcasting an international identification code.
Confirm your nationality and association.
He ran away.
I'm going after him.
Be careful, Elena. It's not over yet.
Don't hurt him!
That's up to him.
Wow! He defeated the G-Monster!
I don't like this.
What? You're jealous?
That's not it. But I just know I don't like it.
Come on, where are you?
Feeling better?
I know that uniform...
Yeah. I guess you know about Generation Bleu.
Though we don't specialize in rescuing kids floating on water.
Thanks.
And?
And what?
Where have you hidden it?
Huh?
I see, so we're gonna play that.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm Fleur Blanc. Nice to meet you.
What's your name?
Fukai Ao.
Fukai Ao? What a simple name.
That hurt.
That turquoise-haired kid is really that Fukai brat!
But what does GenBleu want from a kid?
Are you telling me the idol's hitting on him?
Is that seriously what you first think of?!
I guess they're looking for that FP.
Shall we get going?
Where to?
Well...
How about visiting the cave for old times' sake?
Where is that kid?
He caused a lot of trouble for the base! He piloted that giant!
I don't know where he is.
Come on now, Mr Niigaki, you're a resident of the island.
I work at the base. Think of me now as a man of the SDF.
Where is the kid?
I was just about to go out and look for him.
He's just a normal child. There's no way he can pilot an IFO.
Normal? We have witnesses telling us that his hair was turquoise.
Turquoise?
Mama! Mama!
I'm sorry, Ao.
No way...
Fukai's kid Ao piloted the giant?!
They said his hair was turquoise.
That suspicious foreigner blew his cover.
Naru!
Sis!
What do we do?
We catch him before the SDF does.
Even if we have to resort to using force,
we'll make him spit out whether he got the giant from the Japs or from the UOA.
It's for the sake of complete Okinawan independence.
Got it. We'll be right back.
Where's Naru?
Who knows?
She said we mustn't tell you!
He's not here either.
There's only one place left.
Ao!
Everyone, including my dad, is looking for you.
So are the SDF and the people from Generation Bleu.
You're famous.
I just wanted to protect the island.
But it's not going to work out, huh?
I'm a foreign kid...
Is it my fault that the monster showed up?
Ao...
Look at me...
I'm disgusting, right?
I saw it in my dream.
Your hair turned turquoise and you fought in the sea giant.
Ten years ago, a giant protected me.
It happened again.
Thank you.
Do you want to see it?
The sea giant.
This is the sea giant?
Yeah... This is Ao's sea giant.
To be continued.
PREVIEW
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
As the storm of destruction calms,
an unseen strand of fate from the past is waiting for Ao.
The people who fear and the people who desire the power hurt the boy.
Which path are the people who are fighting against the flow of events going to take?
Eureka Seven AO, episode 3: Still Fighting.
Listen the voice of the children of the stars.