I hear the ultimate stage calling to me...
zetsubouteki ni kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful it's depressing
hanten suru sekai no kattou ni aishiaou
Let's love one another amidst the chaos in this backwards world
bokura ga miteru sekai wa itsudemo sakasama de
This world of ours moves in reverse
A
doushiyou mo nai koto de taigai kimatteku
controlled by forces we can't even touch
A
namida suru hodo kizu tsuku hitomi
There is pain in your eyes so deep I want to cry
A
kokoro de sakebi nagara
Screaming from my heart
A
tada atteitai saigo no futari masarenai mama
The last couple who desire each other cannot be together
A
byouyomi ga kikoetekuru
And time is running out
A
zetsubouteki ni kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful it's depressing
A
sutareyuku doubutsu mitai ni aishiaou
Let's love one another like abandoned animals
A
nakitai kurai kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful I want to cry
A
hanten suru sekai no kattou ni kanjitai yo
Let's love one another amidst the chaos in this backwards world
A
Wings of Rebirth
This voice! This melody!
They'll be perfect for the final movement!
I need more! Play more, Aquarion!
Where is that energy coming from, Shrade!
It's beautiful! Elegant and delicate, but strong and passionate!
I can feel its rhythm in my heart!
I've never felt this way before!
Shrade isn't wearing an Element suit. His body is effectively exposed.
That means he can feel his surroundings keenly.
But it also means his body is taking more damage.
He's seriously risking his life.
Shrade...
Let my heart play its greatest cadenza!
What I saw was real.
You're me.
So of course I could never smell you.
You smell the same as me.
This picture shows me.
And you.
We were originally one person.
Until that day...
No!
No! No!!
Don't leave me!
Amata just watched as fate slipped away from him that day.
And that's you.
You haven't gotten any better.
Amata is a pathetic wimp who can't do a thing when it really counts.
So what about you? You never saved Mom either!
What have you been doing on Altair?
I made it across the dimensions, but I ended up losing Mother.
Mikage found me.
Welcome, fragmented one. Dark Amata.
From this day on, you are now Kagura.
I had lost my memories. Mikage raised me.
I don't care about my mother anymore.
I have no idea who or where she is, just like with my father.
There's only one smell I care about.
My own dear smelly wench, the real Silvie!
I'm not pathetic! And I won't let you have Mikono!
See? Pathetic.
You're not good enough!
Stop! Why are you fighting?
Please! Stop fighting!
The Wings of the Sun are finally awakening.
What's the matter, Amata?
You say you're not pathetic? Prove it!
The hell?
Mikono!
Silvie!
Aquarion?
What's going on?
Detecting higher-dimensional quanta!
They're coming from near the former lake area!
What do these mean?
Aquarion is resonating with that thing.
This is an ancient melody, coming to our ears from 12,000 years ago!
There can be no mistake.
That is the Legendary Aquarion from the myth!
At last!
At last you show yourself, Wings of the Sun!
Where am I?
Aquarion?
It's different...
Mikono! Mikono!
Amata!
Silvie!
I've been waiting for you, Silvie!
For 12,000 long years!
But now I can finally kill you!
You want to kill Mikono!
You bet I want to kill her!
Bitterly, violently, and coldly!
I'm going to kill her over and over!
But first...
I'm going to crush you, Amata!
Wait for me, Silvie!
I'll get rid of him, and then we can kill each other all night long!
What?
I won't let you touch her!
The higher-dimensional quantum emissions are still rising!
Guess that settles it. That's the real deal.
The Legendary Aquarion?
The stories are coming to life...
I can't believe we're actually here for this moment in history...
It's a momentous time, all right. So why is that kid messing around over there?
That is another legend in itself.
High Commander Fudo! When did you return?
You needn't concern yourself with this lovers' spat!
Amata!
You can't have her!
Give up already.
This was destined 12,000 years ago.
You and Silvie aren't fated.
You can't fight fate, no matter how much you struggle.
Fate even brought us together across the worlds.
I have the wings to overcome fate!
Your wings are useless if you can't fly.
Well, can you? Fly if you can!
Stop! Don't hurt Amata anymore!
I hate that smile of yours, Silvie.
It makes me want to kill you even more.
Smile for me more.
More! Smile more!
Where is this?
Am I dead?
Amata!
I'm so glad you're okay, Zessica!
Me too, Amata!
Did you come back because you were worried about me?
Zessica, I finally understand.
I finally know what's precious to me.
Amata...
Wake up.
You can't die yet.
Because...
You haven't fulfilled your promise to me.
Noooooo!
You can't die yet.
Because you haven't fulfilled your promise to me.
What promise?
Please, stop!
I don't want to see you two fight anymore!
I can't do that, Mikono!
I'm going to settle this right now!
Settle what?
You want Mikono because you think you're destined?
Exactly. How many times do I have to say it?
Well, not me!
I don't care if Mikono is the reincarnation of Silvie!
I don't care about whatever was fated 12,000 years ago!
I love Mikono as she is right now!
Amata!
Amata...
Mikono as she is right here, right now, this instant!
Then let's see which one's stronger!
My destiny, or your burning emotions!
Amata!
What the!
The Wings of the Sun!
I won't let you beat me!
I'm so close... I can almost hear the melody I've been searching for...
Shrade!
What's wrong, Shrade?!
Can you hear it, my friend?
Isn't that sound so beautiful?
Silvie!
Mikono!
Shrade's vital levels are dropping fast!
Further combat will put his life in danger!
Element Change! Swap Shrade for Yunoha!
Wait!
I can still fight...
Just a little more...
I almost...
Element Charge! Hurry!
Yunoha Thrul, entering battle!
Not so fast!
The Legendary Aquarion's higher-dimensional quantum emissions are beyond measurable bounds!
Fudo, what is your goal?
Wasn't all this written in the Book of Genesis?
Legends can only be written by great and noble lives.
Using spilled blood as ink.
You won't stop them, then?
There is no difference between moving and stopping.
When you clap your hands, what remains between them?
Nothing. Just an empty void, a zero.
But zero is not always nothing.
Zero is a value obtained by adding a positive and a negative together.
That is Mikono Suzushiro's power of connection.
Dark and light. Holy and profane. Good and evil.
Positive and negative.
Let both their sealed memories be unlocked,
and the infinite power of zero will be unleashed.
Now, a new page is turning!
What?
I can't take any more!
Come to my breast, Wings of the Sun!
He took the Legendary Aquarion!
Amata!
The Gate's open. Let's go.
Both Abductors and the Legendary Aquarion have entered the Dimension Gate!
Please, Chairman Crea.
Once more... let me go once more...
You will die this time.
You must have known since you brought me to Neo-Deava.
That it would end this way someday.
Just promise me one thing.
When you complete your song, let me hear it.
Mikono!
Shrade!
Both Vectors have entered the Dimension Gate!
We've lost contact!
Where are Mikono and Kagura?
Amata!
To complete the final song...
I have to take back the Legendary Aquarion first!
But we can't take him on alone!
I'll Union with you!
Zessica! You're alive!
Amata... this is how I can show my love for you.
Destiny Union! Go, Aquarion!
Amata!
Thank you, Zessica.
My very soul is vibrating!
Aquarion Spada!
The Legendary Aquarion!
Got you.
Wow!
Now repent your sins...
Crucifixion Sword!
Shrade!
The Dimension Gate is opening!
Mithra Gnis is coming out on this side!
We're detecting a Rare Igura in the cockpit!
The Rare Igura Kagura has been after all this time...
She could well be the true Eve.
Prepare all units to sortie!
We cannot let Kagura take our true Eve for himself!
We have reports of crustal movement and abnormal weather all over the world!
The seal on the Legendary Aquarion has been lifted.
The balance between Vega and Altair it sustained is now shifting.
We lost the Legendary Aquarion,
and we can't contact the Elements...
We're helpless here!
What is going to happen to the world?
There is still hope.
The Wings of the Sun will not move in the absence of its chosen Element.
It's time.
Time to fulfill your promise, girl with hair the color of grass.
kimi he tsuzuku sakamichi ni
There were white flowers growing
shiroi hana ga saiteta
on the road on the hill that leads to you
yume kara sameta ato mo kanashii sora miteta
When I woke from the dream, the sky still looked sad
kono kimochi happa no ue ni susunderu
My feelings drift on a leaf in the wind
asatsuyu wo ochiru oto ni mimi wo sumaseteru no
I'm straining my ears for the sound of the dew falling
kamisama anata ga tsukutta sekai wa kanpeki ja nai
God in Heaven, this world You made is far from perfect
koko de wa mainichi koi ga boroboro shindeku
Down here, love is shattered day by day
hajimete suki ni natta no wo anata wa shiranai deshou
You don't know what it's like to fall in love for the first time
chikyuu no uragawa de ii kara soba ni ite hoshikatta
Let it be on the other end of the world, but I wanted to be with him
watashi wo wasuretemo ii kara soba ni ite hoshikatta
Even if You were to forget me, I wanted to be with him
I'll tell you what I like.
Colorful scattered flower petals
and Kagura's screams.
I'll tell you what I hate, too.
Lies and betrayal...
Next Time
Song of Legend
and him.