Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
namida wo nose
take away your tears
kareru made supiido agete
Speed up until they dry
tobikoete yukeru
I can overcome this
kitto kotae wa
The answer is
harukana ano sora no mukou
waiting beyond the distant sky
kotae ga mitsukaranai koko de wa
There's no answer here,
tameiki wo tsuite sora wo miru
so I sigh and look up at the sky
aoku somerareta hitomi no oku de kagayaiteru no wa
Shining deep within my eyes, reflecting its blue,
doko de mo yukeru, yume wo miteru
is a dreamer who can overcome anything
jibun na no sa
It's me, myself
Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
negai wo nosete
carry your dreams
nobashita te wa asu wo egaku
My hands willl draw tomorrow
mou kowaku nado nai
I'm not scared anymore
namida no ato
The memory of my tears
nijiiro ni somatte tondeyuku
are dyed by rainbows and fly
ano sora no mukou
far away beyond the sky
Hey, look!
A child is down there!
Who the hell are you...
Who's there?!
Who am I?
If I have to introduce myself...
From this moment onward...
My name is Truth.
No One Is Innocent
Where's the enemy?
They just arrived on the floor right below us.
They will be here soon.
Intruders?
We don't know who or what they are,
but security has been mobilized.
To be safe, the two of you stay there and wait for orders.
What? In a guy's room?
I'm sending someone over to pick you up.
Serves you right for inviting yourself into my room.
Oh please! If I weren't here, you wouldn't have been able to answer the phone!
I would!
By the way, is Elena there?
Huh?
Elena?
I've been trying to contact her using emergency channels, but she's not responding.
1980, Generation Bleu was founded to protect Earth.
Nosferatu's Great Prophecy
Maybe I should write this down?
He did not trigger any sensor detections?
In my opinion, this is an attack without an official proclamation of war.
But the witnesses say there was only one attacker.
Can this really be treated as such a matter?
There are already fatalities amongst the guards.
This is no minor affair.
Have you received any intel, Hallström?
No. The Americans don't know anything.
Erase all data, transport the IFOs, and secure the pilots.
In the absolute worst scenario, destroy that and the HQ with it.
What about Blanc?
He doesn't need to be informed.
Hurry.
Emergency alert. There's a confirmed intruder in HQ.
Casualties have also been confirmed.
Mirror, what are you doing here?
Tonight's gig is cancelled.
They told us to hurry to the shelters.
I'll be there right away! Please go on ahead without me.
Be quick.
Wow, he's closing in.
Don't move!
What are your intentions?!
Where are you from, you terrorist?!
You're Mirror, right? I'm a huge fan of yours!
That's wonderful.
I'll ask you one more time! Who the hell are you?!
Who am I?
I am Truth.
Welcome to my live show, The Ball.
Fuck it! Shoot him!
Shoot him now!
Who are you?
I'm Mirror.
Mirror? What are you doing here?
I'm a singer here.
I see. So you sing...
...the truth.
The intruder...
The intruder is heading for the coral—
If he gets to the bottom—
That's not it. He's not going for anything underground.
Operation of the central shaft cablecar line is fully suspended.
Where the hell is this?
A temporary stop?
It sounds like something's going on down there.
We're at the Generation Bleu's headquarters!
No worries!
Oh lord...
That's quite the reaction from meeting a nice woman.
More like because we got this job.
Now Ao's not the only one getting recognition.
Keep your mouths shut!
What?
What are you doing?
I'm looking for the truth of the world.
The truth?
He's here!
Hey!
Up? You said he's heading upwards?
The intruder?
Yessir. Since his last appearance at the Central Market station,
we haven't been able to track him down.
But judging from his path so far...
Graffeud!
Strengthen the defense of the central shaft against entry from lower levels!
Order team Pied Piper to scramble.
What?!
What are you so surprised about?
The intruder is heading upwards.
So this is what we should do.
Are you saying he's going for the IFOs?
Or the pilots.
And if his target is on the lower levels, I'd say an IFO assault would be more effective.
Scramble? Are you kidding me?!
We haven't even loaded the Nirvash yet!
I don't care if it has to launch alone!
Are the Americans here for it or what?
Ao, hurry!
If they can't load you into the Triton on time, you'll have to launch from here!
Roger!
Who are you?
It is you.
I've always wanted to meet you.
Hey, what are you doing on Nirvash?
That's...
Nirvash?
I see, so that's what this machine is called.
And what are you doing...
in that woman's machine?
Woman? You mean my mother?
Get away from there!
Get away from there right now!
If not—
Miss Rebecka!
Ao, go now!
Get away from the base and go somewhere safe!
But—
Nirvash performed an emergency launch.
It's flying in the 57th tunnel.
Open Gate A303.
I see, so you're using what belongs to that woman.
In that case...
We're back!
Sorry for having you discharged early from the hospital.
I'm happy to see you all in one piece.
For the time being, I will take command of team Goldilocks.
Y-Yessir.
And Ao?
At the moment, Fukai Ao is...
Stanley!
Fukai Ao is...
Granny! Sis is gone!
What? I told her to stay in bed!
Don't tell me she's gone there again...
The island has changed since you left.
So it's our fault?
It's changed ever since the beginning of time.
Having the Allied Forces supervise us is no different from having the Japs on our necks.
I'm the only one around who still dreams of the Okinawan Archipelago's true independence.
Scub Coral, huh...
Only the main island had one until Iwato Island received its own.
The trapar makers jumped on this opportunity.
The island is as prosperous as it has ever been.
Pushing for resistance movements at a time like this will only make me a laughing stock.
Jirou, won't you come back to the island?
You can even succeed me if you want.
Who are you kidding?
In your opinion, I've always been "a useless prick."
Don't start counting on me now.
But I'm at my limit...
You've never seen the truth to begin with.
The truth?
Yeah, the truth.
The bigwigs are all hiding the truth.
But I'll find it.
I'll...
I'll do everything you couldn't do.
Sign: Iwato Island Plant Coral Local Support Committee
The island's gonna flourish now!
Yeah.
Hey, isn't that...
Naru! You should be in bed!
I'm sorry, but...
No buts! What if you get even sicker?!
If you get it, go home and be a good girl!
Understand?
Yes.
Ao?
We shouldn't do this! They'll get mad at us!
And my cough is getting worse.
You wanted to see the Scub Coral, didn't you?
I got this sickness in a Scub Burst, after all...
This way.
We can get in this way.
I'm kind of scared.
Let's go.
You've changed, Ao.
Really? I can't tell at all.
Why did you come back?
How was Generation Bleu?
It's got nothing to do with them.
I came back because I wanted to see you.
Me?
I want to know...
About what?
The truth.
You don't need this.
Take a deep breath.
How weird. Breathing isn't hard at all.
Me too.
It feels a lot better when I'm with you.
Naru!
What have you done, Naru?!
Naru.
Ao?
Hey, that woman's son.
I'm Fukai Ao!
What have you done to Naru?!
So your name is Naru?
Don't touch her!
Ao!
Hey!
Nirvash, we're going!
Hey, what exactly is going—
Let me on!
Let go!
Let go of me!
Is that the sea giant?
What did you do to my hometown?!
I thought that you might've been an existence close to the truth of this world.
But Naru is even more interesting.
What?!
Naru is a normal girl!
You people see nothing.
Shut up!
What the hell is that?
What exactly is he?!
That's...
The sea giant...
Thank you.
Hey!
Naru!
You can fly.
Naru, come here! Get away from him!
Stop, Ao.
What are you talking about? He's not me!
I know.
You even had Noah with you.
Then?!
But it's enough.
He's my sea giant!
Naru?
I can fly with him!
So take me with you!
Don't do that, Naru!
This world is erroneous anyway.
Naru!
Naru!!
Where am I?
In the hospital. You've been out cold for three days.
In the hospital?
Yeah. You don't remember?
You flew off with the intruder and crashed.
We hurried after you,
but there were no signs of the intruder.
Only the Mark I was there.
The rescue team got you out and brought you here.
The Security Service is chasing after the intruder who made you crash.
I'm glad... So it was just a dream.
And...
Yeah?
Miss Rebecka told us not to tell you,
but this is all over the news now.
Middle schooler girl gone missing at Iwato Island Plant Coral
Involvement by unidentified man possible
Missing: Arata Naru (12)
An incident happened on your home island.
Isn't she your friend?
Just how much of our budget do you think we pumped into the Mark I?!
We couldn't secure it. There's nothing we can do about it now.
I would say our country should not depend on IFOs.
What?!
But I just can't accept the fact that
Generation Bleu is using the Mark I.
It's funded by our taxes.
Shall we harass them a little?
Yes, he infiltrated the headquarters.
Yes, that was according to our reports.
He called himself Truth.
He may be the terrorist in question.
And it seems like that is still under Generation Bleu's headquarters.
To be continued.
takanaru shinzou no koe wa
My heart is racing and beating loud
itsu shika kokochi yoku najinde ite
But that feels cozily familiar
kaze ga tsuyoku fuiteite mo
Even if the wind is blowing hard
me wo tsumuranaide itsu datte mae wo muku yo
Don't close your eyes and always look on ahead
nakitaku nattara omoidashite
If you feel like crying, remember
damatte chikaiatta yakusoku wo
the promise we made together
tabidatsu hinadori no uta
The young birds in the sky sing
ima mo mada umaku tobenai keredo
though they still can't fly well
meguri meguru toki wo koe
Even if we go beyond the edge of time
hitazura ni tsunaida te wo tadotte
I'll only follow you as we hold hands
kotoba wa
"So I never let you go!" My words
sora ni kieteku bakari da toshite mo
may get lost in the infinity of the sky,
chirabaru hikari no naka de
but among the glittering light
mayowazu ni kimi wo sagashidaseru kara
I can still find you without hesitation
Preview
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
As Naru was taken from him by his enemy, Ao grows more and more impatient.
Fleur tries to gain strength from her warped feelings for her father in the fight.
What do they find at the barren land that's at the end of their paths?
Eureka Seven AO, episode eight: One Nation Under a Groove.
Listen to the voices of the children of the stars.