High Commander Fudo is gone?
He left a note.
It seems he left early this morning.
To search for... the Legendary Aquarion?
Does he have a lead on it?
I don't know.
There may be something in the Book of Twin Stars, but...
The Book of Twin Stars?
Why are there so many holes?
He's in this one!
Not again. This one's really deep.
Andy!
What's the matter with him?
Why is he so depressed after he saving all of us?
Andy dug us an awesome hot spring!
What happened out there?
Mix, do you have any idea?
Nope! No idea! What could have possibly happened?
Oh no!
Mix...
zetsubouteki ni kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful it's depressing
hanten suru sekai no kattou ni aishiaou
Let's love one another amidst the chaos in this backwards world
bokura ga miteru sekai wa itsudemo sakasama de
This world of ours moves in reverse
A
doushiyou mo nai koto de taigai kimatteku
controlled by forces we can't even touch
A
namida suru hodo kizu tsuku hitomi
There is pain in your eyes so deep I want to cry
A
kokoro de sakebi nagara
Screaming from my heart
A
tada atteitai saigo no futari masarenai mama
The last couple who desire each other cannot be together
A
byouyomi ga kikoetekuru
And time is running out
A
zetsubouteki ni kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful it's depressing
A
sutareyuku doubutsu mitai ni aishiaou
Let's love one another like abandoned animals
A
nakitai kurai kimi wa kirei sa
You're so beautiful I want to cry
A
hanten suru sekai no kattou ni kanjitai yo
Let's love one another amidst the chaos in this backwards world
A
Rare  Igura
A concert?
Thank you. I'll think about it.
Don't think. Come with me.
I'll be waiting.
Later!
You got asked out again?
Your new look's doing wonders for you, Zessica.
It's not sweet enough.
And how about your daring confession in the mock battle?
You were so brave!
Sorry, did I make you do that?
Not really. I said it because I wanted to.
Besides, it got me to move forward.
Really?
But I might be moving into another dead end...
Miss Suzushiro!
Yes?
Perfect. I was going to take this up to your room.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Mikono!
Oh, I'm sorry. I wasn't trying to hide this.
It's a letter from my father.
Your father?
We don't really get along.
I wasn't expecting a letter from him.
Maybe he's worried about me.
Well, of course. He's your dad.
I guess I'm not one to talk.
Oh, no...
I remember my mom a little bit,
but nothing about my dad.
I don't even know what's going on right now.
You mean...
when I protected him?
Stop!
Don't shoot, Amata!
Please, forgive him!
I don't mean to blame you for anything!
But we all have to work together now.
I know!
I'm the one who's supposed to connect everyone together.
But I don't know if I can!
This isn't...
Well, this is different. What's the matter?
Father's letter to you got delivered to me by mistake.
Sorry. I opened it first.
Yeah, Dad's handwriting is terrible.
And why'd he send a sealed letter, anyway?
Hey, what's wrong?
Nothing.
See you tomorrow.
Mikono!
I'm so stupid.
I shouldn't have kept reading it.
I don't know why Mikono is at the academy,
but I hope she isn't holding you back.
You know she's never been good at anything.
Just say the word and I'll have her out of Neo-Deava
and back home with me.
I'm still completely useless to Daddy.
Mikono?
You're worried about Andy?
He's really depressed right now.
And it's all my fault.
But I thought you two were getting along really well.
It happened on that field trip.
The worst part is, I go around telling people to say what they feel,
but when it came to it, I just couldn't do it.
I can't stop seeing my dad in boys.
Your dad?
You know why I have boy problems, right?
Yeah...
How about you, Mikono?
What's your relationship with your dad?
Me? I...
Um...
What is it, Mikono?
If you're not going to tell me...
I was always afraid of what he thought of me.
Whenever I was about to say something,
I'd be afraid he'd get mad and stop.
But he'd get mad at me for not speaking my mind anyway.
Oh.
I guess we'll never understand.
Even dads are men.
And us girls can't figure out how men feel.
By the way, is Shush a boy or a girl?
Well...
Zessica?
Why are you practicing at this hour?
I remembered, I'm a fighter girl.
I know I've been depressed lately,
but I don't want to lose one edge. It's all I've got.
Good night!
Zessica...
What am I doing?
This is a dead end.
Ianthe's operating level has just passed 40%.
The amount of energy required for dimensional warping is what's hurting us the most.
Continued travel to Vega will put a strain on the populace.
Mass rebellions have been forecasted.
Then we've reached the end of the line.
Where is Kagura?
I'm sorry. We don't know.
Mikage is probably behind this.
He doesn't care one bit for Altair's future.
Prepare the Ahura Gnis to sortie.
Sir?
I'm going to Vega myself.
It's time to taste the air of that old battlefield.
Alicia...
For the sake of bringing this world back to life,
I shall find the True Eve.
And I might also find...
the son you left on Vega.
You read it, didn't you?
You know, Dad's letter.
I'm sorry.
I don't really mind.
I was just worried it was getting you down.
Parents freak out about the stupidest things.
You can send me home.
What?
Daddy's right. I'm holding you guys back.
If I'm going to be useless, I should do it at home.
Mikono!
Ow!
What was that for?
You've always been too worried about what people think of you.
You could never say anything because you were
scared of making people mad or hurting them.
But I think you were really mostly scared for yourself.
For a long time, I thought of you as my useless coward of a sister.
But I met this guy, and right away he said...
I know I haven't known her for very long,
but I think she's changed since then.
Mikono is really trying to change herself!
Amata told you that?
As much as I hate to admit it, he was right.
You've really changed.
In fact, I want Dad to see how you've changed.
Cayenne!
That's a new sound.
A powerful, intense sound.
The sea. It's making me nostalgic.
This is the Vega of my youth.
Oh, Izumo. You want to bloom a flower after all this time?
Or are you looking for a seed dropped by a flower?
We've sighted an unknown enemy mech!
Seems like we've got a boss battle coming up!
You're late, Andy!
Sorry...
Are you okay?
Sure. I'm fine...
Andy!
You can't dig in here!
Forget it. He's out of commission.
We've got five usable Vectors! Have two of them back up Aquarion!
The Elements going out are...
They're up to you.
Cayenne! Amata! And...
I'll go!
You can't! It's too dangerous for you to go!
I can't be myself if you won't let me fight!
Right now, we have to be fighters before girls!
We want to help and be part of the team!
What are you...
Let them go.
We can only do so much with men alone.
Fudo... did I do the right thing?
Then Aquarion's pilots are Amata, Zessica, and Malloy!
Cayenne and Mix, you're the wingmen!
Roger!
Zessica's too excited.
I'm worried about her.
I have a bad feeling about this...
Let's Union! I'll be the head, got it?
Zessica...
Roger!
Heartbreak Union!
Go, Aquarion!
I can be with Amata, if only in a fight...
I can feel Zessica's emotions!
Union is amazing!
Aquarion Gepard!
We'll deal with the grunts!
We may just be Vectors, but we'll still mess you up!
Let's end this!
Good effort, but you're still greenhorns.
No way!
He didn't take any damage at all!
Damage report!
West side barriers have been obliterated!
The enemy unit absorbed Gepard's beam, amplified it, and fired it back!
How about these?
Such youthful passion is lost on Altair.
But it won't win you this battle alone!
Calm down, Zessica!
It's too dangerous to shoot him!
Get in closer!
I know already!
Malloy! Back me up!
Got it!
The Curse of Malloy!
Contrary Twister!
How's that feel?
Fragility? Interesting.
But the young are always more fragile than the old.
I would like to avoid useless destruction...
So let me demonstrate the vast gap between our powers.
One more time! Contrary Twister!
That won't work again!
Gepard!
The Union broke!
That impact knocked Malloy out!
Vector Y is flying on autopilot!
I'll go!
Element Change to Mikono!
Cayenne, Amata, and Mikono will Union!
Zessica, back them up!
Why?
You're too hotheaded today!
What's the matter with you?
Amata! Cayenne! We're going to Union!
The enemy is heading this way!
That Abductor doesn't look like it's attacking...
He's tapping into our communications!
What?
Soldiers of Vega.
I am Izumo Kamurogi, the chief commander of the planet Altair.
I would like to speak to your leader.
The chief commander?
Him?
I am Crea Dolosera, the commander of Neo-Deava.
Even your commander is an Igura, a female.
I was under the impression that
women were not disposed to battle.
Perhaps what you say is true.
But when necessary, women can be even stronger than men.
Perhaps.
We require the most powerful Rare Igura among you.
The most powerful Rare Igura?
I have no desire to wage war on this world.
All I ask is that you send a Rare Igura to our planet.
No way in hell!
Wait.
Miss Chairman?
If we have a chance to settle this diplomatically...
What would Fudo do?
Zessica's Vector is heading towards the Abductor!
You want a woman? Take me!
Maybe that'll change things!
That machine...
So it is a Rare Igura!
Cut it out, Zessica!
Don't throw yourself away! You're not thinking straight!
Yes, I am! I...
I see that Rare Igura has a strong will.
I'll take her.
Pursuit Union!
Go Aquarion!
Aquarion Evol!
The flying Machine Angel!
I sense... him inside the machine...
Let's make sure, Izumo.
With your very own eyes.
Mom?
Why is that image there?
Something is manipulating Amata's heart.
Clear, sweet, yet bitter.
Mikage, you snake! This is your doing!
But it stopped the Machine Angel.
It really is him...
What's happening?
Amata! Stay focused on your enemy!
Zessica!
I won't let you take Zessica!
Don't regret this, Zessica!
Mix!
I won't let you! Infinity Punch!
Let us meet again, winged boy.
She sacrificed herself for me...
Mix...
Mix!
MIX!
kimi he tsuzuku sakamichi ni
There were white flowers growing
shiroi hana ga saiteta
on the road on the hill that leads to you
yume kara sameta ato mo kanashii sora miteta
When I woke from the dream, the sky still looked sad
kono kimochi happa no ue ni susunderu
My feelings drift on a leaf in the wind
asatsuyu wo ochiru oto ni mimi wo sumaseteru no
I'm straining my ears for the sound of the dew falling
kamisama anata ga tsukutta sekai wa kanpeki ja nai
God in Heaven, this world You made is far from perfect
koko de wa mainichi koi ga boroboro shindeku
Down here, love is shattered day by day
hajimete suki ni natta no wo anata wa shiranai deshou
You don't know what it's like to fall in love for the first time
chikyuu no uragawa de ii kara soba ni ite hoshikatta
Let it be on the other end of the world, but I wanted to be with him
watashi wo wasuretemo ii kara soba ni ite hoshikatta
Even if You were to forget me, I wanted to be with him
I hated myself for being afraid.
But maybe fear is what gives us the power to move forward.
I have to take my own step forward.
Next Time
First Reunion
Next time: First Reunion.