Kokoro
masshiro PAGE mekuru
I walk through the white pages of my storybook
Incoming Text
tobidasu irodoru hajikeru
just waiting to be painted
mangekyou no fuukei
with a kaleidoscope of my experiences.
From
Me
To
You
kizukeba STORY wa mada
This story has only
gikochinaku hajimatta bakkari
just barely begun
shinkokyuu wo mou ikkai
I take a deep breath
tabi suru kaze tsutsumikomu you ni senaka wo osu
and the wind wraps around me and urges me forward
aa yawarakakute atatakai kimi no te
Your hand is so warm held within mine;
nigiri shimete sono kokoro no oku made todoku you ni
it reaches all the way to my heart.
hohoenmi de kureta nara nigirikaeshite kuretara
I can't see a brighter future
boku wa tada mae wo miteru
than you smiling and taking my hand as well
We'll v2 when we get a raw without an earthquake warning.
From Now On
It's already this late?
How did time pass so quickly? I feel like we just started!
How are you doing, Sawako?
You still have your solo part in the costume parade to worry about.
Make sure you sneak in a nap sometime.
It's okay.
Even if I weren't doing this, I wouldn't
have been able to sleep tonight.
Does anyone have extra pins?
I do!
Sawako, I think your phone is flashing.
Oh, it is! I wonder if it's my dad?
This is such a long night.
So you did like him!
Yui and Andy sitting in a tree!
I can see it!
Andy
Kazehaya's
Friend
Andy's a good guy.
This is so embarrassing!
I-I overheard their conversation!
I'm asking Yusuke about Andy for you!
Sadako, what does your magic see for them?
I-It's okay, be honest!
Be honest?
I think you two will be wonderful! Just beautiful together!
Yes! I so agree!
See, I knew you two were compatible!
Yeah, and now even the infamous Black Magic Café's Sadako says so!
Oh no! I can't believe I said something so irresponsible!
I think I'll go for it now.
Wow, it's like Sadako's transferring power to her!
Lucky!
No, no, it's nothing like that.
She's just in the same position.
So it'll all be over tomorrow.
It's been a long time coming.
I bet Kazehaya's freaking out now because he can't talk to Sawako.
Why are we making a float right now?!
Well, because the costume parade is tomorrow.
'Cause we're really slow.
'Cause Joe messed up the measurements.
Sorry!
I keep repeating the same moment over and over again in my mind.
To reassure myself that it wasn't just a dream.
Shota Kazehaya
Tomorrow
I want to talk to you again.
Sawako Kuronuma
Re: Tomorrow
Okay
School festival, day two.
Chizu! Are you all done?
Yup. I just need my snake.
Where's Sadako?
Yano-chin's helping her get ready.
Keep your eyes open wide!
There, all set.
How's it going?
Done yet?
Yup, just finished.
Did you see the girls yet?
Yeah! They look great— really funny!
Your costume's so cute!
It looks great on you!
Ch-Chizu?
Sorry! I just had to check if you really had feet or not.
I really wanted to use some blush or sparkly eyeshadow,
but I had to focus on making it look intense.
Sadako's supposed to be dressed as Okiku from Bancho Sarayashiki.
Takahashi!
Are you going to portray her as being unfortunately tied to a well?
No one better for that than you!
A convoluted love story about a woman who was unable to trust men,
and a man who went crazy because because he could never win her trust.
Is that how the story went?
It could be interpreted that way.
You have a great part.
Y-You're amazing, Takahashi!
You're perfect as a bearded wise man!
I'm glad the float and the costumes
were all able to be finished on time.
Why do you look so tired, Ryu?
I'm a growing boy.
Class C's "Seven Lovers" is pretty awesome too!
Am I wearing this right?
I have no idea. Make it up!
Yano!
How do you like my talisman costume?
Wow, it suits you!
You look just like an idiot.
Oh yeah!
Chizuru, you're a martial artist?
Nope, a snake!
Looks good.
Oh really? Thanks.
Yano!
Where's Kuronuma?
She's in the hallway talking to Chigusa right now.
Thanks.
Kazehaya.
Sawako's the one who made your costume.
Hey!
It's almost time!
Everyone that's finished, come line up in the hallway!
Huh?
What is it?
Did you see Kuronuma?
She already went out.
Got it.
What are you doing?
Are you off to get dumped again?
I don't mind!
Doesn't matter anymore!
He's "wide eyed and super excited" Kazehaya now?
He was just "nervous and super depressed" Kazehaya a minute ago!
Whatever.
Just move it.
Do your solo part just like we talked about yesterday!
I'm sure Shota's excited to see you do it too.
Kuronuma!
This is why...
I don't want to let you see me like this.
Thanks for replying to me yesterday.
No, thank you!
Kazehaya!
Our Buddy Joe: Amitabha
Do you think I'd look better if I
jumped everywhere instead of walking?
I'm sorry.
No, don't—
I'm talking to Kuronuma right now.
Wha—
Wh-What?
Emergency Earthquake Announcement
There's something I want to say to you.
Earthquake in Tochigi prefecture, Kantou, etc. Warning: strong tremors.
Emergency earthquake announcement.
Can I go first?
Please, before I run out of courage...
I was really happy visiting the shrine with you on New Year's.
I was scared of how happy I was.
I wanted to keep you all to myself,
but I didn't want you to hate me for it.
There's a chance that putting my feelings
into words might make them impossible...
But...
From now on, I want to try to change things.
From now on, I want things to be different between us!
It's so hard to start things anew...
But if it's Kazehaya, I'm sure...
I'm sure...!
Gather up!
Watch me.
I'm going to do my best!
So many things have changed,
since I met Kazehaya.
I'm going to put on a really good show with
everything I've learned in the past year!
I'm sure I won't let people down anymore!
After falling in love with Kazehaya,
I've changed.
Kuronuma!
I like you!
Hey, how should I take what you just said?
A-As a compliment!
I want to be friends with all of them!
I'll do my best so that we can be friends!
You don't have to do anything.
It's fine.
Next up is second year, class D!
One plate...
Two plates...
Plates...
No matter how many times I count them, I'm still one short.
Now!
Do it!
I wanted to offer my thanks. A cold drink for you.
Please enjoy.
This is a bribe, isn't it?
It is, but...
Please don't look at us like that. It's scary.
We will now begin the closing ceremony for
the 43rd Kitahoro High School Festival.
First, we'll start with the winners for each category.
For the wall posters, first place goes to...
Third year, class B with western films!
Next, for the refreshment booths, the
winners are second year, class D!
The Black Magic Café and consultations
were well received by all. First place!
Sadako!
Next we have the costume parade.
We've got this...
The drinks that second year, class B offered to the judges
were considered a bribe, and they therefore
received zero points for the event.
What?
We hope you will understand our decision.
Thank you for your patience, and we will
now proceed to the overall rankings!
What did you say?!
You listen up!
Hidden desires—
My hidden desires—!
Tuna! Sea urchin!
Abalone!
I can't believe we only ranked sixth...
But we got first place among the second years!
We were so close.
Without that bribe, I'm sure we would've
placed high in the parade too.
Yeah, Sadako's performance was amazing!
Oh right, the after party's at the usual place.
Okay.
Sawako.
My feelings aren't any different from yours.
We feel the same way, don't we?
I thought it was impossible...
But he didn't deny it.
This possibility that I've been holding on to is still there.
I like you!
...all of...
I want all of you.
Same here.
This is like a dream.
I've finally reached you.
There isn't anyone that means more to me than you do.
douka ima dake wa furimukanaide
Please don't look at me right now
yuugure sawagu kaze
The sun's set, the wind's blowing,
furesouna kyouri
and we're so close that we can almost touch
kimi wo mitsumeteru zutto
My gaze has always been fixed on you
kimi ga suki de
I like you
I've always liked you
kono omoi koi demo ii
I don't mind if this emotion is what they call love,
kizu tsuitemo ii
and I don't care if I get hurt by it
nando demo tsutaetai
I just want to tell you, over and over again
kimi ni todoke
I want to reach you
Preview
After the Festival
A blushing profile.
The gentle sea breeze.
Next time: After the Festival.