masshiro PAGE mekuru
I walk through the white pages of my storybook
tobidasu irodoru hajikeru
that's just waiting to be painted
mangekyou no fuukei
with a kaleidoscope of my experiences
From
Me
To
You
kizukeba STORY wa mada
This story has only
gikochinaku hajimatta bakkari
just barely begun
shinkokyuu wo mou ikkai
I take a deep breath
tabi suru kaze tsutsumikomu you ni senaka wo osu
and the wind wraps around me and urges me forward
aa yawarakakute atatakai kimi no te
Your hand is so warm held within mine
nigiri shimete sono kokoro no oku made todoku you ni
It reaches all the way into my heart
hohoenmi de kumeta nara nigirikaeshite kuretara
I can't see a brighter future
boku wa tada mae wo miteru
than you smiling and taking my hand as well
Unrequited Love
What? No way! What on earth?
Seriously! Even though she knows you like Koichi, Misato!
What's so good about Koichi anyway?
I'm sure Misato thinks he's cute.
She does, I'm sure!
Kurumi!
Wait, really? You don't like anyone, Kurumi?
But you're so cute! That's such a waste.
I'm so glad I got to become friends with you, Kurumi!
Yeah!
Me too!
I'm so glad we're all friends!
Wait, Miyagawa said he liked Kurumi?
How could he do that? Miki's had a crush on him for so long!
It's because Kurumi's been exchanging notes with him.
She doesn't like it when guys like someone else besides her.
That's why she always does this!
I can't believe she calls herself Kurumi when her name is really Ume.
I only became friends with her cause all the guys are
willing to talk to you once you mention her name.
Hey, when Kurumi gets a crush on someone, we'll get in her way, okay?
Since she got in all of ours!
Yeah, let's do it!
Yeah!
You're still here.
Is something wrong?
Nothing.
Really?
Yup. Are you staying after for practice?
Yup. Just came to pick something up.
I see.
Yeah, I did leave it here.
Good luck!
Thanks!
Are you really alright?
What's wrong?
This boy... he was different.
This boy, who had so many friends...
We're in the same class again!
He always saw me as me.
When I started to like him, I kept my
feelings hidden deep down inside of me.
But I've tried really hard to get him to fall for me too.
I've tried harder at that than I have at school.
I went to Kitahoro high school because he did.
Kazehaya!
We were in different classes, but...
What's up?
I was told to bring this printout to you, class rep!
Thanks!
Don't they look good together?
I always went to talk to him.
So that maybe one day, he'd look at me the same way I look at him.
Practice for the sports festival?
Yeah, it's a drag, but Kazehaya will be
there! Things always seem more fun with him.
Yeah! He got elected for sports festival
class rep before he knew what hit him!
Yeah!
Yeah, I heard that Kazehaya's class D's rep for the sports festival.
Really?
Then you should become our class rep, Kurumi!
Me?
Yeah! You totally should!
This could be your chance, Kurumi!
I told you, it's not like that!
I don't mind being class rep though.
Then just do that!
But I can't just elect myself! It's embarrassing!
Kazehaya! You were picked as a class rep too?
Oh, you were too!
Let's do this.
We both got the short stick this time, huh.
That seat's open.
Thanks.
Oh right, thanks for the CD earlier too.
No problem. There's actually one I'd like to borrow from you as well.
Sure. I'll bring it for you.
There's been a lot of talk about Sadako lately, hasn't there?
Yeah, everyone's gossiping about her.
I wonder what kind of girl she really is.
She's with Kazehaya a lot, isn't she?
Now that you mention it, yeah. I wonder if they're dating?
I'm sure that's not true!
It could be.
It wouldn't be that weird for Kazehaya to fall for her, right?
It would, it would!
Kazehaya's just talking to her because he's a nice guy!
And if he were to fall for someone, it'd definitely be you, Kurumi!
Now that's not possible!
What are you talking about? You two are so close!
It's just cause we went to the same middle school.
Why don't you just go out with him?
We're really not like that!
Maybe you don't think so, but what about him?
You're the reason I do things like that.
Kazehaya was changing right before my very eyes.
Yes, because Sawako pushed herself in between us!
Kazehaya?
Sawako, you're all sweaty!
Thank you...
Don't worry about it. There, all better.
Did you need something, Kurumi?
Oh no. I just wanted to talk to Sawako.
We finally got to know each other better recently!
Right, Sawako?
Ri—
We're friends now, right?
Lunch time already?
I need to do something about her.
Yeah, lunch time then nap time!
What's this?
I have no choice. This is the only way.
I want to thank you. Please meet me
behind the sports equipment room at noon.
Sawako Kuronuma
You see?
We should cheer them on.
Kazehaya... !
Why...
Why?!
Things didn't work out in the end.
I wonder why it couldn't have been me.
I've always, always liked him.
I've liked him for much longer than Sawako has.
Kazehaya...
I wonder what would've happened if I'd
confessed to him before he met Sawako?
No, I'm being stupid!
Even though I did my best, it was just impossible.
It was Kazehaya's decision, after all.
Kazehaya and I wouldn't make a good couple, would we?
No, that's not true—
Then I want you to support us.
You're the only one I've told about this.
Unless you think there's someone better for him.
No. I think you two would make a great couple.
Sawako! Then you'll—
But I can't. I wouldn't be able to fully
support you from the bottom of my heart.
Kazehaya's special to me too.
I'm sorry I can't agree.
I'm sorry I can't help you, but I understand how you feel!
So at least I could listen to you if—
How annoying.
Why isn't she backing off?
Can't she feel the difference between us?
That voice is coming from Kurumi's direction.
Is there someone else there behind her?
Sawako's a lucky girl.
But it's just so strange.
Kurumi!
Don't call me Kurumi anymore.
U-Ume?
Sawako...
Your name is going into my book of People Who've Called Me Ume.
People Who've
Called Me Ume
Sawako Kuronuma!
Is it okay if I call you that?
What's wrong with you?
I'm going.
Ume, wait!
Don't call me Ume!
Wait, then what should I call you?
Ume is the only thing I hate about myself.
Don't group yourself in with me.
You don't know anything about me.
I've liked Kazehaya since middle school.
I've tried so hard to talk to him, to
make sure he didn't get a girlfriend...
Y-You've worked so hard...
I mean, I...
Anyway. I know him better than anyone.
This isn't some two day crush.
I've always liked him!
I've always been waiting for him.
Sawako always faces everything and everyone straight on.
She faces me, and Kazehaya, the same way.
I told you, you're annoying!
You haven't worked for him at all! Why do
you deserve to be around him all the time?
I hate you!
I thought if it were you my competition,
there was no way I could lose!
I like him so, so much more than you do.
I do!
I think you're much cuter the way you are
now than you were when I first met you.
I know I'm cute!
But that doesn't matter!
If Kazehaya doesn't think so, what does it matter?
I know he doesn't like me.
I know because I've always been watching him.
Why did you come back?
I don't want you to see me like this.
Because you know him so well.
Because I thought we could understand each other.
You...
She's so dense.
Wait, do you think that Kazehaya possibly likes me?
Me? Who was friendless until recently?
Kazehaya doesn't judge people like that.
He's nice and always wants to help people.
He always gives people the benefit of the doubt.
When he laughs, you can't help but
feel better and laugh along with him.
Yeah! And he's serious when it matters.
He actually has a quick temper, but it's
because he cares about doing the right thing!
He's nice to both guys and girls.
He's honest,
and—
Why am I talking to you about this?!
I'm so happy we were able to talk like this.
I've never spoken like this to anyone before.
This was my best shot.
We just entered high school together.
People were finally supportive of us.
If I wanted to make him like me, it was now or never!
Yet...
It's all over now.
Kazehaya thinks I like Arapin.
No matter what I say now, it'll just look
like I'm denying it out of embarrassment!
I had planned on giving up at that point.
But then Sawako said..
That's no good.
I didn't like it when Kazehaya accidentally thought I liked Sanada.
But since it's a misunderstanding,
he'll understand if you talk to him.
Do you think he'd really understand if I told him the truth?
Are you an idiot?
See you!
Kaze—
Don't give up!
I don't want him to... misunderstand me!
Wait...
Wait, Kazehaya!
I don't like Pin!
I like you, Kazehaya.
I've always, always liked you, Kazehaya!
Kazehaya...
It's always been you.
I couldn't possibly like anyone else.
I'm sorry, Kurumizawa.
I'm sorry.
It was my fault.
Sorry.
But I have someone I like.
I like her more than anyone else.
I'm sorry.
I know. It's so obvious.
But did my confession make you feel happy at all? Even just a little?
Yes, it did.
Thank you.
Will you call me by my name? Just once?
Ume.
That typical old woman's name isn't that bad after all.
I didn't want to tell you at all, but
I guess not everything goes as planned.
As planned?
You have no taste in women, Kazehaya!
Bye bye!
I can't believe I told him.
That wasn't like me at all.
But ever since then,
I haven't had to use the book of People Who've Called Me Ume.
I wonder if he'll accept them from me.
Sawako will definitely make chocolates herself.
Ayane and Chizu probably won't.
Tomorrow's the last time.
I'm going with the expensive one!
douka ima dake wa furimukanaide
Please don't look at me right now
yuugure sawagu kaze
The sun's set, the wind's blowing,
furesouna kyouri
and we're so close that we can almost touch
kimi wo mitsumeteru zutto
My gaze has always been fixed on you
kimi ga suki de
I like you
I've always liked you
kono omoi koi demo ii
I don't mind if this emotion is what they call love,
kizu tsuitemo ii
and I don't care if I get hurt by it
nando demo tsutaetai
I just want to tell you, over and over again
kimi ni todoke
I want to reach you
Preview
valentine's day
I want to give them to him.
But I can't.
I can't stop hesitating.
Next time: Valentine's Day.