hikaru suiheisen
Just over the bright horizon,
s
t
r
U
hajimari to owari no
where the beginning and the end
s
t
r
U
tokeau soko wa
melt into one,
s
t
r
U
namida no furusato na no
lies the homeland of tears
s
t
r
U
furueteru te de
I've already pocketed
s
t
r
U
shinjirareru mono
my trembling hand
s
t
r
U
poketto ni tsumekonda
which holds my beliefs
s
t
r
U
kanata de yurameiteru shinkirou
A mirage shimmers in the distance
s
t
r
U
sora miagereba
I look to the sky
s
t
r
U
michibiitekureru you na
hoping it will show me the way
s
t
r
U
natsukashikute atsui hikari wo kureru
And it gives off a familiar, warm light
s
t
r
U
anata wa chiisaku te wo furu yo
You wave at me faintly
s
t
r
U
ikanakucha
I must go
s
t
r
U
mou nakanai yo shangurira
Don't cry anymore because Shangri-La,
s
t
r
U
aratana sekai he to daibu shiyou
a new world, is waiting for us
s
t
r
U
aoiro ni dakareta boku wa
As I'm embraced by its blue...
s
t
r
U
kono mune no takanari to tomo ni
My heart beats loudly
s
t
r
U
It feels weird to fight alongside the Japanese...
Pied Piper 01, are you ready?
Yes!
Moving into formation.
He keeps up all right. Not bad at all.
Huh?
Allied Forces incoming. Begin maneuvers!
Roger!
All clear in the direction of Hitoyoshi.
Maintain altitude at 3000.
How much fuel have we got?
To be honest, we're cutting it close.
The number of times we can scramble depends on Han Juno's father.
So we're not out of the woods yet, then.
We will be entering their territorial waters soon.
All ships stop! Reverse at full speeds!
Warning.
Your vessels are about to trespass on Japanese waters.
Please retreat immediately.
World To World
This is Fleur Blanc.
She has officially inherited the CEO position of our company.
The Allied Forces are repeatedly demanding the extradiction of team Pied Piper.
Of course we have no intentions of complying.
Thank you.
Let us discuss the details then.
First, let's discuss the replacement pilot for RA-301 Kyrie.
Sure. Can we see the list?
The emergency state warning has been lifted as of 4:30 PM.
The Allied Forces vessels that tried to enter our territorial waters
have accepted our warning and retreated.
I wonder if Okinawa used to be like this as well?
Being the enemy of the world sure puts you on your edge.
I guess.
Well done. I'm impressed.
I think the back should be a little tighter.
Really?
Well, it's Rebecca's, so—
Wanna go grab something to eat?
It's on me, President.
No, I'm going to head back to the hotel.
You can all just take it easy if you'd like.
Fleur, I'll be your bodyguard!
She's accepted her father's death?
It would seem so...
Anything about Elena?
Elena Peoples is currently affiliated with the American base on Guam.
No matter how you look at it, she's definitely a traitor.
I see.
Should I tell Ivica and the kids?
No, I'll tell them.
Sign: The Dolphin
It's so stuffy!
You're all so old, yet you're still IFO pilots?
Oh well, foreigners all look so old.
They're all Coral Carriers.
Even in the Allied Forces, they can only be found in this unit.
Stanley!
It's the result of the Big Blue World's research.
Coral Carriers have high IFO piloting aptitude even if they're adults.
I'm alone...
It's like I'm in one of those school life anime!
I'm Maggie Kwan.
Let's get along, girl-to-girl.
Are you a Coral Carrier too?
No way, I'm not that old...
In Hong Kong, we had the Chinese Plant in the South-China Sea,
so I grew up breathing trapar.
Just like you.
By the way, what does "Coral Carrier" mean?
Coral Carriers are people whose body was infected by the Scub Coral.
They initially treated it as if it were a disease...
But I've heard rumors that it's the result of human experiments that were performed
after we started cooperating with your company.
Don't hold back.
You must be hungry. Eat as much as you like.
This is the usual hangout for us pilots.
It might not suit the tastes of a foreigner though.
Not at all! It's all really good!
Then try this too.
Okay, thank you!
Does anything feel off your new board?
It works perfectly.
It's the fruit of the research conducted in hopes of getting the Mark I ourselves.
The maker wants you to test some new weapons too.
Oh right, you don't have FPs.
Not that we really miss them.
Those things are so cute!
I'm going to work then.
You're going to work every day, but what exactly are you doing?
A bit of this and that.
We all talk about the future of our world...
And I sing together with the Scub...
Hear that? The Scub sings!
Coral Carriers...
In the past few months, there's a boom in their numbers.
Most of them are from this area in Okinawa.
You were the first one of them, Naru.
Most of those people are gathered here on Iwato island now.
Around you, Naru.
Why are you looking at me as if I'm an alien?
We aren't all so different from the others.
Free the Scub!
The Scub is our friend!
We oppose the plants!
Destroy the plants!
After stopping the plant's operation, what do you plan on doing next?
Just leave the Scub Coral naturally as it is.
Then the planet will naturally be covered with trapar.
You're late, Naru!
Sign: Welcome to Japan,
Team Pied Piper!
Now that the Allies have thrown you away, you come crawling to us?
But you'll just be used as a pawn again.
He stinks of booze!
Man...
You talkin' to me?!
Nakamura!
Behave yourself.
Huh? Don't get so high'n'mighty just coz you're from Chukyo!
I'm a proper Japanese too y'know!
Independence my ass!
What, my dad and my grandpa called this place their "second home"...
But as soon as the trapar business boomed, they ran back to Naha right away!
But I'm not going back!
You're Okinawan?!
Huh? I'm Japanese!
I'll make this country the world leader!
Yeah, yeah, I get it.
The world leader! You get it?
Sure, yeah, whatever you say.
This world is mistaken.
Truth used to say that all the time.
I've been thinking so too, ever since I was a brat.
I want to correct this mistaken world.
That's why I joined the Japanese Army!
But is Truth's way the right way?
Throwing the world into chaos...
What... was that just now?
Could it be that you're from another world too?
And so I ended up coming here from the world where there's a heart carved into the Moon.
So I'm...
Like a slider, or a traveler from an alternate dimension?
Like... that sounds really cool.
LFOs...
Where am I?
Hey, do you know Ao?
What happened with the Quartz?
Eureka!
I've finally found you! Take me with you to the other world!
Don't you remember me?! Look!
Ah, you're the girl from the other day?
You've grown so much.
The other day?! It was five years ago!
You left me there all on my own...
Five years ago by the Caribbean Sea!
I didn't have a choice. You were about to get caught up in a Scub Burst.
I had to take you—
Take me back!
Take me back to the other world!
I'm sorry...
Given the way I am right now, I can't stay in any timespace for very long...
So I can't take you back to your original time either.
My original time?
What do you mean?!
I was talking about the place where there's a heart carved into the Moon!
Oh, you saw that?
But I think you've gotten the wrong idea.
I saved you in this world, but in an earlier time.
You saw my world as we moved in time...
I've got it all wrong?
Where's Ao? Is he fighting with the Scub Coral?
Screw you!
Elena?
No, that's not my name!
I came... I came from that world... That world...
My wife was born in mainland Okinawa.
Ten years ago, when she was visiting her home with our kids,
a Secret killed them all.
But now I know it's actually all because of the Scub Coral.
Let's work together to save this world.
Um, I...
I hear you resigned. What are you planning?
Calm down, Nakamura.
I still have my plan.
I'll make the Japanese army the strongest army, so Japan can rule the world.
I've learned about human history since I came to this world.
Hitler, Napoleon, Alexander...
You're not the first person to embrace those ideas, but—
Farewell. I owe you one.
2020, there was a Scub Burst in the Caribbean Sea.
1981, there was another Burst in the same area.
Many children fell victim to it, and some of their bodies were never found.
All members of No. 204 Special Flier Unit: prepare for deployment.
There's a new Scub Burst on Indonesian territory...
If Eureka is moving from Burst to Burst...
I have to tell Elena!
Elena! Elena!
Elena, respond!
We've arrived at the target area. Altitude 5000 feet.
What's that?
Secrets are attacking other Secrets?
When a new Scub appears, we emerge automatically.
But we have taken responsibility for our actions, as per our contract.
Then we have nothing to do?
Chief, aren't you forgetting something?
Quartz retre—!
Credo?
But team Goldilocks are gone...
It's me, Ao.
Elena?!
So you've really joined the Allied Forces?
Stop, Nirvash! It's Elena!
The fuck? Normalfag showing off? Or not?
Just that "privilege of the chosen one" bullshit?
Well, fuck that!
Elena!
Stop it! What's wrong with you?
Shut up!
You and your mom keep looking down on me!
Still nothing?
You son of a Eureka!
Stop locking on!
Don't let Ao shoot Elena! Get between them!
Elena... I see!
Don't shoot, Ao...
What are you saying?!
I agree. The Allied Forces must not get the Quartz aggregate.
Listen, Elena!
I looked you up! What that Eureka woman was saying is true!
This voice... are you Maggie Kwan?
I found your people! You are from—
No! I'm going back!
To that wonderful world!
This isn't my world! This isn't me!
Listen to me, you idiot!
You're from this world! You can't go back to where you don't belong!
I see... So that's why you wanted me to shoot you...
Elena, I...
Boring.
I didn't want such a boring answer!
No! This setting is just wrong!
I'm a chosen child, with a bit too much pink, but many secrets!
It's my fate that you'll take me home, Ao!
Elena...
Don't call me that!
It's a lie... a fake...
You're not a fake!
You're you!
Was it a lie too when we fought together, when you saved me?
Shut up!
Listen! I want to be with you, Elena!
Ao...
Fleur too! The Chief too! Noah too!
We should all be together!
You're part of the family I met as I'm looking for Mom!
Let's go home together...
Elena...
I knew it...
I loved you because I could never reach you...
No matter how far I go... It's still the same sky...
That light...
Don't tell me it's Truth?!
Fire it...
Fire it... Fire it! Fire it!
Destroy! You must destroy!
You must destroy everything!
To be continued.
futashikana*
s
*T/L Note: I'm so uncertain
boku
no sekai
ga ima*
v
*T/L Note: In the blink of an eye,
mabataku
ma ni
kawari-
hajimete
hirogaru*
A
*T/L Note: my whole world started changing and opening up.
ano hi mitsuketa yume no tsuzuki wa doko*
A
*T/L Note: That day, I found out where my dream continues
sugu ni
sagashite
miseru yo*
A
*T/L Note: I'll show you its sequel now
ima mo boku
dake wa
oboeteirun da*
N
*T/L Note: Right now, I'm the only one who still remembers
natsukashii
nukumori*
.
*T/L Note: that familiar warmth
saa
mou
ikou
ka*
A
*T/L Note: Now let's get going
machiu-
keteru
unmei ni*
)
*T/L Note: I was frozen with fear
tachisukumi
obieteta*
H
*T/L Note: thinking of the fate that awaited me
mou
kess-
hite
mayo-
wanai
you ni*
A
*T/L Note: I'll become so strong that I won't
tsuyoku
natte
yuku yo*
Z
*T/L Note: be uncertain ever again
nido to modorenai kako mo ashita kara kate ni shite*
A
*T/L Note: The past that can't be written will support me from tomorrow on
sou
yatte
noriko-
ete yuku
no sa*
q
*T/L Note: I'll overcome it all
sou shite boku
wa boku ni naru*
A
*T/L Note: and I'll become myself
sou shite boku
wa boku ni naru*
Don't repost to any manga readers!
You have to sign up for our forum to download!
Preview
Galaxy 2 Galaxy