Love Forbidden
I declare love to be forbidden!
The Order
Against Love
Who is that guy?
Maybe he's part of Neo-Deava.
He looks like a juggler.
Or a clown.
What do you mean, love forbidden?
But the wall's finally gone!
Yeah!
Welcome back, Ms. Chairman.
Chairman?!
Ms. Chairman, please enjoy these donuts.
Thank you.
This little girl is the chairman?
Yes.
And that is Neo-Deava's High Commander, Fudo Zen.
The High Commander and the Chairman have been on a journey
to unravel the mysteries of Aquarion.
I suppose their return means they've found something.
I'm afraid I have been told nothing
about either these mysteries or the forbidden Aquarion itself.
Miss Suomi, do you know the story of Apollon and Silvie?
Of course. Everyone knows that fairy tale.
I think there was even a movie about it.
It was called Skies of Aquaria.
Correct. 12,000 years ago,
after they defeated the Dark Angels,
Apollon and Silvie were separated.
But fierce passions can bring destruction.
Apollon and Silvie were torn from each other and still yearn to meet again.
And this causes the modern Aquarion to go berserk.
Berserk?
That's why Neo-Deava sealed away Aquarion's full power.
You already know that very well, don't you, Mister Donar?
Yeah, and I wish I didn't.
But our enemies are growing stronger.
We at Neo-Deava are forced to rethink our strategies.
You're right.
We have no choice. The forbidden powers are all we have.
The donut is an empty space surrounded by a ring.
You must eat the empty space at your center, Donar Dantes.
osore
Even if you're scared
living your life   don't give up now   keep moving on
Just live your life, don't give up now, keep moving on
kimi wo dakishimeru nandomo nandomo nandomo
And I'll come for you over and over and over again
ashita boku wa kimi ni deau darou
We'll find each other soon enough
wazukana hoshiakari wo tayori ni
By the faintest glimmer of starlight
boku ni wa kimi ga wakaru yo wakaru yo
I know you, I know you
sen'oku no toki wo koe futari hiraku densetsu no tobira
It's been billions of years, but now we can open the door to our legend
naraku no ao tobikoete
I crossed over the deep blue void
kimi to hai ni naru tame
so I could burn to ash along with you
nagaki rinne wo kanashimi tsurete tabi shitekitanda
I've had a long journey on the vast wheel of fate, gathering sorrows along the way
zenryoku de mikansei kimi no tonari de
I'm not perfect, but I'm giving all I have
kawaita kokoro hodoke chi wo nagasu kedo
If I open my fragile heart to you, I know I'll bleed...
soba ni iru yo zutto yorisotte zutto
But I'll always be with you, always be in your arms
futari hikari no fune ni noru
We'll get on a shining ship of light
kaze no hajimari no oto kanadeyou
And call forth the wind with our voices
Pardon me, Jin. Izumo wants to see you.
Wha— A reproduction of Alisia!
Where did you get this?
What does Izumo want?
Yeah?
Jin, the data you brought back has been analyzed.
The Machine Angel's parameters depend on its form.
That's what I thought.
It fought completely differently pre and post transformation.
One more thing.
When it used that last attack,
we detected readings consistent with a Rare Igura.
A Rare Igura was in that thing?
Izumo, Kagura's Mithra Gnis has deployed.
That impetuous fool.
Don't tell me he's going to Vega with just his Gnis.
The warp gate is opening!
What?
The Mithra Gnis has entered interdimensional space!
Who opened the gate?
Did he wake up already?
In short,
starting today, Holy Angel Academy is a coeducational school.
That means all of you are in the same class.
I know it might take some time to adjust,
but please try to not let this cause problems.
Wow! It's Shrade in the flesh!
Even the air is polluted...
Your first assignment together is a social field observation.
You will go out into Neo-Kowloon in mixed teams.
Understood?
Sounds like a waste of time.
Wow! We're diving right into the good stuff!
Mikono...
Ow!
Amata! We're in homeroom! Stop clowning around!
What is this?
Please take a handout.
Walk along the promenade...
Bungee jump off the Kowloon Tower...
Tea time at a hotel with an ocean view?
Isn't this...
The standard Neo-Kowloon date plan?
You'll need these, too.
What are these?
It looks stupid.
What about mine?
The chairman has exempted you.
Here are your groups.
Group A: Cierro, Enji, Yoka.
Group B: Malloy, Aika, Mist.
Please give me a cute one, please give me a cute one...
Group C: Andy, Mix, Yunoha.
Who's Yunoha?
You got someone cute like you wanted, didn't you?
She sure is cute.
For a doll! A cat doll, no less!
That's a cat?
I can't believe I'm with such a noisy, annoying boy.
Sure, she's fiery, but she's freaking hot!
And man, look at those big bangs!
What the hell?
The next group is Shrade, Cayenne, and Sazanka.
Looks like it's us, my friend.
Don't call me that.
But you put my soul at ease.
You have a soul?
You don't mean that.
The final group is...
Amata, Mikono, and Zessica.
Uh, hi.
All the groups will go separately from here.
Don't miss the boat back.
Understood?
Yes, ma'am.
Many of the Elements are getting electrocuted.
They really are young.
What are these bands?
They monitor the Element's vital signs, heart rate, perspiration,
and release an electrical charge if they pass a certain limit.
I think it's cruel!
I can see no purpose to this foolish training!
There is one, though.
It's critical for getting the most power out of Aquarion
without reliving the Aquarion Disaster.
The Aquarion Disaster?
Nine years ago, when Aquarion was
deployed to counter the first charge,
it went berserk during combat.
Two of the Elements went missing in action,
and the sole survivor, Donar Dantes,
lost both his arms and the woman he loved.
Let me feel them...
Danger Zone
The melody of love is ephemeral...
Aquarion resonates with the emotions of its Elements,
and amplifies their energy to fight.
Its power is directly based on the intensity of those emotions.
Do you know what the most intense emotion is that a person can have, Miss Suomi?
Hate? Jealousy?
No.
It's love.
Love?
But even in their own minds, they cannot let their feelings actually become love.
If they ever find themselves truly in love, Aquarion will go berserk.
Just like what happened to Donar and his beloved.
But if they can stay just at the very edge of love,
Aquarion will unleash its vast powers.
The relationship between Amata Sora and
Mikono Suzushiro is just short of that border.
That's how they used the forbidden attack.
This armband is made to catch and prevent the Elements from feelings of love.
Our goal is power just short of the berserk.
This is special training to pull out of love!
Just as they say.
I have to keep my students from
suffering the same thing I went through.
Especially Amata.
He reminds me of myself when I was young.
That's why I'm here.
It's adorable!
Look, Shush, it's a cat!
Cute? Mikono is way cuter...
Ow!
Amata?
What happened?
My butt!
Don't forget that love is forbidden, Amata.
Can't take my eyes off that kid for a minute.
Something smells.
"Observe the people by the poolside of a classy hotel".
And they even bought us these
swimsuits. Not that I don't appreciate it...
But seriously, what's up with the doll?
Well, here I am.
Ow... huh?
Today's special training is also a simulation of Element groupings.
If the chairman is right, Mix would make an excellent soldier
because boys don't affect her at all.
Wrong. Girls like her completely close themselves off from others.
That makes it hard to get them to the edge of love.
So why are Shrade, Cayenne, and Sazanka a team?
They even told us what to order when we went out to eat.
This is ridiculous.
Here is your watermelon juice.
Um, is there only supposed to be one?
That's what was ordered.
Well, let's drink.
What?
This is part of our training.
We don't have much of a choice.
I guess he's shy around girls. Please excuse him.
Okay...
Shrade and Cayenne drinking juice from the same cup!
There's nothing that can knock Shrade off balance.
Impressive. But it looks like Sazanka gets her shocks from different things.
Miss Chairman, about Shrade's practical combat record...
I'm aware of his health concerns.
Shrade Elan hangs on the very edge of life.
In a way, there's no better place to find feelings on the edge.
How cold.
The combination we have to watch most closely is...
Amata, Zessica, and Mikono.
But Mikono hasn't manifested any Element powers yet!
If the ring does not surround anything, a donut is just a lump.
Mikono Suzushiro forms the ring where the donut surrounds emptiness.
But for everything sweet...
Oww!
Are you okay?
Damn. If he keeps at it, there won't be enough blow darts in the world.
Amata's heart starts racing when he looks at me.
Oh, Amata.
You look happy, Mikono.
Is it 'cause he likes you?
No!
You sure?
You know, I like innocent ones like him.
Okay, next is...
Amata!
You're with me!
Come on!
Hey, I can make him fly too!
Amata! You'll fly for anyone, won't you?
It's not just anyone, it's me!
Ow!
What's the matter, Shush?
Oh my god! Who is that?
I think he's cool!
Smells good.
Are you all right? We can take a break if you want.
Are you still mad about the last fight?
You play with peoples' feelings. I'm not listening to you.
Please forgive me. My whole life is but being played with.
By an Abductor called disease.
Three bungee jumping tickets, please.
I have to do it too?
It's training.
You can stay back if you're scared.
We'll just have fun together!
Quit it!
That's so cool!
Fine. I know when I'm a third wheel.
Enjoy, you two.
Mikono, wait!
Mikono, wait! I—
You're such a creep, Amata!
You've been flying for Zessica all day!
I thought I was the only one...
What was that last thing?
Go away!
Mikono!
A fiery sunset...
Just like in...
Skies of Aquaria!
This song!
Why does this feel so nostalgic?
I met you just a few days ago.
But I feel it's been a very long time.
It's weird...
I don't think it's weird.
I think we were destined to meet.
Are you okay?
I can't believe I said that!
Forget it! Forget the whole thing!
Do I have to?
I don't want to forget it!
Mikono...
This is bad! Mikono's love index is shooting up!
Oh no!
They're almost in love!
Mister Donar! Stop them!
Damn it! They're out of dart range!
Amata!
Danger Zone
Stop! Amata, Mikono! Don't do this!
The scent of forbidden love is as sweet as honey.
But honey is sure to attract ants...
Found you.
You stink.
You stink deliciously.
Mikono!
This is...
It's not love.
a forbidden meeting.
Forbidden
Meeting
Mikono!
kaze ni ubawareta wake janai
We weren't spirited away on the wind
katamichi bun no yuuki de bokura
We knew we could never return, and found the courage
higeki wo ukeireru
to accept the hardship
kokoro ga koko ni atta hazu no kuudou
There's an emptiness where my heart used to be
motto boku ga ookikereba
If only I was stronger
kimi wo mirai wo sukueta darou ka
I could have saved you, and our future...
taisetsu na hito wo mamoru sube ga tatta hitotsu shika motenai
I only know of one way to keep the people I love
sonna anata ga haguretadayou sora
And you left me and disappeared into the sky
anata ijou no hito ni deaenai
I'll never find anyone like you again
tsuki ni aragau nagai furea
A long flare reaches out against the moon
hajimaru mo sezu owaru monogatari
The story ends before it could even begin
kizutsukiuru yawarakasa
So soft, so fragile
tojikometa senritsu kanaderu hodo
I will call up the melody locked away
utau hodo kowareru hodo ni
And sing it until I destroy myself
anata ga koishii
That's how much I love you
Let us talk about seven days from now.
The upcoming scherzando battle
will be the dal segno into darkness.
Isn't that right, my friend?
Next time on Aquarion Evol: The Agitato of Life.
Next Time
The Agitato of Life