The Legendary Forbidden Union of the End Special
After 12,000 years...
A new legend is born...
Apollon, do you remember the day the world began?
Due to a miracle, the sacred and formless void
was filled with over a billion galaxies, each with over a billion stars.
A miracle?
Yes. The miracle of our meeting above this world.
Silvie!
Now we begin to walk a new path.
Skies of Aquaria again?
Sorry, sir! I'll clean up right—
You're the only reason it keeps getting shown, you know.
No one else cares about it one bit.
I'll never forget how lovely you smell.
What do you like so much about this movie, anyway?
I bet you fancy Alisia, the girl who played Silvie.
You can't just watch as destiny flies off...
When I see her, that's all I can think.
You're a strange one.
I'll take over loading the films.
Go take a break, Amata.
Just clean up the seats before you go.
Thank you, sir!
I'll be waiting for you.
Even if I have to wait for 12,000 years.
Damn, there's still trash down here.
This sucks.
E-Excuse me...
I'm sorry! I'll leave!
Wait!
Are you a fan... of Skies of Aquaria?
Oh, no. This is the first time I've seen it.
Oh. Okay.
Well then.
Wait!
Could you please, um, tell me your name? Maybe?
I'm Mikono Suzushiro.
My name is Amata! Amata Sora!
Oh.
Um...
Yes?
Thanks for coming today.
Excuse me...
Do you sell posters for this movie?
Sorry. It's over ten years old. They don't make them anymore.
Then, would you mind talking to me for a while?
I want to hear more about Skies of Aquaria.
Really?
I need to finish up some work, but...
I'll be waiting for you.
Even if I have to wait for 12,000 years.
I'm kidding.
I just wanted to say that.
Damn it! No! Not now!
Do you mind waiting just outside?
I'll be out in five, no, three minutes!
Three in each should be enough.
I can't believe she spoke to me.
And it's a cute girl to boot. I must be dreaming.
Stop! Don't go! Don't go away!
I could only watch as destiny flew away.
But I'm different now.
Don't freak out, Amata.
She did say...
I'll be waiting for you.
Even if I have to wait for 12,000 years.
When this song was composed, I'm sure no one even imagined
that the Aquarias would have to go into battle.
Then the Abductors came through the Dimension Gates.
They've destroyed our cities and taken away our people.
We still don't know why they do this.
In fact, we know nothing about them.
But if we, the Daughters of Heaven, work together, we—
Excuse me, Miss Zessica!
Yeah?
You have deployed four times and
experienced Union in an Aquaria, correct?
Tell your fellow Daughters about the rapture
of being chosen by the holy guardian.
Oh yeah, about that.
It feels really good.
Of course it does!
Offering your purity to an Aquaria is pure—
But I'm sure Union with boys is so much more intense than doing it with girls!
Impure thoughts!
Fortunately, the Guize Stone protects the purity of the Daughters of Heaven.
Impure Unions are completely impossible!
But—
An Aquaria is a sacred cradle.
It cannot brook a woman who has been sullied by a man's touch.
Exactly!
Let us on, mister!
New China City's traffic core was paralyzed in an Abductor attack. Repairs are underway...
The Abductors attacked again.
Sounds like it.
Those Abductors are making this place too quiet.
The theater's customers are drying up.
They could come out anywhere at any time.
The Aquarias fight them off, but they just keep on coming.
Abductors or not, I can't stand being cooped up at home.
I have to get some sun!
That's some optimistic thinking.
Most people call it stupid.
Are you okay?
What the hell is that?!
I'm sorry!
This is my cat, Shush.
I think he likes being around here.
That's a cat?
Of course it's a cat!
Kind of a weird-looking cat.
I found him running from the Abductors.
Oh yeah, tell me about the movie!
All right.
Skies of Aquaria.
It's based on a book about a war with the Dark Angels
that supposedly took place a long time ago.
That children's story about what
happened 12,000 years ago?
Yeah, the movie didn't do that well,
but the theme song won awards at film festivals.
Oh, I love that song!
The singer was the girl who played Silvie...
Her name's Alisia, right?
She's a great actress, she seemed really nice,
and she's so pretty!
Yeah, she's pretty...
She's so pretty it's sad.
Aah! Shush, don't eat the whole thing!
Aww...
Is that all you got, maggots?
You aren't fit to lick my boots.
You can't pilot an Aquaria if you don't have guts!
You hear me, you worms? Guts!
Pick up the slack or I'll taze your worthless asses!
You're not supposed to miss, Cayenne.
I just slipped up.
Were you having another vision?
What was it this time?
A wedding in mourning clothes.
Mourning clothes?
Damn it! If I had girls cheering for me,
I would be much more motivated!
If only the Berlin wasn't—
Andy! You're not thinking of sneaking to the other side again, are you?
Of course not, Commander Donar!
You're gonna need something a little stronger than a taze.
How about something like this?
Ow! Ow! You're already doing that!
Man, I thought I could get into Neo-Deava and score Unions with all the hot chicks.
I'm so close, but...
I haven't even seen one yet, let alone talked to one...
This... is...
This is a complete disaster!
Did you know, Amata?
Supposedly, somewhere, there's a school that trains Elements,
the people who pilot the Aquarias.
Only people who've been chosen by the Aquarias and granted special powers can go there.
People like Apollon and Silvie.
Amata, have you ever wanted to pilot an Aquaria?
I guess I've thought about it.
But I'd never be chosen by anybody.
I'm totally useless.
Oh, well...
Me too.
I'm completely useless.
We're a useless pair!
I'm gonna go to the bathroom!
Go on ahead! I'll catch up!
Respond, Kagura. Stop fooling around.
That Mithra Gnis is just a test model.
The objective of this mission is strictly information gathering.
It smells good.
This must be Vega.
Eight, nine, ten.
"Useless pair," she says.
Depressing words, but when she says them so cheerfully...
I feel happy.
How long ya gonna be in there?
Daddy, I can't hold it om anymore! I gotta go!
I'm so sorry!
I'll be out right away!
What's going on?
Abductors!
Mikono!
This way! To the shelter!
It's an Aquaria!
The Abductors just don't know when to quit!
Every time we chase 'em off, they come back with more!
Enough with the chitchat, Andy.
We'll intercept them with the Aquaria Type-M!
Roger that.
May the legend guide our hands.
They've certainly brought quite a party with them.
There's heavy damage at ground zero.
Mr. Principal, I mean Commander!
Don't you think those boys out there have terrible discipline?
Discipline? As if you could claim your girls are any better!
A large Abductor unit is approaching the battlefield!
There's no data on it! We've never seen it before!
What?
What is that thing?
We've never seen that machine before!
It's fast!
This thing's on a different level from the other Abductors!
It's stronger and faster than anything we've faced!
We're reading vital signs from inside the enemy machine!
What?
It's piloted!
A being from another dimension!
Damn you!
It's fighting in circles around the Aquaria.
It's like that Abductor's playing with it!
This is bad!
The Vectors are taking heavy damage!
Tachyon levels falling!
Mr. Principal! I mean, Commander!
What?
Understood. Roger.
We're authorized to deploy the Type-F.
What?
Are you serious?
We're going to have the Type-M and
the Type-F operating at the same time?
Commander! You know this is forbidden!
We can't let the Type-M be destroyed.
Get that Type-F out there.
Target acquired!
Missiles, locked on!
The Type-F?
We meet at last, boys.
Boys are so rough when they fight. It just looks disgusting.
Cayenne! It's really you!
Look! Girls!
Professor, is this okay?
We're in trouble now.
We can only pray that the worst does not come to pass:
The boys and girls together in Union.
No matter how close they get, they are doomed to never touch.
The barrier of chastity, the Guize Stones will see to that!
Well, isn't that funny. The new prey smells different.
We'll catch him in a pincer attack!
Got it! Don't screw up!
Hold still already!
Damn, he's tough!
Stupid boys! Get out of our way!
What'd you say?
Are they even trying to cooperate?
Not likely.
This is their first time.
What is it doing?
Get us down, Mix!
Roger!
Are you okay, Mikono?
Amata! You're bleeding!
Don't worry about it.
But...
This is just my body... it's nothing...
I'd rather my body get hurt... than my heart...
Type-M, do you read? Come back us up!
Not happening! Malloy's taken serious damage!
His machine's out of power!
You're pathetic! You boys can't even—
Watch out!
It's on all fours!
That's...
What's going on?
Huh?
Mikono!
Amata! Stop! You're hurt!
Their aura levels are dropping sharply!
What?
The Unions are breaking!
The Aquarias!
I can't hold back any longer.
What?
Mix! Sazanka!
Andy!
What are you doing? Who told you to come back?
I dunno! I got pulled back here!
I can still fight!
Mix?
The Aquarias ejected the Elements on its own?
I'm sorry, Mikono.
Amata? Sorry for what?
I just wanted to protect you!
I'm sorry!
Fly!
The Wings of the Sun!
Vital signs from inside Vector Z!
Someone snuck in?
Did a terrorist hijack the Vector?
Is that a boy and a girl? But how?
Quickly! Eject them!
Yes, ma'am!
I can't! Their life energy has merged with the Vector's power!
What if those two were called by...
Aquarion?
Impossible!
Where are we?
This must be a Vector cockpit.
How?
I don't know how...
But I feel like I know
what I have to do!
Amata?
We've gotta stop him!
I know already!
Shatter the name of falsehood.
And as it shatters, speak.
Speak the name of truth!
And so, you will inherit a new legend!
The name of truth...
The name of truth?
Yes. I have to speak the name of truth.
Genesis Union!
GO! Aquarion!
What?
Did he say Aquarion?
What does that mean?
Aquarion. He knows the forbidden name...
No! Stop! This Union...
I've never felt like this before...
Commander, what is Aquarion? Tell me!
It's all right! They have the Guize Stones!
They can't complete the forbidden Union!
I'm being torn apart!
If this keeps up, our rules and our feelings will be torn apart!
We'll be torn apart... and then burst!
I'm going to burst! Something in me is going to burst...
It's breaking!
What is that thing?
Aquarion is... evolving!
Aquarion Evol!
What's that smell?
Something smells... awful.
The forbidden name, engraved now unto a new body.
Aquarion Evol!
The legend of the end... is about to begin.
Aquarion?
My brain is boiling over...
It's pumping through my veins.
Now I know what that smell was...
Aquarion Evol?
Aquarion, the forbidden...
It's using Vector Z as the head.
Who knew the Aquarias had another form?
It's filthy!
You said impure Unions couldn't happen!
The seal has been broken.
Thanks to those two.
Amata! What's going on?
Are we in Aquarion?
What does "Evol" mean?
Mikono, I...
Mikono! Is that you?
Cayenne!
Get away from him!
Who are you?
A terrorist who hijacked an Aquaria?
A terrorist?
You're wrong!
Amata isn't—
You be quiet!
What's going on? A couple of civilians are the head?
Professor! Override the Union from headquarters!
We're trying!
Status?
No good! It just won't respond to our commands!
I've seen this before.
You have?
Mr. Principal! I mean, Commander!
What is Aquarion?
We purposely separated the boys from the girls into Aquaria Type-M and Type-F.
But now male and female are together as one; a complete being.
But can a mortal use the weapon of a god?
What's the matter? Done already?
Come on, get up and fight me!
What are you doing, you moron?
You're not helping!
Stop! Please, stop!
Let's get out of here! We can't fight him!
Let's get out! You can get us out of here, right?
Hey, you! What are you talking about?!
Amata! We have to escape!
What can a useless pair like us do?
Be quiet, Mikono!
Mikono...
Enemy reinforcements!
They're not little ones either.
Three large units confirmed!
What are you doing here?
Master Kagura, we have official orders.
Please return to Altair with us immediately.
Did that geezer Izumo send you?
We've already found Rare Iguras.
Further combat would be meaningless.
Combat isn't meaningless until I say it is!
Damn it! What do I do?
Enough sitting around!
I'll show you how to fight!
First, unlock the lever, like this.
Whoa!
Zessica's Element power was channeled through the machine!
Her power is resonating with the boy's!
So this is a mixed Union.
Commander, the Aquaria has powers we've never seen before!
Forbidden powers.
Master Kagura!
You're holding me back!
What?!
You're not using this, are you?
Please stop already!
The hell?
What is he?
I can smell you...
and I'm gonna stick my fangs into you.
He stole a part from another machine!
He's moving like an animal... or a monster!
No...
Mikono...
No... no... no!
What's with her?
She's done nothing but whine this whole time!
This is a battle! Suck it up!
Mikono's just a girl.
Can I even protect her?
Mikono!
What just happened?
Is that a funeral procession?
The wedding in mourning clothes.
This is the dark vision I had.
A wedding?
That's his Element power, the prophecy of despair.
He foresees terrible things that will happen to those around him.
How come we can see his vision?
It's Aquarion.
It has reclaimed its terrible, forbidden name,
and is showing us the prophecy.
This is the disaster foretold in the prophecy.
The terrible Union of despair!
Mikono?
Why me?
Who is that guy? Show us your face!
Who are you?
Master Kagura!
I know you're in there!
You smelly wench!
I'm going to get you!
Watch out!
This is your fault, kid!
You caused this worthless Union!
You dragged Mikono in with you!
This entire disaster is your damn fault!
You're right.
It is my fault.
Whenever I get excited, I fly.
This has happened ever since childhood.
Everyone else hates me for it.
It even took her away from me.
I never wanted to use my power again.
But I wanted to protect Mikono, so...
But...
I just put her into even more danger.
I should have known that I can't protect her.
I'm just useless.
Amata...
Come out, you smelly wench!
Shields falling! Aquarion's not going to last much longer!
To inherit a legend is to become a legend.
Are you prepared to do that, Amata Sora?
I'm sorry.
I called us a useless pair, and said that you're like me.
But you're amazing, Amata.
We've only just met, but you're willing to protect me.
Even though I'm weak, and all I ever do is cry.
Mikono...
Thank you.
And I'm sorry.
Mikono's hand...
It's small...
Smooth...
Warm...
And soft!
What the...
No way!
Aquarion is... flying!
That acceleration isn't all coming from Aquarion!
They're almost into orbit!
It must be that boy's Element Power!
Whoa!
Is he dead yet?
Damn you!
A Dimension Gate!
Kagura.
I'm sorry, but you're out of time.
Izumo! But I...
"Can still fight"? This is no time for jokes.
Just admit you've lost and come back already.
Fine!
Hey!
Amata?
Amata!
Cayenne!
You're not nearly good enough for Mikono.
Cayenne. Zessica.
Bring the boy and girl back to base.
Roger on the boy, but the girl's useless to us.
We can't just let someone who has been inside Aquarion leave.
Fine.
I finally found...
the one person who'll wait for me.
Perhaps that flying boy is...
No, he couldn't be.
The wild child's back.
Jin.
What did you do to my Gnis?
And how was the harvest?
I found one.
My very own wench.
kaze ni ubawareta wake janai
We weren't spirited away on the wind
katamichi bun no yuuki de bokura
We knew we could never return, and found the courage
higeki wo ukeireru
to accept the hardship
kokoro ga koko ni atta hazu no kuudou
There's an emptiness where my heart used to be
motto boku ga ookikereba
If only I was stronger
kimi wo mirai wo sukueta darou ka
I could have saved you, and our future...
taisetsu na hito wo mamoru sube ga tatta hitotsu shika motanai
I only know of one way to keep the people I love
sonna anata ga haguretadayou sora
And you left me and disappeared into the sky
anata ijou no hito ni deaenai
I'll never find anyone like you again
tsuki ni aragau nagai furea
A long flare reaches out against the moon
hajimaru mo sezu owaru monogatari
The story ends before it could even begin
kizutsukiuru yawarakasa
So soft, so fragile
tojikometa senritsu kanaderu hodo
I will call up the melody locked away
utau hodo kowareru hodo ni
And sing it until I destroy myself
anata ga koishii
That's how much I love you
Unions are supposed to be really hard.
So it's okay if you're not very good the first time.
Next time on Aquarion Evol:
Measure of Excitement ★ Rapid Rise!
Next Time
Measure of Excitement ★ Rapid Rise