Kokoro
masshiro PAGE mekuru
I walk through the white pages of my storybook
Incoming Text
tobidasu irodoru hajikeru
that's just waiting to be painted
mangekyou no fuukei
with a kaleidoscope of my experiences
From
Me
To
You
kizukeba STORY wa mada
This story has only
gikochinaku hajimatta bakkari
just barely begun
shinkokyuu wo mou ikkai
I take a deep breath
tabi suru kaze tsutsumikomu you ni senaka wo osu
and the wind wraps around me and urges me forward
aa yawarakakute atatakai kimi no te
Your hand is so warm held within mine
nigiri shimete sono kokoro no oku made todoku you ni
It reaches all the way into my heart
hohoenmi de kumeta nara nigirikaeshite kuretara
I can't see a brighter future
boku wa tada mae wo miteru
than you smiling and taking my hand as well
Just Give Up
Sadako's
Black
Magic
The herbs I picked look like they've dried pretty nicely.
Does anyone want to try a taste?
You guys should try it!
Or you could make Joe drink it later!
Good idea!
The black curtain for the café has
been ordered and will be delivered.
The mural and the wall poster should be finished on time.
Whoa. We're so behind!
Yeah.
If we only work during school, I don't think we'll finish on time.
I think we will.
Hey, Sadako still hasn't come back.
It's okay!
I just saw her earlier.
Yeah! She looked like she wasn't feeling
too well, but she said not to worry.
Yeah!
Oh, what's that herb you have there?
This is the chameleon plant and Thunberg's geranium .
They're good for treating diuresis and constipation, I think.
Chizu, do you want to try some?
Sure!
Here Andy, take this one too.
Thanks.
Oh, wow.
Hey Ryu!
Sorry I haven't been able to help out.
It's alright. You couldn't have skipped practice!
Yeah, you guys have summer preliminaries
right after the school festival, don't you?
Hey, what were doing about the bottom part over here?
Which part?
Here.
Were we going to run wire through it for reinforcement?
I don't know… You'd have to ask Kazehaya.
Where is that guy?
It's not like him to skip.
Shota!
Ryu.
Sorry. Everyone's already started working, haven't they?
Yeah.
I think there was something they needed to ask you.
Oh.
Did you go confront her?
Yeah.
I got rejected.
I guess I was annoying to her after all.
She didn't want people to get the wrong idea about us.
I think she felt that all of the things I did
for her were making other people suspicious.
I tried to tell her how I feel and how much
I care for her, but it didn't work out.
I couldn't hold it in anymore.
I see.
It hurts more than I thought it would.
I didn't think I was annoying enough to make her cry like that.
That idiot!
You look terrible.
Kurumi.
Friends? More like rivals!
Kazehaya rejected me.
What did you say?
Do you think we're friends now or something?
Don't group yourself with me.
You're not my rival.
What are you doing? Let go of me!
Because I was rejected?
More like because you didn't try.
Because you hurt him!
Hurt him?
I hurt him?
Because I couldn't leave him alone even though he likes someone?
Because I bothered hi—
Because you're an idiot!
Wasn't Kazehaya the only one who never looked at you out of pity?
Even though even Chizu and Ayane did!
Open your eyes!
What…?
You are not the same as me.
I told him.
What?
Even though he rejected me, I clearly told him how I felt!
Don't you dare put yourself on the same level as me!
I've always, always been watching Kazehaya,
sometimes even without noticing it.
That was delicious.
Sawako's curry is the best!
It was hayashi rice, wasn't it?
Haeshi?
From: Chizuru Yoshida       Title: Now!
Sorry for the short notice, but we're meeting at my house to make the costumes for the costume parade. If you're free, come over!
W-Would it be alright if I went over to Chizu's house right now?
Now?
Are you preparing for the school festival?
Yeah.
For the costume parade.
Costume?
Ah, I have some snacks for you to take over then.
Snacks?
Be careful walking at night!
Yes, be careful.
I will!
Bye!
Her school festival…
I remember helping to make our class
float back when I was in high school.
I did the refreshment booth.
Dried bonito and seaweed, big Shiitake mushrooms and dried sea slugs.
What? Oh, soup stock?
It was so hard to cut the Shiitake!
That's a delicious sounding…float? Soup?
Don't let anyone see us!
Quietly now, quietly!
It's stuck!
Lift it up!
What are you guys doing?
I'm pretty sure taking your floats out is against the rules.
Please, Pin! Pretend you didn't see us!
Every other class is doing it!
We won't finish on time otherwise!
You're our homeroom teacher!
Yeah, but I don't really care.
What does he mean by that?!
He's supposed to be our teacher.
Just warning you, you guys better not get caught
by another teacher. I don't want to deal with it.
Phew, safe for now. But what do we do about this?
Lift that side first.
Got it.
Shota!
You're more of a jerk than I thought.
When did you get like that?
What?
Don't "what" me!
You pretend to care, then make the other
person care for real... You're scary.
And yet you look so harmless…
You rejected Kuronuma, didn't you?!
I was rejected!
You totally fooled me.
I can't believe you went off so fast to reject someone.
Seriously, what do you plan on doing in the future?
Becoming a gigolo?
A host?
Or maybe a—
I'm the one that got rejected!
What?
I. Was. Rejected!
What? Did you run over there just to turn her down?
Why would I do that?
Kazehaya?
Oh, did Pin catch you?
Sorry! You guys go on ahead!
Gotcha!
I went to confess to her.
It just… didn't go well.
I was rejected.
I get it.
So you weren't able to really say it. You just tiptoed around it.
What a pansy.
I said everything I had to!
Whatever. It's fine.
Leave me alone.
Yeah, you're right.
You said before that you don't understand Kuronuma,
but really, you already have trouble with yourself.
It's fine like this, isn't it?
Just give up on her.
Huh? What's weird.
It doesn't match.
Oh no! What happened?
That's because it should probably be like this.
Oh no! I jumped into their conversation!
I see!
It fits now!
Thanks, Sadako!
I'm gonna go bring us some drinks.
Chizu?
What?
Um…
Thank you!
Thank you for texting me and inviting me over…
and for what you said after school.
You have us!
How long do you plan on putting yourself down for?
It made me really happy to hear you say that.
Last year, when I first became friends with you and Ayane,
that was the first time I ever felt that someone liked me!
I-I said it!
Don't forget that!
Now, for those drinks!
Isn't that great?
Look how happy she is after hearing you say that.
Hearing me say that?
Hearing me…say it.
I told him.
I clearly told him!
Did I…tell him?
Did Kazehaya hear me say it?
K-Kurumi!
M-Morn—
S-She turned away from me!
Sadako!
Teacher!
Oh no! I-I…!
I showed you such an embarrassing side of me yesterday!
No, no!
Actually—
Hold it right there.
You've really done it now.
What do you want with her?
Stay away from her!
Aw, so mean.
Didn't I tell you not to do anything uncalled for?
And what did you do?!
Aw crap!
I'm sorry, Sadako!
I think Kazehaya might actually like you after all!
Wait—!
What did you—! So loudly too!
It's a misunderstanding!
You've got it all wrong!
That isn't "like" in the way you're thinking of it.
What was that?
I'm not sure, but I think Sadako's denying Kazehaya likes her.
What?!
Ka—
Kazehaya!
Ryu!
You guys are late!
Everyone's already here—
Wait, why are there so many people here?
Ah, Kazeha—
Wait!
Come with us!
Wait! This is dangerous!
Shut up and just come!
What was that?
Did something happen?
No…
nothing.
Oh man, can we finish the float on time?
It'll work out.
Seems impossible.
We'll probably have to pull an all-nighter before the festival.
Yeah…
What, this year too?!
What, it was all just talk!
Yeah, he didn't even say hi to her.
Yeah.
I might not be the right person to say this,
but I don't think you're saying enough.
If things keep going like this, will I
never be able to talk to Kazehaya again?
Will I only be able to watch him walk
away without even saying good morning?
He might never smile and say good morning to me again.
He might start avoiding me.
Kazehaya used to be there waiting for me…
he used to call out to me when I was all alone.
I might've…
done something bad!
Don't you take that tone with me!
Right…
Should I sew it shut for you?
That big mouth of yours?!
That'd be troublesome…
See, I'm a pretty honest fellow.
I don't care.
Would you move?
You're in the way.
Can't you do this somewhere else?
Oh right, Kurumi. What'd you do after that?
After what?
After you came to find out what happened between Sadako and Kazehaya.
What?!
Kurumi, you're not planning something again, are you?
You didn't do anything to Sawako, did you?
I told her off.
What of it?
What?!
What's wrong with telling off a girl who can't
even give a guy chocolates on Valentine's?
What?! Why do you know about that?
Was it your fault?!
Yeah! I interfered!
But so what?
She was the one who couldn't give it to him!
I didn't tell her not to give it to him!
Kurumi
She's got a point.
No, interfering's not good.
Kurumi
Sawako
Wait, what?
Kurumi, you liked Kazehaya too?!
Your voice is too loud.
Yeah.
What? Man, that's tough...
Then if I were to go out with Sadako, wouldn't that be good for you?
Don't get ahead of yourself!
Didn't you want to get in her way?
I…
I don't want to think that I lost to a girl like her!
I didn't think she was so weak!
It's disappointing!
Wait—!
Kurumi!
So Kazehaya really does like Sadako, doesn't he.
It has nothing to do with you.
Why do you have to say that?
I can't leave them alone.
For Sadako's sake—
For Sawako?
More like for yourself.
So that you can give yourself the satisfaction
of saying "I'm such a great guy!"
Do you know how much Sawako suffered just because of you?
You know how badly outsiders can mess things up.
Leave her alone.
A Beautiful Table Setting
My eyes really weren't open.
I haven't been trying.
douka ima dake wa furimukanaide
Please don't look at me right now
yuugure sawagu kaze
The sun's set, the wind's blowing,
furesouna kyouri
and we're so close that we can almost touch
kimi wo mitsumeteru zutto
My gaze has always been fixed on you
kimi ga suki de
I like you
I've always liked you
kono omoi koi demo ii
I don't mind if this emotion is what they call love,
kizu tsuitemo ii
and I don't care if I get hurt by it
nando demo tsutaetai
I just want to tell you, over and over again
kimi ni todoke
I want to reach you
Preview
To You
I want him to know.
I want to tell him.
Next time: To You.