Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
namida wo nose
take away your tears
kareru made supiido agete
Speed up until they dry
tobikoete yukeru
I can overcome this
kitto kotae wa
The answer is
harukana ano sora no mukou
waiting beyond the distant sky
kotae ga mitsukaranai koko de wa
There's no answer here,
tameiki wo tsuite sora wo miru
so I sigh and look up at the sky
aoku somerareta hitomi no oku de kagayaiteru no wa
Shining deep within my eyes, reflecting its blue,
doko de mo yukeru, yume wo miteru
is a dreamer who can overcome anything
jibun na no sa
It's me, myself
Escape
kono kaze ni
Let the wind
negai wo nosete
carry your dreams
nobashita te wa asu wo egaku
My hands willl draw tomorrow
mou kowaku nado nai
I'm not scared anymore
namida no ato
The memory of my tears
nijiiro ni somatte tondeyuku
are dyed by rainbows and fly
ano sora no mukou
far away beyond the sky
Of course, everyone here knows Miller.
She was scouted while performing here, right?
By Generation Bleu, I think.
There's really no mistake, Gazelle.
Miller and her band are...
Did you hear about that here?
I don't know, but a company like GenBlu signing a musician directly is a bit strange...
Well, GenBlu HQ is a big city where tens of thousands of people live.
But they said it's just a six month contract...
What exactly do you guys want to know?
The identity of the woman named Miller!
This is Miller, right?
Yeah.
This proves Miller the singer really exists.
The whole thing is nonsense!
Have you ever been to one of her shows?
It's so passionate and sexy!
Compared to her, that girl is just...
Y'know, just a little female geek.
We're going to America.
Again?
To Elena Peoples' birthplace?
The Plateaux of Mirror
Kyrie.
Kyrie!
Respond to me!
Elena!
Elena?
Is that... me?
Is that another comic book quote?
I don't think so...
Where's Ao?
I don't see any Secrets around.
There is no mistake that a Scub Burst has occurred.
The pillars of light that come with the emergences of Scub Corals and Secrets have been sighted.
The Secret is definitely closing in on the Scub.
I've been wondering for a while, but what exactly are those pillars of light?
Ao, that's a—
Where do the Scub and the Secrets come from?
There are multiple theories in regards to the origin of Secrets.
But researchers have yet to reach a consensus.
There are theories that state that the
aggregation of trapar in the atmosphere...
is a natural phenomenon due to chemical reactions,
while others state that in parallel to our world, there is—
My nose! My nose!
This is going to take forever, so save it for another time, Fukai Ao.
Yes ma'am...
The dust filter can't take much more. Return for now.
I'm clear.
I've got visual on the Scub Coral.
But I don't see any signs of...
What's that?
We've got no data on it.
It might be that Truth guy again...
Truth?
Truth!
Wait! Don't enter the ZOA carelessly!
We have yet to detect any signs of the Secret or Truth.
Huh? You okay, Georg?
You're not acting strange because I hit you earlier, are you?
Oh my, you broke him.
Chief!
Where'd Truth go?
He vanished.
I swear I saw him. He was huge...
You still worried about your little girlfriend?
You're pretty annoying today, Fleur.
Did you have a fight with Mr. Papa again?
Don't call him that!
Did you?
I just asked her how things are going with Ao lately.
My dad's such an idiot.
He just doesn't understand anything!
Ao and me? That's hilarious!
He's like half my age!
Not to mention he's in love with his little girlfriend.
It's not love!
And Fleur already has someone else she likes.
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
You're not getting away this time, Truth!
What?
Or not...
The President?
Stupid dad! Stupid dad! Stupid dad! Stupid dad!
It's Genten Papa!
It's unclear if we managed to drive the Secret back.
Retrieving the Quartz and confirming that the Burst has calmed down will be enough.
To be safe, I'll tell the Australian army to remain alert, not alarmed.
So... are you surprised, President?
President!
Hey, Mr. Blanc! Are you listening?
Of course! What have you found in your investigation so far?
The facility is locked down.
Well, no surprise there.
I heard by the time we took Elena in, most of the children were already gone.
What kind of facility is this?
We have no data on it.
You know that some children are born with the ability to pilot IFOs, right?
Like Ao.
It's not yet proven,
but it is widely believed that being born in an area with high trapar density
causes changes in brain structure.
Children like that were gathered and researched in many countries.
That place is one such lab.
Elena was raised in here?
You still think she and Miller are one and the same?
You've seen the security footage too, haven't you?
We are well aware of the unusual activities of our company's contracted artist, Miller Joe.
From her communication records, we suspect she's an American spy.
But Miller Joe being the same person as Elena Peoples is just your theory.
Elena has undergone training in our company for over two years.
How could she debut as an indie artist in Manchester...
if she was undergoing IFO pilot training 1300km away?
Gazelle, what's the matter?
Remember what Truth said?
You can't see the truth.
What did you say?
The truth only shows itself to the ones who try to see it.
He said that this world is wrong,
and that I can't see the truth.
So what about it?
I don't get it!
Oh please...
I don't get it, but I don't like it either!
Headquarters, 20 floors underground.
This is as far as the emergency staircase takes me,
but it's clear that it goes even further down.
There are clearly traces of another culture.
One different from ours... Something from a different world...
You're telling me this isn't Miller?
Yes. Miller is an agent we've selected carefully in cooperation with the British intelligence.
We had prepared her so that she could get contracted with Generation Bleu.
Oh, I remember. Our IFO budget was cut thanks to that stunt.
We have all her physical data on file, of course.
She does indeed look very similar, but there are slight differences in the voiceprint.
I ordered my man who works as her producer to procure saliva samples,
and we checked for DNA matches.
They are totally different people!
For at least two months, the person we have been in contact with was not Miller.
So who is she?
No way!
Looks like we're going to have to remove the outer armor to clean the sand out.
How long is Stanley going to be our substitute chief for?
Stop being so selfish!
He's been graphing your weight gains! He's obviously teasing you.
I-I'm not the only one who got fatter!
It doesn't matter who it is.
There's no one like Bruno.
That's right... I wish I could hug his big bear belly again...
Chief, has team Goldilocks been ordered to scramble?
What are you talking about?
But then...
Stop them!
Bruno!
I am... Miller...
I am... Elena...
I am...
Miller!
Elena!
Truth got away today, but I'll find him eventually.
And then—
Wh-What's wrong?
I told you, we're leaving together!
Yeah, I've been waiting! Let's go!
The sky is so beautiful!
It's the sky of Iwato Island!
What's up, Noah? Where's Ao?
Team Goldilocks?!
Oh, are you still trying to run away?
So many bears!
It's not a bear! It's my Hans!
Alex! Are the children all right?
The systems have been shut down.
We're opening the canopies now.
No!
Let me go!
Bears!
Okay! Bring all three of them here right away!
Mama! I must save Mama!
Mama! Mama!
It's confirmed that oxygen inhalation eases the hallucinations.
Begin!
Mama! Mama!
Just as Georg deduced, the trapar in the air is the cause of the problem.
Those particles react with the trapar in the air
after entering their bodies, stimulating the brain.
It has no effect on us, but it causes hallucinations to the
children whose brain structures have been altered by trapar.
Strengthen the filters of all air conditioning units to filter out trapar.
Now we have to figure out how to get rid of the particles in their bodies...
It's possible that every one of those particles is a Secret...
Are Ao and Elena going to be all right?
He's different from us on a genetic level.
Ao and Elena, huh?
Where are we?
Huh?! What?!
How did...
Didn't you tell me before?
That you wanted to see the real thing, not just a broadcast.
But only adults can come here.
Miller, is that you?
Where have you been? What are you doing taking to the stage by yourself?
We've been summoned. Let's go.
Ao! Elena!
Ao, we must run!
Wasn't I just in Generation Bleu?
They've been misleading us!
This isn't the real world.
Our world is outside here.
Ao, we'll lead you there.
I must search for it... Let's go!
The Ryukyu SDF? It's the men of Pippo's dad.
Elena, take care of Ao!
Why does a Pied Piper pilot disguise herself as Miller and send us intel?
Is it fake intel?
No, that can't be. Because...
Ao, once we're in the real world...
I'm sure we won't have to fight ever again.
And then—
Stop already, Miller.
It sounds like you're triggering your death flag!
I see...
What do you mean by flag?
And Miller is—?
Should we fire warning shots?
No need.
The car's AC filter is filtering out trapar.
Can you hear me, Ao, Elena?
Chief?
Don't let them fool you!
We're leaving! Together!
That's right, Ao!
I've seen it! A different world!
One that's outside of this boring world!
Isn't that what you've been looking for?
Don't worry, I'll take you away from this island!
Island?
Naru... Mom...
Heh, we look so similar!
Maybe we were related in our past life?
Then... please tell me!
Who am I?!
You know, right?!
It's me!
Elena!
Elena! Ao!
It's an enemy!
An enemy spy has infiltrated our base!
The enemy?!
Fire! Stop it!
I told you that you were triggering your death flag...
Noah! Where have you been?
I've been looking for you!
So are you sure that they're two different people?
They existed at the same time.
That said, Miller's just a pile of ashes now.
I can't finance any further investigations.
Wait, President! Hey!
It's too bad. We finally found someone who knew the Peoples.
Who cares about what she's been through before she entered the facility?
We're going!
Why are you bringing up Mistress Elena's accident again?
Accident?
You're reopening the investigation, aren't you?
Five years ago on a Caribbean sea cruise,
the Mistress was caught up in a Scub Burst...
The Master grieved greatly...
He even fell ill.
What are you talking about?
Elena Peoples is... a Generat—
Ah... That was taken a year before Mistress Elena died.
But then... who's the current Elena Peoples?
Elena! You should be in bed!
I'm just watering it.
I did feel down, but I'm fine now.
Sweet dreams, Miller.
Sweet dreams, Elena.
To be continued.
takanaru shinzou no koe wa
My heart is racing and beating loud
itsu shika kokochi yoku najinde ite
But that feels cozily familiar
kaze ga tsuyoku fuiteite mo
Even if the wind is blowing hard
me wo tsumuranaide itsu datte mae wo muku yo
Don't close your eyes and always look on ahead
nakitaku nattara omoidashite
If you feel like crying, remember
damatte chikaiatta yakusoku wo
the promise we made together
tabidatsu hinadori no uta
The young birds in the sky sing
ima mo mada umaku tobenai keredo
though they still can't fly well
meguri meguru toki wo koe
Even if we go beyond the edge of time
hitazura ni tsunaida te wo tadotte
I'll only follow you as we hold hands
kotoba wa
"So I never let you go!" My words
sora ni kieteku bakari da toshite mo
may get lost in the infinity of the sky,
chirabaru hikari no naka de
but among the glittering light
mayowazu ni kimi wo sagashidaseru kara
I can still find you without hesitation
Preview
Next time on Eureka Seven AO.
Pied Piper goes into space with the whole world's eyes on them.
Ao faces a new challenge fighting in zero gravity.
What will the appearance of the silver wings at a decisive moment show him?
Next time on Eureka Seven AO,
episode 12: Step into a World.
Listen to the voices of the children of the stars.