Give Mikono back!
Infinity Punch!
Infinity, you say?
He's got an Infinity Punch too?
But it's different!
His arms are following his punches!
The effect comes before the cause!
Are those punches violating the laws of causality?
A mere dog with wings dare speak of infinity? Ridiculous!
Infinity is a power of God.
The power to appear at any place and bless at any time.
Where is this?
Silvie!
Why can't I reach her?
Why can't I reach you, Silvie?
Damn it!
This Union is making Amata suffer.
Who're you?
This is the labyrinth of Mikage's mind.
Please, kill me.
What?
If I die, Mikage won't be able to control the Wings of the Sun.
It's what I get for being so stupid.
I can't think of any other way to stop Mikage.
Amata's going to suffer if he loses Mikono.
I don't want Amata to suffer.
Please.
I can't handle any more!
The Union's about to break!
How dare you!
Goodbye, Amata...
Can't do it.
Why?
You don't deserve to get killed over the likes of Amata.
Pathetic Wingless!
I no longer need your body!
The true Wings of the Sun were wielded by the gods of old one by one.
Now that they have been awakened,
the cursed bride and I are all the Elements it needs.
Reverse!
Contrary Twister!
Now hear the wedding bells of revenge!
I will take this harlot's body and forge a new world as the God of Genesis!
Awaken, the other Sun!
Cayenne! Yunoha!
A dark sun!
The temperature is rising all over the world!
The water levels of the oceans and every body of water are dropping!
The Wings of the Sun has become a scorching flame to dry up the planet!
Mix!
The whole planet's going to die!
But we don't stand a chance with just Vectors!
Amata! Let's Union!
Andy!
It's been a long time, Amata!
Mix! You're back!
This song! Impossible!
Shrade!
It's confirmed to be the Vector Shrade was last in!
But there don't seem to be any life signs...
Detecting another Vector!
It's the one Zessica was piloting before!
Now we've got two spare Vectors!
If we can just find one more...
Yo! You didn't forget about me, did you?
Vector Z, Malloy, reporting in!
I'm from the south, you know! The scorching sun and I are buddies!
We have three Vectors free now!
Cayenne, Yunoha, redeploy!
And Element Change!
Switch out Malloy... for me!
Chairman Crea!
Don't be rash! If you need a pilot, I'll go!
Donar, Suomi. You two must survive.
If worse comes to worst, you two will be the Adam and Eve of the next generation.
Wha?
Yes, Ma'am! Understood!
Cayenne! Yunoha! Follow me!
Roger!
Good luck!
This song! Shrade!
Can you fill my seat? I wonder.
I entrust it to you, my friend.
Shrade...
I want to defend both Jin's homeworld and the Earth!
Shrade! Your spirit stayed to fight with us!
Come! Let us fight!
For our precious friends!
For our precious partners!
For our precious ones...
For our precious feelings!
Come with me, Shrade.
Dear Friends Union!
Go, Aquarion!
Aquarion Geparda!
Now let us fight together, Cayenne.
Yes, my friend!
Pathetic.
What?
Watch out!
We're surrounded!
Teleport!
Chairman?
Here we go!
Hole! Hole! Hole!
Let's play together!
The Requiem of Genesis!
I'm getting too old for this.
Too old?
Insolent bugs!
Spatial Augmentation!
I can't give up now...
I can't give up now!
You suffer and suffer, and still you stand...
Do you really want this harlot so?
I'll put you out of your misery.
He's pulling the two planets together by force!
He's absorbing the life from both worlds!
You're the ones from 12,000 years ago.
Yeah. I still remember your smell.
Apollo!
Is that you, Apollo?
There is no need for sorrow,
my future yet still dear sister.
Brother!
Born from Man and Angel,
my suffering and my salvation.
Toma!
I'm sorry.
I remember now.
It's all my fault.
You sacrificed yourselves because of me.
Do not apologize.
You did all you were able to, just as did we.
And hey, we met again, just like we promised.
Amata! Apollo!
Because Man and Angel were connected.
Not just once, but twice, you stole away the one I loved, you harlot!
Do not fear!
High Commander Fudo!
Those are the shadows of Toma's heart, separated from his pure love.
The shadows of Toma's heart...
Mikage!
Do not turn away.
You must see the rest of this story.
Overcome your fears and find the truth.
You are now ready.
Apollonius...
Apollonius! Apollonius!
Apollonius.
I will burn all you hold dear.
Mix!
The Union broke!
He did that with just one attack!
Amata!
Damn it, Mikage!
Let's give them a hand, bitch!
You got it, asshole!
Amata!
Zessica!
Kagura!
Save it for later!
Let us fight with you!
For Mikono, and for our world!
Zessica...
I'm sorry.
Don't be stupid, Amata.
What are you apologizing for?
Then thank you, Zessica!
You're a real dumbshit.
Way to make a bitch cry.
Let's get 'em, kid!
Pure Love Union!
Go!
Aquarion!
Kindness within strength!
Passion within weakness!
They're so wonderful!
Aquarion Evol!
Apollonius...
What is this?
You loved Apollonius so much...
Apollonius...
But you were betrayed and hurt...
Even so... even through all that...
Apollonius...
Apollonius!
I...
I love him.
That's right.
You... you still...
So close...
I'm sorry.
I never wanted to acknowledge it.
That I stole your love away.
That I hurt you so badly.
It's somewhat late for apologies.
I don't care what you do to me!
Just spare all the other people of the world!
Mikono!
Amata! Stay away!
Everyone get away!
No! I can't leave you behind!
And I can't let this go!
I'll connect them!
I'll connect this soul torn between love and pain back together!
Enough of this pathetic joke!
Mikono!
Reverse!
Take this! All Together Punch!
Go!
Mikono!
Pathetic!
We're burning up!
I'm not giving up yet!
I let my Mom slip away from me!
I've regretted that ever since!
But now I understand!
That's how Silvia... how Mikono felt 12,000 years ago when I left her!
I was born again so I could learn that!
I won't let you slip away from me this time!
I won't leave you again!
I want my love, Mikono, to be with me as I fight to save the world!
Amata!
Pathetic winged mongrel!
Is this where it ends?
Right here?
Amata...
Amata.
Amata!
Accept the present, Amata.
Amata...
Amata.
Mom...
Dad...
Amata!
You're wrong, Mikono!
You can't connect them by yourself!
If someone's with you,
if you share your feelings with someone,
that's how you connect!
I'll be with you!
Whether we grow old and wrinkled together,
or it ends for us right here as a legend!
I'll be right there by you!
We'll fly to infinity!
I'll love you to infinity!
Amata!
You crazy asshole...
I was reborn to love Silvie, over 12,000 years.
But you love Mikono now, the way she is.
This is a dumb kanji pun based on what Kagura just said. The whole kanji is
'omou', but the top part is 'ima' (now) and the bottom part is 'kokoro' (heart).
So go! Finish this and complete your love!
Kagura!
Mikono!
Amata!
Genesis Union! Go!
Aquarion Evol!
What?
Nope.
That's not an Evol.
It's got a new name now.
Aquarion...
Love!
Amata!
Mikono!
I...
I love you!
Get a room, you two...
Aquarion Love's tears!
They're crossing space to rain on the parched earth!
The separated worlds are being united again!
Curse you...
This cannot end here.
I just need a body!
You!
Why can't I move?
Why won't you obey me?
Apollonius?
I will accept you into myself.
Let us watch over this age together.
Sleep within me, shadow of love.
After all these eons, we are now together.
You betrayed me not once, but twice.
Yet why...
Why do I feel so warm inside you?
Shush?
Amata!
And now, love is permitted once more!
Love is permitted once more