All of you are going to be born again!
And I'll be waiting for you!
As time flows on, we are all being born moment by moment and reborn moment by moment.
The instant that nothing becomes something...
is now!
What happened?
Mikono?
Happy birthday!
No way!
osore
Even if you're scared
living your life   don't give up now   keep moving on
Just live your life, don't give up now, keep moving on
kimi wo dakishimeru nandomo nandomo nandomo
And I'll come for you over and over and over again
ashita boku wa kimi ni deau darou
We'll find each other soon enough
wazukana hoshiakari wo tayori ni
By the faintest glimmer of starlight
boku ni wa kimi ga wakaru yo wakaru yo
I know you, I know you
sen'oku no toki wo koe futari hiraku densetsu no tobira
It's been billions of years, but now we can open the door to our legend
naraku no ao tobikonde
I crossed over the deep blue void
kimi to hai ni naru tame
so I could burn to ash along with you
nagaki rinne wo kanashimi tsurete tabi shitekitanda
I've had a long journey on the vast wheel of fate, gathering sorrows along the way
zenryoku de mikansei kimi no tonari de
I'm not perfect, but I'm giving all I have
kawaita kokoro hotoge chi wo nagasu kedo
If I open my fragile heart to you, I know I'll bleed...
soba de iru no zutto yorisotte zutto
But I'll always be with you, always be in your arms
futari hikari no fune ni noru
We'll get on a shining ship of light
kaze no hajimari no oto kanadeyou
And call forth the wind with our voices
Beasts of Love
Hah. All your smells are weak.
How is he here?
It's that beast boy!
Those who do not complete the rite of passage will not grow.
Being reborn from the darkness was a good trial for them.
Get the girls back! He's after women!
That's discrimination!
Give it a rest! Do what he said and get away!
We're just up against a person!
Show me what you learned in hand-to-hand training!
Follow my lead!
What?
Donar!
Professor!
Hold it!
I'll handle this with my holes!
Holes?
Whoa!
That Special Training of the Grave really worked!
Spatial Augmentation!
They're a really good team.
It's like they're synchronized!
The wife is supporting the husband.
That power of reversal!
Reversal?
He reversed that filling power into an opening power!
Are you messing with me?
You get your hands off of Mix!
She smells good too.
There's my smelly wench!
Why me?
Defend Mikono!
I'm on it! Mikono!
Mikono, hurry!
Malloy!
Wait!
Don't you dare get between me and my wench.
Are you calling Mikono a wench?
Don't you dare!
He can even reverse damage he takes?
My wench!
Those eyes...
They're locked straight onto the thing he wants...
Go back!
That noise! Not you again!
Cut that crap out!
I'm only playing the air and the earth.
I'll show you! Reverse!
I've learned to play the dissonance of your tone's inversion.
Get out of my way!
My wench is mine!
All mine!!
He inverted it in one beat.
The savage strike of a beast.
That could be interesting.
You think he's into Mikono?
Tell me another reason for a boy to chase a girl like that.
Ooh, how about a boy and another boy?
Why would he...
A wolf?
Wait, that's him!
What?
You're not getting away from me!
Reverse!
According to Malloy's report, he's taken Mikono and is hiding in the city.
You guys search on the ground.
Roger.
Let's split up.
You guys go that way.
Amata!
Wait for me!
Amata...
You awake, wench?
Relax. I'm just going to kill you.
Right here in my arms.
Mikono!
You hear me, Mikage? I've got her.
The source of that smell.
Hurry up and get me back.
Can't you hear me?
Does this thing work differently?
Are you there, Mikage?
I'm done here.
Of course I hear you, beast of love.
Can't I be mean for just a little while?
I envy you. What you desire is already in your grasp.
Mikono!
Wait!
Amata!
Calm down, Amata. I'm sure Mikono's fine.
Don't say stuff just to make me feel better.
I'm not!
I know...
You know what?
He's not going to hurt Mikono.
I'm sure.
How do you know that?
Well...
He and Mikono are destined.
You're not destined to be with her, Amata.
You smell.
You really stink.
Why?
Why do you keep insulting me?
Because I hate you.
I want to kill you.
Why?
What did I do to you?
You were on Vega, that's what.
What?
Well, then...
then kill me right here!
What?
No, don't.
No...
Even I couldn't...
Not in a place like this...
What?
Stop!
If you say so, I'll stop.
But you aren't!
You want me to lick you too?
I really, really hate you.
I want to kill you.
Are you...
talking backwards?
I only lie to you.
Why?
His eyes...
Why are they so familiar?
I finally found you.
What?
Come with me, Sylvie.
Sylvie? You called me that before.
Sylvie and Apollon.
This is our legend.
Underneath the Tree of Life, on the day the world began.
The great Tree of Life governed the lives of all the creatures of the world,
and of the very planet itself.
As the two races waged war,
the Wings of the Sun awakened and pollinated the tree.
But the flowers wilted before they could bear fruit.
Eventually, the earth would be unable to support life.
Apollon and Sylvie separated to protect the Tree of Life.
Then, Sylvie said...
I'll be waiting for you.
Even if I have to wait for 12,000 years.
Wait for me, Sylvie.
I'll be back for you in 12,000 years.
That's what Apollon said?
Yeah.
That's me.
It's me.
You're... Apollon?
And you're...
I'm...?
Are you saying Mikono is Sylvie?
That's impossible. How could you even think that?
I saw it?
You saw it?
It's related to Cayenne's vision of the wedding in mourning clothes.
You saw that too, didn't you, Amata?
What does it matter? Apollon and Sylvie are just a story!
How can you be sure?
I was actually a little glad.
If Mikono's destiny is with him,
then just maybe, you and I could...
Zessica, what are you talking about?
A butterfly!
At this hour?
No!
I can't be Sylvie!
I'm not Sylvie!
Sylvie!
What's that?
Mikono!
Amata!
Don't scare me like that, Sylvie.
Mikono!
Amata!
Not him again!
Give it up already!
Amata!
I'm fine.
I did it.
You did what?
The special training is working.
I resisted his power, just for a moment.
Here he comes!
Figured. He's coming this way.
I'll keep him busy for Mikono.
You contact Cayenne!
Damn it, he's being the hero.
There she is!
It's Mikono!
Amata!
Cayenne's coming to help!
Get out of there!
Not yet!
I have to keep him on me until Mikono escapes!
Amata...
Just die already!
Damn it...
I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
As many times as it takes!
Am I going to die here?
I'm sinking... into the darkness...
I'm alone in the darkness again.
Amata Sora, do not be afraid.
The darkness is no longer a place to suffer in pain.
Rid yourself of your attachments.
That is how you will become connected.
Yes.
I'm bound, alone in the darkness.
I have to free myself from my attachments and my past.
Why don't you stay down?
Fly, straight in reverse!
Why won't my power work?
Those free of attachments cannot be led astray!
Why, you!
Cayenne!
Looks like I made it in time.
Don't let your guard down, Amata!
I'm gonna finish him off, so-
Amata! Take him out!
Don't hold back! Our lives are on the line!
Stop!
Don't shoot, Amata!
Mikono!
Mikono?
Amata, please!
Don't shoot him!
Please, forgive him!
Mikono...
Mikono... why?
Perfect.
Like the butterfly, the symbol of rebirth,
may forbidden love be reborn.
After 12,000 years...
kimi he tsuzuku sakamichi ni
There were white flowers growing
shiroi hana ga saiteta
on the road on the hill that leads to you
yume kara sameta ato mo kanashii sora miteta
When I woke from the dream, the sky still looked sad
kono kimochi happa no ue ni susunderu
My feelings drift on a leaf in the wind
asatsuyu wo ochiru oto ni mimi wo sumaseteru no
I'm straining my ears for the sound of the dew falling
kamisama anata ga tsukutta sekai wa kanpeki ja nai
God in Heaven, this world You made is far from perfect
koko de wa mainichi koi ga boroboro shindeku
Down here, love is shattered day by day
hajimete suki ni natta no wo anata wa shiranai deshou
You don't know what it's like to fall in love for the first time
chikyuu no uragawa de ii kara soba ni ite hoshikatta
Let it be on the other end of the world, but I wanted to be with him
watashi wo wasuretemo ii kara soba ni ite hoshikatta
Even if You were to forget me, I wanted to be with him
It's getting me excited.
The 12,000 year old smell of fate is bubbling up.
Let the stink take you, Sylvie.
Next Time
Confessions
from the Soul
It'll only hurt to resist.