You've been staying up late every night.
Here, your lunch.
Are you sure I shouldn't come
to the sports festival?
No. Don't.
Fine, fine.
Are you writing?
It's fine.
I was like that once, too.
Do what makes you happy.
That's the whole point of being young.
I've never let anyone
around me read my stories.
After all, Dazai said,
"One cannot influence another,
nor can one be influenced by another."
Sports Festival
Participants in the girls' 200-meter sprint,
please assemble at the entrance gate.
On your marks...
The blue team's gonna win this year!
You're pretty gung-ho, Chinatsu.
It's the sports festival.
I want to look good for once.
I'm getting nervous.
Get in place for the girls' 200!
Next, the girls' 200-meter sprint.
Don't you think these headbands look dorky?
Long night?
The deadline's coming up.
The newcomer award?
Yeah.
Let me read it.
No way.
C'mon, let me read it.
Hey, cut it out.
Go, red team!
What are you competing in, Kotarou?
The boys' 200.
Oh, yeah?
What lousy luck.
Akanecchi's up next.
Go for it, Akanecchi!
Akanecchi!
On your marks...
Set...
She's fast!
Awesome!
Hey, check out her butt.
I have equipment duty.
Later!
Hey, buy me a drink if the yellow team wins.
What? No way.
Juice is fine.
You totally think you're going to win.
What makes you so confident?
All right, thanks in advance.
You can't be serious.
You don't think you'll win?
Buy me juice if I win, then.
Sure. I'm going to win anyway.
What the heck?
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Come on, be men!
Win as a team!
What are you doing here?
Oh, Sonoda-sensei.
Don't drink the tea without asking.
Hey!
Thanks for the tea!
Win as a team!
The red team takes the win.
We won.
I've done my part.
Your part?
My muscle.
You're up, huh?
I really don't want to.
Go embarrass yourself.
Dazai said, "Be laughed at.
Be laughed at, and become strong."
I don't really want to get laughed at, though.
Next up is event number 4,
the boys' 200-meter sprint.
Who's up now?
No idea.
Curly-kun.
Azumi's up.
Is he fast?
Nope, not at all.
Uh-oh.
Yes! First!
Not bad, second-years!
Starting in the seventh heat,
the third-year students will race.
Hira!
Go get 'em!
On your marks...
Set...
Yikes, Hira's fast.
There's no way he can keep up with him.
He got passed.
No good.
That was sad.
Akane?
Huh? Hey, what was that?
You two heating up?
It's nothing, I swear.
Hira's good-looking, don't you think?
You're close to him in the
track club, right, Akanecchi?
Go out with him.
I-I'm not!
She's blushing!
I'm not...
Okay, we'll see you.
Yeah, I'll be back as soon
as I let the teachers know.
Sensei's not here right now.
What's up?
I fell on the track.
Are you hurt?
Hey, are you Curly-kun?
From Akane's class?
Sorry, Akane told me there was
a boy with really bad bedhead.
Oh, want me to treat you?
Clean it out really well
in the sink over there.
I already washed it at the tap outside.
Can I see your hand?
You cleaned it pretty well.
Huh? What is it?
Whoa, you're close.
Don't you need to disinfect it?
Nah, it'll heal faster this way.
Ow!
Sorry!
See you.
So sloppy.
I was so hungry...
I thought this might be the last time we
do this, so I put a ton of effort into it.
Eat up.
It's so good!
You won't be able to run if you eat too much.
There's only one more event.
The team relays.
Oh, well, that'll be a piece of cake
compared to a track meet.
Yeah, I guess.
I brought my camcorder.
I'll be sure to film every moment.
Stop it! You're embarrassing me!
Come on! The relay is the
highlight of the sports festival.
It's the main race.
Don't pressure her like that, Dad.
You're making her nervous.
Am I?
The afternoon events begin in ten minutes.
All students, please assemble
at your respective team tents.
Those of you participating
in the scavenger hunt,
please assemble at the entrance gate.
Jeez, Dad.
Hey, Mizuno!
What was she doing?
Let's work just as hard
in the afternoon race.
Boys, please prepare for the next event while
the girls prepare for the scavenger hunt.
The next event should be...
Huh? Mizuno, do you have the program?
Yeah.
Here you go.
After the scavenger hunt is...
The obstacle course.
Let's move the stuff in
front along this wall here,
and move the vault and
balance beam to the exit.
All right, let's get to work.
All right.
Let's go.
This way!
Okay.
Scavenger Hunt
Third-Years
Mizuno, thanks for this.
Oh, sure.
It's gone!
Huh?
The second-years are almost done.
Did you put yours in?
Hey, Akane.
Huh? Oh, yeah.
Now where did I put it?
Where... Huh?
On your marks...
Set...
It's missing.
Hey!
It's empty.
The boxes are empty!
Where are the slips for the third-years?
Th-There.
Got them.
Hey!
Take them from here.
Seriously?
Oh?
What? What's your item?
Someone you like
Can't tell you.
Sorry.
Hey, have you seen my potato
mascot around here?
Huh?
Potato? You mean that thing?
Yeah.
This is bad, isn't it?
It's bad.
Potato?
Red team!
Go!
Give them a cheer, first-years!
If we can take the next one, we'll win.
Yellow's on our heels, though.
They've got Hira.
Next up is event 16, the team relays.
It will be the last event of the day.
Let's all cheer them on
and make it memorable!
On your marks...
Set...
Akane, are you okay?
Did you find your potato?
No.
The red team is in the lead,
followed by yellow, blue, and white.
It's a close race.
It's not over 'til it's over.
The yellow team finishes first,
followed by blue and white.
Finally, the red team makes it to the goal.
Once the tallying is done, we'll have the
awards ceremony and the closing ceremony.
All students, please line up
in front of the main tent.
You really messed that up.
Sorry.
Come on, guys.
Stop it. Don't be mean.
Akanecchi did her best.
Yeah.
Seriously.
Don't let him get to you.
Why is he like that?
I know, right?
They told me to talk to you.
Are you bummed out?
No.
Good thing it wasn't a track meet.
Yeah.
You'd better get serious at the preliminaries.
You could make it to prefecturals.
You can do it, Mizuno.
You got this!
That's hilarious.
Seriously, she actually dropped the baton.
Come on, cut it out, you guys.
Is this yours, Mizuno-san?
How?!
I found it in the storage room.
Thank goodness!
I get so nervous without this.
I even messed up today, you know?
I really don't like being in front of people.
It's so embarrassing,
but I really like running, so...
I'm hopeless, right?
N-No, you're not...
You don't need to be embarrassed.
I think... you're fine the way you are.
See you later.
Oh, yeah.
Mizuno-san
Today
Thanks for earlier
Good work
Good job!
Curly-kun!
Say what?
That's your nickname.
That's a weird nickname lol
You have crazy bedhead.
Also, I think this part was a bit confusing.
Try to make it a bit clearer.
Okay.
It was actually a fun read.
Didn't you say you were
embarrassed to show people?
Yeah...
It's so embarrassing,
but I really like running, so...
I realized it's a complete lie that
people can't influence each other.
A Handful of Sand
Setsuko and Nagahara
I'm so jealous!
Isn't that the expensive one?
Such a celeb!
I'm not, really.
You're so lucky, Secchan.
You're so rich, and you're
so close with your boyfriend.
What's Nagahara like?
He's really nice, and he's a gentleman.
So he's manly only when he's around Setsuko.
Manga Café
Internet
Seriously.
I never knew.
Only when he wants to mess around.
Ryouko-sensei and Roman 1
No!
He's my student!
Someone you like
Ryouko-sensei and Roman 2
You like Ryoko-sensei, Roman?
Yup, I love her.
She's an awesome teacher.
That kind of "like"?!
Aira and Kaneko
Go out with me.
What?
Just do it.
No way.
Wh-What?
You're turning red.
W-Well, with you looking at me like that...
H-Hey!
What? Do you want me to?
You idiot!
Hurry up.
Wh-Why would I?
Damn it!