What are you thinking?!
You won't get your way!
Hinata, you're running too far away!
Shoyo, I don't think that's
a scheming face...
I think he's actually
smiling, maybe...
Don't say "maybe," Nishinoya!
Hinata, I'll kill you!
Kageyama's actually trying to smile...
Use the signs I told you about.
We're changing our plan.
Thanks!
Did Sugawara-san tell you about the signs?
I heard it in between sets.
All right!
Let's keep it going!
Heck yeah!
Go, go, go! Go, go, Seijoh!
Episode 22: Evolution
Don't look so amazed. I was pretty nervous.
Really?
Of course, there were third-years that
played at last year's Inter-High,
so I wasn't able to play in
a lot of official matches.
I hate to say it,
but it's likely that Kageyama's had his
feet on the court more than I have.
Despite that, Kageyama was
freaking out quite a bit.
Speaking of, the King's
going right into a serve.
Do you think he'll be all right?
Kageyama, nice serve!
Nice serve! One point!
Kageyama looks pretty happy.
Yeah.
It sort of puts me at ease.
What does?
Apparently every player feels
the same pride about the fact
that they're going to be on the court.
No matter whether they're some
genius or just a regular guy.
Kageyama-kun, relax!
Oh. Apparently, he's fine.
We're ending this the first time!
Yeah!
Watari!
Service ace!
He even got it from the libero!
Karasuno                            Aoba Johsai
And now they're tied.
Yes!
I'm sorry!
It's all right! We'll get the next one!
Yeah!
He's asking for a high five, you idiot!
Yeah...
Kageyama just gave someone a high five.
Sorry! Cover!
Right!
They broke it! It's coming back!
Chance ball!
"Bring it"...
...or "to me"?
Which will it be?
They didn't say anything?!
There it is!
That quick is so insane!
All right! Now Karasuno's
turning things around!
Karasuno                            Aoba Johsai
Sugawara-san compliments me
a lot if I make it!
Hey, Hinata.
Well done...
Are you my boss?
Hinata's so sharp! Damn!
And Kageyama's playing like a fish in water.
Kageyama...
..."Tobiuo".
(Tobiuo = flying fish)
Damn it.
All right, calm down.
There's no need for us to panic
and break down for them.
We just have to get one back,
and we'll be fine.
Right!
Hey, that facial expression
and pose piss me off, so stop.
So rude!
Iwaizumi-san, nice receive!
Kageyama has apparently
regained his usual rhythm.
I'm sorry...
Don't mind!
No, that's not all...
He was only concerned about
the opponent's block.
I should have made it go
towards the side a little.
Don't worry. They were all good serves.
Now, just slightly, his concern is
for his teammates as well.
Thank you.
All right... Don't hold back.
If we don't get this set, it's hopeless.
Make sure you use that freak
quick as much as possible!
Kunimi, nice serve!
All right!
Nice receive!
Kageyama told Hinata that if he's around,
Hinata would be the best...
But even with you...
You, with Hinata's attacks...
You're the best.
All right! They broke 20 points first!
Karasuno                            Aoba Johsai
Now it's the final scene...
That hurt, you idiot!
All right, we're in the 20's.
I'm driving some spirit into you!
I guess our issue might be over there.
Why did it turn into
Tsukishima versus Kageyama?!
One more!
Hinata, nice serve!
Net in!
Chance ball!
Mattsun, nice cover!
Kageyama!
All right!
How would you like the toss?
A bit higher would be great.
Got it!
Karasuno                            Aoba Johsai
All right!
I guess even Seijoh would
call a time-out after that.
When #10 falls back and when #11 moves up,
the number of times Karasuno uses
the center decreases, doesn't it?
Yeah. Simply put, I think that Tobio
doesn't get along with the giant.
In yesterday's match,
as well as today's, they don't seem
to be communicating very well.
I think that out of all
of Karasuno's spikers,
Tobio has the hardest time
accommodating that giant.
I really don't want to be friends with you.
Why?!
You seem like you'd use
our weaknesses against us.
Why would I use my teammates'
weaknesses against them?!
I think that Sugawara-san makes
sure to pay attention to all of
Tsukishima, I think you're
jumping too soon for the block.
Hold back a little.
the spikers' expressions as well
as how they're doing that day.
Understood.
Yamaguchi, make sure you
clearly call everything.
Right.
What?
He may have asked me to read his expression,
but I don't see anything other
than a face pisses me off.
Kageyama.
First, you need to have
a conversation. Talk.
Especially with Tsukishima,
communication is key.
Right...
Got it!
He picked it up! Here comes the counter!
Nice receive!
Left!
Tsukishima's not hitting
it with all he's got.
They caught up!
Damn, they're tied now.
A break!
Yeah, totally.
Sensei.
Right.
All right!
Maybe they lack attack power, after all.
Karasuno not having #10 here would be rough.
Come on, your faces! They're all tense!
Calm down and go! Your moves are great!
Yeah.
Hey.
How was that toss, damn it?
Why are you talking like Tanaka-san?
What was that, damn it?
It's like you're saying, "Shut up, and hit
this toss, you commoner," and it pisses me off.
What?!
Dang it, Tsukishima...
You sound like a kid. Stop picking fights!
What do you mean by that?
I have my own way of doing things,
so I'd rather you keep
your tosses consistent.
Um, what does that mean?
I'm assuming that when Kageyama
sets an A-quick to Tsukishima,
the course it should go in is
being determined by the toss.
Cross
If the ball is about a ball's width
away and center, it's a cross,
and if it's further, it's a turn.
Turn
Kageyama is, of course, setting it
where he thinks it'll succeed the best,
but I think Tsukshima is having
a hard time hitting those.
You're not the only one thinking.
"The shape of the opponent's defense."
"The best attacks I've been doing today."
We're all thinking about that.
Even Hinata has started thinking enough
to use normal quicks now, right?
Though just barely.
What'd you mean by that?!
What do you mean, "just barely"?!
Now, now....
All right.
You're rather agreeable today.
You feeling okay?
We're just going to have to try and find out.
Tsukishima's probably not used
to people who face him head on,
We're taking this set, no matter what!
and he can't run from that.
Right!
Nice, Noya-san!
I have my own way of doing things,
so I'd like you to keep
your tosses consistent.
A feint!
Yeah! He got over the block!
He totally did it!
How annoying!
I thought that he was going to hit
it hard up until the end.
Nice! Tsukishima's lively after
getting through the opponent's guard.
"Lively"?
It's hard to see, but that expression
he has means he's pretty into it.
Oh.
Chance ball!
Another feint!
Nice, Watari.
It's coming back!
Chance ball!
#11's pretty good.
But Seijoh's block is pretty high, so
I think they're avoiding a straight-on attack.
With a feint, you can sort of run away.
Looks like #11 is running away
from the blocks after all.
All right!
Nice, Mattsun.
Damn it. They're taking back
one point after another.
Karasuno                           Aoba Johsai
Center, #11!
Again? All right! This time I'll get it!
Nice receive, Watari!
All right!
Center!
Tanaka, nice receive!
Damn it!
Be careful!
Sorry, it's a bit short! Cover!
They really need to get this.
Will it go to the ace after all?
We're all thinking about that.
#11 again!
No! Don't go out too far!
All right!
You piss me off, you know that?
They're being too cautious about the feints,
so our defense is being
concentrated up front.
I'm sorry!
They got us.
It's all right. Next time!
Kn-Knife... Nuff... Nice.
Don't mess up that line, Kageyama!
Wow. Kageyama complimented Tsukishima.
Kageyama is definitely changing, as well.
How much do you suck at compliments?!
Karasuno                            Aoba Johsai
Karasuno's at set point.
Seriously?!
Just one more point!
We won't let you have it!
Go, go, go, Hajime!
Karasuno                            Aoba Johsai
Push it, push it, Hajime! One more!
It'll be fine!
One point!
If we can get this one point,
like we usually do, this set will be ours!
Congratulations.
Best Setter Award
Oikawa Toru
The third year of junior high,
our last tournament...
That's a rare smile, with no ulterior motive.
My smile is always straightforward and pure.
"Straightforward and pure" coming
from you is already impure.
Of course I'm happy!
It's the first time I've received this.
Oikawa Toru, overall,
is a pretty silly guy,
but there was a time that
he wasn't smiling.
He had a more athletic build than others.
He was also blessed with natural ability.
Especially when he began junior high,
the way he matured was
way ahead of the flock.
Miyagi Prefecture Junior High
Newcomer Volleyball Tournament
Even then, there were walls
that he could not climb.
Thanks to the Young Giant Ushiwaka,
Shiratorizawa Academy Junior High
was eventually known as
the best in the prefecture.
Why can't we win?!
When we fought them, we lost.
We couldn't even get one set.
We tried to go higher, to a higher stage,
but we were thwarted until our
third year in junior high.
Then...
My name is Kageyama Tobio and I came
from Akiyama Elementary School.
I've been playing volleyball
since the second grade.
It's a pleasure to be working with you!
A genius appeared at his back,
and his talent shone
with astonishing brightness.
More than anything, it appeared that
he was very happy to be touching the ball.
Plus, the way he was able to handle the ball
was on a totally different level than others.
We'll have him play the basic positions,
but he'll be a setter some day.
Indeed.
After that, Oikawa ended up
practicing even harder.
You're overworking yourself!
The coach just warned you
about that yesterday!
If you get hurt, everything
will be pointless, you dumbass!
Come on, you're done. Stretch!
He seemed to be panicking.
That panic surfaced in a practice
match in the form of an
unbelieveable amount of combo misses.
And then...
Kageyama, give it a shot.
Yes, sir.
Okay!
Front! Front!
Got it.
Nice cover!
Nice key!
Nice serve!
Oikawa-san.
Please show me how to serve.
Get away.
Don't come over here!
Calm down, you dumbass!
Sorry...
Kageyama, I'm sorry,
but we're done for today.
Oh, okay...
The change-up today was to cool your head.
You need to have some more composure!
Right now, I can't win against Shiratorizawa,
so there's no way I can have composure!
I want to win and go to nationals.
To win, I need to...
"I" this, "I" that. It's annoying!
Do you think you're fighting by yourself?!
You've got to be kidding, you dumbass!
If you think how you're doing equals
how the team will do, I'll punch you!
You already did!
There's no one on our team who
can beat Ushiwaka one-on-one!
However...
There are six players on a volleyball court!
Even if our opponent's some
genius first-year, or Ushiwaka,
the team with the better six
is stronger, you dumbass!
"The team with the better six is stronger."
Sorry, did I headbutt you too hard?
Well, how do I put this?
I suddenly feel invincible.
More importanty, Iwa-chan,
is "dumbass" the only insult you've got?
Want me to make your nose bleed
from the right side, too?
Nice course!
One more!
I don't know how to put it, but it
looks like Oikawa's gotten over it.
Yes.
Oikawa-san, please show me
the basics of a serve toss.
Heck no, you idiot! Idiot!
Oikawa! Stop picking fights
with the first-years!
Our last tournament in junior high...
Kitagawa-Daiichi                     Shiratorizawa
We fought against Shiratorizawa Junior High,
and were able to get our first set.
We ended up in second place
behind Shiratorizawa.
Best Setter Award
Oikawa Toru
Oikawa was given the Best Setter Award.
This award is proof that our
spikers gave it all they had.
Does that mean Ushiwaka's even higher?
Once we get into high school,
that's when...
we'll show Shiratorizawa who's boss!
Naturally.
And Tobio-chan,
I don't know where you'll
be headed after this,
but I'm gonna crush you,
so you better be prepared.
Blow your nose before saying your line!
Would you like a tissue?
Shut up!
Go, go, go! Go, go, Seijoh!
Karasuno                                      Aoba Johsai
Bring it!
Push it, push it, push it! Push it, Seijoh!
Nice serve!
Now we have Oikawa-kun serving...
The second opponent you want to show
who's boss is right in front of you...
You can give it all you've got.
I know.
Go!
Nishinoya!
It went up!
Yeah! But it's going to go
right back to Seijoh's side.
If they miss a serve here, they'd be losing
this set, and yet he served like that...
He's amazing!
Chance ball!
The receive went perfectly
back to the setter.
The highest probability is that they'll
use a quick attack from the center.
It probably is. I know that's what I'd do...
But in this stage where they're being
pushed into a corner, Oikawa-san...
will set it to Iwaizumi-san!
All right!
Karasuno                                      Aoba Johsai
Seriously?
Karasuno got the set back.
Damn it! I'm sorry!
Don't mind!
Why are you laughing? I'll punch you!
Stop saying you'll hit me
all the time, Iwa-chan.
Don't worry. I'd only say that
to you, and I won't hit you.
Right then, doing a quick attack from the
center would have been the cliché move.
What?
But apparently Tobio was able to read
that I'd send to the left.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Do you understand what this means?
It means it's come down to
not only methodical thinking,
but, in the end, our effort, as well.
My perfect trust with you, Iwa-chan.
Like I'd ever want that with you.
That just means they were making
rather comprehensive decisions.
What did Mr. Refreshing
tell Tobio?
The dictator king is somehow
trying to become a decent king.
What is this?
I'm really pissed off, and yet...
Hurry! Let's hurry up and finish
the final set!
Next Episode Preview
We've gotten to the final set.
Man, I got way too worked up,
even though it's out of character.
That's rare.
Though my selling point is the
fact that I'm a cute beauty.
Make volleyball your selling point!
Next time on Haikyu!!:
The Point that Changes the Momentum.
Episode 23:
The Point that Changes the Momentum