In Use
Her injuries are minor,
so the pain should
subside relatively quickly,
but she should avoid strenuous activities.
Yes, doctor.
Also, I noticed signs of malnutrition.
Malnutrition?
Do you know why that would be?
No.
You'll have to withdraw from the tournament.
They asked that you not participate
because they can't be responsible
for a minor getting hurt.
You've caused a lot of trouble for everyone.
You need to take a step back.
Episode 8
Worrying and Racing Ahead
You haven't been eating much lately.
What's going on?
I'll never get in...
There's a weight limit,
and they won't take anyone who's over it.
At the equestrian school?
Yes.
What's the limit?
Oh...
Even if I lose weight,
there's a parent interview.
And if I get any taller,
it'll totally ruin my chances.
When I called them,
they were completely discouraging.
It's not my fault I'm tall!
I told you.
You got yourself here because
you were stuck in your dream
world, ignoring basic facts!
Hey...
Can you see how naive you've been?
I'll pay for your education,
so study and go to university.
Once you have a career,
you can ride in your free time—
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
Get out!
Come on.
You'll face a few problems,
changing your plan this late,
but there's no rush.
Take your time.
1st Choice: Riding Academy
2nd Choice: Nothing <3
Why are they using our room?
Don't you know you have to audition
to use the main stage
during the White Festival?
All music rooms are reserved as
practice rooms for those participants.
We want to use this one.
You can't just do that.
We've got the vice principal's permission.
And what about us?
I'm sure there's room for you by the bike rack.
But there's no piano there!
Oh, you actually use one?
Everyone's in a mad scramble
to secure practice rooms
before the festival.
It's because you don't know this stuff
that people think you're playing around.
Horseback riding does
not constitute work.
It's play!
Must be nice to have
so much free time!
Shut up.
And don't make me laugh.
What makes you so great,
when all you're doing
is chugging down the tracks the
vice principal laid out for you?
Don't assume we're out of the running
because we didn't know about this.
If you think too hard,
you might hurt your little brains.
Sawa...
We're only getting started,
but you have the nerve to
tell me we have no chance?!
Huh?
Maybe it'll work out just fine!
Trying to take away our
one chance is so unfair!
Sawa!
Let's go.
You have a piano at home, right?
Yes, but my room won't fit five people.
The guys can stay outside.
I'm going home.
Don't be a brat!
Think about the times we had nothing!
We've got a piano at my place.
There room for five people?
Probably.
And it'd be okay?
For sure.
My parents aren't home in the afternoon.
Where do you live?
About thirty minutes from here.
I'll lead the way. We'll take the train.
Okay!
Party at Wien's house!
This is why people say
we're just playing around.
Would you rather she act
like the vice principal?
Sawa, we're leaving.
Oh, okay, I'll go grab my bike.
But we're taking the train.
Oh, right. Sorry.
Lost love...
Are you friends with any ninjas?
Nope.
They must be in hiding, huh.
More importantly, does your
place have high ceilings?
I wish we could choose
who we fall in love with...
If we had a choice,
we'd be spared a world of pain.
I mean, if you end up with
the person you want, that's great,
but plenty of people don't.
It's so sad...
Konatsu?
I know you'll find someone who loves you,
and who'll take care of you.
Huh?
But until that day,
if you need someone to hold,
you can hold me!
Maeda
Your house has a gate!
Are you millionaires?
This used to be my grandfather's house,
but he donated it to the
company before he died.
Since we had to move so suddenly,
we're renting it for now.
We don't use most of the rooms.
This way.
Come on in.
This place is huge!
There's even a fireplace.
Hey, let's start a fire!
We can't.
It's not used anymore.
These would get in the
way of a badminton game.
You can't play in here.
Sawa, check this out!
Death Chop!
Stop it...
Don't touch those!
Huh?
Ah, sorry.
It's just, those are very important to me.
They're the Gambaraijers,
the heroes who protect the world's hopes.
Oh, sorry...
The red one's missing.
Yeah. Red's on a very important
mission, in a faraway place.
So, where's the piano?
We can't use this.
You guys came all the
way here for nothing...
Not true.
We'll just practice without the piano.
I'm sorry, but I need to go.
If your breakup was that painful,
you should talk to us about it!
What?
We all want to help you.
We do?
So, you can't be a jockey?
I'll never get into the school.
But that's not for sure, right?
Maybe if you try really hard...
Yeah!
You can do it, Sawa.
What if you tried taking a step back?
A step back?
Yes, some distance might help you examine
your feelings with more clari—
Must be nice to be such an expert!
You can only talk like that because
music is easy to go back to!
But if I step back now,
it's all over for me!
I'll have no future!
Sawa...
I'm glad I was able to
go back to music,
because my mother and I promised
to write a song together.
Music keeps me connected to her.
Then again, if I could see her
just one more time...
I'd give up music in a heartbeat.
But that's not an option.
Even a Cat Can Learn
Lessons in Composition
A cat's kicking my butt...
Okita Sawa
Stepping back just means quitting.
Why is everyone telling me to quit?
Am I being naive?
I feel so empty...
It might sound strange,
but according to
virtual water theory,
the Japanese water supply is largely
dependent on foreign sources.
Excuse me.
You asked for us?
Withdraw your application.
Why?
You're just favoring the
music majors over us,
since they're more serious
about the future, right?
We respectfully refuse.
Sakai-san, what are you doing?
I didn't approve your
entry into general studies
so you could waste your
time on such nonsense.
Until I entered the choir club,
I thought of music as a
skill you cultivated alone.
But I was wrong.
You need to be with others,
let your feelings intersect and connect,
and experience joy and suffering together.
I'm not explaining it well, but...
I can't create a beautiful harmony...
...all by myself.
Isn't it more fun?
Isn't it nice to be around people?
Despite what you said,
you always went off and
accomplished things on your own.
Madam Vice Principal, music does love me,
if only a little.
Remember when you told me
I didn't have that special
something that moves people?
I can't do it alone.
But with the help of my friends,
I think I'm finally at a point
where I have the potential
to move people's hearts.
I believe a teacher's job
is to develop that potential!
So please, let us go up on that stage.
All right, but you'll have to convince me.
There's an audition for all groups who
wish to use the main stage.
Don't just tell me your
choir club has improved.
Prove it, by participating
in the audition.
We will.
When is it?
Today?!
This is bad. Very, very bad. Sawa!
She's not here today,
we'll have to go it alone.
Are you nuts?
If we were a choir of 100,
this would be like missing 20 people!
Why won't Sawa pick up her phone?!
Leave a message.
I'll text her.
The customer you have dialed
is away from the phone.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Sawa, we're in trouble!
We just found out we have to
audition for the main stage, today!
Please come! If you leave now,
you could make it!
Without you, we'll be totally—
She's not calling back.
Let it go.
She's in no condition to sing.
He's right.
That hurts...
Sawa's really depressed, so maybe
saying "we want you here" isn't enough.
Ah, yeah.
We should be doing something for her...
When I was depressed,
I wanted to be left alone.
Then again, it was nice to know people cared.
Then we have to somehow
show Sawa that we care!
But how?
Sakai Wakana
I don't think I said anything horrible,
or was told anything horrible that day.
But if I hurt you in
any way, I apologize.
I'm sorry.
Did you get Konatsu's message?
We don't want to give up without a fight,
so the four of us are going to sing.
But we'd feel much more
confident if you were with us.
Wakana is so strong.
Now I'm embarrassed.
I'm asking you to explain your reason!
What? The parents' heights?!
How is that relevant?!
What about a horse's
connection with its rider?
My daughter is serious about this!
She's been riding since she was a little girl.
She can care for them, too.
She's a gentle girl, who understands the
hearts of horses better than anyone...
What?!
I dare you to say that again!
You're dealing with a monk, here!
I'll send you straight to hell! Bam!
My daughter's been through hell.
She's been so worried,
she went on a ridiculous diet
that made her fall off her horse.
Understand?
She's serious.
No matter what he says,
you mean the world to him.
He's just terrible at expressing his feelings.
I'll talk to the school.
You should apologize to your father.
I can't.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Sawa, are you listening?
I only have one thing to say.
I care about you.
I'll always be here for
you, if you'll let me!
And we're still waiting for you.
That's two things.
Anyway, Miyamoto Konatsu will now sing.
I believe in you.
Sawa, I'll wait for you forever.
Here.
Huh?
With the courage to accept
what can't be changed,
you'll move forward again.
Here.
Okay.
Even if you stumble,
even if you lose a match,
there's always tomorrow.
Here.
The light of hope burns
bright forevermore,
because you are a hero.
That's right, you're a hero!
Sawa, that was our—
What a weird song.
You were listening?
Yep, I was.
We're in big trouble!
The vice principal said we have to—
Yeah, I know.
I'm on my way, so wait right there!
But we're taking the train.
Oh, right. Sorry.
I'm off!
Okay, see you later.
Must be our turn soon.
Think Sawa will make it?
Choir club, please get ready.
We're first?!
I wish we could've all been here for this.
I've got it!
Push in Case of Emergency
Don't do it!
If this isn't an emergency,
then what is?
Not this, that's for sure!
Forget the festival,
our club will be disbanded!
Vice principal, there is a call for you.
Please come to the telephone.
Was that you?
Please hurry, Sabure!
Vice principal, there is a call for you.
Please come to the telephone.
Wait!
I made it!
Yeah!
I like red.
Are we really wearing this?
Bursting with flavor! Whitebait White!
Energy Charge!
Episode 9
Turning White and Turning Red
Meat Red!
I don't want curry.