I haven't seen you before.
What is a woman doing here
so early in the morning?
Oh, don't worry about it.
Just come here.
Hey...
Do you like flowers?
Troops—
Let him have it!
Al Huma!
Troops! Follow those two fools!
They're firing the night-banisher.
Close your eyes.
Whoa...
It's just like everyone said! Incredible!
That's... the White Whale?
It's so huge.
Are you scared?
Yeah, I'm scared...
of the blindingly bright future,
where I'm praised for defeating it!
Now, let's run like hell!
Yes.
It's so fast!
You greatly underestimate us,
looking away so carelessly.
The intangible sword,
without regard for range.
That is Crusch-sama's sword art,
famous for its Hundred-Man Strike.
Disperse!
For fourteen years,
I have dreamed of nothing but this day.
Fall here, and leave your corpse behind.
You are naught but a monster!
How wonderfully cooperative of you,
coming here to be slain!
Oh, crap!
Don't you look away from us, moron!
Here, we go!
Everyone, now!
Troops, get back!
Fire at its flank!
Algoa!
Looks like that was pretty effective!
I think we can pull this off!
No, truthfully,
we had hoped that attack would ground it.
It's not losing altitude at all...
We used all of our best attacks
right from the get-go.
If that didn't make it fall,
it's a lot tougher than we thought.
The magic attacks didn't work?
Its white hair scatters mana
and disperses force.
My magic was not as effective
as it appeared, either.
Fire!
Time for the second campaign.
Hack away at its reserve power!
Acting as a decoy now would be a hindrance...
So all we can do is watch
until it makes a move?
I feel just as irritated as you do.
I don't even have any attacks,
so all I can do is watch, anyway...
But with your healing specialty,
you're our lifeline.
Just fulfill that role for us!
We're counting on you.
You've really changed
in just one day, huh?
What happened?
If I had to say,
I've just become a slightly better man.
Wilhelm-sama is...
Upsy-daisy!
Miserable...
What is that?
Something's odd...
What's going on?
The color of its eye...
Have you grown to like flowers?
No, I hate them.
Why do you wield that sword?
Because this is all I have.
It disappeared?
We're going to move! Hang on!
Troops, retreat!
Retreat!
Retreat! Re—
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
That's what the magic fog looks like?
If that hits us...
How many men did we lose?
Twelve from my unit.
We're three short now.
Who was lost?
I don't know.
Fourteen from mine.
One deserted.
I'm missing six. I'm sorry.
No one was riding on the
opposite side from me.
Who is Rem?
Rem... Who is that?
You've forgotten Rem, too?
That's it...
People hit by the White Whale's fog
vanish from existence, along with
any memories of them.
A Fog of Elimination.
You're back?
Forgive my haste.
Damages?
A total of twenty-one lost.
It appears one whole platoon was wiped out.
It won't even be possible
to properly protect the honor of the lost.
My apologies.
Why do you wield that sword?
Because I could not think
of any other way to protect.
Now that it's in the fog,
we won't know whence it will attack.
Staying close is the worst thing we could do.
Disperse immediately.
What is that?
Is that the White Whale?
Hey! What's wrong?
Hey!
Hey! Rem!
That voice is the fog, which is
directly attacking our minds...
Similar to mana sickness,
but much worse...
Some people can resist it, and some can't?
I don't feel anything...
It's all right.
It will calm down now.
Hey!
Enough... Stop it!
Felis!
Have the unaffected help them!
They say hurting people is harder
on an army than killing them,
but what monster does that?
Move!
I guess Felis can remove the effects
of the fog's contamination.
But there isn't enough time...
If it comes for us now, we're finished.
Crusch-san!
I'll buy us time.
Have everyone regroup!
What?
Rem, sorry, but I need you to accompany
me to the most dangerous place here!
Of course. Anywhere.
Wait, Natsuki Subaru!
In this fog...
Anyone who can hear me, listen up!
Anyone who can't, stay where you are!
I'll Return by Death to—
I'm back...
Well, Rem?
Do I smell like the Witch?
Yes, you reek!
That's what I wanted, but did
you have to say it that way?
Those who can move, get the injured
to the foot of the tree!
We'll have to use a bit of force.
With the ulgarm,
it was effective enough
to cover the whole forest.
What will it do this time?
Honestly, it's an unknown quantity...
No, it's working.
It's coming.
I-It's coming!
Ul Huma!
How?
Sis! Together!
Captain!
I got this!
Rem!
Looking away from me? How unfriendly.
And after I have spent the past fourteen
years utterly mad for you!
This is startin' to get fun.
It's more sturdy than expected,
but not all that strong!
No, it's putting up less
of a fight than it should.
I find it hard to believe this mabeast
got the better of my wife,
a Master Swordsman.
The fact that we got the jump on it,
and that it didn't use its fog to
divide our forces to start with—
I'll take one more thing before I leave!
Wilhelm-san!
Be alert!
We don't know whence it will come.
What's up?
It ain't gonna follow?
It comes.
The fog's coming down!
Run!
Hey, have you grown to like flowers?
What is it?
There was talk of conferral,
and I became a knight.
Well, congratulations.
Then you're one step closer to your dream.
My dream?
Don't you wield a sword to protect?
A knight is someone who protects another.
I don't want... to die...
It's humiliating!
I see.
Were you laughing at me?!
Answer me, Theresia!
No...
Master Swordsman Theresia van Astrea!
I won't... come here again.
With a face like that,
you shouldn't be holding a sword!
I am the Master Swordsman.
I didn't understand the reason why,
but I do now.
The reason...
Wielding a sword to protect someone.
That sounds nice to me, too.
Wait, Theresia...
I will take your sword from you!
I don't care about the role bestowed
upon the Master Swordsman!
Wielding a sword...
The beauty of a steel blade...
Don't look down on them,
Master Swordsman!
We have trouble!
You're kidding me...
Wilhelm van Astrea