Hunt them to extinction!
Those in Lutiel's fleet
are now under my command.
Charge the vanguard!
I am less than amused by
their assault on the gate.
"Alea Iacta Est"
It will take six hours for the
Straggle Laser to fully recharge.
We'll need to devise a
plan to tide us over.
But none of our attacks have been
effective against them in the past.
Maximize the rate of convergence
to increase penetration.
Blue 1's attack has already proven
that physical rounds should
be capable of penetrating
the high-energy barrier.
I suggest we take the initiative
and hit them with a saturation attack
to cripple their defense network and
destroy the gate's control system.
Permission granted!
The Star Rose and the fleet ships
will launch a controlled
artillery attack.
Roger. I will link all of our fleet's
sublight-speed guided missiles.
Link established!
Excellent.
Fire all of our sublight-speed
guided missiles!
The sublight-speed guided missiles have
entered their second stage acceleration.
Missile impact in 30 seconds!
All of the sublight-speed guided
missiles have been destroyed!
That is Lumes' unit.
They have the tightest
defenses amongst the Wulgaru.
They destroyed all of those guided
missiles in a split second...
So a long-range battle has
been rendered impossible?
Yes.
The 1st and 2nd Area Fleets'
rate of attrition is at 45%!
The Bela-Russian and the
Great Chinese Alliance's
fleets have begun to pull back.
All fleets, tighten your formation!
Anyone who pulls away from the
main fleet will get picked off!
But the Straggle Laser and our
saturation attack with sublight
guided missiles ended in failure.
We'll have to land a direct hit...
Information on Team
Rabbits... just came in!
No matter how many I shoot,
there's still more of 'em!
They have us completely surrounded.
My ammunition is down to 15%!
I'm just about outta energy!
Move it, you lowly insects!
It makes me sick how you're
swarming everywhere!
Guys...
If you refuse to show yourself,
I will force you to come out of hiding.
Blue 1's remaining
energy is down to 25%.
Rose 3 is down to 18%.
It will be difficult for
them to continue fighting.
Have them pull back, restock and refuel.
This is the Godinion.
Do you read, Kitty?
I repeat, this is the Godinion.
Meow, I hear ya!
All units are to return for now.
I'm confirming the route.
Retreat through Points 21-AF through EM.
I'll transfer the data.
Pull back while I keep 'em busy
with some diversionary shots!
Roger!
All units-
Look out!
There is a rapidly approaching
high speed heat source!
Tamaki, run for it!
What happened?!
It's that fighter from way back...!
He's dangerous! Get out
of there, Big Brother!
You heard him, Big Brother!
Verification on the
hostile object: Complete!
It's the guy from Ceres!
He's blocking our escape route.
Are there any other routes?
We'd have to cut straight through
the middle of the enemy's fleet.
This sucks...
Why are you acting like wusses?!
It's just a single fighter!
I'm sure we'll manage somehow
if everyone goes after him.
I guess that's our only option...
Kei, navigate!
Suruga, offer backup support!
Roger!
Tamaki, take the front of the Kette.
Ange, take the support position.
Roger!
Okay! Charge!
I may have lost my boosters,
but I still have my weapons!
Leave him to me!
He's in position!
He dodged that?
Damn it!
I'm not done yet!
Big Brother!
How much energy do they have left?
Blue 1 is at 1.9%.
He can't even get back off that...
Should we send him a booster?
Can we?
The preparations are already complete,
but I'm not sure the enemy will
give him enough time to dock...
What are his chances of
successfully docking?
43.8%.
It beats doing nothing and watching him
get cut down when he runs out of energy.
Launch it!
Roger!
Asagi, your booster is
coming. Dock with it!
Roger!
Ange, fill in for me right quick!
Sure thing! Suruga, back me up!
She finally said my name!
Hurry it up, ya damn bug!
I'll help you out!
Reinforcements!
To think that I would feel the urge to
immerse myself in the
hunt after all this time!
I never expected Dolgana to
personally enter the fray!
He is the Wulgaru's greatest general.
Ange!
Shit!
I'll deal with this bogey!
My unit's heavy!
Damn it all to hell!
Blue 1, you're down
to 3% residual energy.
You're at risk if you keep fighting!
Cut power to my left arm!
Pull back!
Until we defeat this guy,
that's not an option!
Are there any surplus forces?
No, ma'am!
What weapons do we have
left on this vessel?
Just a multipurpose short-range
guided missile launcher.
It doesn't have the range you need.
I'll go.
But the next time you get in that
AHSMB unit, it could kill you!
Everyone is out there fighting
their hardest so you don't have to.
Are you going to put
their efforts to waste?
That may be true, but I...
I'm ordering you to
wait in your quarters.
Peko, escort him.
Captain Suzukaze!
I love you.
Wha-?!
Reika,
Siegfried,
Guiliano,
Peko,
Natori Shion,
Degawa,
Mayu,
Dan,
everyone on the pit crew,
Commander Simon,
Teoria,
Kei,
Tamaki,
Ange,
Suruga,
and my big brother, Asagi,
I love all of you!
I was born all by myself,
never knowing what my parents look like.
But now I have a family
and I love so many people!
I can't die for their sake...
And besides...
And besides,
I still have a bunch of
manga that I want to draw!
So I'm not going to die!
Probably...
"Probably," he says.
Well, it's just like him to fall flat.
Isn't this when you're supposed
to give up and let him go?
You'll have to pardon me, but
considering our current situation,
I believe it will be difficult to turn
the tables without dispatching Red 5.
Go get 'em.
That's easy for you to say!
His unit is currently locked...
He can go whenever he's ready!
It's all warmed up!
You can take it to full power!
All right, then. Red
5, prepare to sortie.
You'd better come back to us!
Yes, ma'am!
Blast off!
We're counting on you...
So you've finally come.
Izuru?!
Dude, what're you doin' here?!
We told you to keep out of
this, you freakin' moron!
You stoopy-poopy head!
We told you to take it
easy and stay on the ship!
I'll be fine.
After all, I'm the hero... probably.
What's with that, "probably"?!
I've been eagerly awaiting
your arrival, my lamata!
Guys, withdraw while you still can!
Roger...!
The Great Chinese Alliance
is currently fleeing!
Bela-Russia is maintaining their
battle formation as they skirt back.
Africa's forces are in chaos!
The 1st Area Fleet's frontline
rate of attrition is at 64.9%!
How do things look for the Rabbits?
I'll put it on the screen!
So their hands are tied, too.
Fire all of the main cannons
simultaneously at Point DN-31!
While we're doing that, have
the 1st and 2nd Fleets
retreat at full speed.
The enemy is quickly closing in on us!
I don't care if we burn
out all of our cannons!
Fire! Fire! Fire like mad!
There are too many of them!
Enemy fighters are advancing.
What's the situation?
They'll get to start firing at us
long before they enter our range.
This is bad... Can you handle this?
Please leave everything to us!
My dream is to lead a carefree
life living off pension,
so I'll push myself a bit.
I'm sending you all of the enemy's
verified locations and past maneuvers.
Roger. After calculating their
anticipated movement patterns,
I'm going to pull out everything
from the top to 1024.
Inputting random firing coefficients
for the anticipated patterns.
I've indicated that the ship
is to prioritize safety
while also eliminating
any margin of error.
If we drop the safety margin by 0.2,
the evasion rate goes up 14.72%.
How would that affect the safety?
I'm guessing we'll lose
our kitchen plates
and suffer muscle pain in the morning.
Then do it.
Roger! I'm sending over
the pilot control data.
Our vessel will begin
taking evasive measures!
All crew, you have 20
seconds to brace yourselves
and prepare for turbulence!
We're down to 10 seconds!
Pilot controls are set for full auto!
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one!
Accelerate!
The evasive pattern is
within permissible range!
It's a good thing they're drawing the
big shots' attention away from us.
Fire all weapons!
He's faster than before!
If I don't stop him here and now...!
Crap!
What?!
Just now...
Please send me fuel, ammunition,
a left arm and a booster pod!
They're ready to go!
I just gotta input your coordinates.
I should have known.
Please send them over.
Knowing you, don't freak out
and screw up the docking.
Change the parts, quick!
We're all out of spare boosters.
Now what?
I don't care what you
do, just do something!
Now I remember...
That's right.
I shouldn't suppress the
AHSMB's survival instinct...
Rather than defy its survival instinct,
I should provide it directionality!
That's it!
Let me see more of what you can do!
You're just a stinking big bug!
The way you keep scurrying
here and there,
you must be a cockroach!
Let me squish you already!
Damn it! Why can't I hit him?!
Escort vessel Takanami, destroyed.
Close-Support Fleet down to 21 ships!
Our vessel's firing capabilities
are down to 12%.
We've lost our armor plating
from Block 1 to Block 3.
The engine is still capable
of working at maximum power!
It will take another
eight minutes for the
1st and 2nd Fleets to reorganize.
The Great Chinese Alliance
and Bela-Russian's army
are out of our sensor's range.
How long before the Straggle
Laser is fully charged?
It will be ready in ten minutes!
No matter what the cost,
we must destroy that
gate's control system!
Engine at full power!
Have the remaining fleets
enter Code: Fish Formation!
Prepare to charge!
Our ship will now break through the
center of the enemy's formation...
and head for the gate!
Tally-ho!
The cavalry has arrived!
Doberman...?
I'm part of Doberman 2 now.
All units, charge!
Those are the mass-produced AHSMB units!
The enemy vanguard is pulling back!
Retrieving those units made us run late.
Pulling back to lure the enemy in
is a traditional tactic of ours.
Now is the time for a counterattack!
There is nowhere for
us to go but forward!
The 1st and 2nd Fleets
have finished regrouping!
All fleets, advance!
We will seize the gate
in one fell swoop!
Remaining distance: 20%.
The gate is within firing range!
All ships, concentrate
your fire on the gate!
Hit it with everything you've got!
All units, open your
fields to maximum output.
Clear them out.
They blocked our attack?!
Here comes the counterattack!
Enter shock-absorbing
defensive positions!
Damage report!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
I'm not done yet!
Big Brother and Teoria...
Give me the power to protect everyone!
Izuru Hitachi's Harmonic
Level is rising.
Red 5 has reached maximum output.
Contacting Rada and Klein's squad.
Prepare to fire at full power.
Annihilate the enemy
with that one attack!
Forces have decreased by 21%.
We've lost our armor
plating up to Block 5!
It's dangerous to continue
participation in the battle!
But we can't afford to stop now!
Enemy reinforcements!
How much longer before we
can fire the Straggle Laser?
Five minutes!
We're running out of time!
We'll ram our ship into
the gate's control system.
All crew, prepare to abandon ship!
Hold off on that!
We'll hit it with this!
But how?!
Ta-da-da!
Thanks for waiting!
Klein's squad, attack
the enemy vanguard.
Rada's squad, serve as mobile
defense on the flanks.
Don't let them through!
The Straggle Laser will be
ready to fire in two minutes!
Are you all right, Asagi?
"Yeah, this is nothing,"
...or so I'd like to say, but
there are too many of them.
It can't be...!
Something just came out!
It's a new model!
People of Wulgaru, listen to me.
My name is...
My name is Pleguzesia Teoria.
I am a descendant of the great Dakihaan
as well as one who shares the
genes of the rightful ruler
of the galaxy, Eguzes Galkie.
Those who hear my voice,
Pleguzesia Teoria orders you:
Retreat immediately.
Teoria?!
She's pretty...
She's like a goddess.
Don't try to flirt with her.
She waited for the best possible timing!
You knew about this?
You should have shown yourself sooner!
Teoria?!
Teoria!
Not happening!
I swear I will protect Teoria!
I never expected that I
would take you seriously...
Hear the throbbing pulse of my genes!
Like I'm gonna let you get away!
Damn it! You're a lame coward the
way you're so freaking quick to run!
What a pity!
You shoulda gotten
here sooner, slowpoke!
We're going to hit him from both sides.
Stay out of my line of fire!
Don't order me around!
You are doing this of your
own free will, aren't you?
What's goin' on?
A path to our goal just opened up.
Charge full speed ahead!
Roger that!
What are you doing?!
Everyone, return to your posts!
You're up against me!
Don't forget about me!
Stay in formation.
I already told you,
don't order me around!
Release the final safety lock.
Rate of convergence: 500.
Go!
I'm counting on you!
Tamaki, come back!
Roger!
Nine, eight, seven,
six, five, four,
three, two!
We did it!
Fire the Straggle Laser!
Will this do it?
The Straggle Laser has been hit!
Isn't that... Dolgana's unit?
The Straggle Laser has
been completely destroyed.
We've... run out of options.
No, we still have one left.
He's completely awoken...?
The awakened Red 5 will
illuminate the path.
We will hit the gate with the largest
body of mobile mass we have.
Roger!
All crew, quickly abandon
the ship from both sides-
Amane's ship is to stay as it is!
The Star Rose's crew is to
abandon ship on the double!
I'm going to ram the
Star Rose into the gate.
"Flowers Falling in Space"