Woohoo, Dome City!
There are so many people.
I know.
Hey, let's go on the Thunder Dolphin.
Hey, hey, I looked it up.
There's a ferris wheel, and then
there's the roller coasters, and...
What a weird bunch.
Why is it the nine of us?
The amusement park?
My parents got free passes.
I'll go!
I'll invite Azumi-kun, too.
And Hira, so it'll be the four of us.
Amusement park?
Me, too! I'm in!
I don't have that many passes.
Come on, we can split the cost.
Right?
Seriously?
I have a practice match that day.
I'll be in Hawaii.
I'll invite Nagahara and the others.
The more the merrier, right?
Agreed!
Totally.
It'll be fun in a big group, though.
Yeah.
Is anyone available to board alone?
Me, me, me!
We'd have one leftover, anyway.
Viva, off you go!
Roman...
We'd have one leftover?
How badly did he wanna go?
Please make your way to the platform,
and wait behind the white line
on top of the white footprints.
Hey, Azumi-kun, sit next to me.
Hey, Setsuko. Let's do that thing later.
What? Are you crazy?
Viva, off you go!
Wait, wait, it's starting.
No, I'm serious. Come on, let's do that thing!
Crap... Oh crap, oh crap!
Are you okay?
Don't say it!
We're so high up!
I told you not to say it!
Sorry, sorry.
Azumi-kun, stuff like this doesn't bother you?
Nah, not at all.
Let's be like, "Viva Dome City!" on our way down.
Oh, here we go!
One, two...
Viva Dome City!
Viva, welcome back! Viva, welcome back!
Viva, viva! Welcome back!
That was fun.
I thought you'd handle it better.
It was scarier than I thought it'd be.
Are you okay?
Th-Thanks.
That was so fun! Let's go again.
Can't we check out some other ones first?
Are you okay, Akanecchi?
Yeah, I'm fine.
So you don't do well on rides?
Oh, well...
Viva cute!
That looks good on you.
See?
Really?
You should buy it, Kota.
Nope, no way.
That looks good on you, Hira-kun!
You should buy one with Akanecchi.
Come on.
Hira-kun, Hira-kun! Over here.
Say cheese.
You know...
Right?
What?
Nothing!
That looks good on you.
Stop it.
Huh? Where's Roman?
He was here a second ago.
Anyone available to board alone?
Me, me, me!
He'll be fine.
Yeah.
I'll go look around.
Sure.
Curly-kun!
Did you find Roman-kun?
Nope.
Damn it.
Oh, hey. Look. It's our picture from earlier.
What the heck?
I thought it'd make for a good souvenir.
Are you sure? This?
Yeah.
You have your eyes closed, Nishio-san.
You can call me Chinatsu.
That's what everyone calls me. Even the guys.
Yeah, but...
Can I call you Kota, too?
Kota.
Kota, Kota, Kota!
Come on, say my name.
Ch-China...
I can't even hear you.
Once more.
No, I'm good.
Hey...
Everyone went to line up for the next one.
Oh, okay.
Let's go.
Roman
The amusement park group
What?!
I'm at First Aid
First Aid
Please press the intercom button
to the right to enter the first aid station
Tokyo Dome City Attractions
Yes?
Um, I'm Yamashina Roman's friend.
Please come in.
Pardon me.
Kota.
What happened?
And how?
Heatstroke?
You need to drink plenty of water.
Okay.
Please rest up before you go back out.
You be sure to stay hydrated, too.
Right.
Man, you scared me.
Sorry, I'm kinda the sickly type.
Don't push yourself.
I went overboard.
What's wrong?
Well, you know.
Ah... Her?
Who?
Mizuno-san.
Are you two dating?
Why?
Just a guess.
Everyone's here, though.
Yeah.
Why not get lost together?
I'll help you out.
But...
I'll call up Mizuno-san, so...
Quit it.
What? No way...
We're here
We're by the merry-go-round
Okay
Where are you, Akanecchi?
Sorry, I got lost
With Hira?
Yeah
I think they should be around here.
I'm sure we'll find them soon.
Here.
Thanks.
Don't worry about it.
I feel bad, though.
I said it's fine.
No, no.
What are we, two old ladies?
Fine, I'll keep it, then.
Man, that takes me back!
The hero show rocked!
I cheered like mad!
Hey, did you know the Big O
is 60 meters in diameter?
Azumi-kun.
It's 80 meters high.
You sure did your research.
Where's Mizuno-san?
Give her some space.
Seriously.
He likes her.
They're so cute together.
Oh, yeah, take a look at this.
What?
Isn't this great?
Oh my God!
I know, right? Isn't it great?
Sorry.
Jeez, watch where you're going.
Are you okay?
Let's go over there.
Oh, um... Sure.
Mizuno-san.
She's my girlfriend.
We're in a relationship.
Really?
Yeah.
Let's go, Mizuno-san.
Okay.
Aren't we missing some people?
We lost them.
I told them we'll be here on LINE.
Kaneko.
Hey.
Huh? Are you alone?
Can I ask you something?
Is Mizuno in a relationship?
What?! Wait, what, what, what?!
With Azumi.
Yeah.
They are.
What? Really?
I had no idea.
I had absolutely no clue.
Wait, Roman, you knew?
Since when?
Sorry, I got lost in the moment.
Nah.
It's the truth, after all.
Yeah.
Man, I'm hungry.
Me, too.
I wonder where everyone went.
Can we...
A little longer?
I'll let them know.
Let's eat.
Hey, come to think of it...
This is our first time eating together.
Yeah, it is.
Here we go!
I'm soaked.
House of the Haunted Bracelet
We're not even in the picture.
Really?
Come closer.
Okay, here we go.
You startled me there.
Sorry.
Can I see?
Nice.
It's like...
Looks good.
We really do look like we're going out.
We do.
Chinatsu-chan!
Sorry I'm late.
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
Nah.
Chinatsu?
Hey, check this out!
Enough.
Have you seen Akane and...
They're doing their own thing for now.
Apparently they're going out.
Yeah.
Don't tell me...
Azumi?
Are you okay?
Let's go see the fireworks.
Okay.
Sorry, we...
It's starting!
We had no idea.
It's almost over.
Let's come back sometime.
Just the two of us.
Yeah.
They're kissing!
Get over here!
Hira...
Yeah?
Sorry I invited you here today.
Why?
I don't know. Just because.
It's fine.
I'm not bothered by it.
Chinatsu
Morning
Where are we meeting up again?
Yeah
Where are you?
I see you!
I'll be right there
Did you see the fireworks?
Yeah, I saw them
I couldn't confess
Sorry.
Hold Back Nothing When Taking Love
Sakura's Fantasies 2
Sorry.
What was that?
Was it on purpose?
That was on purpose!
Just because he can't bring himself to
talk to me because he likes me...
We're not in elementary school, you know.
Apparently Ogasawara-kun has
a standard score above 65.
He's pretty popular with the teachers.
He looks pretty well-to-do.
And he's a second son.
He's got a lot going for him!
Too bad he's in the judo club.
Ryouko-sensei and the Girls 1
The white light sets the mountains ablaze
Far beyond the distant sky...
See?
Oh, damn!
Boys suck.
I mean, can you blame them?
Ryouko-sensei's so pretty.
I guess.
I liked our last music
teacher better, though.
Me, too.
I mean, I like Ryouko-sensei too, of course.
But she's just kind of...
Kind of...
Annoying.
I know, right?
Ryouko-sensei and the Girls 2
She smells so nice.
Oh man, oh man, oh man...
Boys suck.
Are teachers even supposed
to be wearing perfume?
It's kind of un-classy, don't you think?
I know. She's a teacher.
Ryouko-sensei said she uses this.
Soap scent?
Really?
That's so childish.
Gimme.
Me, too.
I want to try.
Wait, I might actually like this.
It's pretty nice.
I think I like it.
Ryouko-sensei and the Girls 3
Hey, look at this.
What? Isn't that Ryouko-sensei?
"Charming Women We Spotted in Town"?
I know this website.
It's really popular.
Wow!
I saw you on that website, Ryouko-sensei.
Oh my God, you're so cute!
Were the girls always so chummy with her?
Dunno.
Setsuko and Nagahara 4
~The Breakup~
I want to break up.
Why?
Why? Because...
That's all we ever do.
You don't listen to me.
Okay.
Let's take some time to talk.
Break                                      Short Time
Weekdays
Weekends
Holidays
2 Hours
Overnight
We can spend plenty of time here.
This guy's a total loser.
Creep.
Sorry... Can you pay?
I know, I know!
Sakura's Fantasies 3
Nagahara and Setsuko broke up!
What?!
The biggest sleazeball in class
is currently heartbroken.
Maybe he's actually really
sensitive with a heart of glass.
Maybe I'm the only one who notices that.
"Weird... This is our first
time talking to each other,
but it feels like we've
known each other forever."
"Could this be destiny?"
And the two of us fall in love...
Hell no, party animal.