Don't put too much water
on the sharpening stone.
Okay.
70% of it goes at the front,
and 30% at the back.
Okay.
Another day's over!
Yup.
Tomorrow's meal for the Crane Room has been changed
to the Bamboo course,
instead of the Plum course.
Okay.
Oh, Mr. Ren,
the customer in the Wisteria Room yesterday
said that the meal was excellent.
Yeah?
Oh, and...
the shaved line in your
eyebrow looks really cool today!
N-Now, if you'll excuse me...
Don't you think Nako's changed lately?
You think so?
How do I explain it...
She's become a lot more outgoing.
You sure do pay a lot of attention to her.
I'll get it.
Hello, this is the kitchen.
You wanna talk to Minko?
Minko, it's Ohana.
I'm busy right now.
She says she's busy.
Oh...
Look, I'm serious!
What are you talking about?
You're the one who said that!
And, so...
our booth for the 20th Kourin
Festival, in a week's time, is...
...a Princess Café!
After all, the most distinctive
features of our class are
the two princesses.
We should fully
utilize our advantages!
Okay, so the leader of our service team is...
Princess Yuina Wakura!
Thank you. Thank you.
And the leader of our cooking team is...
Princess Minko Tsurugi!
Hey!
Don't just decide things on your own!
Tsurugi.
Let's fest it up together.
A warm cheer of friendship
from princess to princess!
Splendid!
Finally, the guys are in
charge of all the odd jobs!
Are you still in a bad mood, Minchi?
Shut up.
Hey, Team Kissuiso!
I'll be getting off here today.
Let's go home together!
The cultural festival is pretty lively here.
I'm impressed!
Our class is the only one
that's making such a fuss
about it, like morons.
Your previous school was very different?
Well, it wasn't as lively.
As a whole, our generation was
never that interested in it.
What are you talking about?
Well, you're right.
Our class is very excited about it.
Yeah! It's like the best
part of our youth!
As if.
Come on! You agreed to being in
charge of the cooking team.
I didn't really agree to it...
Really?
It's just that everyone else was
going crazy on their own.
Don't be such a party pooper.
Let's all have fun together!
See? Ohana's looking forward to it.
Yup! Yup!
I'd rather you didn't, thanks.
What?
Oh, I was afraid that you were going to say no, Yuina.
Why?
Well, you did say once that you didn't like
working in the service industry.
I don't mind since it's not work.
Besides, it seems like they have
high expectations of me.
At times like this, I'm considerate, so I'll meet their expectations.
Let's do our best!
People always tell me
that I'm inconsiderate.
Oh, I meant, "Let's fest it up!"
Yeah, you are.
Do you have to be so blunt?
Cultural festival, eh?
Let's see... it starts on Sunday,
and you need the entirety of
Friday and Saturday to prepare.
It'll be pretty tough to have both of you off on Saturday...
I really want to go,
since it doesn't happen very often...
I don't mind working my shift...
You can both go.
Madam Manager.
Really?!
Of course.
You need to participate
in school events.
However, you must work extra hard
on the days you're here.
Of course!
Aren't you glad, Nakochi?!
What? Yeah.
Oh, we better tell Minchi!
Let's go!
She seems so happy.
But Nako doesn't.
Yes, this is Kissuiso.
Oh, Kutani Oil!
Yes, it's always a pleasure
working with you.
Oh, Bean-
I mean, Sukegawa?
One moment, please.
Denroku left with his son earlier.
Oh...
I'm terribly sorry,
Sukegawa is currently out-
With his son?!
Cultural festival?
Did you know about this, Mr. Ren?
No.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know that I was
going to be participating.
I don't mind.
You're a student.
Go and have some fun.
Well, there you have it.
Sunday, eh?
But...
Maybe I'll pay a visit.
Oh, it's just that there
aren't going to be
many customers during lunchtime, so I'll be free.
Oh, then you should
definitely pay our café a visit!
We're Class 2-A!
Sure, if I feel like it.
Cleaning
I think that gave
Minchi some motivation.
Definitely.
That's it!
What?
The title for my next work.
High School Girls: The Night before
the Fired-up Culture Festival.
This is gonna be a masterpiece!
Is it gonna be some hot-blooded action novel?
No. No.
What I mean by "fired-up"
is flames of love.
What? That's weird!
It makes it sound like a story
set around a campfire.
That's it!
Burning! Campfire and
High School Girls!
How's that?
It still sounds like an action to me.
Fine, let's change it to:
Campfires and Wet High School Girls.
But wouldn't that put the fire out?
Oh, damn!
Could you please help clean, Jiromaru?
Oh, yeah.
What's your class doing, Nakochi?
Oh, so you're a part of the cultural festival committee!
Awesome!
How aggressive, Nakochi!
Nope, I'm actually really
bad at that stuff.
Everyone will help you.
Yeah...
What are you guys doing?
Running a food stand?
Displaying art.
A girl in our class is part of the fine arts club.
Some of her art work is displayed outside the school,
so we all decided that we'd display
art with hers as the centerpiece.
That sounds wonderful!
I'll be sure to pay a visit.
Thanks.
It's so wonderful for a class
to get together and do something.
It's such a fresh feeling for me!
I'm so excited! Aren't you, Nakochi?
Yeah.
So, Nakochi's class is displaying art.
I see...
I wonder what kind of art they're exhibiting?
Will you come and see it with me?
Hm...
Let's go!
Cultural Festival
Menu
Sure...
And so, I, Minko Tsurugi,
will be in charge of the cooking staff.
I look forward to working with you all.
Even if it's a school event,
we must put all our efforts into
the food we serve our customers.
Let's do our best.
Yeah!
She's completely different from yesterday.
Did something happen?
Well, how do I explain it...
Anyway, it's great that
she's so into it now.
Guys, we can't lose to them!
As we're going to be waitresses,
I want us all to wear cute uniforms.
I don't know if they'll be ready in time,
and it'll cost money too...
Me!
Tadaa!
These are the old waitress
uniforms at Kissuiso.
Madam Manager said
we could use them!
Oh, that's right. You showed
me a few of them during filming!
Yeah!
We hung them outside after
that, so they're all clean and odorless.
We've got loads more,
so I'll bring them in!
All right!
What? We can't broil fish?
Well, it's kinda hard.
We're not allowed to use gas in the classrooms.
We could use the home economics room,
but it's pretty far from here.
Okay, I guess we shouldn't do that then.
Oh, and the smell of fish
might disturb the other classes.
Oh...
We can use a hot plate and a microwave.
Oh, and a rice cooker.
Hey, we can make omelet rice!
I'm all for omelet rice!
We can write stuff in ketchup too!
But that's so clichéd!
That's what makes it so good!
Right?
Really?
194 cm.
Thanks.
Sorry, Mizuno.
I hadn't realized it'd be like this.
The entire class was
supposed to have agreed.
I don't mind.
You also had the duties off-loaded
onto you as a committee member.
I...
Mind getting the measurements over here?
Oh, sorry!
Nako!
Oh... sorry.
Come on, finish it!
And the mother rolly-polly...
Princess Bath
Women
Omelet Rice
Let's party...
Good morning... Let's fest it up...
Bust!
Waist!
Hips!
Morning...
Mr. Ren,
do you mind if I pop out
during lunch this Sunday?
Sure.
Thanks.
All right.
Hey, Minko, isn't that burning?
What?
Oh-
I'm sorry...
Thanks for waiting!
Are you two going to
be back late tonight?
Yup.
The festival's in two days time,
so we need to stay after school and prepare.
I don't mind working...
No, it's fine!
Madam Manager's going
to phone the union
and ask for reinforcements.
The cultural festival, eh?
The whole class working together
towards the same objective...
It's like the best part of your youth!
Yeah, that's right!
Oh, maybe your boyfriend in
Tokyo will pay you a visit.
N-No...
I'm a Shijima girl,
so I don't have a boyfriend,
nor will I ever get one.
What?
That's a little different from
what you said last time.
No it isn't!
Ohana... Your surname is
"Matsumae," not "Shijima."
They're late.
Over here, Ohana!
Ohana, I wanna place an order!
Coming!
Man, I'm so busy!
Ko!
Wow, you're a maid now!
Yeah! I decided to fest it up with you!
Yeah! Let's!
Yeah!
Ohana...
Ohana!
We're almost there.
What the heck was that dream?
What does it mean?!
No... No...
Shijima girls live to work!
I need to do my best.
Yeah, let's make it a
great cultural festival.
I-It's a job once you agree to it,
so I'm going to do my best.
Yeah.
Is this all of it?
My dad said he'll deliver
the rest by car tomorrow.
It's the first time I've
seen your drawings, Mizuno.
Really?
A co-worker at the Kissuiso
said she'd stop by for a look.
Yeah?
Let's see...
Hmm...
Yup! It looks great, Mizuno!
Oshimizu...
that's upside down.
I'm sorry!
No boys allowed! No peeking either!
(But why?) (I wanna see!) (Hey! This makes us wanna peek even more!)
This is our menu.
We'll shop for the
ingredients tomorrow morning.
Jibuni, a dish that uses Noto
beef, and miso mackerel.
Wow! This looks like a restaurant
menu, not a café menu!
Huh? Where's the omelet rice?
We're not making that.
What?
You look really nice in that, Yuina!
Keep the compliments coming!
Your beauty's off the chart!
More! More!
Our Cleopatra!
What the heck?
I'll bring the rest tomorrow.
All right!
Let's take a little break,
and then we'll practice some serving.
Sure!
Our coach is Ohana Matsumae, the
super waitress from Kissuiso!
Okay!
Super...
Why aren't we making omelet rice?!
Excuse me, I need someone to be in
charge of buying the ingredients.
But we asked you
to include omelet rice!
Yeah!
Include omelet rice?
Listen to me...
But why?!
Let's take a break.
Yes. Okay, we'll be waiting
for you tomorrow.
Thank you very much.
Was it okay?
Yeah.
They said they'll be
here in the morning.
Thank goodness!
Cultural festival, eh?
Sure brings back memories.
During college, I was a member of the film club,
so we held screenings.
Yeah?
Oh, it was during one of those
screenings that I met Takky.
"Takky"?
Oops, I wasn't supposed to call her that in public!
I know I need to keep my private
and public lives separate.
It just sort of slipped out.
Oh...
What kind of food did you like best at your cultural festivals?
I don't really dislike
any kind of food...
Oh, I think I remember Takky
saying that she likes takoyaki.
Don't you think she's a little weird?
Right?
I'm going back to work.
Anyway, during the screening, Takky...
Damn, I called her that again.
Huh? Where's everyone going?
Yuina?
What are you doing?
Shush, Ohana!
Things are looking pretty bad in there.
We need omelet rice!
I said, we're not having it!
Wh-What? They're still
arguing over that?
I said I'd decide after
hearing everyone's opinions.
But Kirito really loves omelet rice.
I really want him to eat it...
What? Don't be ridiculous.
That was mean, Tsurugi.
Yuki's liked him since middle school!
What?
I've liked Kirito much longer than that...
You rejected Kirito during
the field trip, remember?
What's that got to do with this?
Yuki's been holding it
in for a long time!
What's she been holding in exactly?
It's a long story.
Hey! We're discussing the
menu right now!
Why are we talking
about who likes who?!
She's gone and done it now...
I took it off the menu because
we can't make delicious omelet rice using
the equipment we have!
Understand?!
I don't operate on an emotional level like you.
But...
Mixing work and love is absurd!
You agreed to do it.
Why would you let the person
you like influence the way you work?!
Yuki!
Wait!
You're absurd!
Sorry,
but I'm treating the cultural
festival as part of my job too.
We're done for the day.
Um... who's going to do the shopping?
We've still got other preparations to make...
I'll do everything myself.
Bye.
Minchi...
Apparently, their class is all working
together towards the same goal.
Wow...
It's the exact opposite of our class.
Next one, please.
Here.
Thanks.
This one's easy to understand,
so I think I'll put it at the entrance.
It is?
Yeah.
Oh!
Oshimizu, do you mind
giving this a title?
What?!
I like it, but I haven't
thought of a title yet.
Now is the Springtime of Youth
Oh!
Check this out, Princess Minko!
Princess Café
The signs are almost done!
Oh.
S-
Slop...
Sloppy!
Episode 19
Sloppy Omelet Rice
Omelet Rice?
But why omelet rice?
The kitchen on the other
side of the counter seemed
Hey, I'm here.
like a magical world to me as a kid.
Hey, it's lit!
Episode 20
Love. Kourin Festival
Wow!