And now, it's your morning horoscope countdown!
In the top spot, it's YOU, Pisces! We predict you'll
be getting close to a certain special someone!
Umaruuuun!
Kirie, we're at the amusement park!
Yes we are, Umaru!
Kirie?
Kirie!
Are you all right?
Do you feel bad?
Um, i-it's nothing.
I haven't been to an amusement park in a while.
Indeed, I'm looking forward to us all going together!
Hey, everyone!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Umaru...!
Are you okay, Kirie?
Your shoelaces were untied. That's dangerous.
I'm just glad you didn't get hurt.
This is my first time to ride a bus, indeed!
We should get to Fujiyama Land in no time!
No! You mustn't push that button!
Oh? Really?
Fujiyama Land has a lot of rides, doesn't it?
Oh! I brought a pamphlet with me.
Indeed, I want to ride the roller coaster!
It's the longest in the world! It's the best, indeed!
I-I want to ride the merry-go-round.
I haven't been on one since I was a child...
I want to ride the spinning teacups.
I want to try this "Hardcore Piloting Experience."
You damn monsters! Die, die!
Ah! It looks like we're here!
Squee!
We've reached the front gate, indeed!
This is indeed where they sell tickets!
With a "free pass," you can ride anything you want.
Oh, no! My eyes were closed!
Don't worry. You're still cute, Sylphin.
You look so pretty in yours, Umaru!
No, I really don't.
Ah! They're doing an anime song concert!
Amusement parks even have events like THIS, huh?
U-um...
Huh?
I have to use the bathroom.
Sure!
I think this horoscope is a lie...
This is bad! I've been gone too long!
No, NO! I can't make Umaru
worry more than I already have!
She might never invite me to anything again!
Umaru...?
Oh, it's Cold and Bristly Girl!
You came to the anime concert as well, did you?
Are you all right?
Big Brother?
"Brother"?! True, they're pretty similar!
She had the same reaction as me...
Are you a friend of Sylphin's?
Shpaa!
I'm her brother, Alex.
This is some merchandise I got at the anime event.
Here, please.
Here.
Sylphin, the show's over, so I'll be going now.
Big Brother...
He's quite thoughtful, isn't he?
Y-yes...
By the way, Kirie, had you met him before?
No! Not at all! I don't know him!
Your brother, you say? Eheheheh...
There's no laughter at all in those eyes!
Well, what do you say we ride something?
A-a good idea.
Why, yes! Let's have fun!
This is fast, indeed!
I am... stumbling... indeed...
That was meant for kids,
so the seats were a little crowded, huh?
But it was really fun!
I could've used an airbag...
What should we ride next?
I'd like to invite Umaru
to ride a spinning teacup with me...
What should I do?
I...
Indeed, I wish to ride THAT!
I-I'm not scared...!
You'll be fine. Indeed, it's almost our turn in line!
Huh?
Say...
how tall are you?
You can't ride if you're less than 140 cm tall.
It's a shame, indeed. We were in line for an hour...
There's nothing we can do about it now.
Let's ride something else.
That horoscope was completely wrong.
Today has been nothing but bad luck.
This isn't just about me, though. I don't want
to inconvenience the others, so I'll just keep quiet.
What's the matter?!
Oh!
Your hair!
Kirie, let's ride the Ferris Wheel.
Thank you very much.
Good thing you could use Alex's present
as a hair fastener, huh?
I-it's just me and Umaru, alone together.
I have to say something.
Something... something!
Um...!
It's pretty boring, isn't it? Hanging out with me.
We wasted an hour in line
for the roller coaster because of me.
Then, I worried everyone by crying out loud...
Huh? Why am I saying this?
I couldn't even take a decent photo
for my free pass. I'm basically cursed.
I'm such an idiot. This is all I can talk about... THIS?
Jeez... there's no way
she'll want to hang out with me again.
Nah...
It's been a LOT of fun, Kirie!
M-me too!
I've had lots of...!
Huh?
You know what?
We haven't gone on THAT yet, have we?
The teacups!
Yeah!
Jeez...
Indeed!
Wow...
You're getting an award in front of the whole school?
Yeah... it's a friggin' pain...
You wouldn't think THIS person would get an award...
Everyone will be rooting for you, so don't flake out.
I don't even really care about it...
Umaruuun!
It's Umaru!
She'll be getting an award today
for having the highest GPA!
Wow!
C-congratulations!
Thank you.
Shbaa!
Congratulations to you!
Sylphin...
Hm? What's the matter?
W-well...
You shall not beat me on these upcoming midterms!
Shbafeen!
I, Sylphinford Tachibana, will take first place!
You've thought of Umaru as your rival, haven't you?
Do you really wish her well?
C-come to think of it, before I started hanging out
with you all, I DID think of Umaru as my rival...
But now, I'm as happy for her as if it were myself.
Indeed, is this strange?!
No, it's not.
It's up until now that you've been strange.
The award ceremony will soon commence.
For academic excellence
in general coursework: Umaru Doma.
My friends are all supporting me...
They're all happy for me!
Thank you very much!
Umaru, you are cool indeed!
Next up, the award for academic excellence
in AP courses goes to...
Hikari Kongo.
Huh?
That was a splendid awards ceremony!
Thanks!
Still...
That was the first time I've seen someone
from the AP classes. They're in a separate building, so...
Y-yes, you're right.
AP classes...
Your grades are beyond reproach,
Umaru. They're exemplary.
If you like, we could move you into the AP curriculum...
Have I met that girl somewhere before?
Cassiopeia... Altair...
Deneb...
Arcturus... Spica.
I finally get it...
This whole time, what I've searched for
has been right in front of me.
This light...!
It can't be... The fifth Precura!
The light of justice: Cura Big-Bang!
Thank you, everyone. I... I have no more doubts!
That was wonderful, wasn't it, Sensei? What a climax!
The scene where Big-Bang
became part of the group, right!
Big-Bang was a loner at first, but in the end,
she had the courage to make friends with the others.
That long process made
the climax so much more powerful!
Shba!
Wasn't it great, Cold and Bristly Girl?
Yeah, whatever.
I can't trust this guy.
He calls my master "Sensei." Just what is he plotting?
I am the Master's one and only disciple!
I must protect her!
So, Alex, do you go back to Germany
when you want to see your friends?
Uh... um... Me?
I'm ashamed to admit it, but when I was in Germany...
I wasn't like Big-Bang, but I was pretty withdrawn.
Huh? Really?!
Well, in middle school...
One day, I couldn't bring myself to go to school.
I spent my days online or watching anime.
Once you've locked yourself indoors,
it's hard to go back outside, isn't it?
I convinced myself I didn't need to interact
with others in order to live.
But then...
Suddenly, the day came!
My savior arrived, the one who suggested
I go to high school in Japan.
That was when my life changed.
You've both been so kind to me
since I joined the company...
And thanks to you, I got to meet Sensei
and even Cold and Bristly Girl!
I get it now; Everyday life means people helping people.
The light of justice: Cura Big-Bang!
Huh?
Wh-wha-?
Um, what's the matter?
Ah, nothing. Sorry.
Say, let's come up with some sweet poses
for those key scenes!
Sounds great! Let's do it, Sensei!
I'll do it too!
Even Cold and Bristly Girl is getting in on it, huh?
D-don't go getting the wrong idea!
I am the Master's top pupil! This is why
I participate in what SHE wants to do!
So, let's all do it together!
The light of justice: Cura Big-Bang!
Okay, Sensei. See you next time.
Till then, Alex!
Yes, hello?
I have a savior...
Hello...
Kanau!
What are you doing here?
I told you everything on the phone!
How can you say that?
We have to celebrate Hikari's award!
Here! Let's mark the occasion
by watching the Precura Blu-ray box set!
No thanks.
WHY NOT?! The final scene where Big-Bang
become part of the group is fantastic!
I don't care.
WHAAAAAAAAT?!
This guy hasn't changed at all since middle school.
Ah!
Kanau! Sen... I mean, Umaru and I
watched some anime again today!
And Taihei wasn't there!
I-I don't need every little detail, you know!
It's so hot.
I'd sure like some chilled rice soup...
Rolling around with my pretty kitty, Necolumbus...
My best dish is...
Huh?
Reckon I passed out. My head's all fuzzy.
I'm scared. Maybe I'm fixin' to up and die!
Nana.
I made you some chilled rice soup.
Big Brother!
Brother...
Am I gonna die?
Ain't no way that'll happen. It's just a heatstroke.
And you ain't eaten, so your body's all weak.
Eat up now.
That sure is great!
That's the last memory I have of my brother.
Big Brother! I ate it and I'm all better now!
Can you teach me how to make...?
Huh?
My brother was gone.
Your brother had to go and get a job.
Reckon he'll be back soon.
I still didn't understand why he left, but...
I knew where he went.
Nana, that restaurant we went to
in Tokyo was great, huh?
One day, I'm gonna live in Tokyo too!
Don't see as how it's a big deal.
We've all been to Tokyo before.
But you ain't never been there alone.
Plus, visitin' somewhere don't mean you can LIVE there.
But, Tokyo's too far for me
to go to school there and live here.
Hello.
Um...
Ah! I-I'm sorry! I-I-I just moved here today!
Oh, is that so?
Th-this man...
He sort of reminds me of my brother.
I'd spoken to Umaru's brother a few times, and maybe....
maybe I've sort of thought of him as MY brother.
Ebina...
Yes?
You're really kind, aren't you?
Oh, Ebina.
G-good afternoon!
It's hot today, so if you stay outside too long,
you'll get a heatstroke.
Y-y-yes, you're right!
It's like that time before, when my head was all fuzzy...
But somehow, it's not scary. It's a happy kind of fuzzy.
That amusement park was fun indeed!
Yup! I'd like to go again.
Kirie seemed a little off-put at first,
but by the end, she was indeed enjoying herself!
You're so thoughtful, Sylphin.
I'm not sure I follow, but I shall accept that compliment!