Misawa Batting Center
The Year Draws
To A Close
We accept point cards
Oh?  Welcome.
Go-Goo—
Good evening...
Haven't seen you in a while.
What brings you here today?
I-I came to see Sasayan-kun...
Oh, Natsume-san.
So many of them...
Sorry about making you come out here.
No, it's okay.
I should have returned this sooner.
I can be normal around Sasayan-kun.
Natsume-san!
He wants to talk to you!
Stupid!
Look at him!
S-Sorry, Natsume-san.
Do you need something?
Huh?
Don't...
If you don't need anything, I'm leaving.
W-Wait, did we make her mad?
Sorry, Yana.
Wild Angels
Baseball Team
Recruiting members!!
Natsume-san.
Sorry, they didn't mean any harm.
They apologized, too,
so can't you forgive them?
I hate it when that happens.
This is why I hate boys.
All they care about is their own fun.
Doesn't matter to them
if I end up shunned
by the other girls.
What?
Isn't it your own fault for
letting it get to that point?
See?
You're just like the rest of them.
You underestimate female friendship!
Listen to me.
Female friendship is lateral.
The nail that sticks out
gets hammered down.
In our world, we're supposed
to all hold hands and
cross the finish line at the same time!
Finish
Together
Sounds like a pain...
What's wrong with that Shimoyanagi-kun?
He kept smiling like a fool!
How stupid is he?
Yana didn't do anything wrong.
You're right.
I'm sorry.  I shouldn't have said that.
I was just a little irritated.
Mitty's busy with her class,
and Haru-kun's been in a bad mood.
Plus, I'm having trouble
talking to Mi-chan-san...
Huh?
Isn't that because you're
in love with him?
Wha-Wha-Wha—
What are you talking
about, Sasayan-kun?!
That's not possible!
Huh?
You're not?
But if you can't even speak
normally around him...
Y-You've got it all wrong!
Well, I've never been in
love, so I wouldn't know...
I'm never going to fall
in love with a man!
Why not?
I don't see a problem.
It's perfectly natural.
You're wrong!  You're wrong!
You're absolutely wrong!
Yo, whatcha guys doing?
Y-You look happy, Haru-kun.
Do I?
Did something good happen?
Were you stalking
Mizutani-san again, today?
What?
That's not happening!
That's not what I meant.
Y-Yeah, I know...
Haru.
Let's go on a picnic.
Next year, after the New Year's rush.
You missed the field trip
last spring, right?
Since you didn't come to school.
F-Field trip...
We can go anywhere you want.
W-Well, if you insist.
Okay, promise!
I'll pack lunches!
In return,
I want you to behave while I'm
busy with my winter prep course.
Sure, I can do that!
She bribed him.
Um, are you sure, Haru-kun?
You're okay with this?
You guys get to come, too!
What?  I can join you?
Yep.
We can all go on a picnic together?
She's making him swallow her demands
while ignoring the problem at hand.
That's what you'd expect from a gigolo.
I didn't expect that desperate rue
to be so effective.
I'll be going then.
Enjoy the rest of the year.
Yep.  Work hard, Shizuku.
Are you really okay with this?
She told us to enjoy
the rest of the year.
That means she doesn't plan
on seeing us again, this year.
It's okay.
We made a promise for next year.
I don't understand Haru-kun...
How can he have such blind faith?
He believes her, just like that?
Let's try this place today!
Another monja place?
Taiyaki this time.
Taiyaki
I don't get why they'd use natto,
limited time or not.
I know.
How's your salty and spicy one?
Pretty nasty.
Let's try the red bean soup place
on the corner next time.
Well...
I feel safe around Haru-kun
because he only cares about Mitty.
Oh, right.
Mi-chan was worried about you.
He was asking how you've been,
since you haven't dropped by.
You haven't visited in a while, huh?
W-Well, there's...
no particular reason.
Isn't that because you're
in love with him?
It's only harder after
Sasayan-kun said that.
Why?
What's that?
Well, if I had to guess...
It's because the restroom reeks of milk.
That's not true.
The restroom is handy and clean.
There's no real reason.
Really?
Bye!
I won't see them again
until next year...
Christmas Eve~
Calendar
Golu: Oh.  Welcome back, Yukke-san
Momo: It's been a while.  How was your trip?
Yukke: Lots of fun (°∀°)m
What have you all been up to?
Momo: I'm hitting a shrine with some
friends tomorrow (*>ω<*)
Golu: Oh.  Welcome back, Yukke-san
Momo: It's been a while.  How was your trip?
Yukke: Lots of fun (°∀°)m
What have you all been up to?
Momo: I'm hitting a shrine with some
friends tomorrow (*>ω<*)
Golu: I went skiing with my friends (´∀`)
Golu: Oh.  Welcome back, Yukke-san
Momo: It's been a while.  How was your trip?
Yukke: Lots of fun (°∀°)m
What have you all been up to?
Momo: I'm hitting a shrine with some
friends tomorrow (*>ω<*)
Golu: I went skiing with my friends (´∀`)
Golu: We had a snowball fight (~Д~)ﾉ・・・O
Golu: Oh.  Welcome back, Yukke-san
Momo: It's been a while.  How was your trip?
Yukke: Lots of fun (°∀°)m
What have you all been up to?
Momo: I'm hitting a shrine with some
friends tomorrow (*>ω<*)
Golu: I went skiing with my friends (´∀`)
Golu: We had a snowball fight (~Д~)ﾉ・・・O
Momo: Sounds fun!!
Hello?
Oh, Natsume-san?
Sorry about calling you on New Year's Eve.
Do you know how to program a TV recording?
My little brother asked me to
record the New Year's special,
but I can't find the instruction manual.
Natsume-san, can you hear me?
Oh, you want to program a recording?
I can help.
Um, what brand is your machine?
Um...
Ba-Banasonic?
Oh, okay.
Yep, that should do it.
Got it.  I'll give it a shot.
Thank you.  Bye.
What?
I'm...
I'm so lonely!
Huh?
Why is Haru here?
Natsume called me.
Yep, need something recorded?
I got you covered.
The Paranormal at Midnight!
Lock on!
Where's your family?
Ooh, an excellent choice!
They went to my Grandma's yesterday.
He's definitely your brother.
Yep, this is perfect.
I was feeling really lonely,
and it only got worse
when I lied online about
doing lots of fun stuff.
Are you really planning
on staying the night?
Yes, I can take care of
myself, so don't mind me.
Oh, this is from my mother.
I don't get it.
She's being really pushy
for someone who's timid.
Well, at least she helped
me record the show.
What did you do for Christmas?
I read books.
Gorillas are awesome.
Oh...
Mind if dinner is something random?
I don't have anything prepared.
Don't worry about us.
Sure.
This is really nice.
Natsume.
There's no reason for you to be lonely.
You can drop by whenever you want.
A hot pot?
Carry that over, Haru.
So did you ever see Yamaken
outside of class?
Huh?
If they become a couple,
will I still get to
spend time with them?
Sorry, Haru-kun.
Huh?
I have to focus on...
Carrot flowers!
...protecting my little world.
Not yet!  I have to skim all the foam!
Oh, oops...
I fell asleep.
Ha-Haru!  Wake up!
It's already past one!
Go home!
Hey, Natsume-san?
Happy New Year!
Huh?
Er, Sasayan-kun?
Oh.
You're with Mizutani-san and Yoshida?
Aren't you coming down to the shrine?
It's packed.
C-Crazy!
There's a crazy crowd!
Now that we're here, we have to
watch the sun rise together!
Aren't we breaking curfew?
It's okay!
This is a Japanese tradition!
O-Oh...
Okay, Haru-kun!
Where's Sasayan-kun?
Crazy!
I can't get any reception
because of all the people!
Well, we'll run into him eventually.
Huh?  What was that?
Why don't you say that again, huh?
Stop yapping in my ear.
I'm in a bad mood.
Get lost.
Huh?
Uh, Yamaken?
He told ya to get lost!
Why are you so cocky when
you suck at fighting?
You're the ones who
keep starting fights.
I don't like pain.
Bring it, brats!
Yeah, let's do this!
Yo!
Ha-Haru!
You guys are fighting again?
You shouldn't fight.
That hurt, stupid!
Why did you kick me?!
Who is this guy?
Hey, brat.  This ain't none
of your business, so scram.
Huh?
Okay, Haru!  These guys are bad people!
Let's get 'em!
Haru's here.
That means...
Oh, Yamaken-kun.
Happy New Year.
I was wondering why Haru
suddenly ran off.
So that fight earlier was you guys.
Why are you standing over here
while your buddy's fighting?
I could ask you the same thing.
Next, please!
I'll take two.
Here you go!
Yamaken-kun, I'll pay for mine.
Don't bother.  I was hungry anyway.
Okay.
Then you shouldn't cut in line.
Mitty!
Haru-kun's fighting over there!
Natsume-san, were the restrooms crowded?
There's no time for that!
You have to stop him!
Damn...
You'll never get through
to Mitty like that.
Shut your mouth!
Ow!  Ow!  Ow!
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
So I have to spell it out
for her the way Haru does?
I love you, so I'll pay for that.
Let's walk around together.
I can't do that!
Gorillas can communicate
with their eyes!
Haru, stop it...
Oh, it's Oshima.
Happy New Year!
Y-You guys also came...
Oh...  So you have...
...friends...
Nice to meet you.
Yuu-chan!
Happy New Year.
I feel betrayed...
What?
Oh, right.
Are you going to draw a fortune?
Love Fortune
This place is famous for its accuracy.
Love fortunes...
I know, right?
A fortune won't do any good.
Terrible
Right next to you
Super
Watch what you say
Terrible
Trouble coming
Learn to suck it up
How's it look?
Fortunes
Oh, Natsume-san,
there's an open spot up here.
I can do yours for you.
Oh, thank you very much.
Up here?
Higher.
Um...
Does this spot work?
I really...
I really want to root for her...
But I can't.
D-Does it have to be Haru-kun?
S-Sorry,
but you'd have a lot more
fun if it wasn't Haru-kun,
a-and you wouldn't have
to feel so bad...
Oh...
Uh-huh, I know what you mean.
In these situations,
I can't help but think of Yoshida-kun.
Sorry, Natsume-san.
I don't know what to do myself.
You haven't done anything
to apologize for.
Is there... someone you like?
Why not?
I don't see a problem.
It's perfectly natural.
I don't have anyone.
Hey, finally found you!
Happy New Year.
H-Happy New Year.
Thanks.  Happy New Year.
Are you going to use our roof?
It's a great spot.
Sorry about imposing all the time.
Natsume-san, what's with
that look on your face?
Mi-chan, is this round one the key?
Yep, that's it.
Oh, Haru.
No diving off the roof.
Sure, no problem!
I stopped doing that!
What does that mean?
Wow!  Awesome!
I've never been on the
batting center roof before!
It's Nagoya!
Stupid, stop pushing!
I'll fall!
Young people have so much energy.
Does she hate my guts now?
Yeah...
Well, cheer up, Yana.
But I kinda dig that...
You look unhappy, Natsume-chan.
You hurt his feelings.
Boys that age are sensitive.
You were watching, Mi-chan-san?
It's New Year's,
I'm happy that Haru brought friends,
and I'm happy that I got to
see you and Shizuku-chan.
You could be a little
nicer to him, right?
I just didn't know how to act
after being so mean last time.
Hey, I don't have any
trouble talking to him...
I hate boys!
And I really hate boys
who try to hit on me!
Ooh, that's harsh.
Most girls your age don't
get to say stuff like that.
Personally, I love girls.
Do you want to fall in love?
Fall in love?
Well, I've got all this debt right now,
but love is good.
It changes people, for better or worse.
You could look at it as a
chance for you to change.
The best kind of love
helps you grow up.
As long as I have Mitty, Haru-kun,
and my other friends,
I don't need anything else.
Then we'll build the Kingdom of Mitty...
Uh, hold on.
An eternal kingdom where
you always have fun and never get hurt.
There's no such place.
You know that.
Then can you and I...
grow up together?
Ah!
The first sunrise of the year,
but we can't see a thing!
We stayed up all night!
Sorry, Yana.
My plan backfired.
How many rings are they up to?
Eighty or so?
Must have been a bad year.
Oh, Sasayan.
Did you apologize to Natsume-san
about the other day?
Was she mad?
Huh?  Oh...
She must be mad...
Well, she wasn't really mad at you.
Huh?  Oh!
It's Sasayan!
Oh, you guys are also here?
What's this?  You're
actually waiting in line?
No one else is with you?
Who are you looking for?
Let's go.
Bye!
I don't know how you can talk to him.
Hmm... Too bad.
Ten,
nine,
She's not picking up.
Sasayan, they've started the countdown!
eight,
seven,
Yeah!
six,
Oh, well.
five,
I can try again later.
four,
Oh, we fell asleep after dinner...
We need to clean up.
It's gone!  I can't find it!
Haru, calm down.
What's missing?
Your TV?  Radio?
There shouldn't be that much traffic...
I can't wait around!
Where are you?!
Next Episode
Spring Is Near
Nobody ever saw him again.