She won't come back, will she?
I did the right thing, didn't I, Onii-sama?
Poor Julio.
It's nothing, Mama.
But I can't believe I couldn't
dispose of that bad Norma.
You did well, Julio.
Really? Did I do well?
I'm so happy.
Mother would never praise me.
She kept favoring Angelise.
She died defending Angelise.
Onii-sama.
Now it's Mama's turn to ask for a favor.
I know.
You want me to open the
singular point, right?
Good boy.
Guard Chief, what are you...
Oh?
Someone help.
Help!
Help! Angelise-oneesama!
Dragon Song
A shift change?
First Troop has been relegated to
backup, due to concerns about our readiness.
Eleanor Squad is on deck today.
Tomorrow, it'll be Betty Squad.
Well, combat's out of the
question with only five of us.
How can you be so nonchalant about it?
If we don't get deployed, we don't get paid.
Shit.
Thanks a lot, Breakout Sisters.
I hope they never come back.
Y-You're right.
Please, give this to Angelise-sama.
I don't think she's getting proper meals.
Please! Please.
I'm hungry.
I guess I can think of it as a diet.
Forget that, I want to take a bath.
How many days has it been?
A week.
No wonder you smell.
You smell the same.
I don't ask for much.
Just some water to bathe in.
It's Salia-oneesama.
Salute Salia-oneesama.
Salute!
She's so pretty and awesome.
I'm totally going to join First Troop.
I'm going to be like Salia-oneesama.
I'm going to be like you, Onee-sama.
Here, for Onee-san.
Thanks for doing this every year, Salia.
What's wrong?
The Youth Group girls called me Onee-sama.
Am I that old already?
You're only seventeen.
I'm already seventeen.
I'm the same age as Alektra.
Alektra!
Maggie, analgesics!
Bring all the bandages you can.
That's Onee-sama's machine.
Hang in there, Alektra.
What happened?
They're, they're all...
Oh, Fei-Ling has a message for Mei.
The family heirloom is hidden under
the bottom of the third drawer.
Idiot! You can deal with that later.
I'm sorry, Jasmine.
I wasn't good enough.
Fei-Ling, Vanessa, the knight's family...
They're all dead.
I couldn't handle the Villkiss.
I wasn't good enough.
Alektra.
That's not true!
Alektra is strong, beautiful, and awesome.
You're good enough.
Who is she?
Salia, of the Primary Group.
What kind of DRAGON was it?
How big was it?
How tough?
I won't forgive it.
I won't forgive it for doing this to you.
I'll avenge you, Alektra!
I'm counting on you, Salia.
I don't even remember that.
It can't be helped. You were only three.
But the family's duty, my sister's wishes...
I've inherited them.
As an armorsmith, I'm going to
free the world with the Villkiss.
For my sister, too.
And as a rider, you can do the
same for Alek— I mean, Jill.
You're right.
Why?
Why not?
I'm going to do my best.
Even more than now.
There's no point.
No matter how hard you try,
if you can't do it, you can't do it.
But—
If you can't understand that,
you end up like this.
What is it that I'm lacking?
That we're lacking, you mean.
Then what does Ange have?
I'm not giving her the Villkiss.
Huh, isn't this...
It's a singular signature.
Location?
It's...
...right above Arzenal.
More enemies inbound.
Scuna class, six. No, 21.
Sixty-five.
128.
Too many to estimate.
We didn't even get a call. How?
This is Commander Jill.
All units, listen up.
I'm ordering Battle Mode, Type 1.
A singular point has opened above the base.
What a waste!
A massive number of DRAGONs are descending.
Second and Third Para-mail Troops,
deploy all units.
Prepare for close-quarters combat.
You are authorized to use anti-air weapons.
Destroy the DRAGONs
at all costs.
Who's going to defend the base
if we deploy all the Para-mails?
What's going on?
Die, bad guys!
Commander, the communicator and radar...
We hereby abandon the command center.
Further communications will be
issued from emergency command.
Yes, ma'am.
It looks like we got most of them.
Thanks to Eleanor Squad and Betty Squad.
They took our earnings.
Huh? They're fleeing.
Singing...
A Para-mail?
What the heck? Where's that machine from?
Ow.
What just happened?
Angelise-sama.
Please say something if you're okay.
Momoka.
Open.
Thanks, Momoka.
No, it's nothing.
Momoka?
It's nothing.
Who did this?
Just after we finally got back...
We'll find out if we go to the Para-mails.
Let's hurry.
But first take a bath.
Good idea.
We don't have time for that.
Second Troop, annihilated.
Third Troop, four units lost
other than the Captain.
Give all command authority
to Salia of First Troop.
Instruct all the remaining
Para-mail to attack the DRAGONs.
Yes.
You heard it, Salia.
And return Ange to the squad.
Only the Villkiss can stop that machine.
Put Ange in it.
Then I'll deploy in the Villkiss.
Shut up.
Follow your orders.
Am I not good enough?
I've always wanted to be useful to you.
I've worked so hard.
And it's still Ange?
Ange's kind of good at piloting,
and she's a bit clever.
But she violated orders, and she deserted.
She's in detention.
And it's still Ange?
That's right.
You think I'm stupid.
Salia.
Everyone, fall back to resupply.
We've got this one!
R-Right!
First Troop deployed.
Good.
Ange, your target is that
unidentified machine.
It's equipped with an
unknown high-yield weapon.
Be careful.
I know, Jill.
Salia?
What are you doing, Salia?
Return to base!
You're violating orders!
Shut up!
You don't get it, so I'm going to show you.
I'm going to defeat them!
I'm going to do it for Alektra.
Fool.
They're not here.
Why?
Did they get wiped out?
No, it's Salia.
More.
Faster.
Can't you fly faster?
Move!
Salia-chan!
Something's wrong.
The Villkiss has to have more power.
Ange was more—
Dammit, my chest! I can't breathe!
It's cramped. Deal with it.
Ange!
Hilda-chan.
Salia, give me back my machine!
I'll take care of it.
It's my Villkiss!
You must think I'm stupid!
Only Ange and the Villkiss
can stop that machine.
Ange's kind of good at piloting,
and she's a bit clever.
No matter how hard you try, if
you can't do it, you can't do it.
No, that's not true!
I worked harder than everyone.
There's no point.
Chase her, Hilda.
What are you thinking?
I'll jump over.
What?
Well, that's something you'd do.
We're charging in.
Why won't you move?
You have to move.
Or else I can't help my beloved Alektra.
Now!
Go, Burn Princess!
Good.
Here we go.
It's over.
What?
We're past the drop threshold.
We'll have to fall.
It's not over yet.
Not for this machine.
That was refreshing.
Hilda.
Now what?
I'm dropping her. Catch!
I'm charging you extra, Idiot Princess!
Let's do it, then.
Damn.
This song...
That's...
For what reason does a false
citizen sing the true Star Song?
And who are you?
What is that song?
The time comes, it seems.
Wait.
The truth is with Aura.
The unidentified machine
and DRAGONs are retreating.
Truth?
I see.
The last key was...
...a song.
That's the real Villkiss.
Jill was right.
Well, well, we made it somehow.
It feels totally different from Ange.
Yes, I am.
She was completely different.
Hilda...
What?
You stink.
A complete disaster, huh?
We have a bad situation.
Worse than it already is?
We lost the plant.
Whoa, this is bad!
Oh, well.
Ange's song was so pretty.
How long do we have?
I don't know, but...
Next episode
I've been in the opening and ending,
kept waiting for years.
My name and identity are left unknown,
and yet I have no role next week.
I'm an important character, am I not?
So why do I have the more lines
in the preview than elsewhere?
Her Right Arm's Past