Lottery
Nice try!
Hot springs! Hot springs!
Win a stay at Kiriyako Hot Springs Hotel
We get a hot spring?
If we win.
But I'd rather have third prize.
Every home needs one!
Cook anything
with this!
Third Prize
Hot springs! Hot springs! Hot springs!
You like hot springs that much, Noel?
What's a hot spring?
Well...
It's a big bath that you go
in with other people, I guess.
Is it bigger than the bath in your house?
Of course.
Is it bigger than a lake?
N-Not that big.
Lottery Ticket
There.
If we win, you can see for yourself.
Want to try?
Hot springs! Hot springs! Hot springs!
Congratulations!
No way.
True Friends
Cheer up.
That's cute, too.
Second
Prize
This isn't it.
Congratulations!
We have a first prize winner!
I don't want it.
Certificate
This is a real nuisance.
Thank you.
Free Accommodation Coupon
Nonoka
I wonder if she'll come.
Welcome—
Oh, Souta.
This is a rare sight,
seeing you help at home.
Not as rare as someone who'd go help
at someone else's shop, like you.
They wanted me to.
What was I supposed to say?
Koharu wanted you to.
What were you supposed to say?
Shut up!
I have to get ready to move out.
Today's my last day.
Sure, sure.
Where'd you get those?
Free Lodging Coupon
The lady from the hotel
came and invited us.
Going to the hot springs would be
nice once in a while, huh?
I don't have one for you.
Why would I go with you?
I wouldn't even ask.
Who would go with their own sister?
What a pain.
Well now that we agree
on something, go away.
You're getting in the way of business.
Oh, yeah.
Koharu, can I ask you for a favor?
No changes today, either.
Shione!
Noel.
Hey, Shione, look! Shione—
The hot springs?
Yeah.
An acquaintance gave me these.
She told me I should invite you.
Me?
Yeah, you, Nonoka.
Who?
Someone I know?
Um...
I-I can't tell you.
I can't take that from someone
I don't really even know.
Not at all.
In fact she's really straightforward
and easy to get to know.
Do you mean—
Here.
Next weekend.
I'll be waiting.
Okay.
The hot springs, huh?
What should I do with the
rest of these coupons?
Huh, what's that?
Oh, Yuzuki, want to come
to the hot springs with us?
The hot springs?
I was just thinking about going!
Koharu.
What's up?
Do you have any coupons left?
Noel.
Good timing.
The hot springs—
Nonoka, listen!
What is it?
I can go to the hot springs.
Shione invited me.
We're going to the hot springs
together on her next break.
Good for you.
Have fun.
Call from
Nonoka
Take care of the shop for a bit.
Oh, here.
What?
Oh, so Noel couldn't come?
But you can come, right, Nonoka?
Oh, good.
I'll ask Koharu what to do
about the rest of the coupons.
Maybe there's someone she wants to invite.
I wouldn't mind just
the three of us, but...
I see, she has some left.
I'm busy anyway.
Oh, Koharu?
Next weekend?
Yeah, I'm free.
There's leftover curry in the fridge.
Heat it up if you're going to have it.
Put it on low heat so it doesn't splatter.
I know how to make it, too, you know.
Still, you have to eat your salad.
You're too fussy about food.
Yeah, got it.
And don't leave the dishes
out once you're done eating.
It gets really hard to wash them.
You should go.
Look at the time!
I'm going!
Take care.
Kiriyako Hot Springs Hotel
I need to tell her today.
I have to be ready.
Thanks for waiting.
You're late.
Sorry.
I was worried about
leaving Dad by himself.
Where's Koharu?
She should be here soon.
I'm glad we aren't really late.
What's wrong?
Th-There's something I want
to tell you before we go.
Um...
Sorry I'm late.
You're early.
I don't think I'm early.
Don't be in such a rush.
S-Sorry, I'll come later next time.
H-How's the shop? It's a weekend.
Don't worry, I took care of it.
Okay, let's go.
Saucer Steamed Buns
They're selling them here, too.
They have good reach, right?
Yeah.
They don't taste bad,
but they were better when
I ate them as a kid.
Um, ma'am?
They're still the best.
Shiihara Saucer Steamed Buns!
What are you doing?
Shione!
Outdoor Baths
(Down the hall and to the right.)
Hey, they have outdoor baths.
Really?
I can't wait.
Enjoy your stay.
Hot springs, hot springs,
hot springs with Shione.
It's a pretty nice view.
What's wrong?
I didn't think you'd say that.
It's nothing.
It's not like I approve of the saucer.
We're just in a cease fire.
What?
Hey, hey!
Why are you getting all comfortable?
You know there's something
we have to do first.
Is there?
It's a hot spring.
We have to go to the bath!
Now?
Obviously.
That was fast!
Cleaning
No Access
We're a bit too early.
I want to go to the hot springs!
Not bad.
That was okay.
Wasn't there something
you needed to do, Yuzuki?
Didn't you have to say
something to Nonoka?
I'll be back in the room.
Be strong.
Yeah.
I know.
Hey, Nonoka.
I have to talk to you.
Hang on.
Koharu?
Be strong.
I know.
Champion
You are the champion!
You're pretty good.
So what did you want
to talk to me about?
Talk?
We can talk later.
Yeah.
Really?
Arcade
Huh? The notice fell off.
I'm playing this.
Out of Order
Looks like it's broken.
Sorry, it can't wait.
H-Hey, Yuzuki!
Shione, hurry, hurry!
So, what's up?
You've been acting weird.
Tell me.
I actually asked Koharu
to invite you today.
I thought so.
You noticed?
It was suspicious.
I thought maybe if we're
in a different environment,
it'd be easier for me to say this.
Sure, I'll hear you out.
Nonoka, please.
Hit me!
Wh-Why?
I can't get it out of my mind
that I did something so awful to you.
So if you're going to forgive me,
hit me really hard!
Please, Nonoka!
Yeah?
But really?
As hard as you can.
Okay.
Here I go.
Ready, set...
I said as hard as you can.
It wouldn't be fair if I got serious.
So we're even now.
Thank you.
Hey, what do you think?
I'm not going to be here
in this town next year.
She could have invited me, right?
I guess I should clean you.
So it must have been that night.
Can I have this?
I don't want it.
Go ahead.
White Bunny of the Snow Country
Let's eat together.
Do you like the saucer, Shione?
Why would you ask such a thing?
You're always taking pictures of it.
I'm taking pictures
to learn about it.
We're eating, aren't we?
I'll make tea.
Yuzuki!
What was that for?
Good, it was you.
I couldn't see without my glasses.
What if it wasn't me?
So, how did it go?
Well...
I'm happy you invited me today.
Thanks, you two.
You're welcome.
Maybe Noel can come next time.
And Togawa-san, if it's possible.
You're right.
Yeah.
That was refreshing.
Let's buy something cold.
Sounds good.
Woo hoo!
Take your clothes off!
This is all a bath?
Obviously.
Let's get in.
Hurry, hurry!
You're right.
It's fun bathing together.
A bath is a bath, isn't it?
So what if you're with someone?
I feel warm.
Are you texting Souta?
Yeah.
I had him help at the store.
I have to thank him.
That's it?
That's it.
You aren't going to say
you wanted him to come?
Why?
Hey, don't you have someone?
Someone?
So boring.
I'm going to sleep.
Hot springs...
When's the last time I wasn't alone?
Are you still up?
Yeah.
Nonoka, thanks.
Thanks, huh?
Thanks for waiting.
You could have shopped at my place.
Gifts?
Yeah. For Dad.
And for Mom.
You're a good daughter.
I don't know.
Oh, yeah. Can we come over
to your place someday?
Sure, any time.
The hot springs were so big!
It was pretty normal.
It was so fun!
Yeah?
Because I was with my friend.
Your friend?
We're friends, right, Shione?
Don't make things up.
I don't intend to make
any more friends.
Oh, yeah. You like the saucer, don't you?
Here.
I couldn't walk around with this.
A real nuisance.
Soup curry?
I tried making it.
Try it.
But we should finish the leftovers first.
Don't get so angry.
I told you not to let it burn.
My bad.
Mom's photo.
Yeah.
I figured she might like it
out here more than in my room.
Hey, Dad.
I want to ask you for a favor.
Warm.
Next episode of Celestial
Method: "What I Lost."
Enjoy.
What I Lost