I might be moving to Chiba
Kotarou-kun?
Sorry, you're moving?
Yeah.
Where? When?
I'm looking up schools in Chiba.
Have you heard of Koumei?
Excuse me, um...
Her grades are good.
There shouldn't be a problem.
Really? That's a relief.
It must be difficult on you.
I heard it was due to her father's work?
Yes.
Koumei Private High School
I was worried because
it's such a critical time.
Here's the application form.
Thank you.
Factoring
Akane-chan!
Your LINE message surprised me.
I wanted to talk.
Yeah.
I had my parent-teacher meeting today.
I'm going to apply to Koumei
with a recommendation.
Sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
We're going to be far apart.
I don't know what to do.
It's not your fault.
We'll be fine, even far apart.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Maybe I'll go to the same school.
Well, not on recommendation.
Just general admission.
Really?
It'll be really far, though.
Apparently it takes over two hours.
Oh, I decided to go to your cram school.
Really? Awesome!
Let's go.
Yeah.
The Kawagoe Festival is this weekend, huh?
I'll come watch.
Okay.
Cheers.
Cheers!
I saw him earlier.
Oh, he's here?
Yeah. Everyone was there.
They're really good friends.
There you are.
You're late!
Sorry, sorry.
Let's go.
Ready?
Rock-Paper-Scissors
Win -> Earn Two
Lose/Draw -> Earn One
Rock, paper, scissors.
You did it!
Damn, I missed!
Hey, let's all go to the haunted house.
That sounds fun!
Isn't that for kids?
Are you scared?
Don't bother trying to taunt me.
That was so scary!
I'm sorry I made fun of it!
Actually, that was kind of awesome.
Wasn't it?
Totally!
That's the one Kotarou-kun's been doing.
Wait, was that Azumi-kun?
Yeah.
He looked really cool.
It's so hot.
That was pretty good.
It was all right.
You're pretty demanding.
Oh, right, about our
light novel discussion...
Yeah?
I think you should keep it as it was.
What do you mean?
That novel you had me read before...
I think light novel fans
would appreciate it, too.
Good job.
We have some time until the next shift.
You can go enjoy the festival.
Okay.
See you soon.
Why don't you go relax?
I have some time
Where are you?
Monzenyokocho
I'm with the track club people
I'll contact you when I'm nearby
Okay
Okay, let's start!
Loser takes the trash.
Rock, paper, scissors!
One more time!
Yes!
Score!
All right!
Here you go! Thank you!
Yeah!
I haven't had imokoi in forever.
Yeah, it's so good.
I know.
I want imokoi.
You're still hungry?
Totally.
You quit the club. Should
you be eating so much?
Oh, shut up.
I have some time
Where are you?
Monzenyokocho
I'm with the track club people
Hey, Mizuno.
Want to get some imokoi?
Time to eat.
You're eating it already?
It's fine, okay?
You look so happy.
It's my favorite.
It's a Kawagoe specialty.
You won't be able to have
any once you move, huh?
Why would you say that?
Oh, my bad.
Sorry.
It's fine.
I just feel kind of weird.
When you told me you were moving,
I didn't know what to do.
I've always had a crush on you.
I always saw you running so hard.
Sorry, um... I'm in a relationship.
I know.
But... why Azumi?
I know you way better.
From the beginning...
I've loved you more than anyone.
Sorry.
You're my friend, Hira.
You're important to me,
but it's not the same.
All right.
I just wanted to tell you how I felt.
Thanks.
Come to Toki no Kane
Good job.
I didn't think I'd get to see you.
I told everyone I was leaving early.
Is something wrong?
Were you with Hira just now?
Yeah.
Just the two of you?
Yeah, we lost a game and had
to throw away the trash.
Why?
I saw your dance, Kotarou-kun.
It was really good.
How long is your break?
About an hour.
I have to go right back.
Oh...
I think I'll have imokoi.
How about you?
I'm all full.
Oh, Kotarou!
Hey, Kotarou.
It's Kotarou.
Looking good.
Hey, you have a girlfriend, huh?
What difference does it make?
Come on, introduce us.
It's not like that.
Man, to be young...
I won't tell your old man.
What'd you say that for?
Go on, move it!
Azumi-kun...
You're acting different.
Not really.
Are you angry?
See?
I'm not angry.
You are.
Is it about me moving?
No.
But what else...
Nothing.
Forget it.
I'm not angry.
Please tell me.
Why?
Tell me.
We're at the festival.
I'm annoyed.
Another guy...
Not that I care.
Hey...
He confessed to me earlier.
I turned him down.
Should I get you some tea?
It's fine.
I don't have time.
I'm gonna go.
See you.
Come to Toki no Kane
Okay
I'll be right there
Come to Toki no Kane
Okay
I'll be right there
Actually
There's something I need to tell you, too
Huh? What?
I might be moving to Chiba
Actually
There's something
I need to tell you, too
Huh? What?
I might be
moving to Chiba
I fell asleep again yesterday.
Me, too.
I get sleepy whenever I try to study.
Seriously.
So I'm like, "I'll just finish talking
on LINE before I start studying..."
And then your parents go, "Start studying!"
Exactly!
It just makes you want to give up.
I know.
Honestly...
Koumei Private High School
Okay.
That changes the meaning,
so you need to be careful.
Koumei
High School
Excuse me...
Why is this...
Oh, we had a request for it.
They said they had a request for this.
Yeah.
Was it you?
I'm applying.
I haven't even told my parents yet.
They probably won't approve.
But I'll convince them.
I was going to tell you after
I talked to my parents.
I've thought about my future.
And writing and stuff.
And I made up my mind.
I want to be with you.
I'm serious about this.
Thank you.
I'm so happy.
Sorry about before.
I'm sorry, too.
I couldn't talk to you.
I thought you hated me now.
Of course not.
The Setting Sun
Sakura and the Graduation Album
Literature club, gather here!
We're taking pictures for
the graduation album.
I never knew we had so many
members who don't show up.
You're in the literature club?
Got a problem?
Uh, no...
Literature Club
I had no idea.
Okay, here we go.
Literature Club