Found it! It's this!
Hot Springs
A complete guide to the most popular traditional inns
I'm nervous...
Yeah...
I just can't open it!
You open it, Minchi!
Why me?
Well, I think we did well, so we should be fine,
but what are we going to do if they've
written something bad about us.
So, what are we going to do?
A perfect score...
F-F-F-
Five out of five stars...
No...
It's five out of ten stars.
What?
Episode 11
Bark at the Night
Takako!
I need to contact Takako!
If you applied the term "retro,"
it would be too much of a compliment.
It's undeniable that the inn
isn't suited for this era,
and the meals served are plain and boring.
Like hell they are!
Mr. Ren is always trying
his best to make
the most delicious meals possible!
Don't you feel frustrated?!
Yeah, and I was certain we
did everything perfectly that day too.
This discussion ends here.
Everyone, return to your workstations.
Madam Manager!
Didn't you hear me?
I don't like repeating myself.
Please!
Let me talk to the person
who wrote that article!
I won't stand for this!
Please!
W-Wait, hang on!
B-Beanman.
Where's Madam Manager?
At Fukuya.
What?
All of the inns around the
Yunosagi Hot Springs
area scored poorly.
This is an extremely serious situation...
considering how, not too far from Yunosagi
something of this scale
is being constructed.
8000 yen a night, eh?
I'd like to pay them a visit one day.
What are you talking about?!
The completion of this project
will be a huge blow to Yunosagi!
We shouldn't be competing
with them on this.
The quality is what counts-
And this magazine
questions our quality!
This is not the time to be
fighting amongst one another.
Everyone in the Yunosagi group
needs to work together.
Watcha doin'?
Sorry for dragging you to help me.
These will be used in the
Bonbori Festival, right?
Yeah. Isn't it a pain?
But Grandma's really
irritated at the moment,
so arguing with her
is a bad idea right now.
Of course she's irritated.
Everyone was given such awful reviews,
and some huge hotel's being built nearby.
But it sounds really nice.
I'd like to stay there at least once!
Yuina...
If you do that, I'm calling you "balut."
No...
You're not the one to blame here.
Umm...
Yeah!
I don't care how you feel.
I'm gonna fest it up!
"Fest it up"?
I just made that phrase up!
You're so funny, Ohana.
You want a vacation?
Yes.
I want to know why the publishers
gave us that review.
Ohana...
We don't have a lot of
customers this weekend,
and even though I tried calling-
That's a waste of time.
Reviews are supposed to be
given by others, not by yourself.
But...
Even if you're unsatisfied with the review,
you need to accept it,
move on, and work to improve yourself.
But...
But it is wrong!
Ohana...
That's because...
Kissuiso...
is a much better inn
than any of the others!
I refuse to accept such a review.
Ohana went looking for a fight?!
She left a note.
Let me see...
"I'm going to
talk to the person who gave
Kissuiso that crazy review.
I'm gonna fest it up."
What does that even mean?
Maybe Ohana's Japanese deserves
a five out of ten too.
Yes, you've reached Kissuiso.
Okay.
I understand.
Hello, you've reached Kissuiso.
Okay.
Madam Manager, a customer who had
a reservation with us just canceled.
Seriously?!
Umm...
This customer's canceling too...
It's because of that magazine!
Madam Manager!
Working hard so
my wish will come true.
My wish at the Bonbori Festival.
Fest it up
"Fest it up."
Nakochi
Sorry...
I can't answer the phone right now.
I need to fest it up.
I need to fest it up in order
to protect Kissuiso.
Well, that article was
written by an editor.
We don't have anything to do with-
You published it yet you're saying that you have nothing to do with this?!
Are you that irresponsible?!
So the mass media really is
as evil as everyone says?!
No...
Well...
Tell me!
Who in the world
wrote this awful article?
N-Now...
You're close! Too close!
I'm sorry!
Please tell me!
Okay...
This is the-
The spawn of the devil!
Ohana!
How have you been?!
It's been so long since
I've felt this warmth!
What's wrong?
You don't look too happy.
Who would be happy after being
betrayed by a member of their own family?
Jeez... you always say such harsh things!
Oh, are you hungry?
I broke up with him soon after.
Work is so much more fun.
That's why I came back alone.
I've always wanted to
do a moonlight flit.
That was the climax
of our relationship.
How...
How can you say such
awful things about your
own home without even visiting?
Rankings like those are
caused by unavoidable circumstances.
Someone high up wants
Kissuiso to score poorly.
I just obeyed their
orders and wrote it.
You wrote that article
without knowing anything
about how the Kissuiso is doing?!
C-Calm down.
Gratin tastes bad once it cools down.
Don't change the subject!
You're always like that!
You never think of anyone's feelings.
You never bother discussing
anything with me,
and always make all the
decisions by yourself.
This article, the moonlight flit,
the time we moved
when I was in 2nd grade,
my Christmas present
when I was in 5th grade...
I didn't want a teddy bear!
I wanted a sticker book!
You promised me one in November!
I can't believe you
still remember that.
It made me sad!
But you didn't say anything
when I gave you your present.
I held it in!
That's right...
I've always held things in.
Even when you went out late at night
and it was dark and I was afraid to be alone,
I still didn't complain!
Parents' day at school,
the zoo, the pool...
I never complained when
you bailed out on them...
You know you just shifted the
subject to your personal grudge, right?
I never complained because it
always had something to do with your work.
That's why I held it in.
I was holding everything
back this whole time
for a job that hurts others?
All this time... for something like that?!
That's right.
I've had this job for a while.
I raised you with a job like this.
Don't tell me
that you thought that all my "work" consisted of
something that you could be proud of.
From your point of view- No,
even from my point of view,
my job is full of crap.
But I still work hard for it.
That's why...
Fine.
Huh?
I get it,
but I want you to write it.
I told you,
I can't put up a correction notice.
You don't need to
apologize in a magazine!
All I'm asking you is
for you to come to Kissuiso,
and write precisely how
you really feel after your stay.
I don't care if it doesn't
get published in a magazine.
As long as you realize that
Kissuiso is a wonderful inn, I...
I can't.
I'm busy enough as it is.
Please!
No.
I'm not giving up.
Not until you write it.
I'll make you write it for sure!
Wait... Ohana!
Seconds.
Thank you, please come again.
I realize that my mother's
a tough opponent.
I've always lost to her up until now.
But...
Yeah, I'm serious!
Stop pulling my leg!
I'm not!
I haven't told Ko I'm in town yet.
No, that's not why I came to Tokyo.
To: Ko
Hey Ko, it's Ohana.
What are your plans for today?
Make this part a bit more provoking.
Sure.
Satsuki?
Yes?
Look at that.
Matsumae Satsuki, regain your human heart!
Wake up!
Release your soul!
Unforgivable
staged articles!
Jeez...
Isn't that your daughter?
What are you going to do?
Just leave her be.
You think she'll give up?
Nah, she won't.
What?
"Unforgivable," eh?
Just how long do you plan on staying mad at me, Ohana?
It's already published.
There's nothing I can do.
No, I won't forgive you.
It's part of my job. Forgive me.
I'll never forgive you!
For eternity!
Do you know what "eternity" means?
Yes!
Looks like I'll never be forgiven...
Huh?
Okay, back to work.
I won't lose.
I'll take her back to
Kissuiso no matter what.
Matsumae Satsuki, regain your human heart!
Wake up!
Release your soul!
Unforgivable
staged articles!
From: Ko
Hey.
I'm going to be at work today.
Work...
To: Ko
Work?
The hauler again?
It's been a while.
This scenery, this
conversation with Ko...
Even though it hasn't
even been 6 months since I moved.
From: Ko
Nah, I'm working at
the huge bookstore
in Ikebukuro today.
Well, Ikebukuro was only
one stop away, after all.
The sign doesn't look
great right now,
so I should read some difficult
books to learn difficult words...
Koichi!
Where should I put this?
Oh, that goes...
Here?
No.
How am I supposed to know?
Come on...
Come on, guys, stop flirting during work.
Y-You've got it all wrong!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Ohana?
Nope, you've got the wrong gal.
Yes?!
What are you doing here?
Oh... I just happened to drop by!
You just happened to drop by Tokyo?
Who's that?
Oh, she's...
I'm sorry for disturbing you!
Good luck with work!
Later!
Ohana!
So, are you almost at your limit, Ohana?
Shut up, old lady.
So you've finally reached puberty, eh?
Come with me to Kissuiso, old lady.
No.
Old lady...
I refuse to receive
sympathy from an enemy.
I refuse...
Ohana!
Ko...
He was cracking up!
Look, Mom!
Shouldn't you be at work?
Nah.
Are you working hard too?
Yeah.
But we also need to show results.
The customer needs to tell me that I'm working hard.
I can't be the one saying that I am.
I guess...
Maybe that was a bit forward of me.
Ko, are you mad at me for
coming here out of the blue?
There's so much I want to tell you.
Ko, did you grow a bit taller?
Ko, what's your relationship
with that girl from earlier?
Ko, do you still like-
I-I'm going for seconds!
O-Okay.
I don't get it.
Why did I come to Tokyo anyway?
I have so many pent up feelings...
Huh?
You still do that?
You mixed tea and Coke!
I want to drink Coke, but the fizz
is too strong for me.
It hurts my mouth.
Don't lose to Coke.
Ko...
How long have you been
working at that bookstore?
About two months.
Everyone at the store seemed
really friendly with each other.
Yeah, we're all about
the same age too.
That girl was cute too.
You think so?
Ko...
I get the feeling she likes you.
Yeah.
"Yeah"? Did she tell you?
What did you say to her?
I told her I couldn't return
her feelings, but...
"But"?
But she told me she'd wait,
so it's kind of unrequited.
It's rude to not give
a proper answer!
That's-
"It's rude to not give
a proper answer."
He should be saying that to
me, not the other way around.
I left his confession unrequited.
That's exactly what I did to him.
I-I'm going now.
Ohana?
I'll pay the bill.
No, I'll-
What's wrong?
I'll meet you downstairs.
I've seen this back before.
The rain's gotten heavier.
Wait here. I'll go and buy an umbrella-
I can buy one myself.
Bye.
Wait!
I don't want to see his back anymore.
Hey, you!
You're drenched!
Wet!
Huh? I-
Get in!
Hey, you're gonna catch a cold!
No...
I hate this...
No!
Help me...
Help me, Ko!
Ohana!
Are you okay, Ohana?!
What are you doing out here?!
Hey, why are you crying-
I don't know!
I don't know...
But I can say this much:
I've...
I've never been moved in so
many ways in one day before.
Do you have a girlfriend, Tohru?
Hey, Ohana! Where are you now?!
It's like a date...
An antagonist. All right.
Are you coming back, Ohana?
Episode 12
See Ya.
See ya.