By joining our revolt, Princess,
you will strengthen our solidarity.
There will be a victory prayer service today
at the new Royal Cathedral.
Key members of the royal family and
various lords and ladies will be in attendance.
Of course that includes Her Majesty the Queen.
We will wait for the ceremony to begin,
and then drop the cathedral's ceiling.
The ceiling?
It's exactly what it sounds like.
Many of the laborers who built the cathedral
are fellow believers in our cause.
The colonies are ruled by the Kingdom,
and their people make up most of the workforce,
but they are only granted
the bare minimum of human rights.
Their outrage was inevitable.
Princess Charlotte,
I swear this revolution will succeed.
Immigration, poverty, classism.
Those are the reasons you fight.
But I can't let you do it.
Not a revolution.
Zelda has set out for the new royal cathedral.
In eight hours, the government
will have changed hands.
Just as we planned.
I knew the old-fashioned intelligence
committees' methods were outdated.
What happened to Seven?
What?
Oh, she's out skiving off.
I have good news.
With Zelda's assistance,
we've gained a powerful ally.
The more people are around,
the harder it will be to make any moves.
I have to do something
while they still think I'm on their side.
I'm betting the odds of this revolution's
success are less than one in ten.
But that will be good enough.
It will cause enough strife within the Kingdom
to give the Commonwealth's forces
the perfect chance to invade.
Control is backing this revolution,
knowing it will fail?
Does it hurt to think of your people?
I'd expect nothing less of the REAL princess.
You were brilliant. At first, you even had me fooled.
How did you dupe Ange?
I don't understand what you're saying.
If you're thinking about stopping the revolution,
you're wasting your energy.
If it comes down to it, I'll kill you myself.
We're going to turn this revolution
into a revenge war.
If you were going to run away anyway,
I wish you'd left me out of this from the start!
My life is not yours to play with!
Princess?!
Wait!
If Operation: Changeling means that
one of us has to disappear,
then you can disappear without me.
From the day we met,
I've always hated that about you.
Goodbye, Ange.
Never let me see you again.
No!
This is...
But it's the old you that I love so much.
Princess?
Mobilize the firefighters!
Prepare to land, just in case!
In here!
What's going on?
Unbolt this door!
Who are you?
Hey, wait!
I have to be sure!
That idiot!
An ox?
Chancellor of the Realm
and Ambassador Extraordinary and
Plenipotentiary of the Eastern Land of Japan,
Lord Horikawa Masayasu desires to attend
your nation's victory prayer service.
First I have to figure out where Princess is.
Yes.
Once the people find out that Princess
was involved with the assassination of the Queen,
the whole Kingdom will fall into chaos.
And we'll be finished with her
as soon as the operation is over?
What a pity.
What's wrong? What was that sound?
What happened?
Where is Princess?
Answer my question if you don't want to die.
The new... royal cathedral.
What are your plans?
T-to assassinate the Queen!
To what end?
To put Princess at the center of the assassination...
And provoke the rebel army to action.
And that's where Zelda is?
Yes.
Do you really think you can get away with this?
I'll be fine.
As long as you don't talk.
Wait!
Goodbye.
You idiot!
I was trying so hard to be discreet here!
Dorothy? How...?
The government ordered me here
to figure out Zelda's plot.
They're playing musical chairs with the military
and we got stuck in the middle.
Things are pretty tense
in the Commonwealth right now.
Beatrice. Get over here.
It was Ange. She ruined our whole operation.
Dorothy.
We have to go help Princess.
Rescuing Princess was not part of
my mission directive.
Oh.
We are spies.
I can't assist with anything outside of my mission.
But...
If you ask me for a favor, as a friend...
I'll do everything in my power to help you.
Thank you.
Miss Ange is back?
Yup. She just got here.
Where have you been?!
We've been ready and waiting for ages!
Waiting?
Yes! We know exactly where Her Highness is,
but Dorothy said we had to wait until-
Liar!
You can forgive a little white lie.
Besides, if you had been open with me from the start,
this would've gone a little more smoothly.
I'm sorry.
Come on, you two!
Never mind that!
If we don't hurry, Her Highness will...!
Stop!
The service starts at 1900 hours.
If we take normal roads, we'll be late.
Can we make it?
Leave it to me!
Princess!
It's true! She's here!
Please wait here.
For you, Princess.
Thank you.
I-it's nothing.
We have scones, too, if you like.
P-please excuse me!
Don't worry about it.
I know. Why don't you join me?
Why don't you ALL join me?
Your concern is unnecessary, Princess.
Satisfying the hunger of four or five men will hardly-
No.
I'm doing it for myself.
I mean, eating is so much nicer
with good company, don't you think?
What's this...?
Oi! Stop! Stop the car!
This road is closed today!
I'm sorry.
We're just in such a hurry.
We're running late for the service.
Won't you please let us use the Wall Road?
Oh, is that the problem?
Let us open the-
Wait a moment.
I heard that the princess was already
inside the Royal Cathedral.
We're going to have to see some identification.
Floor it.
Hey!
Stop!
Intruders?
Yes.
One disguised as Princess Charlotte.
Find them and dispose of them.
Yes, Sir.
Her Majesty has arrived!
Major.
The Queen is here.
So it's time then.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
Our plan is foolproof.
But Major Yngwie...
How exactly are you going to drop the ceiling?
I'll use a key to activate the-
Major.
Show some consideration.
The Queen is a member of Princess' family.
She's right.
That was thoughtless of me.
Not at all.
I agreed to this plan for my own ambition.
But I don't think it's right
to be the only one whose hands stay clean.
Major.
I don't suppose you would let me hold on to that key?
No, that would...
Princess.
I'll have a private room prepared.
You should get some rest.
I'm not tired.
Please get some rest.
Alright. I'll accept your offer.
Thank you. It was delicious.
It is an honor.
Major.
I'll take care of that key.
Certainly.
It's gone!
But that's impossible!
Princess!
Wait!
Before you retire to your room,
I'd like to search your effects.
Oh?
Does this mean you suspect me?
We never were going to get along, were we?
You sneaky little brat.
You were careless, Major.
Zelda, what just...?
Don't worry about it.
I hadn't told her about the assassination.
Yngwie, you're still in charge of the ceiling.
Do what you have to do.
The trumpets of Jericho have already sounded.
They're coming after us!
Fire!
On the right! Fire!
I have a request.
I ask permission to leave your side
to attend to urgent business.
You would abandon your duty?
I beg of you.
Miss Dorothy, can't you go any faster?!
If I could, I would!
How's that?
Dammit!
Fire!
Are we out of options?
Should we capture them?
No. Corpses are easier to deal with.
What the-?
Something's not right.
I wonder what's wrong.
Chise!
Miss Chise!
To repay your hospitality.
All of you, forward!
What?
Assassinate the Queen?
How unsettling.
We think Princess is in
the Royal Cathedral with Zelda.
I saw Zelda in a room above the stairwell.
Really?
I would not lie about this.
I saw it from the chapel.
Ange, you go help Princess!
Take me with you!
You can't drop the ceiling!
If you start a revolution through bloodshed,
someone else will start a new revolution
to right all your wrongs!
Princess, this nation is corrupt.
We are going to take action,
and eliminate the social hierarchy!
I know how you feel!
And so I promise you that I will become Queen,
and I will change this country.
Major.
Don't listen to her. You've already-
Princess.
The promise you just made would mean
renouncing your own position.
Do you really think you can change the country?
Yes.
And I will likely be its last queen.
I suspect my reign will end on the guillotine.
How could you...
Zelda! What are you...!
Don't listen to her lies.
This revolution isn't just for you anymore.
I... made a promise...
When the Revolution tore my friend from me...
I promised I would make her dream come true!
I may be an imposter, but seeing this country
for the past ten years, I realized.
It wasn't only us.
So many people in this nation have been
torn from each other by invisible walls.
When she said she wanted to get rid of the Wall,
I didn't know what she meant.
If it meant getting rid of all the pain and sadness,
I sincerely wanted it to happen.
But I took away her chance!
So I swore I would
change the country in her place!
Princess.
If you don't stop spouting that nonsense,
I'll kill you right now.
You can't!
Our country needs her!
Please, Zelda. Give us a little time.
We can still try to figure out
if this is really the best solution.
Can we, now?
He was weak.
You're a formidable woman.
But I think you will serve me better dead.
You're too much for me to handle.
Princess?
Princess!
Ange!
How is she?
She has lost much blood.
We must tend to her quickly.
It's started.
What do we do?
If we bust up the service, then their
assassination plot will be ruined, too, right?
Huh? Wait a-
Ange!
I will handle things here! Go!
I'm sorry, Chise!
Princess.
You... are our true Queen.
So please... you mustn't die.
I won't.
Let's go.
Zelda!
What the-
Is that a...?
I guess it's time to retreat.
Wait!
Charlotte. You couldn't stay away, could you?
Princess!
I'm sorry!
I was so stupid!
It's my fault you...
Don't cry.
I'm the one who's sorry.
I lied to you.
I knew.
Dorothy told me...
I should have asked all of you for help
from the beginning.
She's right.
You're always running off into danger alone,
never listening to anyone else.
There's always been an invisible wall
around your heart.
Princess!
I promise you again.
I'll break the wall around your heart, too.
And I'll never leave your side until the day comes
that you can smile for all of us.
Yeah.
You let them escape?
Mistakes were made.
I am terribly sorry.
No matter.
Your efforts weren't entirely fruitless.
The idiots! What the hell were they doing?!
They defied my orders!
Where did the Principal Team head off-
Where is our Principal Team?
They are currently recuperating.
Where?
Casablanca.
Contact them straightaway.
A man with a white flower made advances at me.
What?
R-really?
He gave me new orders.
General Al-Kadil is in hiding.
We need to find out what he's up to.
Oh, is that all?
Well, that's pretty much how our luck with men goes.
I cannot imagine Ange
in a romantic affair in any case.
Watch your tongue. Believe it or not, I-
I'm spotting movement.
Just one, eh?
That woman appears to be in the military.
Alright, ladies. Just as we discussed.
Right.
Well, that's the end of our holiday.
No, we'll finish this up and get right back to it.
Then when you get back,
we'll really let our hair down.
Like old times?
Just like old times.
But this time, we'll have all our friends.
I don't know...