You okay?
Yes.
Are you okay, Onee-chan?
I'm the one who agreed to take this job.
Don't force yourself to keep up.
No, I'll be fine.
I'm the one who begged you to let me fight.
But...
We're almost done, anyway.
We managed to finish the job, thankfully.
I wanted to fight some more.
We start heading back to
the capital tomorrow.
Huh? You're wrapping up the trading trip?
Your treatment takes priority.
We need potent holy water from the
capital's church to dispel that curse.
But...
We have a long road ahead of us.
Take it easy.
Okay...
I hope you get better soon.
Thank you, Filo.
Sure.
Master,
something's going on there.
Is that...
a human child?
Rising of the Shield Hero
Melty
Those birds looked yummy.
If we go after them now,
we can hunt them down.
Wait, yummy?
Now look here, Filo.
Those were your own kind.
My own kind?
So big...
Are you a filolial?
You mean me?
You can talk, too?
Yep.
I've always dreamed of
talking with a filolial!
For you. It's dried meat.
Thanks!
Could she be from the village?
Nah, she's too well dressed.
She's probably a noble's
daughter or something.
What's your name?
Filo.
Filo-chan?
I'm Melty.
Mel-chan, then.
Sure.
Oh, I know.
Want some more?
I do!
She must love filolials a lot.
Filo...
We still have work to do in the village.
In the meantime, you can
play with that girl.
You mean it?
Really?
Yay!
Wow!
You can transform, too?
Yep.
That's amazing!
She took that surprisingly well.
They both seem to like their new friend.
Filo needs to spend time with
other kids, so that's good.
Master, can I play some more with Mel-chan?
Just be back by sunset.
'Kay.
Let's go.
Don't go too far, you hear me?
'Kay.
Drink it slowly.
Thank you, Our Savior!
Thank you!
Help her too, Naofumi-sama.
Sure.
Does it hurt?
No, I'm fine.
Sorry. It's all my fault.
You promised not to say that anymore.
I'm back, Master.
Oh, welcome back.
Are you okay, Onee-chan?
Yup!
I made a friend today!
That Mel girl from earlier?
Yep.
She said she's traveled to a
lot of places, just like me.
Huh...
And she told me so many
things I didn't know!
That so?
And she says she got separated from her
people when she was playing with filolials.
Good for her...
Wait, what? Separated?
Naofumi-sama...
I apologize for showing up so late.
Um... Could you let me accompany
you for a little while?
Wait a second. What do you mean?
I was on my way to the royal capital,
but, uh, when I saw the filolials...
I was so engrossed in playing with them,
I got separated from my guards!
Guards?
I hear you're leaving for the
capital tomorrow, Savior.
Could you please take me with you?
Did she learn about me from the villagers?
I'm aware that I'm making a selfish request.
But please, I must return to the capital!
I beg you!
If she is a noble's daughter,
we might get a reward,
but it might also cause problems if
I'm the one who takes her home.
Master, I want you to help her.
Naofumi-sama...
We can't turn her down when
she's having trouble.
I want you to help her as well.
You'll have to cough up a reward, okay?
Of course! I shall ask my father!
We did it.
Yes.
We truly can't find the words to thank you.
I'd rather have money than words.
The next time I'm here,
I'll collect everything I'm owed.
C-Certainly!
Filo...
Here we go!
Did I wake you?
No... I can keep watch now.
It's fine. You can sleep for tonight.
They're both so quiet now.
It's funny after how much noise
they were making earlier.
Aren't you cold?
Nope.
We can't have you catching a chill.
Huh? Where's Mel-san?
You don't think...
Nah, there's no way.
But Filo...
Come to think of it, she did say
her own kind looked yummy.
Yes...
Raphtalia.
Yes?
We saw nothing, okay?
Wh-What are you saying?!
If we just destroy the evidence...
Naofumi-sama!
What, you want us to go confess that
Filo ate some noble's daughter?!
What's wrong, Master?
Filo, where's Mel-san?
Mel-chan?
She's sleeping in my feathers.
Wake up, Mel-chan.
What's the matter?
What are you doing?
Filo-chan's feathers are
so soft and comfortable...
So you took off your clothes?
Yes.
But how did you...
It's so nice and warm.
Do these feathers have
sleep-inducing powers or something?
Well, then...
Thank you all so much.
Can I take her home?
Make sure you collect the reward.
'Kay. Let's go.
Right.
Farewell!
We'll miss her.
I'm sure we can see her again.
Right.
Why's the shield the only one missing?
I've heard about him.
What is he doing here?
Hey, I want to ask you something.
His Holiness the Pope!
If it isn't the Shield Hero.
Welcome to our church.
I saw your magnificent
duel at the royal palace.
The way you fought with the odds stacked
against you left a deep impression on me.
I could not believe you held your
own despite wielding only a shield.
Naofumi-sama...
Spare me the pleasantries.
I need the most potent holy water
you have to dispel a curse.
Holy water, is it?
Yeah.
Then please make your offering.
How much?
If you want the most potent one,
that'll be one gold coin.
Fine by me.
You mustn't, Naofumi-sama!
That's too expensive!
I don't mind.
Compared to you, a gold coin means nothing.
Naofumi-sama...
Cheap Holy Water (Crude)
You wanted a gold coin for that?
Why did you bring a low-quality item?
B-But...
God is equally compassionate to all.
If you did this to satisfy
your personal beliefs,
then I hope you repent at once.
I... I'm terribly sorry!
I apologize for my fellow disciple.
I won't complain as long
as I get my money's worth.
I'm thankful for your understanding.
Curse-Dispelling Holy Water (Pure)
I guess that'll do.
Let's go.
God shows us all the way.
Please be grateful for his guidance.
Everything we have, we are
given by God's grace.
Talk about patronizing.
Naofumi-sama...
Sh-Shield Hero!
We're running.
B-But why are we running?
What else can we do? He's coming for us.
Wait!
What a pest.
This way.
You okay?
Yes.
He's probably after me, so let's split up.
But...
Go get Filo.
We'll regroup by the carriage.
Understood.
This way!
W-Wait...
Surely... I lost him this time.
Naofumi!
You attacked me in the middle of the street?
What the hell is wrong with you?
Shut up!
Where is that slave girl?
Free her!
You're a real pest, too. Raphtalia is—
Not Raphtalia-chan.
I'm talking about the blonde
girl with wings on her back.
I saw her with you, so don't lie to me.
You mean Filo?
Filo-chan?
So that's her name.
I've never seen a girl as perfect as her.
I can't believe there's a girl who's
just like Freon-chan from Hellworld.
I happen to have a thing for angels.
I don't care.
My heart has been in overdrive
ever since my first look at her.
I love other worlds!
I love blonde angels!
Ridiculous.
Dude, what's up with that?
Oh yeah.
That fat bird's yours too, isn't it?
I'll send you and that chubster to hell!
Air Strike Javelin!
Chaos Spear!
Knock it off, you moron!
Don't fight here!
What's the big deal? Go for it!
You wanna say that again?
Take that!
Naofumi!
Please stop, Spear Hero!
Aren't you the guy from before?
Th-This is a public place!
It's no place for a personal duel!
It is now.
Surround them.
Draw your swords.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I declare this an official duel between
the Spear Hero and the Shield Hero,
with the authority vested
in me by the crown!
Put your weapons away!
I will not allow the heroes to
fight among themselves.
That's...
Wh-What are you doing here?
It's been far too long,
Sister.
Please don't think your or the hero's
privilege can cover up this mess.
Spear Hero...
Look around you.
Who would call a man that puts
lives at risk a hero?
Sister, your fun and
games have gone too far.
I'm simply doing my job as the hero's aide.
Is making him fight in a public
place your idea of aid?
You dare defy me, your older sister?
If need be, I will let
Mother know about this.
I'm terribly sorry, everyone.
Melty is Myne's little sister?
Which means she's this country's...
Naofumi-sama!
What happened?
Oh, Motoyasu once again...
Filo-chan.
That's your name, right?
Yep.
You poor thing.
Naofumi's working you
like a horse, isn't he?
I like drawing the carriage.
Naofumi, you swine.
You're making her pull your
wagon like that fat bird?
You'll pay for this!
You called me fat.
You made fun of me the last time we met, too.
I did? When?
I hate you, spear guy!
Huh? Y-You were that fat bi...
Motoyasu-sama!
Somebody take him to a doctor at once!
Filo wins!
Well done. I'm proud of you, Filo.
Naofumi-sama...
He always puts us through hell.
He had that coming.
Sheesh, what's with that satisfied smirk?
Our Savior of the Heavenly Fowl...
No, Shield Hero.
I need to talk to you.
Kid, could you explain this to me?
It's a long story.
Let us discuss things here.
Come on.
You know that's not gonna fly.
Sorry. We couldn't think
of a better place nearby.
Yeesh...
So? Who exactly are you?
Pardon my late introduction.
I am first in line to the throne of Melromarc,
Second Princess Melty Melromarc.
Th-Thr...
In line to the throne?
She'll be the next ruler, basically.
You're ahead of your older sister?
Yes. My sister has always been a
problem child due to her personality.
I'm not surprised.
I had no idea you were the Shield Hero.
But this might be perfect.
What's up?
I...
Sorry, but we're done here.
I can't trust anything you say.
Get lost.
In the Midst of Turmoil