Kiss Him, Not Me
The Strange Room And
The Four High School Boys
Igarashi.
You're amazing, man.
That's the keychain Serinuma
gave us the other day, right?
Oh, yeah. From after the movie.
Why's that amazing?
What?
It's the new mini dolls!
This is the first time I've seen them!
Mini Shion is so cute!
Um, I guess as thanks for today...
I'd like all of you to have one!
animeito
Mu
Iga
Nana
Shi
She gave us anime character keychains!
Who wants those?!
Don't laugh, man.
Isn't it a turn off, though?
Not just the anime characters,
but matching ones for us four.
I dunno, I'd say it's interesting.
Really?
So you're giving up, then?
That's one less rival for me,
so I'd be pretty happy, personally.
Seriously? You're really something, man.
Here it comes!
Leave it to me!
Amazing!
Serinuma-san!
I knew you were pretty athletic, but
I didn't know you were this good.
My body feels so light!
It's like I've grown wings!
Wow, someone's getting ahead of themselves.
Now that I think about it,
she was always really fast at
the jumping side to side test.
It was scary.
That was a brilliant receive.
Why are you acting so excited?
Girls' Locker Room
The girls' soccer club... needs my help?
Yeah. Our club has 11 members,
which is just enough to play,
and we've got a practice
match next weekend, but...
But I hurt my leg.
Since you seem so good at sports,
I was wondering if you could help.
Please!
"Seeming good at sports"
doesn't mean good at soccer.
Okay!
Huh?
Really?
You're a lifesaver! Thanks!
Hey, Kae-chan. You shouldn't just
agree without giving it some thought.
It'll be fine! I may not look like it,
but I know a lot about soccer!
Huh?!
I'm a fan of Cap-Tsuba, Ina-11, and Gi-Killi!
So you watch soccer, Serinuma-san?
Yes! I always supported
Gazel from Aliea in Ina-11!
Yeah?
Is that right?
Is that some kind of good luck charm?
Still, it's my first time playing,
so I have to practice.
Don't worry about us at the history
club, and do your best at soccer.
I'll cheer you on.
I-I'll support you, too! You can count on me.
Should I coach you?
Since I'm in the soccer club,
I think I could help.
What? Really?!
Mutsumi-senpai, Shinomiya-kun,
Igarashi-kun, thank you!
Look at them go.
Oh, but I have practice after school
too, so I can't be there the whole time.
In that case, Nana can teach
you. He used to play himself.
No way.
Stuff like that can't be taught overnight.
A total novice with only one week of
practice will just get in the way.
That's why I'm going to practice!
The ball is my friend! We can get along!
Tsubasa-kun became friends with
the ball because he was with it 24/7!
Th-The length of time doesn't
matter! It's what you do with it!
You've done nothing with it!
Don't take Tsubasa-kun lightly!
The ball has the right to
choose its friends, too!
You're heartless, Nanashima-kun!
Now, now. Let's all relax.
Calm down, Nana. What are you talking about?
Anyway, I'm not gonna have any
part in this. Do what you want.
What's his deal?! Did he
have to put it like that?
I'll get good at soccer no matter what!
And I'll win!
Good to meet you!
Thanks for coming!
Let's start with our usual warm-up routine.
Sounds good!
After some light stretches, 20 laps
around the school grounds.
Twent—
Fight! On! Fight! On!
After that, five sets of 20
sit-ups and reverse sit-ups!
Hands behind your head,
and keep your legs together.
Now, two sets of 10 push-ups!
Lastly, some cool down exercises.
Okay, time to start practice!
That's all for today!
Thanks everyone!
A-Are you okay, Serinuma-san?
I'm... fine...
Amazing. You look like a newborn fawn.
Totally fine!
Actually, I'm not fine at all.
Sure, I lost some weight
and can move more freely,
but I forgot I was originally
an indoor person,
so I've got no muscle at all!
Should we call it a day?
N-No! I can keep going—
5 Days Left
Is that too tight?
With proper taping, you can avoid injury.
Yeah, it feels good!
Thank you, Shinomiya-kun! Nothing less
from someone on the health committee!
Ah, no, it was n-nothing.
I brought refreshments.
Thank you so much!
3 Days Left
Hey, be honest. What do you think of her?
Who, Serinuma-san?
Yeah.
She's a total washout.
She wasn't any better today. What's with her?
Yeah, but it's kinda too late to ask
someone else to help at this point.
We'll just have to giv—
You're the ones that asked
her for help. Drop the attitude.
Crap. That just slipped out.
What's it got to do with me?
Ow!
W-Wait. Hey!
What was with that impossible
curve ball? You're just goofing off!
N-Nanashima-kun?!
I-I'm not goofing off!
Whenever I kick the ball, it always
comes back at me for some reason.
Always?
That's actually pretty impressive.
I guess the ball doesn't
want to be friend-zoned!
Are you serious?
Er, no... sorry.
So this is why they said she was no good.
You know, why don't you just quit?
You can still bow out now, can't you?
Even if you stumble on a beginner's
miracle, that won't cut it for the game.
No.
Nanashima-kun, you were right.
I was naive. I felt like I could do anything...
That's just not true.
But I took on the challenge anyway!
I don't want to give up!
Ba-dump.
What choice do I have?
Give it one more try.
You probably do something weird
whenever you kick the ball.
Maybe your ankle, or follow through.
You don't want to give up, right?
Do whatever you can, then. I'll help you.
Okay.
Nana's here for some reason.
You're right.
After fighting like that,
he sure came back quick.
Now, now. It's a beautiful
thing when people get along.
Time!
First Half    Second Half     Total
Higashinohashi
Josai
They're in stoppage time
and still down one point.
About two minutes or so left?
Yeah. This will be tough.
I have an idea.
Pass it to me at the next throw-in!
What are you gonna do?
It's too late to do anything now!
Don't feel down, everyone!
If we give up right now, that'll
be the end of the match!
Isn't that for basketball?
But she's extremely persuasive!
The opposing team's goal is really close.
If they clear the ball, it's all over.
Serinuma-san got it.
But she's facing the wrong way.
I'm not sure she'll get a chance to shoot.
Wha—
Huh?!
She kicked it without turning around!
Where is she aiming?!
What just happened?!
How did it go backwards into the net?
Did the ball just curve?
It curved like crazy!
So that's how she decided to turn the tables!
That's so stupid! Unreal!
She's gotta be stupid!
Unbelievable. Is this girl
for real? She's hilarious!
Didn't you say you were gonna step aside?
Changed my mind.
Kae-chan, you smell like your compress.
Sorry.
But it's summer break soon!
This muscle pain's nothing!
You know it.
Comiket, performances, concerts, talk shows!
It was worth saving for!
All right! Let's have some fun!
Serinuma. If you fail the next test,
you'll need to take supplementary
classes during the summer.
For two weeks.
Just plan on not having a vacation.
Kiss Him, Not Me
She totally bombed the tests she
took right after losing weight.
So now she's like that.
She's memorizing English and translating
Japanese classics at the same time.
Isn't she an idiot?
You can tell she's going insane.
If I have to take two weeks,
it'll get in the way of
the Mirage Saga events,
since they both happen during the day.
I won't be able to say goodbye to Shion.
I really don't want that to happen!
Mutsumi-senpai.
Serinuma-san, you have no problem
with Japanese history, right?
What are you the most worried about?
U-Um, first of all, math.
Uh-huh.
And science, too.
Stare
It'll be all right. You'll catch up.
If you like, I can help you study.
S-Senpai!
Please do!
Teach us, too, Senpai!
Sure. Everyone sure is studious.
Yup!
As if we'd leave you alone with her!
I'm gonna catch up!
And so, you get this.
Do you get it up to this point?
Yes! This is the first time
I've really grasped it.
Is that right? That's good to hear.
He makes it so easy to understand.
I can always count on him!
I might be able to do this!
Hey.
You're in first-year, aren't you?
Are you able to follow what we're doing?
Meaning: Go home!
Don't worry.
I do second-year level work at prep school.
Meaning: Shut up!
And by the way, you answered
question two wrong.
Meaning: You're an idiot!
Will you be okay?
Hey, he's right. You used
the wrong formula, Nana.
Shut up! I know it's wrong!
Oh? You do? Really?!
I can't say I could possibly understand
why you'd answer wrong on purpose!
Nana, you always get so worked up
when you're caught red-handed.
Dammit, Igarashi, I'll kill you!
You're too loud! Get out!
We'd like to remind our customers
to refrain from activities
that take excessive time,
like studying, or yelling,
while in our establishment.
Meaning: Go home!
We can't stay in the library, we definitely
can't stay in the restaurant...
Not many places for group meet-ups, are there?
There really aren't.
No thanks to you two.
In that case...
How about Serinuma-san's place? Heart.
Huh?
What?!
Well, I was the one who asked
for help with my studies.
So I don't mind everyone
using my place to work.
The problem is...
This sea of rot.
This is bad.
Really bad.
They already saw this,
so I'll leave it alone.
What's bad is...
Those. I have to be careful about
handling those in front of real boys.
But,
closets were made for times like these!
I'll quickly but cleanly put
away all my treasures!
And... sealed!
Excuse us!
Sorry for the lack of space.
Not at all.
No, no. I just did a rough clean-up,
so don't look too closely.
Kae!
I brought you some tea.
Goodness gracious. Hello th—
Was that an afterimage?!
What are you doing? And what's with your face?!
Oh, my. It's just good manners.
We have handsome boys over,
and it's been a while since
I've prettied myself up.
Manners?! More like horrors!
You're trying too hard!
This room definitely suits
Serinuma-senpai, doesn't it?
More like, what are you
guys doing here, anyway?
I don't really understand this part.
What part?
Um... question three.
Wait, um...
Y-You're really close.
Theoretically, isn't that
what a room date is?!
You're an idiot, so you'd fail at
the part where you teach her.
Shut up, first-year!
Well, I get you. A girl's room is something
to get a little excited about, isn't it?
Right? Like looking at
yearbooks together and stuff.
There would only be photos of
the old Serinuma-senpai, though.
Or maybe pull the blankets down a bit.
That's vulgar!
Like you don't wanna see!
Crazy. I didn't know these existed.
That scared me.
Hey, my pen rolled under the bed.
I'll get it.
I'll pick it up.
I had the store give me the display.
I usually put it up for decoration,
but I decided to put it away for today.
So you had this on display.
Yeah. Next to this.
A-An altar?!
Hey, what is that?!
I don't know! But that's the same
character as that keychain we got.
Doesn't he kinda look like Nana?
Shut up! I'm not dead!
Did this person... pass away?
Iga
Nana
Shi
Yes.
May I pay my respects?
Yes, please.
Okay, everyone.
Iga
Nana
Shi
What the hell is this?
Kae knows what she's doing.
The spitting image of me when I was young!
I'm home.
Oh, you're home, Takuro! Kae has
some guests in her room right now.
Boys. Four of them. Heart!
Well then, shall we get started?
Yup!
Okay! Let's do this!
Don't be fooled!
Onii-chan?!
You punks! Yeah, you guys!
You four over there!
Allow me, her older brother Takuro,
to give you guys a warning, man-to-man!
You were probably lured here by her
looks, but don't let that fool you!
This girl is a seriously crazy otaku!
Uh, we know.
It's okay.
We even gave our condolences
to Shion-san earlier.
Gosh!
What's your problem, Nii-chan?!
Not everyone is narrow-minded like you!
Get out!
Narrow-minded. Narrow-minded.
Narrow-minded
You'll say that...
even after seeing this?!
It's...
Look! Otaku are gross!
So what?! There isn't a girl
out there who hates gay guys!
Mu    Nana    Iga    Shi
Oh. It's BL.
I hate you!
Shut up!
Onii-san.
We're studying here, so if you don't mind...
Come, now.
Hey, Wai—
Excuse us.
Th-Thank you.
Okay, everyone. First,
let's tidy up these books.
Uh, sure.
O-Oh, it's fine! I can take
care of it on my own!
Wait.
Don't be so rough with them.
They're important to you, aren't they?
Yes.
Thanks for having us over.
Mutsumi-senpai, thank you so much for today.
It was nothing. Tell your
brother I'm sorry, will you?
I acted rudely back there.
Not at all! He had it coming!
Serinuma-san, take this.
It's for the test.
If you find yourself at a loss,
this will help you decide.
Luck is a skill, too.
Thank you!
Oh, you three.
I've got one for each of you,
too. Good luck on your test.
S-Senpai...
That's the first time I've been
so excited in a girl's room,
so to speak.
Damn, that was fun!
So, this is his way of apologizing?
Yes! All clear! Summer break, come on!
Congratulations!
Serinuma, let's go to the pool.
That sounds like a good idea!
Just the two of us!
The Charm of
Japanese Castles
Let's go to a castle mentioned in this.
And so I...
Prince-sama!
Set all the otaku events as top priority!
I was a gloomy kid when I was younger.
Why?
Everyone said I was delicate,
and girls would tease me.
I was popular! Because I played soccer!
Igarashi was still more popular, though.
You should have played in high school, too.
Nana, why'd you quit?
It wears you out!
I wanna enjoy the school festivals
like normal, then go home.
The cultural festival is fun.
You get to see your efforts pay off.
I wonder what's supposed to be
fun about seeing me cross dress.
I bet you'd look good!
Next time:
The Clear and Blue Autumn Sky,
and Passionate Otome
Look forward to it!!
You wanna fight?!
No, no. Cross dressers are the
flowers of any cultural festival.