Onii-chan's grinning a lot lately.
It's probably a girl.
Trap
Onii-chan, you can use the bath now.
Mom says to hurry up.
O-Okay.
Now, then...
Enter Passcode
The password...
It's still his entrance exam ID?
Tap tap
So careless.
Minagawa Yuki.
Minagawa Yuki:
I think I should take a bath, too (*-*)
Hey! You had a dirty thought
just now, didn't you? (¬_¬)
Just kidding. See you.
I knew it.
Evil wench, seducing my brother...
I'll make you suffer!
Roar
Ding dong
Furuya Jun:
"Sorry, can you stop talking to me now?
I'm trying to study."
It's Hotaru-chan!
"Huh? Why? Did I do something?
Is it because of that?"
"That"?
Did she do something to piss him off?
Yeah, she would.
"That's right."
"But that was only because you wanted it..."
Wanted it? Wanted what?
Did he need her notes or something?
I don't get it.
Let's just be mad.
"I don't care. Forget about it."
"You're awful! It was my first time!"
First time?
Doing what?
Something that was the first time
for her and that Onii-chan wanted?
Oh! I think I know!
"Yeah, I did, but who doesn't go on dates?"
"Besides, it was my first time
going on a date, too."
I knew it!
She doesn't get it!
"What? So our date didn't mean anything?"
See, I knew it!
No wonder he was home late the other day.
He was with her!
"That's right."
"So, sleeping with me meant nothing, too?"
Sleep?
Did they take a nap together or something?
Napping on a date? Seriously?
Onii-chan's so weird.
"All we did was sleep."
"Then what about the baby in my belly?"
Plop
That's what she meant?!
B-B-But you need to do it to make babies.
There's no way Onii-chan would...
"Is it really my child?
Do you have evidence?"
"I haven't slept with anyone but you."
This can't be true!
He's only in high school!
Huh?
Hotaru?
What are you doing in my room?
Mom!
Hotaru?
What's going on?
Onii-chan made a baby!
Hotaru?!
The End
I'm going out with a girl in my class.
After a while, you start
wanting to take care of her.
But I don't know what to do.
Tell Me
Kamine, do you enjoy being with me?
Huh?
Yeah, I do.
I'm really not good at this kind of thing.
Let me know if you ever
have a problem with me.
Can I tell you something, then?
You have a problem?
Oh, no, it's not a big deal.
I think I understand what you're feeling,
but I want you to tell me straight.
That you love me.
S-Sorry.
This stuff is a pain in the butt, right?
No, it's not a big deal.
But why bother?
I feel stupid about it, too,
but I want you to say it.
All right, Kamine.
Sorry.
It's true, I don't think I've really
spoken my mind until now.
I'll be careful from now on.
No, I don't mean from now on, but...
Am I making a mistake?
Um, now would be good.
You're right.
I should show good faith immediately.
Huh?
No, I just mean...
Kamine, is there anything you want me to do?
Um...
Why don't we go somewhere together?
I hate saying it like this,
but how about our first date?
That's not it!
It's not that I want to go on a date!
What?!
I want you to tell me, with your
own words, that you love me!
Why?!
You've never said it to me yet.
H-Haven't I?
A date would be nice,
but I want to hear it in words.
I see.
Then...
It's okay, though.
Wh-What's wrong?
I'm just making you say it at this point.
I'm sorry.
I made things complicated.
No, I'm sorry, too.
By the way, about that date—
I love you, Kamine.
Kamine, I love you.
I know anything I say now will seem forced,
but I love you.
I really love you,
from the bottom of my heart.
I love you!
Sorry.
I should have said so sooner.
I'm dense.
What's wrong?
You're beet red.
Are you angry?
"You know those people who confess by text?
I think that's pretty shitty."
"I'm interested in you, Takase.
Sorry to tell you like this, but I like you."
A text message blunder
made things really awkward.
Advice
Kanda.
Y-Yuki-chan!
Did you do the English assignment?
Huh?
There was an assignment?
This is definitely bad.
I wonder if she read
the message I sent after.
Maybe I should send it again.
No, I should tell her in person, not by text.
She won't talk to me, though.
What should I do?
Stare...
Huh? What?
Sorry, I got curious.
Curious?
About what?
I don't have the brains to explain.
But you looked just like I did before.
What's with this guy?
Have I met him somewhere?
Uh...
It's not your problem,
so if you'll excuse me...
It's a woman, isn't it?
I can tell just by looking at you.
Huh? How?
I told you, you're a lot like me.
I, too, have made many a woman cry.
No, I haven't made that many cry.
But you did make her cry, didn't you?
The one you absolutely shouldn't have.
Whoa!
I think I should ask him for advice!
You don't think I'm a dating master, do you?
Huh?
Bingo!
Dating... what?
Seeing you takes me back to the days
when I would be trembling in the rain.
Then what am I supposed to do?
She won't even talk to me.
I don't know.
I'm stupid. I have no idea.
All I can think to do is
to go to her and hold her tight.
Whoa!
I feel like you might be right,
when you say it.
All right. Then isn't there
somewhere you need to be now?
Um...
Thank you for all the advice.
Advice?
What advice?
I just talked about myself.
About an idiot who gets called
the "dating master."
Senpai...
Now, go to her.
Before she leaves.
R-Right!
Oh, before I go, what's your name—
S-Senpai!
See you!
I feel listless lately.
I catch myself staring
at random things in class.
And my chest hurts a little, too.
It's All the Fever's Fault
Chi-chan, are you all right?
Huh? Oh, sorry.
You're acting weird lately.
Are you sick or something?
Yeah, I think I have a cold.
I don't know why, but I keep
thinking about Sugawara-kun.
This has never happened to me before.
I wonder if it really is a cold.
Pardon me.
My heart's pounding.
It's definitely a cold.
T-Takano?
What's wrong?
I feel feverish.
Are you hurt?
Y-Yeah, I kinda hurt myself in club.
Where's the nurse?
She left a minute ago.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
H-Hey, is the soccer club okay?
Yeah, I guess.
What am I saying?
I can't hold a conversation like this.
My head's hazy.
I should think of things to talk about.
Hey, Takano,
weren't you here to have your
temperature taken or something?
R-Right.
I think I do have a fever.
A-Are you okay?
All right, I need to get back to club.
Ah, wait.
What?
I don't know.
Huh?
No, I mean, I don't know
where the thermometer is.
Oh, okay.
You scared me.
S-Sorry.
You scared me for a second,
saying that with a red face.
Really? Was my face that red?
Compared to usual, yeah.
But it's not what I meant.
I know.
You're not the kind to fall in love.
Apparently, it's state-of-the-art.
It works in five seconds.
Huh.
I hope you don't have a fever.
Yeah.
But what if I don't have a fever?
If it isn't a fever...
What is it?
Normal temperature.
I guess I have a slight fever.
Seriously?
You should go home.
We're starting practice!
I gotta get to club.
O-Okay.
Take care.
Thanks.
If it isn't a fever, what is it?
Next episode: Bruised-Up Angel.
Bruised-Up Angel