The Third Dish
Five
And first place goes to
Yukihira Soma's Chinese Cuisine Stall!
Damn, Kuga. You lost!
I gotta do something.
Food Wars
The Third Plate
The Darkening Dinner Table
We lost?!
Yukihira-chin...
~ Central Area ~
1st Place: Yukihira Soma
2nd Place: Kuga Restaurant
Damn it.
I was so close.
Kuga!
You lost in sales, Kuga?
Crap!
Rindo-senpai!
The Second Seat...
You're hopeless, huh, Kuga?
Aren't you, Kuga?
Shut up!
You didn't even set up a booth and
just walked around stuffing your face!
So what?
Sampling all the food is
one way to participate.
Besides, it's because you
were cooped up in your booth
that you lost to an underclassman, isn't it?
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
Kuga-senpai's outgunned.
Shut up!
I feel like I'm watching siblings.
But sure, he got me.
I guess everything went according
to Yukihira-chin's plan.
We should do a Shokugeki soon—
What are you talking about?
There's one more day left in the
Moon Festival, right?
Huh?
If I don't beat you in total
sales over the five-day period,
I haven't won.
The fight isn't over!
The 92nd
Moon Festival
Moon Festival   Final Day
You're putting up a good fight,
Yukihira Soma.
But at that pace,
it doesn't look like you can
win in total sales, does it?
You got pretty close, though!
Well, the way I imagined it was
Day 1
I'd somehow manage to keep up
with him until the third day,
Day 2
Day 3
Day 4
crush him on the fourth day,
and win in total sales on the fifth day.
You're pretty damned optimistic.
I was sure I had a chance,
and I didn't intend to lose to
him in the restaurant business,
so I'm pretty disappointed.
You're a pretty honest guy!
Central Area Total Sales Rankings
2nd Place: Yukihira Soma's Chinese Cuisine Stall
1st Place: Chinese Cuisine RS Kuga Restaurant
Main Avenue Area Total Sales Rankings
1st Place: Pop-Up Trattoria Aldini
2nd Place: Don RS
Main Avenue Area Total Sales Rankings
3rd Place: Shiomi Research Group
This is even better than last year's!
Anyway, I gotta say,
I almost burst out laughing at the
Momiji Meet-and-Greet earlier.
I didn't think I'd ever hear anyone else
say the same thing you did back then.
I want to join the Elite Ten right now.
Would anyone be willing to accept
a Shokugeki challenge from me?
Of course not!
1 Year Ago
Um...
I don't need to hear any boring talk
about getting to know each
other better and stuff.
Would anyone be willing to accept
a Shokugeki challenge from me?
What the hell?
As if an Elite Ten member would be that easy—
Sure.
Can we do one today, right now?
That is, if I'm acceptable.
Tsukasa       Kuga
We second-years are super busy trying
to beat the guys up top too, you know?
1 Month Ago
Tsukasa-san, you were number one
in sales for five days straight in the
Central Area last year, weren't you?
Will you promise me that if I manage
to pull off the same thing this year,
you'll accept another
Shokugeki challenge from me?
In the end, Kuga didn't get his wish.
Yukihira Soma didn't win
in total sales, either.
This is what you call
a war with no victor.
Each side looks really disappointed, too.
Shut up!
Well, Yukihira-chin might continue to grow.
You're a pretty honest guy too, Kuga.
No way!
I like Yukihira Soma, too.
We almost used up the ingredients.
We had pretty good sales on the
final day, too. We came close.
Hey, Yukihira Soma.
I reserved a table for you tonight.
Huh?
What table?
It'll be in the Yamanote Area.
You're coming, right?
Huh?
Where'd Mimasaka Subaru go?
He left early because he had to undo
a more elaborate lock than usual.
I bet it'll take him a long time
until he can ride his bike.
Okay, then it'll be you and Tadokoro-chan.
Once you're done closing up shop,
let's go together to Tsukasa Eishi's booth.
Aren't you curious what kind of
food the current First Seat makes?
Let's head on over to the Yamanote Area!
Wow!
What's all this?!
It's the Yamanote Area, after all.
It's a completely different
world from the other areas.
Yeah.
Around this time, most of the booths
in the Central Area would be closing up,
but all the booths here
are still going strong.
The customer base is different.
Most of them will be spending the night
on campus or at the Totsuki Resort.
That means a lot of places start
serving dinner courses around now.
I-It's really expensive, right?
Don't worry, Tadokoro-chan.
Tsukasa's place will be on me.
Come to think of it, most
of the Elite Ten, like Nakiri
and Isshiki-senpai, chose this area, right?
Yamanote Area Total Sales Rankings
1st Place: 4th Seat, Akanegakubo Momo
2nd Place: 10th Seat, Nakiri Erina
Yamanote Area Total Sales Rankings
3rd Place: 3rd Seat, Megishima Tosuke
5th Place: 6th Seat, Kinokuni Nene
Yamanote Area Total Sales Rankings
6th Place: 5th Seat, Saito Somei
7th Place: 7th Seat, Isshiki Satoshi
So the sales are going well?
Good.
Transfer my production
fees into the designated account.
9th Seat, Eizan Etsuya
Behind the Scenes
What?!
Eizan-senpai's been managing twenty booths?!
Yeah.
He made a killing.
It's unbelievable that a
student can pull that off.
And what have you been up to, Rindo-senpai?
Hm?
Me?
Huh?!
What?!
2nd Seat Kobayashi Rindo
Sampling
You visited all 120 booths in five days?!
Tsukasa's booth is the last one!
I worked really hard!
I'm not sure that's something you
can manage by working hard.
Man, the Elite Ten's full of monsters.
What are you guys doing?
I'm gonna leave you guys behind!
Yamanote Area Total Sales Rankings
4th Place: 1st Seat, Tsukasa Eishi
Welcome, Kobayashi-sama.
Today's menu is a nine-course meal
Symphony of Fall Ingredients
titled "A Symphony of Fall Ingredients."
This way, please.
It's like watching a stage.
Tsukasa-senpai's in his own world.
There are only three tables?
Tsukasa's handling all
the cooking by himself.
The other staff only serve customers.
So you need to reduce the table
count to make the setup work.
He's handling a nine-course
meal all by himself?!
He must have a lot of confidence
if he's taking on so much work.
Well, the real reason is more like this.
How can I even think of letting someone
else handle finishing my dishes?
The horror!
Once I start worrying about whether they'll
mess up, I can't even cook anymore.
Oh...
Go ahead and take this.
Please take care not to
disturb the plating!
Please carry the dish
with the utmost caution.
I-I will...
Huh?
This is sakura shrimp, isn't it?
Isn't it considered one of the
quintessential spring ingredients?
I thought this was supposed
to be about fall ingredients.
Trust Tsukasa to pull this off!
Sakura shrimp are stereotyped
as a spring ingredient,
but by fall they've grown larger
and developed a more intense shrimp flavor.
So he leveraged that with full knowledge
of this ingredient's properties.
Wow.
Each dish elicits images of the ingredients
that are even more vibrant
than if the ingredients were alive!
And the courses are structured
so that after an acidic dish,
a faintly sweet dish is served.
He's varying the feel of each dish
to prevent each one losing impact
in a brilliant balancing act!
While altering the dish's temperature
or seasoning profile
to change things up,
overall cohesion is maintained.
It's a completely different
playing field of difficulty
than preparing a standalone dish.
You're out of my league, First Seat!
Yukihira Soma...
And Tadokoro-san. Rindo, too.
Is the room cold?
Are you okay?
Let me know if the heat's up too high, too!
Are your seats comfortable?
Is the lighting too dim?
Listen, if you're in the customers'
faces too much with your concerns,
you're going to make them uncomfortable.
What?!
Right, Tadokoro-chan?
Um...
Er, yes.
A little bit.
Oh, no!
Then what am I supposed to do?!
That's why I always say you should
just have more confidence.
As usual, you have a keen eye
for quality ingredients.
It's impressive.
But if you ask me,
I'd like to try a dish that featured
more of your passion for food.
No, I don't need to put myself in my cooking.
What?
My work involves erasing all evidence
of my involvement in the dish.
I focus solely on the
quality of the ingredients
and enhancing them.
But paradoxically, that work involves
expressing myself in the dish.
That defines my cooking.
Well, please enjoy.
Over time, the gourmands
began describing Tsukasa
as someone who kneels before all ingredients
and dedicates himself and his pride to them—
Der Weiße Ritter der Tafel.
The White Knight
of the Table
Doesn't that sound cool?
When I first saw the nickname in a magazine,
I just rolled around laughing.
Tadokoro, did you notice something?
Huh?
Even though he acts so nervous,
he never asked us how we found his food.
He has absolute confidence and humility
when it comes to the handling of ingredients.
He's different from any chef I've ever met.
This is the current First Seat.
Erina-sama...
The Moon Festival is soon coming to a close.
Yes.
He's not coming today, either.
Um, Saiba-sama.
I want to become a respectable chef like you.
Will you try my cooking some day?
Hmm...
All right, I'll accept your offer
when you become a good chef.
I'll look forward to the day
I get to taste your creations.
It's all for the day when he finally comes.
All the guests with reservations
have already arrived.
I'll go take a look.
It can't be...
Excuse me, sir.
This establishment is by reservation only.
Hisako?
It's been a while, Erina.
Father...
That was really amazing food.
It was overwhelming for me.
Who knew a world like that
existed in the culinary scene?
Soma-kun?
All the better!
I shouldn't underestimate the Yamanote Area!
He's all fired up.
I wanna take a look around some more!
But we don't have any
pine tickets or anything.
Right, but there's Nakiri's booth.
Huh? But—
It'll be fine. On the first
day of the festival...
Take a black pepper bun!
Don't be shy.
I said I don't want any!
It's a good thing she owes me one.
I think you just forced it on her.
E-Excuse me.
This is very improper!
Erina, your cooking is
not for such a subpar lot!
You need to be more selective
when it comes to your clientele.
You are degrading yourself.
Hey, boy.
Do you say that knowing who we are?
Well, do you?!
Kita Osaji
Kita Gastronomy Club
Sponsor
Ando Shingo
Food Culture Writer
I remember him.
Could he be Nakiri's...
It can't be!
You were exiled from Totsuki!
Indeed, I am Nakiri Azami,
Nakiri Erina's father.
Erina-sama's father... Nakiri Azami.
I've seen his image once before,
when I was at the academy's library.
Hisako, you must not ask any questions
about Erina-sama's father to anyone.
Do you understand?
His very existence has been
erased from the Nakiri family.
What is it about this man that
has Erina-sama in such a state?
How is it that you're acting so high
and mighty when you've been exiled?
We are official business
partners of Totsuki Academy.
Good point, Sis.
So any insults toward us
would be insults toward Totsuki itself.
I have come back to correct
Totsuki's course.
What did you say?
Of all those who claim to
be knowledgeable about food,
I wonder how many actually
understand true taste.
Common to all fine art is that at its highest,
its true value can only be understood
by those who possess class and taste,
and who have received proper educations.
True gourmet dining is similar.
Its value should be shared
with only a select few.
That is what deserves to be called food.
Everything else is not food.
It is animal feed.
Not that I expect that to be understood
by those who mistakenly believe
it's gourmet dining as long as high-quality
ingredients are being used.
Why, you little—
Thank you for sharing your
most valuable opinion,
but whatever you say carries no weight here.
That's right!
You have no jurisdiction
over Totsuki's affairs!
The appropriate lineage indeed exists here.
And the education, as well.
Now, Erina.
A decade has passed since
I first taught you how to cook.
I want to see how far you
have honed your craft.
A-As I've said, we do not serve walk-ins.
I see there's a table available.
That seat's for—
The menu, if you please.
Your father is hungry.
I want to eat something soon.
Erina-sama!
Y-Y...
Hey, Nakiri.
Is there a table available?
Yukihira-kun?
Hey, hey.
Sorry, can we somehow eat your cooking,
even if we're walk-ins?
Here, I'll give you one
more black pepper bun.
Huh?
I feel a lot of tension in
this room for some reason.
Oh, excuse me.
You seem to be just about to eat, too.
If it's all right, maybe
we can share a table?
Erina, you need to be selective
when it comes to who your friends are.
Yukihira Soma!
I have lost interest.
Arato-san, who was he?
He is Erina-sama's father.
Huh?!
What's with that black-suited guy?
He should at least eat before he goes.
Nakiri?
Are you shivering?
I was just about to pay you a visit.
This reception is a great honor.
You look well, Father.
Begone!
You have no right to set foot in this place.
I told you that I forbid you from
ever claiming the Nakiri name.
I am the one who cultivated the God Tongue
Erina was born with into its current form.
You may exile me,
but my lineage and education
cannot be extinguished.
My greatest mistake was to allow you
to take care of Erina back then.
The mistake is not yours alone.
Had I remained,
I would not have allowed Totsuki
to devolve into what it is now—
a place rife with unsightly, ordinary people.
Oh, Yukihira Soma.
There you are.
Oh, Rindo-senpai.
I saw a bunch of black cars race by,
so I ran after them,
wondering what the hell was going on.
We don't really know, either,
but it sounds like Nakiri-san's
father suddenly showed up.
Ah...
At this academy, cooking is everything!
As long as you have the skills,
anyone can climb the ladder.
That is the Totsuki tradition.
Nonsense.
Allowing subpar students
to fester here when the
mission is to create true
gourmet dining is sheer folly.
That is not up to us to decide.
The ones who decide Totsuki's future
are young chefs with might and talent!
Your solitary rant will change nothing!
The Totsuki Elite Ten Council
have authority equal to,
and perhaps above,
that of the academy's director.
Totsuki Elite Ten Council
Urgent Summons
For example, should a majority
of the Elite Ten want something,
it becomes a directive for the academy.
Yukihira Soma, which side would you pick?
Huh?
Uh, I have no idea what's going on.
Oh...
And here I thought you'd join us in a flash.
"Also"?
Wh-What's this?
A majority of the Elite Ten
agree that reform is needed.
The Council has resolved to appoint
Nakiri Azami as the academy's new director.
This measure was proposed
by six of the Elite Ten.
They support my appointment
as the academy's new director.
There's a new wave.
Riding that wave feels like
the most exciting possibility.
Kobayashi Rindo
Tsukasa
The most powerful group in Totsuki
Academy has turned traitor?!
By this time tomorrow,
everything will be finalized.
Here in the kingdom of gourmet dining,
the jewel of Japan—
Totsuki
I will be the new ruler.
Food Wars
The Third Plate
Next Episode: The Imprisoned Queen
I hope you savor the next episode!