-
Note that though we may
be apart, if I am to hear
Can I copy your homework?
No good.  What was the second verse?
Again?
that you pine for me as the Inaba
mountain pines, I shall return to you.
Chihaya is a good name.
Look, this is your card.
the red that is the Tatsuta River
The first verse for this card
begins with Chihaya Furu.
This is the card you pick
up when you hear Chihaya,
so in my mind, it's the Chihaya card.
Okay!  I can do this!
Good morning!
Huh?
Oh.
Everyone's gonna start
ignoring you tomorrow!
I don't care!
I'm gonna ignore you, too!
I mean it!
I said that I don't care!
If you stop talking to the outsider,
we'll stop ignoring you.
I don't mind.
You should stop ignoring
Wataya-kun instead.
Why do you keep taking his side?!
Why are you so mean?!
There's nothing to like about
this puny and poor bumpkin!
I-It's okay, Ayase-san.
It's okay.
There is!
Wataya-kun can beat
everyone here at karuta!
Right?
I-
I won't let anyone take
a single card from me.
I'll make you eat those words!
Let's have a showdown at the
upcoming karuta tournament!
If anyone takes a card from you,
we're ignoring you until you graduate!
Yeah!
It was a reckless bet,
but it felt so right.
Because I didn't have anything
where I could claim
that no one else could ever beat me!
Chihaya Furu
Verse 2
The Red
That Is
East Osato
Elementary School
Karuta Tournament
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms.
Hey, why isn't anyone moving?
This is just the opening poem.
Opening poem?
The contest begins with the reading
of a poem that isn't one of the Hundred.
Then the match starts.
That's what the handout said.
Oh...
Kakinomoto no Hitomaro
The tail feathers of the
copper pheasant are long,
Uh...
There it is!
Yeah!
You got this, Taichi!
Nice one, Taichi!
Too easy.
You can win this!
Keep it up!
long as the nights I spend alone.
Next will be the first round
matches for the second group.
Mashima Taichi | Tanno Shouta | Umehara Asuka
Will the contestants please
step onto the tatami?
You were awesome, Taichi!
Piece of cake.
Your next match should be just as easy!
I know, right?
Wouldn't it be lame if he
lost in the first round?
You'll understand once
you've seen him play.
Like a boatsman...
Wow.
What was that?
Hey, did you see Wataya's match?!
Yeah, that was crazy.
Does Taichi have a chance?
He'll be fine.
He can do anything.
Besides, his mom will be
on his case if he loses.
Mashima Taichi        Wataya Arata
Yeah, he'll have to do
whatever it takes to win
if he doesn't want to get in trouble.
You don't think he'll lose without
taking a single card, do you?
You're amazing, Wataya-kun!
At this rate, you'll
have a perfect victory!
But you were able to
take a card from me.
That was a fluke.
You're wrong.
Huh?
You have the instinct
of a karuta player.
The instinct of a karuta player?
Hey!
It's on me!
You should be grateful!
Taichi?
What's wrong?
It's not poisoned or anything.
Oh, that's not it...
Thank you.
Hey, Taichi!
What do you think you're doing?!
That was his own fault!
Man, what's Taichi even thinking?
Sorry, I don't have a
handkerchief on me.
You can wipe your face on here.
No, it's okay.
It's no big deal.
Uh, then...
How about here?
It's really okay.
What?
What about here?
I said it's okay.
Over here then?
I don't want to get your clothes wet.
You don't have to worry about that!
If I run really fast,
they'll dry in a flash!
Huh?  That's strange.
What's wrong?
My glasses...
Huh?
Taichi!
Have you seen Wataya-kun's glasses?
Nope.
Isn't that right?
Hmm?  Yeah.
Right.
Really...
Eyesight without glasses  0.03
Ayase-san, I'm pretty sure that Mashima
was the one who hid my glasses.
Huh?
Taichi might be selfish,
but he's not mean!
And that's not me.
We will now begin the final match!
I'll go find your glasses!
Hold on!
Do you really have to lean
that close to read them?
Are you making sure you'll
have an excuse when you lose?
J-Just so we're clear...
If I take a card from you, you lose!
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms.
A mountain stream...
That was fast!
That scared me.
What's going on?
I thought he couldn't see.
I wish...
No way!
Waves...
He memorized the initial
position of every card?!
My life means nothing after...
While some dodge...
Oh, Wataya-kun.
That's the wrong card.
I have learned to both love and hate my fellow man
I deflect your artful words
to keep my sleeves dry
Got it!
Nice job, Taichi!
Time to start your comeback!
The cards have been moved?
My fear is that you will forget
your promise to never forget me,
Where is it?
Found it!
Mashima got another card!
Way to go, Mashima!
Keep it up!
When the misty bridge of magpie
feathers comes into sight,
Awesome!
He got it!
That's it, Mashima!
Don't lose to the outsider!
Wataya's lame!
That's what you get for bragging
about being good at karuta!
Take him out, Mashima!
Get him!
Do it!
That's it!
Sensei!
Can I take Wataya-kun's place?!
Huh?
I'll take Wataya-kun's place!
What are you saying?
You shouldn't interrupt
a match, Ayase-san.
But Sensei!
Wataya-kun lost his glasses!
And um...
I'm his number one pupil!
It's true that he doesn't
have his glasses.
I don't mind.
Chihaya is obviously weaker.
Thank you!
But Chi-chan only has a third
of the poems memorized.
Is she going to be okay?
I'm going to win this
match for Wataya-kun!
No...
the night is nearly past
I'm not doing this for him.
I'm...
I'm the one who's going to defeat Taichi!
May the scarlet kadsuras
of Mount Afusaka...
I know this one!
Wh-What are you doing?!
You're not supposed to use both hands.
Huh?  What order were these in?
You're out of control.
When I was playing against Wataya-kun,
Emperor Sutoku
Swift waters parted by the jagged rocks
I was focused on jumping into action
are joined at river's end
as soon as I heard the first
word of the first verse.
In other words...
I just have to keep cycling
through the first few words
of every first verse!
It doesn't matter what the poem means!
If she reads a card
I don't recognize...
Since the dew atop the blades of grass
I bat away the cards that are
in the area Taichi is looking!
That's cheap, Chihaya!
Am I allowed to do that, Sensei?
The rules allow it.
As long as the correct card is
removed from the area of play.
This girl certainly has style.
For you, I head out to the
fields to pick spring greens
The second verse is "while snow falls upon..."
I can't lose!
Focus on Taichi's movements!
Got it!
Why is she so serious?
Is she...
Is she doing it for him?
For that loser?
Got it!
What's wrong, Taichi?!
You better not lose!
Pull it together!
They're right!
Focus!
For the...
May I find the...
Chi-chan got the card!
Only one left!
Only one left.
Huh?
No way!
I don't recognize any
of the other cards!
What do I do?
Oh!
That's how I see it.
the red that is the Tatsuta River
Chihaya is a good name.
Chihaya
Th-This is...
Impassionate gods...
This is how a karuta
player sees the world!
She did it!
Our sixth grade champion is
Ayase Chihaya-san from Class 1!
Man!  What's going on?!
Who cares if I'm not good at karuta!
That was a really fun match!
Karuta is so much fun!
But it would be a different story if
you were playing against Wataya-kun!
He's going to become a master.
That makes you the Queen, Ayase-san.
Queen?
It's the title given to the
strongest female player.
Queen...
The best player in Japan...
is the best player in the world!
I believe that you have
the talent for karuta.
Ayase Chihaya
This award certifies that you
performed admirably in the
7th East Osato Elementary
School Karuta Tournament
Hello!  Mom?
There was a karuta tournament today!
We don't have any time for that!
There's a scout at our house
right now who's interested
in your sister.
What?!  Really?!
That's amazing!
He must have seen her
in the beauty pageant.
Hurry home.
I'll have a big dinner ready.
We'll throw a party for your sister.
U-Um, there was this karuta
tournament today and I...
Geez...  Hurry up, Mom.
Chihaya?
Oh, Sis?
That's great news!
And today, I was in
a karuta tournament!
Karuta?
Boring.  And lame.
I'm gonna hang up.
How could you lose to a girl?
I was recording your matches.
Now I can't show this to your father.
I-I'm sorry...
It doesn't matter if you
can play karuta or not,
but if you're going to lose,
you're no longer allowed
to play in tournaments.
You're a good student
and a good athlete.
Focus on contests that you can win.
What?
You beat me.
Why are you so upset?
I'm not.
What's that sound?
Huh?
Didn't you hear that slam?
Oh, there it is again.
Sound?
Oh, I can hear it.
See?
How good is your hearing?
I wish I was born with
a more useful talent.
So I could be a good student
and athlete like you.
That's true.
I was born this good.
But I know that you made flashcards
for learning the Hundred Poets.
Don't tell anyone.
They'll think I'm lame.
And then I lost to you.
What's so lame about
losing in a fair fight?!
At least, that's what I think.
Though nobody's gonna praise
you for doing well at karuta.
He doesn't need his glasses...
Or cards...
He can see everything!
What are you doing all alone here?
You like playing karuta that much?
I'll go look for your glasses again!
H-Hey, Chihaya!
There are a lot of crows around here,
and one of them might have taken
the glasses since they're shiny!
I'll go check the hill
behind the school!
Ayase-san!
Ayase-san, it's okay!
It's okay!
I have to find them!
I have to find Wataya-kun's glasses!
I want to help Wataya-kun play karuta!
Ayase-san...
I...
found them in the hallway.
N-No.
I stole them.
They're not here.
Oh, sorry!
Don't tell Chihaya.
I don't want
her to hate me.
Mashima, you're...
a coward.
A Coward
A-A coward?
But...
I understand how you feel.
They're not here either!
How many crow nests are there anyway?
Chihaya!
I found my glasses!
Hey!  Where are you?!
Ayase-san...
Chihaya!
Chi—
Chihaya.
Chihaya!
Here!
That was when I knew.
I would discover many lifelong
treasures this winter.