Tsuritama Episode 9
Striking Underwater
What is this?
Amazing!
I gotta take a pic!
Me, too.
Hai, yoisho!
Haino, haino, haino.
Haino, yoishona.
Men!
The water is a weapon.
There must be no more victims.
And capture JF1 quickly.
Duck!
Get up...
Huh?
Grandma, have you seen Haru?
No.
Maybe he's still asleep.
I can't find him anywhere.
Oh? But there's a typhoon coming.
Yuki, help me close the shutters.
Yeah.
A message for the residents of Enoshima.
An unidentified organism controlling
humans is lurking in the city.
Do not drink or use water.
Unidentified organism?
Like an alien?
Seriously?
Calm yourselves. You can trust us.
You don't look trustworthy to me!
We are licensed members of
the Japanese government.
Do not touch any water until
we give you permission.
You must not drink water from the tap!
You must not wash your
buttocks in the bathroom!
You've got to be kidding.
I can't run my store without water.
Tamocchan!
Huh?
I slipped in a puddle outside.
I'm soaking.
What?
Dry!
Huh? What are you doing?
Hot! Hot! Hot!
Men, the situation is serious.
People burst into dance at the
slightest touch of water.
This is evidence that JFX's
influence is growing.
Have you still not captured JF1?
Catching him won't help.
Yamada, what do you mean?
Haru, I mean JF1, is our ally.
We should ask for his assistance.
Do you intend to protect
your friends again?
Forget about being a student.
As long as we cannot find
JFX, JF1 is our only lead.
You should come up with a plan to remove
JFX from the water instead.
Isn't that more information you
got from your little friend?
We do not believe him.
Once we find JFX, we will
commence a military strike.
That is Duck's policy.
I'm telling you,
they will only fall under JFX's
control and amplify the damage.
Duck's waterproof suits
are impenetrable.
When the typhoon gets here,
they won't stand a chance.
Order your troops to
withdraw immediately.
We should remove JFX from the
water as soon as possible.
Yamada, we did not come here to fish.
Tell me where JF1 is.
I told you, I don't know.
I see.
Whitebait curry is so delicious!
We are just like the whitebait.
Huh?
Swimming in a giant ocean of curry.
But, even a single whitebait
has its own will.
They've already come this close.
Nii-chan, you're sure about this?
Yeah. I wish we could fish
him out of the water,
but we can't do it.
This is the only way.
Actually, I'll go by myself.
You can't! We have to work together!
We have to lure him far, far away.
We have to call to each other so he
doesn't take over our minds.
If he gets the slightest hold over you,
he'll control you, and make
you part of his horde.
I know.
Koko, sorry.
What are you apologizing for?
We might not be able to go home.
I told you, I don't mind.
I ate tons of Enoshima bowls yesterday.
I'm okay.
Koko...
I thought hard about my decision, too.
I'm fine as long as I'm with you.
Nothing can scare me.
Thanks.
I wish I could've fished more.
I didn't get to say good bye.
Nii-chan, don't look back.
I know.
Let's go, Nii-chan.
Haru?
Haru, where are you?
Did he water the flowers?
Dry!
Hot! Hot! Hot!
I told you, I don't know!
He was gone when I woke up this morning.
Hiding him won't do you any good.
I told you...
Yuki, that's enough.
It's their job to suspect us.
Would anyone like
something sweet to eat?
Me.
What?! You found JF1?
You mean Haru?
Group B, continue the investigation!
Did something happen to Haru?
Group A, let's go!
Yes, sir!
Duck!
What's going on? Where did Haru go?
Yuki, did Haru tell you good bye?
Huh? No.
Then I'm sure he's still
around here somewhere.
He promised he would say
good bye before he left.
Koko, Koko.
Nii-chan, Nii-chan.
Let's go, Nii-chan.
Let's fuse!
Okay!
You will be ours!
Nii-chan, I can't go on...
Run!
No, Koko!
Residents of Enoshima have
been forbidden to use water.
Apparently, an unidentified organism
in the vicinity of Enoshima is
controlling people using water...
Yuki, will you be fine by yourself?
I'll be fine. Grandma, don't go outside.
Yes, I know.
No matter what anyone
says, Haru is Haru.
I'll definitely bring him back!
Koko, I'm sorry.
I couldn't protect you.
You should not have eaten
curry on a day like this.
I made this chai three days
ago, so it's still good.
It's all right. I am not so cruel.
Here.
Thank you for the food.
How does it taste?
It's delicious.
Keito-san, this is excellent.
Why, thank you.
Could I have some more?
Me, too.
I have plenty of other things as well.
Wait!
It's me.
Me.
Akira.
Duck!
I am sorry I have been
hiding this from you.
Then you came to Enoshima...
To observe Haru.
Observe him? Why did
you have to do that?
Because it is our job.
At first, I believed Haru
was a harmless alien.
However, I learned Haru
was connected to the
Bermuda Syndrome we have
been investigating.
Bermuda Syndrome?
The phenomenon of boats
and planes suddenly
disappearing from oceans
across the world.
These incidents have been
occurring around Enoshima.
What does that have to do with Haru?
We learned an alien life form is
responsible for the incidents.
The organism has the power to
control others through water.
Control people with water?
You don't mean...
Yes. The organism is one of Haru's kind.
That is what Haru told me.
Haru himself is not dangerous,
but he is involved in an incident
that threatens the world.
Do not associate with Haru any more.
Leave the rest to us.
He is not human, like us.
You were bound to part eventually.
I don't want to.
We had fun together!
We went fishing together.
Are you telling me to
forget all of that?
But if you associate with
Haru, you will be in danger.
I don't believe your ridiculous story.
I could never believe it!
He must be nearby.
We must be heading towards JF1's home.
We've finally got him.
Let's go!
Yes, sir!
Haru!
Yuki, wait!
Haru, you're back!
Good.
Yuki, I don't like you.
Grandma!
Yuki, I really, really, hate you!
Leave Enoshima.
Haru!
Leave!
Everyone, leave! Leave Enoshima!
Leave! Leave!
It's the alien!
Leave!
That's right! I'm an alien!
Enoshima is mine!
Leave, everyone! Enoshima is mine!
There he is! Get him!
Leave Enoshima!
Haru?
Get on the evacuation bus.
Evacuation?
This is the dragon's wrath!
We must find him an
offering! An offering!
Please, wait!
Get on the bus already!
Grandpa!
This man just touched my breast.
What do you think you're doing?
Mari-chan, I'm scared.
It's okay.
They said we'll be able to go home soon.
Did Haru do something?
I don't know what's going on.
Damn it. Where is he?
Where am I?
What?
Grandma, Grandma!
Where are we?
Oh, my.
Huh?
Aliens have invaded Enoshima.
All residents ordered to evacuate.
Aliens?
You're kidding!
Why?
I wish I could stay like this forever.
I wish I could stay like this, too.
Even if the world ends tomorrow,
I know I'll be fishing.
Haru.
What are you doing?
I thought I told you to go home.
Leave! Leave Enoshima!
Calm down, Haru.
Where did you send Yuki?
What do you think you
can do by yourself?
Shut up!
Leave, leave, leave!
Haru!
Nagoya?
What are you doing there?
I don't know, either.
Just come back.
Even if I do go back,
I can't get to Enoshima.
Don't you care what happens to Haru?
Hey, Yuki.
It's not up to us. He's an alien.
What are you talking about?
He's your friend!
I know, but... I don't understand him.
Hey, Yuki!
Miso Katsu
Pig Wrestler
Authentic miso katsu really
is delicious, isn't it?
Yuki, your food will get cold. Eat up.
Grandma, I don't understand.
Why would he do this?
I trusted him.
What is trust?
Huh?
I only believe what I
see with my own eyes.
When it happened, I saw Haru clearly.
He didn't say anything,
but he told me this.
"Keito, help me. Help me."
Grandma.
What?
There's something I've
been wanting to ask you.
What is it?
Why did you invite Haru to stay with us?
Because I love flowers.
What?
I thought you needed a flower, too.
What does that mean?
Haru seemed like a blooming flower then.
Grandma.
What?
Will you be fine by yourself?
I'm going back to Enoshima.
Really?
I can't let the flowers wilt.
No Entry
Reinforcements have arrived.
Continue using your radar to find JFX.
There is no time.
Yes, sir!
The typhoon is coming.
At this rate, everyone in the area
will fall under his control!
This doesn't look good.
What's going to happen to Enoshima?
What am I supposed to do?
Where are you?
I went to convince JF1.
Convince him? I told you,
we do not care for aliens.
Were you successful?
He escaped.
That's what you get for trusting aliens.
Please allow me to fix this blunder.
What do you mean?
I will catch JFX.
As you know, I am a skilled fisherman.
If we do not catch JFX
before the typhoon hits,
we will be in serious trouble.
I've had enough of your nonsense.
Have you forgotten, Yamada?
Duck Rule 9: eliminate dangerous
aliens immediately.
But why?
To protect Earth, of course.
You will be suspended temporarily.
I cannot do that.
Enoshima has been entrusted to me.
You say that after everything
you've already done?
This is why you are still only a child!
Playing with your little
friends suits you!
Sorry, but there are plenty of people
who could take your place.
With all due respect,
what I wish to defend
is just as large as the Earth.
High
Speed
Bus
Station
I regretted doubting
him for even a moment.
I had only one thought.
Leave Enoshima!
Breaking News
Aliens in Enoshima!?
"I want to see Haru.
Right now.
As soon as possible."
Continued in #10