Oh, right...
I'm in love with someone now.
"From Now On"
Right now, I'm in love.
I've heard that when you're in love,
the world starts to look totally different...
In my case, I haven't noticed
any significant changes.
Good morning, uglyface!
Jeez, that's the first thing
that comes out of your mouth?
Kindly cover that mouth of
yours, will you? It's unseemly!
What?
It's just... When I see
those winter uniforms,
it reminds me of when you kneed me
that first day we met,
and it gives me the chills.
Speaking of getting kneed...
...is this what you're talking about?
Ouch!
What do you think
you're doing, huh?
Your new girlfriend just
showed up in her new uniform!
How about a little praise?
Oh, that's what you want?
You're cute. Yes, you're cute.
Not good, not good!
Why am I jumping for joy
over such blatant lip service?
Oh, well, I guess I might have
changed in some small ways.
Like feeling so elated over
the most trivial things.
Hey. Ichijo and Chitoge.
Good morning.
Master Raku!
Good morning to you!
Raku Ichijo!
You bastard... how could you,
when you have Young Mistress!
Like getting even more
pissed at annoying things!
Whatever the case,
as you can see, the romance
I'd always yearned for...
...is something I'm being forced
to share with this guy.
Now then, how is this
going to turn out?
Wait! Seriously, how is
this going to turn out?
Hold up!
It's good that I know
I'm in love with this guy,
Raku and Chitoge's
NEXT STAGE
but what happens next?
If I like him, then does that mean, uh...
that I want to date him or something?
In other words, not be his fake
girlfriend, but his real girlfriend?
Mmm, that doesn't feel right somehow!
In the first place, what would
we do if we were dating?
Like... walk home
together after school...
stop for snacks on the way...
go on dates on our days off...
Hey! Isn't that the same thing
we're doing now anyway?
Then does this mean that I...
...want this guy to like me, maybe?
Ichijo!
Come hither! Come hither!
Don't call me in that creepy way!
I have a feeling that's close.
But I don't know.
Somehow that just doesn't feel right.
Wait! What am I gonna do?
Now I'm getting seriously confused!
What kind of relationship
do I want with him, exactly?
Hey, Chitoge!
What?
You got your locket back?
Yeah. Well, for what it's worth.
And I thought I should
let you three know.
Oh, man! This makes me
feel so complete!
Creepy.
I'm so glad for you.
That you got it back safe and sound.
Well, but the thing is...
All right, then, Master Raku!
Without further ado! Let's open up
that locket with this key, shall we?
Hey, hold up a second, Tachibana!
Oh, where's the harm?
Now you'll finally know
who your first love was.
Well, although it had to be me.
At last, we'll have proof that it was I
who promised you my hand in marriage.
Come, come! You two
standing there...
You're dying to find out
as well. I just know it!
Listen to me!
Don't jump the gun like that!
Um, I...
I don't think... um...
That we need to open it
just yet, you know?
Chitoge?
Well, because! See...
There's no need to rush into it, right?
It might be better to wait
till things settle down.
And besides, this is just something
that happened when we were kids, so...
What's with her?
Just the other day, she was
all fired up to get to the bottom of it.
My, my, Kirisaki.
You must really be terrified to find out
that you weren't his soulmate.
There, there, I understand.
What the...?!
That's not what I meant!
I think I kind of want to know, too...
Kosaki?
If... No matter who opens it, see...
This was something that
happened when we were kids.
So I do want to,
you know, find out...
Actually...
That's why I'm telling you,
hold up, hold up, hold up!
It's still broken, all right? This locket.
Hey, so long story short...
I got as far as extracting
the stuck key and fixing it up.
But there's something stuck
in the back of the locket,
and there's no way to open
the lock by normal means.
I could get it out
by smashing it open.
What's your call?
By the way, Shu,
about that photo book...
Well, but if it's not fixed...
An autographed limited edition!
So anyway...
Don't break it! Don't break it!
This is important to me, you know!
Anyway...
Eventually we might
find a way to open it,
so I want you to wait till then.
And if we still can't figure it out,
and you think you just
have to know the truth,
then let's bust this open
and take a look inside.
I mean, maybe that'll give us a clue.
I suppose it can't be helped.
Not having to break it
would be best, though, right?
Still, I wonder what it could be.
An object that can be placed
in something this size.
You said we would take it out together
when we were reunited, right?
Yeah.
An engagement ring, maybe?
You're all very funny.
Jeez, I got all nervous for nothing!
What are you gonna do
to make up for this letdown?
Hey, I tried to tell you
guys right away!
But... If we'd gotten the locket open,
what in the world would've happened?
If my key had opened it...
If... my key hadn't opened it...
If I just went on
having feelings for him,
and then found out later
that I wasn't his soul mate,
how would I feel, I wonder?
I-I know!
This was something
that happened when we were kids.
But I can't stop thinking about it.
Hey, what am I gonna do?
I'm starting to feel uneasy!
And I still don't even know
how I want this to turn out!
How do I want it to turn out?
Do I want things to stay
the way they are now?
Well, but unless I make a move,
he'll never realize
how I feel about him, will he?
Hey, Chitoge?
What is it?
Look, don't you think you're
acting kind of weird today?
When I saw your face,
I thought, maybe...
But are you...
just like I thought?
No way...
Don't tell me... He noticed?
How I feel about him?
I... Did my face
really give me away?
No, no, no...
Not this moron of all people,
no way would he...
Of course he's going to
say something lame.
Seriously...
why didn't you say
something sooner?
You're...
Hungry, aren't you?
I knew it!
I spend so much time with you,
I pretty much know
what makes you tick now.
You have this intense look
on your face over something,
but when you have that look,
it's usually when you're hungry.
Come to think of it, you didn't
have much for lunch, did you?
Oh, I get it.
You're on a diet, right?
You moron!
All right...
Oh, well!
I'll think about
the complicated stuff later.
Hey, treat me to ramen again!
Why should I...?
Wait, so you are hungry after all!
Never mind that!
"Please Notice"
My lips are so dry these days.
Chitogecchi, don't you wear lip gloss?
Lip gloss?
Hold on a second! I'll lend you mine.
Ta-da!
I bought this lip gloss the other day.
You know, the kind that
makes your lips all supple!
Go on, try it!
Okay!
Hey, you look totally adorable!
You really look good
with it on, Chitoge!
Y-You think so?
Yes! Yes!
You look so good, you're
making me jealous!
So cute!
Dammit! Curse you
and your model's face...
You rock anything
you wear, damn you!
Hey! Ouch, ouch!
Why you little...
S-Stop!
If you like it, you can have it.
Are you sure?
Yeah. To be honest, I didn't
know what to do with it.
And besides, you look
better in it, Chitogecchi.
It's gonna make Ichijo
go all weak at the knees, huh?
Go ahead and put it on
again tomorrow.
I-Is that right?
Will he think I look cute?
But he...
He couldn't be more dense, so...
M-Morning, darling!
Hey, morning, honey.
Hey, it's even chillier
than usual today, huh?
Wh-What did we have
for first period again today?
English, I think.
I don't think there was
any homework.
Well, he missed it
spectacularly, didn't he now?
Although I did expect as much.
C-Come to think of it,
you know winter's...
It is the season for
feeling dry, isn't it?
What's that all of a sudden?
Well, uh... I was thinking
how dry my lips get.
Lips?
Yeah, I hear you!
My lips always get chapped in winter,
and I'm like, "Ouch!"
and there's blood.
And it takes forever
to heal, you know?
What? Notice them!
Come on, I practically
shoved them in your face!
Why, you...! What are you gonna do
about this tiny courage I've mustered...
Come on! Are you trying to tell me
I'm not even a speck in your eye?
Dammit! I'm not gonna let it
end like this, you know!
Oh, good morning, Chitoge!
Huh? You're wearing
lip gloss today, Chitoge!
You look so cute!
Now that it's come to this, I'm gonna
make him notice or die trying!
But lip gloss alone isn't gonna
cut it for that oblivious fool.
Morning, bean sprout!
Yo, morn—
Hey, somehow today is, you know...
Compared to yesterday, it's a little...
The air feels a little warmer, huh?
Well? The shampoo I used this morning is
5,000 yen more expensive than my usual one!
You must've noticed
that, at least, right?
If you sniff this sweet fragrance...
You think?
I was thinking it's
colder than yesterday.
Y-Y-You miserable jerk!
D-Did you just dismiss my secret
weapon shampoo with one sneeze?
Why, you dumbass!
You're nothing but a bean sprout!
Nothing but a bean sprout!
No, wait!
Let's calm down a little!
Even girls don't always
notice lip gloss or shampoo.
No wonder that moron didn't
notice it either - it can't be helped.
I've got to be more
blatant with him.
Ta-da!
How about this?
I almost never do my nails.
Okay, cool!
I think they look pretty cute!
Something this obvious,
he's sure to notice, right?
Hey, hey! Raku!
This is the handout
I borrowed the other day.
I'll give it back to you, okay?
Now then... Comments, please?
Okay.
Ouch! Huh? Hey... ouch! Ouch!
What the hell do you
think you're doing?!
Comments, please?
No, that hurts!
What do you think you're doing?
Oh, does it?
Then maybe I'll pound
you with my fist next?
Why do you get like that?
Jeez!
I never dreamed he was
this much of an idiot!
You dummy! Dummy!
Dummy! Dummy!
Why don't you notice them?
Or is it that you do notice,
but you have no comment?
Either way, it's so frustrating!
Now that it's come to this...
Now that it's come to this!
This should do it! This should
do it! What do you say?
He's sure to notice this,
and if it's this drastic a change,
he won't be able to ignore it, will he?
Oh, wow, Chitoge!
Is that ribbon part of a makeover?
Morning.
M-My, my, darling, you're late today!
Oh, hey... morning, honey.
I kind of overslept today, see...
All that homework
yesterday, you know?
I tried to get it all done
as soon as I could,
but it was harder than I thought.
Oh, is that right?
Well, not that we have to
turn it in any time soon.
Hey!
Come on! Wh-Why
are you ignoring me?
Don't tell me you don't
even notice this?
Is that even possible?
H-Hey, you!
Isn't there anything you'd
like to say about me today?
H-How do you do?
What kind of answer is that?!
Me, too, now that you mention it.
My shoulders got all stiff
from studying yesterday.
Oh, yeah?
You hitting the books, right?
Are you sure you weren't watching
some TV show and lazing around?
Wh-Why?!
Why won't he say anything?!
Don't tell me he really
hasn't noticed it yet!
But if he has noticed, I'm sure
there'd be some kind of reaction!
Just how dense is he, anyway?
Jeez! I don't believe this!
This ribbon was my
most alluring feature!
How can I get him to notice it?
Or is it that he couldn't
care less about me?
Huh? Your lunch today,
it's not the usual Kobe beef,
but Iberico ham, huh?
Vitamins are good for
you, right? Yep, vitamins!
That's what you notice?!
For God's sake, cow or pig? I only
just found that out myself now!
Does this mean the change
in me is less important?!
Soooo annoying!
Oh, man, I'm so frustrated!
Notice it!
Notice it!!!
Excuse me, Mr. Ichijo?
Yes?
I'm going to test your
abilities as a boyfriend.
Please point out any changes
you've noticed in me recently!
This feels so futile.
Have you changed somehow?
Oh, hey, I mean, you've
totally changed, huh?
It seems to me
like you've changed.
Um...
Hey! Have you gained a little weight?
Look, you!
M-M-M-M-My bad!
I was just kidding!
Um... Did you cut your bangs?
No, I didn't!
Are you wearing mascara?
These are natural, I'll have you know!
Did you grow taller?
Who grows that fast?!
Is it your new diet...?
Want me to clock you again?
But I don't know about
any other changes.
Seriously, why did I have to go
and fall for a guy like this?
No way...
This isn't about you wearing lip
gloss for the last three days, right?
You mean you noticed that?
What? Is that the change
you're talking about?
Then... what about the shampoo?
Oh, so you did change it.
And my nails?
Well... I guess I did.
Why didn't you say anything
when you noticed?
Why should I have to
say stuff like that?
I mean, even if I did notice,
guys normally don't go around
saying, "Hey, looking good," right?
Hey!
H-Hold up, forget I just said that!
What do you mean, forget it?
Because it would be weird!
Why should I say
stuff like that to you?
It's not weird!
For a girl, whether or not you notice
that kind of thing is so crucial!
If you want to be popular with girls,
why don't you put some thought into that?
Or what is this?
Is it because you didn't
think I looked good?
Are you saying that I didn't look cute?
I wouldn't go that far, but...
Well, I suppose you were
rather cute, young lady.
In that case, it's all right.
By the way, what do you
think of this ribbon?
Ribbon?
It's not your usual one!
What? You mean
you never noticed it?