but there is only desolation
under an autumn sunset.
Swift waters parted by the jagged rocks
The Fukui Class A champion is
Murao Shinichi-kun from
the Fukui Nagumo Society.
The runner-up is Wataya Arata-kun
from the Fukui Nagumo Society.
The Nagumo Society is impressive.
They placed first and second
in the Fukui tournament,
which features over 100 Class A players.
The final match was excellent.
Players from the same
society showing no mercy.
Murao-kun managed to
outlast his opponent.
Runner-up  Wataya Arata
Congratulations.
You're strong, when you're
serious about playing.
I can't wait to see you play
in the Master match this fall.
National Karuta Tournament
Fukui Champions
Wataya Hajime  Wataya Hajime  Wataya Hajime  Wataya Hajime
Wataya-kun, Wataya-kun.
Oh, Mr. Yoshioka.
Congratulations on second place.
You came so close,
but at least you have
everyone's attention now.
Both you and Murao-kun are
considered possible favorites
for the Master match this fall.
You've begun to prepare for the
tournament this fall—
No, Mr. Yoshioka.
My current goal is the
high school championship.
There's someone I really want to play.
It's that time of year again.
June.
33rd Champion   Mizusawa High School
Time for the National High
School Karuta Championship:
Tokyo Regional.
Chihaya Furu
Verse 3
Feel
Love
Deepen
Mashima-kun!
I've missed you so much!
It's been a while, Oe-san's mother...
Ri-Rieko-san...
Yep, it's Rieko!
You're looking even more handsome!
Who is that woman?
She's all over him!
Hanano-san!
Why are you just standing there?
I'll help you get dressed,
so move to the other room.
Huh?  But I'm not playing.
What do you mean?
You're a member of the
Mizusawa Karuta Club.
All of our members wear hakama!
I've never worn a hakama before.
It's beautiful...
I'm so happy!
At first, I didn't think
this was going to work,
When you raise your arm,
you should hold your sleeve
up, so it doesn't roll back.
but now it feels like we finally
have our second female member!
Counts
as a
male
member
Group A Preliminaries
Mizusawa
Shuryukan
West High
Togu
This year, there are a total of fourteen schools,
split into four groups.
We're in Group A, with
Shuryukan and West High.
Perfect!  I can use the
data from last year.
Say, Ayase, about the order
we're going to use...
Wh-What?!
Huh?!  Fission?!  Cloning?!
Oh, sorry if my brothers are bothering you.
Hey, it's Big Bro!
In our family, we're taught
to run into pretty people.
Tr-Triplets?!
Seriously?
No, they're each a year apart.
Ages 9 - 10 - 11
We're here to cheer for Big Bro!
You look cool!
You're rockin' that kimono!
Do that one thing!
That one thing?
That's so cute!
You look just like Peko-chan!
Oh, he does!
He doesn't!
Are you going to play
in the tournament?
Of course he is.
We were Second Verse Karuta champions.
Big Bro was an ace attacker!
You're also good at
mainland karuta, right?
Y-You bet.
Your brother will dominate
with the power built
from practicing with wooden cards!
My Hero
How can he say that?
He hasn't beaten any of the
second-years in a single practice match,
so he won't get to play.
What?!  Tokyo gets to send two schools
to the national championship this year?!
If there are more than
ten schools in a region,
two get to advance...
We're so lucky!
That makes it a lot easier!
Doesn't matter if one advances
or two advance!
Hokuo Academy will win in the end!
I've been thinking that our Tsukuba
and Retro-kun are similar,
but Retro-kun is way weirder.
I can hear you!
You should apologize to Tsukuba-kun.
I can hear you guys!
Porky.
You're too nice.
Why let Eyebrows, who's stuck
in Class B even though
he tops you all in skill, be your president?
He's probably kept this
a secret from you guys,
but he entered tournaments
in Hiroshima and Kyoto,
and he's still Class B
because he couldn't win.
You're in the same boat!
I ran into you in Hiroshima,
Kyoto, everywhere I went!
Neither of us have made it to Class A!
Well, team matches are
a different animal.
We'll be winning.
That's bull!
Honestly, Hokuo doesn't scare us
now that Sudo-san's graduated!
You won't be able to say that
after seeing our ultimate weapon.
Ultimate weapon?
See you in the finals!
Last year's champions will
now return the trophy.
This was the first trophy
we worked together to win.
We fought so hard.
We were completely focused on our goal.
A year has passed.
We have to win again
and make it to Nationals.
Our next dream is to be
number one in Japan!
Group A Round 1
Mizusawa High School
Nishida Yusei
Oe Kana
Ayase Chihaya
Komachi Tsutomu
Mashima Taichi
Yeah, we want to get off
to a running start.
Let's use the order
Komano came up with.
Sounds good.
I think it's fine.
Oh, then I'll go turn this in.
Huh?  Oh, thanks.
Tsukuba-kun?
Komano Tsutomu [Removed]
Tsukuba Akihiro [Replacement]
What do you think you're doing?!
How could you change the order?!
If you've got a problem, say something!
B-But!
I came within three cards of
beating Komano-senpai once!
I've almost caught up
in terms of skill!
I'm...
Cool down.
If you can't, go home.
Is he playing soon?
Keep it down or they'll yell at you.
Let's switch up the order.
For our first match against Shuryukan,
let's switch me out
for Hanano Sumire.
Huh?
For our second match against West High,
we'll switch out Kana-chan
for Tsukuba Akihiro.
I just checked and
Shuryukan is pretty much
fielding the same lineup as last year.
Going off my data from last year,
they're strong against boys
and really weak against girls.
So it makes sense to
go with three girls.
I think you're right.
The West High team is
still mainly female.
I'm guessing that they still
favor a focused style
with vocal encouragement.
Tsukuba-kun.
Open your eyes for a moment.
L-Like this?
You don't need to lick your lips!
If you keep that look on your face the
whole match, you'll definitely win!
Your loud voice can also
be used as a weapon!
The remaining three players
will have to play every game.
Mashima, Porky, Ayase...
It's on you.
Let's go, Mizusawa High School.
for there is no one else out here
Rain takes longer...
The night breaks to day...
May I live to see...
In the sleepy...
She's so cool!
Uh...
Why are you giving me a chance?
Shh.  You're too loud.
I said a lot of rude things.
Can I go home now?
I'm only here because
you need five people
to make it to the national tournament!
Anyone could take my spot!
Sorry, everyone!
I've been in your shoes.
I was also given a chance.
There's no rush.
You'll get better very soon.
It's okay.
You have the passion and talent.
He's so cool...
Why am I playing in a match?
Nobody told me this would happen!
I just wanted to watch!
Nothing can be worse than
living a moment longer
Which card is it?  Which card is it?
Um...  Um...
Oh, found it!
I'm
glad
you
got a
card
So the flower has wilted...
I know this one!
Hehe
Our hands touched
Our hands touched!
That's Ayase-senpai's opponent...
She won by 25 cards.
A perfect score.
Thank you very much.
Damn!
She never let her opponent
touch her hand.
She wasn't belittled for being a girl.
Memorize!  Memorize!
I know all of the first verses!
Focus.  Focus...
so I can react!
Faster!
I can feel the blood flowing through
the brain cells I've neglected to use!
I'll move faster next time!
You'll start moving faster and
faster to take cards, Sumire-chan.
I hate to admit it, but she's right!
Thank you very much.
But
I
still
lost
Yes!  One victory down!
Oh, Ms. Miyauchi.
Doesn't the tennis team
have a match today?
Our tennis team will be
just as good this year.
It didn't take them long to win,
so I'll be heading over
to the karuta regional.
Ah, I see.
Oh, that's right.
New members.
Did the karuta club recruit
five new members?
Of course!
Look at the 20 applications
I have here!
Oh, that's wonderful!
You always deliver, Ms. Miyauchi.
Though 18 of them quit.
Speaking of the karuta club...
Ayase-san turned in a blank
career plan again this year.
What are we going to do about her?
Some time...
Please give her some time.
She may act like she never
thinks, but she does...
I think.
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
Victory for West High!
Yes!
Mi! Zu! Sa! Wa!
Pight!
Pight?
Honestly, Tsukuba just had to blow it.
He must be very nervous.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
It's okay.  It's okay.
My brothers are watching me.
I have to be the hero!
As friends and strangers come...
First card on the board!
Nice one, Nawano-senpai!
Let's keep it going!
Yes!
So the flower petals...
I hear the beating...
Since I could not hide...
I screwed up!
people would always ask
if I was pining for someone
Since I...
when I cannot bear
growing any weaker
than I already have.
Nothing...
I made the worst possible mistake!
When I get flustered, I forget I'm
not playing Second Verse Karuta!
He went for the card that
started the same way.
He's a total amateur.
Lucky me.
Tsukuba is up against
West High's captain.
She's the only Class A
player on their team.
I guess we're fortunate that
we're not wasting one of
our Class A players on her,
but this is tough for Tsukuba.
I embarrassed myself to
play in this match...
I was so confident...
Karuta was the one thing
I was confident about.
You're so lucky, Tsukuba-kun.
You get to play a Class A
player in an official match.
You're lucky!
Huh?
That's true.
You rarely get to play people
outside your class in tournaments.
This is a chance that only
comes in team tournaments.
That's our captain!
Way to give him a boost!
What?  He's lucky?
That's not it...
Lucky
him
I wanted to play her
She's just jealous!
How am I lucky?!
I want to win!
I want to play someone I can beat!
I can't afford to lose my confidence!
I can't afford to...
Since the dew...
It's not working!
Damn...
I was so close...
I was so close?
She's a Class A player?
Impassionate gods...
Ayase-senpai is way faster.
Nishida-senpai is way stronger.
Kitano Town Children's Center
Big Bro is here!
It's Big Akihiro!
Big Bro!  Help us with karuta!
Were they bullying you again?
Your brother's here to save the day.
It's okay.
It's okay!
This will be a cinch.
Wh-What?!
If you keep that look on your face the
whole match, you'll definitely win!
Your loud voice can also
be used as a weapon!
T-Time to take some cards!
It's on now!
I'll make you good!
There are two cards you
absolutely have to master.
"Feel love deepen" and "Feel sorrow wash"?
You need to make these cards your own.
Since your name is Tsukuba-kun.
But my name's Akihiro,
so I was really good at
the eight cards with
second verses that started like my name.
You always have something
to complain about!
There are sixteen cards with first
verses that start like your name.
Few people can say that they
specialize in the "The" cards.
You're really lucky.
Start with the two "Feel" cards.
Then you have the sixteen "The" cards.
It'll take time, but you
can master those cards.
Feel love deepen...
Start with the "Feel" cards!
widening into a river as it
descends Mount Tsukuba.
The emotions experienced after a long-awaited reunion
banish any lingering memories of the past
Then I move onto the "The" cards!
The emotions experienced...
Ah, that won't work!
There are too many "The"
cards all over the place!
My brothers are watching me.
But...
My teammates are with me!
She's so good!
Another 25-card perfect game!
Her opponent is clearly weaker,
but Chihaya-chan has been flawless!
This is impressive.
Mashima, Porky, Ayase...
It's on you.
One win for Mizusawa!
Yeah!
Y-Yeah!
We wouldn't be this strong,
if the first-years weren't here.
Two wins for Mizusawa!
Not President Mashima...
Okay!  Three wins for Mizusawa!
Not Porky...
They're so dependable
that it makes me sick!
Sorry...
I can't be the hero.
I'm acting like a loser,
but right now, I just want one card!
One card!
Tsukuba X - O Nawano
(13 card differential)
Thank you very much.
Komano X - O Suda
(2 card differential)
Thank you very much.
You were so close, Desktomu-kun!
I almost caught up.
You did a good job against
a Class B opponent.
You were so cool, lady!
You're pretty and strong!
Really strong!
Awesome!  Awesome!
Th-Thank you...
But Big Bro will catch up in no time!
We only played with
wooden cards at home,
but we'll start practicing
with the paper cards you use!
Big Bro will get better then!
Big Bro's super awesome!
Then you should all come to the
Shiranami Society next week!
Shiranami Society?
Hey!  That's no fair!
I got us some new members, Dr. Harada!
It's been a long time.
Yes, that's right.
I'm looking forward to it, Mr. Ise.
I'll get you registered.
I can't wait to watch the
tournament this year.
You'll probably dominate the
individual bracket though.
I still have much to improve.
If you need a practice partner,
drop by the Myojo Society.
Thank you very much.
Oh, there's one more thing
to look forward to.
The grandson of Eternal Master
Wataya is coming from Fukui
to participate in the individual bracket.
Everybody's been talking about it.
How many years has it been since
he's played in an official match?
Even I can't wait.
Arata?