Two months passed since we started
our second year of high school.
Now that we had become
accustomed to our new classes
and to having juniors,
the biggest event of the year was upon us...
No, one of the biggest events in high school:
The school field trip.
Here, Big Brother.
Thanks, Kuzuha.
Well, I'm going to bed.
'Night.
And to me, that day is slightly
more significant than most.
SCHOOL FIELD TRIP
Rikka, are you packed?
I'm opening the door.
Ssh, they'll hear us.
It appears the dark followers
have not spotted us.
But be careful.
Any loud noises will annoy the neighbors.
Like you can talk!
What are you doing with these on, anyway?
I have just returned from my mission
to summon the Dark Flame Dragon.
Wearing these fortifies
the Wicked Lord Shingan.
These are equipped with
the power to see isolated worlds.
And they look cool.
Just get packed.
So cool!
Just get packed and take your bath!
Travelling to the Island of
Tsukushi... of Hesitation
I can see you are fully prepared
for a journey to the dark world.
That's a lot of luggage.
This is actually less
than before. At first...
So, that's why this little bag smells so bad.
What? What do you mean by that?
Because it's "carrion" luggage.
That's funny.
How long are you going to keep doing that?
No go?
Gather round, everyone!
Let's get going.
Master, while you set out
for the battleground...
...I, Dekomori, will keep watch over
our society like a deity of protection!
I trust you.
Time to go!
Dekomori!
Master!
See you later!
You're dressed sharp.
Of course I am. This is
the school field trip.
Destiny could be waiting anywhere.
I will now announce the recreation
programs for each group.
You are prohibited from
going to the other cars,
except to use the restroom.
You are also prohibited
from using your cell phones.
The speed of sound is impressive!
We're not going quite that fast.
However, Wicked Lord Shingan sees all.
This is not a problem.
She's not the girl who went
to her family home last year.
You guys sure do get along well.
Don't take our photo!
Why not? You're going out, aren't you?
It's not like we're...
I won't go showing it to the other guys.
I'll print it out for you later.
Okay, I am giving you one hour of free time.
Meet back here at 2 o'clock!
This place is amazing.
The palace where the imprisoned
dragon's soul sleeps...
banished by the patron saint of darkness.
Known as the Dark Dragonius Saint Palace!
Don't name it!
I will now infiltrate under
the dark followers' noses.
You too!
We must always anticipate the
dark followers' attack.
You brought that all this way just for that?
Full preparation at all times is key.
You must really like those.
I'm blinded!
No duh!
Takanashi!
What is that?
Combat equipment.
As usual.
Okay, I'll take a commemorative photo
of you and Togashi.
Huh?
Don't be shy. This is a school field trip.
Move closer together.
Don't you want to make some
memories with your boyfriend?
B...
Boyfriend?
There you are, Togashi.
You have a copy
of the group schedule, right?
S-sure!
Right here.
Thanks.
I'm bored.
This is tedious.
I must do something before
I lose mental capacity and die.
Can that be a messenger sent by my master?
I'm over here! Dekomori is over here!
Over here!
I thought I was gonna die.
But Mr. Mushroom is such a fungi.
You seem especially enthused about
napping ever since the
napping club competition.
Wake up. Wake up now.
Deko?
You have returned from the dream world!
What is it?
This region is stagnant territory!
We need to escape and
advance to another area!
Advance to where?
Actually...
Oh, I know where to go.
Yayoi Settlement
Museum
TODAY'S ACTIVITIES
Magatama making
Clay flute making
Historic ruins containing
the powers of darkness!
Isn't it amazing?
People lived in this area
from the Jomon period onward,
and there used to be a sea nearby.
I am fulfilled.
Takanashi, what are you doing?
Conversing with the souls
who once lived here so long ago.
Wow, that's amazing. Nibu?
I can hear them...
...the whispers of the Light Beings.
What is your name?
What?
Himiko?
Nibu?
Uh, it's nothing! Nothing at all!
Togashi!
Takanashi is here with us!
Uh, right.
Come on over, don't be
shy. Sorry about before!
I won't pester you anymore.
Right, Takanashi?
Huh? Takanashi?
This seems tricky.
You two are going out,
so there's no need
to be so embarrassed, is there?
I am bound to Yuta by a contract.
But it's a Lover's Contract, isn't it?
Well...
Evil Eye Dark Curve!
Don't misbehave in a place like this!
Rikka!
Nibutani, what happened?
Each room's group must bathe
according to the schedule.
So, you don't want her to get
worked up about romance?
Kind of.
Here are the kimonos.
But you're going out.
I'll wear my sweats.
I forgot my shampoo!
Whenever she starts to think hard
about it, she gets confused.
This place has shampoo.
It won't work.
The idea of romance doesn't
fit into her chunibyo delusion.
Then what are you gonna do?
Can you take care of her for now?
What?
Are you sure? Don't you want to be with her?
I do, but so many people are watching us.
Rikka can't handle that kind of thing.
You're actually kind of nice, you know?
What?
I'm nice?
Exactly! What in the world
do those two want from me?!
Wait, I'll do that.
It's okay 'cause I just put these on.
All-Porpoise
My "all-porpoise" socks.
Huh?
Never mind that!
We need to discuss the Dark
Flame Master and my master!
You're in a bad mood, Deko.
Of course I am! I have
always showed restraint
whether they want to be together or not.
Do they want to be together or don't they?
I know what you mean.
They're like that at home.
Huh?
They're always so secretive.
It makes me feel like the villain.
I know! I know what you mean!
Little sister to Dark Flame Master
and Ghelzonianses!
Call me Kuzuha.
You really love your big brother, don't you?
Not really.
I wonder how they're all doing?
What's this?
I forget.
All
Porpoise
Hey, are you really going in there?
He's right. You should call it off.
Your opinion doesn't count
because you have Takanashi.
It's Isshiki! Isshiki's been captured!
Isshiki!
You're wrong! You've got it all wrong!
WOMEN'S
BATH
I honestly mixed up the men's
and the women's baths!
Isshiki...
Which means we use Route B?
We'd better hurry.
The girls in our class
will be done bathing soon.
Nibutani!
Crush?
Don't you have a crush?
All the boys like you.
She's right. Aren't you
going out with anyone?
What? Uh, not anyone in particular.
Really? Is that true?
Then what about last year?
You had a boyfriend last year, didn't you?
Why the interrogation?
After all, just look.
You've been good friends with Togashi
since you started high school.
Huh?
Yeah. We thought maybe
you guys went out at some point.
And then maybe you were in
a love triangle with Takanashi.
What?!
I wouldn't be so sure.
From my personal viewpoint
as the Love Meister...
...you've never been in a relationship,
never mind a love triangle.
Huh?
More girls are like that than you'd think.
They look like seasoned veterans
when they're only amateurs.
No way!
You have some experience, don't you?
Y-yes. In a way...
...you could say that.
Really? When was this?
In middle school, I think.
Huh? But when you were in middle school...
didn't you go around saying
you were 1,200 years old?
Everyone was talking about it.
They say you still do it on the net.
What do you mean?
We're too late.
Nibutani!
THE WHISPERS OF
MORI SUMMER
LOVE - LIFE - FORTUNE
See?
Horoscopes for the
12 Constellations
COMMENTS:
Mori Summer helped me with my love life.
I am happily dating my crush.
Mori Summer's advice did the trick!
That junior!
I see that look. So, it is you.
N-n-no, it isn't me!
I have nothing to do with it!
Why would I carry on like a Middle Two kid
now that I'm in high school?
C'mon, we have to be up early. Time to sleep!
And then a will 'o' the wisp
crept up beside the girl...
Stop it!
It's not that scary.
Yeah, forget the ghost stories.
I'd rather hear how far
you've gotten, Togashi.
How far I've gotten with what?
You know. With Takanashi.
Like we really need to ask.
You started going out during
last year's Culture Festival.
How do you know that?
Yuta!
Rikka!
Stop that!
A month later comes the kiss.
And then a few dates.
And then you spend Christmas Eve together.
Die, fruitful offline life!
Shatter into a billion pieces!
You're wrong! Don't reshape my love life!
Then when did you do it?
Uh, no. Like I'm saying.
W-we haven't yet.
What?!
Yeah, right.
That's impossible. You're a healthy,
hot-blooded high school student!
Suffer in writhing agony and vanish,
fruitful offline life!
It's true!
I gotta wonder why you feel
the need to lie at a time like this.
I'm telling you, I'm not lying!
All right, then bring Takanashi here.
How could I... do that?
The teachers are patrolling the halls.
There! I just saw a strange
light in the window!
What?
I thought I just heard a woman moaning.
S-stop that.
Rest in peace, rest in peace, rest in peace.
I'll go have a look.
What're you doing? What if someone saw you?!
It's fine. My dark exorcizing
defensive application...
renders me visually
unrecognizable to commoners.
See anything?
Uh, nothing worth mentioning.
So I was seeing things.
Master, why don't you answer?
She'll be asleep by now.
Maybe she's with Dark Flame Master
at this moment.
Don't worry. I doubt they're up to anything.
Hey, isn't that a girl's bag?
Still awake in there?
Oh, crap! It's the teacher!
Anyone still awake?
Sensei, can you please come here?
What is it?
I'm sorry, but I hear strange voices
from over there.
Show me.
We'd better go while you can.
I'm sure I heard strange voices.
Really? There's nobody there.
I think they came from further inside.
Go back to your room. You could be
sent home early if you're spotted.
Yeah.
Yuta.
What is it?
There was a barrier between us.
I think it was the dark followers' doing.
A barrier that prevented me
from approaching you.
It was a form of psychological attack.
But I think I'm all right now.
I know.
I wasn't running from you.
And I wasn't avoiding you.
I get it.
You're trying to say you're too shy.
I am too.
When we have free time tomorrow,
do you wanna look around together?
Just the two of us.
Yeah.
Later, Rikka.
Yuta!
Is it love, or is it something greater?
I don't know what it is yet,
but I had the feeling...
...that slowly but surely...
...that something was gradually
being set in motion.
I can't sleep.
Rikka and I greeted the new day.
Hey, where's Takanashi?
She said she'll be doing her own thing.
What're you doing?
Lend me your power. We need to contain it.
What, that?
Yes.
Begin!
Our day alone together begins!
To be
Continued