--Goddamned corpse!
--Stay down, damn it!
Why are you getting in my way?
--We're going after him!
--You stay here!
No, I'll take him down!
Just stay put!
You idiot! Hide!
Kariaena Island. The city of San-Teresa.
This city is the "front door" separating
the Earth and a strange other world.
A mixture of different races and
diverse cultures, haves and have-nots...
But in the shadows of all this
chaos lurked countless crimes.
The San-Teresa Metropolitan Police maintained
a special unit to deal with these crimes.
I can't believe you just sliced him
open alone, Miss Don Quixote.
It didn't occur to you to arrest him
so we could question him?
Say something!
He was being controlled via mildey.
Even if we did capture him,
we wouldn't have been able to learn anything.
Mildey?
Magic. Magic to control the dead, in this case.
He was devoured by evil latena
and turned into a living corpse.
So you're trying to talk your way out
of this by blaming some weird spell?
What?
You're interfering with the investigation.
Let me guess. Somebody doesn't want
us finding out the deal with this fairy,
and they sent you to get in the way.
What are you implying?
What I just said.
I don't know how much they're
paying you to do it, though.
This is your first and last warning,
Kae Imatoeba.
Never insult me in that manner again.
Next time, I'll kill you. I'm not joking.
Oh, yeah?
Did the words of a lowly Earthling
like me tick you off that bad?
Silence!
Right.
Hey, I have a question.
What?
You're serious about arresting
whoever's behind this
and getting back that fairy, right?
Of course.
Me too, actually.
So why are we yelling and
pointing weapons at each other?
Well, whatever.
Anyway, I hear you when you say
he was being controlled.
Another guy like him almost killed me yesterday.
What? Why didn't you say so earlier?
Don't ask me. I'm not your mom.
Kei, want to guess what I found?
I read the report, Cecil.
I want to know what they've got in common.
That's easy.
The man here, who killed your partner,
and this man here, who almost killed you.
Both of them were dead before they died.
I don't understand...
I'm talking about their blood oxygen
and lactic acid levels.
Both of them should've been dead
after you shot them,
but for some reason kept moving,
and then only after that did they get
the numbers a dead person should have.
That's what they have in common.
So they're like zombies?
I don't know. I'm not sure what
the definition of "zombie" is.
I didn't see any signs of major drug use.
They both seemed to drink and smoke,
but both were in practically perfect health.
I don't know about that.
Um, who is this?
Tilarna Exedilica.
A knight of Mirvor.
Oh, a guest from the other world.
What's she doing?
Looking for magic, she says.
Kei.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm completely sane.
He's the same.
He smells of evil latena.
What's latena?
Latena is latena.
Some kind of magical energy source or something.
I don't get it either.
The latena of a fairy
warped through some horrible method.
They ingested it on a regular basis,
and it turned them into dead men.
Are you talking about a drug? From Semani?
Fairy dust?
These guys were regular users, right?
If you call the dead "regular users," then yes.
The Marzaney Sect has spells
that can control the dead.
Well, that would explain why
it didn't show up on my tests.
That drug is one big mystery to us.
All we know is that it's made from fairies.
To do this to a noble fairy...
What terrible people.
So, can you use magic?
It's called mildey. And I can use a little.
Then follow the trail of this latena stuff.
Like a police dog.
You seem to lack imagination, Kae Imatoeba.
Mildey is powerful, but not all-powerful.
Pound that fact into
what little brains you have.
Good advice from a noble but useless woman.
So um, are you two not friends, then?
If it looks that way, that's probably the case.
Is there anyone out there
who does like this man?
I see.
Kei.
You okay?
I think so.
Call me anytime.
Sure, thanks.
What was that conversation?
Don't worry about it.
No, I'm curious. Tell me.
She's my ex.
What's an ex?
Shut up.
The problem is when the attack occurred.
Either they were watching Alvarez
or there was a leak.
No way to tell.
There's any number of possibilities.
Oh, but you don't have to worry
about our brave knight here.
She doesn't even know how to make a phone call.
I do too. I read it in a book.
Really? Wow, you're so smart!
Sorry.
Anyway, so yeah.
I'll be keeping my reports to a minimum.
Sounds good. Be careful.
Roger.
What do we do now?
We do this the boring way.
But well, it's late. We'll start tomorrow.
I see.
Where are you staying? I'll take you there.
This is my phone number.
I don't want any trouble, so just go
straight to your room and go to sleep.
Don't worry. I'm not a child.
You look like one. That's why I'm worried.
I'm 26, you know!
That's 18 in Earth years. Bye.
Wait!
It's so damn cold tonight...
Hello?
I got kicked out of the hotel.
They say you can't bring weapons into the hotel.
They demanded to hold on to my sword.
Then let them hold on to it.
I can't do that!
To a knight, a sword is every bit
as valuable as their life!
Then sleep on the ground somewhere.
Not my problem.
Wai--
Damn it all!
The sleeping quarters at
the police station are always full.
And a lot of people there don't like Semanians.
Sleep at my place.
At your place?
Don't worry. I'm not going to do anything.
Of course not.
But I don't want any rumors or scandal
or things that could hurt my honor...
Then just don't tell anybody!
Shut up, already.
Come in. You can get your stuff later.
Why are you putting that on?
I have a cat allergy.
Kae!
Kei?
Oh, I meant the cat.
It's the word for it in my language.
I thought you were talking about me.
What's the name of that kae--no, cat?
Kuroi.
What's an allergy?
I have trouble breathing when I'm around him.
It's a genetic thing.
Then why are you keeping a cat?
You're full of questions, aren't you?
Give me a break.
About three months ago, I think it was,
a drug dealer that I was chasing
hit her when she was a stray.
And?
I caught the guy, and she survived.
But nobody else in the department wanted her.
So I'm keeping her temporarily.
Even though you've got a cat allergy?
What else can I do?
It was partially my fault.
I'm looking for someone to take her,
but with no luck.
What?
No...
Is it that funny?
I'm sorry, Kei, but this is...
"You're a good kitty, Kuroi."
Kae Imatoeba, you're more
of a softie than you look.
That's not it.
If I threw an injured cat out in the cold,
I'd have trouble sleeping at night.
I'm just doing it for myself in the end.
So I'm the same as the cat, huh?
If you don't like it, back to the park with you.
No, I'll stay here. I like it.
My place?
No, this kae.
Not you, I mean.
Okay, find a place to sleep.
Don't let Kuroi in the bedroom.
Kei Matoba.
I actually was feeling a bit lonely.
"Thank you."
You're welcome.
Um, "Good night" is...
"Good night."
That's right.
She was making fun of my name
the whole time?
Did I keep you waiting, Mr. Kareem?
Let's not waste time, Mr. Elbaji.
Let's do the deal.
Okay, Mr. Terrorist.
Cash payment is great, huh?
Pay us the rest when you get the goods.
You seem to be doing well.
Yeah, I guess.
Thanks to those poor fairies,
we can all live the good life.
That car, for instance. It's 300,000 dollars.
These sneakers are 3,000 dollars.
But I can have a good time
with a girl for three dollars.
You know why that is?
No.
Because I'm hot!
Earth girls are all about looks.
They're easy.
I'm only interested in the product.
Oh, sorry. Sorry.
Hey, Zelada!
You called, my lord?
Mr. Kareem, allow me to
introduce you to Zelada the Sage.
He's this wizard you were telling me about?
That's right. The greatest in the world
when it comes to controlling the dead.
Your words honor me, sir.
I simply do what I can
for the sake of my master.
He said "the dead."
Does he mean users of fairy dust?
Indeed.
My magics have not the slightest
effect on those who are pure of soul.
And that's where this comes in!
That's the fairy bomb?
A prototype, but yeah.
I'm about to test it right now.
What do you mean?
I called them here. Using 911.
I said something about suspicious
people making a ruckus.
This place is off limits.
--Hands above your heads, all of you!
--Don't look at the light.
And it takes effect instantly!
What's the verdict, Zelada?
It worked, my lord.
The two of them are already dead.
Make 'em salute, then.
As you wish.
Have one shoot the other.
Yes, sir.
Poor bastard! He's dead!
Now... hmm...
Make him dance on the hood!
Zelada, looks like you don't
know how to dance, huh?
I'm sorry, sir.
Hilarious, huh? Huh?
How many can be controlled by this?
Five thousand? Ten thousand?
However many you like.
The most I've ever controlled at once is 100.
What?
That was a prototype.
The finished product will be even more amazing.
We're using the entire body of a powerful fairy.
The blast radius should be...
five kilometers or so?
That's the size of a nuke.
We could use this to overthrow
the government of a superpower!
Use it however you like.
You'll have to rent Zelada too, though.
We'll pay.
Sounds good.
I'll get it ready for you,
so make sure you've got the cash.
My lord, what should we do with him?
Oh, take care of him.
It's not the first time I've been
pallbearer for a coworker,
but you know, it's tough.
It's part of the job.
The force has lost three people this month.
Morale's in the gutter.
But the city council's trying
to cut our budget even more.
They don't see the reality. The bastards.
Chief?
Never mind. Focus on the job in front of you.
Are you sure you're okay?
With what?
Nothing.
Let's go.
Was it long?
Was what long?
Your relationship with the deceased.
You were his partner, right?
Yeah, I guess. Rick was a good guy.
He and I never did agree on which
baseball team to support, though.
In my country, it's said that
those who are mourned by many
go to a country of eternal,
peaceful spring after death.
That's probably what will
happen to Detective Fury.
Trying to make me feel better?
Is that bad?
No.
Do you know what you should
say at times like this, then?
"Dasch zanna." "Thank you," right?
Well done.
Kei, got a second?
What's up, Jamie?
You know a patrol car went missing last night?
The one from precinct 22, right?
It was found in Eastrock Park.
Along with two dead officers.
We know that they were killed
at a construction site in Redmoor.
They were brought here in their
patrol car and then thrown into the lake.
You're sure it's murder?
From the angle of the bullet wound,
this one looks like suicide.
Not sure. We'll have to wait
for the autopsy to be sure.
Let's have our police dog take a look...
Hey, Tilarna!
I'm surprised you remembered my name!
Just take a look at the bodies.
Bonah Tilarna.
That's what I told you to call me.
Just take a look at this!
These are dead.
Just like the assassin and the dealer.
So they were regular users of fairy dust?
These guys were cops.
But I'm sure of it.
If a cop's using, his coworkers
are gonna notice right away.
Maybe they used gold jewelry.
Gold jewelry?
Gold jewelry can be used as a catalyst
to enhance the power of latena.
But if you wanted something
with this kind of power,
you couldn't have a mistake
the width of a human hair.
Even the best craftsmen
in my country couldn't make it.
Maybe I'm wrong.
No, wait.
Maybe a human couldn't do it.
But what about a digitally
controlled manufacturing device?
Okay, there we go.
What?
Not many people are buying
powerful manufacturing machines.
I found someone using a dummy corporation. Look.
Dennis Elbaji.
A Semanian club owner?
What the hell does a guy like that
want with a manufacturing device?
Let's arrest him!
For what?
Anything! We need to
capture him and question him!
We can't do that.
The Earth is ruled by a god named
"fundamental rights."
We need some proof to convince a judge.
But we need to hurry!
We need to do the paperwork.
Her life is on the line!
Her? You mean the fairy?
Seems like this is personal.
What about you, Kei?
Do you not care if that fiel, that fairy, dies?
I feel responsible.
I have my own responsibility towards her.
You going to the bathroom?
I thought it was more important than her life...
"Next time"
Next time on COP CRAFT.