He's sort of transferring, though he
was sort of on academic break...
Anyway, this is Sakishima Hikari-kun,
Sakishima
who'll be joining our class.
I'm Sakishima, who's
repeating this class.
Please call me "Senpai" and respect me.
Well, that's how he is,
so you guys don't need
to hold back too much.
If you don't pay me respect,
I'll be seeing you behind the gym.
Episode Sixteen:
The Whispers of the Faraway Waves
Senpai, show us your Ena.
I want to see your Ena, too!
I remember the Ofunehiki.
Happi coats were totally in after that.
Happi coats were in? What the heck?
Tsumugu-senpai was so cool.
This is so weird.
Huh?
Having the octopus in
the same class we're in.
I haven't heard "octopus"
in a long time.
What?
Well, the octopus is an octopus.
He hasn't changed at all.
Sorry, do you mind if
I sit down for a bit?
I'm old, so I get tired easily.
That octopus-head isn't well yet,
so don't tease him too much.
Whoa, I haven't heard
"octopus-head" in a long time.
You both just said the same thing.
By the way, does that make you
Shiodome's uncle, Senpai?
Meaning Miuna's your niece?
Yeah, but just don't call me "uncle."
Hikari was how he always was.
Hikari was acting just as usual self.
So I thought I would act like
I was my usual self, too.
Sensei's voice is all hoarse now.
Totally hoarse.
It wasn't like that before?
I thought he may have
spoken a little faster.
So, what are you at now?
Huh? I'm fourt—
Not your age. Your height.
158 cm.
Crap! You're going to be taller than me!
What?
That's not going to happen. It won't.
But I haven't grown in five years.
What if I don't grow at all after this?
Then you can have my milk, too.
Watch out.
Talk about bad driving!
One sec.
Minegishi!
What?
I, uh, um...
You don't have to say any more.
I already know.
B— Um...
I won't say anything.
Tha— I'm sorry...
You know...
Is he in our class?
What?
I won't tell your dad.
Wh-What?!
Just tell me one thing.
Do you like him? Does he like you?
Which is it?
What?!
Got it. Never mind.
I get it now.
What do you mean?
I see, I see. So that's your type.
That's not true!
You're totally wrong!
Yeah, sure. I got it.
You don't understand anything!
Welcome home.
I heard you started school today.
Yeah, I went.
Totally acted like the senpai.
Tsumugu-kun brought his
Hama Junior High uniform.
Uniform?
Well, you don't have a uniform.
You can't just keep wearing a
white button-up shirt forever.
Huh?
Now that I think about it,
my Nami Junior High uniform
was taken off by the guys at the
Fishery Cooperative before the Ofunehiki...
What happened to it afterwards?
How would I know?
So you'll have this.
If it fits, go ahead and use it.
It's from when I graduated,
so it might be a bit big, though.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Yeah.
It's huge!
Huge!
Tsumugu grew way too much!
Want me to fix the pants again?
Yeah.
Hey!
Shut up!
Let's go have a new uniform
made for you after all.
What?
You don't have to.
You don't have to hold back.
It's fine. I'll just wear that.
We'll take the train,
go to the department store,
and all eat omelet rice.
Omu!
Receipt
Sazanami Pharmacy
They say that bravado is a sign
of being healthy, but he's...
Well, he is a guy.
Let's let him keep up his façade.
Yeah...
Thanks, Itaru-san.
Huh?
For letting Hikari stay at our place.
Of course.
He's your little brother...
And having such a younger brother
makes me feel younger, too.
Itaru-san...
Tomorrow's my first day off in a
while, so let's all enjoy it.
Thank you for always working so hard.
Nah, it's all thanks
to my responsible wife.
What's the matter?
Omu...
"Omu" is tomorrow.
"Tomorrow"?
When's that?
When you go beddie-bye and
wake up, it'll be tomorrow.
'Kay.
Today's special, so
let's open up another.
Next time, okay?
Next time.
No next time!
Mama!
Mom?
Whoa!
Can you bring a cooling strip?
Oh, right.
This is for your uniform.
It doesn't have to be today.
No.
We don't have to get it made or anything.
I can just go to Saya Mart and—
They don't have any.
You know where the tailor is, right?
Yeah.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
All right, be careful.
We should get going, too.
We have a train to catch...
Can we just not go?
Huh? Why?
"Why"...
Because I don't really
need a new uniform.
No, you need to wear a proper uniform.
What the hell are you
sounding like Akari for?
Let's go!
You say that, but what if we get lost?
We're not going to get lost!
If I get lost.
What?
We'll hold hands so we
don't get separated.
Are we on a date?!
You have the guy from yesterday.
No!
Then, Sayu.
I'll ask Sayu to come along with us.
What? Why are you asking her?
I'll go call her. Stay right there.
Did you remember to bring a
bottle filled with sea water?
I didn't bring that this time!
Miuna!
That happened five years ago.
For me, it happened the other day.
Things are totally different now.
I've changed.
Fine, I got it. Stop spitting on me.
I'm not spitting on you!
Sayu!
How is that you invited me,
but I got here first?
I'm sorry!
It's fine.
What should we get for lunch?
Omelet rice?
I'm not really hungry yet.
Remember those squid ink
chips from last time?
The black ones.
Those were great.
Do they still make those?
I don't think I've seen them recently,
but they have a new
flavor, stuffed squid!
"Stuffed squid"?! Seriously?
Those sound awful.
Whoa!
This place changed, too!
Let's go.
Actually, doesn't it sort of
smell like a fart off and on?
What?
That... wasn't a fart!
Really?
Then is there a pig somewhere nearby?
No! That's not it!
My shoes are just making
that noise for some reason!
Yeah. They're your best dress shoes.
They're your best, yet
they make pig sounds?
They fart?
So they're farting shoes?
Ugh! They don't fart!
Ow! Don't hit me! Ow!
Hey, you guys did have
something to do, right?
Oh...
See? We got yelled at.
That's because you...
Yeah, whatever.
We're going to leave you behind.
Could you take off your
shoes and step up?
I need to take your measurements.
Okay.
It's been a while since I've made a
uniform for a person from the sea.
Hopefully they'll be coming
and going again soon.
Yeah...
I'll go get the material.
What am I even doing here?
Compared to before,
apparently students that go to the
school on the surface have decreased as well.
Um, not Hama Junior High's...
Why are you wearing
Hama Junior High's unis?!
Not Hama Junior High's?
Oh... no.
Hama Junior High's is fine.
No! Make it Nami Junior High's!
Please make it Nami
Junior High's uniform!
What?
Nami Junior High?
I thought Nami Junior High closed...
But he's from Nami Junior High!
Ah, wait one moment.
Why did you...
Nami Junior High is fine!
I'll be waiting outside.
Didn't the tailor seem troubled?
He said he hadn't made a uniform
for a person from the sea
for a long time, didn't he?
But...
Anyway...
Sorry for inviting you so suddenly.
Whatever.
Hey, did you know?
What?
Nah, I better not say it.
Aw, but you're scary.
I am not!
Well then,
apparently uncles and
nieces can't get married.
Because they're close relatives.
I know that! But...
But it doesn't matter since
he's your step-uncle.
Sorry, I shouldn't have butted in.
No, it's fine.
Forget about it.
Why?
Why what?
You were happy for me.
You said you were happy for me, Sayu.
But then why?!
This has nothing to do with that.
Yes, it does!
You're being mean, Sayu.
You're the one that's being mean, Miuna!
What?
Why did you call me to go
shopping with you guys?!
You guys should have
just gone by yourselves!
Did you really want to flaunt
your flirting with each other?
"Flirt"... We're not!
You are!
Must be nice!
The person you like woke up!
It's always you.
All the good things always
happen to you, Miuna!
It's not fair!
What did I even come here for today?!
I have to make it from the
Nami Junior High pattern,
so it might take a while.
That's okay.
What?
I don't need one made after all.
Huh?
I'm really sorry!
Oh...
Stupid Sayu!
Stupid Miuna!
Uh, hey.
Sorry, I'm going home.
Uh...
Uh, wha...
Hello, Shiodome residence.
Oh, Hikari.
Akira?
Yeah, he has rubella.
We got him some medicine,
so he'll be fine.
I see.
That's good to hear.
By the way, I got separated
from Miuna, but...
Contact?
No, I haven't heard
from her. What's wrong?
She's not nearby?
Uh, yeah...
Well, I'll head back now. Bye.
Jeez...
I'm sorry...
No, that's not what I meant.
I'm just trying to figure out what we
should do to kill time till the next train.
But we missed it because of me...
You guys haven't changed at all.
Come on now, you're not
supposed to make girls cry.
Sayama!
Man, you gave the old
guy quite the scare.
What old guy?
Trying to act all mature...
Yeah, well,
I know about all sorts of things now.
Yeah, you are a geezer after all.
So since our place isn't as busy,
we've been getting back
to going door-to-door.
Oh yeah, that shipyard over there...
About three or four years ago, there were talks
about demolishing it and
making it into a parking lot...
But who'd even use it, right?
Stop the car, Sayama.
What? Right now?
Could you give her a ride home?
Please.
Be careful getting home.
Do Not Enter
You know, you haven't grown at all.
Why...
You didn't have to come after me.
Wow, talk about self-absorbed.
I just came to find my old uniform
that was left behind at the Ofunehiki.
I'm totally kidding.
I heard you got in a fight?
Girls always fight so quickly,
but then make up so quickly, too.
I don't get it.
I don't know... if we'll
be able to make up.
That's not true.
It is!
Manaka and Chisaki used
to fight all the time.
Manaka-san and Chisaki-san did?
Yeah.
Usually, Chisaki would
stop talking to her.
And then Manaka would cry.
How'd they make up?
Who knows?
I think that Kaname
might have helped out.
All right.
I guess I'll just have
to play Kaname's role.
U-Um...
Your nose! It's totally like a red pig!
Idiot!
Don't be mad!
Miu—
Miuna!
It's cold...
I can't breathe...
It hurts...
Hikari...
What's that noise?
I can breathe?
Miuna!
Seeing Hikari in the sea...
He shouldn't look any
different from usual...
But he was much brighter and special.
What are you doing?!
I could swim!
Wha?
I could breathe!
It's so pretty!
The sea! It's amazing!
Come on!
Wha... you...
I have to tell Mom that I could swim!
It wasn't hard at all!
Sayu?!
Thank goodness... you're okay...
I saw this on the ground....
Sayu...
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Jeez!
Does a pig live in there or something?
No!
How many are in there?
There aren't any!
Jeez!
Triangle
Pardon me...
What day is it today?
Hey, good morning.
Kaname...
When do you want to go see Kaname-san?
I'm not going.
A lot's changed, so it
must have been surprising.
Kaname changed?
There's no way things
have changed since then.
Episode Seventeen: The Sick Two