Captain!
Homecoming
Hey, Verde!
What's this?
I'm going to disappear...
As long as this song is being sung,
I can't maintain my true form.
Aria...
I wanted to make your dream come true.
Gaul-sama!
Shinku!
Guys!
Everybody!
Hero!
The healing song is purifying him.
Can we stop it?
It's a demon!
A disciple!
Well, sure it is, but...
Sharl, I'm asking you, too.
There's still things I need
to talk to him about.
Then use your hero crystals.
You can use defensive techniques
to shut out the power of the song.
I see.
Thanks.
Don't blame me for whatever happens.
Hero Crystals,
activate!
I didn't know you could use them like this.
Yeah, I can't hear the song anymore.
Gaul...
Everyone, I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I wasn't paying enough attention to Verde.
I didn't realize what he was thinking.
I dreamed of going to the surface,
and all Verde did was try to
make that wish come true!
Hey, Verde.
I don't know what happened
or the details of what's going on,
but no matter the reason,
a man must never make a woman cry.
Maybe you did do something wrong,
but just crying and apologizing
won't help anything.
And
it's not a bad thing to
have dreams or hopes.
I'm sorry, Verde.
I made you sad.
It's not your fault, Aria.
I'm a demon. A disciple.
Even if you're a demon or a disciple,
you're still Verde.
You were always with me when I was lonely.
You were always thinking about me.
You tried to do everything you could for me.
You're the
kind Verde that I love!
What's that?
Oh no!
Wait!
That light is...
A cursed blade.
It shattered.
I knew it.
He was possessed by a cursed blade, too.
I'm sorry, Aria.
Heroes of the surface,
I'm sorry.
What's this?
It's okay.
This is a good change.
Verde will slowly regain
his original form inside this crystal.
He was probably
originally a high-level spirit
or a local god's servant.
The cursed blade possessed him
and turned him into a
Sickness Demon Disciple.
Normally it would take
a very long time for him to regain
his original form, but...
If you keep him by your side
and sing him gentle songs all the time,
he may wake up fast.
That's right.
Yes.
Her voice...
It's a pretty voice.
Aria-san!
Rebecca-san.
I'm sorry to worry you.
And you, too, princess of the surface world.
My name is Millihiore.
Nice to meet you, Songstress of the Sky Sea.
I will sing a song of healing as the
songstress of the Star Festival.
Princess Millihiore, will you sing with me?
Yes, I'd love to!
This is a big help, Couver-sama.
It's nothing!
People of the surface,
and Dragon Priestess Sharl,
once again, I thank you.
It took a long time,
but I was able to find the Fire Dragon.
Yahoo!
Now we don't have anything to worry about.
It's time to say goodbye.
Yes.
But before that...
Right!
I'd like to give you a sign of thanks
for your courage and effort.
What's this?
I believe on the surface,
you call it a Phantasmal
Beast or a Divine Beast!
Phantasmal Beasts are truly legendary!
They're said to be servants of the gods,
and just seeing them will
bring you good luck.
The only ones I've ever seen are
Pega and this one.
Pega is one, too?
Yeah, he looked like that
before he transformed.
He'll look like that too,
once he transforms.
I will give him to you
as a sign of friendship.
What? Me?
It seems he's taken a liking to Prince Gaul.
That's great.
It's wonderful, Prince Gaul.
Then as a representative of
the Tri-country Alliance,
we'll keep him in Galette.
Will that be all right?
Yes, that would be ideal.
It seems like keeping a phantasmal beast
would be a scary experience.
Huh?
Bye-bye, everyone!
Bye!
Goodbye!
Prince Gaul.
Aria-san is over there.
I see.
Couver.
Can you head over there?
Sure.
We should all say goodbye.
No, Prince Gaul.
She saved your life,
so go yourself.
Ready, set...
Those guys...
This is the second time you've saved me.
You and your friends saved me and Verde.
There's a lot of things
I wanted to talk about, but...
I don't know how to thank you.
You don't need to thank me.
You saved me, and I saved you,
and we both went on an adventure.
You're my friend now, just like all of them.
Same with Verde.
I want to see you and everyone else again.
Yeah, me, too.
So I'll come back.
Can I go see you, too?
Of course.
Right,
guys?
Sure thing!
If you want to see us,
that's a good enough reason to come see us!
You don't need any reason
to want to see someone,
or be with them!
Yeah!
Thanks!
I love you, everybody!
You were looking good back
there, weren't you, Gaul?
Not really.
I just said goodbye, is all.
Yup.
It was great, wasn't it?
Yeah?
I hope Aria-san can come
to the surface to play.
You're right.
Even if you're far apart,
as long as you're thinking of each other
the bonds between you won't disappear.
But to keep those bonds strong it's best to
see the people you care
about once in a while.
Right!
Okay, we're almost outside.
The Fire Dragon is waiting.
Yeah!
Fire Dragon!
Sorry for putting you through all that!
This is goodbye for today.
Come see us again.
The people of the Sky Sea
will always welcome you.
A lot happened,
but everybody's safe,
and it's peaceful again!
I didn't get to do enough fighting, though.
Don't you think so, Eclair?
No, well...
It's a good thing to not have to fight.
We were able to restore peace
without anyone being hurt.
I'm very glad.
Yeah!
Okay, we're almost beneath the clouds.
Wow!
The light falls down here, too, doesn't it?
It's so pretty.
I've never actually seen it before.
Me, too. I've only heard of it.
It's probably falling on the surface.
I'm sure the people on the
surface are very confused.
And so our adventures in the
Sky Sea came to a safe end.
The princesses explained what the
strange presence from the sky was,
and that it would continue for several days.
So this light is a present from
the Star Whale in the Sky Sea!
It doesn't hurt at all, so don't worry!
It's an extremely rare natural phenomenon.
When nightfall comes,
drink and watch it!
It went by so fast again...
But a lot happened, and every day was fun!
You can come back next time, right?
Yeah.
I can come on long weekends, too.
And I can plan my weekends
around the war games.
Me, too.
This time I got to take a vacation,
so next time I have to do my
job as a Hero in the games!
Yes!
As leader, I'll do my best, too!
I have to do my best, too,
so I can be an official ruler!
I'm cheering you on!
Let's do our best together!
Yeah!
For some reason I don't feel very sad.
Me neither, actually.
We can always talk, and we can
see each other whenever we want.
But once I get back and I'm alone,
I'll be sad.
If that happens,
I'll call you right away.
Yeah!
Me, too!
Those two are such good friends.
You're right.
So why don't we be good friends, too?
We're both heirs to the Hero King, after all!
Yeah!
Hmm... what else am I forgetting?
This is for you, Nanami-chan.
It's a present from Leaf.
Thanks!
Well, even if you forget something,
you can come get it back quickly.
If it's something Jamie can carry,
he can hop back and forth quickly.
You're right.
But I don't want to leave
with my room a mess.
As Galette's Hero,
it's kind of embarrassing.
Y-You're right.
Okay, let's hurry and get it cleaned up.
Okay!
Yes.
Okay, Hero Rebecca!
See you next time!
Right, Cou-sama!
I'll be back soon, okay?
You're sure you didn't
forget anything, right?
I'm all set!
The way things happened last time,
I want to make sure things go okay.
It'll be fine.
I'll go home safe and come back soon.
Indeed.
Listen, Shinku...
Yes?
What Nanami-san and Rebecca-san
said to Aria-san...
You don't need a reason to want to see
someone, or to want to be with them.
Do you remember?
That that's what you told
Rebecca-san a long time ago.
Um... It was a long time ago, wasn't it?
I kind of remember, maybe?
When she was young,
every time there was a long vacation,
she would be so happy to see you,
but she was worried you might
want to play with somebody else,
or that you were bored when you were with her
because she wasn't good at sports.
A lot of stuff like that.
So she didn't say what she was thinking.
Becky was so quiet when she was little.
But she says
you told her that.
"You can come see me just
because you want to.
I'm happy and having fun when
I'm with you, Becky."
It made her very happy, she said.
I think I remember.
I still haven't spent a lot of
time with you, Shinku.
But even so...
I want to see you again soon.
And I want to keep playing with you forever.
Me, too.
So I'll be back soon.
I promise.
Okay!
Are we home safe?
Yeah.
What about Becky?
I'll call her.
Hello? Shinku?
I'm just fine!
I'm back safe!
Yeah! I'm glad!
Talk to you later!
Okay, let's do our jobs here on Earth,
and get ready to go back to Flognarde!
Yeah!
I'll give my studies and
sports everything I've got!
And your love life, too.
That's a different matter.
This is the end of our fall adventure.
But at the end of the year, and New Year's,
and then next spring...
I'm sure we'll be going back
to our other home,
where the people we love live.
To Flognarde, the place we love!
Okay, everybody!
See you again!
See You Again
Yeah!