Is it possible to have a happy
marriage to a human woman?
I certainly don't believe so.
No. It is.
And this time, I'll prove it to you.
Yes, I'll prove it with our eternal love.
Hozuki City's 48th
7/24-25 Kagurazaka Festival
#6 "Devil and Sense of Loss"
July 15th
Shinjuku Ward Kagurazaka
Izumi, are you over there?!
Dunno!
Gotcha!
Six wins in a row!
This isn't going well.
It's been so long, I've lost my intuition.
You're weak now that you're
a productive member of society, Arata.
Super weak!
One more time, damn it!
I won't lose this time!
Thanks for having me over tonight.
Helping with the family
business again tonight?
Yeah. We got a lot of reservations.
It's rough when your parents
own a restaurant, huh?
It sure is rough when your
parents own a restaurant.
Oh, right.
Want to go to Kagurazaka
Festival with me next week?
Kagurazaka Festival?
Won't you be helping your family then, too?
I managed to get them to give me time off!
How about it?
It's on a weekday, right?
As long as I can go before work.
Yes! You're paying, Arata.
Listen...
Just kidding! That was a joke!
It's been so long since I've
been to a festival with you.
I can't wait.
Yeah. Take care.
Oh, dear.
I finally lost him.
That guard dog of yours is persistent.
What do you want?
I wanted to thank you for earlier.
There's no need.
So this is her, huh?
Which parts of the earlier girl were right?
Voice and right leg.
I'm almost there.
The eye, which goes in last, is right there.
All that's left is the left hand.
Okay. I found a girl who I think
will meet your conditions.
I'll tell you about her.
You're certain?
As near as I can tell.
It's for your help earlier.
Storage #1
Morn—
G-Good morning...
Morning.
Well, see you later.
Senda-san, are you going somewhere?
I didn't tell you?
I'm on a work trip to Romania
for the next two weeks.
Romania?!
You're going overseas?
Lucky...
I would be, if it weren't for work.
You guys hold down the fort
for the next two weeks.
Bye.
So, let's get to work.
Head out on patrol.
Okay.
Do you remember what happened at Toyama Park?
Of course...
One of the female victims woke up.
Really?
So you need to go talk to her.
Kyoichi's on the way there already.
Huh? What about you?
I've got analysis work to do. You two handle it.
Visiting hours are almost over, so hurry.
Got it.
July 16th
Sorry I'm late.
This is the information from the police.
Her name is Shiba Yuko.
She's fully conscious
and remembers everything,
so we were able to find out her
address and her family information.
The issue is right here.
Birthdate: 11/10/1965
Born in 1965?
If this is true, she's in her 50s.
But she doesn't look that way.
She seems to think she's a teenager, too.
Um, does that mean she was
a teenager when she was kidnapped,
and then she came back without aging?
Yes.
Typical of a supernatural disappearance.
Shiba Yuko-san, right?
Yes...
I'm Sakaki Kyoichi.
I'm with the Shinjuku Ward Office.
Okay...
Can you tell me what happened to you?
Sure.
I really don't remember much, though.
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
How are you feeling? Does it hurt anywhere?
No, not really.
Good to hear.
First, can you tell me what school you go to?
I'm a second year student
at Shirakoma Girls Academy.
Oh, my childhood friend goes there, too.
I've heard they have a good choir.
They go to national tournaments all the time.
Me, too.
I joined to be part of the choir.
We were all looking forward
to going to nationals this year.
But now...
What happened?
I really don't know.
After practice ended...
Everything just went black,
and it was dark for so long after that.
So long?
Was there light?
No.
But I could see my hands and stuff, somehow.
And blackness... it was like ash.
Or fine sand. Falling from above.
Black sand?
Thanks. Anything else?
Actually... my throat
would sometimes feel cold.
Like someone put a knife to it.
Your throat?
Does it hurt right now?
No... but when I remembered,
I suddenly got scared.
Your voice sounds normal.
It's a little husky.
Husky? Nobody's ever said that before.
Can you try singing a high note?
Like you did in choir.
Wait... Wait a second.
No! How?!
I can't sing!
Why?!
So, she lost function in
a specific body part.
That's the natural assumption.
In her case, she's retained
her ability to speak,
but lost function in a certain vocal range.
Her singing voice was stolen...
I see. So that's it?
Did something happen?
I just got a call. Another victim woke up.
But they say her right leg won't move.
She didn't get hurt or anything?
I'm looking into it now,
but there's another problem.
Another problem?
She went missing in Hokkaido.
I see.
Either way, we need to look into this more.
And work with the police, too.
Work with the police, huh?
The cops and ward office have
different things they can do.
First, head back here. I want
to show you what I've got.
Roger.
Sakaki-san?
Oh, sorry.
It's the only possibility, huh?
Nee-san...
July 18th
Um, what did you want to talk about?
First, look at this.
Unsolved Missing Girls Cases in Tokyo
The part with a red bookmark.
This is the girl from yesterday.
Name: Shiba Yuko
There's a missing persons case
I've been following for a long time.
I think these girls are its victims.
This many?
Now, look at the blue bookmark.
Sakaki-san, this is...
Yes.
Name: Sakaki Shiori
She's my older sister.
17 years ago, we lost our parents.
The two of us lived in an orphanage.
Kyo-chan!
Onee-chan...
You had me so worried!
It's not my fault.
I know!
But you can't get violent.
If you hit first, it becomes your fault.
Let's go home. The nuns are worried.
Kyo-chan—
Onee-chan!
Onee... chan...
She was kidnapped by an
Another right in front of me.
At the time, I had no idea
it was an Another, but...
That's awful...
Ever since then, I've been searching
for the one who kidnapped her.
Searching? How?
I went to the police.
But all I learned from that is that the police
can't help you with Another-related cases.
After that, a lot happened. I became
a host because I needed the money.
That's when Senda-san found me.
And that's when I realized that at this
Nocturnal Community Relations job,
I might be able to find a clue.
And I suppose I was right.
What do you mean?
The black sand.
What she talked about?
That's right.
I think that the one who kidnapped
the girls we found in Toyama Park,
and the one who kidnapped my sister,
are either the same Another,
or the same type of Another.
Remember what Huehuecóyotl said?
That there was a nasty devil
that went around collecting girls.
You're right...
I want to know for sure.
Can you act as a go-between
and let me talk to Huehuecóyotl?
Please.
Yes. The man you were with held a tremendous
sense of loss, and that tripped the device.
This was it.
Sakaki-san's sense of loss...
When you say "talk," do you mean "negotiate"?
You said that human common sense
doesn't work on Anothers, right?
You're right to worry.
I'm not going to negotiate, though.
But...
I'm begging you.
I won't negotiate. I just want
to hear what he has to say.
S-Sakaki-san!
Please.
Fine.
I'll talk to Kohaku when I get home.
I owe you one, Miyako.
Also, this is absolutely not work-related.
So don't tell Theo.
But...
Senda-san's not here, so I don't
want to cause extra problems.
When it's time, I'll tell him.
All right.
Sakaki-san.
What?
She might be alive.
What do you mean?
I was just thinking...
that your sister might be safe.
What?
The girl in the hospital was born in 1965.
And she came back.
Don't you think she might be alive?
I see...
Yeah... you're right.
You're right.
Thank you, Miyako.
March Chiyoda Another Accident Reports
August Shinjuku Another
Accident Reports
July 23rd
I knew it.
Hey, Arata!
Yes?
You missed another thing
on your paperwork.
You've been screwing up
all the time since last week.
Sorry...
You've been kind of weird lately.
Are you not feeling well?
No, that's not it...
Want to get some fresh air, Miyako?
Can I take him on patrol?
Oh, I guess it's that time.
In this state, he's just
getting in the way, I guess.
Okay, let's go.
Right.
Those two are hiding something...
Umeya
I didn't see Kohaku yesterday, either.
I don't know where he is...
Don't worry. I've waited 17 years.
I'm in no hurry.
What is it?
Um... I think we should tell Theo-san.
I'm sorry.
This whole thing is just me being selfish.
I apologize for getting you involved.
But I want to keep that at a minimum.
But...
Don't worry. There's nothing to worry about.
Hozuki City's 48th Awa Dance
7/24-25 Kagurazaka Festival 7/26-27
July 24th
Hey, sorry I'm late.
No, I just got here.
What's wrong?
We just sounded like we
were from some old manga.
I never thought I'd actually say that stuff.
Yeah.
I guess it does feel a little unlike us.
Yeah, I agree.
Do you have time before work?
If I leave at 6:30, I'll make it in time.
I'm fine.
I'm thirsty.
What do you want?
Something that's not carbonated.
Got it.
Thanks!
Izumi!
He's late.
He's finally showing up late for work?
It happens to everybody.
There hasn't been any incident reports.
He'll be here soon.
Hey!
What?
What are you two up to?
What do you mean?
You think I can't tell?!
How long have we known each other?!
What are you hiding?!
It's none of my business what
you do when you're off the clock.
But think about the new kid a little.
It's interfering with his work.
That's...
Miyako Arata
Shinjuku Ward Nocturnal Community Relations
Miyako?
Miyako, what is it?
They took her...
What?
Miyako Arata
Shinjuku Ward Nocturnal Community Relations
Izumi... my childhood friend... was taken
by an Another right in front of me.
I think it's the one you were talking about.
The one who took your sister...
They were surrounded by black sand.
Black sand?
Like we saw in Toyama Park?
That's got nothing to do with your sister...
Or does it?
Answer me, Kyoichi!
During the Toyama Park incident,
it occurred to me that Huehuecóyotl
might have information.
So I tried to talk to him, using Miyako...
"Talk to him"?
Negotiating with them is dangerous!
You lectured the rookie,
and then you go and...
Arata, I'm on my way.
Stay put. Got it?
Miyako Arata
Shinjuku Ward Nocturnal Community Relations
Yeah...
Damn it! Why Izumi?
What are the odds...
It's not a coincidence!
Kohaku, show yourself!
You're here, right? Kohaku!
You called?
I like that look on your face.
I never really got to see it before.
You bastard...
Wait. Think about it.
I'm not the one you should be mad at.
It's that devil who's collecting
all the human females.
The ones I used in the
kyoshi ritual, and now her, too.
Then tell me! Where is Izumi?
A place you cannot reach.
Can't reach?
Where?!
Hell.
#7 "Sense of Loss and Proof of Despair"