To think that the DRAGON
would launch an attack.
This Para-mail... It isn't a DRAGON's, is it?
It is the Misurugi royal family's
duty to Manage the Singulars.
Mister Julio—no, Your Majesty, please explain.
There's no sign whatsoever that
the Dawn Pillar was activated.
Nonsense. Impossible.
We must re-establish Arzenal
and reinforce it immediately.
But we cannot.
This machine... it can't be.
It's the Villkiss.
It should have been destroyed
during the revolt.
It is the Rosenblum royal
family's duty to Manage Arzenal.
Why was this neglected?
The commanding officer
reported nothing out of the ordinary.
Was she duped by the Normas?
How incompetent.
No wonder a princess could so
easily be abducted by the Norma.
I won't allow Misty to be insulted,
not even by you.
Be calm, you two.
Silence, boy.
It was your sister that took my daughter.
That thing is no longer my sister.
Do you think we'll accept such an excuse?
You family of criminals...
Stop it.
Right now, we need to
discuss how we'll protect the world.
Without the Norma to rely on,
will we humans have to do battle ourselves?
You're all hopeless.
Embryo-sama...
Completely hopeless.
Her Right Arm's Past
We have two options.
One, surrender unconditionally to the DRAGONs.
Two, wipe out the DRAGONs.
That's unthinkable.
Right. Then three, rebuild the world.
Destroy it all, and reset it.
Kill the pests, replace the dirt,
and purify the world.
Destroy and rebuild it?
Can that be done?
If we can obtain all the
Ragna-mail and mail riders, yes.
Brilliant! Let's rebuild.
Immediately!
It was all a mistake in the first place...
That the wretched Norma exist,
and that the world needs them.
Nonsense.
Are you saying we should abandon
all the world's development?
Can you propose another way?
I suppose that is the only way.
Here. Use the tools in the yard.
Be careful, Julio-kun.
Leave it to me, Embryo-sama.
We're leaving, Riza.
They're playing a dangerous hand.
Destroy everything and rebuild, huh?
I have to hurry.
Don't touch me!
So these are all the survivors.
Who has command experience?
We're regrouping and
reassigning all Para-mail troops.
Hilda will be the interim captain.
Ersha and Vivian, you're her lieutenants.
What?
She's a deserter.
You're making a deserter a captain?
Why not Salia?
She's in detention for violating orders.
If you have a problem with me,
why don't you do it?
I-It's the commander's orders.
I have no choice, so I'll deal with it.
Right, Chris?
Para-mail troops are to organize
themselves and then stand on alert.
Yes, ma'am.
Destroy and rebuild, huh?
Hey.
My detention is over, isn't it?
Yeah.
Then tell me everything.
You promised.
Now, when we're busy as hell?
Who do you think saved everyone?
Fine.
But ditch the maid.
Hey! Where are you going, Ange?
Dammit! When we've got to hustle, too.
Huh, where's Vivi-chan?
Ow.
I fell?
Why?
Whoa! I overslept.
Why in the bath?
Secrets should be shared
when completely exposed.
So, what do you want to hear first?
Everything, from the beginning.
About the DRAGONs, about that woman...
About my Para-mail, and my mother's song.
Your relationship with Tusk...
Everything.
Fine.
Long, long ago, there was God.
God was tired of seeing war
after war, and of seeing
the earth in ruins.
What are you talking about?
Everything, from the beginning. Right?
Peace, friendship, equality...
We speak of beautiful things,
but the history of
humanity is a cycle of war,
hatred and prejudice.
That is the true nature of human beings.
Something had to be done,
or they would eventually perish.
So, God decided to create anew.
A new humanity.
A gentle, intelligent humanity
with no desire for conflict.
The advanced information technology, Mana,
allowed things to be
manipulated with the mind.
This ended suffering of all kinds,
and granted wishes of all kinds.
It led to the creation of an ideal state,
where anything could be had.
All that was left to do was to
watch over humanity's development.
At least, that was the plan.
But there they were.
No matter how often the system was rebuilt,
some female babies couldn't use Mana.
It was a mutation that expressed an old gene.
This mutation led to fear among the people.
But God decided to take
advantage of the mutation.
He propagated the notion that these girls
had rejected the world.
That they were antisocial monsters,
bent on destroying it... Normas.
The world united for the
sake of dealing with the Norma.
People took solace in knowing
who to discriminate against,
and there was stability.
Sacrifices, scapegoats, necessary evils...
Call us whatever you want.
We were also just created...
To bring stability to the world...
To be discriminated against.
What's wrong? At a loss for words?
It's all just so silly.
I'm impressed you could come
up with such a stupid story.
I heard it straight from him.
So, there's more, isn't there?
There's no need to hurry me.
And so the world of Mana became stable,
and it seemed like the beginning
of a prosperous history.
But some people wouldn't allow that...
The Ancient People.
Outcast survivors of the old
humanity that couldn't use Mana.
They challenged God many
times in order to reclaim
their place in the world.
After a long war, and grieving
for their fallen comrades,
they finally captured it.
The weapon of God,
Ragna-mail.
A mechanical angel of
destruction and creation.
The ultimate weapon that
was the Para-mail's prototype.
That's the Villkiss.
With it, they could fight just as well God.
The Ancient People boarded the Villkiss.
But they couldn't handle it.
It was locked...
So that mere insects couldn't use it.
With a mere handful of survivors,
the Ancient People had only
to wait for their own demise.
That's when they found out that
Normas sent off to the edge
of the earth were being forced to
fight the DRAGONs with Para-mails.
They set off for Arzenal.
There was contact...
Between the Ancient People and the Norma,
the two abandoned humanities.
They became allies, and made preparations
for when one would
emerge to open the lock.
And she finally arrived.
Alektra Maria von Loewenherz.
The first Norma born of royal blood.
Alektra Maria von Loewenherz...
I've heard of her.
I think she was First
Princess of the Galia Empire.
I heard she fell ill
and died when she was ten.
It was discovered
that she was a Norma.
She got thrown into Arzenal,
and she fell into despair.
But her royal blood and royal ring
unlocked the Villkiss.
Many came to her side.
Soldiers to protect the Villkiss,
and armorsmiths to repair it.
Doctors, weapons makers, dogs...
It was the beginning of the revolt
of the abandoned, of Libertus.
In the pits of hell,
I and the others found our calling.
To destroy this made-up, piece-of-shit world.
But I wasn't good enough.
I lost everything.
The ring, my friends, my right arm... everything.
But I can't let Libertus end.
Not with so many dead friends.
That's when you showed up, Ange.
Jill, you liar...
I couldn't do it.
The Villkiss's last lock is open.
You're going to destroy it, Ange.
This world, with that song.
So you brought back my ring.
Yeah.
You kept me alive for Libertus?
That's right.
I needed you to become stronger.
Princess Alektra, huh?
I'm grateful to you.
Thanks to you, I learned how spoiled,
pampered and sheltered I was.
So my answer is, "No."
Oh?
Even if everything you say about
God and Libertus is true,
my path is my own to choose.
No matter how glorious the duty,
I'll see things with my own
eyes and decide for myself.
I won't let anyone make me do anything.
So you won't join Libertus?
I don't hate it...
Killing DRAGONs, making money,
and buying what I want.
I don't hate my life.
I see.
By the way, in that story...
You never mentioned the DRAGONs.
I feel taller.
Is it my growth spurt?
Why can't I connect?
Hey, it's Officer Emma.
Hey!
It's Officer Emma!
Whoa! Are you all right?
What the heck?
Is this me?
What was that?
All units, type one battle formation!
It's a DRAGON!
There's a survivor in the base!
Rosalie and Chris will cover the residential area.
Ange and I will cover the maintenance deck.
Ersha, let Salia out and search Jasmine Mall.
Yes, ma'am.
The rest of you stand guard here.
Vivian.
Where's Vivian?
She's not in her room, either.
Angelise-sama!
You're late.
Where were you?
Good! All units, go.
Yes, ma'am.
Be careful, Angelise-sama.
Hey, Maggie.
Get all the inhibitor you can.
All right.
I'm so hungry.
How did this happen?
I knew it, it's curry!
Time to eat.
Huh?
That's weird.
Oh, it's me that's weird...
There it is.
Salia, Ersha.
Go after it.
Isn't this...
The El Laguna hourglass that does not turn
How does it know this song?
Time does not flow from it, lu la la li la
The flames of countless lives,
Fall through and become stars
What's that idiot doing?
Is she trying to kill me?
That bitch!
They fly beautifully,
And fade away in the
cradle of life and death
Ange!
Step away!
Jill.
Quiz time.
What's a DRAGON, even though it's human?
Oh, wait...
A human, even though it's a DRAGON?
Huh?
I don't get it...
I got it. It's Vivian.
Welcome back, Vivian.
Angelise-sama!
Hey, what's going on?
I thought I saw Vivian
come out of the DRAGON...
What's a DRAGON, even though it's human?
A human, even though it's a DRAGON? Huh?
Angelise-sama!
Stay away.
What's going on?
What are these?
DRAGONs, right?
What's happening?
You know how the story goes.
"The monster was human all along."
Angelise-sama.
I was killing humans?
With these hands...
I thought you liked your life?
Killing DRAGONs and making money.
Go to hell, bitch!
I won't use the Villkiss anymore.
I won't kill DRAGONs.
To hell with Libertus!
Fine with me, if you want to
live and die as God's pet.
God, huh?
I've never called myself that.
Though it may be appropriate,
in the sense that I'm a creator.
Embryo.
You're beautiful when you're angry, Alektra.
Or are you Commander Jill now?
Here it comes.
This is the International Rescue Fleet
of the Norma Administration Board.
Normas, thank you for your
good work fighting the DRAGONs.
We will hereby begin your rescue.
We have plenty of water,
clothing, and warm food.
Please abandon your weapons
and prepare for evacuation.
Let's go to our final reunion, Angelise.
Next Episode
I'm totally fine with Vivian being a DRAGON.
You never change, Ange!
But that song is mine.
You're going to have to pay for singing it.
It'll be 700 million.
Arzenal in Flames
You never change, Ange...