It was the night of Christmas Eve.
Man, that thing looks really nasty up close.
Luseat of the Seventh Garden...
Luseat of the Seventh Garden
Rank/ Raid
Just like the recon team reported,
he looks just like the one from Heilos.
Let's finish it up quick and eat some chicken.
It won't be quick.
But if we do it like we planned,
it should work out.
So what are our odds, honestly, Shiroe?
Fifty-fifty.
We're within twenty meters.
Be careful!
Come on!
Dinkuron
Race/ Elf
Guardian, Lv. 94
Good Status
Phys Def Up, Dodge Up
Guild
Silver Sword
Heal!
Putting up barrier!
I'm within range!
Anchor Howl!
Let's go, raiders!
Begin the attack!
The Changing Battlefield
The Changing Battlefield.
Groups 3 and 4, focus on healing.
Group 2 will stay close.
Everyone else, buff attackers
and assist Group 1's tanks!
Oh, no!
Be alert!
Watch what Luseat is doing!
Party 1       Party 2        Party 3        Party 4
Two insta-kills.
Conditions for critical unknown.
Strengthen forward buffs!
Sasameyuki, count!
One, two, three, four...
While we revive them and heal the wounded,
whittle him down from long range.
Five, six, seven, eight, nine...
I've seen that skill before, but...
It's far more powerful than it was in Heilos.
Time from the motion to activation is shorter, too.
Twenty-three! Twenty-four!
It's coming.
Get back! Get back!
No, the motion is different.
It's a different skill!
Each of his hits is so strong.
Stand in the wrong spot,
and you'll be killed instantly.
Eighty-eight, eighty-nine, ninety.
It's coming.
Defend!
Sacred Wall!
Sanctuary!
As soon as he's done, we counter!
You got it!
No insta-kills!
Cool down is ninety seconds!
Get me healed already!
Once your barriers are up and
you're healed, go back at him!
I'm doing it!
After he uses his skill, he's wide open.
That's our chance to attack!
That's the second time,
and already, no more insta-kills.
That's impressive.
They pick things up quickly.
Increase our damage output!
Stop wasting time.
Pick up the pace!
Cross Slash!
Round Windmill!
Turning Swallow!
Resonance Beat!
We're keeping a good pace.
Wait! Your DPS is too high!
You're generating too much aggro.
What's this?
A paralyze... No, a root?
It's coming from his feet.
I... I can't move!
We're taking damage.
Attribute is Evil Poison!
Race/ Elf
Guardian, Lv. 94
Good Status
Def. Up, Dodge Up, Damage Bl.
Bad Status
Evil Poison Root
Guild
Silver Sword
Our attack speed and damage are dropping!
This attack pattern didn't exist in Heilos.
It isn't doing much damage, but...
Anchor Howl!
He's ignoring me?
Anchor Howl isn't working?
An area-of-effect root that does minimal damage?
Watch out.
AoE barrier! AoE heal!
Stick it out!
Crap.
T-Ten dead... No, eleven.
Group 1 healers, maintain the front lines.
Group 2, fall back to raise and heal.
Groups 3 and 4, drop damage
output to seventy percent.
Focus on recovering.
This is great.
This is what I call a raid!
Lightning Straight!
Wyvern Kick!
That bastard...
Tanks, switch.
Naotsugu, draw his attention!
I'm on it!
Look over here, big guy!
He's taken enough damage
that he's changing modes?
Before, you had to do something
in the dungeon to trigger it,
but I guess this one can do it whenever he wants.
I guess you'd call it "True White Knight Mode."
It's just getting started.
Stay focused.
Just like the recon team said,
the fragments of his armor turned into monsters.
Shadow Vanguard
Rank/ Raid
Look at them all.
What a pain.
The little ones are nothing.
We can take 'em.
Forwards, pull the raid mobs.
Everyone else, concentrate attacks on Luseat!
Whoa!
What?
That's not good, Naotsugu-san.
Seriously? His HP is recovering!
Luseat of the Seventh Garden
Rank/ Raid
I get it.
Luseat's HP recovers each time we
defeat one of the Shadow Vanguard?
Hey, he's returning to Black Knight Mode.
This guy needs to chill out.
Eighty-eight, eighty-nine, ninety.
Wait! Wait!
This thing's in the way!
It doesn't matter if his HP recovers a little.
Hit him hard enough that
the healing can't keep up.
Whittle him down!
Again? Why?!
This is a problem.
Luseat of the Seventh Garden
Rank/ Raid
There's no end to them.
We should all just gang up on the big one!
We can't ignore the Shadow Vanguard.
They're strong enough to threaten the rear fighters!
If they go down, we'll lose the whole team.
The problem is the number of people.
The same number of Shadow Vanguard appear
as the number of people that attacked
Luseat in Black Knight Mode.
I see.
Which means...
If we reduce our numbers by having
only the high damagers attack,
and have everyone else focus on buffs,
we can keep the Shadow
Vanguard down to ten or so.
You heard him!
Pull them, but don't defeat them!
I know!
I hate to admit it, but right now,
I can't beat him.
No, I haven't forgiven him...
Someday, I'll crush him.
And in front of everyone.
I'll smash in his pale face,
and make him shed tears of regret.
HP down to fifty percent or so.
Okay, we can do this.
I'll get a phantasm-class item on this raid,
raise my level, polish my skills...
And someday, Shiroe, you ass of an enchanter,
I'll...
Sixty-nine, seventy, seventy—
What?!
That's...
Taltaulgar of the Fourth Garden
Rank/ Raid
Taltaulgar?!
It's Ibrahabra!
That's impossible!
Ibrahabra of the Third Garden
Rank/ Raid
This is Luseat's zone!
Wha—
This can't be...
Three raid bosses...
At the
same time?
Why?
That isn't fair!
One raid boss at a time.
That's the rule.
Fight fair and square.
You're kidding.
Was this designed to be impossible?
We can't beat this...
Party 1       Party 2                  Party 3      Party 4
Shiroe!
Shiro!
Look at you...
You look so stupid.
This is
my hometown?
The place where I was born and raised?
Ramen
The sign...
What was this place called?
I see.
This is what it means to lose memories.
That's right.
I died.
There was nothing special about this town.
It wasn't exactly inconvenient,
but if you wanted anything specific,
you had to go into the city.
A small, normal town, like you
could find anywhere.
Shirogane
That's me.
Both my parents worked,
so I'd often leave my house,
and go out walking around at night.
When I was alone at home,
even being in bed was painful.
I was scared to go downtown.
So...
I spent many nights on this bench.
When something was bothering me,
that was all I could do to help me forget.
Oh...
That's why I've come here.
Because I failed again.
I was often told that I seemed mature for a child.
And I think, for my age, I was
intelligent and self-controlled.
But because of that,
I ended up distancing myself
from the other kids my age.
I made a lot of mistakes.
I mocked the kindness of others.
When people stretched out their hands
to me, I smacked them away.
When I needed to stay and fight, I ran away.
I didn't understand how hard my parents
were working, or how they felt.
Welcome home.
I wasn't able to make dinner, so buy something from the
usual deli, okay? I spoke to your teacher, so I think we'll
discuss your last test on Sunday. The bath's been cleaned,
but you can have a shower if you'd prefer. Get to
bed early. I'll be home by the time you wake up.
Sorry about everything.
They were all small failures,
but ones that I couldn't fix.
And each time, I came here and cried.
I swore I'd never do it again,
but I always did.
When you die, you learn a lot...
That you suck, that you're petty, that you're lame.
If you die a hundred times,
you learn that a hundred times.
It gets too painful to continue.
I see.
So this is what it is to die.
It means feeling like you want to die.
I've felt that many times.
The night I threw away the notebook
that was so dear to me,
the night I forced myself to smile and say goodbye,
the night I bid goodbye to the library...
I've felt it again and again.
Why did Demikas knock me away?
Why did William accept my request?
Why did Naotsugu follow me?
I'm hiding something from the people I care about,
the people who believe in me.
There's a possibility that there are
Minami spies in Akihabara.
You don't know where information might leak.
Exactly.
Minami isn't what I'm really worried about.
In this world,
there is something besides adventurers
and People of the Land.
The third party that brought us here.
I've used my Round Table connections
to try to find out who it might be.
I asked Roderic to investigate the flavor text.
I asked Soujirou to see if the monsters were changing.
I asked Michitaka about southern plants.
I asked Karashin to gather and
organize Eastal folk literature.
Of course, it was without telling
them what I was really after.
Everything I managed to get together gave
the impression that there was no third party.
However...
Proof of it appeared at the perfect time.
It seemed set up to make me believe it.
That's an excuse again.
I thought I was doing it to avoid worrying them,
but I'm still causing trouble for them.
Just like how they waited for me back then.
I'm sure everyone else...
I was only pushing them all away.
I should have been more open with them.
And Kinjou, too.
I doubted him and didn't tell him enough.
I should have told him what I was really after.
Yes.
That's right.
I have to go, don't I?
I have to get up from this bench,
and return to everyone.
The Earth?
Then this is...
The Moon?
Latin?
It means "Sea of Tranquility," I think.
This really is the Moon.
But why?
Might it be the test server?
Elder Tale, the game, is divided
among thirteen servers.
The test server is a fourteenth, unofficial server.
I'd heard rumors that it was on the
Moon, but I can't believe it's really...
I didn't think it would be so quiet here.
Yeah.
Something disappeared...
Did you also feel it, my lord?
Akatsuki...
Amazing, isn't it?
It isn't snow, is it?
No.
Everyone's thoughts...
The memory fragments they offered up,
so they could rise up once more.
You were defeated, Akatsuki?
I see.
So was I.
I died.
You, too, my lord?
Yeah.
It's been a heck of a Christmas Eve, my lord.
I failed.
I was naïve.
I couldn't trust them enough.
I don't understand.
It isn't that I'm upset because I couldn't win.
You didn't do the best you could.
You didn't do what you needed to do.
Akatsuki, you may have fallen.
But you haven't lost yet, have you?
It's okay.
I know.
I know you're working hard.
So I will, too.
It's strange.
I didn't think I'd see you here.
Yeah, my lord.
It is strange.
I'm going to try again.
I will, too, I guess.
Everyone taught me.
My lord...
And so, I revived.
Feelings exposed.
What else is there?
What else can I do?
Nothing.
No matter what anyone else says,
no matter what they think,
I'll keep moving forward.
That's my decision.
There's no way back.
Again and again...
Until I plant that flag on this land.
Next time: Guild Master.
Guild Master
Rise up once more.