Why?
Why couldn't you find
it anywhere in Izumo?
Hanzo!
I am terribly sorry.
Without any information about
its form or properties,
our search has been difficult.
Silence!
You will bring the priestess
Sanada took in to me!
Intimidate that disobedient
Sanada while you're there, too!
Understood.
Open the gates!
Hey, Saizo.
Do you like this pink one or this teal one?
There are a whole bunch
of other colors, too.
Whatever.
Don't you know what day it is?
As a festival priestess,
I'm supposed to celebrate
the harvest with a dance!
I'm just asking you to
help me choose my outfit.
Fine, then that one.
This one? I thought it'd be nice, too.
Saizo!
Dark and Light
I don't care about her dance or festival.
I don't have time for this crap.
A woman?
With blonde hair?
It can't be...
Iga Ice Technique!
Sohyoga!
Whoa, wai—
Ana!
Is that you, Saizo?
Yeah, nice to—
Kak dela?
You've grown so much,
I hardly recognized you.
Don't hug me!
What are you talking about?
We're childhood friends.
I heard you got yourself a master.
Yukimura? Are you serious?
Why?
What do you mean, why?
What's a talented girl like you doing
working for a crazy guy like him?
I went out for wool and
came home shorn, I guess.
I tried to kill him in his sleep,
but screwed up the job.
But he said he'd hire me, so I defected.
What?
You'll understand someday.
Who's the girl?
Huh?
Isanami.
Oh, she's my...
Saizo, you cheater!
That's enough.
Yukimura-sama!
Old man!
Saizo, you've got to treat women better.
Do you need me to show you?
No.
Ana, how did things look at the border?
There were rumors going
around about an uwabami.
Uwabami? Isn't that a snake?
That's right.
It's so big, it can swallow
people and beasts whole.
We can't have that. It'd ruin the festival.
Would Sasuke be fine on his own?
If he's not, he'll let us know.
But the festival's more important.
I'm counting on you, Isanami.
Heave, ho!
We're grateful for another
bountiful harvest.
Eat and drink your fill today.
Cheers!
He's oddly charming, isn't he?
You've got strange taste.
So, you're jealous.
Huh? Of what?
Saizo, you're scared, aren't you?
Of what?
Of fighting for someone.
Even though everyone yearns to find a
master to serve, or something to protect.
What?
Bull's-eye.
That's ridiculous.
I'm happiest doing whatever I want.
You're so stubborn.
People like you float away if they don't have anything to hold them down.
I've had enough of this.
Oh? Running away?
I'm not into festivals and dancing.
I'm gonna go stretch my legs.
What's with Saizo?
I can't let it get to me.
I'm a priestess.
She's rather frantic, isn't she?
It's novel, but it's not bad.
Good job, Isanami!
Saizo?
Saizo!
Where are you going? I'll go with you.
But you're the festival priestess.
Let go of me.
No. I'm finished dancing,
and I want to always be with you.
You'll only be a burden to Saizo
if you cling to him like that.
I'm gonna go kill that uwabami.
You stay here.
I'll be fine because you'll protect me!
Fine, do what you want.
Enjoy yourselves.
Ana!
Wait!
Enough, you...
Over there.
There's something scary over there.
There's nothing here.
That's what doesn't make sense.
I haven't heard a single bird chirp all day.
It is pretty dark in here.
What's wrong?
I couldn't sense its presence at all!
Because it's a snake!
I hate snakes.
Hey!
You really are a burden.
Saizo?
Run, Isanami.
I'll save you.
Are you stupid? I can't protect you now.
Just go.
You'll be okay.
You're strong.
Get back.
Saizo.
That took all my gunpowder.
A puppet technique?
It's being controlled.
Don't move, Isanami.
Saizo, you're bleeding.
I'm fine.
Saizo!
That uwabami was set to
explode when it died.
Whoever was controlling it
must be a hell of a puppeteer.
Saizo?
Isanami, is that you?
Saizo!
You're all right.
I'm so relieved.
Thank goodness!
Ow!
Oh, sorry.
I can't believe we've been
buried alive together.
We'll be together until our last breath.
Why are you always so optimistic?
It's not optimism.
I know I'll be safe with you.
What makes you so sure?
Because you're my light.
Your light?
Yeah. You're my one light in the darkness.
What?
I faced so much difficulty
and fear after I left Izumo.
You're the only one who
extended a helping hand.
My turbulent emotions
calmed in an instant.
I felt so warm.
That's impossible.
I'm someone who takes.
I pass from darkness to darkness,
but I never reveal myself in the light.
Rescuing you was a coincidence.
That's not important.
You're dazzling in my eyes, Saizo.
You must've had nice parents.
Parents? I don't have any.
They told me I was abandoned in
front of the Izumo shrine as a baby.
The priest raised me.
He's gone now, though.
He died protecting me in Izumo.
So you're the only one I can rely on, Saizo.
Got it?
I told you, I don't care.
I'm putting out the fire.
We'll run out of air.
Huh?
The smoke's flowing to the side.
What is it, Saizo?
If the air's flowing this way,
there might be an opening leading
outside in this direction.
You mean we can get out?
If we can open a big enough hole.
If this place collapses,
we'll be crushed and die together.
I believe in you.
Om Marici Yeh Svaha!
Hey!
Come on, let's get out of here.
Saizo!
The castle's under attack!
What is this?
The smoke's getting in my eyes.
Calm down, everyone!
Women and children outside first!
Criminals! Show yourselves!
Show yourselves!
Where is the priestess?
Where is the priestess of Izumo?
I-I don't know.
Where is she hiding?
The uwabami was nothing
more than a rumor?
Your efforts are futile.
My snake is rigged with explosives.
If you try to kill it,
you'll destroy everything and
everyone in the vicinity.
If you don't believe me,
why don't you try it?
A puppet technique.
These lands belong to Sanada.
I will kill those who defile it.
Kill? What strong language.
I, Okatsu, will destroy you.
Come.
Eat him.
Damn it. You wait here.
Saizo.
There's no way I can just wait here.
Well, don't you have some poise.
Poison?
You'll lose your vision soon.
Did I get in your way?
You certainly did.
I was just having some fun with this boy.
Oh, my apologies.
But now that I've found you,
I can't let you get away with this.
Go right ahead.
Let's see if you can do something about it.
Sasuke.
I don't require the assistance
of an Iga. She's mine.
I apologize, but I don't intend
to let this fight drag on.
I've already wasted plenty of your time.
You mean...
You finally realized why you're here?
Is someone there?
Are you all right, sir?
I can't see because of the smoke.
Go towards the light.
You'll find an exit there.
Thank you, Miss.
Hey!
What a brat.
You've done it now, boy.
What?
The forest is my domain.
You will not leave here alive.
Is anyone still here?
Are you all right?
What?
I finally found you.
My name is Hattori Hanzo.
You'll be coming with me,
Miss.
Unfortunately for you,
you're not taking her anywhere.
It's my job.
Saizo.
Stay back, Isanami.
He's strong. Be careful.
I have no intention of losing.
This'll be quick.
Hey, you.
Are you familiar with the expression
"pride goeth before a fall?"
Who cares?!
Gotcha!
He cut me.
Hey, you.
You really should read
the Heike Monogatari.
If you live, that is.
He's fast. Who is this guy?
Get away from the castle, quickly!
Yukimura-sama.
It's made of iron.
A couple of men tied up together
is hardly an attractive sight.
How can you say that at a time like this?
Everyone's made it to safety.
Do it, Rokuro.
Rokuro!
I have no choice.
These ropes cannot be cut.
Saizo.
You think you can do whatever you want?
I'll kill you!
You're welcome to try.
Ninpo Samidare!
You can't evade what you can't see.
That's what you call a feat of Marici.
Not a problem.
I'll simply cut them all down.
It's nothing more than a distraction.
Is this all the alleged
prodigal ninja can do?
The Iga ninja, Kirigakure,
also known as Marici because
no one is able to cut him.
I can't tell you how many
times I've heard the name.
What about it?
Now it's my turn.
Too bad.
Om Sumbha Nisumbha Hum Vajra Hum Phat.
Ougi Kasho Zanmai!
Saizo!
Saizo...
Terrible... Terrible, terrible!
Miss, you'll be coming with me.
It's my job.
Damn it...
You're dazzling in my eyes, Saizo.
Let us be on our way.
I won't let you take her.
You don't know when to give up, do you?
Have you changed your mind about me?
Why... won't you die?
Saizo, Isanami.
The Sanada ninja.
Defeated Okatsu, did you?
Unfortunately, we'll have
to postpone this battle.
Wait!
Saizo,
Isanami.
Saizo!
Shut up.
You're way too loud, monkey.
My head's pounding.
Perhaps you had too much to drink.
You should retire early tonight.
No, it's because you—
If you have trouble
sleeping, I can help you.
That's quite all right!
If anything, I'd like to use
a lady's chest as a pillow.
What're you doing, old man?
You'll get in the way if you
sleep out in the hallway.
The next episode of Brave 10
is "The Valley of Whirlwinds."
Bring it on!
The Valley of Whirlwinds