Japan...
So peaceful, I think I might yawn.
I've come to see you...
Black Tiger.
This time for sure, I'm going to...
"Fate"
Hey! Tsugumi!
What's up? You need me
for something?
Well, it's Honey.
She says you can go home
without her today.
She forgot her homework, and
they're making her do it over now.
In that case, I guess I'll hand off
my guard duty to Mr. Claude.
Oh, one more thing, Tsugumi.
About today's pop quiz...
the parts you helped me out with
came up. I really owe you one.
Thanks, man.
B-Being thanked for such a trivial
matter as that b-b-brings me no joy!
That was just a matter of your
feeblemindedness, no more.
You just can't say "You're welcome," huh?
If you ever get stuck again,
I might be inclined to help you out.
Raku Ichijo!
What...
Hey, you're...
I've missed you...
...Black Tiger.
What's it been, a year?
What are you doing here?
There are tons of things
I want to discuss with you.
Hey! What do you think you're doing,
blasting those things on school grounds!
If you have to fight, do it
somewhere else where it's safer!
Anyway, stop that!
Stoooop!
Are you an idiot?!
Butting into a shootout
with your bare hands...
You're lucky you got off
with slight injuries, but...
Well, it couldn't be helped.
There was nothing else I could do.
No, thanks! It's not
that much of a big deal.
Shut up!
I don't want to be
indebted to you, that's all.
What is this place?
It's the apartment I'm
renting for my personal use.
Normally, I sleep at
Young Mistress's house,
but for some missions,
I need a place like this.
Oh, yeah?
Stop gawking and staring!
I'm not staring, I'm not staring!
So?
Would you mind telling
what the deal is here?
Why was I, someone
who just tried to kill you,
not only invited inside your home,
but even served hot tea?
Black Tiger?
What are you talking about?
You're the one who wanted to
talk to me, remember?
That's not what I'm talking about!
Black Tiger?
I see that guy over there
is totally clueless.
"Black Tiger," you see, is that woman's
alias in the American underworld.
Several years ago...
she burst onto the underworld
scene like a comet,
and though I was, at the time, the undisputed
queen of completed missions among my peers,
she rocketed past me
in the blink of an eye,
and because she worked
in demonic beast mode,
she came to be known by
the nickname, "Black Tiger."
So you're a hitman, too?
Yes, that's right.
I may not look it, but in the underworld,
I'm a fairly well-known ace hitman.
Known as the "White Fang" of the Beehive.
Her name is Paula McCoy.
She's a former colleague of mine.
Don't call me Paula!
It's really been a long time, huh?
It's so good to see you doing well!
Listen, I'm about to have
dinner. Want to join...
Stop it with the feels!
What am I, a relative?
I didn't come here
to get cozy with you!
I've come to settle the score with you!
Since that day...
ever since you toppled me
from my No. 1 status,
I've held you up as an example.
But to be honest, right now
I'm sorely disappointed.
For the last few days,
I've observed your comings and goings.
That slack expression...
that slack vibe!
Like any ordinary girl-next-door
living a complacent, degenerate life!
So that gaze I've been sensing
lately... that was you, Paula?
That's because my current
mission is to guard Young Mistress.
Is that really all there is to it?
Whoever you are now, you don't
have the bite you had before!
You're just like a tiger
who's been defanged!
What happened to you?
Did you break down somehow?
Or do you fear the battlefield now, maybe?
Oh, or could it be that you've met
someone and now you're in love?
That guy right there, for instance?
Not on your life!
Oh, really? Then sorry.
Anyway, I can't let you
go slack like this!
It's pointless unless I surpassed
who you were back then.
Why are you so obsessed with me?
If it's a role model you're looking for,
there's no shortage among the top brass.
Don't go telling me
you've forgotten.
That's something I'll never forget.
The day you and I first teamed up.
So you're the Black Tiger?
I'm Paula! Nice to meet you!
Ooohh, so hot!
Are you a boy?
ALEADY HAS
A LITTLE
You have absolutely no chest.
Who the hell are you to talk?
Come on, what about you?
Looking just like a boy yourself!
Who in their right mind says
stuff like that to a stranger?
I was self-conscious about it!
So self-conscious about it!
Since that day, I went on
countless missions with you,
ABDUCTION
but you always, always
hogged all the credit!
Anyway!
I've made up my mind
not to forgive you!
Someday, without fail,
I'm gonna make you eat it!
Hey, there's really
no need to cry, you know.
Don't think you've won, now!
Sobbing!
Now that it's come to this,
I'll have to resort to force!
Prepare yourself, Black Tiger!
Come on, draw!
Hey, hold up.
You haven't had any
dinner yet, have you?
Why don't you eat first?
Wow! It's nikujaga! Looks yummy!
Give me back my seriousness!
Hey, you can cook?
Well, after a fashion.
What do you mean, nikujaga?
What's up with this homey atmosphere?
This is not the Black Tiger...
Back in the day,
you were the kind of person who guzzled
her targets' living blood and cackled!
I never! I never!
Hey, is she all that different?
The old Tsugumi?
Totally different!
Three years ago,
when she annihilated a certain
organization all by herself...
You should've seen the authorities
quake in their boots.
"The Beehive gang's got one
hell of a watchdog!" they said.
Isn't she talking about the time
Chitoge got harassed by thugs?
What the...?!
Where did you hear about that?
There are numerous legends
about the girl she was back then.
I've carried out a lot of
missions with her,
but she's clearly head and
shoulders above the rest!
It was precisely because of
who the Black Tiger was that I...
So I can't fathom how
she became so tepid.
Hey, this is good.
Are you sure about
giving me some, too?
Might as well since you're here, that's all!
If you don't want it, don't eat it.
What's this? It's super-delicious!
Hey, this is impressive!
Really great flavor here.
To tell you the truth, Honey can't
cook a lick, so I was getting worried.
I think I want this recipe, actually!
Y-You do?
Yeah! I bet you're gonna
make a great wife!
Who'd ever want to be
your wife, for God's sake!
Hey, no, I never said mine!
Okay, then whose?!
Hey, that's dangerous!
Hey, Black Tiger...
All right, why don't we do this?
Have a showdown with me.
If I lose, I'll walk away
without a word.
However,
if I win, you're going to
come back to the U.S.
And there, I'll have you
regain the fangs you've lost!
Hey...
I see. Fine by me.
But if it's a showdown,
I'm not going to hold back.
All right, what kind of
showdown, then?
Target practice?
Close quarter combat?
Arm-wrestling?
Till now, no matter what kind of
competition you challenged me to,
you've never once
gotten the best of me.
Time limit, one hour.
Battlefield, this entire city.
Condition for winning...
Whoever...
...steals a kiss from
this guy first wins.
Whaaat?!
"Showdown"
What kind of competition is that?!
Why should your
competition involve...
My... uh... lips and all?
Come now,
leading a man astray is a legitimate
skill for a hitman, isn't it?
N-No! We can't compete that way!
What's this?
Someone of your stature, Black Tiger,
backing off a challenge you initially accepted?
Just hear me out!
You might find this
hard to believe, but...
This guy is actually...
Young Mistress's boyfriend!
He's Young Mistress Chitoge's?
Right! She's absolutely right!
That's no lie!
Just ask Honey, she'll
confirm it right away.
So this showdown of yours...
True... That wouldn't do, would it?
But surely you haven't
forgotten, Black Tiger?
"Iron Law"
That "Iron Law" of the Beehive Gang?
Once you've accepted a challenge,
under no circumstances should you back off!
The moment you said, "Fine by me,"
you took this showdown
past the point of no return!
Rest assured.
Whichever of us steals that
kiss, I'll keep it a secret.
Besides...
Even if he is Young
Mistress's boyfriend,
he can't be more than a fling, right?
FLING
Someone as forgettable as this guy?
FORGETTABLE
Man, you sure are rude!
If it were any other competition, true,
I might not be able to beat the Black Tiger.
But judging from what I just saw,
I'm guessing the Black Tiger is inept with guys!
I have the edge in this showdown!
S-Steal a kiss from him?
Me... from him?
Th-Th-There's no way I can do that!
But if I end up
losing this showdown,
I won't be able to stay by
Young Mistress's side again.
I don't want that!
Not only that, but...
Now, then!
All right, this showdown's on!
Don't mind if I do!
Hey... Hold up!
My body moved of its own accord!
Not only that... What's this
I'm feeling right now?
I'd rather die than kiss this guy!
And yet...
...the thought of Paula
stealing a kiss from him...
That's what I like to see, Black Tiger!
Die... I'm gonna die...
I'm gonna die! They're gonna kill me!
Who the hell can play along
with that kind of game, anyway?
Anyway, I've got to run!
I could have endless lives
and it wouldn't be enough!
I've got absolutely nothing
to do with their showdown!
Come back here!
You let me kiss you!
Damn.
Merely thwarting Paula
won't get me anywhere.
Now that it's come to this...
Raku Ichijo!
Hold still! It'll be over soon.
Hey, but you...
Don't say a word.
You serious?
I can't do it after all!
Why would you hit me?!
Just as I thought, this
showdown is mine to win!
A smoke screen?
Oh, no!
All right,
with this much distance between us, even
the Black Tiger won't be able to track us, will she?
Now, then...
Little boy, just resign yourself
and offer your lips to me.
I promise I'll be gentle with you.
Who are you calling "little boy?"
Anyone can see that
you're younger than me!
Why is this happening to me?!
I've never kissed anyone
before in my life, you know!
If this is gonna be my memory of
my first kiss... That suuuucks!
Oh, but it's my first time, too.
What, it's your first time, too?!
Then are you sure
you're okay with this?
It's your precious first kiss.
And you're using it on this showdown!
I don't understand what you mean.
Are first kisses that precious?
Everybody kisses, you know.
And basically, a kiss is just one
membrane touching another, right?
I can't believe you're getting
flustered over such a thing.
No wonder you Japanese are...
Well, maybe it's not
that precious to you.
But for people who want to
cherish it, it's definitely precious.
For me, too.
Even if it's not me!
And besides,
the truth is, winning this showdown
isn't your real purpose, is it?
All you really want is for Tsugumi
to acknowledge you, am I right?
What...
That's... not...
It's no good.
I've totally lost them.
What am I gonna do?
If I lose, I'll have to
go back to the U.S.
I'll be separated from
Young Mistress yet again!
But what can I do?
By now, they've already...
Why am I feeling this way?
Why do I feel so anxious?
I don't know why, but
I feel such hopeless dread.
The thought of somebody
stealing a kiss from his lips...
I don't know why,
but I just can't stand it!
What am I supposed to do?
I can't stand it.
I can't stand it, I can't stand it,
I can't stand it, I can't
stand it, I can't stand it...
What the hell?!
Don't tell me she's found us?
Even though we're this far away?
Hey, Tsugumi! Save me!
Nice timing!
Miss... Tsugumi?
That's...
Is that really Tsugumi?
I see.
At last you've decided to go all-out.
I've missed seeing you like that.
How delightful, Black Tiger.
This murderous vibe...
Now you're really you!
Now we can finally
have some fun and...
What? Where'd she go?
She destroyed a concrete
pillar with a single kick?
What the hell?!
But that's just otherworldly...
Both your speed and your power!
Far from losing any, what you're
showing now is way better than before...
Paula.
Yes, ma'am!
Don't resist.
You hear me?
Y-Yes, ma'am...
Raku Ichijo?
Yes!
You... Don't tell me you're...
Don't say a word.
All right!
Now I've stolen a kiss from his lips!
That means I win, right, Paula?
Hey, what was that just now?
That's not what you call a kiss, is it?
What are you talking about?
You said to "steal a kiss
from his lips," remember?
So for all intents and
purposes, this should suffice!
Or do you have a problem, maybe?
None whatsoever. I'm sorry!
Still...
Your movements when you attacked me,
and when you spirited this guy away...
They were quite masterful, you know.
You've become so strong.
That makes me happy, too.
Why...
Why did you disappear
all of a sudden, dummy?
My bad.
They summoned me on short notice.
And you were out
on a mission at the time.
All right, just as I promised,
I'll be leaving now,
but you better come back to
the U.S. someday, Black Tiger.
Sure.
Oh, man.
I really got myself
dragged into a mess.
You got a problem with that?
Not really.
Oh, man, I'm wiped!
So? What are you gonna
do now, Black Tiger?
About what?
That guy is Young Mistress's
boyfriend, right?
Are you going to be okay with that?
Well, now... What could
you be talking about?
Seriously...
What are you guys talking about?
None of your business!
She's such a child.