Were you just singing?
I was on my way to pick up
the uniform I ordered,
but I couldn't find the shop,
Are you listening to me?
so I've been wandering around all morning.
Where'd you get that?
The croquette place by the station.
Are you all here together?
Hey, guys, are you okay with me
calling you by your first names?
What are you doing now, Sakai-san?
I'd like if it you all called
me by my first name.
Nothing. Probably going home.
You were singing, weren't you?
Uien, was it?
Nein! It's Wien.
See you later.
Ween.
Wien.
So, you were singing, right?
Ween!
Wien.
Wien, got it!
Shut up!
It all sounds the same!
Tanaka-san, go show Wien around.
Wien.
Wien?
Sakai-san, will you come
over to my house for a bit?
Your house?
Episode 2
Gathering and Struggling
Sawa! Kona-chan!
Aloha!
Hi, Shiho-san!
Heading to the beach?
Yup. She your friend?
Yeah, Sakai Wakana-san.
She's in my class.
I see. Well, you girls have fun.
I'll be back by dinner.
Aloha!
Your older sister?
My mom.
That's it, Sabure!
You've gotta eat a lot, so
you can grow up big and strong.
So do you.
Say what?
Why?
She's my pet, too.
I'm home!
Thank you for having me over.
Ah, welcome.
Sorry about the moldy smell.
Huh?
So, Okita-san, is this temple your house?
Yeah.
And you can call me Sawa.
[Epic Failure] Joint High School Recital
Have you seen this before?
It's a recording of last year's recital.
Look, there's Konatsu.
She was so nervous, she couldn't sing.
Sorry, I laughed again.
If you were too nervous to actually sing,
you could've just lip-synched
until it was over.
The end result was a huge failure,
but I like what you did.
It makes me laugh, every time.
Sorry! I'm kidding!
Hey, Sakai-san, can we put your
name down for the new choir club?
She doesn't want this to
be her last time singing,
so she's been practicing hard all year.
No matter how slight her chances,
I want to support her.
So, please!
We need at least five
people to start a club.
You don't have to actually participate,
if you don't want to.
Push too hard, and she'll
just get mad again.
If you just need my name, sure.
Seriously?!
Awesome!
Shimada Clothing
Girls are pretty complex, huh.
And they wear the weirdest
outfits on our days off.
You think so?
Wanna grab some food?
Right now, it's just me
and my sister at home,
so there's no one around
to cook a decent meal.
Sure.
Could this possibly be...
Thinly-sliced meat, cooked with vegetables
in a light-but-savory sauce...
A bastion of Japanese cuisine...
Yes! This is none other than sukiyaki!
It's a beef bowl.
Listen, let's eat, and then
we'll go buy you a better book.
Why don't you get your little
brother to make his friends join?
Good idea! Motion accepted!
The dancing violinist Kumagai
Tetsuji will be there,
so you could try to recruit people
who'd join because of him.
We'll use that, too!
I know him.
He has a very weird style.
Oh! And we could get Shiho-san
to make us some flyers.
You know she's going to
go completely overboard.
Huh?
My mom gets asked to make
illustrations and flyers all the time.
Well, her drawings really pack a punch!
Makoto.
Quit doing that!
I want you to invite your
friends to join my choir club.
What? Not a chance.
Moving your porn stash to a
new hiding spot won't help.
Mom!
Choir Club
Join the Choir Club
and meet Kumagai Tetsuji!
Please take one!
We're starting a new choir club.
Thank you.
Have a flyer. It's for our choir club.
Here.
Good job!
Yes, of course.
I'll make the announcement
at the next board meeting.
Yes, yes.
Thank you.
Yes, goodbye.
Come in.
Thank you.
Is there a problem with the
current choir program?
Well, I'm not allowed to sing.
I have enough members,
and it won't be like the other choir.
I want to perform at the recital
with a completely new concept.
I'm sure it'll create a big—
I'm sure the vice principal
has her own ideas.
Performing at the joint recital
with a random group is...
Club Application
Choir Club
Sakai Wakana
Invited by a friend
This could be interesting.
It might also be a good incentive for some
of the top hitters in the music program.
Would I be acceptable as advisor?
Of course.
I have always had faith in the
potential of my young students.
That's the kind of man I am.
Thank you so much!
I did it!
Mwah! Mwah!
Very interested in...
Miyamoto-san, is something wrong?
Hey!
Each and every arrow is important, you know.
Right.
When does the new choir club start up?
Tomorrow, during lunch break.
Really? That's good.
So, I want to choose our song right away,
but looking at sheet music
isn't giving me any ideas.
I also can't choose a song that only I know.
But I was hoping to have a song
we could start practicing tomorrow...
You can play piano?!
It's a mandatory part
of the music curriculum.
Although, I'm not as good
as the piano majors.
Sakai-san, I know we said you'd
be a member in name only,
but could you help us out the next
two days, while we choose a song?
What about the actual recital,
and your rehearsals?
My brother's asking a friend of his,
who plays the electone, as we speak,
but I want to pick a song and start
practicing, as soon as possible!
Please!
I'll buy you a cake!
Two cakes!
One is enough.
Oh, thank you!
All right, can you play
through these in order?
You just want to get the
feel of them, right?
Yeah.
Start with this one.
It's kind of strange, huh?
There are scribbles all over it.
I've never heard it before,
and the music was even written by hand.
I like this song. It reminds
me of the Condor Queens.
Do you know them?
They're a pretty old band.
I'll lend you one of their CDs some time.
Okay.
This song might work!
Play it again, right from the beginning.
Melody of the Heart
Sure.
If there are no objections,
this is the song I'd like us
to perform at the recital.
What time will rehearsals start?
I've got cram school,
so I can't stay too late.
Same.
Well...
Miyamoto-san, I'm heading out.
Sure, thanks!
Why don't you all submit the times
that are good for you to me?
Okay.
The recital's coming up fast,
but we'll rehearse as hard as we
can, so we can blow them away!
35th Joint Recital
I got the principal's permission.
I know.
What are you singing?
I can't allow you to sing this song.
You'll have to select something else.
You can't—
Why?
This isn't a song you can
sing for the fun of it.
But I like it.
It's new to me,
but it's like I can feel how much
the composer enjoyed writing it.
It's very straightforward and sincere.
You can tell the composer loves to
sing, and yet there's also joy...
I feel like it incorporates
everything I'm feeling right now.
And that's why I want to sing it.
Enjoying something and
bringing joy are different things.
You are incapable of bringing
those two together.
A fresh wind races through
the grass and leaves.
The view is clear,
as far as the eye can see.
And now, a graceful light is flooding...
Sawa!
Is the principal here?
Not yet. And nobody's heard from him.
Can someone else drive us?
If you don't have anyone supervising you,
you'll need to go back to your classes.
"Participation in club activities
without an advisor's
or assistant advisor's
supervision is prohibited."
As club president, I'm
sure you know this rule.
But...
Who's your assistant advisor?
Ms. Takahashi.
I'll try to get in touch with her.
Since you'll need to stay here with
your club to await further news,
you'll have to appoint someone to lead
the afternoon rehearsal in your place.
Okay. Makoto!
Me?!
Can you read music?
Where's Sakai-san?
What? Right now?
She said you're the only one who can do it.
I'm sorry...
I wrote down everyone's
parts and their positions.
The music is here.
Call me if you have any problems.
I'll let you know how things
are going on our side, too.
I really am sorry...
Two cakes.
Ms. Takahashi isn't answering.
I'll go to her house.
What? Are you sure?
Sure, it's close by.
If the principal shows up,
pick me up on the way with the bus.
I'm starting to feel a little nervous.
Yes?
Um...
You must be one of Tomoko's students.
Yes!
Is she in right now?
She just went to the
hospital for a check-up.
Can you tell me which hospital?
Miyamoto-san!
I found the principal.
You "found" him?
Joint Recital
Rehearsal's started.
Is everything okay over there?
They just found the principal,
but I'm not sure what's going on.
Shirohamazaka High School Choir Club?
I'm here with Mr. Tada...
Yes!
I have to go.
Okay, I'll be there soon!
Look, I stopped, okay?!
And I just had it waxed!
I even wax my bicycles. That's
the kind of man I am.
Sir!
Understand?
Maternity Ward
Ms. Takahashi!
Okita? What are you doing here?
Are you pregnant?
No.
The principal's out.
What?!
But I called the school and
arranged for the bus to leave,
so I think we'll make it, somehow.
Then we'll go to the auditorium.
Great. Where are you now?
I'm at the hospital, so...
Konatsu!
You're here?!
Could you please let the
choir club sing last?
They said they're on their way
and will definitely make it.
I know it's asking a lot to change
the program last-minute...
I just got a call from the principal.
Huh?
Though I don't want to,
I'll put your club after the voice majors.
Thank you very much.
Almost there.
This is really cutting it close.
Yeah.
Where's the rest of your group?
On their way.
Sakai-san's the only one there.
Sakai-san?
Wow...
Goodness, that scared me.
Do you want us to crash?!
I've trained.
This isn't going to be like last year!
Relax, relax, relax.
Next up, we have the Shirohamazaki High
School Choir Club performing "Melody of the Heart."
Where's Miyamoto-san?
Not here yet.
Found you!
Hurry! They're introducing you guys!
Is everyone else already out there?
What? They're not with you?
We've finally cleared the congestion,
so it shouldn't be long.
How's it going over there?
Are we going to make it?
Sis?!
I'll tell them you're not going on.
I'm going home.
You get all these people involved,
and now you just wanna quit and go home?!
What's wrong with you?
This is your last chance!
You're right.
I've got to overwrite last year's shame!
Singing is all that matters!
I don't care if I make a fool of myself.
I have to see this through!
Thanks for all your help, Sakai-san.
I'm going to find the answer
you wanted last time.
What do you sing for?
Are you ready?
Yeah.
We've just gotta get through one song.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Just imagine you're looking
at a pumpkin patch.
I've never seen a pumpkin patch...
A watermelon patch, then.
You're rude.
Sakai-san?
Okay.
What did she say?
I think I owe her three cakes now.
All right, let's do this.
A fresh wind races through the grass and leaves.
The view is clear, as far as the eye can see.
And now, a graceful light is flooding,
softly illuminating everything.
Even if you can't see the stars
because of the rain,
the future you're dreaming of
is still right there.
Let's sing every day,
with all our hearts,
our song echoing to the skies,
and beyond.
And if it should ever
reach you again somewhere,
I want you to remember
the days we spent with beaming smiles.
Let's sing every day,
with all our hearts,
our song echoing to the skies,
and beyond.
And if it should ever
reach you again somewhere,
I want you to remember
the days we spent with sparkling eyes.
The days we spent with beaming smiles.
I'll be hospitalized for a while,
so you'll have to take over
my duties for the time being.
Yes, sir.
You can call me Sawa.
Tai-kun?
If we do this, I want to win.
Please let us sing here!
Episode 3
Swinging and Meeting
But if I win, both of you have
to join the badminton club.