The Third Plate
Nine
The dining hall side needs reinforcements!
We won't let you lay a finger on this dorm
until Yukihira's Shokugeki is over!
They got through our barricades?!
Shit! We're done for if they get inside!
Wait.
Something's off.
They're not rushing in?
I can't believe my glasses
broke now of all times!
What's wrong, Marui?!
Wh-What's going on?!
Yukihira
Soma
Eizan
Etsuya
In the Shokugeki between
Yukihira Soma and Eizan Etsuya,
Yukihira Soma won with a score of 3 to 0.
Eizan
Etsuya
Soma-kun won...
I repeat, in the Shokugeki between
Yukihira Soma and Eizan Etsuya...
But how?!
Yukihira!
He really beat the Ninth Seat
of the Elite Ten...
Eizan might've taken
the Shokugeki more seriously
if he'd wagered his seat, but...
Yukihira Soma...
Hey, Isshiki. Hard at work
on the paperwork, huh?
Are you cool with all of this, though?
Your dorm's about to get shut down.
How can you just watch that
happen from over there?
Polar Star Dormitory won't get shut down.
Soma-kun knows that the true worth of a chef
can only be gauged through
their creations.
I know what he's capable of.
He will easily overcome
Eizan-kun's rigged match.
Rather, what will be critical
is what follows that match.
That is when the true battle begins.
I must make the necessary preparations
for that, no matter what happens.
Looks like things are playing out
exactly as Isshiki had imagined.
Yukihira
Soma
Eizan
Etsuya
So the eviction's been canceled.
Yay!
Nice! They're leaving!
Shove it!
So Polar Star Dormitory's safe!
I'm back.
You idiot!
You up and did a Shokugeki all by yourself!
You didn't even talk to us!
You're so reckless!
You idiot! Fool! Nincompoop!
We were all worried about you.
But I'm so relieved now! Seriously.
Thanks so much, Yukihira!
Soma-kun...
Welcome home!
Yeah!
But how'd you beat Eizan Etsuya?
Oh, well a lot of things happened.
I still can't believe it.
So what's with the helmets?
Oh, um, they're from back
in the golden age...
Let's leave the talk for later
and get back inside the dorm for now.
Yeah!
We need to celebrate how we
managed to save our dorm!
Food Wars
The Third Plate
May the Polar Star Shine Eternal
Celebration Party
Cheers!
Hunting the Survivors
Well done, Yukihira.
You too, Arato!
Yukihira!
I was watching your Shokugeki!
Takumi-cchi, Isami-cchi.
Takumi-kun's in his usual lecture mode.
Nag, nag, nag, nag, nag...
Oh?
You're not mad at him?
No lectures?
He had no choice.
Your home was under threat.
Even I would've done the same.
Takumi-kun...
Nakiri-san, hello.
Wow!
You were really at Polar Star Dormitory.
H-Hello, Aldini brothers.
In any case, this is a night to celebrate!
You guys should eat before you go!
I guess he did just wrap up
a really challenging match.
All the tension's left him.
But man, you're amazing, Yukihira.
You crushed the Ninth Seat in a Shokugeki.
That means you might even win against
the Tenth Seat, Nakiri-chan.
What?!
Don't be ridiculous! How rude!
And who are you calling Nakiri-chan?
What?
Erina-cchi...
"Chan" = No Good
But you let Yoshino call you Erina-cchi.
You can't use "chan" with me!
It's too undignified!
Yes! That's right!
Besides, Erina-sama is only the
Tenth Seat due to her restraint.
Her true abilities would
place her at a higher—
Oh, well. I was the one who suggested
the topic for that Shokugeki.
Even though Eizan-senpai came up with
his dish halfway through the thing,
he still managed to create
something impressive.
I want to face him soon on equal terms.
So it wasn't a satisfactory victory.
I get you, Yukihira!
Now that I think about it,
what's going on with the other
groups who are facing shutdowns?
They're still between a
rock and a hard place.
Oh?
But thanks to you, Soma-kun,
the situation has slightly improved.
I-Isshiki-senpai!
Where have you been?!
Sorry, all.
I am an Elite Ten member, after all.
I was concerned that if I did
anything rash to help the dorm,
the Azami administration
would up the ante on us.
I mean, I was wondering if you'd
turned on us, Isshiki-senpai.
Yeah, it wouldn't have surprised me.
What?!
How could I ever do that?
Don't you understand how much
I love Polar Star Dormitory?!
Um, Isshiki-san...
What's improved?
Right.
Upon learning of the Shokugeki's results,
the Azami administration has
made a new announcement.
Central has agreed to accept any Shokugeki
challenge from an organization
that is trying to overturn being shut down.
Of course, the Shokugeki will be
official and judged by neutral judges!
It doesn't change the fact that the
academy remains under Central's control,
but Eizan-kun's rigged match
method has been shut down.
You made this happen, Soma-kun!
You have brought the Shokugeki back to life!
Thank you, Soma-kun, for saving our home.
Oh, there's no need to thank me.
This place is important to me, too.
Thanks to all of you for
protecting the dorm, too.
Well, enough serious talk.
Let's just enjoy the rest of the evening!
Yeah!
Wh-What?!
He's naked, save for an apron?!
Naked?!
But with an apron?!
How vulgar!
Look away!
Look away, Erina-sama!
It's not my first time seeing this,
but he still leaves quite an impression.
It wouldn't be Polar Star Dormitory
without it, I guess.
Wiggle
Hup! Hup!
Wh-What is going on with
the people at this dorm?
Wiggle
Th-They're totally fine with him
wearing nothing but an apron!
This dorm really is quite strange.
It is!
No, it's bizarre!
Bizarre!
Bizarre! Bizarre! Bizarre!
Erina-sama?
Hisako, do you know how
to use a washing machine?
Er, a washing machine?
Well, yes.
I see.
It's impressive that you can use
a device with so many buttons.
Um, Erina-sama?
A-Anyway, forget washing machines!
I'm just trying to say that there
were a lot of things and oddities
I had no idea about before
I came to this dorm!
R-Right.
They really are very strange people.
And Yukihira-kun is right in their center.
When Polar Star Dormitory was under siege,
they seemed to feel that Yukihira-kun
would be able to pull off a miracle.
You did, too, Hisako.
What?
Me, too?
You seemed to know that Yukihira-kun
would manage to do something.
Why'd you look that way?
U-Um, well...
What can I say?
It's not like I had any
reason to feel that way.
I did have a premonition...
That perhaps the one who'll
save Totsuki from Azami-dono
is that man.
Nakiri-kun, Arato-kun...
You should come join us!
Please put on some clothes!
It's fine.
It's comfortable once you get used to it!
I don't even understand that!
Hup!
Several Days Later
Isshiki Satoshi, Seventh Seat
of the Elite Ten.
Today, you will step down from
the Totsuki Elite Ten Council,
Totsuki Elite Ten, Eighth Seat
Kuga Terunori
Totsuki Elite Ten, Third Seat
Megishima Tosuke
along with the Third Seat, Megishima Tosuke,
and the Eighth Seat, Kuga Terunori.
This happened faster than I thought it would.
You are calmer than I thought you'd be.
I was more than expecting it.
Someone who does not ascribe
to Central's teachings, like me,
in the Elite Ten would only
be a hindrance, wouldn't it?
It's helpful that you
require little explanation.
The other Elite Ten members
are in agreement, as well.
But why, why?
I don't think we need to kick
them out of the Elite Ten! Why?
Well, Kobayashi Rindo was the lone protest.
You aren't forcing Nakiri Erina,
your daughter, to step down?
She will eventually return to my side.
I am certain that she
will join me in my cause.
Well, thanks to you,
we're going to be very busy.
With Shokugeki?
That's right.
You worked behind the scenes,
reaching out to relevant parties
to lay the groundwork for these
new rules we must now follow.
We must allow organizations who wish to
overturn our closure directive
to face my pride and joy,
the soldiers of Central.
"Rules Concerning Shokugeki involving
Organizations Opposing the Azami Organization,
also known as the Isshiki Rules."
Who names stuff after himself?
That's kind of annoying.
Still, because Isshiki clarified
that Central cannot contact judges,
the legitimacy of their
ruling has been established.
Of course, I was against rigged
matches in the first place.
There's a clause requiring Central
to accept any Shokugeki challenge
that involves overturning the
organization's closure, too.
Isshiki's pretty thorough.
It's also annoying that this forces
us to face subpar opponents.
I was first place in overall
sales at the Moon Festival.
They should just have
Central win by default every time.
You'll just have to accept this, Momo-senpai.
And Rindo-senpai,
please wear the Central badge.
Really?
But that looks like it'll
always get in the way.
Don't "really" me, please.
But, but...
Don't "but, but" me, please.
Okay.
The rest of you should put your badges on,
too, before Nene gets mad at you.
No need to tell me twice.
Well, let's get going, then.
It's time to start hunting the survivors.
Hunting the survivors?
That's what Central's calling
Shokugeki matches with
organizations that want to survive.
The first set's happening today.
They're not trying to sugarcoat it, huh.
Students from Central will
be participating in the matches.
Yeah.
The pro-Azami Elite Ten will be a given,
Academy Director
Elite Ten
General Student Population
(Pro-Azami Administration)
(Anti-Azami Administration)
and the rest are high performers who could
be called the Elite Ten's reserves.
The Elite Ten's reserve troops, huh?
I want to check them out.
Huh?!
You'd better not be thinking
of doing something again.
No more going off on your own!
If you're going to watch the Shokugeki,
I'll go with you.
I'd be too worried if I
let you go by yourself!
I guess it'll be fine if
Takumi-cchi goes with him.
I mean, he's basically always at the dorm.
Yeah, let's go.
It's just for scouting purposes, understand?
I-I want to go, too!
I'm sure Regional Cooking RS
will also be having a Shokugeki.
True. My Miyazato Research Group
will be fighting the same foe.
Watching the matches wouldn't
be a waste of time.
There's supposed to be three separate arenas.
Oh, then we can just all split up
and cover them all.
Yeah!
Let's do that.
Hall A Group
We'll be going to Hall A, then.
Let's do our best!
Hall B Group
We'll be going to Hall B!
I'll be worried about Erina-sama
while we're all gone.
Nakiri-chan will be fine.
Fumio-san will still be here.
Hey!
Don't call her "Nakiri-chan"!
S-Sorry.
Hall C Group
All right!
We'll go to Hall C!
Yukihira, today is for scouting
purposes only, understand?
Don't take this too far.
I know, I know.
Hall C
Elite Ten, Fourth Seat, 3rd Year
Akanegakubo Momo
Elite Ten, Ninth Seat, 2nd Year
Eizan Etsuya
Hunting survivors or not,
Japanese Food Industry Council
President
Oizumi Kakinoshin
I won't let anything detract from the
fairness of this match while I still live.
Japan Gourmet Society
Director
Saotome Seishu
Yes, it's our responsibility
to provide fair judgment.
Wow, what a crowd!
Um, this match is the Fourth Seat,
Akanegakubo-senpai,
Chocolate RS
vs.
Akanegakubo Momo
versus the Chocolate RS.
Eizan Etsuya
vs.
Western Cuisine RS
There's also Eizan-senpai
versus the Western Cuisine RS.
Looks like there will be several Shokugeki
happening in parallel at each arena.
The Don RS guys aren't here, huh?
Shiomi Research Group's
Hayama isn't here, either.
Let's go, Bucchi.
Help my cooking.
All right.
I hope it baked okay.
She ripped off the teddy bear's
hands to serve as oven mitts...
Is there some meaning that I'm missing there?
Rumor has it that she does it
every time she cooks.
She works fast, as expected.
She is called the best patissier
at Totsuki Academy, after all.
The cake we ate at the Autumn
Leaf Viewing was super tasty, too.
Done.
How beautiful.
But what of the taste?
Western Cuisine RS
Chocolate RS
Akanegakubo Momo and Eizan Etsuya
both won in a complete shut-out.
Wow...
A sweeping victory by Central.
Huh...
I want to fight them.
Soma-kun!
Yukihira, I know I sound
like a broken record,
but today is for scouting purposes only.
You can't challenge them—
I know, I know.
Yukihira...
Come to think of it, I haven't seen
Eizan-senpai's specialty dish yet.
Next time, let's give each other a lot
of time to prep and do a Shokugeki!
Some day, for sure.
Damn brat!
You're going to pay...
I'll make you regret humiliating me.
In quite a state, aren't we?
Weren't you supposed to be good
enough to be an Elite Ten member?
Well, we'll take it from here.
Let us handle the rest of the Shokugeki.
You lost to a first-year, Eizan-kun.
Oh?
Central's soldiers, hand-picked
by Nakiri Azami.
They're now part of the
faction that rules Totsuki.
You really don't mind
that we're selecting the topic?
Yeah.
We'll compete against you with
dishes that you specialize in.
We'll crush you in the very genre you've
been trying to perfect your skills in.
That's in poor taste.
You're just trying to mess with them.
But that makes victory
even sweeter, Momo-senpai.
Spanish Cuisine RS
Underestimate us all you want.
But we've been honing our craft
at Totsuki all this time.
It won't be that easy!
Grains RS
Moroccan Cuisine RS
Spanish Cuisine RS
Now, choose.
Will you close down your research society,
or will you be expelled from Totsuki?
We'll accept closure.
Worthless, the whole lot of you.
You get it now, right?
You weren't chosen.
So you should obey!
That's the correct choice!
Bowing down before us in Central
is your only remaining path!
I can't let that pass!
I can't let that pass.
Huh?
What?
Did you first-years say something?
We said we can't just have you guys...
...tell us how much we're worth.
Not only Soma-kun, but even
Takumi-kun couldn't hold back!
You're the first-year who defeated Eizan,
and you're one of the students
from the Autumn Elections.
I wouldn't run your
mouths to me if I were you.
I'm an elite who will shoulder
the next generation of chefs.
An elite?
That's right.
I'm an elite hand-picked by
the current academy director.
You shouldn't try to oppose me.
I feel no sense of identity from you.
Your strong emphasis on being chosen
comes across as a reflection of the low
self-esteem you experienced beforehand.
Is your inability to avoid
describing yourself as an elite
due to a lack of confidence
in your own cooking?
You said some smart-sounding
stuff there, Takumi.
So, was it true, senpai?
You assholes!
I'm gonna beat you up—
Don't act out.
High School Division, 2nd Year
Kumai Shigemichi
Shige!
Let me down! Hey!
I'm not letting you down.
Fine, I'll do as you say!
I will! So let me down!
Don't carry me around!
You're so easily provoked, Ren-chan.
Shut up, Mea!
Listen up, first-years!
High School Division, 2nd Year
Kusunoki Rentaro
I'm gonna fight you in a match one day!
Just go, okay?
High School Division, 2nd Year
Yanai Mea
Make sure you nail the last match, too!
High School Division, 2nd Year
Kofuru Rui
He's going to do another match?
Who is he going to face?
What?
Oh?
Hm?
Nakiri Alice?!
Kurokiba!
Oh, you two. Hello!
Why are you here?
You joined a research society?
I was shocked, too!
When I was in junior high,
I did a Shokugeki against
the Cutting Edge Cuisine RS.
Of course, I won.
I'd taken their space and equipment...
Shokugeki Notice
Cutting Edge Cuisine RS
Chief: Nakiri Alice
but I'd apparently become
the RS's chief on paper!
I was so shocked to learn about it!
That's horrible on so many different levels.
So that's why you got dragged
into the hunt for survivors, huh.
You may call me Chief Alice.
You didn't even know for all this time!
Why do you care whether the research
society gets shut down, then?
Well, I suppose...
So Cutting Edge Cuisine RS will be disbanded.
Several Days Ago
I can agree to a Shokugeki
challenging that decision, though.
No, I'm fine with that.
Huh?
Having "chief" as a title is rather
refreshing, and a bit hard to let go of,
but I'm not interested in it at all.
So please leave us.
Smart choice.
You riffraff should just shut up and
watch the Azami administration prosper!
Who'd you call riffraff?!
What? What's this all of a sudden?
I'll crush anyone who attacks me!
I'll use my cooking to drag you down with me!
Ryo-kun...
Very well.
I'll accept this challenge!
So, Ryo-kun's the one
who'll be in this match.
Go, Ryo-kun.
Expose that self-proclaimed
elite for what he truly is.
'Kay.
The last Shokugeki to conclude
the first day at Hall C...
Kurokiba-kun!
...will be the kitchen dictator,
Kurokiba Ryo versus
Central's rookie, Kusunoki Rentaro.
Ryo-kun, don't you dare lose!
I'm ordering you to win as the
chief of Cutting Edge Cuisine RS!
I'm not going to let Uncle
Azami get his way anymore!
Kurokiba Ryo...
He made it through to the finals
in the Autumn Elections.
Something really pissed me off earlier.
I'm gonna take it all out on you.
You're not a bad one to crush to
wrap things up on the first day.
If you're gonna try to crush me,
I'm just gonna crush you right back!
Go, Kurokiba!
I'm watching you from right here!
Oh, thanks for letting us barge our
way into such a good viewing spot.
Hmph!
Huh?
Oh, Momo-senpai's always like that
at first, so don't let it get to you.
You can easily take at least a
month getting her to look at you
and have a decent conversation.
Huh?
How'd you manage to get through camp
and Stagiaire and stuff like that?
I have no obligation to
explain that to you.
You're annoying.
Huh? What was that?
What?
Soma-kun, you're pushing her too far!
The topic is salmon!
Oh, that's some nice salmon.
Look at the color and shine of those gills.
Seafood...
Ryo-kun, focus!
Kusunoki Rentaro versus Kurokiba Ryo.
Let the Shokugeki begin!
Totsuki
Food Wars
The Third Plate
Next Episode:  The Salmon Will Dance
I hope you savor the next episode!