I see that you are awake,
Slaine Troyard.
Where am I...?
My castle. You are safe now.
Take your time and rest.
What happened...?
I remember being interrogated
by Count Cruhteo, but then...
You have nothing to fear.
I have dealt with him.
The count... is dead?
I am indebted to your father. Hence,
I am obligated to repay that debt.
Indebted?
When war first broke out 15 years ago,
I came down to Earth as a scout.
There, I was caught in Heaven's Fall
and was mortally wounded.
Amidst that cataclysm where
the Moon was sundered,
the Earth's crust deformed, and there
was nowhere to turn for help,
I was found by your father,
Dr. Troyard, and he saved my life.
Father did that?
I have seen clearly the depths
of your loyalty to the princess.
Your devotion in concealing her survival so
as not to alert the assassins is admirable.
How did you know
that she...?
Count Cruhteo is no traitor.
Quite the contrary, he is a true knight
who has sworn fealty to the princess.
While I am the traitor who
plotted her assassination.
Pay close attention to your surroundings.
Come on, infrared, too.
Keep your guard up.
Yes, ma'am! Three aircraft,
2 o'clock! No IFF signal!
Flagging as hostiles! Almost in
effective weapons range!
Now engaging!
Wow, Inko's good.
She has pretty good instincts.
You here to practice, too, Calm?
I got assigned
to maintenance crew.
For now, maybe.
You mean there might
be an opening?
This is war, after all.
Let me try.
Hey, Sniper Girl.
But I thought you hadn't
had any military training.
I learned from games.
Sim-Kat 10, you mean?
That's such a solid game...
I'm only so-so in live drills,
but I kick ass on that game.
Man, I'm amazed you learned to pilot
the real thing from a game...
The Martians, huh?
They look exactly the same as us Terrans, huh?
You'd never know unless somebody told you.
Inaho's such a jerk. He knew who she
really was, but didn't tell us.
My Nao has grown up, I guess.
I just wish that he had opened up
to his big sister, at least.
Since he met a girl
he likes, and all...
Come again?
What's that supposed
to mean?!
Given the times we live in, a Martian
won't be met with open arms,
but if he marries a princess, my little Nao
would be marrying into serious money!
Is that true?!
Is that what he'll do?!
I don't get that vibe at all.
He never cracks a smile, and he has the
same old grumpy look on his face..
It's totally different.
Really?
I'm family, so I can tell.
I know how he looks when
he's happy, when he's depressed,
and when he's lying.
That is his "I'm on
cloud nine" face.
I dunno...
For starters, that cold fish listening intently
to a girl is unusual in and of itself, right?
Now that is true!
For that boy, it's the ultimate
expression of affection.
Warrant Officer Kaizuka!
May I take a break?
Sure.
Me, too!
May I use the simulator?
Sure, of course.
You don't want to join them?
Can you really tell?
When someone is lying?
Pretty much. I mean, I can tell
from your face that you're lying.
A Martian!
And a princess, to boot!
Guys sure love to try to
tackle a challenge, huh?
But you have a shot, too,
so don't give up. Hang in there.
As a big sister, I love that my little
brother is so popular with the girls.
These are the 26 Landing
Castle drop points
confirmed before contact
was lost with our main force.
However, the Mars Knights
consists of 37 Clans.
There is a possibility that other
Landing Castles have come down.
Given what we've seen,
there is a possibility
that their invasion has
extended to urban areas.
Therefore, we can minimize the
possibility of enemy encounters
by plotting a route through low
population density areas,
avoiding radar, and flying
at low altitude.
Mizusaki.
Ma'am?
Would you like to know
why you can't get a date?
Possibility, possibility, possibility...
If you do nothing but play it safe,
you'll never bump into Mr. Right.
I was given to understand that one
should form a bond first, ma'am.
All right, let's go with your "I want to
make steady progress towards my goal,
even if means holding my nose"
sort of operation.
You don't approve?
No, I think it's
a very simple operation.
She doesn't approve...
Target destroyed.
Okay, simulation complete.
"Rayet," right?
You've got some skills.
Gamers are a formidable bunch.
Increase the difficulty.
Maybe we should call it a day.
I'm fine, keep going.
Okay, then. Why don't I throw in
something we fought recently?
Try this.
Beginning simulation.
Thermal signature detected.
Off my 10 o'clock.
Almost in effective range.
Don't do that, Rayet.
The gun barrel will overheat.
Simulation complete.
I'm sorry. I made it too
hard all of a sudden.
Did it throw you?
Warrant Officer Kaizuka.
Dr. Yagarai.
How is the exoskeleton working?
Wanna arm wrestle?
Thanks, but no.
Actually, would you mind if I borrowed
your simulator program later?
You joining the fight, Doc?
No, it's not for that.
I need it for treatment.
Damn it...
I can't believe our captain turned out
to be your kid sister, Humeray.
Probably explains where
she gets her guts from.
Rayet.
May I join you?
Suit yourself.
Terran food is most delicious. So many
unusual dishes not found on Vers.
Is that optical camouflage, too?
No, Inaho's friend Nina was kind enough
to allow me to borrow these.
She thought it might be difficult to
walk in a cramped ship in that dress.
Isn't she kind?
Highness, this is for you!
How lovely!
A papercraft Terran bird!
Thank you, I shall treasure it.
That was most thoughtful
of you, commoner.
When there is peace between
Earth and Vers,
we shall speak of this to
His Imperial Majesty, and-
Why?
Why did you reveal your identity?
Martians are seen as the enemy.
How can you be so
calm and composed?
Even though you were
betrayed by Martians...
You're crazy, lady.
Mind your tongue! How dare you say
such a thing to Her Highness?
You thought they were
your friends...
Hey, come back here!
This is the problem with Terrans!
How do you feel?
No problem. I'm fine.
I recreated the scene based on
your descriptions, Lt. Marito.
It ought to be close, but if I got
something wrong, please tell me.
Is this really going to help?
PTSD...
One treatment for post-traumatic
stress disorder is to
recreate the incident that caused it
and to relive it again and again.
Relive a terrifying experience often enough
and you get acclimated to it, huh?
We'll just have to see.
Let's begin.
Fine, whatever...
All right, here we go.
Oh, come on... Even games are more
realistic than this these days.
Oh, are they?
But we aren't playing a game.
Uh, this street is flipped.
I'll fix that for next time.
What's that down there?
That's Humeray, your war buddy.
Give me a break. This blocky guy
ain't what's bothering me!
Trust me. Just be quiet
and watch.
Come off it... Are you
messing with me?
What the hell?! That's-
Marito!
What the hell is that?! Nobody said
there was something like that here!
Don't be scared!
We outnumber them!
Platoon Commander to all tanks!
Piecemeal attack!
What the...?
Marito!
That thing's doing this?
It's flying?!
Our shells, they-
Marito!
Anti-gravity? No...
This tank is a lost cause.
We're bailing, Humeray!
I can't...
My legs are pinned!
Fire!
Humeray!
Marito! Get me out, Marito!
Marito! Marito!
Hurry, Marito!
Marito! Shoot me!
Please! Marito!
Hurry! Hurry!
Shoot me! Marito!
Lieutenant! Lt. Marito!
Are you all right, Lieutenant?
Everything you saw
is in the past.
You're safe now.
This isn't Tanegashima.
Like hell we are...
This is a battlefield now, too.
I think that's enough
for today.
Talk about pathetic... Being scared
of that blocky thing.
No, that isn't what
you are afraid of.
It's the fact that you
killed your friend.
This is crazy, this is crazy,
this is crazy...
This is so crazy!
Why did she reveal her identity?
Why is she so calm?
Why? Why? Why?
Why... is she...
Why... am I...
What is the matter?
Not hungry?
Do not worry,
it is not poisoned.
Had I wished to kill you,
I would have done so long ago.
Milord...
Yes?
Why are you so determined
to fight Earth?
It is a lord's duty to his vassals
to fight to expand his territory.
Just for that?
It is that great a cause.
These are creatures that fly
through the air, I understand.
Yes, Milord.
Oh, actually, this type
of bird is flightless.
Unimaginable luxury to
the people of Vers,
who subsist on
chlorella and krill.
I feel nothing but indignation
towards the Terrans who
so offhandedly sent them
as relief supplies.
This is not a luxury item.
It is processed food tailored for
space transport and preservation.
Culture is the sole
domain of Earth,
blessed with abundant water and air,
overflowing with countless living creatures.
On Father Vers, although technology
is advanced thanks to Aldnoah,
culture has not
developed at all.
There is no reason that we should not seize
this world and its plentiful resources.
But even so, surely there is no need
to exploit Princess Asseylum to-
It is too late.
The war has already begun.
Her Highness will be
a human sacrifice.
She is innocent!
She is royalty.
Her very lineage is her crime.
Fifteen years ago, the royal family whipped the
knights into a frenzy and sent them against Earth.
For that, I will make them pay
with their own flesh and blood.
Please don't kill her.
We are a people oppressed under a feudal
system centered around Aldnoah.
Our impoverished, shabby country looks with
scorn upon a world with a vast history.
Such nonsense...
It is only natural that Vers, where the masses
had been controlled by saying,
"Be envious of Earth, be jealous
of Earth, despise Earth,"
is so corrupt that only through invading
Earth can its great cause be maintained.
Your injuries attest
to that all too well.
The royal family chose war.
To maintain order on Vers.
And then... Heaven's Fall came about
as a result of that war,
and my betrothed, Orlane,
lost her life!
This war is my vengeance.
This war is my appointed task.
Defy me, and I will show you no mercy. Even if
you are the son of the man I owe my life to.
I was worried that they would be more hostile
towards us, but it was for nothing.
Yes, I am relieved that the
people of Earth are so kind.
They must understand that you are not
their enemy, but rather a victim.
Deep down, we are all
fellow human beings.
Though our places of birth may differ,
we are capable of mutual understanding.
Some of them are rude
and strange, though...
Oh, my apologies!
I forgot your new clothing!
I'll go fetch it at once!
Oh, that was fast, Eddelri...ttsuo?
Shouldn't you be
with Seylum?
Her name is not "Seylum"!
It is Her Royal Highness Asseylum!
Aldnoah drive, output falling!
Switch to auxiliary power!
Unable to maintain altitude!
Rate of descent increasing!
Impact in 30 seconds!
All hands, brace for impact!