In order to restore my faith in this world,
Let's start a competitive karuta club!
Please come see Ayase Chihaya in class 1-2!!
I have learned to both love
and hate my fellow man
Swift waters parted by the jagged rocks
are joined at river's end
Waves creep closer to the Suminoe shore...
in my dreams, I creep closer to you
Like the sound...
After many, many years...
Look for the sound...
I can't beat Chihaya to the
first-syllable cards.
Reassess the situation...
"Would this" was already read so
I can take "Would the" on the "Would."
"My only thought as I" and "My only thought as the"
are both still in play, so I'll have to be careful there.
"So the flower petals" was already read,
so I can take "So the flower has" after "flower."
"Though my" was already read,
so I can take "Though I" after "Though."
For "While it pains", "While it may" was read,
but "While it brings" wasn't, so I'll have to pay attention.
For "The hazy early morning light",
"The hazy early morning mist" was already read,
so on "The hazy", I'll move towards
"The hazy field" on the opponent's side.
"In the" and "In order to" have already been read,
so I can take "In order for" on "In."
but instead you see a pale
moon in the dawn sky
In order for us to find our way home,
the plum blossoms still smell the same
would I rather never seen her again?
Chihaya doesn't know how to make adjustments
based on which cards have been taken.
I reacted first...
But...
I couldn't take the card...
Chihaya Furu
Verse 7
But for
Autumn's
Coming
Thank you very much.
You're so good, Chihaya-chan!
I see...
I should have passed you the "I know" card,
and then I should have waited before-
Chihaya-chan?!
Oh, don't worry.
She just fell asleep.
J-Just like that?
She just bulls her way through a match
by relying on her fast reflex time,
and I still can't beat her.
What does that mean?
In karuta, it refers to the speed
at which someone reacts to a card being read.
Some people say it's
the most important quality
a karuta player can have.
She was born with it.
Chihaya's karuta is driven
by that innate ability.
Unfortunately, I don't have
anything like that.
Amazing!
Then it's actually possible
for Chihaya-chan to play in
the Queen match wearing
a hakama from our store!
On national TV!
What do you think about this one?
Or would the violet one be better?
Uh, wait...
There are plenty of
better players in Class A.
This one looks better,
but I should choose this one
if I want people to understand
how wonderful kimono are.
Wait, this...
Chihaya and I are on completely different skill levels.
I have no interest in becoming a Master,
so I don't mind losing.
But...
If he were here...
If Chihaya were to practice
with Arata instead of me,
would she become a better player?
I forgot!
I'm gonna go do some scouting!
Scouting?  For a fourth member?
You have someone in mind?
The second-smartest person in our
grade, after Mashima Taichi,
Desktomu-kun, who happens to be in my class!
Huh?
You two can practice!
Oh.
We need five members before we
can become an official club.
If you don't have enough members,
you can't be a club!
Two more to go!
I'm heading out then!
Sure, thanks!
Bye-bye!
Doesn't he creep you out?
School's over and he's still studying.
Look at that Tsutomu-kun...
I mean Desktomu-kun.
He only leaves his desk
to go to the restroom.
Doesn't he look like a jelly bean?
I don't like school.
There are too many judgmental fools.
Okay, solved that problem.
However, I like to study.
The harder I work, the higher
our class's average scores are.
I'm willing to help out those fools.
But it's kinda sad when he's
glued to his desk all day and
only second in our grade.
I know.
When you put it that way,
Mashima-kun from Class 1 is really something.
He doesn't study much,
yet he's top of the class!
I wish we could arrange a trade.
I'd rather have a number one stud
than number two Desktomu-kun.
I know, right?
Is he upset?
Nah, no way...
Really?
Heya!  I'm Ayase Chihaya!
I'm here to scout you!
Let's play karuta together
in the karuta club!
Consider this a bribe.
Hey, Komano-kun.  You're the second-smartest
person in our grade, right?!
I've heard that karuta is a
great sport for smart people!
If you join, we'll have four members
and be one member closer to
becoming an official club!
It doesn't matter if you
don't have any experience!
I don't understand.
Oh, karuta as in Hundred Poets.
Is there any point to playing karuta?
Can you become number one by playing karuta?
Um...
There's no such thing as
professional karuta, is there?
It's just a game, right?
Why should I play this game?
Will it help me with my studies?
Is there any benefit for me?
I don't care about your excuses!
Stop griping and play a game!
Jam Bread
The field of play is supposed
to be 87 centimeters wide.
You can use your elbow plus or minus
a number of cards as a reference,
so remember how many cards
it takes to get you to 87.
Hey!  This is embarrassing!
Shut up!  Just come inside!
Huh?
Hey, guys!
Let's teach him how fun karuta can be!
Huh?
Don't be ridiculous!
You dragged me all the way here by force!
But!
I understand.
The karuta club is short on members, yes?
So you just need to bolster head count.
Look elsewhere, if you don't care who joins.
You've got it wrong.
I do care who joins!
Liar.
I'm telling the truth!
Just play a game!
I promise that you'll be hooked!
I'm busy!
If I had time to play karuta,
I would be studying instead!
Komano-kun, you want to
become smarter, right?
Huh?
Karuta is a mental game.
First, you have to memorize
the positions of the cards.
The fastest people can memorize all
of them in five- no, three minutes!
Stronger memorization skills will
help you with your studies!
Memorize the positions?
Of every card?
Uh-huh.
Liar!
I'm not lying!
This is the most basic step!
No grace...
I'll show you right now!
Wait!
Hey, wait!
Why me?
Taichi, let's play!
Wait, what?
Huh?
Hurry up!
Fine then.
Mashima Taichi...
He's had the top score
on every monthly test.
The players get memorization
time, so hold on.
The match will begin in 15 minutes.
W-Wait...
Huh?
Memorization is the most basic step, right?
If karuta players all have excellent memory,
you should be able to play
with the cards flipped over!
What?!
This isn't Concentration!
Plus, the cards get moved around.
It's impossible!
I knew it.
So you're given memorization time,
and you still can't do it.
Nothing impressive about that.
Goodbye.
Wait!  Don't leave!
We'll give it a try, so wait!
Chihaya!
Who is this annoying brat?
You're the one who said that we
should look for someone smart!
Someone smart?
But I've never played karuta
with the cards flipped over.
Same here!
But I can't back down now!
Mizusawa
Very well.
I will play in your stead!
It's okay, Oe-san.
Chihaya, let's give it a try.
Huh?  Is it okay, Taichi?
We won't know where the cards are
if you send them all flying,
so control yourself.
Uh-huh.
Would the, May you, A night,
As friends, My only thought as the,
Impassionate,
In order for, My own home, The emotions,
A mountain stream, So spring nights,
The storm will,
As the first, Impassioned was, As my
The autumn paddy, I know, The sight,
No more, So the flower petals, A house,
Memorization time is over.
While some, May the scarlet, Since I...
Please flip the cards over.
They won't be able to play flipped karuta.
It's impossible to memorize the positions
for all of those cards in 15 minutes.
Impossible...
Let's begin.
Naniwa Bay, now the flower blooms,
but for winter
Here comes spring, now the flower blooms
May the solitary night spent together
"Bring a life..."
It's the right card!
While some dodge the famous waves of
Takashi shore to avoid getting wet,
"I deflect your..."
It's right!
Our memory is still fresh at the beginning.
The cards may be flipped over,
but we should be able to find most of them.
The problem is later when the cards
start getting passed around.
It all comes down to concentration.
I deflect your artful words
to keep my sleeves dry
My own home is a retreat lying
southeast of the capital
That's the right card.
Now I'm mad.
I memorized that card.
Chihaya doesn't have her usual edge.
She's not as confident.
It's because her memorization skills are still lacking.
I-I can beat Chihaya...
Um, that one is "So spring ends"...
Then it's "No more, As friends,
While it brings, As my, None are."
I'm going to move a card.
Huh?
What?!
Hold on!  Hold on!
What was that card?!
where I can hide from the
troubles of this world
A mountain village grows...
Swift waters parted...
are joined at river's end
This isn't the Taichi I'm
used to practicing against.
are joined at river's end
May you never forget your...
Impassioned was your promise of salvation
He was guarding both cards!
We're over halfway through and he can still
remember the positions of the cards!
May the time we spend
apart from one another be
I-It's right!
as short-lived as the reeds of Naniwa Bay
I have no interest in becoming a Master,
so I don't mind losing...
I don't mind losing...
As the first frost has fallen,
I definitely hate to lose!
Chihaya!
I'm the one sitting across
from you right now!
He did it!
Thank you very much.
I'm so mad...
I win.
Wait.
You're just going to leave without
a word after that match?
Oh, er...
What's your name?
Why...
do people like him exist?
Ah, hey!
He has friends, talent...
Whose are those?  Desktomu-kun's?
They're perfect!
Lemme see!
Me too!
Thanks, Desktomu-kun!
Make sure you get the top
score on the next test.
The top score...
Become number one...
Win...
But I know...
Even if I do become number one,
they'll never let me in their circle.
Hey, if you're a little interested now,
why not join the karuta club?
I can't play karuta...
I don't have the talent!
I'm not like you!
All I can do is study!
I belong behind my desk!
Focus on contests that you can win.
I could spend my entire youth on karuta
without ever becoming better than Arata.
I don't have any talent for karuta either.
It's tough, but I still play!
I keep losing, but I still play!
Because when I win...
I feel so happy!
Okay, that was lame.
But...
Instead of a karuta genius,
I would rather have our new member
be someone who puts
in effort on the tatami.
Wh-What are you talking about?
Tatami?  Karuta?
That doesn't make any sense at all!
Man, look at my desk...
I see.
Sorry about that.
It's tough, but I still play!
I keep losing, but I still play!