Forever... Forever...
The first day I touched you,
my heart pounded so hard.
So that's why I decided
in my heart to follow you.
The scent of the flowers and wind,
the smell of this soup...
It doesn't matter if they disappear,
as long as I can be with you.
I could hear the sound
of this tiny hope growing.
A New Journey
I can hear the song of love...
I wish Minori could've come.
She's working at Karashin's place.
Miss Minori is a working lady.
"A working lady"?
Is that something people normally say?
Miss Isuzu,
are you okay?
Are you tired?
No, I'm fine.
I'm full of energy.
Really?
Yeah.
That was really amazing, though.
You really seemed like a pro!
Aw, stop.
The owner was really happy.
He looked like he was glad
he asked you to do it.
Don't make it sound like such a big deal.
It's basically a once-a-week part-time job.
And the song was just a cover of
something I heard a long time ago...
But everyone looked truly happy listening to you.
That's right.
Miss Isuzu is such a great artist,
she must have a muse.
Give it a rest.
That was nothing.
I just know a little bit because I've always had
instruments in my house since I was little.
Your sweet melodies bring life
to the city streets at night,
and your dazzling voice brings peace to
the hearts of even birds and beasts.
Honestly, Rudy...
What's wrong with saying it was great,
when it was great?!
Shut up, Rudy!
What's wrong with it?
What's wrong with it?!
First Order of Knights of the People of the Land
Drill Guidelines
A quest?
Yes, I plan to send Tohya and
the other new members on it.
And I'd like Serara to go, too.
If she's okay with it, that's just fine with me.
But what quest?
This.
A magic bag?
Yes.
Dazaneg's Magic Bag.
I want them to get the materials for it.
Oh, "Get the Magic Bag," right?
The one where you hunt the mini-wyverns.
They've reached the minimum
level required for it.
I see.
They're already above level 45.
Tohya seems to want to go.
He keeps bringing it up.
I'm sure they want one.
It's convenient, since it holds everything.
I don't think that's all it is.
I think they actually want to try
a real quest, all by themselves.
But will they be okay on their own?
Excuse me.
I thought you might be tired.
Thanks.
Are you done working at Karashin's place?
Yes.
Thanks.
Oh, great timing, actually.
Everyone complimented me,
but I'm not that good.
It's always been my friend...
No one ever told me my music was bad.
But no one ever told me it was good, either.
But even if I can't be a pro like you, Dad,
I can at least play the lute once in a
while to blow off steam, right?
Because...
It makes everyone happy.
Why are you grinning like that?
Huh?
No way... I was grinning?
You were.
You still feel great after that concert, huh?
I guess.
Me, too.
I never imagined myself on
the stage, playing drums.
You were really good.
Aw, you're flattering me.
Anyway, bards are amazing.
You have an aura that makes even someone
like me able to play, just by being near you.
But you know, it seems you need
musical sense for it to work.
I tried asking Rudy, but...
How's this, Miss Isuzu?
It's great, right?
How about this?
Oh, my God! My hand's stuck!
I can imagine...
But that just means you have
really good musical sense.
That's not true.
I've just been used to music
ever since I was a kid.
You know...
I played soccer.
I practiced a lot,
but I was no match for the guys
who were really good.
You can tell when someone's a natural.
Even when you're a kid.
But even if I sucked, it was fun.
You have fun playing music, too, right?
Yeah.
You like it, right?
And you get to keep doing it, so it's great!
Do you remember what happened just
after we were saved from Hamelin?
We stayed with the Crescent
Moon Alliance for a while,
but you two had already decided
to come to this guild, right?
But I was suddenly free,
and I had no idea what to do.
And then I found this lute.
With the dolphin pattern lacquered on...
It was so beautiful.
I knew it was something Marielle
had made long ago,
so I asked her to let me have it.
And then I made a bunch of adjustments,
and now it's my own personal instrument,
the Flying Dolphin.
Thanks to this, I...
Well, how to say it...
It gave me the drive to keep going.
I'm happy I can keep playing music.
Tohya?
Isuzu?
Oh, Minori?
You're back.
Tohya! Isuzu!
Shiroe wants to talk to us.
A journey!
An adventure! A quest!
Mt. Fuji                                                    Akihabara
The Redstone Mountains are near Nagano, right?
Redstone Mountains
Mountains, rivers, forests!
And villages we've never been to!
Tohya, stop staring at the map,
and pack two more pairs of underwear.
There's no room for all that.
We don't have our magic bags yet.
If you want to know about traveling,
ask me, Rundel Haus Code.
That's right, you used to travel alone.
Indeed.
Until partway, I was with other adventurers,
but I came all the way from Bogport
to Akihabara on my own.
So I have plenty of experience.
Huh?
What's wrong?
My very important brush is missing!
I can't maintain my appearance
as an adventurer without it!
My elegant, flowing hair!
Rudy?
Here.
It's in your toiletries set.
Miss Isuzu!
You're so wonderful!
Come on, clean all this up.
You guys ready?
We're in perfect shape, Master!
Good.
Put a barrel of water on the carriage.
We know.
Okay, good.
Making progress, everyone?
Wh-When did you get in...
You little—
If you want any advice from me, just ask.
I'm an idol who travels the whole galaxy!
I told you to get off me!
Oh, come on, Naotsugu...
You know you love it—
I do not!
What's with everyone?
They're worried about us.
They really care about us a lot, huh?
Everyone always looks out for us.
Yeah, but they try not to let
us know they're doing it.
It's kind of tiring, knowing they're
looking out for us all the time.
Hey, want to bet on who comes next?
Nyanta!
I think it'll be Shiroe—
Preparations going well?
You win.
Is something wrong?
N-Nothing.
Um, I think we'll be done packing soon.
Then we'll split up and go shopping,
pick up a carriage and weapons...
Nyanta's going to come and
help us choose a carriage.
I see.
I made this. It's a little more detailed.
Bye!
Okay, let's finish here and go shopping.
Yeah!
Hey, stop staring at the map.
Amenoma
Welcome.
Hi, there!
Once we have weapons, then we'll need armor.
We'll have to make a few more stops.
I can tell you're a samurai!
You look great with a katana.
I wanted to take this opportunity
to get a new one,
but at my level, there aren't
too many I can use...
How about caltrop?
Don't you think trying a ninja's
weapon would be interesting?
Looking for weapons?
Akatsuki brought me along with her.
You could go with shurikens, too.
Yeah, shurikens are a choice for a ranged weapon
that can be used regardless of class.
Kunai are valuable ones, too.
I'd recommend the ones on the wall there.
They're easy to use in a variety of situations.
Oh, um...
Well, no matter how good your weapon is,
in the end, it's all about your heart and body.
Listen! When the time comes, a man
needs to put his body on the line.
Right!
I know, Master!
And when even that's not enough,
remember this! Pant—
So cute!
Please do not blow the flutes inside the store!
These flutes are the ones that summon horses.
But wow, look at all the animals you can summon.
Everything from dangerous beasts to pets.
Ew! You can summon rats and snakes, too.
What about the griffon? The one Shiroe has?
You need to do a special quest to get those,
for things like a griffon or pegasus.
A pegasus, huh?
I want a pegasus.
If I could ride on one with him...
Meow.
A pegasus?
That's right.
I risked my life on a quest to get it for you.
You're so wonderful, Nyanta!
We'll ride it together.
Call it.
Okay!
No!
No way!
There are actually a lot of different
types of carriages, aren't there?
Wow!
This one looks really tough!
It has fire, cold, and electricity
resistances at rank 80.
I want this one!
But it's expensive, right?
Here.
Let's go see the next one, Tohya!
That's kind of weird-looking.
Well, the people who make
these are quite hardcore.
This is it!
This gorgeous, fit-for-a-celeb feeling...
It's truly the perfect carriage for me,
a noble and great adventurer!
It's as though it was made just for me!
This doggy is all screwed up.
Well, this looks like a reasonable choice.
Yeah, it looks good.
Yep.
You have excellent taste.
It's simple, but the chassis and suspension
are made in an interesting way.
It's lightweight but tough, and the gyration
radius of the front wheels—
But it's expensive, right?
Leave the negotiations to me.
Nyanta showed me this great ramen place...
I'll do what I can.
All right!
Does that taste good, Danish? Croissant?
Those names sound like something
Serara would think up.
Want to give them cabbage, too, Isuzu?
Sure, I do.
You, too, Rudy.
That is no longer amusing to me.
Just so we're clear, I'm a pro at handling horses.
Come on!
They're our companions from now on, after all!
Now, now, you shouldn't
scream like that, Miss Isuzu
Horses are easy to spook.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Apologize properly.
I-I'm sorry!
You apologize, too.
Why do I—
Forgive me...
Forgive me, horsey!
Okay!
It's done!
I like it.
It's cool.
I'll draw a picture to finish it off!
J-Just a giraffe...
Tonight's dinner was specially made by Serara.
Nyanta taught me how to cook,
so I'll do the cooking on our journey.
You look good in that Newlywed's Apron Dress.
I tried it, too, but when you wear it,
you really look like a newlywed.
A-A-Aw...
N-N-Newlywed!
Safe.
Let's eat!
Delicious!
You're right.
I was feeling kind of bad that I couldn't eat
Nyanta's cooking while we were on our trip.
Yeah, this'll do just fine!
Meow.
Anyway, isn't it kind of a shame for you, Isuzu?
Why?
During the trip, you won't be
able to play your concerts.
Yeah, but the trip itself is like a tour, so it's fun.
A tour?
That's when a musician goes on a trip to perform.
Yeah! I can go "dum da-da dum" on the carriage!
Oh! A tour!
We can do performances as we travel!
Yeah!
That's nice! A tour!
A touring trip around the galaxy!
I'm the galactic idol!
You're going beyond Izu.
Everyone join in with me, Tetra!
A tour, huh? Amazing.
Will you go around to villages,
doing the forty-two?
Forty-two?
I don't think there are that
many villages on the way.
No, the forty-two is...
There are about four or five villages
between here and the Redstone Mountains.
Awesome!
Let's visit the villages and perform!
We'll need to visit them for
water and stuff, anyway!
That's okay, isn't it, Shiroe?
Of course.
Just don't get too out of control.
If anything happens, contact us—
No, if you can, I think you should avoid telepathy.
Why?
Worry about things and solve them
yourselves, as much as you can.
Journeys like this are a good chance to learn that.
Go and see a lot of different worlds,
and enjoy a lot of different things.
Okay!
Allow me to be your guide and lead this tour.
Yeah!
A tour is also a valuable experience!
Let's do our best, Isuzu!
Aren't you happy?
I'm happy...
Of course I'm happy!
I'm going to stock up on spare strings!
Let go, Miss Isuzu! That hurts!
I can't wait!
Maybe I should get the more expensive strings!
Goodbye!
Remember to keep your weapons maintained.
If you get lonely, remember me and blush!
Take care.
It's finally time.
Yeah.
Our journey is beginning.
Our tour is beginning.
Our adventure is beginning!
We're on our way, Shiroe!
We're going to see a lot of different worlds!
Let's go!
To the west!
Minori and the others enjoy their journey.
Fun things, hard things...
Everything they encounter in
this new world is exciting.
But an uneasy mood gradually overtakes them.
A mysterious person appears before them.
It's a new person in glasses.
Next time: The Midday Vampire.
The Midday Vampire
I have friends to run with me?