Let's go to the beach sometime.
The sound of
waves makes me feel a bit tingly.
We should get going.
Yeah.
Episode 7
"Bicycle"
Morning.
I'm coming in.
Oh.
Sleeping outside?
You've liked girls before, too, haven't you?
I never thought of it as anything
more than a weird feeling.
I surprised myself.
I'm surprised you'd like such a simple girl.
Don't look down on me.
I wouldn't.
Hopefully you won't need us anymore.
I don't hate you guys.
All I can hear
is your voice.
I keep seeing you, too.
Touko, Yana-chan is here.
Yana-chan?
Yeah? So what's the event?
Fifty-meter freestyle.
I just hit 32 seconds the other day.
My goal is 31 seconds flat.
You're really going for it, Hina-chan!
You're working toward your
dream job as a model, too, right?
I've secretly been rooting for you.
You sure do have a nice body.
I'm jealous.
Thanks.
Let's go shopping for clothes sometime.
I'll help you choose.
Really? You would? Yes, please!
Touko.
Sorry for just showing up.
Let's talk outside.
See you soon, Hina-chan.
Okay.
About Yuki-kun the other day...
That slap of yours...
It's okay. I didn't like
what Kakeru-kun did either.
Kakeru-kun, huh?
What?
Whatever. You make yourself so obvious.
I do?
Yeah.
Yuki's so stupid.
Can't he tell he doesn't stand a chance?
Did you hear Sachi is staying
at the hospital today?
Yeah, for tests.
Nothing to worry about then, I guess.
We should hold back on the visits,
so we don't get in the way.
Yeah,
let's not get in the way
of their secret dates.
Sacchan's fine. It looks
like she's doing well.
Huh?
Oh, no, I think she'd be happy if we visited.
Yeah, it's me.
Sure.
See you later.
Everyone's so scattered lately.
It's been a bit weird, ever
since that David showed up.
Ready.
Here's your cola.
Visiting hours at the hospital
end so early.
I wish they'd let us stay till 10 PM at least.
Your pianist hands are so strong.
Here comes a crescendo!
Ow, ow, ow!
Fortissimo!
Ow!
I'll be going now, too.
Call me if there's anything you need.
Okay.
Oh?
Come in.
Oh...
Your friend?
My boyfriend, Hiro-kun.
Oh?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Sachi's mother.
I'm Sacchan's b-b-boyfriend,
Hiro Shirosaki.
My grandpa made these cookies.
Thanks.
Hey.
I didn't know there was
a swallow's nest here.
Hey, hatchlings.
Looks like it.
I know there are at least two.
You know, I've lived here all this time,
but you seem to know so
much more about this place.
That makes me a little unhappy.
Knowing a few small things about this city
doesn't compare to you having lived here.
Huh? That's not true.
You're amazing, Kakeru-kun.
I made a fool of myself.
That's not true.
Yana-chan came over today.
We talked about yesterday.
You certainly are friends.
Um, what are we,
you and I?
Sorry.
Now I can't look at you.
Have we become more than
just two people who share a weird ability?
Look out!
I saw you falling.
You'll be okay as long as
we stay like this, right?
The future can't be changed.
Let's go to the beach.
It's safer.
The beach tomorrow. For sure.
What are you looking at?
Here he comes.
Oh?
There he is, right on time.
He's coming, the 5:30 guy.
He's so amazing.
That's my sister's friend.
Really?
You know him? Have you talked to him?
I haven't.
Really? That's a shame.
He's just so hot.
I know.
But I heard he's kind of in a mess.
What's wrong?
Hey there.
Coach.
You've been training, huh?
Your record at the track
meet—I'm impressed.
It was so bad.
No, it wasn't.
Call me if you want to talk about anything.
Oh, I have summer camp for a week
starting the day after tomorrow.
I'd prefer if you could call
me before or after that.
Working hard first thing in
the morning, huh, Onee-san?
You're keeping up well
with your club work, too.
Hey.
I saw Yukinari-san yesterday.
From our pool we can
see him on his routine run.
I don't really get it,
but he's kind of our club's idol.
They're talking about making
a fan club and stuff.
Wow! That's Yuki-kun.
Small world, huh?
Yuki-kun's hot.
I'm not surprised.
True, he looked good running.
Yeah, Yuki-kun is good-looking.
Onee-chan, did something happen?
Why? Nothing.
You're such a bad liar.
Um... I'm going to go visit Sacchan.
I have to go, too.
My tests are starting soon.
Oh, really?
I'll get going, then.
Thanks for coming every day.
Sure.
Bye.
Nee-chan.
Yes?
I'm coming in.
Welcome.
How are you? Doing okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Oh, that's—
Wait, let me guess.
A gift from Hiro-kun.
Right?
Right.
Kakeru-kun?
Oh, um, Okikura-kun.
Yeah.
So Kakeru-kun
said something a bit nasty.
Yana-chan heard him, and...
When?
Tomorrow afternoon.
Ah. I heard the weather
will be nice tomorrow, too.
I thought maybe if we went to
the beach together tomorrow...
What?
Yeah,
I thought maybe I might see something new.
"Something"? Those sparkly things?
I think being with Kakeru-kun,
I'm starting to understand what those are.
I'll let you know when I have a better idea.
Okay.
What?
Where're you going?
The coach is coming.
Hina.
Hi again.
I'm Touko Fukami's sister, Hina Fukami.
Hey, um...
please stay attractive.
Please stay attractive.
Is it not the future?
What's wrong, Sacchan? It's so late.
I want to go to the beach.
I'm being discharged tomorrow.
Let's all go in the afternoon.
I want to see Yukinari-kun
and Yanagi-chan, too.
And I want to light fireworks at night.
Okay. Sounds good.
I know it's short notice,
but I'll let Touko-chan know.
Got it.
I'll tell Yanagi-san and Yukinari.
What'll you have?
You never replied to my message
about going to the beach.
You can make it, right?
Yanagi-san said she can come.
Ah.
Don't "ah" me!
Are you okay?
What the heck, man?
He's going to the beach with his
girlfriend today, right? How nice...
He's grown up to be a weird kid.
Oh? I think he's a charming young man.
That doesn't sound like
something a mother would say.
So, about that thing—
The tests got delayed.
She's staying until tomorrow.
Is that so?
Sachi, I'm positive I told you yesterday.
Is that right?
Goodness.
You're causing trouble for Mr. Boyfriend, too.
No, what trouble?
You said "Mr. Boyfriend"?
Okay, I understand.
Bye.
Well, I'm going home now.
Okay.
Sorry.
Take care of Sachi, please.
Right!
I should text everyone to let
them know we're canceling.
I hate David.
You do? Why?
Everyone gets split up when he's here.
True, everyone's kind of scattered lately.
Oh, so should we move the beach to tomorrow?
Touko-chan has a date at
Hinode Beach with David.
So I never contacted Touko-chan.
Oh.
But wouldn't that mean
you tried to get everyone to ruin
David's date with Touko,
just because you hate him?
Yeah.
It would.
So you called me to get me to do that?
Sacchan, that's so...
I'm going home for today.
Over here!
Hiro.
I'll give you a ride.
Sure.
Sorry, can't make it today.
Oh.
Okay, I'll pass it on.
We're not doing the beach trip today.
Did you hear me?
Did you wait long?
I don't mind waiting.
So you did wait.
Is it tingly?
What?
The sound of the waves.
It feels a bit different from before.
I don't know that I've ever
come at this time of day.
This is for you.
Glass beads.
They match.
Thanks.
There's something that's been bothering me.
You said I would fall.
I did. Don't ever go anywhere high!
Do you really think that's possible?
To put it bluntly,
I can never
go anywhere I might fall from.
That's impossible.
Then what can we do?
Are they really fragments of the future?
But—
But you're the one that told me so.
We should think it over a bit more carefully.
I'm going to go buy juice!
Kakeru-kun, what would you like?
I'll have water.
As a kid, I used to wonder why grown-ups pay
money to buy water and tea
from vending machines.
There's Halpis Water right next to it.
Oh, so you were invited, too.
Isn't Touko with you?
She went to get something to drink.
Oh. Now's a good time to tell you, then.
It's your fault Yuki
isn't attractive anymore.
Sorry to interrupt.
I'll be going.
Hey.
You're a cute couple.
No!
Touko!
I'm going to get a proper explanation.
I think I won't ask.
Touko, what's wrong? What did you see?
I think I want to visit Jonathan.
Episode 8
"Snow"