The weather's so nice again today.
That's right.
Leo-sama. Nanami-san.
Good morning.
Indeed.
Violet-san, good morning!
That's a lot of paperwork!
Yup.
This is the list of participants
for the upcoming annual event.
Looks like we've got a lot again this year.
It's a wonderful thing.
Event?
Some kind of festival?
Oh, this is for my arranged
marriage meetings.
All these people want to marry Leo-sama.
I see.
An arranged marriage, huh?
An arranged marriage?!
The Lion's Arranged Marriage
Leo-sama's meeting with potential husbands?
Yup.
You come, too. It's fun.
I can watch?
Sure.
Actually, invitations should've gone to
the Princess and your knights.
Noir and I are going to
be doing the commentary.
Commentary?
Yup.
We've got a lot of people
here this year, too.
25% more than last year, it seems.
Merchandise and concession
sales are doing well.
It's a good thing.
It's thanks to everyone.
Well, there's a lot of things
I could say about it,
but it's a wonderful way to earn money.
It's time, everybody!
At the mics today we've got Framboise
Charley from Galette National Broadcasting,
and Jean Casoni!
And providing commentary is...
Crown prince of Galette,
Gaul Galette des Rois
and Noir, the center of the Imperial
Guard Unit "Genoise".
Thanks for having us here today.
Lady Leonmitchelli, one of the most powerful
and beautiful women on the continent:
there are no shortage of men
who want to marry her.
And there's only one thing
she has to say to them.
I want you to fight me one
on one, and defeat me!
I, Leonmitchelli, will accept
a challenge from anyone.
If you want a shot at
marrying me, come get me!
Chosen warriors from
every nation have appeared to battle her.
They all look strong.
And they're all looking at...
There she is!  Lady Leo!
I am Leonmitchelli Galette des Rois!
I'm happy you've all come here
today to try and marry me.
People older and younger than me,
knights and nobles, royals and citizens.
Men of many positions are here,
but you have only thing you must do!
Defeat me!
I promise to give marriage
proposals from those who
defeat me top priority and
serious consideration!
This is an arranged marriage?
It seems like how she'd do it, I guess.
I was surprised, too.
Well, it's pretty strange, but...
The fact that it's a worthwhile
commercial enterprise
is what makes Leo-sama amazing.
Yup.
What's wrong, Vert?
No. It's nothing.
Okay, it's time for our first fight!
The challenger is a young knight
from the land of Orange, here for
his second time, Lord Raymond!
In the war game a few days ago,
he succeeded in defeating 500 enemies!
Lady Leo, let us fight!
Yes, come!
Please go out with me,
and hopefully marry me!
I'm moved and grateful for your request.
But...
You're not there yet!
Here I go!
He's down!
Down! Lord Raymond was wiped out instantly!
Lord Raymond's a strong knight, but...
It's amazing he was able to
even take the first blow.
So true.
Lady Leo is praising him for
his excellent fighting.
Lady Leo is wonderful!
Isn't she?
Round two!
Defense Minister of the country of
Dragée, and master of the long sword,
Lord Belier, has come to the fight today!
Lady, please come with me this year.
Once again, I'm honored by your request.
But...
I will win you with this blade!
The battle begins!
National Defense Blade:
Dragon King's Rage Slash!
Lord Belier's crest blade!
The dragon's aura is attacking Lady Leo!
I just fought a dragon a few days ago
and your vigor matches
that of a true dragon!
Lion King Roaring Thunder Blade!
Exploding Lightning Fang!
The fight is over!
Lady Leo strikes with
one slash of her blade!
Lord Belier is down!
Leo-sama is so cool!
Next up is the incredibly
strong leader of the knights
from the Dukedom of Camibel.
Lord Dorg!
His massive strength and
specially-ordered axe
are said to be able to destroy a fortress!
Here I come.
Lord Dorg.
You've gotten even stronger, it seems.
I'm so happy and grateful you said that!
But it's
not enough yet!
She was every bit as strong
as the massive Lord Dorg.
Our leader's got incredible strength.
She won't lose in a contest of strength.
Our fourth fighter is General Alfried
from Eldonia in the West!
I'll share my burning love with you!
And General Blood, also from Eldonia!
Winner of a thousand battles
in his own country's coliseum!
Lady, this year...
Leader of Lagunia's assault forces
and master of martial arts,
it's Lord Deen!
The swordsman Miyama from
Hinoura in the east!
Lady Leo keeps winning!
She's not letting any of
her suitors get near!
Oh, we've got a message from the VIP seats!
Hi!
Yup!
Leo-sama keeps winning!
If you're too strong,
you'll never find anybody to marry you.
Nobody's asking you.
They're all such fierce opponents that
I'm truly enjoying myself.
It's great fun to be able to
fight without holding back.
I'm grateful to every one of my suitors!
There are only a few suitors left!
Who's next?
Thank you for having me here.
Maybe I shouldn't be talking,
but the next fighter is really tiny.
Where'd he come from?
The next challenger has asked that
their name and nationality...
be kept secret.
I'm sorry.
I'm the one who said I'd
accept anyone's challenge.
It's fine.
So your weapons are a sword and...
Is that a crossbow?
Yes.
Then I'll fight you with
a short bow and a sword.
Thank you very much.
Hey, Gaul-sama. Is that...
Yup. Seems like it.
Now let the games begin!
First they'll be fighting with the bow.
Both of them are quietly
drawing their bows...
That was...
He's fast!
I couldn't follow that at all.
Leo-sama got a hit in when
she was shot, didn't she?
Yeah.
That probably saved her
from a second attack.
He might be really good.
Yeah, they're amazing!
There aren't that many fighters this
good in the countries around us.
If they're hiding their name and
face, they must be someone I know,
but I can't figure out who.
Have you and I met before?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I just can't seem to remember.
If I win, I'll tell you.
I see.
But I don't enjoy fighting when
something's bothering me.
I'm knocking off
that cloak.
Aerial
Explosive Slash!
Oh, wow!
I suppose we should've guessed!
The challenger is a young boy!
He's really cute.
Hey, isn't that...
He's got the same ears and tail as you?
Is that...
Yup.
The 8th Prince of my homeland, Halver.
Leaf Lang du Sha Halver!
I remember!
We have met before!
I helped you practice with
the bow and sword, too.
You were such a little kid,
but you were always serious
about your training.
Even if we haven't had much of a chance to
see each other over the past few years,
I've never forgotten you.
But I'm sorry... you'd grown up so strong
I didn't realize it was you.
Thank you.
But I still have a lot of growing up to do,
both physically and in my training!
Prince Gaul, Noir-san,
who is that?
The 8th Prince of the northern
country of Sankt Halver.
He's a distant relative of our Vert.
That's right, Vert-san is
also from Halver, isn't she?
I'd heard he'd been practicing
his sword and archery,
but I never thought he'd get that strong.
And I'm really surprised he's
one of Leo-sama's suitors.
This brings back so many memories.
What were we talking about when we last met?
You showed me the path I should travel!
You're really growing up.
You should keep learning from the
knights of your country and train every day.
Okay!
You've got such a pretty face.
If you get stronger, I'm sure
the girls will love you.
Really?
What?
Do you have a girl you're in love with?
No, well...
It's okay. That's healthy.
Get strong and tell that
girl what you think of her.
Will she love me back?
Sure!
If you're a strong, kind, and smart adult,
I'm sure she will.
Oh, I remember
that now!
But if you're here...
A romance with a childhood friend!
Prince Leaf is so wonderful!
That's right!
Um, so that's why
I was hiding my name and appearance.
So you didn't have to think about
anything else during the fight.
I-I see...
Thank you for your kindness.
If I win, there's a lot I want to tell you.
I'd love to hear it,
but sadly it won't be happening this year.
Because I'm going to win!
What's this?
Both of them are ready to end the
fight with their best moves!
The next strike will likely end the battle!
Exploding Heat Dragon Slash!
That's right. That's the
kind of tactic I like!
A huge explosion!
Their attacks collided
and there was a huge explosion!
Who will still be standing?
Wh-What's this?
The prince couldn't match Lady Leo!
But he fought a
great battle and almost won!
Well done. I'm grateful.
Thank you.
I won't praise you
and tell you you've gotten stronger.
I must get stronger so I won't lose to you.
Then I'll get even stronger.
Everybody, give them another
big round of applause!
I-I didn't expect this!
Lady Leo's armor was
this close to being completely destroyed.
Um...
What is going on here?
An after party for the
arranged marriage games.
A place for ladies and gentlemen to meet
and get to know each other, I'm told.
It's also a place for people of other
countries to get to know each other.
And it's a great place for young people
to meet new romantic encounters.
We're going
to see the princess, okay?
I'm not good with parties.
I'm more interested in
food than meeting men.
I want to go with you.
Me, too!
That's not fair, Yukki, Rico!
You come with us, too, Hero!
Everybody!
Hero!
I've seen the broadcasts of your activities!
And you were amazing today, Prince Leaf!
You were so cool!
Really!
Thank you.
It's amazing how strong you are,
but it's also amazing that you
decided to come here today!
It's wonderful that you're
thinking about marriage
at such a young age.
Marriage? I don't really
know what that is,
but I wanted to be able to talk to Leo-sama,
so I joined today.
Huh, Leaf?
You didn't want to marry Leo-sama?
At an arranged marriage
you spend a lot of time
talking to somebody in
a quiet place, right?
No!
An arranged marriage meeting is the
first step to a marriage, and...
No, well...
I can't believe I did that in
front of all those people!
Well, it's okay.
It's true that you like Leo-sama.
And Leo-sama seemed to like you, too.
Yup, yup!
Prince!
Oh no!
We need to let him lie down.
That's one more thing to look forward to.
It was another wonderful arranged
marriage meeting this year.
Leaf, I'm looking forward
to the day you defeat me!
Um, I'll do my best.
The Little Prince and
the Legendary Hero
Do your best, Leaf!