A request?
For me?
I'm so happy for you, Iris.
Your destination is Kazalli.
Kazalli?
That's my hometown!
Oh, that's right.
Who is the client?
It's a woman in her 40s named
Sarah Florent. Do you know her?
No, I don't.
All right!
To commemorate Iris'
very first commission,
let's all get lunch.
I'm the only one in my village
who became a Doll.
I wonder if she heard about me
from someone.
I'm just happy to be able to go home
and show off this uniform.
I know all my friends and family
are going to want to come see me.
Careful not to get carried away.
Remember that you are representing
the CH Postal Company--
I know that!
I believe that was a disingenuous answer.
What? What did you just...?
We've received so many
voting letter requests lately.
Well, I suppose it is the first election
since the war.
With the House of Lords making moves,
I'm sure the House of Commons
candidates are desperate.
Do you think the two of them will be okay?
I have the worst luck.
It would've been a great opportunity
to show off my impeccable typing skills.
There is no need to worry.
I will be typing for you.
That's not the point.
Kazalli is a village half-way
up the mountain
whose main industries
are dairy and agriculture.
There are no other particular
characteristics or history to mention.
-Sorry we don't have much going for us.
-There is nothing wrong with that.
When there is something of value,
it attracts crime and trouble.
Northern Leidenschaftlich
had iron and copper ore deposits,
which enticed the Gardarik Empire
to attack.
Right.
And that's what caused the war.
My uncle said he would volunteer to fight,
but my aunt was against it.
So, he ended up not enlisting.
Which kept him safe, thankfully.
Sorry.
What was that apology for?
Because you ended up injured.
Why are you responsible for my injury?
I might not be responsible, but...
An apology is admitting responsibility
and asking for forgiveness.
Okay, I get it.
Times like this and when I first met her,
I could never fully understand...
who Violet Evergarden was.
LEIDENSCHAFTLICH
KAZALLI
It's so much more humid than Leiden.
Aren't you hot in that?
It is not a problem. I am accustomed
to these temperatures.
All right then.
Iris!
Welcome home!
Welcome back!
I'm glad you made it.
Mom, Dad! Uncle and Auntie, too!
What happened to your arm?
Are you okay?
Oh, this? I just tripped...
Been so busy working that I strained it.
That is not accurate.
-I get a lot of requests, you know.
-That is also not accurate.
Ouch! Ow! Oh, no. It's starting to hurt!
It must be hard work
being a star Auto Memory Doll.
Star?
Oh, Dad! Stop exaggerating!
But what are you going to do
about this letter then?
Oh, that?
That's why she's here, too.
I will travel anywhere
to meet your request.
I am an Auto Memory Doll.
Violet Evergarden at your service.
Is she a doll?
No, she's an Auto Memory Doll.
My goodness!
The city Dolls are something else!
Hold on a second!
I'm wearing my Doll uniform, too!
It looks good on you, Iris.
You're like a fine career woman!
What's that supposed to mean? Seriously.
Oh, by the way,
do you know a Sarah Florent?
She's the one who requested me.
She should be here.
That's the name of your
late great-grandmother.
I'm the one who requested you.
I thought we could see you
if we hired you for a letter.
-Are you kidding me?
-So, this was a false commission?
As it was written in our contract,
we do not accept the use of aliases
or false commissions.
Please excuse me.
W... Wait, Violet!
I will now start your request.
Please enter the correct name
in the contract.
What kind of invitation would you like?
An invitation to Iris' birthday party.
Me?
Your birthday is the day
after tomorrow, remember?
I totally forgot.
She said she wanted to invite a huge crowd
for a big celebration this year.
We will have to write one immediately
if it's in two days.
There is also delivery.
-It's so pretty!
-What happened?
Leave her alone!
Please don't be concerned.
Do you have the invitation list?
Yes.
This is it.
I want to see.
There's so many males on the list.
-Well, you are at that age.
-So?
Don't you think it's time
you get married?
-What's that supposed to mean?
-You're our only child.
We want you to come back and get married.
Quit your Doll job
and move back in with us.
That's why you brought me back here?
By lying to me?
You lied to us, too!
The most popular Doll in Leiden?
That's enough.
In any case, we're throwing you
this birthday party.
Violet, please type this guest list.
Copy that.
Eamonn Snow.
Don't send one to him.
Even though his name is on the list?
Yes.
-Why?
-Just because.
Your parents are the ones
who chose these guests.
I don't believe you have the right
to remove him from the list.
Just do what I say.
-But...
-I'm the one who was requested!
You're just my stand-in. Got it?
Thank you.
I finished delivering my share.
I have just finished as well.
Why don't you come over and have dinner?
Although, there isn't much
we can offer you out here.
I do not require much
in regards to hospitality.
What? Well...
And while I do not have much evidence
to base it on...
This view seems like a great example
of wonderful hospitality.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Happy birthday, Iris.
Thanks.
Is your arm okay?
Yeah, it's totally fine!
-I heard you became a Doll in Leiden.
-Really? That's so cool!
Well...
Iris!
You have a second?
Talk to you later then.
-Yes.
-Sorry about this.
Do you remember them?
Montgomery just got
his teaching certification exam.
And Hans is training to become a cobbler.
Oh, Eamonn!
Long time no see.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Iris, happy birthday.
Why are you here?
Because...
I received an invitation.
You sent him one?
After I went to confirm with your mother,
I was instructed to send him one.
Iris?
Iris!
It's all because
you sent him an invitation.
What is the connection between that
and suddenly feeling ill?
I asked you not to send it.
-Why did you do that?
-I simply accomplished my mission.
I didn't want to see him.
Why not?
I cannot understand
if you do not explain your reason.
He rejected me before!
Do you mean
that you approached him romantically,
but you were rejected?
You expressed your affection,
but you were turned down?
Yeah!
That's exactly what that means!
I can't believe Iris.
I'm sorry.
Ms. Violet.
How is Iris doing?
She is crying.
She's crying? Why?
Did something happen to her?
Iris?
Iris? Are you okay?
Cheer up.
We'll find someone better for...
You're still talking about that?
This is all because of that party.
I wish I never came back!
I brought you dinner.
Did you tell everyone?
-Tell them what?
-About Eamonn!
-Yes, I did.
-Why did you do that?
I did not think it was a secret.
And they were all
very concerned about you.
That's not a...
You really don't understand
other people's feelings, do you?
I am very sorry.
I thought I had come to understand
emotions better.
But people have very complex
and sensitive emotions.
Not everyone can express
how they truly feel.
They end up contradicting themselves
or lying,
which makes it very difficult for me...
to understand what's true and what's not.
I am truly sorry.
Stop bowing.
I know you didn't mean any harm.
It's not like I always know
how other people feel either.
Is that true?
Yeah.
Eamonn is a childhood friend.
He was always very kind to me.
I loved him for the longest time,
and I just assumed
he had feelings for me, too.
I wondered why he didn't confess to me.
Which is why I told him
before we graduated.
I told him, "I love you."
But...
I'm sorry.
I only think of you as a friend.
I wanted to disappear.
I couldn't stay here anymore.
Even though I wasn't a good writer,
I studied hard...
and went to Leiden to become a Doll.
One needs a lot of courage
to say the words "I love you."
Especially if the feeling isn't mutual
and it makes you want to flee.
I wonder if it was the same...
for the major then.
-Who's the major?
-My superior officer.
I became a Doll so I could understand
what the major meant
by "I love you."
I felt that I was finally able to learn
a little bit about Violet.
The major provided his love to her
who only knew the military.
And she is doing everything she can
to figure out what that means,
in her own way.
Hey, Ms. Auto Memory Doll.
Can you write a letter for me?
What type of letter?
An apology letter to the people
who attended the party.
Very well.
Make sure it's a polite
and heartfelt letter!
-Shall I send it to Eamonn as well?
-Wow, you don't let up.
But, yeah, send one to him.
And to your parents?
Would you be interested
in telling them how you really feel?
You will be able to tell them
through a letter.
Emotions too difficult to express
will come through.
"Dear Mom and Dad,
I'm sorry for ruining the party.
I will send an apology letter
to the guests.
Also, thank you for commissioning me.
This was actually
the first time I was requested.
That made me very happy.
Work can be hectic,
but it's what I've chosen, so,
I will continue to do my best.
I'm sorry for always making you worry.
But...
please continue to watch over me
a little bit longer.
This is the first commemorative letter
from the future number one
Doll in Leiden...
to her parents, who she loves very much."
Are you sure you have everything?
Yeah.
Just let us know
if there's anything you need.
I'll be fine!
And also...
Thank you for the letter.
Oh, I mean...
she's the one who typed it.
Yes. I will hand you an invoice later.
-You're going to charge me?
-Letter writing is my job.
-Then how about lunch for three days?
-That will not be enough.
Call it a company discount!
-The train is leaving.
-Iris.
-Happy birthday.
-Take care.
Did the letter successfully reveal
your emotions to your parents?
Can't you tell from seeing their reaction?
It was a good letter.
The letter you wrote got through to them.
Because it was a good letter.
Did I write... a good letter?
Why are you talking like that?
Those flowers...
Oh, they're irises.
Look.
You know, I was born
when these flowers were in full bloom.
That's why my parents
gave me this name.
What's your name?
I see.
Would it be okay
if I gave you a name then?
Violet.
I have a feeling you'll grow into the name
when you're older.
Don't be a tool,
become someone
that matches with their name.
Subtitle translation by
Zensho Yamamoto