It's short!
Nice cover.
More importantly, Kageyama...
Karasuno             Shiratorizawa
We get to play one more set!
Haikyu!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Shiratorizawa!
Episode 07: Obsession
If you play a disappointing match,
Shiratorizawa!
you're going to be running
back to school from here.
Shiratorizawa!
We actually had to do that
when I was a first-year.
Shiratorizawa!
At the third-years' retirement match.
You are you, and that's the
only reason you need to win.
Shiratorizawa!
Because you're all members that
I chose without hesitation.
Shiratorizawa!
Karasuno             Shiratorizawa
The final set...
I'm thinking about starting with Sugawara.
Shiratorizawa!
Right!
We're counting on you, Sugawara!
It'll be fine.
Sugawara-kun, give it your all!
This isn't the first time I'm
going in during a pinch.
Suga-san, give me a whole bunch of tosses!
Karasuno
Shiratorizawa!
Damn it...
My body's warmed up, but my hands are cold.
Shiratorizawa!
P-Please wait a while to marry me!
Don't worry. I don't plan
on marrying you, Sugawara.
You don't know that!
I'll hold your hand for you.
No, I'll do it.
No! Stop! Shimizu's
scent's gonna go away!
Shut up! It's not fair
that you're the only one!
Don't touch me!
They look like they're going to be just fine.
Stop!
It's finally the final set.
Sugawara's starting?
I-I'm even more nervous now.
Kageyama was getting pretty exhausted.
They're probably going to let him rest
and put him back in when
they need him the most.
That's only if they can make it that far.
This might be a bit much for
Mr. Refreshing, don't you think?
Huh? You're changing your setter?
That's lame.
If you get lost, just toss them to me.
Well, aren't you reliable!
What are you, the ace?
I am the ace!
We're counting on you, Tsutomu.
You can do it, future ace!
Right!
We're going to cut them off at one!
Yeah!
Fly
Sorry!
Asahi!
All right!
Yes!
Yeah!
Karasuno             Shiratorizawa
The fifth set only goes
up to 15 points, right?
It does?
Yeah. It goes really quick.
Hopefully they can make it
without them catching up.
Sugawara is a dependable setter.
He won't fall apart.
Yeah!
At least, we hope...
It's Ushiwaka!
All right!
Karasuno             Shiratorizawa
Damn it... This pressure is insane.
Taichi, nice serve!
Front!
Got it!
Sorry!
That toss was low... Stop panicking!
It's definitely going to be the left.
Out!
D'oh.
The middle was blocked, so you went
for the safe left the second time.
You're so easy to read.
Well, our left is pretty efficient, so...
I want to break your heart in two!
Our spikers are strong.
I know that more than anyone.
Asahi, nice serve!
Got it!
Our team is plenty strong.
But...
Nishinoya!
we don't stop there!
From a libero setting
to a synchronized attack with
everyone other than the libero?
Asahi-san! There's still time,
so will you hit one of my tosses?
Noya-san! Let me hit one, too!
Heck, yeah! Of course, Ryu!
Hey, me, too!
Oh, are you going to set some
up for us, Suga-san? Thanks!
Oh, no, no.
I'm going to spike!
All right!
All of them...
No one to follow up and block?
Yeah! I love ya, Suga-kun!
Looks like we didn't have to
worry about him falling apart.
Looks like our minds were a bit closed.
My weapon is my reliability.
But...
I can do new things, too.
Karasuno                Shiratorizawa
All right! It's a break!
Nice kill, Suga!
Yeah!
We did it!
Satori!
How many times do I have to tell you?
Don't jump just on your hunch!
But I've scored a ton of
points just on my hunches.
That's not going to happen all the time.
There are limits to individual skills.
There's no point if you don't feel good now.
Practice always stops when Tendo's around,
though it's nice to be able to rest.
Or rather, Tendo's sort of scary.
You never know what he's thinking.
I know, right?
I...
Just want to play volleyball
that makes me feel good.
I don't have any complaints,
as long as you can score.
Keep on breaking them!
What, you say?
Their hearts...
Haikyu!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Wakatoshi-kun, did you catch Sadako
when it was on last week?
I didn't.
It's scary, but I ended up watching
it because the leading actress,
Brunhilde Reiko, is super cute!
I see.
Isn't she cute? Brunhilde Reiko.
The only person who could excitedly
talk to Wakatoshi about TV is Satori...
I don't know who that is.
But you know, I don't know about the
other girl, at least in my opinion.
One of them doesn't look too excited.
No matter how you look at it.
You never look like you're having
fun doing anything, Wakatoshi-kun.
That's so rude!
Why did you start playing
volleyball, Wakatoshi-kun?
I learned it from my father
for a little while.
Huh...
Ushijima
I thought it'd be better to fix
his left-handedness early on...
What? No, that's not necessary.
We've always done that in our household.
I'm sorry, but please... Anything but that.
The fact that he's different from other people
will probably end up being his strength.
I won't complain about anything else!
Was your dad a volleyball player?
Yeah, he was a secondary league player.
But apparently, before he got married,
he got injured quite often and retired.
Huh... What's his name?
Utsui Takashi.
Don't know him. So his name's not Ushijima?
He married into my mother's family.
Though my parents divorced a while back.
Huh? Oh, sorry...
Hm? It's fine.
Do you ever see him?
No. He's overseas right now.
Wow, that's so cool!
So if you become a star, your dad
will probably watch you, too.
Perhaps.
I think back in your dad's time,
Shiratorizawa conquered nationals.
Seriously?! That's awesome!
So you wanted to be like
your dad, or something?
No, not really.
Oh, I see.
It's just...
Our ace was literally the best ace in Japan.
Back then, he was 190 centimeters tall.
He was a third-year in high school,
but he was still growing.
But it wasn't just his physique.
He made you think that if you tossed to him,
he would never disappoint you.
He would make it work.
It makes you get all excited.
I wanted to be like that.
Karasuno              Shiratorizawa
All right!
Why don't you do that, too, Kageyama?
I can't... I haven't practiced that.
I haven't practiced to
match up with Nishinoya-san.
Shiratorizawa!
That was fast! Already?
Well, once someone gets the lead in
the fifth set, it's over in no time.
Shiratorizawa!
Take it back! That is all.
Karasuno!
Right!
Shiratorizawa!
Karasuno!
Karasuno sure does some reckless attacks.
Yeah. I've never seen a libero set up and
then everyone else come in to attack.
Shiratorizawa!
Karasuno!
You're impressed with that,
but you don't like their #10, huh?
Shiratorizawa!
Karasuno!
You probably don't like their #10
because he's so enigmatic, right?
Shiratorizawa!
Karasuno!
Things you can't understand are scary, right?
Shiratorizawa!
They're not scary.
No, I mean, they're sort of creepy.
If anything, the feeling of something
Shiratorizawa!
being slightly creepy must
be a new feeling for you, huh?
Shiratorizawa!
Karasuno!
Asahi-san, one more!
This time, it hit the net on our side.
Karasuno                Shiratorizawa
One more!
All right, they broke through.
How beautiful.
All right!
The fact that he's different
from other people
will probably end up being his strength.
Karasuno            Shiratorizawa
Ushijima-san! One more nice serve!
Wakatoshi! Get an intense one over!
Bring it!
Nice kill, Ushijima!
Sorry!
We'll get the next one!
Ushijima! Ushijima!
Stop them here!
If you don't, it's going to get rough.
Daichi-san!
Suga, get the last!
He got the setter to take it. That's good...
Tendo-san!
Righto!
Hup.
I thought he would definitely hit to me,
given which way his body was facing,
but...
he changed the course right when he hit it.
Join a strong team.
Nice toss, me!
Strong guys and interesting guys
gather in a strong environment.
Nice aim!
I'm surprised you were able to hit that.
And if you become stronger, you'll be
able to go up against various people.
Strong guys, weird guys, and new guys.
I'm sure that they will make you stronger.
Well, that's only if you want
to continue playing volleyball.
It doesn't matter how,
but if you end up liking volleyball
in some way, it'll make me happy.
That was really sharp. That was amazing.
If I were to borrow Tendo's words...
"I'm starting to get into it."
Out!
All right!
Shiratorizawa turned it around!
Karasuno                 Shiratorizawa
Wakatoshi's serves can still
be pretty hit-or-miss,
but he's doing amazingly today.
Looks like you set our ace on fire.
He got it!
Get the last one over!
Chance ball!
Ushiwaka from the back?
One touch!
Be Courageous Warriors
Nice kill, Ushijima!
So annoying...
Ushijima! Ushijima!
Thanks!
That was close...
Usually, you want to jump up against the
spiker that's going to hit right in front of you,
but Tsukishima usually
doesn't fall for decoys.
So he's read blocking.
Wherever the toss goes up,
Tsukishima will be there.
When there's a wall,
no matter where you are,
that itself is extremely unpleasant.
And if that keeps happening
all throughout five sets,
no matter how unflappable
someone may be,
it'll end up being pretty stressful.
The front!
Chance ball!
What?!
You're not getting it over.
One more! One more!
One touch!
He's just like Aone-san!
Nice one touch!
Crap... Tsukki is so freaking reliable!
Chance ball!
He read us?
Using the middle where there's
a block waiting is scary, right?
I get it. That's why you go for the left.
Yup. Totally understandable.
One...
more...
time!
Such intense concentration.
With such a long rally and exhaustion,
it wouldn't be weird if their bodies
were moving faster than their minds...
But he just grasps the
necessary information.
Nice aim...
Out?!
Sorry.
D-Don't mind...
He missed? Lucky!
That's not lucky at all!
It just means that his mind was trying
to avoid the block that strongly.
Huh?
What? It was overruled?
What?
The ball hit the line just a little bit.
It's Shiratorizawa's point.
Seriously?!
But that was great determination!
Switch it up, switch it up!
Um...
There's something wrong with his hand.
Damn it...
What?
It must have been cut when
you touched Ushiwaka's spike.
I hope that's the extent of it though...
Narita!
Yes!
Karasuno            Shiratorizawa
Damn it, at a time like this...
Thankfully, it was just my pinky.
If I can just endure the pain...
How long does it take
for it to stop bleeding?
If we just tape it up so it'll be stiff...
The next rotation will have
Hinata on the front line.
I need to figure something out by then.
Get him to the infirmary.
Oh, dear. He got hurt?
Glasses leaving this late in the
game is going to hurt a lot.
You'd better buy me some time!
By the time you get back,
we'll already be bound for nationals!
All right! Concentrate!
Right!
Kazuhito! You're not alone in your blocks!
I'll be right behind you!
Right!
Don't hold back and go for it,
just like we practiced.
Right!
Looks like he had to go away.
But we're not gonna hold back.
Of course not.
Stands
Kei!
What are you doing here, Nii-chan?
Though I knew.
I came here to see my younger
brother fight bravely, of course!
Though it looks like you're
not going to die from that.
What do you mean, "die"?
Even if I'm alive, I'm being pretty
useless when it matters most.
Though, after five sets, I'm pretty tired,
so it's sort of nice to be able to rest.
Even though my hand hurts.
"My teammates will win,
even if I leave them alone."
You just have to believe that.
Don't worry.
You won't have to worry about
going back just to see them lose.
Japanese National High School
Volleyball Tournament
To think that Tsukishima's able to make
those kinds of faces now...
If we don't show them what we're made of now,
when the hell are we supposed to show it?
Bring it.
Bring it!
Nice, Daichi!
Center!
He's doing that again!
I hate dumps... because I'm scared of them.
It's the same with spikes.
Thinking about missing if I had
the nerve to poke my nose
into something other than
my usual job... I can't risk it.
Fly
But...
There'll be no victory
without risks, either.
Karasuno is only Karasuno when
we're persistently attacking!
Right!
Synchronized attack: all!
Go!
Don't come to our team, Tendo!
Monsters aren't allowed on human teams!
Yeah, he does look like a monster.
Good job reading that, Satori.
Yeah, it was just a hunch.
Ever since I saw that expression,
I couldn't be satisfied with
just a one touch anymore...
Tendo, what are you doing?
Look, isn't my old hairstyle
super fashionable?
Whoa, what? Seriously?
It's the same as Tsutomu's!
Did you call?
Don't look! You'll end up
wanting to shave your head!
Episode 08: An Annoying Guy
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"An Annoying Guy."