What?
Huh?
You mean...
Like I just said, they've
decided to demolish...
Sakura Hall at the end of the year.
You'll be moving into the regular
dorms in April, so start packing.
Wh-What—
It's great news, kouhai-kun!
Haven't you been listening to
what Chihiro-chan's been saying?
Aren't you happy that they're
going to rebuild Sakura Hall?
I'm already so excited, I don't
know what to do with myself!
I won't be able to sleep tonight!
In fact, I'd rather sleep through the day!
"Rebuild"? Is this actually a positive thing?
No. When I said they're getting
rid of Sakura Hall, I meant it.
They're not rebuilding it at all.
It's going to disappear completely.
Chihiro-chan, I don't remember hearing
or accepting anything like that!
Who made that decision?
An expert inspected...
the building's condition over winter break.
Winter break?
Oh, right.
I'm locking up Sakura Hall
at the end of this year.
What?
I'm going to go have some fun in Australia.
You'll all have to go home.
Are you saying you tricked us?!
Calm down, Sorata.
This doesn't make sense.
Sakura Hall is old, but it's not so old...
that it needs to be torn down right away.
If they have to demolish it, can't they
wait until these guys graduate?
If you just tell us they
decided to demolish it,
Chihiro-chan, you realize
we'll fight this decision.
It was decided in a board meeting.
They even gave you permission to keep...
your cats in the regular
dorms for a while.
That's all. Dismissed.
Sensei!
We can still live in Sakura Hall.
I'll convince the principal
to change his mind!
Don't bother.
If you go after the principal,
he might never recover.
It's not a good idea to portray Sakura Hall...
in a worse light than it already is.
But I can't accept this!
I can't believe they'd ignore the
opinions of the current residents.
She's right. And doing it
so underhandedly, too—
Are you sure?
Misaki and I are graduating, but for you,
this is a unique opportunity
to return to the regular dorms.
But...
The regular dorms are nice and clean,
and you'll never be
bothered by drafts again.
The cafeteria workers will
prepare your meals for you.
Unlike this place, you'll never need
to worry about various things.
That's not the point—
For you, Kanda, you'll be
able to use your free time...
to prepare for the title screening.
Akasaka, don't you care if
Sakura Hall just disappears?
I am calmly weighing the
pros and cons. That's all.
Hey!
Well, let's not get ahead of ourselves.
We should consider all of those things, too.
To think the first thing
I heard after coming back...
was the news of this
dorm being demolished.
Jin, does it really not bother you
that Sakura Hall's going to disappear?
Of course it does.
We owe them.
It's our turn to do
what we can for them.
If we can't convince the
principal, what should we do?
Their reasoning for suddenly demolishing
this building doesn't make sense.
If it was something they could tell us,
they would have told us by now.
What are you going to do?
Well, for now...
Yeah, don't worry.
No matter what happens,
I'll take care of you.
You understand the
situation, don't you?
Sakura Hall is going
to disappear, right?
That's right. You know what
that means, don't you?
From April, we'll all live
in the regular dorms.
What? I'm surprised you
understood that much.
No matter what happens,
you'll take care of me.
I knew you didn't understand.
Listen, I can't do that
in the regular dorms.
Why not?
Men and women eat separately,
and men can't enter the women's dorm.
I won't be able to...
wake you up every morning
or cook for you anymore.
That is a problem.
I like Sakura Hall.
You're right.
At first, I wanted to leave as
soon as I found homes for them.
That's the picture we took
when I first arrived here.
Everyone's in it.
Now that I think of it,
the principal made me move here.
Principal's Office
Kanda Sorata-kun, do you understand why...
you've been summoned here?
Yes. It's about my cat, isn't it?
We've been turning a blind
eye for the last month,
but keeping live animals in the
dorms is against the rules.
Get rid of the cat...
or leave the regular dorms
and move into Sakura Hall.
Your choice.
I will move into Sakura Hall.
Kanda-kun?!
Do you have any regrets?
None!
So, you accepted your fate.
Yeah, I'm at that age...
when kids like to rebel
against authority.
You're an idiot.
What else could I do?
He told me I couldn't keep
my cat in the regular dorms!
Are you really going to
move into Sakura Hall?
Once you're exiled to that
place, you're done for!
You'll never be able to
return to a normal life!
Sakura Hall is the one
place you should never go!
That's what they say about Sakura Hall!
Don't worry.
I'll find someone to
take Hikari and return...
to the regular dorms
by the second semester.
Sakura Hall
So far, it's about three times
more rundown than I expected.
It's okay. It's not as though
aliens or ghosts live here.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Excuse me!
How careless.
I'm coming in!
My room is...
Kanda Sorata
Room 101.
It's pretty big.
It looks like it's been
properly cleaned, too.
This place is great.
There's even storage...
Maybe I'm just too tired.
Burglar!
You give up, Mr. Burglar?
I'm not a burglar! I'm a
first-year student...
Wait, are you the second year,
Kamiigusa-senpai?
How does a burglar know my name?!
Because you're famous.
You're the art scholarship student...
who made that hugely popular anime...
Punishment!
Y-You've got the wrong idea!
I'm Kanda Sorata, a first year,
and I'll be living here starting today!
That's what all the burglars say!
No, they don't!
This is Hikari.
They kicked me out of the regular
dorms for owning a cat.
I see. Soratan and Hikarin, is it?
So you're more of a cat
person than a dog person?
What?
I-I suppose I am.
I'm definitely a "this" person!
Was that even one of the options?
I'm Soratan.
Anyway, Soratan...
Please don't call me that.
What am I, a moe character?
Sorapyon
Okay then, Sorapyon...
Now I'm some lazy mascot!
Okay then, Sorani...
Now I'm an organic compound...
What don't you like
about them, Soranya?
Friends give each other nicknames.
My head's starting to hurt.
Anyway, Tan-Tan.
That doesn't even resemble
my name anymore.
The CEO of a certain company...
would go jogging in the
park every morning.
Okay.
The park was littered with empty cans.
Unable to ignore them, the CEO decided...
to pick one up every
day he went jogging.
But because a lot more cans...
were thrown away than
the CEO could pick up,
there were increasingly
more cans, not fewer.
But the CEO kept picking
cans up every day.
Unbelievably, after a
considerable length of time,
the number of cans began decreasing.
Truth was, other runners
were inspired by the CEO...
and had begun picking up cans, as well.
Fin
Sounds like a nice story...
It is a nice story!
It means humans aren't so bad.
Even though some throw away cans.
So, why did you suddenly
tell me this nice story?
No reason!
An alien!
Where?!
Right here!
You're a funny kid, Sorachi.
I was called funny by someone
who's funny in the head.
Shut up already.
What's all the fuss about?
Sensei, help me!
Who are you?
I'm moving in today...
Oh, right. The principal
said something crazy...
about a student joining Sakura Hall.
It's not crazy at all...
Anyway, Sensei, why are
you dressed like that?
I'm on my way to a mixer.
I don't have time to
worry about my students.
What did you just say?!
Are you a boy or girl? Boy or girl?
Why does summer have to be so hot?
A girl! So you're Hikari-chan!
Doesn't make any sense.
I feel like my heart is breaking.
What have you been shouting about?
Jin, it's Soran! He's moving
into Room 101 today!
Then, his surname must be Yaren.
It's not! I'm Kanda Sorata, a freshman!
And this is Hikarin.
Ah, so you're the kid with the
cat from the regular dorms.
I'm Mitaka Jin. I'm in Room 103.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, Mitaka-senpai.
Don't call me Senpai. Just call me Jin.
In that case, Jin-san, I'd appreciate
it if you could help me.
Misaki, go easy on him.
That's all you're going to do?!
Even if it's you asking,
Jin, I can't do that.
I want to become even
better friends with him.
She didn't use honorifics?
Misaki and I are childhood friends.
Of course, that's not the full
extent of our relationship...
My girlfriend is a married woman.
I'm about to go on a date with her.
What?
See you later.
What is it?! What did Jin say?!
Come on, keep it together, Soranyan!
Hey!
Sakura Hall
Victory!
That's 98 wins in a row!
Only two more for 100 consecutive wins!
I'd like to unpack my stuff soon...
You can do that anytime.
You're living here from
now on, Sora-chan.
I'm leaving as soon as I find
someone to take Hikari!
Save it for after you've beaten me.
That's 99 wins in a row!
After all the time I've
spent playing this game...
I believe professional wrestlers
are the greatest warriors!
Professional wrestlers
are really strong!
You're just needlessly strong, Senpai!
Could I at least take a bath?
What are you? A little girl
worried she might stink...
of sweat in front of the boy she likes?
"Why are you standing so far away?"
"N-No reason. Stay away."
"What's your problem?
Do what you want."
You'll give him the wrong idea.
But I'm a guy...
Anyway, I'm going to go take a bath.
What?! You're abandoning
your 100 win streak?
Girl In Bathroom!!
I guess I'll have some
water and try to relax.
Huh?
What could be making that
noise at this hour?
S-Sensei? Or is it you, Jin-san?
Are you back already?
G-G-G...
G-G-G-Gho...
The room next door...
That was a real live person, wasn't it?
What are you screaming about?
Another monster!
You got a death wish or something?
Oh, Sensei. It's you.
You're back from your mixer?
A long time ago.
All of them sucked, but they
kept going on about how...
my personality's terrible
and I drink too much.
Those idiots!
More importantly, I just saw a g-g-gho—
You saying I look old and withered?
I'm still in my twenties.
Nobody said anything like that.
I just saw a ghost.
Its hair reached all the
way down to its waist.
It disappeared into the
room next to mine!
Oh, yeah. He comes out
of there sometimes.
So there is a ghost?!
Akasaka Ryunosuke in Room 102.
What?
Kanda Sorata      Akasaka Ryunosuke      Mitaka Jin
I'd completely forgotten about him.
I've only seen him about three times.
Akasaka Ryunosuke
Sensei, don't you look
after this place?!
Akasaka's an extreme recluse.
He's a first year like you,
but he hasn't gone to school
once since he enrolled.
You're pretty lucky to meet Akasaka
on the day you moved in.
Please don't treat a reclusive student...
like some kind of good luck fairy.
It really is amazing.
Your reaction is far more amazing!
Anyway, isn't it your responsibility
to make him go to school?
Making someone do something
they don't want to do...
will just make their life unpleasant.
You've thought this through.
I'm sorry.
That's why I don't do any
work at Sakura Hall.
I don't want to.
You were talking about yourself?!
Here.
What?
If you want to talk to Akasaka, text him.
That's his number.
Wait—
He lives in the room next to
mine and I have to text him?
Let's see. That should do it.
Composing Message
My name's Kanda Sorata, and I've moved
into Room 101. Nice to meet you.
Sending
Message Received
Akasaka Ryunosuke
That was quick. What's it say?
"Ryunosuke-sama is currently developing
a motion engine... okay?"
Akasaka Ryunosuke
Subject: none
Ryunosuke-sama is currently developing a motion engine,
okay? He cannot answer your message, okay?
"He cannot answer your message, okay?"
"Yours sincerely, the recently
born Maid-chan."
Um, how am I supposed
to interpret this?
Akasaka, you're a funny guy.
Akasaka Ryunosuke
Subject: What's the joke?
Maid-chan is working as hard as
she can, okay? From Maid-chan.
"Maid-chan is working as
hard as she can, okay?"
"From Maid-chan."
Enough of that.
Can't you talk to me normally?
I am talking normally, okay? Sorata-kun, you
must be a stupid kid, okay? From Maid-chan.
Akasaka-kun, could you stop ending your
sentences like that? It's annoying.
What's up with this conversation?
I am not Ryunosuke-sama, okay? From Maid-chan.
That's ridiculous! Quit making fun of me!
That's ridiculous!
Quit making fun of me!
Message Received
Akasaka Ryunosuke
"Maid-chan is an AI program
I created to answer...
my messages automatically.
She composes appropriate responses...
within a second of receiving
a message and sends replies.
You couldn't even figure that out?"
Akasaka Ryunosuke
Subject: none
Don't waste my time. Akasaka Ryunosuke
No one would expect you to use...
an automatic answering program
for your personal number!
Akasaka Ryunosuke
Subject: I see.
I had no idea someone existed in this world
who couldn't understand that. Sorry. That is all.
"I had no idea someone existed...
in this world who couldn't understand that.
Sorry. That's all."
I don't feel like I've been
apologized to at all!
Thanks for waiting!
I wasn't waiting for you!
Sorachi, let's play Metal Cluster next.
What? Isn't that a single-player game?
We'll play in turns and compare our scores.
Watch me play for about three hours first.
It'll be morning by then.
Anyway, why did you come
dressed like that? Please leave!
Don't sweat the small stuff.
Sit down, Sorapu.
Fine. If you won't leave,
Kamiigusa-senpai...
Then I will!
I can't stay here any longer!
Come on, Sorapi!
What am I going to do now?
No! Absolutely not!
There's no way they'd let
me keep a second one!
I'm home.
Keep quiet.
What are you doing?
Jin-san, did you just get home?
Meiko-san didn't give
me a chance to sleep.
H-How adult of you.
Is Meiko-san someone else's wife?
Yeah. I have three other
girlfriends, though.
You have four girlfriends?!
And who's your cutie there?
I picked her up in the park...
Ah. What's her name?
I'm thinking of calling her Nozomi.
If you pick up a third one,
you'll have to call her Kodama.
There won't be a third.
I'm not even sure they'll
let me keep a second one.
Welcome to Sakura Hall!
Welcome to Sakura Hall
What is this?!
As you can see, it's a new
resident welcoming party.
It's six in the morning!
Misaki insisted on doing it.
That's why I wandered home at this hour.
I'm glad you went out so I could
make it a surprise, Sorakyun.
You did this all yourself?
Misaki was looking forward
to having a new resident.
She's been keeping this
room clean by herself...
so it'd always be ready
for someone to move in.
That's why it was so tidy.
But why hotpot?
We always serve hotpot at
Sakura Hall welcoming parties.
Yeah, but in the middle of summer?
Don't worry about that. Sit, sit.
Hey...
Who's that? Is she a new resident, too?
Yeah. I just picked her up in the park.
I was hoping it'd be all right
for me to keep another cat.
Let's hold a Sakura Hall meeting, then!
A Sakura Hall meeting?
When we have to make a decision,
we hold a meeting with all the residents.
Her name's Nozomi, apparently.
Okay, who thinks it would
be fine to keep Nozomi? Me!
Ryunosuke has no objections, either.
That's great.
Are you sure you want to make
this decision so easily?
What about the teacher's permission?
We don't need it.
That's how this place works.
Come on. Let's keep partying!
Nozomi! Hikari! Kouhai-kun! Eat up!
Let's use that.
Huh?
My nickname.
I'd like you to call me
kouhai-kun, Kamiigusa-senpai.
You can call me by my name, then.
We're friends now.
Okay. Misaki-senpai it is.
Get a little closer.
Sakura Hall
What about Akasaka?
Don't worry about him.
I'll add him in later.
Add him?
I'm starting to get the feeling
we'll be together for a long time.
Don't joke about that!
I'm going to find owners for these cats...
and leave by the second semester!
Come on, kouhai-kun!
We're taking the picture!
Strike a pose!
I'm definitely leaving!
It was only Hikari at first...
Komachi made these scratches.
I've tripped down these stairs.
And I've fixed the front
door plenty of times.
Sakura Hall is definitely rundown.
It's cold in the winter
and hot in the summer.
The floor in the hallway falls
through from time to time,
and the lock on my door is broken,
so I have no privacy.
The second floor leaks, too.
But...
Yeah. I realize now that everything that
used to bother me has turned into memories.
When the bath broke and we went
to the public baths together.
When we took out that hornet nest.
You're right.
I've been filling up my journal
faster since I came to Sakura Hall.
I feel like I'd be losing
something important...
if Sakura Hall disappeared.
I don't want that.
Well said, kouhai-kun.
You're exactly right.
The hotpot party on the roof.
Turning Sakura Hall into a
haunted house over the summer,
and inviting all the kids
in the neighborhood.
Playing possum every day
when you came back.
They're all wonderful memories.
Well, all your memories also involve
someone getting mad at you.
A lot has happened, but I
believe we belong here.
What do you think, Akasaka?
Pros and cons aside,
Sender: Mitaka Jin
Subject: The real reason for tearing down the building
Can you hack the server and investigate?
it disgusts me that their reason
for doing this isn't clear.
I like Sakura Hall.
So do I. That's why...
We'll stop them from tearing it down.
Sounds good.
Yeah!
Okay, let's hold a Sakura Hall meeting.
The curtain's rising on our
first defense of Sakura Hall.
#19 There's No Place Like Sakura Hall
Is everyone ready?
Yeah!
Yeah, I don't have any
time to get all depressed.
Life has its ups and downs.
#20 So We Can Keep Saying We're Home
There's no way I'd fall any farther.
I've got a feeling a lot of good
things will happen next week.
Don't, ponytail.
You'll set a downer flag.