Maison de Ayakashi,
also known as Ayakashi Kan.
A luxury apartment complex,
complete with bodyguards.
Secretly, it's a place where humans
partially descended from
supernatural creatures live.
It's a place full of eccentric people.
It's also where I met
my Secret Service bodyguard,
Miketsukami.
I learned that the one I had
once exchanged letters with
was him, pretending to be Kagerou.
Afterwards, he explained the
situation and apologized.
He said that he had carefully
preserved all my letters.
But that if I wanted,
he would return them, as they
were never meant for him.
I told him he could keep them.
Because I had sent them to him.
Then he gave me one of those smiles,
like he was about to cry.
And then, I made up my mind.
And then, I made up
my mind.
What are you doing?
Sorinozuka.
Are you helping out today?
Do you need to see your dad?
Go on in...
N-No, it's fine.
Why not?
I just stopped by...
S-Sorinozuka...
Are you sure this is all right?
Your cover will be blown.
Don't worry about it.
If people see something they can't process,
their brain adjusts to it, anyway.
Even if someone took a picture,
I'd just get coverage during some
summer urban legend special.
Special Report
Flying Cloth Monster
Who is the boy riding it!?
That's so careless!
And here we are.
You shouldn't transform in a place like this.
It's wrong to confuse people just for fun!
I'm sorry.
I just got told off by a kid.
You know,
you kinda seemed like you didn't
really want to see your dad...
And if you enter through the front,
the lounge is right there,
which means you might run into him.
Sorinozuka...
Yeah?
You carry a supernatural creature's blood,
like my father does, right?
Yes, that's correct.
Isn't it true that people like you
have the same personalities, and sometimes even memories, as your ancestors?
How does that differ from
normal reincarnation?
If my dad dies, will he be reincarnated again?
If he marries a woman who isn't
my mother in his next life,
will he be the father of
someone other than me?
Um...
I expected this to be a more
clear-cut father-son dispute.
This kid thinks about some complicated stuff.
How long have you been
thinking about all this?
I only just now found out about it...
When I heard my father and the others talking,
I understood what it means to have the blood.
Wow.
I'm surprised you can worry about
something so far in the future.
I don't even consider what I'm
going to have for dinner.
Then let's bury a time capsule!
Both your entrance and your
comment were quite sudden.
If you're so concerned, why not
write your father a letter?
B-But what can a time capsule do?
Then your father can read
your letter in his next life.
My father... In his next life?
You could write something like,
"Don't marry anyone but Mom!"
Or like, "I'm your only child, Dad!"
But...
Hey.
Don't worry.
Just let me handle this.
First, let's gather all our friends together!
No matter what you do, you have to
have fun doing it with everyone.
A time capsule?
Well, I'm a delinquent,
so don't expect me to go along...
In that case,
I'll write you a letter, Watanuki.
I'll write a letter for you, in your next life.
But in your next life,
maybe you won't be friends
with me in my next life.
So you wouldn't read my letter...
Idiot!
Of course we'll be friends!
I'm going to buy some stationery!
Good luck!
But what will we be in our next lives?
What would you like to be?
I'd like to be a steamed bun.
Filled with red bean paste or meat,
pizza or Belgian chocolate,
custard or stew.
Steamed buns are always filled
with wonderful things.
I want to be filled with
wonderful things, too.
So in the end, you want to be
something that gets eaten.
I want to keep eating until
the moment I get eaten.
This soil is hard...
Hurry up. Don't make me regret
playing along with this.
Yeah...
I'll help.
Oh, thank you.
You know, just looking at us now,
we kinda resemble a family.
He's even got the droopy eyes.
RenRen, did you dig the hole?
I just buried him.
It's a little late to ask, but do you
think it's okay to dig a hole here?
It is a shared property.
Generally, nope.
And will this complex even
survive for that long?
Death
To My Future Self
Th-That's cute.
So that's what's going on...
Want to join in, Ririchiyo?
Hah... A time capsule?
What are you, a kid?
Why would you ask a high
school student to do that?
Well, I won't force you.
See ya.
Well, it just happens I already
had my stationery set out.
I guess I could participate.
What a coincidence.
H-Hey... Don't get the wrong idea!
It really was a coincidence...
I was writing a letter to include
with a box of cakes!
Sure, sure.
But you know, you've really changed.
When you first got here, you told
everyone to leave you alone.
From...
From?
F-From now on,
a little interaction
with others won't be something
I'd d-dismiss out of hand...
F-For a while,
I'll probably say rude things and
make you guys uncomfortable...
That's fine.
I'm pretty dense, anyway.
J-Just don't come crying to me.
Bring it on.
Big Brother wants to make a time capsule?
Yeah.
He said you should participate, if you want.
And this... Hmph.
Because I dropped that melon I got you before.
But don't expect anything special.
You did not need to...
And the melon from earlier...
I preserved it, to keep it fresh,
and I have safely stored it.
Don't. Just eat it.
When did you manage to get this, though?
I just picked it up during my lunch hour.
What of it?
You exposed yourself to such danger?
Thank you so much.
I shall treasure it always.
I said to eat it.
Anyway, I'm going to the garden.
To the garden?
You're participating in the
time capsule project?
Wh-Why? Is there something wrong with it?
Are they forcing you to take part again?
N-No...
N-Not this time.
Sorry for acting out of character.
Then...
Would you go down to the garden
and wait for me?
I shall participate, as well.
You really should interact
more with others.
That's a skill that can only be learned by
hurting and being hurt by others.
You've really changed.
It's strange, given that I
came here to be alone...
But meeting these people has
made me want to get involved.
Since I met him,
I want to change.
I may hurt people.
And I may get hurt myself.
But I won't run away and
stay apart any longer.
I want to better myself,
and stay by Miketsukami's side.
Well? What did you write?
S-Since I don't know what my
future self will be like,
I wrote down some goals for myself.
Yeah, that's true...
We have no way to know.
That's just how it is.
Kotarou,
you came here, too?
Yeah.
Where did you get that post?
So you also have some words that you'd
like to leave in the time capsule?
How sentimental.
I'm writing a letter to you, in your next life.
But I don't know what to write.
Will I really be myself in my next life?
Of course you can't write a letter to
some old man you've never met.
People become themselves
through their encounters.
With different things, people, and emotions.
A me who has not met your
mother or you is not me.
Was that too romantic?
I see...
I guess you're the only dad I have.
Oh, is this happily ever after?
Why are you looking so smug?
You knew something again, right?
Could you actually be kind?
Huh?
At first, I was a bit worried because I
didn't know what you were thinking.
I think you're mistaking meddling for kindness.
You can't be sure, huh?
Hey.
What are you doing?
Who instigated this?
Who?
I heard about it from him.
Him.
Me?!
That sounds like fun!
I want to do the time sale, too...
It's a time capsule.
You leave a message,
within a durable box,
for someone in the future.
You're quite a knowledgeable tranny.
You really...
Well, if you've dug the hole,
I suppose it's too late.
Just be sure you cover it back up.
Bye-bye!
I think we have all of them now...
Wait.
Miketsukami wanted to add something, too.
Ririchiyo,
are you sure this is the letter
you meant to leave?
To Miketsukami
Weren't you going to give it to Miketsukami?
Didn't you want to include it
with the box of cakes?
Could you have put the time capsule
letter in the other box?
How embarrassing...
So, what's in that letter?
But I won't run away and
stay apart any longer.
"But I won't run away and
I want to better myself."
I want to better myself.
"And stay by
Miketsukami's side."
And stay by Miketsukami's side.
Ahhh!
What the hell was that?!
What's wrong, Ririchiyo?
It isn't like you to lose your composure.
It's possible he hasn't read the letter yet.
Why don't you just call him?
That's not the speed of a novice anymore.
Yes?
Do not read that letter!
I read it.
Why?
Why did this have to happen?
I'm pretty sure I can guess what you wrote...
But it's obvious you both feel
the same way, so don't worry.
Why get all worked up?
Actually, as your big brother,
I feel a bit lonely.
But does he feel the same?
It's possible Sou's feelings are
merely based on respect.
He is seven years your senior.
But that man isn't the type to
have moral issues with that.
I'm worried...
Want this?
Yeah, he's a lolicon!
Perfect label for that stupid fox!
You needn't get so depressed about it.
If we hang around here,
he'll join us soon enough.
I'm not mentally prepared!
I'm going on a journey!
Take care!
And presently...
Why did this happen?
It's as if I confessed to him.
I didn't want to do that at all...
I'd never do something like that.
Her everyday, uncontrollable bad mouth.
What are you talking about?
Don't get ahead of yourself.
Every day, I act precisely
in the opposite manner!
It isn't like I wanted to be his girlfriend,
or anything silly like that.
I'm just grateful to him.
I wanted to change...
He gave me the courage.
That's why I want to grow into a better me,
and give a little back to him.
I forgot...
I turned off my phone.
The least I can do is make sure
I can tell him I'm safe.
Otherwise, I'm effectively
sabotaging his work.
It rang the second I turned it on!
I-I haven't even devised a strategy...
Plan One:
The Blitz
I'm fine, so don't bother looking for me!
Click
Too suspicious.
The root problem must be addressed.
Plan Two:
Just Explain Yourself
That letter has no deeper meaning.
You were unable to reach me until
now due to bad reception.
Reeks of justification. Sounds like a lie...
That letter?
Plan Three:
Pretend Nothing Happened
Oh, it really doesn't mean anything.
Actually, I wanted to discuss something else...
Who the hell is that?
I-I have to answer,
or the call will get dropped.
I just need to explain, as naturally as I can.
That letter doesn't have a deeper meaning!
Ririch—
I was just looking for a long-term
contractual partner.
Is that a problem?!
May I ask you where you are right now?
I'm at Seijou Park! So what?!
Anyway, I don't have any special
feelings toward you!
Yes.
I know that quite well.
Y-You know?
Yes.
N-No way...
Even I thought that was an obvious excuse.
R-Really?
Yes.
You've told me so quite plainly.
And I am not that shameless.
I do try to be aware of my position,
my nature, my standing, how I got here...
I am someone who has done things
that you ought never to hear of.
For me,
simply being by your side makes me happy.
You actually write letters and
e-mails to the real me.
You cannot fathom how much that means.
I can imagine no higher form of happiness.
B-But that's...
That is how
I sing praises of you, as if you were sacred,
while I indulge in my own fantasy.
I wish for no further happiness.
Imagination is free, is it not?
Do you understand?
This is the kind of man I am.
I do see, Miketsukami...
You hate yourself.
Somehow, I think I always knew that.
Because you always slight yourself.
Because your eyes seem so cold.
Because you seem lonely.
I understand.
I understand you...
I hate myself, too...
But I was able to wish to change.
By falling in love with you,
I gained that courage.
You gave it to me.
Miss Ririchiyo.
I'm afraid.
But up to now, I've hurt many others,
all to protect myself.
That's why, if it will give you
even a tiny bit of courage,
I don't mind getting hurt this time.
I love you.
Even... Even if you...
cannot love yourself...
I...
love you.
Ri—
I love you!
I love you...
I—
Miss Ririchiyo!
I love you...
I love you!
Miss Ririchiyo, I love you!
I love you...
I love you.
If...
my words were able to help you,
I truly am happy.
There is no happier feeling than this.
Look, those grown-ups are doing pervy stuff!
Wow...
Th-They're staring at us, M-Mike...
They are.
D-Don't sniff me...
It'll corrupt these children!
L-Let's separate...
Miss Ririchiyo, this is like a dream to me.
Are you listening?! Let go—
When I got that letter,
I told myself that I must not misunderstand it.
Otherwise, I'd have lost my composure.
But in reality,
I was so happy, I could have died...
The Day We Came Together
Want to get ice cream at the concession stand?
What are you eating right now?
This is soft serve.
I'm back, you human toilets!
If you're looking for the girls,
they went to a camp by the sea.
Abandonment play, sadistic.
I found you, you worms...
Did you think you could run from me?
It's Master Kage.
Wh-What the hell are you doing here?!
All right, come on over.
You want to join us, right?
Cut up that squid.
Ririchiyo, I'll put sunscreen on you.
Blue School Festival
Cross-dresser, incoming!
It's the old standby, "boy dressed as girl."
Watanuki, you look quite cute.
How did your exams turn out?
I guess I can say that, thanks to everyone,
my score was just fine.
They took away my candy...
Where shall we go today?
W-Well...
You look great in that.
I brought you a drink.
Miketsukami...
I need to use your restroom.
Feel free.
I guess you found it.
You did say that you loved me
the way I am, right?
I didn't know this was the real you!
Miss Ririchiyo.
I have only one dream.
A dream?
What is it?
I don't care if it's a lie...
It can be a superficial lie,
existing only right here, right now.
Miss Ririchiyo, I want a child.
I want a family...
Someday.
I thought about you,
in your childhood that I'd never seen.
I imagined it.
I see...
You were lonely, and you were precious.
I see.
But I don't want to answer
on the spur of the moment.
Because it's important.
Miss Ririchiyo...
All right.
I prefer it that way.
Let's take plenty of time,
and think it over together.
Time is a burden.
That is what I believe.
The time you have lived thus far...
We'll remember it, again and again.
The story of a long, long time.
The story of a
long, long time we'll live out together.
And the story moves from spring to summer...