- Ryuko!
Are you all right?!
It hurts!
It hurts like hell!
But it's what I deserve for
being such a huge dumbass!
I can't believe she's still alive
after snapping her own Life Fibers!
By the way...
Nui's injuries are healing!
So she's indestructible, too?
It's the power of the Life Fibers
inside her body.
It was a mistake to throw
your Scissor Blade at me.
You can't defeat me,
and now I have both halves!
Get going, Senketsu!
Be with Ryuko!
Right!
I'll just have to shred
that dumb ol' Senketsu again!
I don't think so!
He used me as a springboard?!
Let's go, Ryuko!
Life Fiber Synchronize!
EPISODE 22
TELL ME HOW YOU FEEL
Harime!
She's cowing Harime through
sheer intimidation, eh?
You stay put right there.
Aw, but I'd tailored Junketsu
just for you!
I won't let you wear
that lame getup!
Quit while you're ahead.
I'm never taking Senketsu off.
Mako and Satsuki's blood is
flowing through Senketsu now.
He's way warmer and feels better on me
than that monster, Junketsu!
- Ryuko! Thank you for saying that!
Dummy, clothes don't cry!
You're getting all damp and gross!
You were so comfy, damn it!
I'm so sorry!
What's with this "friends" garbage?
It's so gross I'm gonna barf!
Don't talk crap about it!
The word "friends" don't
come close to covering it!
They're something more,
something I can't explain!
That's what Mako Mankanshoku
and Senketsu are to me!
What, me?!
Yeah, you. I can't tell
if you're weak or strong!
Like a woman who barges into your
heart when you're not looking!
Or someone who cries, laughs and genuinely
worries about me even though he's clothing!
Bat-crap crazy people like that
try their damndest to help me!
And I have to live up
to that craziness!
You people only see
one thing.
To make it so the whole world is cut
from the same cloth — Life Fibers.
But you see, I'm never
gonna let that happen.
The world's better off having bat-crap
crazy people wandering around it!
I didn't understand a word of that,
but you're so totally right, Ryuko!
If you don't understand, hush!
Darn it, that's why
I hate humans!
If that's how you want it, go ahead and
die without being understood ever!
Dad's Scissor Blade...
I finally have it back!
In that case, maybe I'll make the people
you're trying to protect attack you!
Have a taste of Mind Stitching!
It's no use!
Oops, sorry about that!
That was a decoy!
It's all over, Ryuko!
Yeah, for you.
MY ARMS!
My arms, my arms, my arms, my arms,
my arms, my arms, my arms!
MY ARMS!
Do you have any idea how
valuable my arms are?!
They're the arms of the Grand Couturier!
That's why I chopped 'em off.
Kidding! Even if you chop them off,
they'll pop right back, good as new!
Oops.
Clumsy me.
They can halt Life Fiber regeneration?
Those scissors can do even that?
Just give it up, Nui Harime!
This can't be happening!
You're really making me angry!
Every last one of you!
I'm pissed, I'm pissed, I'm pissed,
I'm pissed, I'm pissed,
I'm pissed, I'm pissed!
Hououmaru!
You're not getting away!
Senketsu Shippu!
What the—? Ow!
I'd better not do it, Ryuko.
You've lost a great deal of blood.
Chasing after them
would be dangerous.
But we've still got these
guys to deal with!
Hououmaru made a mistake because
she was desperate to rescue Harime.
She's right! Which makes this
a golden opportunity!
It was nice of them to
bring us both Life Fibers
and new members for the cause!
Exactly. Don't just stand around doing
nothing, Elite Four, get to work!
Give me those!
Nonuple-mount Emergency
Rescue Suction Device!
NONUPLE-MOUNT EMERGENCY
RESCUE SUCTION DEVICE
You!
You're Hakodate of the Tennis Club...
TENNIS CLUB PRESIDENT
OMIKO HAKODATE
...and Fukuroda of the Boxing Club!
BOXING CLUB PRESIDENT
TAKAHARU FUKURODA
KUSANOSUKE YAGURUMA
And there's more!
TATAMU OTTE
AIZENBO FUGUHARA
MAIMU OKURAHAMA
FORMER ACROBATICS CLUB
Medics!
Yes, ma'am!
Tend to the students who
have been extracted!
On it!
All right, Mankanshoku family,
let's help people for a change!
If they're buck-nekkid, they've got nothing
to steal, so I'm just not feeling it...
Mataro! That's enough of that!
Ow! I'll do it, I'll do it,
I'll work seriously!
Sewing Club, collect the Life Fibers!
Bring them to the lab ASAP!
Collection complete.
Let me out!
Who asked you for help?!
I haven't been beaten yet!
Please calm yourself,
Grand Couturier.
What can you possibly do
in your condition?
Surely the task you must see to right now
is the completion of Shinra-Koketsu.
How do you intend to apologize
to Lady Ragyo for this fiasco,
losing both arms in a battle
you did not need to fight?
Me? Apologize?
As if.
Hurry back to Honnouji Academy!
I'll finish up Shinra-Koketsu!
And after I'm done, I'll teach you what
happens when someone mouths off to me.
If you finish Shinra-Koketsu,
what happens to me is of no concern.
What shall I do with Junketsu?
Keep it in restraints
for the time being.
You're not going to terminate it?
The battle isn't over yet.
Planning to put it on again, huh?
Can you wear that monster?
I won't make the same
mistake twice.
After you couldn't
synchronize with Senketsu?
Stop it, Ryuko. Satsuki risked
her life to save you, too.
So what if she did?
That don't excuse the attitude
she's given me all this time.
What do you want from me?
Let me belt you one.
Ryuko...
If I punch you without holding back
and you're still on your feet,
I'll admit that you have the strength
to fight alongside me.
Ryuko, that's crazy!
A bare-skinned human would die if
hit by you while synchronized.
She's no ordinary human.
This is the great Satsuki Kiryuin, right?
Very well, strike me.
We face Ragyo Kiryuin.
If I am to fall here, I have
no chance of winning this battle.
I shall withstand your blow.
Show me that you aren't all talk.
Here it comes.
Gamagoori!
Stay out of this, you bastard!
What is it with you people?!
Are you mocking me, Matoi?
What?!
I'm asking you if you threw
that punch with everything you had!
Yeah, I did!
Don't make me laugh! If that's true,
why are we still alive?
I thought ordinary humans would die
if you hit them full-force!
You got in the way,
so I pulled them!
A likely excuse!
You pull your punches just because
someone gets in the way?!
Such a woman is not worthy
to punch Lady Satsuki!
Don't turn this on me!
No, our anger is directed
at the right person!
As if we would allow a half-assed blow
like that to land on Lady Satsuki!
What are you two doing?
Our face is Lady Satsuki's face!
Our limbs are Lady Satsuki's limbs!
For her, we could be smashed or
sliced off and have no regrets!
However, these limbs have a
mind of their own,
so we can be rather obstinate.
We, the Honnouji Academy Elite Four, are
Lady Satsuki's irresistible spear! Her unyielding shield!
If you want to strike Lady Satsuki, strike us!
But you'll find that we don't yield easily!
What the hell is it with you people?!
I don't get you at all—
So you're protected by a bunch of
bat-crap crazy people just like I am?
So it would seem.
"To defeat Ragyo, I must treat
all human beings as pawns."
Or so I thought.
I thought the same of you.
Ever since the day you appeared
wearing Senketsu,
my intent was to train you into a powerful
asset to turn against Ragyo and her people.
I made you believe I was your
father's killer to get you
to come after me and gauged your and Senketsu's power.
If you could hold on to
your free will without
being swallowed up by the Kamui,
you would surely prove useful when
it was time for the coup against Ragyo.
I believed I could manipulate
you and use you
as an asset against Ragyo even
without telling you the truth.
You bitch...
However, that was a grave mistake.
In the end, I was employing
the same methods as Ragyo.
It's a given that I would not
be able to win like that.
The biggest fool here is me.
Satsuki...
I understand now. The world
is not cut from the same cloth.
It is because it is overflowing with
inexplicable, unidentifiable things
that the world is so beautiful.
Fight at my side so that we may
protect that world, Ryuko!
Sheesh, even when you apologize,
you turn it up to 11...
I don't feel like hitting
you anymore.
I have people I want
to protect, too.
I got no problems with stopping
that excessive mother of ours.
Now that you've made up,
let's have dinner!
Your croquettes, ma'am?
That's right, croquettes stuffed full
of minced, unidentifiable things!
Dig in, dig in!
Yep, when it comes to unidentifiable things,
my family's the best there is!
Dig in, too, Lady Satsuki!
This is...
Yummy, huh?
Yes, it is.
There will be
after-dinner tea, as well.
Ryuko.
You were somewhat touched
earlier, weren't you?
When you heard what
Satsuki had to say.
Geez, this outfit doesn't
know when to let up!
You could have come out
and told her so.
Seriously, you are so obnoxious!
And you are a woman completely
devoid of feminine charm. Sheesh.
Senketsu, you were lonely from having no
one to talk to for so long, weren't you?
That's why you're making
all this pointless chitchat.
That's not true!
I'm not that prone
to feeling lonely!
Fine, fine.
Get all the idle chitchat out
of your system while you can.
Pretty soon, we won't
have time for it.
She'll be coming soon.
It's me.
I see. Ryuko did, did she?
Yes, have Nui work faster.
What a nuisance my daughters are.
I guess I didn't
discipline them properly.
Ryuko Matoi! Satsuki Kiryuin!
I'm gonna make you pay, you hear?
What I'm injecting into Junketsu is
a mixture of Lady Satsuki and Ryuko's blood,
as well as Senketsu's Life Fibers.
In other words, you're
using Senketsu's power
to forcibly dye Junketsu
with Lady Satsuki's colors.
If I'm going to put on something
that I can't wear properly,
we should simply re-tailor it.
It's far too late to be concerned
about appearances.
The only thing on your mind
is victory, huh?
It looks like you've stripped yourself
of all extraneous thoughts.
You're a proper Nudist, yourself.
Iori, status of our own forces?
Come on, nothing?!
You can count on me.
We collected more Life
Fibers than we expected.
I'm just about to start on
manufacturing Goku Uniforms.
Can you manage this
by yourself?
I'm more than enough!
Three-Star Goku Uniform, Tailor's Regalia!
THREE-STAR GOKU UNIFORM
TAILOR'S REGALIA
Ragyo Kiryuin's ultimate objective
is to transform the entire human race
into Life Fibers and cover this world.
This is the Starseed Cocoon Sphere.
STARSEED COCOON SPHERE
All of REVOCS' products have
Life Fibers incorporated into them.
Upon receiving a powerful signal,
those Life Fibers will awaken.
Humans with no resistance to it will
be converted into energy sources,
and all clothing will
transform into Covers.
Seven billion Covers will rise into the
stratosphere and enshroud this planet.
You're telling me that she's trying
to make the Earth wear clothing?
That's messed up.
I had heard that she was trying to turn
the human race into Life Fibers,
but I had no idea her plan
was this epic in scope.
To what end, though?
Life Fibers are an organism
that drifts through space.
If they reach a planet that
harbors intelligent life,
they cause them to evolve into a state more
suitable as an energy source for themselves.
They then cover the planet with the beings
that have been converted into Life Fibers,
and then, using the planet itself as an
energy source, cause it to explode,
and that force scatters
new seeds through space.
That is how they continue
to reproduce across the universe.
Good grief, talk about making
things up out of whole cloth...
There you go again.
Why do you keep blurting out dumb puns that
we've been restraining ourselves from saying?
I've had just about enough of your lack of tact,
you stupid Northern Kanto monkey!
Mock Northern Kanto once more,
I'll mix you up with limewater and boil you!
Now, now, what's with all
the "yakking" about "konnyaku"?
That's enough, you two!
Behave yourselves in front
of Lady Satsuki!
Don't worry about it, Gamagoori.
Hearing you two bicker makes me
feel like I have truly come home.
Yes, ma'am!
Okay, I've managed to hack into
REVOCS' communications satellites.
I'll put up a video feed of
the Original Life Fiber.
They've beefed up their security,
so their cameras are all I can get a peek at.
Ragyo...
Original Life Fiber's destination,
Honnouji Academy.
Exactly as expected.
Honnouji Academy?
That's right.
By attaching the Original
Life Fiber to the massive
transmitter installed at Honnouji Academy,
she can send out the signal to transform
all humanity into Life Fibers.
So to stop her plan, we just need
to smash that transmitter, then.
Oh, there is one
unexpected item, though.
What is it?
These missiles that are about
to strike this ship.
Report stuff like that
right away, darn it!
Mr. Mikisugi.
"Mister"?!
I'd like to put you in command
of the operation.
M-Me?
I will go with Ryuko
to stop Ragyo.
It is inappropriate for someone
on the front lines to be in command.
Ah, I follow you.
Elite Four, is that clear?
Yes, ma'am.
All right, we'll see to the destruction
of the Honnouji Academy transmitter,
and Satsuki and Ryuko
will keep Ragyo Kiryuin
and the Original Life Fiber occupied!
All hands to your posts!
There you go again,
telling people what to do.
You aren't going?
Can you go?
I have no choice.
Hurry up and get changed, then.
Lady Ryuko, please look
after your sister.
I know.
Let's do this, Si— Sis...
There's no need to force
a pretend sisterly bond.
Your blood is flowing through Junketsu.
That's more than enough.
It is?
Yes.
You two...
You can get maudlin later, Senketsu.
Let's do it!
- Life Fiber Synchronize, Kamui Senketsu!
- Life Fiber Override, Kamui Junketsu!
KAMUI SENKETSU         KAMUI JUNKETSU
Ryuko.
I see 'em.
Senketsu Shippu!
SENKETSU SHIPPU
Grab on!
I don't need your help.
Junketsu Senpu!
JUNKETSU SENPU
It's even absorbed my abilities?!
Hey, not bad!
Let's hurry!
Yeah!
All right, we're setting course
for Honnouji Academy!
Satsuki, the ship!
There was another under the water?
What the hell is this?
It appears to be a Covers
specialized for combat.
This one will be formidable.
Honnouji Academy Fight Club President
Mako Mankanshoku is back in action!
FIGHT CLUB-SPEC TWO-STAR GOKU UNIFORM
FIGHT CLUB PRESIDENT MAKO MANKANSHOKU
BACK IN ACTION
Rest easy, Ryuko.
I'll keep this ship safe!
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
To wrap the entire world in a single cloth.
That is Ragyo's giant wrapping cloth.
A SINGLE CLOTH
GIANT WRAPPING CLOTH
This anime would also wrap up
THIS ANIME
if that happened, so Ryuko, Satsuki,
and Mako rise up to prevent it,
TO PREVENT IT
RYUKO AND SATSUKI
MAKO
THEN
as do the reconstituted
Elite Four!
Next time on Kill la Kill,
"Imitation Gold"!
EPISODE 23
IMITATION GOLD