The Scale Festival starts tomorrow, huh?
Everyone is really excited.
It's our first festival in Akihabara, after all.
Since the festival was approved,
many guilds have been making
special items for the event.
So it seems.
Licensed by the Round Table
Princess Figures (Wood Carved)
Only 40 of Each Design!
500 Gold
Just hearing there's a festival makes
a lot of people want to do something.
Decorations?
You've got quite a lot there.
They won't even fit in my magic bag.
The Crescent Moon Alliance will
be selling winter clothes?
We're having a fashion show, as well.
That sounds nice.
It starts tomorrow, so we're
doing the final touches today.
Don't work too hard.
I heard Crescent Moon Burgers
will be making their return.
That's right.
So, what will you be doing during the festival?
I'll be going around and
enjoying all the different shops.
I will eat...
And eat some more!
And Akatsuki and the others?
Come to think of it, I didn't hear.
What'll the girls be doing?
Here, take one!
Please come as a couple!
I have to invite Shiroe!
All-You-Can-Eat Cake Buffet
Come as a couple, and get in free!!
I've only made it this far because of you.
It's true.
All-You-Can-Eat Cake Buffet
Come as a couple, and get in free!!
I'm done with this!
Swallow and Young Starling
Swallow and Young Starling.
Shiroe...
Shutting yourself up in here again?
Handling the Round Table's paperwork,
investigating this world...
I have a ton of work to do.
Are you eating enough?
Sleeping enough?
Yes and yes.
I ate two hours ago, and I
took a fifteen-minute nap.
That's fine, then!
Here is what you requested.
Oh, thanks...
You didn't need to bring it.
If you had just sent a message,
I would've come to get it.
So you say, but would you really have come?
I've heard you've been locked in here for ages,
so I wanted to check on you, too.
Thanks.
How's the Scale Festival looking?
Karashin's going all-out.
He's really taken charge of the event.
He does good work.
You should take a break
for these next three days.
Yeah...
During the festival, it'll be pretty noisy,
so I probably won't be able to concentrate...
That isn't why!
This is a good chance for you to
become closer to your guildmates.
And...
Log Horizon is one of the Round Table guilds.
You'll be out there, making the event fun, right?
I'll try.
You'd better!
Right!
Akatsuki and Minori are so cute, too.
I'm so excited already!
What's that?
An Akatsuki doll that Akatsuki gave me!
A voodoo doll?
Truly, as long as I have my fantasies,
I barely even need to eat!
They say that man does not live by bread alone.
But with bread and fantasies,
you can get over almost anything!
God almighty!
You're just playing around,
aren't you?
She's right... During the festival,
it'll be hard to do much.
When reports come in,
I'll have to do some fancy footwork,
so I'll end up waiting, anyway.
Since then, nothing has happened in Minami...
M-My lord...
Welcome back...
Has something happened?
No... Well...
You want a red bean bun?
Red Bean Buns
Eh?
Great weather today!
It feels like forever since I was outside.
This is for you.
You're sure?
In this world, red bean buns are expensive.
I want you to eat them.
Thank you.
Delicious...
It's been a long time since I've had one.
Wh-What?
There's bean paste on your mouth.
Oh, thanks.
Lately, you've looked pale.
That isn't true.
Really?
M-My lord...
What's gotten into you?
What are you going to do during the festival?
The festival?
Oh, I'll probably have to help with things.
Henrietta asked me to.
I see...
No, I mean...
My lord, do you like c-c-ca...
All-You-Can-Eat Cake Buffet
Come as a couple, and get in free!!
Voilà!
What is that?
So, about the Scale Festival tomorrow...
Would you go to this with me?
A cake buffet?
You enjoy sweets, don't you?
From the way he eats his red bean buns,
that would seem to be true.
I certainly don't dislike them...
Let us go, my lord.
If we go as a couple, it's free!
It's free! Totally free!
Let's go!
Um...
Shiroe!
My lord!
This is a problem.
What should I do?
I know.
Maybe not this...
Minori!
There's a pre-festival dance tonight.
Wanna come with...
Uh, what are you doing?
I'll be going out with Shiroe tomorrow,
but I'm not sure what to wear.
Going out?
With Shiroe, the shut-in?!
I don't think I've seen him outside for a week.
So, where are you going?
A cake buffet.
Shiroe, eating cake?
Why?
Well, if you win this contest,
you get two tickets to the Twilight Banquet
with Princess Lenessia on the second day.
Participants compete to see who can eat the most slices!
The top two teams advance to the final battle!
No one trusts Shiroe. They say they
don't know what he's thinking...
But he's actually really nice.
I'm sad that they don't understand him.
I want them all to know more about him.
I understand!
Okay! Got it!
I'll help you!
I'll coordinate your outfit!
Really? Thanks!
Why does Minori have to put pressure on me?
My rival is a middle-schooler?
Even if he does normally treat me
like a kid, this doesn't seem fair...
Is it my lord's fault for treating me as a kid?
Is it?
But...
...because of you.
My lord didn't judge me based
on my appearance or level.
He accepted me for who I am...
My lord said he'd attend the buffet
with both Minori and me.
But it's supposed to be a couple,
so we'll probably be alone...
Is this situation...
...a date?!
Impossible...
Impossible!
And what will I wear?!
What do you suppose is going on?
It's getting lively around here.
I have no cute clothes.
What am I going to wear?
Oh, I'll ask someone to help me.
What's happened?
I felt it...
Akatsuki needs my help!
Akatsuki!
I'll pick something myself...
Crafting Guild
Council Office
Knock First!!
No, no...
That's going to be expensive.
No, I'm afraid not.
The Council doesn't play favorites.
Your location is determined by lottery.
We must adhere to that.
Hey, you're doing all that yourself?
I don't have a choice.
This place is like a business congress.
Then, are these all...
I asked everyone to submit them
so I could check for any dangerous items.
It's a terrifying amount.
Isn't it?
The People of the Land's
merchants are also coming.
I'm getting the sense that the festival
is a lot bigger than it should be.
The next few days are gonna be hell...
Huh?
When did you get here?
Please help.
This is rare.
Are you alone?
What's wrong?
I...
...require fashion!
Huh?
Shiroe, of Log Horizon...
And two others?
Yes.
Sorry to ask this of you...
Oh, if that's the case, I understand.
I'm sure this will be difficult for you...
But good luck!
What did she mean?
It really is all couples...
Let's eat!
I'm glad all three of us could get in together.
What? All three of us?
Yes.
I just got permission from
Kanako, the organizer.
We'll have to eat twelve to enter
as a trio, but I think we can do it.
Okay.
Let's win, and go to the finals!
Right, Akatsuki?
Yes.
To be honest, I don't think
I could've eaten here twice.
But...
What is this feeling? Pressure?
That's a wonderful kimono, Akatsuki.
It's rare to see you in a kimono.
What's up?
Th-This is...
A guild called Kimono Komachi made it for me...
Does it look okay?
It's a gr—
It is not for graduation.
It is for fashion.
Gr—
It's graceful, and really nice. Yeah.
R-Really?
Yes, it's very cute.
You look good, too, Minori.
Thank you.
Isuzu chose this for me.
Really?
Yes, she took me to a bunch of stores.
Why don't you come with us sometime?
Okay.
Isuzu knows a lot about clothes.
I was surprised.
That looks so good!
My lord! My lord!
I have high hopes for this!
Aren't they pretty?
Isn't this exciting?
Yeah, I think I could eat four of those.
Here you go!
Eh? Huh?
Here, enjoy!
"Enjoy"? But those are whole cakes!
It's a little present from my guild!
Present?
Um...
Let's start with one.
Yeah.
Let's eat.
It's great...
Really, my lord? You like it?
What are you doing?
Serving my lord.
Serving me? That's a whole cake!
I'll cut it up.
That isn't the issue.
It's not fair that you got to bring two!
Unbelievable.
Crap... Is that how this looks?
Is he trying to show off?
Die.
This isn't good... I'll get them both involved.
I hope his glasses break.
I need to avoid making a fuss.
Minimize damage and retreat.
My lord.
Here.
Am I supposed to eat that?
Of course, my lord.
Say, "ah."
Come on, it'll fall off.
Is it good, my lord?
Mhm.
Shiroe!
Say, "ah"!
Try this, too.
Is it good?
Well, yeah, it's good, but...
I'd rather fight a dozen raid bosses at once!
My lord.
There's still more.
"Ah"...
Me, too!
"Ah"!
Someone help me!
Café Kanako
Thank you!
Sorry you had to pay.
We couldn't eat them all.
I had no choice.
Will you go home and rest, my lord?
I was going to see the rest of the
festival, but I think I will...
Um... You two go on without me.
I need to make a stop before going back.
Thank you!
Dandelion barley tea is good for digestion, right?
I'm sad I couldn't attend
the Twilight Banquet,
but Shiroe worked hard for me.
I'll have to thank him.
It hurts...
Three people eating twelve whole cakes?
How did she figure that?
Oh, right.
A cake buffet?
It'll probably be there tomorrow.
Why not go?
It'll be free.
That sounds great!
I'll definitely go.
Thanks for the information, Shiro!
Sure.
I wonder how many whole
cakes he'll end up eating...
But all the girls love Soujirou,
yet he still does well running his guild.
Naotsugu or Chief Nyanta seem more
like guild masters than I do.
I don't really have the presence.
Maybe Henrietta's right, and this
would be a good chance.
I should make time to spend with everyone.
My lord.
When did you get there?!
Just now.
Is something wrong?
No, nothing...
The town is even more lively than usual.
It is a festival, after all.
When we first arrived in this world,
I never would've imagined it.
Yeah.
You're quiet.
I'm always quiet.
Yeah, but...
My lord...
Do you, well...
Dislike cake?
Or did you not have fun?
That's not true...
Anyway, I'm sorry we didn't get to the finals.
That doesn't matter to me.
It was Minori who wanted to go.
I see...
But was that cake okay with you?
It felt like I was doing all the eating.
Did you have any?
I...
I wasn't there for the cake.
Oh...
It's hard to hold a conversation
with you, my lord!
I don't know what to say.
You just don't talk much.
That isn't true...
I have all sorts of things to discuss.
Then give us something to talk about.
Was that a little harsh?
Um, I didn't mean... I'm sorry.
Er...
Wait...
It's fun to do this.
Is that really fun?
It is.
Oh...
Is this part of her lord-and-servant role playing?
This is enough?
Yes...
I see.
What is this?
Why?
Akatsuki...
likes...
Shiroe!
I...
I also...
like him.
It isn't fair!
Shiroe is mine!
Not fair?
How could I have said that?
It hurts...
This isn't...
Minori?
What are you doing here?
Whoa...
Look at your face...
Tohya!
Well? What happened?
Listen, Tohya.
I...
think I like Shiroe...
What?
You're just now figuring it out?
It was obvious to the rest of us.
No way...
He's nice, and he's caring.
He's like a teacher.
I can see why you'd admire him.
How could you tell?
Of course I can tell! We're twins!
I admire him, too!
You like him, too?!
Not like that!
This is a problem...
Why?
"Why"?
I don't think it's a problem.
It's not a problem...
You're just hurt, Minori.
Is it okay?
You can't help it, right?
You're right...
It isn't a problem...
It just hurts.
I haven't lost anything,
and I haven't done anything.
I haven't done anything yet, have I?
That's true.
Yeah.
The girl simply admired him.
She wanted to be like him...
To follow him.
To stand behind him. That was all.
But it didn't take long for those
feelings to turn to love.
Minori is in love with Shiroe.
Student of the Mage
Next time: Student of the Mage.
We will change the world.