Sugane, we're counting on you.
Okay.
Also, the newbie's starting today.
Understood.
I'll be going, then.
All right. Take care.
What is the matter?
I have a stomach ache.
Please stay calm and look
at the information.
Would you like to match?
Yes     No
Excuse me, you should
give her your seat.
Huh?
What the hell?
The jerk thinks he's so cool.
Thank you.
No problem.
"Target is on the move toward
Tachikawa station."
It is as stated in the prophecy.
"There will be moving steps
south-southwest of the box."
Tachikawa Station North Exit
Steps?
"A nameless chaos shall
appear once more."
Target has passed the fourth floor.
I'm counting on you, Sugane...
All right! Let's do this!
So... cute...
There she goes again.
Hajime really likes her planners.
She's always fiddling with them.
Look! I got another one yesterday!
What?!
What are you going to do with so many?
Well, you see,
this one is for planning school stuff.
This one is for planning
personal stuff,
and this one's for writing
down random thoughts.
As for this one, he's just to admire.
"He"?
As for this newbie,
I wonder how I should pretty you up...
What?
Oh, if that's the case...
Hey, why don't we go
lie in the sun together?
Hey, did you see yesterday's
TV special on the supernatural?
Yeah, I did.
I can accept aliens,
but Gatchaman being real?
It totally threw me off.
Gatchaman, huh?
The name sounds kind of cute.
Gatcha, Gatcha, Gatcha, Gatcha.
Man, I'm hungry.
Um, who are you?
You're really tall.
Everyone has power that
is concealed deep within.
Awaken!
Spread your as-of-yet
invisible wings...
Oops.
Is this hide-and-seek?
Hm...
This way?
This way!
All right, I'll get it right this time.
You're making me think you're there,
but you're there!
Gotcha!
The chosen fledglings
will become the wings
that will protect this planet.
Wings, thy name is...
...Gatchaman...
Gatcha... man?
H-Hey, I can keep this?
Hey, I'm gonna keep it!
Yay!
Target is on the move
toward Tachikawa station.
There will be moving steps
south-southwest of the box.
A nameless chaos shall
appear once more.
Target has passed the fourth floor.
I'm counting on you, Sugane...
Uh, this is kind of awesome.
I think I'm gonna get full!
There you are, MESS.
You have absorbed innocents.
I will have you relinquish them to me!
Amnesia Effect!
Wow!
So cute!
Go, Bird!
Let's go!
There you are!
Gatchaman!
The Infinite Blade, Storm!
None may escape my infinite reach!
Amnesia Remind!
Ow!
Hi!
Are you the Gatchaman I just saw?
What happened to him?
This NOTE has words
flooding out of it—
Could you be...
the new team member?
I'm Ichinose Hajime!
I think I somehow became
a Gatchaman today.
Nice to meet you!
Oh! We're in the same school!
Let's go together!
Ow!
Sorry!
I guess I'm late again today.
I wonder if I'll pass my classes okay.
"Morning," Sugane-kun.
Late again, too.
Good afternoon.
Oh?
Um, does Gatchaman really exist?
Of course not.
Although few and far between,
some information exists.
Oh, really?
What? This is a panda.
Nah, no way.
Gatchaman exists!
It's Senpai and me!
Listen!
Our identity as G—
Our identity is an absolute secret!
NOTE!
So cute!
Wh-Why was such a joke chosen...
Come with me.
We will go to our base now.
Really?!
It's within walking distance.
That's surprisingly close.
This is the entrance?
The base is underground?
Listen, newbie.
Oh, I'm Hajime.
That's the last we'll
see of your antics.
The responsibilities of
a Gatchaman aren't fun and games.
You must always face them
with a sense of tension.
Understood.
So Gatchaman do exist!
Is it true you're protecting Earth?
I'll introduce you to the team.
Hey.
Where did you get your swimsuit?
The design's super cute!
I'm dreamy...
Wow, you're super cute!
You're really too bold!
I'm O.D.
Nice to meet you!
O.D.-san, nice to meet you.
Well, I'm a sad Gatchaman
who can't even transform.
Sniff, sniff!
Oh, really?
Let's get along, okay?
This one's Altair.
Al-chan.
Cute!
Al-chan!
Come on, Utsutsu.
You're Utsutsu-chan?
Nice to meet you.
The man over there's Jou-san.
I pass.
Jou-san?
Nice to meet you.
Ah, there you are.
Welcome to the Gatchaman CAGE.
I'm the leader, Paiman.
Huh, a panda?
Listen up, newbie.
Oh, I'm Hajime.
Never mention that animal's name again.
It is my most hated
life form in existence.
The leader's command is absolute.
Obey me at any cost, henceforth.
So cute!
You're talking a lot!
Don't be so full of yourself, human!
I have, thus far,
protected seven planets!
Oh, so you are protecting Earth!
And you're so tiny!
I'm impressed!
First, I'll explain the NOTE to you.
Great! That's what I wanted to hear.
The NOTE is the source
of our Gatchaman powers.
Everyone here had their NOTEs
extracted from them by Lord JJ.
"Source"? "JJ"?
Didn't you meet a tall guy?
Oh!
So he's JJ.
The NOTE is our spiritual essence.
In other words, our soul itself!
Our soul is our NOTE?
Awesome!
That's really fun!
We engage with the enemy on a daily basis,
but we must not be noticed by humans.
Thus, we use our NOTE
to cast the Amnesia Effect.
Amnesia Effect.
Understood!
You're a surprisingly quick study.
Once you cast the Effect,
humans become unable to see us.
But they can still feel you
if you bump into them.
So you have to avoid
them while you fight.
Understood!
Once you terminate the Effect,
you'll also transform back to your normal self.
Oh, but I saw Senpai
at the station today.
The Amnesia Effect does
not affect NOTE holders.
I see!
Oh, and you can use the NOTE
to communicate, like a cell phone.
If you input words or talk into it,
it's transmitted to the
NOTEs of everyone else.
Isn't it unreal?
It's way too convenient.
Yeah, way too convenient!
Deployment orders from Lord JJ
will also be sent to your NOTE.
Personal use of the NOTE's
communication functions is strictly prohibited.
They are for missions only.
If Lord JJ learns of
their personal use,
we would be turned to interstellar
ashes and dust in a single gesture—
Loves bamboo in particular <3
H-How dare you...
On our sacred N-N-N-N-N-NOTE...
Sugane, I leave the rest to you!
What?
This is how we transport the aliens
we've captured from various places.
So this is an alien?
It's pretty!
No photos!
Don't underestimate aliens!
Our leader is one, too.
Really?!
The Gatchaman's mission
is to eradicate alien criminals and
unidentified objects that
have infiltrated Earth.
Eradicate?
Anything in existence that harms
humans becomes our target.
Recently, though, our targets
have been mostly of this type.
It's the thing you saw
earlier this morning.
We call them MESS.
"MESS"?
It means discord and chaos.
It destroys everything it touches
with its long tentacles.
The MESS will be our primary
enemy for the time being.
Anything that appears
in this area falls
under our jurisdiction
and is eradicated by us.
They are Big-Smalls.
They are workforce clones that
support our Gatchaman duties.
They are in charge of salvaging
humans who have been absorbed
"Salvaging"? You mean rescuing?
Yes. We rescue them.
Wow, they're back!
That's awesome.
Their memories will be wiped later.
Most people are salvaged that way,
but some remain missing.
I see.
I wonder why MESS-chan
does such things...
It's so cute.
Newbie.
Oh, I'm Hajime.
From this point onwards,
I would like you to carry out
your duties appropriately.
We are protecting human lives
on Earth from that dangerous object.
Yeah?
Sugane, you've come a long way.
Whoa, here it comes!
Summons from Lord JJ.
Whoa! What?
Wings of Six, gather at
the Spiritual Precipice.
Oh!
JJ! Thanks for earlier!
Watch your words!
He's a transcendent being who's
bestowed our powers upon us.
In other words, he is like a god.
Wonderful scissors!
Senpai, where are we?
We're at the Spiritual Precipice.
It separates us from JJ,
an insurmountable—
Hey, do you have a death wish?
Lord JJ, the G Team has assembled!
A wind of disquiet nears,
but it cannot sway us, as of yet.
For now, contend with
the nameless chaos.
However, chaos and threat may
not be one and the same.
The judgement is yours to make.
What's this? A poem?
The white-winged bird is not
among you because it is lost.
Harden your resolve
and await the next word.
Gatcha!
Fine, fine.
Gatcha, Gatcha.
Gatcha!
See you, JJ!
Ow!
Be more serious, newbie!
JJ?
"To the north,
beneath dragons racing
in four directions,
the nameless chaos shall
appear once more."
Let's go!
H-He vanished!
Senpai, I'm coming!
Senpai!
You're going too fast!
What'd he mean by "beneath dragons"?
"Dragons racing in four directions"...
Oh, that must be it! Beneath that.
Amnesia Effect!
What?
This bus itself is probably the MESS.
Really?
They can camouflage themselves
as all manner of things.
Go, Bird!
Hey, newbie!
If you can't act, just stay put!
All right, let's give this a try!
Let's go, NOTE-chan!
"Go"...
"...Bird"?
Got it!
That's...
Gatchaman
is here!
Gatcha... They're here!