I'm pretty sure it was around here...
No fair, Sou-kun!
No fair, Souta-kun!
No fair, Souta!
Did you have to say that, too, Akane?
I just felt like it, really.
My name's Ruri.
What type of joke was that?
What?
If Her Flag Breaks
Flag 5
Believe and Wait for Me.
I'm not Going to be Late for My Date With Everyone.
So can I ask you something?
Sure. Whatever you want.
W-Well...
I really want to go out somewhere
with you, even if only just once.
Sure, that shouldn't be a problem.
I guess you did say okay,
but...
I can't believe you kept a secret like that
from your sister, Sou-kun.
I-I'm sorry!
I'm a thieving cat, a homewrecker.
Cats are cute!
We can all just accompany him.
Akane wasn't the only one who put
in long hours for the track meet.
We all did.
That's a good idea!
I see!
That means you should come
with us, too, Nanami.
Let's go, Nanami-chan.
Huh? I'm good...
I'm impressed you were able to include
yourself as part of the date today
just like that, Nanami-san.
No!
I didn't want this at all!
Okay, now we're going to decide who
gets to be with Souta-kun first!
Yeah!
I'm totally not going!
We've figured out who's going when.
Hurry up and get ready.
Also, I'm not going.
I'm totally not!
Did you have to say that twice?
Ruri isn't going, either, supposedly.
She's looking into something, I guess.
I see.
That's that, I guess.
Anyway, I guess I'll go have fun today.
Oh, no!
How careless of me.
Oh, yes, I may be staying here today,
but you don't need to get me
anything while you're out.
Especially these limited-time only cakes.
I don't need them!
I don't need them at all!
Why are you saying everything twice?
Megumu!
Sorry, I guess I'm a little late.
No, I just got here.
I'm going to be a man today
and escort you around.
She's pulling her boyfriend everywhere.
Must be nice to be on a first date.
Souta always finds a way into trouble,
and Akane and the others are
always doing something silly,
but they're all gone today!
I'm the queen of the Quest Dorm right now!
I can do this and no one can stop me!
We didn't get it again.
This is harder than I thought.
Souta-kun...
Huh?
You did it, Souta-kun!
Souta-kun?
I began to see flags,
not only on on humans, but on other things, too.
There must be something at Quest Dorm...
Souta-kun!
S-Sorry, Megumu.
You wanted this, right?
Yeah, thanks.
It's so cute.
Oh, yeah.
We should go someplace you
want to next, as thanks.
Hm, what do I want...
Oh, I guess I'm kind of hungry.
Then I know a good place!
It's very manly, with extra-large portions!
Megumu, what's this supposed to be...
It's a super-special parfait
that no one has ever finished.
Now show off your manliness and eat it all!
I don't think this is going
to work, man or not.
I'm so full...
Told you.
I'm so full?
Fine. I'll help you out.
Yep!
Friendship is when you
fight your battles together!
There's some cream on your face.
What? Really?
No, a little more to your right.
I can't get it.
Oh, jeez... Get it for me, Souta-kun!
Is everyone here an idiot?
Souta-kun, hurry.
Thank you, Souta-kun.
Yakisoba
Sorry, did you wait long?
No. I've been waiting
for you all my life.
You waited that long?!
It's Akane's turn now!
This is my first time going
somewhere with a boy,
so I asked my father and mother what to do.
Asked them?
My father told me this place would be great.
Hm?
Okay, here we are!
This is surprisingly normal.
My father said that any couple
that got on these boats
would definitely break up,
so they're perfect.
I get it now.
Anyway, about that.
We're not a couple, so I don't
suspect there will be a problem.
Actually, since we're not a couple,
then we'll never leave each other's side.
I never thought about that.
Of course, I'd like for us
to be a couple someday.
T-Time for me to show you my
authentic Italian boating skills.
Paddle.
Paddle. Paddle.
I'll concede that was impressive,
but something seems off here!
You mean like we're in the wrong
timezone and I'm Japanese?
Yeah, I guess you could say that...
Anyway, let's paddle together.
Yeah, that's best.
You mean we get to work
together, the two of us?!
Let me know if I do something weird!
I'll take one paddle,
and you get the other one.
Akane!
Are you okay, Akane?
Yeah.
Is something wrong, Akane?
I...
Thank you.
Y-Yeah...
A-Akane!
Yes?
M-My mom told me to
wear my good underwear, so I...
What is your mom teaching you?!
Did I do good? Did I do bad?
Who cares?! We just need to
get your clothes dry!
I guess we should go somewhere
where there won't be any people.
I have an idea...
It's so fun by myself.
I can eat and sleep as much as I want!
There really isn't anyone here.
It's always been like this.
Huh?
Not many people come here.
That's why I got to be such
good friends with her so fast.
Wait... Is this where...
I wanted to come here with you at least once.
Not too long ago I couldn't
even come close to here,
but now I'm fine.
You said that nothing can happen to me
until I see her again.
I haven't run into her again yet,
but I did meet you,
and have become close to you.
Akane...
That's why I want to thank both of you,
you and her.
Maybe I should be the one saying that.
S-Souta.
Oh, Rin-kun?
Okiku made me wear this.
I bet this frilly stuff
doesn't look good on me.
I know you think so...
A yandere flag!
N-No, it looks good on you!
R-Really?
Y-Yeah.
You're really cute.
Cleared
She's too easy...
It's great how quiet it is!
I wish it was this quiet all the time!
It's been a while since I could
just sit back like this.
It's been kind of busy lately.
Let's do something tomorrow, too.
Sure.
Looking at them brings back memories.
Yeah.
We were always together.
Oh, yeah, I forgot I have this.
Oh, this brings back memories.
So you brought these for me.
Every day was so much fun back then.
I wish life could've stayed that way.
Souta...
Don't look at me like that.
I'm having tons of fun right now, too.
Oh.
Rin-kun, you remember this?
Yeah, I remember.
That was when we took on the
bathhouse's chimney and won.
Speaking of which...
We did it, Souta!
Yeah, I'm glad we made it
to the top before I moved.
S-Souta... I...
Anyway, to commemorate this moment,
I say we have a pissing contest.
Wh-What are you saying?
What? You scared of losing?
Fine. You're on.
On your mark...
You idiot!
R-Rin-kun, what's up?
I-I know we were kids, b-but still...
All right! You're a man, take responsibility.
R-Responsibility for what?
You know exactly what I mean!
Y-You know...
Rin-kun?!
Hey— Rin-kun?!
O-Okiku-nee...
Sou-ku—
Hm?
You all want to go somewhere with me?
I can go with you if you really insist.
We're back.
Hm?
I'm back.
Rin-chan'll be fine once she gets a little rest.
I'm glad.
Sorry.
There might not be enough time
to go somewhere with you now.
It's fine.
But...
Oh, right.
If you're really upset about it,
then sleep on my lap for a bit.
Normally it's the guy who asks that.
I really like that.
Okiku-nee, that's...
Oh, this?
You remembered.
Of course I did.
What's wrong, Okiku-chan?
I...
I want to be a big sister.
But now I can't...
Okiku-chan.
Sou-kun?
This is important to me,
and I'll give it to you.
And... And...
I'll... I'll be your little brother.
Sou-kun...
I can't be your little brother?
No, you can.
I'm...
I'm really happy.
But...
Then will you call me "oneechan"?
Sure.
Okiku-neechan!
Thank you, Sou-kun!
You know, I haven't been that great.
I really haven't be a good little
brother character for you.
I keep telling you, you're not
a "little brother character,"
you're actually my little brother.
Yeah, that's true.
My real sister got mad at me for
being someone else's little brother,
but both of them are important to me.
You're so cute!
I love you so much!
Women
I had a great day.
It was so much fun.
I had Quest Dorm all to myself.
That's great.
I think it was bad of us to go off
and have fun without you.
Yeah.
You let us have your time with Souta.
I'm impressed by your kindness.
Hm? Yeah.
It's amazing how far Souta's come.
I never thought he'd be going on dates
with girls on his days off.
Is something wrong?
No, nothing at all.
You guys haven't forgotten, have you?
Hm?
You know, don't you?
Souta told you all, I'm sure.
While I was watching
the house, you know...
We know... what?
Souta and all of you suck!
Huh? I guess I was hearing things?
Souta-san.
I have a report on the
underground passageway.
Right.
I have concluded that the passageway exists.
However, according to my ground scans,
it seems the passageway was buried.
I see.
So I... dug it again.
What?!
I couldn't call myself an android
if I didn't have a drill or two.
You have everything, don't you, Ruri?
We're here.
So this is the First Gate.
The truth of the world might be...
behind this door.
There's nothing here.
Knight, magician,
bishop, ninja...
The same as the letter.
I don't really recognize the others.
I cannot scan the interior.
It seems to be made of a special material.
Guess we can't solve the mystery that easily.
What shall we do with this?
Let's just leave it here for now.
Roger that.
Okay, let's head back for today.
Hm?
So what's over there?
The outside world.
I've confirmed it connects to
the forest behind Quest Dorm.
What's this light?!
I believe it's being generated
by a large amount of energy.
Ruri, watch after the
people in the dorm.
I'm going to take a look.
What's going on...
I can't say I think very highly
of you messing with this world's flags,
Mr. Enormous Death Flag.
Roar! Gawo!
I've been wondering for a while,
but what's up with that roar thing?
It's an official greeting.
Official?!
It's not "roar," anyway. It's "gawo!"
The "wo" from "gawore."
In English letters, it's "w-o."
A very detailed answer!
Now say it with us!
I'm not letting up until you say it.
I guess this is the "teacher won't let you go
home until you eat all your school lunch flag."
Roar. Gawo.
Flag 6
Phew. Don't scare me like that. I guess you're just a little sister.
Too quiet!
Roar! Gawo!
If Her Flag Breaks
I hope you watch us next time!
Illustration: CHAN X CO