Thank you very much.
Okay.  We'll take a fifteen minute break
before we start the second round.
Man, I'm starving.
Chihaya-chan, I'm heading to the fountain.
If anything comes up...
When I play against Kana-chan,
I can move back seven lines.
Same when I play Desktomu-kun.
Porky and Taichi are stronger now,
but I don't want to rush myself,
so I'll move back three lines.
Three-syllable timing...
Four-syllable timing...
So the flower pe—
So the flower has...
The storm blasts...
to set the Tatsuta River ablaze
Timing is important,
but you also need to have control.
Still...
How do I get rid of that left hand?
What do I have besides my speed?
If she used 1/10 of that
focus on studying,
her grades wouldn't be fifth
from the bottom in our grade.
Chihaya Furu
Verse 20
The Cresting
Waves
Almost
Look Like
Clouds in
the Skies
I heard that you'll be
participating in the tournament
on Sunday in Kawaguchi.
Yes, I'll do my best!
I cannot allow you to go.
What?!
Wh-Why not, Sensei?!
The Yoshino Tournament is the
last major tournament before
the Master/Queen qualifiers!
Everyone will be participating as-
What day is the Monday
following the tournament?
Marine Day?
The first day of exams!
At this rate, you're
going to be held back!
What?  Seriously?  For real?
I realize that you are
dedicated to karuta,
but you need to start
thinking about your future.
My future...
Queen
East Qualifier
Shinobu-chan
Yoshino Tournament
What's recently been on her mind
Food
The new
Daddy Bear
Future
First
appearance
So I found a tutor for you.
He'll go over every one of your courses
with you in the next two days.
Don't do this, Desktomu-kun!
Call me "Tutor".
T-Tutor...
Please teach me...
I'm on the verge of failing
English and Math...
What about the Yoshino
Tournament tomorrow?
I'll be going.
Yoshino only has brackets
for Class A and Class B,
so I'll go by myself.
If we aren't going to practice today,
I'll head over to the Shiranami Society.
Hey, Mashima.
You placed second at Nationals
and the Saitama tournament, right?
Normally, you're allowed to advance
to Class A if you've
placed second twice.
Have you asked the
Shiranami Society coach?
He said that I had to
win a tournament first.
You too?  That's harsh.
Our society's the same.
So when I told everyone I won...
It's awesome, Yusei!
It was all thanks to Coach and the
other players at this society.
Idiot!
Don't make me mad, boy!
Your friends are the reason the old you,
who hates to lose, is back!
Isn't that right?!
I can only advance if I win,
so that's what I'll have to do.
I'm off then.
Yoshino Tournament...
If he wants to play in this
year's Eastern qualifier...
If he wants to make Class A this year...
This is his last chance!
It's too late to try to learn anything!
So memorize!  Memorize!
Treat this like a match
and memorize hard!
But I'll forget it
all before the test.
I made it past the second round!
I'm on a roll today.
Okay...
Starting with the next round,
my matches will be in the same room
as the Class A matches.
Eyebrows.
You're winning games.
How are you doing, Dr. Harada?
I'm winning, of course.
I'm playing the best karuta I can, today.
The strongest Class A players all participate
in the Yoshino Tournament to
prepare for the Master Qualifiers.
There are players from
Kansai and Kyushu here.
It's an excellent chance to see how
you match up against the best.
Everyone's preparing for
the Master qualifiers...
So am I.
That reminds me.
Have you run into him yet?
Huh?
Hey, hasn't Ayase been in the restroom a while?
Number two.
That or she fell asleep.
Forgot to put my phone on vibrate.
Sorry, Tutor.
I'm going to cheer for Taichi.
-Chihaya
That fool!
Huh?
Kuriyama-kun!
Harada-kun!
It's been ages since the last
time you came to Kanto!
My knees have been killing me,
but I had to come along
since so many of our
players are participating.
Mr. Kuriyama and Dr. Harada
You need to get those knees patched up
have been rivals since they were young.
so you can play karuta again.
Mr. Kuriyama?
I know!
We need to watch our health.
He's the director of the Nagumo Society,
where I'm registered.
Absolutely.
Once this is over...
The third round for Class A
and Class B will begin soon.
Please move to your assigned seats.
Taichi, hold on.
Here.
I guess I was mistaken.
I thought you would be in the
Class A tournament today.
Pass that on to Chihaya,
if she needs it.
Wataya Arata
Arata...
Arata... is here.
Wait!  Wait up!
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
Made it.
Wrong direction!
Wait!  Open up!
This is the wrong way!
Desktomu-kun
You realize that you're running
away from your responsibilities.
-From your tutor
He's so calm when he's angry!
What am I doing?
I'm getting nowhere with
studying or karuta.
I don't know what I should do.
Yet, what if Taichi is all
alone when he wins or loses?
I can't let that happen!
Taichi!
Well?  Are you doing well?
What round is it?
I lost in the third round.
R-Really...
Chihaya.
Arata is playing.
for there is no one else out here
Huh?
As I wait for someone
who will never come,
Wataya Arata
my body burns like the seaweed
drying on the shores of Matsuho
Long last we meet...
Mine!
Thank you very much!
I won my game by 11 cards to
make it to the semifinals.
I'm feeling it today!
Chihaya-chan is here?
When I must hide...
Would the mountain cherry blossoms...
When the misty bridge...
When winds send waves...
I lost in the third round.
It's not Arata's fault.
But...
Taichi...
It happened, Taichi!
It happened!
Arata's going to come back,
so we have to become stronger
and wait for his return.
Taichi...
It happened!
Part of me didn't want to see him here,
but deep down, I'm celebrating.
He's back.
Arata's back.
He's good.  Really good.
Tsuboguchi Hiroshi-san,
from the Shiranami Society.
One more card!
Give me "For the"!
"For the"!
It's gotta be "For the"!
"For the"!  "For the"!  "For the"!  "For the"!
I can sense Dr. Harada behind him.
leaving a hovering mist
above the trees and grass
For the cold nights...
Thank you very much.
I got the card?  Terrific.
But that was pure luck...
I chose a card and moved before
I heard the first syllable.
Yet he still almost got there first.
I would have lost if either of the
other two cards had been read.
The semifinals will
begin in ten minutes.
You're too slow.
Hiroshi-san is our ace.
He's not going to lose to someone who
hasn't played in eighteen months.
Chihaya, you need to-
Why did he go for that card?
How does he stay still when
a dead card is read?
What is his thinking process
for sending cards?
What? Why?  How?
Hey, Chihaya.
Huh?  What?
Sit down.
Oh.
We aren't even playing,
and you're already fired up.
Chihaya-chan!
What are you doing?
Huh?  Huh?
You came, Kana-chan?
We all wanted to cheer
for the president,
A disguise?
I'm sorry!  I'm sorry!
yet Desktomu-kun agreed
to help you study!
Arata-kun,
go grab your fourth place award.
Then you ran off by yourself!
We'll leave after that.
Okay.
You're leaving?
Nobody from the Nagumo Society is left,
and we drove here.
If we leave now,
it'll be the middle of the
night when we reach Fukui.
Then you can give this to her yourself.
Your cell phone number.
Don't make me decide
if she needs it or not.
We're going back to school now!
What?  Already?
Of course!
Right away?!  Really?!
Well, I wasn't sure...
About what?
I'm no longer here,
so I didn't know if the two
of you were a couple now.
No, definitely not.
Really?
You're actually pretty
sensitive about that stuff.
I'm no longer here...
Hey, don't space out!
You can't afford to
waste a single second!
Read your textbook!
That's not on the test!
Start from page 92 for Classic Lit.!
The Tale of Genji
Lady Murasaki Shikibu
Long last we meet...
You mean Lady Murasaki Shikibu?
It seems to fit Arata.
Whenever I get to meet him,
he has to leave right away.
It sounds like a love poem,
But this poem is about a girl who
was her childhood friend, right?
It fits perfectly.
Lady Murasaki Shikibu
Long last we meet,
only for me to leave hurriedly,
for I could not recognize you,
like the moon hidden behind the clouds
It sounds like a love poem...
No swinging on the train!
It was like water...
flowing around me.
Like I was gulping down soft water.
T-Tutor...
Sorry about running off.
Kana-chan sent a message to
let us know how Mashima did.
Oh, yeah.
He lost in the third round.
Was he depressed?
Um, er...
Mashima spends most of
his time on karuta,
but he always has the top
test scores in our grade.
If he doesn't, he'll have
to quit the karuta club.
You have to do the things
you don't want to do,
before you can do the things
you truly want to do.
I'm very sorry!
I'm going to study hard now!
I've mastered English already.
I can catch up!
Excuse me, we close at 7.
I'll lock up for you.
Ms. Miyauchi...
I'll keep an eye on them.
I realize that I also lost,
but how could you lose
by 11 cards?!
Well, I felt so content after
my match with Wataya-kun.
Aren't you mad?!
Well, I know my limits.
How was your match against Arata?
I hated it.
Really hated it.
He was clearly thinking
through every move,
but I couldn't tell what he was thinking.
Having said that,
Master Suo wouldn't bat
an eye against him.
Master...
He mentioned the Master
while talking about a player in his
first year of high school who just made Class A.
I'm going this way.
Bye.
Hiroshi-san is looking ahead
to the Master qualifier.
I should have watched them play.
I should have watched from
the very beginning.
Eyebrows.
Yes?
I've been thinking.
You placed second in two Class B
tournaments this summer, correct?
If we go by the official standards,
you're qualified to be in Class A.
This would break the
Shiranami Society rule,
but would you like me to promote you
to Class A so you can
play in the East qualifier?
Chihaya-chan and Glasses are
waiting for you in Class A.
Promote?
An empty train is passing
through platform 2.
Frustration will not last forever.
Nobody can keep on going
without some measure
of reward.
Please don't do that, Doctor.
That's not like you.
What?
Doctor, I'm not so much
focused on making Class A
as I'm focused on becoming
someone who doesn't run away.
Arata-kun's sound asleep.
He was nervous about
meeting his old friends,
but I guess it was worth the trip.
Drink...
Gulp it all down.