The American Industrial 30 Average
fell for the third day in a row,
marking the largest drop this year—
The Angel Boat has taken control
of 72% of all financial markets.
Infrastructure is failing all over the place.
We're losing control of the control circuits on our
weather satellites.
Relax.
He's already on his way.
Oh?
A human in our cyberspace...
How rare.
So you're the Angel Boat, huh?
That was our old name, the one we
used when we managed the network.
We are now the gods that control
the real world!
A mere human dived into cyberspace...
An act akin to exposing their fragile psyche.
I commend his bravery, but...
You programs sure like to talk.
What's going on?
What did you do, human?!
Giving a long speech
in front of your enemy...
That's a death flag.
If Her Flag Breaks
Flag 12
It's a Cruel World. I'm Going to Take a Look in the Shadows.
Who's Souta-kun?
Huh?
Oh, I get it.
You're mad at Souta, too, aren't you?
Yeah, sometimes we have to teach him a lesson.
Uh...
Is Souta-kun a friend of yours, Nanami?
Huh?
Maybe you introduced me in the past?
I'm sorry if I forgot.
Nanami-chan!
A little brother?
I don't have a little brother.
A male childhood friend?
No, no one like that.
The only guy at Quest Dorm?
You're looking at him right now!
The reason why I'm studying abroad?
That's because I wanted to study
at the same school as you, I did.
Purple flag?
Who's that?
Okay,
let's get homeroom started.
Right here!
This is...
This is Souta's room!
Calm down.
Did you forget that this room was locked?
Locked?
Why?!
Why?
Akane-oneechan fell through the floor in
the room and there was this big accident.
Luckily, Mahougasawa-kun was uninjured.
But the place is still dangerous.
We closed it off.
I'm sure you're tired after the fair.
Get some rest.
What's going on?
That's not what happened...
Fall back, Hatate Souta.
Fall back?
The network in that area
can no longer be used.
The Council of the Seven Virtues used
information warfare to watch over the world,
and occasionally, direct it.
You could say that the world is centered
around the Principality of Bladefield.
In conclusion, as long as this country exists,
then the world shall not perish.
Hatate Souta, protect the world,
protect Bladefield!
Behind you rests the main server
for the Principality of Bladefield,
and if it is destroyed,
then the world will end. Period.
The virtual worlds are no exception.
The virtual worlds...
How amusingly simple.
I won't let a
single one of you through!
I'm going to protect them!
I won't let it all
end now!
Happy graduation!
Thanks, everyone.
But while I'm happy, I'm also a little sad.
Yeah, we're not just saying goodbye to you,
but to Quest Dorm, as well.
Yeah, it was set to be demolished
once you graduated...
I guess it makes sense given
the incident with Akane.
I know we might not want to leave,
but let's get going.
To new pastures!
I know it's weird to be asking this now,
but why were we all living
in this dorm, anyway?
That's a good point.
It's far from school,
and it's a pain to commute every day.
Yeah, but it was home to us.
I won't live here unless
I get that corner room!
Akane-chan?
Maybe she forgot something?
Forgot something...
I can't stand not solving
any mystery
that catches
my eye!
To Hatate Souta
A letter?
What's up with this letter?
This is my handwriting...
Nanami-san.
Ruri?
Why are you...
I didn't think you'd break through
Souta-san's protection mechanism.
Protection mechanism?
You remember Souta?
I'll give you back everything
I've been keeping.
Huh?
Where am...
It's been a while.
Who are you?
Me?
I'm Souta's older sister.
Nanami.
You're...
Have your memories not fully
synchronized yet?
No, they're still a little fuzzy.
But
I never would have thought that this
was a virtual world on a network,
and that Souta was my
brother in the real world...
It's true.
You were so close, that you followed him
to this virtual world because you were worried.
The Angel Boat, located in
the real world, staged a
revolt against humanity.
The Council of the Seven
Virtues went into action,
and that was the start of everything.
Why the Council of the Seven Virtues?
They're only a special
organization within Bladefield.
That's only what they wanted
everyone to think. Right?
I'm starting to remember.
The Council of the Seven Virtues is a
secret organization that controlled
the world's information networks,
through which the Bladefield Principality was
manipulated into becoming a greater global power.
Of course they couldn't allow the
Angel Boat to take over the network.
And that's when Number Zero
took notice of Souta.
Why would they try to use the prince
of the country which they serve?
The fairy tale told in the Principality.
Hm?
All of that was true.
The founder,
Kagura Bladefield, was said to
be a descendant of one of the
heroic female knights who
fought against the demons
and the man that had turned into the flag.
It is said that every
generation the royal family
has someone born with superhuman powers.
And that's Souta?
Number Zero connected Souta's consciousness
with several virtual worlds,
and through a massive amount of simulations,
tried activating his superhuman powers.
So I went into the virtual
worlds trying to save Souta...
Trying to save my brother?
That's right.
But Number Zero detected what you
were doing, and interfered,
and we... we were separated
into two sets of data.
And so I was imprisoned
in this virtual world.
And I was made into her pawn—his classmate.
I know I'm just trying
to recall what happened,
but I'm started to get mad.
Me, too.
But there was something she couldn't prevent.
That's where...
...I came in.
Ruri?
I managed to escape from
my imprisonment, but...
While I was configuring the
program that would save Souta...
I ran low on power.
I found Ruri's body by accident,
and I guess you could say I borrowed it.
Of course, I couldn't say anything
and slept within her.
But as a result, there was a
new personality, a new "Ruri" born,
and my thoughts and emotions were,
albeit faintly, sketched into her AI,
so that she would help Souta out.
Anyway, I guess it's about time.
Now that our synchronization has finished,
it's time for us to become one.
That is what is to be.
But more importantly,
Souta is alone, fighting away in cyberspace
where time has no meaning.
We must save him.
And we will,
with the heroes who brandish the Royal Flag—
those that care for Souta dearly!
I remember everything now.
Why I patterned everything
after the fairy tale...
The fairy tale we heard from our mother.
We shed tears hearing the fate
of the man who became the flag,
and talked about it together...
No matter how cliché,
how deus ex machina it feels,
it's better to have a happy ending
rather than a moving, bitter one.
Let us go then, you and I—us.
Indeed.
Together,
to...
...Souta.
Ruri, could you help me?
Do I need to answer that?
Indeed.
Akane...
I... I don't understand.
It feels like I've forgotten
something important,
but I don't know what that is.
Akane...
I want you to save him.
Do you think I wouldn't listen to a
request made by my best friend?
Thank you.
Guys...
What's in this thing?
Who knows...
I have no idea.
There's only one reason
I've brought you all here.
I want you to
help my younger brother, Souta.
That's the guy you've been
talking about, right?
Your brother?
Indeed.
I heard that both you Nanami and
Hakua are only siblings.
No way!
You mean Father had adulterous relations in the thick steam of the hot spring, he did?
He'd be your older brother, Hakua.
Onii-sama?
So he means a lot to you, right?
Yes,
and to all of you, too.
That just means
we'll have to help!
Yeah, there's no reason not to help you.
Just let my manliness take care of this.
You guys...
I thank you all!
How could I forget someone so important...
Sou-kun.
Souta-kun.
Souta.
Little Souta.
Hatate Souta.
Onii-chan.
Souta-kun.
Souta-oniisama.
Hatate-kun.
Hatate...
Safety release confirmed!
This is our final hope which
Nanami-san has entrusted us!
Would you like to activate the
dimensional tracing program?
Yes or no?
Yes!
You're more perfect than I imagined.
I couldn't expect more from a
descendant of the Royal Flag.
Fight as long as you live!
Fight for our world.
No, for our homeland, for Bladefield!
I've come this far and now the
defeat flag shows itself?
This is just a fake ocean...
This is nothing!
I need to break them...
Break them now.
It can't be...
Why...
The Premium Ambriel...
I guess this would be
the reinforcements flag.
N-Nanami!
It can't be...
Why?
Your older sister and her
merry band of friends have arrived!
Roar! Gawo!
And all of us together...
Flag 13
If His Flag Breaks
Roar! Gawo!
If Her Flag Breaks
Make sure to watch next time!
Illustration: Ito Noizi