In this world, dominated by machines,
some humans side with the machines.
Everyone has their own reasons.
You're going to side with the machines and sell out the humans?
What do you know?
Damn you!
Machines and humans are the same.
Just kill me!
No! We are not the same.
God created this world in seven days.
Isn't it just as easy to destroy it, then?
But why?
Seems it's a great deal of trouble.
Big brother,
this is the gun you gave to
the little lady, isn't it?
I fixed it up great.
Here! All repaired.
Take better care of it.
Got it.
Thanks.
You're pretty careful.
Don't sneak in like a thief.
You might end up being shot.
Sorry for last time.
My information was wrong.
Don't get your information wrong.
I'm okay.
Does your "okay" means you
want it or you don't?
No, I don't want it.
There's one named Jay.
Jay?
An officer in the machine
military. High-ranking.
You're his target.
You're certain this time?
Yeah...
So you come here to say what?
To tell you to be careful.
Is that it? Just "be careful?"
And you're not going to do anything?
I know that style.
You take no risks,
just saying "good luck" or talking
about how you "care about me."
It doesn't cost you anything
to say that, does it?
What good do you think that is
to the person you're talking to?
You just want to please
yourself, you know that?
You're right.
He has a special gun, I heard.
Special? How?
I don't know.
Hey, hey. Wait a second.
What do you want to do,
you puny humans?
You want to mess with me, human?
Better stop looking down on the machines!!
You probably wonder how long I'd continue
to sing in front of Machines.
You may think its worthless,
but I'm a singer.
I cannot live without singing.
Even in front of machines,
it's better than not singing.
That despair is the "sickness unto death."
Kierkegaard, wasn't it?
I agree with him.
So I'll keep on living and stay optimistic
under any devastating conditions.
Machines want to copy everything humans do,
so I sing for them.
But at the same time,
they need to feel fear as well.
Otherwise, they wouldn't be the same as us.
Though, I do not know if they have
this emotion we call fear.
"Isn't it dangerous," you ask?
Of course, it is dangerous.
But that's where the fun is.
It makes me feel alive.
Even in the Reserve Area, if we
continue destroying them,
they'll strike back.
That's the fun part.
You see, I'm not afraid of dying.
I want to die properly, if I can:
die properly as I feel the fear.
Oh, it's time the little lady got here.
I heard about you from Xiaogang.
You are one of Eleven.
Isn't this a Wizard Gun?
You know of them?
I've heard about it, but this is
my first time seeing one in person.
Care for a drink?
I don't drink alcohol.
We, Eleven, are born to resist
against machines.
We're monsters, in a sense.
I'm not a monster.
I'm not the same as you.
It is not the strongest of
the pieces that survives,
nor the most intelligent, but rather
the one most adaptable to change.
Evolution Theory...
No point quoting Darwin now.
Machines acquired intelligence, and
they're destroying human society.
You're still so young.
Youth doesn't necessarily solve everything.
Life isn't about holding good cards;
it's about playing those you hold well.
What's your card?
I wonder too.
I haven't made up my mind.
Right. Just look after your card well.
You might be better off
doing what you want by yourself.
Don't you want to listen to my singing?
I'm leaving.