That damn Sanada Yukimura
dared to embarrass me!
I didn't expect my plan to backfire.
This is all your fault!
What an accusation.
What will you do?
Will you have me killed, Lord Ieyasu?
You must stop at nothing
to capture Yukimura!
Well, now.
I doubt he's the type
to come along quietly.
Then kill him!
Execute him on the spot!
The Birth of a Warrior
Sanada's party seems to
be heading toward Omi.
He must intend to flee to
Ishida Mitsunari's castle.
I won't let Sanada or the
Kushimitama escape.
Hey, old man.
Why don't you tell us
what you actually did?
It seems Ieyasu really didn't
appreciate my performance.
That can't possibly be the whole story.
Who cares? It's funny.
If anyone comes after us,
we'll slaughter them.
I'll kill them. I'll kill them all!
There he is! It's Sanada!
Get them!
They just won't give up.
Whose fault is that?
Isanami, get on Rokuro's horse.
Huh?
Saizo, Kamanosuke.
Go ahead.
Way ahead of you.
Yukimura-sama!
Ben-chan?
I thought you'd be coming back this way,
so I've been waiting for you.
Good work, Benmaru.
Better safe than sorry.
Yeah, right.
I bet you set those traps for us,
so you could laugh at us again.
Ben-chan, I'm so happy to see you again.
Miss.
Our pursuers must have
heard that explosion.
Yes.
Let us hurry.
I doubt we'll be able to escape so easily.
They're fast, too.
Saizo, Kamanosuke.
Scout the road to Sawayama.
We'll hide in the forest up ahead.
Got it.
Let's kill them all.
You don't know what
scout means, do you?
Scout our enemies' guts, right?
Moron!
I can't tell if they're on
the same wavelength or not.
Isanami, are you tired?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I don't mind the view,
but you should cover up.
Yukimura-sama.
Don't worry. Saizo will be
back before you know it.
We'll return to Ueda soon.
Okay.
What is this?
They put up barricades everywhere.
What're we supposed to do?
Hurry. Let's go back.
I wonder if our lord will praise us.
It's no use. Every road has been blocked.
If we continue on our path,
we'll end up at Lake Biwa.
They must intend to cut off our
escape and kill us in one fell swoop.
We won't be able to swim. It's too cold.
Old man!
Don't worry.
I've got my warriors.
How can you say that?
You're as demanding as always.
As long as I have you,
I know we'll make do.
No, you won't.
Thanks for the other day.
You came all the way here to thank me?
You fool, I'm the one chasing you.
At least, I'm pretending to be.
I'm here to reclaim what you stole!
That's quite the accusation, Masamune.
Besides, you can't handle this treasure.
You arrogant bastard!
I'll crush you!
I didn't expect you to bring so many men.
Kanetsugu joked about it,
but he wasn't too far off the mark.
You're a coward.
Sanada Yukimura!
Whoa, there.
I won't let you touch
the old man or Isanami.
Here they come.
Like hell they are!
Ougi Otsumuji!
Run, Isanami!
Looks like quite the brawl.
Guess I'll join them.
There!
I won't go easy on you.
What is this?
We can't go any further.
Old man, Isanami!
Are you all right?
Seriously.
I didn't expect you to make it this far.
Thanks to you,
we've got more work to do.
Date ninja?
Don't worry.
I'll finish this quickly.
He's the Iga Marici.
I heard he's a stone cold killer.
Saizo!
You actually believe a guy hanging out
with this bunch is a stone cold killer?
I don't know about this Iga Marici,
but it sounds like a load of crap!
Saizo, you're scared, aren't you?
Of fighting for someone.
I can't get enough of those eyes.
You're completely emotionless.
All you do is kill.
You're my one light in the darkness.
We need you.
I have my warriors.
I'm not an Iga ninja.
I'm one of Sanada's warriors,
Kirigakure Saizo.
Here they come.
Time to have some fun!
What are you doing?
There's only five of them!
My lord?
I never expected much
from these fools anyway.
It's time to end this, Sanada Yukimura.
Naval units?
Are they the enemy's reinforcements?
They sure know how to
show us a good time.
Lord.
Please stand back.
What are you bastards
doing in my territory?
Kakei-san?
Fire!
He's got the devil's own luck.
Safe!
Yukimura-sama, I am glad
you are all right.
Has everyone else been well?
Yeah. You seem well, Kakei-san.
You saved our lives.
No. It was not me, but this fellow.
Wanna come live on my boat?
I'll give you everything you want.
Who do you think you're talking to?
I'll kill you.
What a scrappy woman you are.
You're perfect for a pirate.
Huh? What makes you think I'm a woman?
I'm a man!
What?
This guy's a dude?
Seems that way.
Jinpachi, you must not speak
to Yukimura-sama that way.
Now, now. It's quite all right.
I am Sanada Yukimura of Ueda.
I must thank you.
I'm Nezu Jinpachi.
Wine and women are my pleasure.
My boat is my love.
Live for fun is my motto!
Another weirdo.
You've got the right idea.
That's a huge cat!
Kitty, kitty.
He's so cute.
He's so fluffy.
I only helped because you told
me there were hot chicks,
but this hardly seems worth it.
How dare you be so impolite?
How am I being impolite?
On this ship, my word's absolute.
Um, I'm a girl.
Who has time for a
flat-chested dog like you?
Keep your mouth shut, kid.
Flat-chested... dog...
Where's the busty blonde you
were talking about, Juzo?
There is one in Ueda.
You bastard.
How dare you insult Isanami?!
You moron, we're on a boat.
You'll follow my rules
while you're on my ship.
He stopped Seikai's club
with his bare hands.
Jackass!
Onii-chan!
Seikai!
What was that? It felt like a shock.
Go take a nap, you musclebound kid.
Jinpachi!
You're way too weak to be
getting violent on my ship.
Besides, I haven't given these
guys permission to ride.
What are you saying?
Juzo, I know we've made
a brothers' pact,
but I don't owe these clowns anything.
Which means...
I'll test you to see if you're
worthy of riding on my ship.
Sounds interesting.
Think you can win, boy?
This smell...
It's sake.
What?
What'd you think it was?
Swords aren't the only
way to settle matters.
If you can down all of this,
I'll let you ride on my ship.
Very well. We accept your challenge.
Are you stupid?!
Look at how much is in there.
Can't you see how wasted you'll get?!
No matter.
This isn't the time for heroics.
I've never had anything other
than the temple's sake.
I'm so excited.
This'll be my first drink.
I hope it's good.
This isn't for kids!
What?
Don't "what" me!
You don't know what you're getting into!
Why're you being such a square, Saizo?
Already?
Come on.
Let's drink!
I wonder how Yukimura-sama
and the others are doing?
I hope he hasn't gotten himself into
trouble with the women in the capital.
The mansion's been practically empty
since Kamanosuke and Seikai left, too.
What are we going to do if
something happens to them?
Nothing will happen. I am here.
You never waver, do you?
You are also here.
Oh, really?
I'm honored.
Delicious.
Is it? Drink up.
You're a strong one, aren't you?
It's been a while since I've seen
someone enjoy sake so much.
I could never stop
drinking such good sake.
Why don't you have some more?
Why am I the only one
drinking from a bowl?
Onii-chan, you'll catch a
cold if you sleep out here.
The sake's good, but I'm hungry.
Miss, apparently this guy's
not a cat, but a panther.
A panther?
Right, Veronica?
Ver... Vero...
Vero...nica? Panther?
Which?
Miss!
Are you drinking?
Kakei-san.
A ninja never gets drunk.
Of course not.
I've built up a tolerance
against alcohol and poison.
But, Kakei-san, what are
you doing on this boat?
You never came back to Ueda.
Don't tell me you've decided
to become a pirate.
Do not be foolish.
I traveled the country
broadening my knowledge...
...as I searched for a new gun.
I heard a pirate named Nezu
had some imported guns,
so I found my way onto his ship.
But, of course, he was not
eager to part with his guns.
And then?
He challenged me to drink as well.
After the second barrel,
he called me his brother.
I don't believe this guy.
He happily gave me a gun,
though not for free, of course.
I've been working off
my debt ever since.
And he's as rigid as always.
Well, you saved us because you
happened to be on this boat.
Why were all those men
chasing you, anyway?
You'll have to ask Yukimura
for the details.
There's a limit to how much
I can do to protect him.
He even egged them on.
I can't believe the guy.
You've grown softer.
What're you guys talking about?
Saizo, what are you talking
about? Let me in, Saizo.
You're annoying.
You are acting like a
woman, Kamanosuke.
What?
Who do you guys think you are,
treating me like a woman?
You are quite the aggressive drunk.
I'm a man!
Is there something on my face?
No. Are you really the lord of Ueda?
You look like a common playboy
and his friends to me.
Don't I?
You're not even mad.
You definitely don't seem
like someone important.
Thank you.
What were you thinking then?
Surrounded by all those
men without any escape,
your only destinations
were Hell or Heaven.
Who knows what I would have done?
I don't believe it.
You can't tell me you
weren't thinking anything.
I had my warriors, so I
knew it would work out.
Warriors?
Or else I expected to meet someone new.
Are you a genius or a moron?
Who are you to ask such a question?
You're just a pirate.
Because I'm free.
You're always bound to someone
by invisible lines on land.
As long as you're there,
you belong to someone.
I don't belong to anyone.
I'm my own man.
On the wide open seas and
under the endless sky, I'm free.
I don't have to do crap like pay taxes
or fight anyone's wars out here.
The pirate's life is best for
drinking and having fun.
You don't like being tied down?
Yeah, I'll pass.
Those who are bound are
bound wherever they go,
and those who are free are always free.
Huh?
Whoever you serve and wherever you live,
if they are your own
choices, you are free.
Your heart can never be bound.
What would a lord with servants know?
That's not very nice.
You pay them, don't you?
Unfortunately, I don't have much money.
I've got hardly any land either. However...
They are all here because
they choose to be.
You're terrible.
Saizo?
I think I've been looking
for a place like this.
Captain!
Yeah! See you guys later!
Is the pirate coming with us to Ueda?
Seems like it.
What?
When did you trick him, old man?
We're gathering more and more people.
It's strange.
The bond between men is
an interesting thing.
Yeah.
First I met Saizo, and then
everyone else in Ueda.
Kamanosuke, Onii-chan, Benchan, the
pirate. All together, there's...
Ten of you.
Let's go back to Ueda.
Okay!
Tell me that busty blonde's
gonna be there this time.
You can count on it.
You're a strange one, aren't you?
Why are you going all the way to Ueda?
If I don't get to see the
girl Juzo was talking about,
this'll all have been a waste.
The busty blonde really
does exist, right?
You mean Ana? Yeah, she exists.
Did Kakei-san really call
her a busty blonde?
Yeah...
Saizo, Yukimura-sama's calling you!
Kakei-san, you may be serious,
but that doesn't mean you're blind.
The next episode of Brave 10
is "The True Face of Ice."
The True Face of Ice
Bring it on!