True Calendar Year 70
Sakimori Academy Entrance Ceremony
To all of our new students,
congratulations on being
admitted to Sakimori Academy.
On this beautiful Spring day,
you have embarked on a new chapter in
your lives as Sakimori Academy students.
I welcome you all
as your senpai in school, as
well as in life to some degree,
and am sincerely happy to be
able to learn alongside you.
You might sometimes have
misgivings about this new, strict
life away from your families,
and it might seem stiff
and formal sometimes.
I have no memories of anything up
until middle school. That's why...
That's the next town over from mine!
What a coincidence!
...I couldn't make small
talk like everybody else.
I don't know anything about myself.
Am I a kindhearted
person? Am I cheerful?
What's my family like?
Do I have friends?
What are my favorite things?
Before I talked to anyone else, I
had my hands full talking to myself.
"What kind of person is Marie Nobi?"
But that was always a
question without an answer.
- Why don't we go today, then?
- Can you go?
Sure, I wanted to check out
some accessories, anyway.
True, that store has all kinds of stuff.
Yeah, their stuff is super cute.
I...
Marie... I don't believe it, you're a...
Marie Nobi. Did you pilot a Valvrave?
What? What are you talking about?
This much power, just from
adapting the Valvrave tech...
Captain Cain... The Valvraves...
Both go way beyond human understanding.
X! Fall back!
I used up this much energy?
Yamada! Get up!
We're Kamitsuki remember?
You aren't dead, right?
No, somehow...
But my temperature's
maxed out. I can't move.
Löwenglitzen emission test complete.
Deviation from theoretical
values, 0.007%.
Lieutenant X-eins, proceed to Phase
8 after replacing energy pack.
Blitzendegen. Will replace energy pack.
Man, I'm so jealous!
I call dibs on a Kirschbaum
next time, got it?
All forces, we're pulling out!
Sir? The place I saw the
JIORans is farther up ahead.
This is one of L-elf's plans.
The other Valvraves are probably
lying in ambush up ahead.
Don't go around issuing orders!
What should I do?
I have command authority here!
L-elf's plan was to lure the
enemy out onto this plateau
- It's too great a risk.
- What is?!
and then use bombs to collapse
the ground out from under them!
L-elf is here.
He not only knows this terrain
like the back of his hand,
he's also trying to exploit
one of its features.
I have to risk it...
Its features?
There should be five Valvraves,
but there are only two here.
He has a reason for committing
only a small force.
A-drei? You're Lunar Orbital
Navy, what are you doing here?
He must be trying to bait us.
H-neun!
L-elf is hiding in that cave.
Bomb it from the air and
collapse the bedrock.
Are you sure?
Settling things once and for all
where we all shared in that sin...
Don't you feel the hand of fate at work?
He's there, huh?
Is something happening up top?
Someone is there who knows
both me and this cave.
We'll only catch half of
them, but we have no choice.
Podded missile volley, fire!
L-elf... Don't tell me
you had the same idea!
The Valvraves?
Yes. I heard that they
have come down to Earth.
And where did you hear this
bit of information from?
I do have one or two friends.
Besides,
don't you have dreams of
this country of students?
A-drei, where are you?! A-drei!
Marie? L-elf?
The Valvrave...
So, you're awake?
Don't worry. I no longer have
any intention of shooting you.
We've been completely
trapped by the cave-in.
Our only way out is to use Unit 1.
Can you hear me?
I can hear you. I'm just a
little overwhelmed right now...
What's wrong?
The wound, it's healed... Why?
You don't know about your own body?
I didn't know. I'm like Haruto?
Tell me. What kind of human am I?
Why am I missing memories?
Memories?
Yes. I only have two
years' worth of memories.
Because I used them.
You're that... from earlier...
It's because I used them.
It melted?!
Why haven't we heard from L-elf yet?!
He hasn't checked in!
It's Units 3 and 5 that
are the real problem.
What about Haruto's Unit 1?
I can't reach him.
Maybe I should go take a look.
It's too dangerous! We're
waiting here for L-elf!
Still no signal...
Even though I'm ready and
waiting to hack the ship!
They're finally here!
Look at all of them!
We can't handle all these!
The army's trying to save face, huh?
Too bad, we seem to be doing just fine.
X-eins! H-neun! We're falling back.
Huh?
Our objective is simply the operational
testing of the Kirschbaums.
Besides, as much as I hate to say
it, we don't have jurisdiction here.
Hey, are you all right?
Pull yourself together, K-zwölf.
Wait! Calm down!
Calm yourself, K-zwölf!
K-zwölf?
K-zwölf...
I've sent out a rescue signal.
Don't worry.
Y-Yes, sir.
You haven't mastered mental
control yet, I see.
I...
It's no wonder, then.
You don't have to worry, I'm with you.
What am I gonna do? The plan is a bust!
I can't even try to contact the
others, not with this guy here...
Lieutenant?
Could you step to your right?
Yes, sir.
We've stumbled across something
that really takes me back!
Just as you are doing now,
I underwent Karlstein
training in this area.
But then certain facts came to light
and I was forced to kill a friend.
Right here on this shoreline.
My friend was a Royalist.
That is, he had ties
to the old government.
If the military found
out that a traitor to
the current regime was
a member of our team,
the team would be put
on trial for his crime.
H-neun. X-eins. Q-vier. Me.
And L-elf.
What kind of crime?
A capital offense.
That's why we killed
our friend in secret.
In order to survive.
In order to survive...
"If you are going to be killed, kill."
It's something that my friend carved.
Pino is Marie's friend!
Friend? My friend?
1796 days ago, you and I first met.
Where?
Before the Valvraves were completed,
you and I were in the same place.
You were a test pilot.
That is what they called you.
My vessel was still very
small back then, too.
You climbed into me every day.
But you were lonely.
I'm lonely, too! So let's be friends!
Friends? You mean it?
Friends? I don't know
about any experiments.
I ate them. The information
you call memories.
Consumed? Used?
Information? You mean Runes?
Runes?
The elementary particles of information.
I see. The information that
humans possess is memories.
Then the reason I have no memories is...
Yamada! We're falling back to the sea!
Oh, crap!
Run!
Runes. My food. I use
them whenever I move.
Formless. Invisible. Energy.
I can't believe it, you ate my memories?
I can't remember it!
The school entrance ceremony...
How did I...
Sakimori Academy...
How did I get there?
Cherry blossoms?
The cherry trees were blooming?
It's no use! I can't
remember anything else!
What did I do at the entrance ceremony?
I... used Runes just now.
Now I get it.
It was all connected.
The Valvraves and my memories.
And now my oldest memory just vanished.
Help!
Units 3 and 5 are taking a pounding.
Unit 3 cooled down but still can't move!
Unit 5 is almost out of spare
Impact Booster coolers!
My brother and the others
have been found, too!
Units 4 and 6 are out of action!
That just leaves Unit 1!
I have to help them...
If I use this... I'll forget even more?
I told you to run, Senpai!
I can't leave you here!
Operate Unit 1, Marie Nobi.
If you don't, your classmates
will be wiped out.
I only have two years of memories...
The heat buildup isn't stopping!
Why won't Unit 3 cool down?!
Stop it! Don't hurt him any more!
I'm the leader!
The children have nothing
to do with this!
Professor!
I talked them into it!
Hurry out there! Save them!
Where's Unit 1?!
L-elf!
But if I pilot it... I'll...
Let's make new ones, then!
You can't create a past, but you
can make all kinds of futures!
Futures?
Let's make some future
memories together!
Together?
Yeah, together! Let's be friends!
Friends...
Unit 1! Who's in it?
Committing one more
won't save them now!
Crush them, Blume!
That's amazing! It can do that?
Haruto Tokishima. Let's
get to the transport.
You made Marie pilot it?!
She was Unit 1's original pilot.
Its pilot?
I'll explain later. Let's go!
It's okay. I'm still okay.
Incredible! He can bring
up that kind of power?
I can make new memories
and friendships,
so I'm going to go on fighting!
No!
Marie, you are broken!
Your limiter is broken!
You are losing lots of information!
That's why you were
fired! As test pilot.
Gap! Loss!
L-elf!
Resume operation. We're
stealing this transport.
I'm still okay!
Even if they shatter,
I can make new ones!
There's the signal!
Go 15 meters clockwise down
corridor 18, then go right.
Once you're through the authentication
gate and security door,
go straight 30 meters, then left.
You're five blocks from the bridge.
I'm okay! I'm okay! I'm still okay!
Three left!
It's up to you, Haruto!
Control established over transport.
Remaining enemy blocks, 12%.
I'm being hacked?
Ladies and gentlemen of
New JIOR, can you hear me?
We are the Dorssian Royalists.
We are prepared to offer you assistance.
Royalists?
Set your course to magnetic
bearing 37 and—
We're lifting off. We'll
retrieve Unit 1 in the air.
But I don't—
Just keep an eye outside.
Units 3 and 5 have landed!
It's stopped...
It's that thermal runaway phenomenon
that the Lunar Orbital Navy reported!
Marie! Marie!
Are you okay? You aren't hurt, are you?
Who... are you?
A friend?
Of course I'm your friend!
What are you talking about?
Oh... We're friends.
Are there more here? More friends?
Your best friends are here!
"They're idiots, but some might
turn out to be geniuses."
You were the one who said that to me!
I see... They must
really have liked her.
That girl, I mean.
Marie?
I see. I had friends like that.
Marie, what happened?
That's great.
I had friends who meant that much to me.
It's even bigger than it was in space!
Marie! Marie!
Are you okay? Marie?
Marie?
What's wrong? Come on, answer me!
Marie... Goodbye.
Next time, episode 17, "The Rune Abyss."
Valvrave the Liberator...
The system that will expose
the truth of the world.