Hey, wake up.
I picked her up on the northern front.
She doesn't have a name.
I've just been calling her "you."
Hey, say hello.
You can't treat a child like that!
Gil, she's no child.
She's a weapon.
Weapon?
Just a war tool.
Okay.
I'll take her.
I see.
I'm glad to hear it.
I've already made arrangements
with the army.
LEIDENSCHAFTLICH
DEPARTMENT OF THE NAVY
I demand to see
Captain Diethard Bougainvillea.
I told you, you can't see the captain!
There's a matter
that requires his confirmation!
Stop asking already!
-What is going on here?
-Captain! My apologies, sir.
This woman was demanding to see you.
Stand down.
Unless you want to die.
What are you doing here?
Captain.
As I thought,
once a weapon, always a weapon.
Captain, tell me!
Is it true that Major Gilbert
is missing in action?
You didn't know?
Gilbert is no longer...
That's not true! That's impossible!
The major is alive!
Why are you making that face?
You were just a tool to him.
You are just an emotionless tool,
so, how could you be sad?
Why did you tell her?
She should be able
to accept the truth now.
You idiot!
You always have the worst timing!
To top it off, you have no idea
about how women feel.
Hurry up and go find her already!
Yes. I know.
Oh, Young Master!
And who is this?
Could you draw a bath for her
and get her a change of clothes?
What should I tell the madam?
She is currently at the mansion in Leiden.
There's no need to tell her.
I am just looking after this girl
for the time being.
It's okay. Just come with me.
Ow! Stop! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Stop!
Young Master,
I managed to get her changed,
but she would not stop struggling.
No, that is all right.
Take her to the parlor once she's eaten.
Please.
You'll catch...
You'll catch a cold.
You have to use a blanket.
It'll be cold tomorrow, too.
Stop! No! You can't go outside!
What happened?
So sorry,
she's been looking all over for you.
She wouldn't even eat.
We cannot take her to the front lines.
The girl is too unstable.
Why are you opposing this?
This is an order from the top brass.
You've seen what she can do
on the training grounds.
She's only good for killing,
and completely useless otherwise.
Just take her with you.
-But--
-Don't get so worked up.
Just exploit this orphaned girl
as much as you can
and dump her in the battlefield
when she's no longer of use.
-She isn't ready...
-That's enough!
I don't have time for your hypocrisy!
This is an order! You're dismissed.
The United Gardarik Army
has begun advancing to Bociaccia.
We immediately set up a defensive line
along Bociaccia's capital city of Capria,
and they've now entered
a war of attrition.
Our forces number 30,000
to their 60,000.
Our forces are holding on, but the enemy
brought cannons to the front line.
Our soldiers' morale
has taken a hit from the bombings.
There's a chance the front will break.
-And, so, Major Bougainvillea.
-Sir.
I'd like you to lead a company
to take out the cannons.
Yes, sir. I will not fail.
You'll be staying here.
Don't move until I get back.
Understand?
Major, we are ready to go.
I'll be right there.
Major. An enemy guard.
What's going on? What's happened?
Enemy attack!
Contact the main battalion!
Leidenschaftlich is under attack!
Get more soldiers!
Sir, the enemy is close!
Attack!
Yes?
It's you.
Is the major...
Is the major here?
He's here,
right?
The Young Master is...
Gilbert Bougainvillea.
This is the major's name.
Violet.
You're not a tool.
You should become someone
that matches their name.
V...
Violet.
You can understand me?
Major.
Violet.
That's right.
You're Violet, and I'm the major.
Major.
Major,
I finished reading.
Good. Next, let's learn how to write.
Major, here is my report.
It's well written.
From now on,
I want you to hand in a daily report
to help you practice writing.
Understood?
I will submit a daily report.
While we didn't find his body,
we did find his ID tag
under the debris.
And so, he was deemed missing in action.
Gilbert is no longer...
Today is Thanksgiving.
This city was occupied
by Gardarik forces for three years,
but they were finally liberated.
Violet,
you did this.
There's a Thanksgiving tradition
here in Machtig
to give gifts
to those you are thankful to.
Violet.
Is there anything that you want?
Something I want?
Yes. Tell me something you want.
Yes, sir. If that is your order.
It's not an order.
I want to express my thanks to you.
Thank me?
That's right. For all the fight...
No.
Let's take a little walk.
Major.
What am I supposed to want?
Let's see.
A girl your age would want
dresses or accessories.
Yes.
In that case, I wish for
dresses and accessories.
What's wrong?
I see your eyes.
This is the same color as your eyes.
What is this feeling...
I feel...
when I look at this?
It's a beautiful brooch, isn't it?
Beautiful?
Yes.
I've never heard of the word
"beautiful" until now.
Is it similar to the word "pretty?"
Yes, I'd say so.
Are you sure you didn't want one
that matches your eyes?
Yes, this was the most beautiful one.
I did not know the word,
which is why I've never said it before.
But your eyes were beautiful
from the moment we met.
Major.
-The brooch.
-Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
WESTERN FRONT
OBERGERG
LEIDENSCHAFTLICH ARMY
FRONT LINE HEADQUARTERS
The Gardariks pulled back
from the west coast.
Do you think we'll be
home by spring?
Yeah, let's all make it home together.
Gilbert!
It's been a while.
Lieutenant Colonel Hodgins!
You don't need to call me that.
Yes, I do.
You have the higher rank.
It's strange how your blunt attitude
seems so endearing now.
You haven't changed either.
Even after becoming a lieutenant colonel.
In my case,
it's because they kept sending me
to places we could win without fighting.
Your family is an important
financier of our military.
You can't blame headquarters
for keeping you safe.
Still, I don't feel good
being promoted like this.
Anyway, what about you?
How have you been?
Eating enough food?
I hope you're getting enough sleep.
You can relax, he is only joking around.
He may be older than me,
but we were in the same class
in officer school.
I've seen her
at the training ground before.
You still had her by your side?
Isn't she the one
who wreaked havoc in Capria?
There are rumors going around
that she's your weapon.
You should make her
do something else.
Sorry about that. Um...
She's Violet.
She didn't have a name,
so, I gave her one.
Are you also using her
for Operation Regain Intense?
If this operation succeeds,
the enemy will crumble.
It will likely be the final fight.
Yes.
You know, once this war is over,
I'm thinking about quitting the army
and starting a company.
A company?
I'll hire you when I do.
I don't like the idea
of working under you.
Then I guess I'll hire Violet instead.
You know...
that might be a good idea.
Huddle up!
Major.
What is it?
-Do you no longer need me?
-What are you talking about?
After I am dismissed,
will I be transferred to
Lieutenant Colonel Hodgins' command?
Will I never receive any orders
from you again, major?
You've done nothing wrong.
We're going into battle in a few hours.
We can talk about this later.
This is the plan.
The enemy's main headquarters
is located in Intense, here.
It's surrounded by cliffs,
making it a natural fortress.
Attacking from the front
will be too difficult.
So, our artillery
will bombard the enemy first.
While the enemy is distracted,
we'll use the sewers
to infiltrate Intense,
rush to the cathedral,
and take control of their headquarters.
After we do,
we will send up a flare
to signal our reinforcements
to charge, and our operation is complete.
-Understood?
-Yes, sir!
Five minutes until artillery.
Okay, go!
Fire artillery.
Fire artillery!
Fire!
Follow her!
All squads, report!
Squad 1 has lost three!
Squad 2 is mostly intact!
Squads 3 and 4 have lost half our men!
We're going to need help!
Okay, Squads 1 and 2
will secure the perimeter
and draw the enemy reinforcements in.
Everyone left in Squads 3 and 4 will
take control of the cathedral with me!
-Let's go!
-Yes, sir!
Fire!
Gilbert, we're counting on you.
Major!
Circle right!
All units, charge!
Major?
Major!
Subtitle translation by
Zensho Yamamoto