Kobayashi!
Hmm?
Here.
Field Trip Notice
A lunchbox?
Yeah. Field trip, next week.
Oh?
Make one!
Sure. What kind of lunch would you like?
Oh, don't worry, Miss Kobayashi.
I'll do that.
I'm better at it.
Oh? Is that so?
Yes. I'm the best!
Hah! I'm better than the best.
I'm even better than that.
Oh? Look at you talk, Tohru.
Seems like we'll have to settle this.
Don't underestimate the master
of the house, Tohru!
What's happening now?
Field trip...
lunch...
competition! Three round match!
Field Trip Lunch Competition
Three Round Match!!
- The Next Day -
Commentator               Judge              Head Judge
Commentator   Judge   Head Judge
You guys even prepared this set?
You'll each be making three dishes:
a salad, a meat course, and a dessert.
Use all your skills and entertain me!
What is your character even
supposed to be anymore?
The ingredients are your choice.
Stay within budget as you
make your decisions.
Be sure not to strain
Miss Kobayashi's wallet.
Hey!
Now then...
Begin!
They're both driven to win.
Kobayashi's into it.
Oborozuka Shopping District
Fresh Vegetables
Vegetables, Fruits
Oboro Tomatoes
On Sale!
Sweet Tomatoes!
Meat
Done!
First dish, complete!
Contestant Kobayashi's appears
to just be cherry tomatoes.
Did you throw the match?!
Mine's a seafood and paprika Caesar salad!
There's no comparing the two.
Yeah, there's no need to compare them.
The winner of the first round is Kobayashi.
Wh-What?!
I can't accept that!
How did my special salad lose
to these cherry tomatoes?!
Here.
Allow me to explain.
That's because you didn't
understand what a lunchbox is,
Contestant Tohru.
The amount you prepared
is too much!
Shock!
I'll win next round!
Tohru.
Lady Tohru.
Huh?! Bacon and eggs don't work?!
Head Judge
Hamburger's better.
But bacon and eggs are delicious, right?
Hamburger's better!
Head Judge
They're no good.
I often asked my parents
to make them though...
Last is the dessert round.
Something in a cup, or a fruit, would work.
You're to bring one item that isn't cooked.
Yes.
Tohru.
This is unusual, isn't it?
For you and Miss Kobayashi to fight.
It is...
Why did I...?
I'm heading off.
Take care.
This is deplorable.
What's so bad?
I'm happy to see Tohru like this.
What should I bring for the third dish?
But I'm going to win!
Because...
Because!
This fight only happened because
you've grown so close to each other.
Hmm?
Maybe I should call it pro-wrestling?
Every now and then is fine.
She may be a maid,
but she can be my friend, too.
Are you saying you and a
dragon are equals, human?!
Yeah.
At least, Tohru and I both feel that way.
Mini Jellies
That's why we fought today.
Huh?
Is Tohru still gone?
Close enough to fight, huh?
Hmph.
Disgusting.
I'm back!
Huh? Miss Kobayashi?
You're late.
I'm sorry.
I won't lose!
Yeah. I'm not going to lose either.
Oh, I need to take off my shoes.
Third round complete!
Orange
What's that?
Oh, would you like some?
Sure.
It's good!
What's this? Where do they sell it?
Th-The shopping district, I guess?
She's done it now.
Yeah.
Wow, a fruit?
It's my first time seeing this.
I've won this round!
Hm?
Items from the other world
are against the rules.
T-Tohru!
Whew, thanks for the meal.
Sure!
Even after everything,
your food's still delicious, Tohru.
Jeez, you flatterer.
There's dessert, too.
What's wrong, Tohru?
Who would've thought I'd
find you hiding out here...
Tohru!
Elma
Our room...
Have you forgotten the laws?!
Dragons disrupt the order of this world!
You're returning with me!
Hmph, I see you're as damn stiff,
strict, and persistent as ever.
I'm not going back.
Lady Tohru and Lady Elma
are on very bad terms.
Oh?
Like cats and dogs.
Oh, did you learn that idiom at school?
Good girl.
They look like they're about to explode
any second, but will things be okay?
Last time they fought
three islands disappeared.
That's dangerous!
Our power's equal,
but this time I'll settle the score.
I can't believe she can calmly let her
stomach growl in this tense situation.
Dragons are imp—
Or maybe not. She looks embarrassed.
Blush
You've being very distracting, human!
That's quite the attitude from
someone who just destroyed my home.
Please follow our laws before you
try protecting order in this world.
Huh? Oh, um...
Even Tohru wouldn't do something like this.
Probably.
I'm sorry!
Wait, why am I the one apologizing?!
She's easily influenced.
Hey, she doesn't seem like a bad person,
so why don't you get along?
We're from different factions.
Not all dragons are united in thought.
There's the harmony faction
that values law and order,
the chaos faction that yearns
for chaos and destruction,
and the spectating faction that doesn't
work with either group or each other.
Wow.
So Elma belongs to the harmony faction,
and I'm with the chaos faction,
so we oppose each other.
So you're one of the villains.
No, that's not true.
I'm a good dragon,
on my best behavior in this world.
That sounded forced.
Anyway!
I'm taking you home, Tohru!
By force, if I have to!
Try it!
I'll eliminate you from
this world without a trace!
Take this somewhere else!
I've prepared another dimension,
so we'll do this there.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm surprised to see the fiendish
Tohru listening to a human.
What in the world happened?
Hurry up!
Ah!
You cheated!
I simply respected order like she said.
It was a peaceful resolution.
Now, now, time to fix what she destroyed.
By the way, where'd you send her?
The field Kanna and I played in before.
Where am I?
- The Next Day -
How dare you trick me!
You're back again?
I can't believe you sent
me to another continent!
Let's stop this.
I'm happy as long as I can quietly
be a maid in this world.
Tohru? What's going on?
Would you please understand?
Like I'd believe you!
You're planning to take over
this world, aren't you?!
I'm—
Be quiet!
I will take you—
Oh, my.
Haven't you eaten anything since yesterday?
I-I'm not from this world,
so I can't interfere...
Cream Bread
Oh, something like this should be all right.
Here, want some? It's cream bread.
W-Well, I'll kindly take you up on the
offer to help restore my strength.
What's this?!
What is this? This is super good!
It's melting in my mouth!
All right! I'm energized now!
Time for our rematch, Tohru!
If you leave, I'll give you all of these.
Cream Bread
Sorry for the intrusion!
Huge balls are...
balls are...!
Episode 8
New Dragon, Elma! (She's Finally Appearing, Huh?)
Hm?
Huh?
I'll be working with you starting today.
My name is Joui Elma.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
No way!
Wh-What's going on? Why are you here?
I could ask you the same, human.
Emergency Exit
This is where I work.
Hmm?
So this is just a coincidence? Why?
I-I'm investigating.
I'm investigating the cultural
standards to see if beings from
the other world really can integrate here.
I see.
She did say you were with
the harmony faction.
But hey, can you do this job?
You can't use magic, you know.
Silly question!
There's no way I can't do human labor.
Just watch me.
What the heck is this?
I can't understand any of it.
What is this box?
What is everyone doing with them?
Oh? Something popped up.
Then you do this.
Oh!
Then push this.
Human, you do some pretty difficult work.
But I've memorized romanized
character input or whatever, too,
so I won't stay behind anymore!
That so?
Now then, when will I earn
my pay for today's work?
Oh, uh, a month from now.
I can't receive it tomorrow?
No. We total out at the end of
the month, and today's the first.
Oh?
What do I do for rent and food?
Well, if you commute from the other world...
Oh, could it be that you can't go back?
Ah...
I don't possess enough power to
open the gate between worlds.
She came through the gate Tohru opened.
I thought your power was equal to Tohru's?
I'm just as strong.
But we were born different.
Hmm.
Oh, wait.
Takiguchi Butchery
Here.
Well, I'm sure you've got a lot
on your plate, but hang in there.
If you're going to be working with me,
I'll have you learn a lot more.
You have my gratitude.
Those are hot, so be careful.
Later.
So good!
I guess I should keep quiet
about meeting Elma today.
I'm home!
Welcome home!
For tonight's dinner...
What? What?
There's a strange smell on you.
A dog?
It's a dragon!
Are you secretly cheating on me?!
I'm not! Today at work...
An office romance?!
You've picked up another weird phrase.
Can't breathe...
Miss Kobayashi!
Thanks for your work today!
Thanks to you, too.
You've learned a lot about
PC operation, huh, Elma?
Leave it to me!
I'll prove myself useful at this job.
Well, you've still got a ways to go.
Oh, Miss Kobayashi, sweet chestnuts!
Let's have some sweet
chestnuts on the way home!
They're delicious!
Sure, sure.
Why, you...
- Sunday -
It's been a while since my last day off.
I want to take it easy today.
Yes, yes, pardon me.
I'll clean everything so you can enjoy your
day off in a clean room, Miss Kobayashi!
Huh?
Kobayashi Kanna
I'm grateful for that, but...
What are you doing?
How's that?!
When I get serious,
I can make a room spotless of all dust!
It's brand new, as if Shiva passed through!
Even the furniture's...
A space for relaxation
doesn't need any of that!
Please enjoy sleeping to your heart's
content in this spacious room!
As if I can!
Put it all back!
Good grief.
Kobayashi.
I'm hungry.
Oh, all right.
Let's have breakfast.
Hold it right there!
I'll make breakfast,
be it a full course meal
or an imperial feast!
Oh, shall I slaughter a cow?
Let me have a light breakfast.
Understood!
Done!
Sandwiches!
Oh!
They look good.
What meat's in—
Tohru.
Show me your butt!
You want me to satisfy your lust,
not just your appetite?!
Are you an idiot?!
Yes.
I knew it.
Tail, again?
What's going on?
What do you mean?
You're oddly gung-ho.
You can't tell?
I can't.
You're spinning your wheels though.
It's like you've reverted to how you
were when you first came to me.
Oh, coming.
Oh, it's fine. I'll get it.
Coming.
Miss Kobayashi! Good morning!
Elma?
What are you here for?
Well, you know.
You're always helping me out.
So I brought something to thank you.
What's this?
A protective charm.
It turned out well, so.
Wow, it's handmade? Thanks.
Ah...
So that's it.
Oh! Tohru!
Today I'm taking you ba—
Be gone, Elma!
Miss Kobayashi.
I'm selfish.
Even so, I'm holding back
and putting up with it a lot.
Yet, you're being mean.
I work hard too,
wanting lots and lots of praise.
Wanting you to pet my head a bit.
Tohru.
I'm not used to being wanted.
That's never happened to me before.
I don't have a clue what to do about it.
Often I think human relationships
are just confusing.
Sometimes I even put distance
between myself and others.
I've had friends, but never close friends.
So here.
Well, um...
I can't make it any clearer than this.
Take the hint, take the hint.
Yes, I'll take it.
Oh, right.
I'll make you a protective charm, too.
You'll gain the protection of evil gods!
It'll be great!
I don't need that.
You're surprisingly forward.
I'm not!
Next Episode
Tohru! You're too dangerous!
You know that yourself!
Elma, you...
What?
For now, please put down the
cream bread you're holding.
Th-They're good, though!
Episode 9
Sports Festival! (There's No Twist Or Anything)
I don't care.