New Year's
Another New Year
New Year's food!
We've got a lot here.
Let's see.
Everyone put work into their cards.
Oh, this one's from the President.
Pussy New Year!!
Amakusa Shino
Hey, hey. Come on, now.
Dum
Tweet
Ousai Academy Student Council Rules,
Article Two, Paragraph Twelve:
Dum
Cinderella comes running
naked at midnight.
What do you even say to that?!
Do you know what cherry
blossoms stand for?
No, I didn't know they
stood for something.
Tell her, Shino-chan.
Being well-cultured, noble,
pure, and innocent.
Ultimate legendary days!
Do you remember what I told you?
No problem here.
Of course.
Well-cultured, noble,
pure, and innocent!
Happy
New Year
Happy New Year.
Tsuda
Takatoshi
here
Tsuda Takatoshi here.
I'm here
at a New
Year's sale
We've been
here since
five in the
morning
I'm here at a New Year's sale.
We've been here since
five in the morning.
I didn't think you'd want to come.
I'm a little surprised.
I'm here to help
my sister carry stuff.
Hey, you're not
supposed to carry me!
Right... Sorry.
You sure don't want to be here.
Seitokai Yakuindomo
It's Happy New Year's
I brought some hot tea.
Thanks.
I feel warmer already.
But if you drink too much
you'll have to take a leak.
Yeah.
Marking territory.
Putting down fertilizer.
Why won't you say
"go to the bathroom"?
Happy New Year!
We're opening up!
Oh, it's a mystery bag.
That's up there.
Oh never mind, I can reach it.
Right.
Oh?
Happy New Year.
Ousai's a relatively
well-known school.
Make sure you all keep
yourselves in line.
Especially you,
Vice President Tsuda.
That was pretty good, Igarashi.
Huh?
This is what you meant, right?
well known -> gets around (F)
in line -> erect (M)
Hello, everyone.
Flash
Happy New Year.
Oh, Happy New Year.
Flashes her peace sign too
Huh?
It matches my "V-line" perfectly.
Got you now!
Happy New Year, everyone.
Are you taking pictures, Hata-san?
What are you taking pictures of?
Swap pictures.
Oh, I mean snap pictures.
Messed that up.
Huh? Did you really?
Taka-nii!
Let me borrow some money.
Guess I'll have to.
But I want it back
with some interest.
Always wanted to say that
Taka-nii.
You totally took that the
wrong way, didn't you?
Third
Trimester
What is your resolution this year?
I want to make good on my promises.
Makes sense wanting
to get things done,
given you're the President here.
Prez,
I need your approval on that
sign we mentioned ASAP.
Got it.
This is my sign to tell
people I need to get laid!
So you're wrapping your
hair around yourself
so they look like tentacles.
I don't understand what's
going on anymore.
My resolution?
I guess I want to
make sure I stay fit.
Well, that's just boring.
Boring...
You're the Vice President,
so you should...
Hm?
I can't remember what
I wanted to say...
I guess I want you to service
me more with your mouth?
I think you meant "lip service."
Resolution?
I guess I'd like to develop my
arm strength.
That's rather specific.
I picked up a ball that
fell near me the other day,
and this person wanted
me to throw it back.
There.
Flop
And well, it was kind
of embarrassing.
I see.
That makes sense, though you'll
develop muscles during puberty.
I'm past puberty.
Resolution?
I guess I want to do
better under pressures.
Oh, no!
Oh no! I messed up when I said that!
I can't believe I did that...
You're not acting
very calm right now.
I keep doing it!
Blow
Hm?
Also, I...
And you kept your calm there, huh?
Resolution, huh?
I guess I want to be
more honest with myself.
I see.
Hey, don't get the wrong idea.
I'm not doing what you think I am.
I'm practicing my soap opera moves.
I see.
My resolution for this year?
I want to get to the nationals!
You like martial arts too much.
Why all the passion?
I guess because of my parents.
They were always practicing
pro wrestling at night.
I guess you grew up innocent.
What about you, Hata?
You have a resolution?
My resolution?
I want to get a real
exclusive story,
but I think that'll be pretty hard.
My readers are all high
school students, too.
Why's that?
Kids like scandals regarding the
relationships between men and women.
What was it? People something
other people's misfortune?
I'm sure that something's
pretty salty, though.
I mean, a man and woman is involved.
It's "enjoy."
She got there before I did.
Squid and Takatoshi!
Squid &
Takatoshi
Nude!
Squid & Takatoshi Nude! #6
Seitokai Yakuindomo
What is it?!
Don't move, Hagimura!
This is fake slim*.
Continued
in the latter half
It's cold.
Really cold.
You two don't have it together.
Kids play outdoors in the cold,
and they don't have problems.
We're in high school now,
so we're not kids.
Yeah.
We might even be sent here
by the wind god himself.
You don't sound like
a high schooler.
Setiokai Yakuindomo
What it takes to stand above someone
Hmm...
It feels weird wearing new shoes.
Wearing shoes that don't
fit gives you blisters.
Oh, good morning.
Hi there.
Hey.
And if you rub that
area, it'll get stiff.
I didn't think I'd
get to say something
like that so early in the morning.
This world works wonders.
And you're thinking
about that this early?
Lunch
It's so cold, my lunch
got all cold, too.
Yeesh, it's a little bland.
Chomp
Rice tastes better
right after it's made.
Clothes are better right after
they're taken off too, right?
Don't look at me like I gave
you that idea at some point.
Yeah, that's true.
Prez, that's mine...
Oh, sorry.
I almost had an indirect kiss there.
I wonder if he wore your
panties on his head,
if that'd also be an indirect
kiss of a different type,
his lip* and your puss*.
I don't know if that helps.
I'm thinking of trying
to get a manager.
It's hard to manage everything
with so many members.
I see. So, what's up?
I want to create some fliers,
but I'm not good at writing
up stuff like that.
Do you think you could
write up something for me?
I don't mind,
but I think you should work
on that for your own benefit.
I agree.
I have until I have to send a
letter to my parents for my wedding.
I guess that's a nice goal...
Ousai Judo Team
Looking for a manager
Come to the dojo if you're interested.
Someone not currently in a club!
No experience needed!
Someone who wants to do something memorable in high school!
Maybe I'll give it a try.
Seriously?
Yeah.
Not in a club
I meet the requirements, too.
I'm not in a club.
No experience needed
I'm a virg*n.
You're not doing it. I'm
making that decision now.
Always come in from behind
Opinions are
split about how
practice is going
to continue
Everyone,
I have three arrows here
that Archery didn't need.
Watch this...
Snap
Everyone follow me!
Right!
She persuaded them by force...
Let's get a pork rice
bowl on the way back.
Right!
Hey
Hey, you can't go eat right
after you get out of school.
Growl
We have a reason.
We have a practice match tomorrow.
I see...
So you're going to have pork
so you don't pork it up.
I'll give you this
so you'll be safe.
I'm sad I get where
you're going with this.
They say pork will put
hair on your back.
It's cold again today.
No one catch a cold.
Don't shake your covers off while
you're sleeping, or something.
Everyone here is a heavy sleeper,
so I don't think that'd happen.
Bang
I heard that!
How do you know how
well everyone sleeps?!
How do you think we know?
Yeah, you need to tell us in detail.
The student council is tenacious
when it comes to stuff like this.
My shoulders are stiff.
snap
How about I give you a rub?
Thanks.
Rub
Come on! Grow bigger and
give her more backaches!
Scream
Stop!
You dummy!
Valentine's Day Plan
Next week is Valentine's Day.
We have to give
chocolate to Tsuda.
According to Aria,
Dejima-san is teaching people
how to make chocolate.
How about we all make some together?
That marker's almost out of ink.
You sure?
Class on hand job
Some of the characters
aren't written correctly.
Let's lend our hand to do the job?
Let's lenD OUR hand job?
The kitchen's pretty big.
You're good at making sweets?
That's right.
I can make anything.
I can make Japanese food,
Western food, sweets...
Get a man...
Okay, so let's start getting ready.
Right.
Huh? Did they not hear me?
Dejima saved my life.
What's that about?
Last night...
Roll
Catch
Watch out!
I almost fell and got hurt.
I see...
I see.
Wait a second.
Why was Dejima-san there
in the first place?
Next we'll be making our patterns.
Click
The breaker tripped.
Miss, where are you?!
Say something if you're fine.
I'm fine
I'm fine.
It's dark and something sexy
could happen, but I can't see!
I sense some bad energy.
Crap.
What is it?
What's wrong?
I wanted to see if the
chocolate hardened yet,
and then I slipped and my hand...
This might not be that bad.
Yeah, brings back memories.
You know when you're a kid and you
want to see how much
you've grown and stuff.
All right. I'm going
to remake the thing.
Takatoshi-kun.
Hm?
Here's some chocolate.
Some from me, too.
Thank you.
Hey, Tsuda, don't fall for them!
Yeah!
If you're going to be "dere,"
be a "tsundere" first!
That's not what I meant.
Tsuda, take this.
Thanks.
No, you're always
helping me out, anyway.
I think you have that backwards.
It's kind of embarrassing
to hand this over.
Suzu-chan, if it's hard
to give it to him,
just follow this script.
Tsuda!
I've got some Valentine's
chocolate here.
I don't want you to
get the wrong idea.
I had to make it. I mean you're
part of the student council, and all.
I see.
Depressed
Sorry you had to go
out of your way...
Huh?
This happens
when someone
doesn't get
that you're
being "tsundere"
Todoroki Nene's
Trivia
Todoroki Nene's Trivia
All right. We're
going to get started.
Wait!
What's that?
This is a traditional plant stalk
from the Kumamoto Prefecture area.
Back in the Edo period,
the Higo Hosogawa clan,
during one of the daimyo's
routine visits to Edo,
presented this sex aid to the
Tokugawa shogunate.
Don't try to make it sound fancy.
They'd take giant elephant ear
stalk and let it dry it out,
and weave it into a
cylindrical shape.
When you want to use it, you
let it soak in warm water,
and it becomes soft.
I see...
It's hard to describe,
so I'll just show you.
Zip
This is over!
Todoroki Nene's
Trivia
All over...
It's traditional!
It's almost time to think about
giving stuff back for White Day.
Please have
these!!
Please have these!
But it's kind of weird exchanging
presents with girls.
Well, you're an extremely
intelligent individual.
I can see why everyone would like
you, regardless of their gender.
Hey, what's with all the
sucking up, Hagimura?
embarrassed
Though if you're going
to be good at something,
sucking's probably it.
Maybe I was wrong.
Seitokai Yakuindomo
Vir*in
Taka-nii,
did you think about what to get
people in return for Valentine's Day.
You give candy for White Day,
but that'll get expensive.
Well, it doesn't have to be candy.
There's something else that
you can let them suck on.
Well, I can't go into more detail.
I think you already went
into enough detail.
Well, I came, but...
I'm not sure what to buy.
Oh, Taka-kun.
Hi there. Bark.
Uomi-sa--
Hey.
Onee-chan.
Very good.
White Day
You're getting stuff
for White Day, too?
Too? That's why you're here?
Oh, girls give each other
chocolates a lot as of late.
Wait, so are you giving it
to your fellow... virg*ns?
Surprise
No.
Who are you giving presents to?
The student council, the teachers,
and my classmates.
You're popular, Taka-kun.
Nah. I'm just socially obligated.
I'm not sure about that.
Some of those people
might really like you.
Did you find any pub*c
hair in your presents?
No.
I thought of making
stuff by hand, but...
You gave up on it?
It took more time than I thought.
The student council
keeps you busy, huh?
Also, you know what you're getting
if you get stuff off the shelf.
And you know there aren't
any bodily fluids in there.
That's enough.
Oh...
I forgot I was your
onee-san for a second.
Oh, Tsuda and Uomi, isn't it?
What are you two doing here?
Well...
Uomi-san is trying to take Tsuda
around and have him strip.
I think she's thinking something
different than the others.
I can't tell them I'm here for
the Valentine's presents.
I'll make sure they don't find out.
We're on a date.
They
found
out
after
all
So we ran into him while he's
picking stuff out for us.
That was bad timing.
I wonder what you say in
a situation like this.
Shino-chan,
Tsuda-kun is a masochist.
So I yell at him?
Worried
I'm worried.
Student Council
Here's a small token
of my gratitude.
Thank you.
Th-Thanks.
Thanks.
There's none for you.
But I had some of your chocolates!
Yeah, and...
Nude!
Squid &
Takatoshi
Nude!
Squid & Takatoshi Nude! #6
Seitokai Yakuindomo
Someone was trying to
make this worse for me.
Tsuda,
why are all of these people here?
That's because that's
everyone I ran into
after I went to the cafeteria.
Of course, I don't think
all of you are suspicious.
I want to hear your alibis.
One of these people will lie,
and another will be the culprit
Suzu head
I saw yogurt... on that thing...
when I first got back to the
student council room
from the staff room.
I see...
I got the mast*rbation aid
out of storage and my enema
really started kicking in, so
I had to rush to the bathroom.
Then when I got back to the student
council room, you were here.
There were a lot of questionable
things in there,
but it sounds like you're
telling the truth.
Shaking
I went to the dojo for fun,
met the President in
front of the cafeteria,
we walked together to the yard,
and Shichijou-senpai was there.
You're so scared, but what
you said sounded normal,
so that really worries me.
I went to the cafeteria, ran into
Kotomi, and saw Aria in the yard.
I'm a D-cup.
I put the white stuff on there.
Huh? It was you after all?!
Squid &
Takatoshi
Nude!
All of that, and it
ended like this?!
The End
Good morning.
Morning.
Tsuda, you haven't slept in lately,
even though you're not
good with waking up early.
I got one of those eco-pillows.
It's made out of natural materials,
so I'm able to sleep
on it pretty well.
Tsuda-kun!
It sounded like you said you
got a pr*state massager?
Pant
You ran all the way over here
to see if I said that?
Seitokai Yakuindomo
I can't believe
you're washing that
You've got a pretty simple
lunch here, Tsuda.
My parents were gone
on a business trip.
Yeah, but you still need to make
sure you eat a balanced meal.
How about I make you one tomorrow?
Are you sure?
In that case...
Could I ask you to make two?
Sparkle.
Oh, right.
Then do you have any requests?
Hm...
Anything's...
I guess it's kind of mean
if I just said "anything."
Maybe a sandwich, or something?
Man Woman Man
I hear those that like sandwiches,
also like sandwiching at night.
That's a lie!
How about cut up hot dogs?
That's pretty basic.
A lunch, huh...
I wonder if I'd look more
adult if I made him one, too.
H-Hey...
What do you like to eat?
Gummies, I guess?
Get the hint already.
The next day
Prez....
Kotomi, why are you so out of it?
I was so excited for your lunch,
I didn't eat breakfast.
Growl
I was just kidding.
Sorry.
This is good.
It's great.
I'm glad.
I'm sure you made it
with lots of love.
Hey, don't tease me, Aria.
I have lust in there, instead.
If that's the emotion that
got you to make this food,
I'm actually kind of impressed.
Suzu-chan, you eat a lot.
I'm still growing.
I won't grow if I don't eat a lot.
You're coming into heat.
Suzu Head
Height!
That was good!
No problem.
I'll wash out the lunchboxes
and give them back to you.
You sure?
Yeah.
It's normal to wash whatever you
borrow before you return it,
but I borrowed some underwear
from Dejima-san today
and she told me to return
them without cleaning them.
Make sure they're clean
before you give them to her.
Anyway, I'll see you tomorrow.
Right. See you then.
Oh, Prez.
Thanks for the lunch today.
I'll make you another
one if you ask.
Sorry about that.
See you later.
Right.
"Sorry about that," huh?
Oh.
Onee-chan.
Taka-kun.
Uomi... san?
Next episode
there will be blood
maybe?
Tsuda Takatoshi here.
Seitokai Yakuindomo
Next Episode Preview
I'll be a third-year next year.
I need to think about my future.
Huh? What's going to happen to
the Prez and Shichijou-senpai?
Yeah, what's going to happen?
I wonder what'll happen.
How are we ending this thing?
You'll have to see next episode.
Let's all see each other again!
How to talk about love properly
Long-range attack
Hair showing
Cherry Blossom Sky
You don't really want
this to stop, now do you?