What about these?
Miuna, those are weeds.
Probably shouldn't use those
for a bride's bouquet.
But they're so cute.
Aren't there fancier flowers like
roses or moth orchids growing around here?
Oh, henbits!
Should I really be helping
Aka-chan get ready to be married?
Well, it looks like hibernation
is totally out of the question.
But I guess it can't be helped.
What's wrong?
I'm a bad person.
Huh?
I want Hikari to be saved, too...
But for some reason, I didn't
want him to go hibernate.
And actually, I don't actually want
to be apart from Aka-chan either...
And yet...
So you don't want to be
apart from Hikari?
Does that make me a bad person?
I don't want...
Kaname...
I don't to be apart from him either!
I'm totally evil.
You're not evil!
I'm—
Nope!
I'd never lose to you! I'm totally more evil!
So you're Miuna-san...
A pervert!
Huh?
Miuna! Make him eat the flowers!
Take that!
Episode Twelve:
I Want to be Kind
We're so sorry!
Ahem.
I had no idea you were
Aka-chan and Hikari's dad...
Well, your fingers are super hairy and
you had a pervy aura so...
Oh, I'm sorry!
No...
Don't worry about it.
Please!
Huh?
Could you tell...
Aka-chan and Hikari to
go sleep in the sea?
So virtuous! Good girl, Miuna!
Please!
No one knows what will happen
even if we do hibernate.
Huh?
The threat to the surface is still
far off into the future.
Therefore, both Akari and Hikari might
be happier living on the surface.
Now that you mention it...
Yeah... Yeah!
Yeah!
Thank you, Mister!
Wrong.
Aka-chan's going to be your mom.
Oh, right. Um...
Thank you, Grandpa.
Huh?
I think Hikari and the others
should be out of school soon.
Yeah.
Please excuse us.
Hey, wait up!
"Grandpa"...
Hikari, where are we meeting up today?
The Fishery Cooperative.
Got it! Go ahead without me.
Where's Tsumugu?
Yeah, I'm having him go
with the wardrobe crew.
So with Chisaki and Manaka?
It's a little nerve-racking to have
those two go on the train into the city alone.
Thrift Store
Oh, this might be good.
That's a little out of our budget.
Then...
How about this?
I think the spot on that
is a bit too big...
Are you from the sea by chance?
Oh, yes.
Hey, if you're looking for a kimono,
how about this?
That's rather dull.
T-Tsumugu-kun!
Right?
But...
Look.
Oh!
It's so pretty!
It's just like I heard.
This was sold to us by a
lady who lived in the sea.
It's apparently made
to reflect Ena's shine.
I'll sell it to you cheap.
Thank goodness we were
able to get a nice one.
I know.
The hem is a little short,
so I'll have to fix that later.
Hey...
Will you guys come with me for a bit?
Just one sec.
I wonder who that is?
I'm pretty sure that's
Tsumugu-kun's mom.
Huh?
Here, take this. For Grandpa.
Okay...
I'm glad that you seem well.
How's Grandpa doing?
The same as usual.
I see...
Hey, do you want to
get something to eat?
I'm with my friends, so...
I see.
Enjoy.
Thanks.
You know, thanks to Miuna,
I realized something.
You knew of the danger that
was coming to the surface,
and for the sake of my future...
That's why you disapproved of me
getting married to Itaru-san, right?
Yet I had no idea, and
acted like a child.
I'm sorry.
After seeing her,
I realized something, too.
Huh?
If there were some way your mother
didn't have to leave us forever,
I probably would have chosen that.
Dad...
How's the Ofunehiki... and
the wedding coming along?
Apparently Hikari and the others are
taking care of my wardrobe, too.
Everything's so perfect that
I don't think I can tease him anymore.
I see.
I heard that the Ofunehiki and the
hibernation are on the same day.
It's fine.
Watch me be a bride from
the sea along with Mom...
Dad...
Stop.
You don't have to do that.
Let me say it.
This is the only chance I'll have.
When Mom died, you were the
one who had it the hardest.
And yet, you never let those
emotions show, and you watched over us.
After Mom died...
The first time you made soup for us...
I'll never forget how it tasted.
The giant and uneven pieces
of carrots and daikon...
It was clumsy yet warm and kind...
It reminded me of you.
The love... that you gave us...
I'd like to give that love to
Miuna and Itaru-san as well.
I'm sorry for being a selfish and
difficult daughter to the very end.
Thank you for everything you've
done for me over the years.
So cool!
We're gonna wave this.
Right.
So that Ojoshi-sama can head toward
the Sea God without getting lost.
So that everything goes where it belongs.
Without getting lost...
Everything goes where it belongs...
Here, hold it.
Hold it tight now.
So... heavy...
You can do it!
Hikari-kun.
When we do the Ofunehiki, do you
want to wave one of the flags?
Huh? Are you sure?
Wow!
You don't have any
strength in your back.
I guess it's too much for a kid.
No, please let me do it.
Hey, if you do it like that,
you're going to get blisters.
Hikari sure tries hard.
She's totally asleep.
Why don't you sleep, too?
It's hard staying awake because
your Ena's gotten so thick, right?
Yeah...
Hikari's gone as far as stealing
other people's lunches,
but apparently that's still not enough.
Maybe it doesn't just
have to do with food.
Maybe it's something much
bigger and periodic.
Was that okay with your mom?
Sorry, I ended up using you guys.
I don't really want to talk to her.
I might have thought that I was
the only one who was suffering.
Everyone is going through a lot,
and they're all suffering...
And yet, everyone is
still trying so hard.
I even ended up taking it out on
you and saying something awful.
I'm sorry.
It was pathetic. Truly.
Did you decide on something?
Huh?
I hear it in your voice.
I don't think boys that are too
intuitive are very popular.
All the sudden, we're back.
I don't remember what
happened after we sat down.
Manaka, your drool is sparkling.
Hey!
Hey! Over here! Over here!
Wow!
Such a big flag.
I wonder when Hii-kun became a guy...
Manaka?
I-It's nothing. Let's go.
We've got the kimono now
so it's almost done.
Don't mess things up.
It'll be fine.
Hey, over there...
Huh?
Oh, you're back.
S-Sir...
There's nothing to worry about.
Children's cells move a lot faster.
Their Ena developed fast,
so they fell asleep without
waiting for the hibernation.
Without waiting for the hibernation...
We're about to receive the ritual prayer
from Uroko-sama, and she'll go into hibernation.
You guys'll be hibernating before us...
Hm?
But it looks like your Ena hasn't
developed very much...
W-Well...
Oh, there they go.
No matter if it was our turn or the
surface's turn to do the Ofunehiki,
the songs were always our duty.
Talk about crappy singing.
Guess that's what you
get from people without Ena.
You guys teach them.
That's what happens when we hibernate?
When you actually look at them...
...it looks like they're dead.
Kaname!
That's what you wanted
to say, right, Manaka?
Hey, this is nostalgic.
Huh?
Oh, our heights!
157 Hikari
155 Kaname
154 Chisaki
Manaka
That's right.
We marked that at the entrance ceremony.
Since we did it in grade school,
we decided to keep doing it.
Hey, let's mark our heights now.
I'll go look for something
to write with!
Right.
All right, let's check
out the faculty room.
Okay.
We're counting on you.
You really are amazing, Hikari.
Huh?
Say, Hikari...
There's something I want to tell you,
so maybe after this...
Found one.
Right! Thanks!
What is it, Chisaki?
N-Nothing...
I'll tell you later.
You sure?
Hey, did you find any?!
Quiet down.
All right. This will be on the test.
Thanks, Namiji Junior High
Make sure you check your textbooks.
He's mimicking Sensei!
Hii-kun sounds just like him!
Sensei's strike zone
is on the higher side.
Sensei, I have a question.
Yes, Kaname-kun, what might it be?
Sensei doesn't say that.
Righto.
So what might it be?
How do you feel about Manaka?
Kaname, why would you do that?
This can't be okay as is.
Huh?
Even if we eat a lot,
our Ena keeps developing.
Once we hibernate,
there's no guarantee
that we'll wake up together...
I-I already know that...
No, you don't.
We may never see each other again.
Never see each other again...
That's right.
We don't even know if
we'll really wake up.
Never see each other again...
I...
Hikari!
love Manaka.
H-Hii-kun...
Come on, stop joking...
It's not a joke.
I love you.
Even though you like Tsumugu, I...
I don't understand...
Manaka...
I don't understand any of that!
Manaka!
That was horrible, Kaname!
That's going too far!
I'm doing the best that I can, too...
Manaka...
Don't run after her!
I...
Hikari, I...
Chisaki!
Chisaki.
Hikari, I...
But... you like Manaka,
so I couldn't say it.
I wasn't scared I'd be rejected.
I was scared that if
I said how I felt,
all our relationships
would have changed.
But that wasn't true, either.
I figured it out.
I'm in love with the Hikari
that loves Manaka so much.
So, I'm sorry.
It was enough for me just to say it.
I'm satisfied.
Go run after Manaka.
Hikari?
First you say don't run after her,
now you tell me to run after her.
Talk about demanding.
I'm just like you.
Huh?
I was scared of
destroying our relationships.
It's enough that I was
able just to say how I felt.
I wonder if they will be destroyed.
No, they won't.
Nothing will change.
You're so kind, Hikari.
Huh?
No...
I want to be kind.
I want to have a beautiful heart.
As beautiful as the view of
Shioshishio we can see from here.
Mom?
Oh my...
I was just thinking that I still need
to put everything else away...
Sorry, I'll...
It's fine, Mom.
Your Ena's gotten so thick.
The hibernation is coming up soon.
Manaka?
I-I... forgot something at school.
Huh?
Manaka?
Gramps, it's late.
But...
See?
It's that weird cough.
Once the sea goes into hibernation,
we may not be able to get any more fish.
Before that...
I'll go.
Just relax and rest.
I'm scared...
I'm scared. I don't know.
Where should I go?
Where should I go...
Over here! Over here!
H-Hii-kun!
What's the matter?
I always admired it.
Why?
Beyond the sea, beyond the sky...
You were crying.
I was surrounded by noise.
The sun that was so far, far away.
Episode Thirteen:
Fingertips Beyond Reach
Hii-kun, wave that flag!