You're going to ruin her if you continue to
do nothing more than let her live with you.
Elias...
That's right.
His name was given to him by my master.
Welcome, Elias, to this dizzying,
disgusting, beautiful world.
All right, take care of Elias for me,
Lindel.
This is all so sudden.
Well, from now on, you're Elias.
For a few years, the two of us traveled
the forest, chasing reindeer.
We traveled, enjoying the sight of
the lakes and fields as we went.
Hey, what are you doing?
You shouldn't take things you
aren't even going to eat.
I shouldn't?
Elias seemed to be missing something.
He learned quickly, but he seemed as though
he was looking at everything from the outside.
One day, when we were running
low on food, we visited a home.
Hello, I'm a shaman.
Is there anyone sick or injured here?
Would you spare me some food
in exchange for healing?
My grandson happens to be bedridden.
I can make use of my hands for a fever.
It must be awful for you.
You'll be better soon.
Sleep well.
You're his little sister?
Don't worry.
Your brother will be fine.
That man...
There's something in his shadow.
I'm scared!
What is it?!
It's a monster!
A m-monster!
Hurry!
It's evil!
It's a demon!
He was going to take the kid!
There was a child with the sight in the house.
Shit.
Sorry, Lindel.
It's not your fault.
You demon!
Demon!
I'll kill you!
Evil!
Demon!
I'll kill you!
Send for help!
Stop, Elias!
Veil of the forest, lift yourself for us!
He's gone.
Where are we?
This is where the forest gods live.
Lindel.
This is what happens when
I force myself to use magic.
We need to get out of here.
Spruce.
Take us outside, to Lindel's reindeer.
I taught him that.
You're surprisingly good with your hands.
I've seen you do this lots of times.
Thanks.
Is something wrong?
Lindel,
I'm pretty sure I've eaten humans before.
What do you think, Chise?
What if he's a man-eating monster?
I could see things from the other
side ever since I was little.
A lot of them would talk about
how tasty or gross humans are.
I was really scared.
But Elias has never scared me, not once.
So, if he really used to...
Tell him the rest yourself.
But you were the one who asked.
My bad.
You're well-spoken.
You should talk to him lots, too.
What did you say in response, Lindel?
Me?
I said...
I bet I'm tasty. Don't eat me.
I'm... not going to eat you.
Okay, good.
But sometimes I feel the urge to...
Even though I'm sure I don't really want to.
Aren't humans afraid of things like me?
Hey, there are lots of
things that eat humans.
I have no reason to be fearful
of you in particular.
Eat all kinds of things, and soon enough,
you'll forget all about your
ambivalent taste for humans.
I kind of killed the
conversation on purpose.
I was actually scared, after all.
You were, huh?
You'd be shocked, too, at least for a moment,
if you found out that the cat curled up on
your lap actually ate humans, wouldn't you?
Comparing him to a cat?
Either way, my fears vanished as
soon as I took a sip of the soup.
Also, that soup tasted unbelievably bad.
Thank goodness for Silky.
Still, humans are the most easily-scared
and cruel creatures of all.
I told him he shouldn't tell
people about it too much.
I don't know if he's following my advice,
or if something else happened...
But he absolutely refuses to
tell people about himself.
He's still stuck as a child.
Sorry for the long talk.
You should get some sleep.
Can't sleep, Chise?
Nah, thanks, Ruth.
Did I look tasty?
I guess I've heard something
he didn't want to say.
It's morning.
Oh, right, I'm in the land of dragons.
Good morning.
Morning.
Chise!
Human!
Morning!
Morning.
Morning—
Chise!
That girl sure does fall into water a lot.
Chise, are you all right?
There was this amazing thing.
Why are you cutting my hair?
Even since long ago, hair
has always carried magic.
We'll use this as the core of the wand.
You don't see many Asians
with red hair like yours.
It's a perfect color for magic.
Red is the color of the earth,
the color of the flames and blood
flowing through the stars.
Choose a handpiece from one of these.
The red elderberry knocks on the
door to the black goddess.
The willow lingers between
the living and the dead.
The hazel wards off evil.
The yew is a symbol of eternity.
It can draw or banish magic.
The checker tree has a powerful life
force and brings order to the wicked.
I saw him when I first came here.
I had him dry the wood out.
Well, let's get to carving.
Oh, sorry, there's nothing
for me to teach you.
Just carve it as you like, so that
it's comfortable for you to use.
It's customary for one to carve their own
wands, and for their senior to finish it.
It would be good to talk to
yourself as you're carving.
To myself?
I'll go take a look around.
Take your time.
Talk to myself?
You have to talk to yourself, don't you?
Ruth...
I guess I've never really thought
about myself until now.
It's dark now.
Take a break.
That's some amazing focus.
You're almost done.
Right.
Just a little more work.
Not bad at all, for a beginner.
Let's finish it tomorrow.
The moon's bright tonight.
I can show you something nice.
The moss here grows flowers.
Flowers?
The elves created this land.
They adore it.
Dance with the elves, and
the flowers will bloom.
Do you know my other name?
Echos, the song of a hundred flowers?
Names are very important
for mages and sorcerers.
Usually, they're called by the name that
describes their features and their true nature.
My spells are songs.
Let's have them bloom
for us, just for tonight.
Like snowmelt, it was both low and high.
It resonated through the wind.
Let's dance.
Elves?
I've never danced before.
Just twirl around with them.
Listen carefully to the sound, to the song,
to the sound of the wind,
to the sound of the water.
Humanity still remembers the sounds
that filled our bodies from long
ago, before even language itself.
Magic is the same way.
Listen to what is around you,
and offer out your hand.
You still remember that.
I'm spent.
I wonder what he would say,
if he saw this scene.
Elias.
Chise.
Why did you make a water mirror?
A water mirror?
A water mirror lets you see
a person through the water.
Huh?
Is he singing right now?
Yes.
No wonder.
His magic connected there to here.
I see.
Elias...
Yeah?
You look troubled.
Did something happen?
I suppose.
A little.
Is everything okay?
Home is a bit cold without you.
Even though it's summer,
and I have the stove on.
The flowers are beautiful here.
I wish I could show you.
Take them in, and tell me about
them when you get back.
Here's a small taste.
Elias,
I heard all kinds of things about you.
That old bastard...
So I'll tell you what I haven't
been able to tell you, too.
I'll head home as soon as my wand's done.
Okay.
Please.
Two kids.
I don't even have kids, but
I feel like I'm raising both of them.
A girl who hadn't a place to return is
shown the way by Lindenbaum's staff.
What does she choose at
the end of her wandering?
Please... Connect me to that person.