Target silent. Mission complete.
Damage report.
Rosalie, minor damage to right thruster.
Still flight-capable.
Ersha, right shoulder damaged.
Ange, lost.
Good work.
All units, return.
Um—
The Vill—
Ange's unit has not necessarily been destroyed.
We should search for
and retrieve it immediately.
You're kidding.
We're exhausted from the fight.
We have no fuel.
And you're telling us to find the Burn
Princess and that cruddy machine, Captain?
Hilda's right.
We'll send out a recovery team later.
All units return.
We're going back.
Ange, Lost
Sorry.
I tied you up just in case.
Why are you—
Sorry, I—
No!
What is this place?
Why am I—
Want some help?
Piss off, cockroach!
Why won't it move?
Damn,
damn, damn!
How could you?
I saved your life—
Come any closer, and I'll shoot.
Calm down! I don't intend to hurt you.
Besides, you're shooting at me.
You bound me, stripped me, and groped me.
L-Like I said, I—
You would have done more
filthy and perverted things
to me, too, wouldn't you?
More filthy and perverted things?
You think I'd feel up an
unconscious girl's shapely breasts,
or taste every inch of her vulnerable body,
or use her to admire the
mysterious female figure?
Do I look like I would do that sort of thing?
You would do that sort of thing?
You dirty pervert!
You misunderstand!
I really meant to help—
Pervert! Animal in heat!
Hey, hello? That was an accident.
I hear the Villkiss is down.
And we just found someone
who could handle it.
The machine was in good shape. Why?
We can think about it later.
Right now we need to focus on recovering it.
I know.
I'll form a recovery group right away.
And Ange.
Retrieve her, too.
Dead...
...if need be.
Mei-chan.
You're going on recovery, right?
We'll help, too.
But you both just got back.
She'll die if we don't hurry.
Ange is still alive.
I know it.
We have to find her quick.
I bet she's hungry.
Come on, let's go.
Why don't they even pack emergency rations?
A Norma's casket, huh?
No.
Ow!
Someone...
No...
No one will come.
Hey, are you all right?
Help me.
Dad!
Mom!
The Villkiss...
You shouldn't force yourself.
I sucked out the venom,
but you're still numb.
Just so you know,
I've never done anything perverted
to a girl that can't move.
You might not have made it
if I hadn't gotten to you in time.
You should learn from this,
and never go into the rain forest half-naked.
I don't need your help.
Here.
What?
Eat.
You haven't eaten at all, have you?
I don't want it.
I don't even know what it is.
There's nothing weird in it.
Here.
It tastes bad.
I'm glad you like it.
It's sea snake soup.
Do you trust me a little, now?
Hopefully you won't punch me,
shoot me, or tie me up anymore.
I'll think about it.
What's wrong? Does it hurt?
Did you say you sucked out the venom?
Yeah.
With your mouth?
From here?
Well—
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
I never said I wouldn't bite!
Thirty minutes until refueling is done.
Too slow. Do it in fifteen.
You seem eager.
Hilda-chan.
I don't get it.
Why are you trying to help her?
Are you being meddlesome again?
I know you girls can't forgive Ange-chan...
And that you would like to shoot her down.
But someone has to accept her,
or she'll always be alone.
That would be lonely, wouldn't it?
We're all Normas, after all.
Besides, Ange-chan is a lot
like how you used to be.
That's why I can't just leave her.
Like me?
That wretch?
I'll kill you, too.
Refueling, refueling.
Huh, Hilda?
Can you move now?
What are you doing?
Repairs, I guess.
You can fix it?
Bits and pieces of Para-mail
wash up here sometimes.
I got the hang of it after studying them.
Can you bring me that hex wrench?
Why don't you just use Mana to move it?
Why don't you?
Why do you know about Para-mail?
What are you?
I'm Tusk.
I'm just Tusk.
No, I mean—
I knew it, the output circuits are shot.
But the radio will work once we fix it.
Then you can contact your people.
It's no use fixing it.
They won't come, even if I contacted them.
Even if I went back, no one
would be waiting for me.
Oh.
If you're okay with it,
why don't you stay here for a while?
I won't do anything weird.
I suppose.
I didn't think there were so many stars.
You never noticed?
I haven't looked up at
the sky in a long time.
It's pretty.
You're even prettier.
U-Um—
Be quiet.
Isn't that a DRAGON?
They're taking it? Where? Why?
That's—
Let's run.
That's not going to hurt it.
So you'd rather we just get eaten here?
The Para-mail.
It would work.
But it's not fixed yet.
Then fix it now.
All right.
Hurry.
Over here, you shambling corpse.
Here.
Hurry.
You!
It's dead.
It must have been trying to help its friend.
It must have wanted to go back
to its own world together.
We won't be able to stay in this forest.
We have to hurry.
What about you?
Would you come with me?
You're a bit violent, but you're
pretty and cute and beautiful.
And I've seen you naked.
And I did all those things.
I'll take responsibility.
Ange-san, please respond.
Are you dead?
Please tell me if you're dead.
What?
Ange here.
I'm alive.
No way.
Ange.
Is it really you?
Requesting rescue.
R-Roger.
I'm going back.
I think it's...
...the only place I have.
Besides, I have to get them
back for what they did.
I see.
Thanks.
I would have been dead without you.
You're welcome.
Sorry I can't come with you.
Listen, nothing happened between us.
You didn't see anything.
You didn't do anything.
You didn't suck venom out of me.
Forget all of it.
Got it?
Yes.
Ange.
My name's Ange, Tusk.
Nice name.
See you, Ange.
What a strange person.
And now for a quiz.
Who's still alive after falling?
The answer is Ange!
Here you go, Ange-chan.
Thanks.
Oh, my.
Hey, Vivian, do you still
have those weird mascots?
Ange, you said my name.
There's nothing in my cockpit.
It smells like curry, is that okay?
No.
Next episode
And we fell for it.
A gorgeous beach, a mysterious jungle,
and a beautiful encounter...
But nope, it's more gory battles.
Forget vacations and romance,
it's all about survival.
I'm not falling for it again.
This preview's probably all lies, too.
Momoka's Here!
Momoka's not actually coming.