One touch!
He sure is persistent...
That brat with the glasses.
Would you let me set the timing
for the three-person block?
They finally got a clean one in.
Total defense.
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Haikyu!!
Karasuno              Shiratorizawa
All right!
Nishinoya, nice receive!
Episode 04: The Halo Around the Moon
It was only possible because
you all narrowed the gap.
Great job on the block timing!
Oh, right.
I see!
So that block really wasn't
done to stop Ushiwaka,
but to guide where the ball was going to go.
Nice combo play!
That was sort of like mobbing.
Mobbing?
Um... Mobbing is where smaller
birds will attack larger,
predatory birds in groups
to try to chase them away.
You know some pretty cool words, Yacchan.
Using a connecting block as a starting point,
they were able to connect everything
naturally in that volley.
They were finally able to give it shape.
Yeah.
Total defense! So cool!
Even if we can't stop him by blocking,
we'll be able to fight Ushiwaka with this.
They were finally able to lift up
one of Ushiwaka's spikes.
Things are getting interesting.
Damn it. They wasted two sets.
Is that old guy a tsundere?
That was uncalled for.
Asahi, nice serve!
Out!
All right!
Seriously?
All right, they broke through!
Take this set!
They definitely got us with
that serve, but we're going to
hurry up and turn things back around!
Right!
Be Courageous Warriors
Shiratorizawa Academy Volleyball Club
Asahi, one more! Nice serve!
Tsutomu!
Right!
Nice receive!
Ohira-san.
Got it!
It wasn't Ushiwaka this time?
I'm sure they'd worry about his
stamina if it was every time.
Ready, and...
Tch.
Feint!
Sorry! It's going—
Victory!
Yeah!
Shiratorizawa           Karasuno
Not yet. We still need two points.
Just how righteous are you?
This puts Ushiwaka on the back line...
But...
that means he gets to serve.
It's mine!
Get the last one over!
Ryu!
Got it!
Chance ball!
Gimme!
Where is he—
A dump?!
Damn it!
Be Courageous Warriors
Nice kill, Shirabu!
Shirabu! Shirabu!
Depending on Ushijima-san
isn't my only job.
All right!
Not bad...
Nice job, Shirabu!
Karasuno             Shiratorizawa
Sorry. It would have been
better if I hadn't touched it.
Nah, I wouldn't have been
able to get that either way.
This isn't where we relax!
Right!
They got the set point first!
Is something wrong?
I was just thinking that Kei
was acting a little weird.
I might just be imagining it.
His eyes seem much more lively than usual.
Does Kei actually have friends
at school besides Tadashi?
Out?
No...
Cover!
Left!
Tanaka-san!
Three blockers!
A block out!
Nice!
Nice, Ryu!
And now, it's a deuce.
Karasuno                 Shiratorizawa
All right!
We're counting on you, Hinata!
Make sure you get them back
for all the times you got hit!
Hey.
Now Suga-chan can't come in
anymore this time, right?
Yeah.
There's a rule where the same player can't
be switched twice within the same set.
But we got through Ushiwaka's serve.
Now we amp up our attack power
with Hinata on the front line.
Karasuno definitely has the upper hand.
Tsukishima, nice serve!
One touch!
Hey.
If my serve is cleanly received,
there's a good chance of them doing a quick.
Try jumping as high as
you can against their #5.
Chance ball!
Bring it!
Give it to me!
All right!
A return dump...
Man, people who hate to lose can be scary.
It's not good for my heart.
Nice, Kageyama!
Yeah, great job, King.
Tsukishima!
Karasuno                 Shiratorizawa
All right! They got it back!
Now it's set point!
Karasuno, fight!
I'm sure this is extremely obvious,
but it truly is hard to score
more than one point in a row.
Well, this game was designed
so that each side has equal
chances to attack.
Not to mention, when we get
into the last part of the set,
each side gets that much more eager to win.
But...
Each side has to start scraping away
at their opponent's sharpened defense.
Even with pure height and power,
their persistence,
their ability to connect,
and, to some extent, the calmness and
stamina to maintain teamwork...
In order to win, they need the
tremendous amount of energy
required to score two points in a row.
They're still serving strong
like it's natural for them.
That's to be expected from them.
Sorry, it's long!
Kageyama, push it over!
Got it!
Nice, Tsutomu!
Chance ball!
He's...
Is he going to feint?
He's going over there?
There's...
1.5 blockers!
All right!
He sure is a first-class decoy, damn it...
Tanaka, nice kill!
Did he set to their #5 because he knew
our eyes would be on their #10?
Nice toss, Kageyama!
Actually, it was a little
early... I'm sorry.
You sure are hard on yourself.
It really does piss people off when Hinata is
scuttling around in front of you.
Get as wild as you can,
you weirdo duo.
You fools!
Karasuno              Shiratorizawa
Shiratorizawa's taking their first time out!
Haikyu!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Shiratorizawa!
Karasuno              Shiratorizawa
It's true that they're different
from anyone we've faced so far.
Shiratorizawa!
But there's no reason for us to panic.
We just have to score
points like we usually do.
Shiratorizawa!
Anyway, make sure to break their streak!
Right!
Shiratorizawa!
Man... When I saw the first set,
I thought it'd be an easy win
for Shiratorizawa, but...
I guess they're what you call a dark horse?
But Karasuno's a former
powerhouse school, too.
Well, yeah. They've got
Nishinoya from Chidoriyama,
Kageyama from Kita-Ichi,
and Azumane from Seikodai.
They've got quite the lineup.
Even if it gets rough,
or you start panicking,
don't let your guard down!
All right!
They can't seem to get
those last two points...
I'm pretty sure both sides are thinking that.
However, if Karasuno loses this set,
they're gonna be done.
We're counting on you...
We're counting on you, Eita-kun.
Right!
Semi-san!
Semi! Get a nice serve in!
So Shiratorizawa is using their pinch server.
Nice serve, Eita!
Sorry!
Daichi-san!
Above you, Shirabu!
Right!
Semi-san!
Come on, Tsutomu!
Right!
All right!
Break!
Yeah!
Nice kill, Goshiki!
Karasuno             Shiratorizawa
Come to think of it, I guess he was a setter.
Concentrate!
Right!
Nice serve!
Daichi!
Damn it! It's short!
All right. It's off.
Huh?!
All right!
A quick there?! You guys
are seriously messed up!
Hinata, nice kill!
Looks like logic doesn't
work on this side either.
Who does Karasuno's setter think he is?
Karasuno              Shiratorizawa
Tanaka, nice serve!
Got it!
Come on, break... Break through!
Left!
All right!
Wakatoshi!
Three blockers!
Damn! It looks like that libero's
getting the hang of it.
But Ushiwaka's still only using
about 70% of his strength.
Would you be able to get those?
Not a chance.
Damn it!
All right!
Sorry! It was close to the net!
Karasuno              Shiratorizawa
We're not done yet... We've only just begun!
Shirabu-san, nice serve!
Got it!
Nice receive!
Right!
All right!
Shit!
Nice, Daichi!
Yes!
There's no way that I can beat Ushiwaka.
Our bodies are different.
Our experience is different.
The time we've given volleyball is different.
There's no way that I can beat him.
But...
I was hoping they could break through
while they still had Hinata as a decoy.
Hinata looks so anxious
on the back line.
He sucks at both serving and digs...
Hinata, nice serve!
Right!
If their #5's guess blocking
is either 120 points or 0 points,
I'd say read blocking stays at
about an average of 75 points.
Well, our blocks definitely need more work,
but maybe it looks cooler to bystanders
Nice serve!
when people go for the 120 points.
We can't let the opponent setter
feel the pleasure or accomplishment
of overcoming our blocks.
Got it!
Persistently, begrudgingly,
Nice receive!
yet nimbly, and absolutely...
They won't get through easily.
Continue pressuring them
and piling on stress.
One touch!
Connect!
Hit! Hit!
Nice, Tachi!
Got it!
You suck at serving, you suck at receiving,
and your setting and
blocking are below average.
Then what are you doing on the court?
You score points!
All right!
Karasuno                Shiratorizawa
Break!
A back attack with minus tempo.
Great job, Hinata!
He's gotten even faster after
that time Oikawa stopped him.
Taichi! Don't just stand there!
Nah, that one was impossible.
Nice one touch!
Hinata, one more! Nice serve!
If it weren't for Hinata's cover,
it would have just been blown away.
But if we didn't have that one touch,
we might have been done right then.
Shirabu.
Gather them to me.
Crap!
Out? But if I judge wrong
here, I'm going to be killed!
It went in!
It's off.
I'm sorry!
Wakatoshi!
We've got three.
Ready, and...
Nice kill, Ushijima!
Ushijima!
Karasuno              Shiratorizawa
That was intense...
It was like he changed the flow of
the game with a single strike.
Don't fall behind! We're
going to keep going forward!
Right!
That was intense.
All right!
Synchronized attack!
We're definitely not losing
when it comes to scoring points.
Yeah!
Karasuno              Shiratorizawa
Daichi-san, nice serve!
Ushijima-san!
Ready, and...
So persistent!
Return it! Return it!
Nice, Daichi-san!
Chance ball!
Open the way...
for our spiker!
I was waiting
for this fraying caused
by slight annoyance and panic.
There's no way that I can beat Ushiwaka.
But...
I'm planning on stopping at
least a few of his spikes.
He stopped Ushiwaka?!
Who is that guy?
No idea!
Amazing!
Karasuno              Shiratorizawa
They took back the second set!
It was just one block.
It was just one point out of 25.
This is just a club.
But once that moment arrives for you,
that's the moment you'll
be hooked on volleyball.
All right!
Tsukishima!
Ow!
Ushiwaka's spike just now...
Tsukshima, are you seriously Tsukishima?
Did you seriously just seriously?
There wasn't a moment to spare
in his run or his jump.
But the toss was probably a bit
close to the net and low...
Tsukishima didn't let that escape him.
Or...
Was he waiting for that?
Sorry for saying something
like we could still fight,
even if we can't stop him with our blocks.
Huh?
You were making a weird
face back then, Yamaguchi.
Huh?!
No, I was also thinking that Tsukki
was definitely doing his part.
Despite how he looks,
Tsukki hates losing,
so I figured he would probably do something.
Tsukishima, nice block!
Great job stopping that!
I'm sure there were other blockers
before that were at my level,
but I think that Nishinoya-san's receives
and that weirdo duo's attack
that completely ignores their blocks
added pressure to their setter.
You were thinking about all that?
Scary... Tsukishima, you're scary.
I think that Kei might have been
waiting this whole time for the timing
of Shiratorizawa's tosses to skew.
I can't believe he thought that far ahead.
Tsukishima-kun is smart,
so I believe that he's always
thinking about volleyball,
as well as other things...
I'm sure he's pretty obstinate.
Sorry about that.
Oh, no...
It's just that at that moment,
I think the only thing on Tsukishima-kun's
mind was stopping that block.
Just purely...
Like he was solving a
difficult test question.
Yeah.
Tsukishima!
That one point was worth 100 points!
If you're a
middle blocker,
you try it, too
Thanks.
What?!
Calm down, Hinata!
I'm sure he meant it as,
"If you're a middle blocker, you try it, too,"
but calm down!
Please stop making such a fuss.
That was just a point.
The game's just getting starting.
Yeah!
Tsukki finally stopped Ushiwaka!
Kei usually doesn't show
his emotions and is blunt,
but he actually works really hard,
is kind, and is a really good boy.
Who are you, his mother?!
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"Individual VS Numbers."
Episode 05: Individual VS Numbers