Takeshi, you've received an invitation
from the Schuberstein Competition.
It's in Germany...
You're finally going overseas!
The Maihou Competition's around the
same time, but let's cancel that one.
Mr. Takayanagi.
I won't be going to Germany.
What?
I'm going to enter the
Maihou Music Competition.
But why? They
invited you, you know!
It's a golden opportunity
that almost never comes up!
And you also need to get overseas
exposure before the Chopin competition!
You already won Maihou last year,
so there's no reason to make it a priority...
But there is a reason.
Kousei Arima might be competing.
You keep saying that, and
how long have we waited?
But he hasn't shown his face in
public for two whole years now.
There are even rumors that
he can't hear anymore.
He might be competing this time.
Takeshi!
I know it's ridiculous.
But my goal isn't to go overseas,
or to play in the Chopin competition.
My goal is Kousei Arima.
The competition that he'll be playing in.
It's gonna be all right. You
can do this. You can play it!
I like your expression.
Don't get overeager, Takeshi.
All right, that's
a great start.
Takeshi!
Is she listening to another
person's performance?
What an intrepid soul!
Arima?
Are you watching?
Are you listening?
Arima?
Could this be the same piano?
He sounds totally different
than everyone before him...
Confronting the music with sincerity...
A strong will enabling him
to stand up to his fears.
An unswerving fortitude at his core.
This is Aiza's Chopin.
I'm grateful to Arima-kun.
He's the one who made him grow up.
Just by existing...
...you pushed the pianist,
Takeshi Aiza to the top.
The reason I was able to hang in there
during the two years you were gone...
...was because I always believed
that you'd be back one day.
Have I caught up to you yet?
Or am I even further behind?
Will you let me chase you
down like a mirage again?
Will you be the one
I aspire to be?
Hey, answer me. Show
me what you've got!
Come on, now it's your turn.
Kousei Arima!
Huh! Well, I gotta
admit he's pretty cool.
Just as expected!
Awesome, awesome!
Oh! He looked this way!
He's so cool!
What's up with that?
It's the TAKESHI Brigade!
A rival is a special thing.
All the more so for adolescent boys.
A rival can make you grow far
faster than being taught by someone.
It's all because of you.
It was you who made Takeshi
reach those heights, Kousei Arima.
It was all for the sake
of catching up to you...
That's what the piano is saying.
Do you feel that way, too?
Don't make me laugh.
It's over!
That was great.
Good job!
Now they start trembling!
Good job.
Well? Did you see that, Arima?
You were amazing.
Uh...
Hey, that was nothing.
Creepy...
There will now be a
15-minute intermission.
We will resume judging at :45.
He was really cool, wasn't he?
That was really tight!
Aiza-kun sure has
great presence!
You could even
say he's imposing.
He didn't make any
real mistakes, either.
You can tell how grueling
his practice sessions must be.
He doesn't look it, but he's a
diligent player, don't you think?
Even though his mentor,
Takayanagi-kun is so shallow!
Name of mentor: Akira Takayanagi
First place in all of his recent competitions.
He's certainly flying high at the moment.
He's a phenom ready to
take the world by storm.
In comparison,
she's fallen quite far back in the pack.
Man, she's cute!
Let's see.
Oh crap!
Oh, it's Igawa-san.
She's popular, too.
I knew they seemed familiar.
When I used to go cheer Kousei on,
both that Aiza-kun,
and Igawa-san...
I used to see those
three together all the time.
I remember because their
names were always at the top.
But of course, it was Kousei
who always ended up in first place!
Yeah, and why are
you acting so smug again?
So listen, is this Emi-chan
any good at the piano?
She's got to be good.
Because she's cute!
I know how to size up people.
I bet Emi-chan's gonna
run away with this competition.
I mean, 'cause she's so cute.
Already using her first name?
Jerk...
Hmm, but I think Igawa-san's
been struggling a little lately.
An honorable mention at
the Kumagai Competition,
third place at the
Tanizaki Music Festival,
and the other day, she didn't even
make it past the preliminaries.
Sounds like she's been
running hot and cold.
To think that those three always
used to be a lock for the Top 3...
Pardon me.
Oh,
Mr. Takayanagi.
Hello, Ms. Ochiai.
Tell me...
How's it going with
your student, Igawa-san?
What a snide man.
Aiza-kun's performance was masterful.
I'm sure it's all
due to your instruction.
Well... thank you very much.
In my case, the student
has surpassed the master!
But I do believe it's time for
him to start thinking globally.
Since there probably isn't anything
left for him to accomplish domestically.
No one can challenge
him anymore in Japan.
You saw that yourself, didn't you?
In everyone's eyes, Takeshi is No. 1!
Today, he'll destroy Arima,
and head overseas!
Feel free.
So how's she doing? Igawa-san?
That girl... Emi can be
so temperamental, you see.
The most trivial thing can have
a drastic effect on her performance.
Like her new shoes pinching her toes,
or her neighbor humming in a bizarre way...
She can even be swayed
by the weather that day.
For the last two years,
it's been so hectic for everyone,
trying to keep her motivated...
Because the goal she should
have vanquished had disappeared.
But... it's different today.
The last two years...
The goal she should have vanquished...
The goal she should have vanquished!
Are you implying that she
doesn't see Takeshi as her goal?
Well, Aiza-kun doesn't see
Emi as a rival either.
"The results speak for themselves..."
It's written all over your face.
Are you trying to pick a
fight with me, Ms. Ochiai?
You're the one who threw
down the gauntlet, Mr. Takayanagi.
We women are combative
creatures. Do you understand?
Little boy?
We will now resume judging.
Aiza-kun's reign will end today.
Emi will bring an end to it.
Ugh, goosebumps.
It's turning red!
It's been a while
since I felt this way.
That's right...
It's been two years.
When I was five,
I went to a piano recital
to cheer on a friend.
Just when I was about to
fall asleep from boredom,
He appeared onstage.
He was such a
bundle of nerves,
my heart started pounding.
That Arima-kun was? Hmm...
I found out later that...
that was the first time he'd ever
performed in front of other people.
That moment of silence before
his fingers touched the keys...
The time he took to bid his
hesitation and confusion farewell...
The moment his fingers touched the keys,
my future was decided.
I did it! Oops!
What, you started bawling?
Embarrassing, I know.
I'm sure it was awkward for young Arima!
He was crestfallen, and
beat it out of there.
My heart wouldn't stop pounding,
and tears were filling my eyes.
All of my emotions came
gushing out at once.
I was just so moved.
As if I was embodying all
the pleasure music brings.
But he, on the other hand...
Kousei Arima changed.
Like a machine.
His mother's puppet.
A slave to the sheet music.
A pianist made only for competitions.
So Kousei Arima's mother,
Saki Arima, was dreaming.
I can understand that.
She entered her son in
that competition to test him,
and her dreams for him began
with his magnificent performance.
The dreams that she could
never realize for herself.
And so she drilled him...
to give performances that would leave
results, that could win competitions.
Exactly what the score
calls for. Like a machine.
I get it.
As an instructor, it's painful
not to be able to deny that.
But you're different, aren't you?
Because you're a strong child.
You know, she can be unfriendly, and
she says stuff that sounds pretty mean,
but she really has a thing
for you, you know, Arima.
For me?
Yeah, I swear, it's like
she's in love with you.
I mean, she was always telling me...
"Takeshi, you don't know
the real Arima, do you?"
So beautiful...
Pretty!
She just takes my breath away.
Her, and the black piano...
I mean, really... what a sight!
What a lovely sound. But...
If that's all she's got...
It's true that Emi can be erratic.
Like a stormy sea,
the waves of her emotions
are surging unsteadily.
That being the case - today...
It wouldn't be a surprise to see
those waves reach their crest.
Hey, hey...
I'm in sync with the piano.
My fingers feel light.
Today, I'm in the zone. It's probably...
...because the scone I had
for breakfast was so good.
Because my new dress looks good on me.
Because I'm having a good hair day.
That's got to be it.
No, of course that's not it!
I'm not a child.
So why am I making
excuses to myself?
He's here. After two
years, he's so near...
He's gotten taller. He looks
a little more mature.
But I knew him at a glance.
Ever since that moment, my
excitement has been surging.
He's right there, and he's watching me.
Do you feel that way, too?
Don't make me laugh. Because I...
I've been playing the piano all this
time in order to reject Kousei Arima.
I know that she has the technique.
But not at this level...
Go! Go! Emi!
Let it all out with a bang!
Let your feelings reach them!
A fourteen-year-old girl
has this audience enthralled.
Is she really a
junior high student?
I'm going to reject you.
Even if I lose,
even if I get trounced, I'm going
to reject you every time.
Playing for competitions...
That's not the Kousei Arima
that I want to hear.
I'm going to reject
you with my playing.
What I want to hear is...
Red, yellow, yellow...
Are these her emotions?
Red and yellow...
Anger and...
Do you feel that way, too?
Yes, I do.
I'm only here because of you.
Just under four minutes...
A performance lasting
just under four minutes...
That's what made me a pianist.
Come back, come back,
the Kousei Arima that I looked up to!
Let it ring! Let it ring!
Let it ring!
My piano!
Let it ring! Let it ring!
Let it ring!
I see...
Red and yellow. Her anger,
and... Her loneliness.
Chopin's Étude,
Op. 25, No. 11.
"Le vent d'hiver" - Winter Wind.
Super-cute!
Dial it down, Watari!
Right... So you play by pouring your
soul into the notes, too, huh?
Let it ring.
Let it Ring
Episode 9
Resonance
Watch Again Next Week!