Are you all right?
What happened?
It looks like the
Aldnoah drive shut down.
That shouldn't be possible!
This ship's Aldnoah was
activated by Her Highness!
So long as she lives, it can't be shut down
by another without her consent!
So long as she lives...
Where is Seylum?!
Where is she?
Damage?
Damage to hull, negligible. Departmental
damage checks underway.
We are currently operating
on auxiliary power.
It's a good thing we were
flying at low altitude.
Our gravity field was
churning up the snow,
and that seems to have acted
as a shock absorber.
Launch our Kats
and put them on watch.
Repair any damaged areas ASAP.
Engine room, inspect the Aldnoah drive and
determine cause of shutdown.
Where is Capt. Magbaredge?
Bridge.
Send medics immediately!
Captain? Where are you?
Breathing and pulse, both stopped.
Princess...
Bring towels!
I'm going to use a defibrillator.
We have to dry her off!
Hurry!
Right!
I'll help.
Setting counter shock
to 200 joules.
Clear.
I'll do it!
No, you're too light.
You think fast on your feet.
We learn this in school.
Students never take it seriously. All they
do is giggle about the mouth-to-mouth.
It could save a life.
Should I take over?
I can handle it.
Milady!
Good. Are you all right?
Inaho...
Where am I?
It looks like you passed out while
taking a shower. What happened?
I...
I was attacked... by her!
Don't move.
You...
Rayet? Why?
Where's the patient?!
Stay back!
Get back!
Get out of the room!
Now!
Dr. Yagarai.
Yeah...
Who are you?
A Versian- No, a Martian.
Why...?
The one who tried to assassinate you
at the Shinawara parade
was my father.
He was a Martian spy living on Earth.
He was promised a title and
a reward if he killed you.
But when he completed his mission,
he was put down like a dog.
To silence him!
Martians can't be trusted!
Martians are all the enemy!
I can't go back to being a Martian.
But I'm not a Terran, either.
But you... you revealed
yourself as a Martian!
In spite of that, you were accepted! In spite
of that, you made a place for yourself!
In spite of what you are!
He thought they were
on the same side, but they...
It's all your fault...
My father is dead
because you came here.
This war started
We were betrayed
because you came here.
I'm all alone
Because you came...
Because you came!
In spite of all that,
how can they not hate you?!
I'm sorry.
I've brought you nothing
but misery, haven't I?
I was a fool.
Milady!
I thought I was working
towards peace.
I thought I was doing
the right thing.
But I was merely acting
like a spoiled child.
Relations with Earth are worse
than ever because of me.
Many people have
lost their lives.
No matter how much I tell myself that
I did nothing wrong, the reality of it
is that I have brought misery
to countless people's lives.
To yours.
To your father's.
I will not ask you to forgive me.
Nevertheless... I am sorry.
Why?
Why are you crying?
My father tried to kill you!
I tried to kill you, too!
Why won't you hate me?!
Why are you forgiving me?!
Why are you
being kind to me?
Why?! Why?! Why?!
Why?!
How stupid are you?
Give it a rest, already...
What am I even doing?
No!
What are you doing?!
Automatics won't fire
with the slide open.
I thought this was the best way to stop
you without it discharging accidentally.
No, I meant-
To be honest, I couldn't care less
if you're a Terran or a Martian.
You hate our enemies, and those
enemies are trying to kill you.
But most importantly,
you've fought at our side.
What other reasons
do I need?
You trust me?
At the very least, I don't
think we're enemies.
As to whether we'll be allies...
that's up to you.
You might come to regret this.
I'm taking you into custody.
Warrant Officer Kaizuka.
Yes, ma'am.
Do whatever you want.
What's that?
A Martian trinket?
No, I'm told that it's a
Terran good luck charm.
Dr. Yagarai, what's the
princess' condition?
She seems fine. But to be safe,
she should rest for a while.
I see. But I'm afraid that
that's out of the question.
I am fine. I shall
see to the drive...
Milady...
That reminds me, Captain.
This is technically
privileged information, but here.
What is it?
A patient file. Lt. Marito's.
Patient file?
It's also a prescription.
For you.
For me?
Thanks.
Compared to where I've been sleeping
until now, this is paradise.
Aldnoah drive online.
We have power!
We're good to go.
Deucalion, lift off.
That girl's father tried to kill
the princess, a fellow Martian.
Martians killed her father,
and then that Rayet girl turned a gun on the
princess even though she's a Martian, too.
And I... killed my own
best friend.
What was it like to be shot
by a friend, Humeray?
Slaine.
This is our data on Tanegashima, the
island where you were retrieved.
An enormous dock
and shipbuilding facilities...
You saw a ship?
Yes.
And that ship was Aldnoah-equipped?
Most likely.
And was it Princess Asseylum
who activated that Aldnoah?
You hold your tongue out
of concern for her?
Are you familiar with this?
What is it?
The Deucalion.
A Kataphrakt belonging
to Viscountess Orlane
that has gravity
control capability.
Viscountess Orlane?
The woman who was
to be my wife.
We did our very utmost.
Using the power of the Aldnoah that His Majesty
bestowed upon us, we ruled the people,
cultivated the wastelands of Vers,
expanded our domain,
and tried to amass wealth.
But no matter what we did, we would
always be limited by something.
Limited?
By water and air.
In the time of the people of the ancient
civilization that created Aldnoah,
water and air
were yet plentiful.
But all Vers has now is an atmosphere
that is nearly a vacuum
and what little water
remains underground.
In fact, owing to that thin atmosphere,
Vers is constantly buffeted by storms.
As it stands, no matter how much land there is,
the harvest it yields will always be meager.
The more our population grows,
production always falls short of demand,
and we grow ever more impoverished.
It was always a fool's errand
to live on that world.
But our second emperor, Emperor Gillzeria,
was a believer in Aldnoah's power
and focused all his efforts on developing
our industrial capacity.
The royal family, the masters of
Aldnoah, ruled with an iron fist
and turned a deaf ear to the pleas
of our suffering people.
And then... the rising discontent of the
populace was directed against Earth.
He whipped the people of Vers into
a frenzy, saying that it was Earth,
with their claims of sovereignty,
obstruction of independence,
and attempts to rule us
from their distant world,
that was their enemy and
the source of their suffering.
Horrifyingly, those lies
were supported by all.
They were the superior race,
and the filthy subhumans who hoarded Earth's
bounty for themselves were evil.
Planning to invade Earth,
we passed through the Hyper Gate
and gathered our forces.
Foolishly thinking all the while
that our actions were just.
And then, my Dioscuria, with its
superior flight capabilities,
and Orlane's Deucalion went down to
Tanegashima as an advance party.
How unimpressive...
This was hardly worth steeling our
resolve and coming down for.
Do you not agree,
Milord Saazbaum?
Indeed. This is quite
a disappointment, Orlane.
We will be able to take this planet
far more easily than we expected.
Our people will be most pleased,
to say nothing of His Majesty.
What's going on?!
Powerful space-time
distortion waves?
The Hyper Gate!
The Moon... has shattered?
We're withdrawing, Orlane!
What's the matter? Withdraw at once!
The surface is unsafe!
The distortions are affecting
my antigravity device!
I can't fly!
I'm coming to assist!
You mustn't! It is too late!
Leave me!
Hurry!
Orlane!
I will have my revenge for Orlane,
mark my words.
Count!
Count Saazbaum!
This is the battleship Deucalion.
HQ, requesting docking clearance.
Welcome, Deucalion.
Clearance granted.
Set down in Dock #6.
Deucalion, acknowledged.
I see it with my own two eyes,
and I still can't believe it.
A flying battleship... It's like something
out of those Japanese comic books.
I heard it was abandoned because
they couldn't activate its Aldnoah.
Those reports that they're harboring
Princess Asseylum must be true.
We finally made it...
Yeah.
United Earth Headquarters...
Touchdown in 3... 2... 1...
Ship is down.
Now mooring.
I suppose this means our
voyage is over, too.
Yes, for now.
For now, ma'am?
If we keep the ship,
what will the enemy do?
Now that we're here,
we're safe, right?
This is a secret base
600 meters underground
that was designed to withstand
a nuclear strike.
They say that lots of refugees are being
housed in the massive shelters here.
At capacity, they're supposed to have
3 years' worth of supplies stockpiled.
But apparently, the numbers
don't add up.
Are they over capacity?
The opposite, apparently.
They have too many provisions.
It looks like most of the refugees
never made it here.
If this place is destroyed...
Terrans might go extinct.
It's huge!
Hey, Inaho.
I looked around.
There's lots of Areions sitting around, so
why would you keep using that Sleipnir?
I'm used to it.
That's all?
Heavier armor wouldn't have helped
against anything we've fought so far.
If you're okay with it,
suit yourself.
Do we even have to fight now? We can
let the professionals do their job.
Right?
Yeah.
You can't be too careful.
It's got conformal
power assist, huh?
Aldnoah...
This is what started it all.
Thank you very much, Inaho.
I'm given to understand that it's
you whom I owe my life to.
No, it's because
we're in a war.
How many times
does this make it?
I'm not sure. And I wouldn't
say that I've saved it.
This is a war, after all.
You're a kind person, aren't you?
You are.
After all this is over...
We will remain friends
after all this is over, won't we?
Yes.
I'm glad.
Milady, it's time.
Very well.
Then let's be off, Eddelrittuo.
If you'll excuse us.
I am Asseylum Vers Allusia.
I am the Princess Royal,
granddaughter of
Rayregalia Vers Rayvers,
Emperor of Vers.
I address the people
of Father Vers.
I call for an immediate cessation of
hostilities in this meaningless war.
I am safe.
Alive and well.
It is not Terrans who made
an attempt on my life.
It was a plot by the Orbital Knights, who have
their sights set on an invasion of Earth.
The Terrans are innocent.
Stop the fighting immediately.
And then make peace
with Earth.
I beg you, put a stop
to this tragedy.
This is the Tharsis!
I retrieved it
from Castle Cruhteo.
He was unworthy of it.
Its Aldnoah drive
is powered down...
Which means that
Count Cruhteo truly is...
Princess Asseylum's location
has been pinpointed
via laser transmission
to the Moon base.
The Moon base is under the control
of those who feel as I do.
Her Highness' proclamation
will reach no one's ears.
The final battle is about to take place
at the enemy's main stronghold.
Even with the full might of a Landing
Castle, it will be no easy feat.
My debt to your father
is paid.
You may join my forces
or you may flee to Earth.
Do as you will.
Milord Saazbaum, all launch
preparations are now complete.
Begin Landing Castle descent!
Destination: UE Headquarters!
Novostal'sk, Russia!