Take the weretiger alive?
What are you after?
My target has always been...
My target has always been you
and you alone, weretiger.
Your fellow agents lying there
just got caught in the crossfire.
This is because of me?
Indeed.
That is your karma, weretiger.
You will cause ill for everyone
around you, just by being alive.
My karma?
Ability:
Rashoumon
Rashoumon.
Where... am I?
I see you've come to, brat.
Kunikida... san?
Damn, I can't believe you pulled
this during such a busy time.
I...
I was... attacked by the Mafia.
I remember now...
Kunikida-san, where are
Tanizaki-san and Naomi-san?!
Calm down.
They're both okay.
Are you... sure?
Yes.
Dr. Yosano is treating
Tanizaki right now next door.
What a nice big injury
you've racked up, huh, Tanizaki?
Do you like my treatment that much?
All right, I'll give you the extra
special treatment plan this time.
Scream
Ah...
That's... treatment?
I heard, brat.
Huh?
You have a seven-billion-yen bounty
on your head on the black market.
What?
Seven billion, huh?
You've moved up in the world.
No wonder the Port Mafia are keen
to get their hands on you.
Seven billion?
My target has always been you
and you alone, weretiger.
I see.
Wh-Wh-What should I do?
The Mafia might launch
a raid on the Agency.
But why me?
Don't panic.
The Port Mafia are certainly
violent to the extreme,
but keep your cool.
Ideal
Losing your cool can kill
even the most skilled.
That's what my mentor would tell me.
Um, it's upside down...
Your notebook.
I haven't lost my cool!
I'm not going to panic over the Mafia!
I'd beat them back, even if
they attacked this very second!
I'll go like this, and this!
Kunikida-san's pretty wound up...
Slash and burn like a pro,
His explanation's all over the place!
stabbity-stab and beat them all!
It must mean the Agency's
situation is pretty dire,
and all because of me.
He'll come for sure.
You caused this.
The worst-case scenario may come to pass...
Think about what you can do.
What I can do?
By the way, brat.
I've been looking for something...
Have you seen my glasses?
Episode Four:
The Tragedy of the Fatalist
It's time.
Stay back.
Sorry to bother you at work, folks.
Wh-Who the hell are you?
We're here for work, as well.
We'll be done soon enough.
We've heard rumors that an unruly bunch
have been selling Port Mafia
cargo on the black market.
They're supposedly based right here.
We're just looking for evidence.
Do you mind if I look through the cargo?
There's the evidence, right here.
That's impossible!
It's a steel pipe.
You've never seen a gift in action before?
Kill them all.
The best smokes are always
after a job well done.
An explosion?
What's going on?
I hear it's a massacre.
Damn...
The military police say the
Port Mafia's military squad did it...
The Black Lizard group,
the most violent of them all.
The Black Lizard?
They're as good as special ops,
and merciless to boot.
The Port Mafia's Black Lizard...
If they were to attack the Agency...
The worst-case scenario.
Yes?
Who is this?
It's me.
Weretiger!
I see...
He saw the business card
I left at the Agency.
Your colleagues saved you the other day,
but that won't be the case next time.
What do you want?
I'm going to quit the Agency.
I'm going to quit, and go on the run alone.
Catch me if you can!
I see.
So you're telling us to call
off the war on the Agency?
Call the Black Lizard!
Oh there you are, brat.
Thanks to you, it's a huge mess.
It's highly probable that this will
turn into the worst-case scenario.
Investigation Report
Come help carry these—
Hey!
There's no need to worry.
The worst-case scenario
won't happen anymore.
This agency is safe.
Huh?
Hey!
Come help, brat!
Where are you running off to now?!
Get out, you good-for-nothing!
No orphanage would welcome the likes of you!
The world would be a better place
if you'd just die in a ditch somewhere!
You're late.
You're two minutes late.
Black Lizard Commander
Tachiwara Michizou
Don't be so uptight, gramps.
What a glum place.
Where's Gin?
Is he late, too?
He's already here.
He's behind you.
Black Lizard Commander
Gin
Heh, a creep like always.
You get on my nerves.
Wanna fight?
Stop it, fools.
Would either of you like to be reported KIA?
Black Lizard Leader,
Hirotsu Ryuurou
Ability:
Falling Camellia
Fine.
You're a hard one to read.
We're all here.
Well done.
And?
What's the target that takes
three of us to crush?
The target...
is the Armed Detective Agency's office.
The Agency?
Not the weretiger, then?
The previous attempt failed
because the Agency interfered.
We won't make the same mistake twice.
We'll annihilate the Agency first to
prevent them from acting as his guard.
No survivors?
Fine by me.
Understood.
I can't have Akutagawa-senpai
taking a back seat
to a mere detective agency!
Fear death.
Fear slaughter.
Those who desire death
have an equal desire to die.
Worthless men
have no right to draw breath.
Your resolve is admirable.
I will give you a reason to live.
I have finally found a reason to live.
A reason to live?
No, a reason I'd kept on living till now.
That's right.
I've lived to this day so that I can
be in a double-suicide with you.
I'm sure of it.
Ah, bella donna.
Feel free to do it on your own..
A double-suicide is not possible alone.
By the way, Dazai-san?
Do you have a proper life insurance policy?
Why would you ask that, bella donna?
Well...
Because you have racked up quite a tab.
If you haven't gotten one yet,
I'll be happy to refer you one.
Ah, your vitality is blinding.
Aw, if that's the best you've
got for changing the subject,
I'm going to go ahead and barge into
your agency on the fourth floor.
Ah, your decisiveness is even more blinding.
Not even a sentry?
Talk about careless.
Who are you?
Apologies.
Even though you're a detective agency,
we forgot to make an appointment.
And we forgot to knock.
The Port Mafia's Black Lizard.
Well, I hope you'll overlook these mishaps.
Our errand will be over soon enough.
Get out, you good-for-nothing!
No orphanage would welcome the likes of you!
The world would be a better place if
you'd just die in a ditch somewhere!
They were right.
There's nowhere I can belong.
Gunshots?
But that's where...
Why's the Agency being attacked?!
Oh, sorry!
Why is this happening?
It's all because of me
that everyone's in danger again!
Stop!
What?
Huh?
There!
Hup.
So you're finally back, brat.
Uhh...
This is why I hate raids.
They really throw off
our budget projections.
How much do you think repairing the office
and replacing inventory will cost?!
Using machine guns for a raid
was a little over the top.
It's your turn to go
around the neighborhood
with apologies and gifts, Kunikida-kun.
So it is the worst-case scenario!
Huh?
So this is the "worst-case scenario"?
This is the Port Mafia military squad
said to be on par with special ops?
Huh?
Kunikida-san, what should we do with them?
Throw them out the window.
Roger!
Hup, hup.
One...
Two...
For the umpteenth time,
Three!
I wish they'd give up on raids.
So it's the "umpteenth" time?
The Agency's far more violent
than the Port Mafia.
Bye!
Hurry up and help with the clean-up, brat!
Have a nice trip!
I can't believe you wandered
off in the middle of it all!
I told you, you're a member
of the Agency now.
You should be thinking about
what you yourself can do.
Well, helping with clean-up
is about all you can do.
Think about what you can do.
I see.
Hey, if you've got time to laugh...
What, are you crying?
I... I... I'm not crying!
You are.
I'm not!
Just look at you.
You're so typical for your generation.
Even when given a job,
you just go off and play without permission.
You cry if anyone gives so
much as a word of criticism.
That's not it.
That's not what this is about.
But you're crying.
I am...
But that isn't what it's about!
The only reason they can call
themselves a detective agency
and function as one
is my ability, Ultra-Deduction.
Oh, a murder case has
arrived on our doorstep.
Okay, Atsushi-kun,
come with me on the case.
Uh, I'm not sure I'm up to the task...
Next time on Bungo Stray Dogs,
Episode 5: Murder on D Street.
Episode 5
Is this going to be an
actual detective story?
All is well that is well by me.