People say that when someone
dies, they can go to heaven.
But I don't think that's the case.
When someone dies,
I'm sure that person journeys
into people's hearts.
They live on as a memory,
just like my mother and father
currently live on in our hearts.
But that, too, will eventually wane.
That's why people desire to leave
something behind in this world.
So others don't forget them.
Is this even going to show up?
The viewfinder's completely black.
So they're not forgotten...
Wh-What's going on?!
Such...
...a beautiful hand...
Hand?
Huh?
Why am I...
Yesterday I was trying to test
out the high ISO film...
And then I...
Kai-kun!
If you don't get up soon,
you're going to be late.
Okay.
You're going on a business trip abroad?
It'll just be for three months.
I see.
Where you going?
Bolivia.
They don't have enough
people there, supposedly.
Hey, Kai-kun.
Hm?
Is it okay for your sister to leave you?
You want to go, don't you?
So go.
Have fun.
I can make my own food.
It'll be summer break soon, anyway.
Don't go too crazy because
you'll be on your own.
I know.
Also, that's bad manners.
I'm going to go shopping
and such on the way home.
I'll be back by seven.
Got it.
Have fun.
You, too.
So I'll be on my own, then...
This is a nice place to shoot.
Red... hair.
Why?
How come...
...I'm standing out so much?
Did I get something wrong?
So, have you figured out where
we're going to film yet, Kai-kun?
Huh?
Didn't you go searching
for a spot yesterday?
With that?
No, I just went to test out the film...
You're going to shoot a
movie, right, Director?
I'm just kind of messing around.
Just because I felt like it.
Come on.
I was gonna help you, too.
If Tetsuro-kun were in the movie,
I think all the girls would go wild.
You think so?
I'll pass.
Actually, what about you, Mio?
Kai, wouldn't Mio make a good lead?
It's summer, so we could make it
like an idol video, or something.
What do you think?
It won't cost us any money, and
we wouldn't need a script.
That makes sense...
They're staring at me...
Their imaginations are
running wild with me...
The guys are showing their
true colors here...
I was just kidding.
But I kinda...
...want to try something.
And what would that be?
I'm not sure.
Just something.
Yeah.
We are in high school, after all.
And it's summertime.
Yeah.
We might just have to do something.
And here I was wondering
what you were filming...
Huh?
So she's your type, huh?
The camera's still recording...
That wasn't what I was trying to do...
I see...
She's like the complete
opposite of you, Kanna.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means what it means.
But what is that supposed to mean?!
I told you it means what it means.
What the hell?
You always—
It's okay. Calm down, Kanna.
Whose side are you on anyway, Mio?!
And unsurprisingly, I hadn't noticed yet.
Teachers' Room
Sorry I'm late.
I'll be transferring in today.
My name is Ichika Takatsuki.
Our drama...
We're starting homeroom now.
...had already begun.
Everyone take your seats.
The camera was already rolling.
Ichika Takatsuki
Were you in any clubs at your old school?
You don't get many people transferring
at this time of the year.
Your hair color is really pretty!
I...
Is it natural?
Are you going out with anyone?
Come on, you wolves bare
your fangs elsewhere.
Wh-What's wrong, Yamano?
Who cares?
Besides, we're her classmates.
If you guys don't settle down,
you won't like what I'll do.
What are you doing for lunch today?
Oh yeah, I was watching TV yesterday, and...
My name is Remon Yamano.
Oh, I'm... uh,
Ichika Takatsuki.
Huh? Is something funny?
I think we'll be good friends.
Y-You think so?
Yamano-san...
You can call me Refon.
Uh, so Remon...
May I ask you something?
What ish it?
Why are you wearing a different uniform?
That's a secret.
A major secret.
I-I see.
Anyway, you've got quite the
biased collection there.
Huh?
I-Is there something weird about it?
I've got carbohydrates, a drink...
Pretty average, don't you think?
Am I violating some sort of regional taboo?
You're pretty weird.
What was weird?
How am I weird?
The way you're acting now.
Her name is Ichika Takatsuki-san.
She transferred into class 3-A today.
She's 160 centimeters tall,
and 41 kilograms.
Her three sizes, starting from the top,
are 92-58-88.
Her shoe size is—
How did you find all this out?
Well, I...
Teacher,
could you give me the
details on the third year
who just transferred in?
Aw, Ishigaki-kun...
Just don't tell anyone else, okay?
So that's basically how it went down.
I'm pretty sure that was illegal.
You gonna say "thank you"?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
What are you doing over here?
Tanigawa.
Sup? You eat lunch already?
Yeah.
Oh, that's what's going on.
You trying to sneak more footage of her?
N-No.
I just happened to hit record
when she was there...
Liar.
I'm serious!
What?
I just wanna hit you now!
Wai—
You're already hitting me!
Shut up!
They're having their lover's quarrel.
Stop it, Tanigawa.
All right!
We're doing it!
I-I can't do that.
I don't have any cute swimsuits, and I...
Kai!
Let's go.
Huh?
What?
Go where?
S-So what's so wrong with my lunc—
Hi there.
Sorry, do you have a second?
Hey, Tetsuro.
What are you trying to pull?
Just let me handle this.
N-Never mind.
Uh, what is it?
You're Ichika Takatsuki-senpai,
who just transferred in today, right?
My name's Tetsuro Ishigaki, a first year.
This is Kaito Kirishima.
We're trying to put together
a film with some friends.
And we were wondering if you
wanted to appear in our movie?
What?!
Huh?
Hey, what are you saying?!
Sure.
Huh?
If you think I'd be good for the part...
I'd love to do it.
Once something starts moving,
it's hard to stop.
Sinsh you're ashking...
I'll participate, as well.
Huh?
Remon Yamano, third year here.
Nice to meet you.
Before I even knew it, the camera...
What? Third year?
She's older than us?
Episode 1
I can't,
Senpai.
...had begun to roll.
Sometimes asking is all it takes,
Free-style swimming
for class today.
but I never thought she'd say okay.
Ichika-senpai's just too kind.
You're nuts.
I do something the second I think of it!
That's my policy.
Man, this feels great.
The view's great, too.
You sound like a dirty old man.
Are you really gonna make a movie?
We already told some senpai, so...
Right?
Wh-What's it going to be about?
We'll just let the tiny
Remon-senpai handle it.
I mean...
Let me handle the plot.
I have a script I wrote for Lucas.
A Hollywood script?!
It wasn't something they
asked you to write, was it?
That's what she said, anyway.
Fine.
Huh?
Then... I'm in, too.
Me, too.
I might be able to help out
as a stagehand, or something.
No, you should be on screen.
No, I couldn't possibly!
Why not?
It'd be fine.
I can't!
A movie, huh?
Director,
would it be too much to
ask you for direction?
Then...
I'll guide you step-by-waist.
You mean step-by-step.
What are you laughing at?
Nothing, really...
Wait, what is that?
Huh?
That right there.
What?
Isn't that a hickey?
What?!
Huh?
Oh, here.
You're sure prepared...
Wait, what is that?!
I told you it was a hickey...
That's not it!
I bet some bug bit me when I was out
filming yesterday, or something.
For the love of God,
I don't remember anything
happening that'd cause thi—
H-He...
He went quiet.
Y-You don't remember anything?
Just what were you filming, anyway?
That wasn't what happened!
That they would lower land
taxes for the farmers,
give the citizens free speech
and freedom of assembly,
I'm glad...
and request a more equitable renegotiation
of foreign treaties with other nations...
...he's doing well...
These were the three primary demands of...
So we'll all get together,
since we have tomorrow off,
and have a kick-off meeting for
the production of the movie.
Right.
I'll contact Remon-senpai and the others.
Then, I'll see you guys later.
Right.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah.
I should get going, too.
Right. Take care.
He doesn't look it, but Kaito's
actually pretty excited.
Really?
Yeah.
Did I do something I shouldn't have?
Shouldn't have what?
Well, I guess the more chances
for you, the better.
Good luck.
It kinda pisses me off when you
look down on people like that.
What am I getting all excited about?
But a movie, huh?
Isn't that...
This shouldn't be wrong now...
What are you doing?
I, uh...
I'm Kaito.
Kaito Kirishima.
Oh, Kaito-kun.
But why are you here?
I saw you from over there.
You're fishing, right?
Y-Yeah.
This is one of my hobbies.
That's good and all, but...
There aren't any fish in this river.
Th-Thanks for telling me...
I'm glad to be of help.
I don't really know this area very well yet.
So you were a big help.
If you go up a little farther,
you'll find a bigger river
which has to have some fish.
I guess I'll get going...
Huh?
Never mind.
I guess I'll be seeing you
around from now on.
Oh, uh, yeah.
See you around, then.
I wonder if I shouldn't have done that...
Maybe I should have talked to her longer.
You know, I could have...
I bet you moved here by yourself.
Wow! How'd you know?
I could tell by that piece
of luggage you're carrying.
It's rather simple profiling.
And I have further deduced
that you have no place to stay
and don't know what to do.
Pretty impressive.
You had an issue with the place
you were supposed to stay.
Ding, ding, ding.
And so you're at a loss.
You fishing there was proof of that.
Ding, ding, once again.
Would you...
...like to stay at my place?
Huh?
It's really up to you.
Is it really okay?
Of course.
We're actually at my house right now.
What a large house!
My grandmother passed away
and left this house.
It's really too big for me, honestly.
Having someone else here really
wouldn't affect me in the least.
How wonderful!
And if you're with me here,
I could give you some acting
direction for the movie.
Then I could really guide you step-by-waist.
I think you mean step-by-step.
Oh, you're right.
Wait, is this reality?
Huh?
How long have I been talking?
A while now...
Kaito-kun?
But that really helps out.
I honestly didn't know what to do.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
You asked me if I wanted
to stay at your place.
That's when you started listening...
W-Wait a sec...
That was just kind of my imagination...
I was talking to myself.
My sister lives here with me.
If I suddenly brought a girl home,
I think she'd pass out...
That... makes sense.
Yeah, that makes sense.
I understand.
Sorry for asking too much of you.
Huh?
Where are you going?
Some place that'd be good to
set up camp around here...
Oh, damn it!
Huh? Is that you, Nanami-san?
Oh, Kanna-chan!
You're not usually out and about
so early, especially around here.
I'm just doing someone else's
job, and I had to get ready...
Ready?
Yeah, but this thing started
acting up out of nowhere...
Oh, I know.
Kanna-chan, could you help
me out for a little bit?
Huh?
Just sit anywhere over there.
I'll put your luggage over here for now...
That's heavy.
How did you carry this all that way?
Oh, the gra—
Gra?
Oh, you have to grab it like this.
There's a trick to it.
Anyway, you can stay here one night.
You can stay here tonight, so...
What's wrong?
Sorry.
It's the first time I've
been in a guy's room.
I-I see...
Oh, we can't just sit here!
I'll bring you some food later!
Wait, my sister is going to come
home around seven...
You need to take a shower now...
Are your clothes in there?
S-Sorry...
What's in there, anyway?
Let's see...
This is the shampoo...
Pajamas...
I guess my sister wears negligees...
Anyway, I need to get
something for her to wear.
I... I put...
...your change of clothes on
top of the washing machine!
Thanks.
You don't have to open the door!
There's still a bit of time before seven...
What a day...
I met senpai...
We're all going to make a movie...
And for some reason she's now in my house.
Anyway, I need to get my
stuff cleaned up and change.
Oh, yeah.
I need to move these, too.
What's going on?
This is where that bug bit me...
What is this?
Kaito-kun!
About these clothes...
Kaito-kun?!
Kaito-kun!
What's wrong?
Hang in there!
Kaito-kun!
That's...
His cellular metabolism is...
Rinon!
Good, it's working.
Sorry.
I'm really sorry.
You'll be fine, okay?
You really helped me out.
Thanks, Kanna-chan.
No, it's okay.
So you'll be somewhere
else for three months.
Yeah, take care of Kai-kun for me.
You can come and stay here, if you'd like.
I couldn't do that!
I'm wishing you luck, though.
What are you talking about?!
Don't be silly...
I, uh...
What's wrong?
It looks like my eyesight
has gotten worse again.
I saw an illusion of Kai-kun being held
by some girl while they
were surrounded by light...
What are you talking about?
That's funny.
I know, right?
Uh...
This isn't...
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh—
Th-Th-Th-Th-Th—
What are you doing?!
That's really embarrassing!
Huh? I...
A-Anyway, let go of him.
And unsurprisingly, I hadn't noticed yet.
Wh-What?
Put some clothes on!
Dynamite!
All I know...
All that's left behind is...
Episode 2
Together with Senpai...
I don't want you...
These overflowing feelings...
...to find out.
...they won't stop.