I heard you're Embryo's knight.
I wanted to see how strong you've become.
I'm disappointed, Salia.
Jill.
It's been a while, Salia.
Why did you come here, after so long?
To see my ex, of course.
Haven't you heard?
I was Embryo's lover.
Now, move.
I won't believe anything you say anymore.
I'm Embryo's knight.
Salia, Captain of the Diamond Rose Knights!
I won't let you go to him.
Hear that, Ange?
Huh?
I bet we can go to Aura, though.
All right, I'll take it!
Stop, Ange!
Aren't you going to fight me?
If you get in my way, I'll cut you!
Oh? I'd like to see you try.
A Battle With No Tomorrow
Space-time convergence is at 83%.
Twelve inbound from ten o'clock.
Understood.
I'm a beetle that's flying into the fire!
Gravity wave interferometer
has exceeded 30 TeV.
Five more at two o'clock.
Understood.
Thanks.
Massive fleet coming from starboard.
Understood.
I shoot them down,
but there's no end to them!
There's no time to complain.
We're all taking this ship back home.
Protect it well.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm counting on you, Salamandinay.
Such pointless resistance!
They can't stop the world from ending.
I'll stop it!
I made a promise with Ange...
That I'd protect this world!
What a pitiful man.
Ange is coming with me to the new world!
Damn you!
Weak.
You thought you could kill me?
Don't make me laugh!
Marika's death will be a complete shame,
unless I kill you!
It's her fault for getting killed!
She was used and abused
because she was weak.
So she paid for it!
That's why Embryo-kun made me strong.
A Ragna-mail and a knight's crest.
You think that makes you strong, Salia?
Embryo-sama gave me everything.
Strength. Love. Everything!
Love?
He doesn't love anyone.
He feeds and cares for people...
So he can use them later.
That's how he played me.
I lost everything.
Wake up, Salia.
I told you, I'm not going
to believe anything you say.
You're the one who was using me!
Beauty that will never to be tarnished!
Gallantry like that of a lithe beast!
She is indeed well worth the taming.
But you haven't yet seen Ange's wildness...
Clad only in what she was born with.
I know.
I even know how many moles
there are on her inner thigh!
You don't know anything about Ange, do you?
Ange is violent and temperamental,
but she smiles and gets angry and cries.
She's the cutest girl there is.
Tame her?
You're a sad man, aren't you?
Oh? You've changed, haven't you?
Wait! What have you done to Ange?
We did it! We went all the way.
What?
We touched, kissed, and lay in each other's arms!
For three days and nights!
You would insult my wife
with your asinine lies?
It's the truth.
Ange accepted my everything.
With the softest, warmest,
deepest part of her!
I'm not afraid of anything anymore!
How obscene and depraved!
I won't forgive you for disgracing my wife!
I'll erase your existence
from every universe!
Aura! It's you, isn't it?
Get out of my way!
Particle field down to 17%.
Field has been breached!
Port impact imminent!
Status?
Engine One has stopped.
Aurora is losing altitude.
Bring it back up!
I can't, we're descending!
All units, brace for impact!
Damage report.
Blocks Two, Three, and Seven
breached on impact.
Momoka! Painkillers, please.
Okay.
The particle field is gone!
Anti-air guns aren't responding.
Dammit! We're sitting ducks.
Mei, can you fix it?
On it. I'll clean it up within twenty minutes.
I'm counting on you.
No.
Mary, your twelve!
Did we make it?
Ersha!
Why are you taking so
much time on these toys?
You're late, Ange.
Huh?
I'll let you take care of the toys.
Wait, you're going to fire that?
It's the only way we can save Aura.
Won't it blow Aura away, too?
I'll fire at 70% power. Don't worry.
Then do it!
The wind flies, El Ragna,
making promises with destiny.
The wind goes, El Ragna, with roaring wings.
Space-time Convergence Cannon
This song...
It's Salamandinay-san.
I had nothing!
Flying to the stars, El Ragna,
over thousands of leagues to the beyond.
I wasn't royalty.
I don't know that song!
I don't have the ring!
No matter how hard I tried,
I was never chosen.
Not by the Villkiss!
Not by you!
Going to the stars, El Ragna,
instantly, for eternity,
But Embryo-sama chose me!
That's why, Alektra,
I don't need you anymore!
Calmly, calmly, tenderly fades away.
In the cradle of life and death,
So you have become strong,
Salia!
Ah, the journey of rebirth
lasting thousands of years.
Seeking hands to join,
Wind, blowing from soul to soul,
Blow to new worlds.
This song...
Space-time convergence is at 91%.
Maggie-san.
I brought bandages from storage.
Vivi-chan, take those two and run!
Ersha.
This way, discs!
Ersha!
What's going on?
The gravity field must have weakened
due to the space-time convergence,
causing the singularity to dissipate.
Can you hear me?
False people... no, Norma.
I am the priestess of Aura, Aura Midgardia.
Priestess!
The people of Aura will assist your ship.
Badass!
The tides have turned, Embryo!
Does it seem that way to you?
Embryo, what are you...
Chris!
Embryo-sama!
What...
You shall help buy me some time.
It's not responding!
Tania!
Erma!
You're using your own people as bait?!
I must go and pick up my bride-to-be.
Take care of the rest of this, everyone.
Embryo-sama!
Salia!
This is Embryo's true nature.
Wake up, Salia.
Before you lose everything the way I did!
Alektra!
It can't be.
It can't be... can it, Embryo-kun?
I've been abandoned again.
I've been betrayed again!
I won't believe anything anymore!
Die, everyone!
Chris!
Die! Die!
Die, everyone!
Stop, Chris!
Stay away! Die!
What did you expect?
Can someone who calls himself
your friend really be your friend?
You let him trick you, you idiot.
It's because you guys abandoned me!
I never abandoned you!
You all made a fool of me.
Even though I'm suffering so much...
I'm in agony!
Why don't you understand?
All you do is whine.
Give it a break, you emo bitch!
Yeah! How could I know
when you never said anything?
I'm an idiot, y'know!
Go away!
Rosalie!
Chris!
Let go!
We're falling.
I don't care.
I'll die with you.
I can't live without you!
You're lying.
I love you, Chris.
You abandoned me...
I never abandoned you.
Dreams fly, El Ragna,
hope becomes the key to the door.
Believe me, please, Chris.
I would never abandon you.
We're the only ones that know your bust size,
where you're sensitive,
and where you hide your stash.
To dreams we go, El Ragna, toward the light.
We're the only ones that know everything!
Rosalie.
Trust me again, please.
Be my friend, please,
Chris.
Vanishing back into the wing beats of return,
Ah, the true dawn pierces the clouds,
reaching towards the peak of the sky.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Chris.
I won't forgive you...
Until you buy me a new barrette.
I'll buy you the best one there is.
The withering flower is fleeting.
Will you stop cheating
when we're playing games?
I will.
I give myself to love.
Will you let me have the bath first?
Yeah.
Hold up your courage
and raise your first voice.
But I did something I can't take back...
Let's buy Marika a grave
and remember her forever.
And towards the winds of
dawn, dusk and eternity,
This is stupid.
It's the end of the world.
What the hell are we doing?
Making up, right?
Ah, the journey of rebirth
lasting thousands of years.
That was my line!
Seeking hands to join,
Wind, blowing from soul to soul,
Fly to new worlds.
Aura!
That?
It's our mother's light.
Aura.
Ange.
You lose, Embryo.
Alektra.
You're leaving, aren't you?
Whether you win or lose,
you're ditching this world.
Take me with you.
What?
What's gotten into you?
I understand now.
I still...
Unfortunately, I can't.
Why?
You loved me so much.
I only saved you.
I couldn't just stand by while you
struggled with your taboo passion.
That's how you took everything from me.
My heart, and everything else!
Are you going to use that
right arm of yours to kill me?
No.
You wouldn't die, would you?
So I'm doing this instead.
Now you can't get away.
Now...
Alektra here.
I've captured Embryo.
I'm about to destroy his mach—
I see. So that was your plan.
Huh?
No.
Your main body...
Goodbye, Alektra.
I have no need for women from my past.
Captain, space-time convergence
is at 95% and counting.
What?!
What's going on?
It should be out of energy!
I don't know, it's...
Aura's energy will act as a detonator
for the space-time convergence.
The universe's phase energy
will take care of the rest.
Embryo!
Ange.
Space-time convergence is at 97%!
Next Episode
Next week's the final episode.
Is everyone ready?
Are we really going to be able to
wrap this up in one more episode?
We could do a theatrical release or extras
on releases. There are plenty of ways.
What the hell did "Cross" in
Cross Ange mean, anyway?
To the End of Time
Ange is always cross, I guess?
It's a pun?!