I'm Kurihara Osamu, a first-year in high school.
The candle we both lit in
our hearts on a holy night
can never be extinguished.
You kissed Nanako-san on Christmas?!
The very first day you started dating?
Yeah.
Isn't that too fast?
There aren't any rules for that—
It's too fast!
Huh?
Then when is it okay for you, Takeo?
The autumn of my third year in high school!
Why autumn?
My Birthday
Okay, I'm off to a date with Nanako.
Hey, you do well by her.
Of course!
He's so easygoing...
Why is it the autumn of your third year?
Spring would be too fast.
And I thought winter would be too slow.
Hmm...
A kiss...
That's so far beyond holding hands.
Good thing you don't have cavities.
It's mouth to mouth.
It's a big deal.
I bet it's an even bigger deal
for girls than for me.
When the time comes,
I hope I can make it a good experience.
Takeo-kun, your birthday's in three days.
Oh, but maybe you'll be spending it with
your family because it's New Year's Day.
No, it's fine.
Really?
Then I can see you?
Sure.
Want to do the holiday shrine visit together?
Okay!
Takeo-kun?
I can't, not yet!
Right, this year, I'll be spending
my birthday with Yamato...
Sunakawa
Oh, welcome back, Makoto!
Thanks.
Welcome back, yourself. You came home?
Yeah, just now.
Bullet train was supper crowded.
Home's where the heart is.
The last day of the year should
be spent with family, after all.
How's Takeo?
Are things going well with him and his girlfriend?
Yeah.
Hello?
Oh, Yamato-san... Long time, no see!
Oh, hello.
It's been a while.
What's the matter?
Did you get mixed up, trying to see Takeo?
No, that isn't it...
Tomorrow is Takeo-kun's birthday.
Oh, yeah.
I was wondering what kind of cake to make.
Oh, right.
He likes everything, so that almost
makes it harder to choose...
Why are you guys in my room?
How about the first cake you made for him?
The cheesecake Takeo ate that first time?
Oh, right!
I don't have to make something new.
Okay, I'll try doing something
with a cheesecake.
Thanks, Sunakawa-kun.
Good... I'm glad we figured it out.
Oh... And um...
Uh...
I'm wondering what Takeo-kun would
think if a girl tried to kiss him.
Huh?
Weren't you worried before that he
mistakenly thought you were naïve?
Oh, yes.
That's been cleared up.
But he isn't holding back because of me.
Takeo-kun's just very modest.
Modest
Right...
You might have something there...
Yeah.
He said he won't kiss until the
autumn of his third year.
Huh?!
He said spring would be too early.
Th-Third year... Autumn... Okay.
Okay, Takeo-kun...
Then I'll wait till third year.
But if you wanted to,
you could just do it whenever.
Huh?
I think Takeo would be happy.
What?
What should I do?!
Now she doesn't
know what to do.
Have you ever kissed someone, Sunakawa-kun?
Dostoevsky
Why aren't you saying anything?
Of course he hasn't.
Are you being pretentious?
He's never had a girlfriend.
Right, sorry for asking such a strange question.
Thank you for helping me
today by hearing me out.
And thank you, too!
Take care.
Have a good New Year!
Okay.
You, too.
Yamato-san really loves Takeo, huh?
Sincere
So she's going to kiss Takeo...
Imagining it, I feel a little down!
Then maybe you
shouldn't imagine it.
How's Oda-san?
Oh, he's fine.
Actually, ever since MM Land,
he's been coming on really strong.
Gouda!!
Singing Contest
Have a happy New Year, everyone.
And so ends this year.
It was a good year...
Take, if you're sleepy, go sleep in your room.
Oof...
What are you up to tomorrow?
At ten, I'm going to a shrine with Yamato.
Oh, okay.
Goodnight.
Night.
Happy Birthday, Takeo-kun!
Oh, thanks.
Were you sleeping, Takeo-kun?
Oh, don't worry about it.
Sorry about that.
See you tomorrow... Oh, it's already today!
Yeah.
Goodnight.
Night.
This year will be a good year, too.
Ram  HNY  Gouda Takeo
first laugh of the year
Happy New Year!
Happy New Year.
Here, your New Year's gift.
New Year's Gift
Oh, thanks!
I'm off.
Okay.
Yamato!
Takeo-kun!
I love her this year, too.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
It's her second time saying it.
It's my second time saying it.
Yeah.
I was really happy I could be there
for your birthday this year.
Oh, I guess it's last year now.
Yeah.
So I'd like to make your birthday
something you'll never forget.
Okay.
I'll never forget, not ever.
Aren't your hands cold, Takeo-kun?
Not at all.
I need gloves!
I see.
I love her!
Do you always come here, Takeo-kun?
Not always...
But last year, I was going to take
entrance exams, so I came with Suna.
I came last year, too.
This year, your family will be having a new baby.
Yeah.
It'll be fun.
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
Wow, look!
Fortune | Great Luck
You got "great luck" on your fortune!
What did you get?
I got "small luck."
But if you got great luck,
that's what I'll have, too.
If you got small luck, I'll have small luck, too.
Oh, right!
Fortune | Small Luck
Romance: Women will do well to take the initiative
I don't care if I have small luck...
I've never been lucky with fortunes.
Romance: Sleep on it, and wait for good news
I hope everyone will have a good year.
I hope that my little brother or
sister will be born healthy.
I hope that Yamato and I can...
I hope that we'll stay together.
Hey, Takeo-kun... I made a cake.
Can I come to your place?
Sure!
I haven't really cleaned up, though...
Is that okay?
Fortune
Yeah.
Good
I'm home!
Welcome back.
That was quick.
Yeah.
Yamato's with me.
Oh, hello, Yamato-san.
Happy New Year.
I hope we have a good year ahead!
Crap... It's messier than I thought.
Oh, I'll help, too.
Take!
Mom's going with Dad to the shrine
and the New Year's sales.
We'll stop on our way home to buy food,
so we won't be back for about five hours.
Okay, that's a long time.
Make yourself at home, Yamato-san.
Would you like something to drink?
No, I'm fine...
Happy New Year!
We're here, Takeo!
Here's your present!
I just got it at the arcade!
Thanks!
Whoa, your girlfriend is here?
Seriously?
Can we come in for a bit?
Sure.
Nice to meet you.
Sorry to interrupt...
I'm Yamato. It's nice to meet you.
We went to elementary school with Takeo.
Oh, I see.
Yep.
Hey, is Takeo here?
Oh, cut it out.
Congrats! Happy Birthday!
Can we come in?
Sure.
I just can't start the new year
without seeing Takeo first.
No kidding!
But, Takeo, it's so funny that you
were born on New Year's Day.
It's funny every time.
Did Takeo ask you out?
I know the story!
Takeo saved her from a groper.
Yes.
I asked him out.
For me, it was love at first sight.
Yamato-san, you have good taste.
Please take good care of Takeo.
See you, Takeo!
Sorry about that.
They come every year.
No problem.
Oh, Takeo-kun...
This is my present to you.
Oh, thanks.
Can I open it?
Sure.
It's the first time I've gotten a
stuffed animal as a present.
If you press the stomach, it squeaks.
What a shocker!
Squeak
Why did Yamato think to give
me a stuffed animal?
How cute!
A-ha ha
I wasn't really sure what to get you,
but she was so cute, I couldn't turn away.
I see, so it was cute...
She gave me something she liked.
I also baked a cake.
I consulted Sunakawa-kun,
and decided to bake the first cake
you had from me, a cheesecake.
Happy Birthday, Takeo-kun
I thought about serving it
when everyone was here,
but I wanted you to see it
before it got all cut up.
Yeah, I can't let anyone else have this.
Oh, I brought candles! Sixteen!
I think there's a lighter in the kitchen.
I'll go get it.
Okay.
Okay...
Happy Birthday, Takeo-kun.
Yep, thanks.
It's beautiful.
Thank you, Yamato.
Takeo-kun,
you have to close your eyes and make a
wish before you blow out the candles.
Oh, okay.
Slowly, okay?
Got it, make a wish.
I'll never forget this.
Not the phone call right at
the stroke of midnight,
not the stuffed animal or the cake.
I'll never forget.
I hope Yamato will stay happy all year...
Yamato...
Thank you!
Can I blow them out now?
the candles
Huh?
Y-Yeah!
Could it be...
Good.
Oh, I forgot to bring a knife and plates.
he didn't...
I'll get some!
I don't think he noticed at all!
orz
We're back.
Oh, hey, Mom.
Welcome back.
Are you going to fillet fish or something?
I need to slice a cake.
Here's a knife.
Found a knife.
Don't want to mess up the cake...
Digging in!
It's delicious!
I don't remember cakes being this delicious.
Thank you, Yamato.
It's been a great birthday for me.
I'm glad.
I'm happy...
From: Yamato
Takeo-kun, I'm glad I could celebrate
your birthday with you.
Congratulations!
Oh, and I forgot to say it earlier,
but Happy New Year.
I'm looking forward to our time together.
I love you, Takeo-kun.
For Yamato, January first isn't New Year's Day.
It's my birthday...
She almost forgot it was New Year's Day.
Suna!
Happy New Year!
Yeah, Happy New Year.
Takeo, here's your birthday present.
Notebook
Oh, thanks.
Good luck on your studies.
Where's Yamato-san?
I just saw her home.
I got a stuffed animal from her...
Huh, a stuffed animal.
That sounds like her, all right.
I'd never think
of giving you a
stuffed animal.
I think so, too.
She baked me a cheesecake.
It was a cute, round one.
It was a great birthday.
Congrats, I'm happy for you.
She asked me to close my eyes and make
a wish, before blowing out the candles.
While my eyes were closed,
a bug landed on my mouth.
I was making a wish, so I
almost opened my mouth.
A bug?
I didn't hear one flying around,
so I didn't notice it at all.
It was pretty big.
It was kind of soft.
It stayed for a while...
I wonder what kind of bug it was.
Doesn't that mean
you were kissed?
A kiss?
A kiss...
A kiss!
It wasn't a bug!
It wasn't a bug?!
Yamato!
So I'd like to make your birthday
something you'll never forget.
Yamato!
Happy Birthday, Takeo-kun.
Yamato...
I'm glad.
Hi, Takeo-kun, what's wrong?
Yeah, I'm home.
Huh? Look outside?
Yamato
What's wrong, Takeo-kun?
Yamato...
Did you
kiss me?
Huh?
Let me do it over!
Eh?
One more time... Properly, this time...
I love you.
I'll be good to you! I will!
Yeah! I will, too!
Yeah, thanks.
I'll be good to you.
Thank you, Takeo-kun.
I'll be good to you, too.
Yeah, me, too.
My sixteenth birthday...
I'll remember this day for the rest of my life.
Welcome back.
Suna, it's thanks to you!
Thank you!
Don't mention it.
Thank you.
It's really all thanks to you!
No, not really.
I don't really want to think about it.
I didn't do anything.
It's because you put yourself out there!
Thank you!
You're being loud.
Well, I'm glad to see you looking so happy.
By the way...
In this kind of situation,
when does one have a second kiss?
I think whenever you feel like it.
I see!
But sometimes, Yamato may not feel like it!
Then you shouldn't do it.
Like I'd know.
I'd like to practice reading people!
Think "yes" or "no," and let me feel it.
There's never gonna be a "yes."
Why not just do it on anniversaries
or something?
Anniversaries!
I see.
You're the best, Suna.
The next one's Valentine's Day...
That's nerve-wracking to think about!
It's getting hot.
My Mom
Next time: My Mom.