Those are Covers...
Run, everyone! Run!
Beautiful...
Ryuko!
Very few humans are merged
this perfectly with Life Fibers.
Truly, you are my daughter.
No way! Ryuko's the daughter
of the director?!
I'm being pulled up!
Mako!
Sis!
Cut the thread!
Escape, Mankanshoku!
Mankanshoku!
Some-bo-dy-help!
Shut up!
My dad is Isshin Matoi!
You can't be my mother!
That's impossible!
If I'm not, how else do
you explain your body?
I said, shut up!
Calm yourself, Ryuko!
Stay out of this!
How very, very interesting!
I knew there was something
special about you!
You're the greatest, Ryuko!
I'm... not... done just yet...
- Lady Satsuki!
Satsuki!
EPISODE 19
RAINDROPS KEEP FALLING ON MY HEAD
ONE MONTH LATER
Hurry, Guts!
Get out of my way,
you stinking business suit!
How ya like that?!
Oh, crap! Is this the end of the line
for Mataro Mankanshoku?!
Turn into a rotten dust cloth!
You're that Elite Four chick!
Oh, you're that slacker's—
The streets are crawling with
these scraps of cloth....
Let's get out of here!
Then follow me!
So you kids have survived on your
own this past month, huh?
You're that slacker's
kid brother, all right.
Your ability to survive is the one
impressive thing about you.
The name's Mataro!
Come on, my ride's
waiting over there.
NORTHERN KANTO, SUSUKIGAHARA
Run! Run!
Hurry! Just across this hill,
there's a chopper waiting!
Damn, they caught up, huh?
Hold together...
Blade Regalia MKIII!
THREE-STAR GOKU UNIFORM
BLADE REGALIA MKIII
Damn, it's finally
reached its limit?
Boss! We'll hold 'em off here!
You guys...
The Northern Kanto Gang Leader
Alliance has some pride, too!
Understood. Show those scrap cloth
bastards what human beings will do
when their backs
are against the wall!
Okay, guys, cut loose!
Tear 'em a new one
from the inside!
Hurry! Get aboard while they're
keeping them busy!
I'm sorry, guys...
I saw your Northern Kanto hooligans
prove their resolve.
This is a war of attrition.
I know that it won't last long.
True.
Even so, we did manage
to save a few lives.
Their sacrifice wasn't in vain.
OSAKA
NUDIST BEACH SECRET BASE
Show the people we rescued
to the living quarters area!
Good work. Looks like
you guys had it rough, too.
Yeah.
Is that Mankanshoku's
little brother?
He said he and his friends had been living
in the sewers under Honnou Town.
They're an impressive
pack of rats.
I said the name's Mataro Mankanshoku,
Elite Four chick!
I'm Nonon Jakuzure.
Call me Lady Nonon, slacker junior!
If you want others to call you by name,
address them properly first, Jakuzure.
I'm ever so sorry,
Mr. Disciplinary Committee Chair.
Northern Kanto Gang Leader Alliance
has now fallen, too.
NUDIST BEACH COMMAND CENTER
This means that all academies that were
under Honnouji Academy's control
have all been destroyed
by the Covers.
Which means that the
bastions of the resistance
movement Satsuki built to fight the Life Fibers
have been lost.
Sanageyama also lost his Goku Uniform,
which was the last we had left.
All we have left now are
Jakuzure's Bakuzan-Gako
and Gamagoori's Bakuzan-Kouryu.
Both were reforged from
Lady Satsuki's shattered Bakuzan.
And my Tailor's Glove
and your Dotonbori Robo.
DTR.
Whatever.
"DTR," got it?
I only hope that the item
that Iori is frantically
working on is ready in time.
If they hadn't been destroyed by you people,
we would have more proper facilities.
If you were planning to
rebel against Ragyo,
I think you could have
at least considered the
option of joining forces with Nudist Beach.
When many people know a secret,
it's going to get out.
Even at Honnouji Academy,
the only people who were
aware of her real intentions
were we of the Elite Four,
the Sewing Club's Iori,
and her butler, Soroi.
Well, considering that I never
caught on that you guys knew
that I was undercover as a teacher,
I can't really brag.
But why isn't there any uproar among
the media and the populace
even though Covers are attacking
academies all over Japan?
They're already being
mentally influenced.
Clothing made by Ragyo Kiryuin's REVOCS
has reached the entire population.
The Life Fibers woven into them are
manipulating the minds of their wearers
and devouring any unnecessary
information from their brains.
"They have eyes but fail to see,
and ears but fail to hear," huh?
Well, they do use human psychogalvanism
as their energy source.
Honnouji Academy's students have
been building up a resistance
to Life Fiber manipulation
by wearing Goku Uniforms.
Pretend to be obedient to Ragyo,
and use her money to create
soldiers to defeat her...
That Satsuki Kiryuin girl
is a real piece of work.
What's even more impressive
is Mr. Soroi here,
who played dumb as he served
Satsuki as her butler.
I merely made tea.
As I do now.
However, I have not given up on making
more tea for Lady Satsuki.
You're right.
After all, even we
Elite Four survived.
(BACK-ALLEY) INFIRMARY
What about the other one?
Ryuko... Why won't you
wake up, Ryuko?
I'm so sorry that we can't
speak with you, Senketsu.
The rest of us can't tell
what you're saying.
Mrs. Mankanshoku...
But it's plain as day that you're alive,
that you're Ryuko's Sunday best,
and that you're worried
sick about her.
Mrs. Mankanshoku!
Now, now...
If I were 20 years younger,
I'd wear you in a heartbeat.
How is Ryuko today?
I can't tell one way
or the other.
But the wound from when her heart
was pulled out is already healed.
It's... how to put it?
Downright inhuman.
What did you say?!
Calm down!
You carried Ryuko's unconscious body to us.
Even if we can't talk to each other,
we understand how you feel.
Well, when a patient wants to sleep,
it's best to let them sleep.
After all, she had
a few nasty shocks.
I still can't believe that Ryuko's
mother was Ragyo Kiryuin...
I hadn't heard anything about it
from Dr. Matoi, either.
If I'd known sooner, maybe I could've
done something to soften the blow.
What's done is done.
Sometimes things work
out just by being alive.
Dad!
You're alive!
You're a Mankanshoku boy, all right!
See, sometimes things
do work out.
True.
I'm sorry.
I never found Sis.
Boy, you were searching
for Mankanshoku?
Yeah. I thought that if I
stayed in Honnou Town,
I might be able to find that
cloth bastard that swallowed Sis,
but before I knew it, it was all
I could do just to stay alive.
I'm proud of you
for trying, Mataro.
Don't grieve just yet! Mankanshoku
girls don't die that easy.
Listen, boy! I will rescue
your sister, no matter what!
Ira Gamagoori will devote
himself body and soul!
Ow! You're breaking
my collarbone!
Dad!
Oh, that's broken, all right. That'll be
10 million yen in damages, buddy.
Ten million?!
When I look at your family,
it gives me hope that the
human race can still survive.
HONNOUJI ACADEMY
You have certainly exceeded
all of my expectations.
In the sense of
your foolishness.
The students at the academies that
Honnouji Academy had conquered
have all been assimilated
by Covers.
If humans wear clothing for the
first 20 years of their lives,
their resistance to clothing
completely disappears.
Center your efforts around students
in their late teens
who haven't lost that resistance,
and defeat me.
But it was all for nothing.
The more your followers resist,
the more they nourish the
Covers as energy sources.
And before long, even your
little sister will return to me.
Little sister... Ryuko Matoi?
Yes. To think that she
was the baby
that I thought had died
all those years ago.
Soichiro had deceived me
about a great many things.
Matoi and I... are siblings...
He was a stupid man.
Soichiro faked his own death
and entrusted his revenge to you.
He changed his face and body
to become Isshin Matoi,
and not only did he raise the
baby whose death he faked,
he founded that silly
Nudist Beach organization
and gave a Kamui to Ryuko.
Dad... I...
I...
Ignorant of all this, you earnestly
believed everything he had said
and crafted your rebellion
plot against me...
It's so noble that it
brings tears to my eyes!
What garbage.
As if a woman whose very
tear glands are Life Fibers could cry.
Even if that were the case,
I am your mother.
You should graciously accept
any kind words I have to offer.
Kind? That doesn't suit you.
Are you sure?
I'd like to think that my sparing your
life was out of maternal kindness..
That is what is garbage.
You're letting me live because
I'm more valuable that way.
No more, no less.
Oh? How so?
Shinra-Koketsu.
You also know
about that, do you?
I put two and two together.
I see.
In that case, I suggest you get
the rage in your heart to seething!
The deeper your rage,
the more useful you are to me!
The work seems to be
progressing smoothly, I see.
I have to hand it to Satsuki!
The Sewing Club members
here are pretty capable!
So, it was worth the trouble
of Mind Stitching them, eh?
They're way better
than Covers!
Is Satsuki doing well?
Yes. She was dying to wear
this outfit soon.
Non, she won't wear it!
Satsuki's gonna get eaten by it.
By my masterpiece.
Anyway, it's Ryuko that
we need to worry about!
Yes, I know.
I've already taken steps.
Having two teenaged daughters
does keep one busy.
Both of them have grown into fine
young ladies, just like their mother!
La vie est drôle!
Yes, life is indeed amusing.
I can hardly wait to
show this to them.
This ultimate Kamui!
They're finally here.
We'll hold out as best
as we can.
As long as you're alive,
things will work out.
It's pretty unusual to hear
you sound so wishy-washy.
Maybe.
DTR, launching!
Brace for impact!
Use this.
Swords are more your thing.
Thank you.
Well, let's get going, Monkey.
Looks like I finished up
just in time.
It's ready?!
Theoretically.
Give it a test run.
There's an awful lot here, too.
It's like they're having
a winter clearance sale.
"A whole bunch" vs. five, huh?
I think I may cry.
Stand firm!
We're the mightiest five!
Do you seriously mean that?
We have no choice but
to go at this seriously.
Well, I'll give it my best.
That's the Mankanshoku
family's pet dog!
Could it be?!
Let's try this out right now!
Mankanshoku!
- She's out!
Cloth-form Covers are fed
energy from their parent body,
the Original Life Fiber,
via a linkage thread.
That's why we can cause them
to shut down if we sever that.
However, human-form Covers have
swallowed humans to use as energy sources,
so they can
operate autonomously!
If we can extract the
human it's swallowed,
the Cover will shut down
without its energy source!
Yes! We thin out their number...
And rescue our allies.
- A weapon combining offense and defense!
This is the Emergency Rescue
Suction Device!
EMERGENCY RESCUE SUCTION DEVICE
In Heaven's stead,
I smite clothing!
LIFE FIBER EXPLOSION
I'm saved!
Mankanshoku, are you all right?
Yep! Mako Mankanshoku has returned!
Wait, you saved me, Gamagoori?!
Yes. I gave your
little brother my word.
In any case, put this on.
Whoa, I'm in my birthday suit!
All right, quit your flirting. If
it works, go rescue more people.
Hang on, how do you put this thing on?
I am not flirting!
We'll talk later.
I'm stuck!
Get clear, Mankanshoku.
Kay!
Hang on, isn't this Osaka?
When did I get back here?
Hey!
Mako, you're okay!
Sis!
Dad! Mataro!
What are they doing?!
What is this, the
Covers Orchestra Club?
Are they calling me out?
What's this noise?
Oh, dear...
That's—
Ryuko!
Cut out all the sawing racket,
you bastards!
Get lost!
What the—
With just one blow?!
And she even extracted
the people inside!
Ryuko! You're awake!
Get away from me!
I'm done with you.
I'm never putting you on again.
Ryuko!
Just looking at you pisses me off!
Cause we're both the
same breed of monster!
That's right! I'm not human!
I'm a Life Fiber monster!
Damn you, Ragyo.
You let me live in order
to use me, is that it?
But that is a miscalculation
on your part.
As long as there is
breath left in me,
Satsuki Kiryuin has
a chance at victory!
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Hello, everyone! I have
sad news for you today!
SAD NEWS
This will be the final preview for the
television broadcast of this show!
From now on, please tune in
to the web previews!
WEB PREVIEW
Our battle is
only just beginning!
JUST BEGINNING
Next time on Kill la Kill,
"Far from the Madding Crowd."
EPISODE 20
FAR FROM THE MADDING CROWD