Wait! Wait for me!
Mukaido
Ow!
Why didn't you take care
of that last night?
Because...
Ow!
Well, we've never bought
or worn swimsuits before.
No kidding, it's so annoying.
They don't even have them at Saya Mart.
I thought I could get
one easily by asking Akari.
Well, Saya Mart doesn't have everything.
What the heck?
They have indoor slippers! And shorts!
Relying on Akari-san again?
Why not? She's there anyway.
Hikari, you really don't change.
What?
Are you saying I haven't progressed?
S-Sorry to keep you waiting!
Let's go!
O-Okay!
Well, whatever.
That works.
Episode Six: Beyond Tomoebi
Ew! You pervert! Lech!
What the hell, you peeping tom!
Hurry up and leave.
Girls should head to the changing room.
Huh?
Did you plan on changing with the guys?
Girls' Changing Room
I totally got fat. I'm sad.
Same here!
Egawa's totally going to call us fat.
So that's how they change.
Those towels are really nice.
You don't have swimming
class in the Village of the Sea?
N-No, we don't. This is our first time.
How lucky.
Be careful, Hiradaira-san.
Huh?
Man, our class sucks.
There's Hiradaira!
She's totally stacked!
Wow.
Hey!
Hikari, st—
Hiradaira-san really is big.
Let me touch them.
Huh?!
Aw, no fair!
Is that how girls become friends?
Girls are amazing.
We'll be timing you guys today!
What are you whining about?
You did it last year too.
All right, let's warm up!
Girls, out of the towels.
No!
Sexual harassment!
Too bad. My strike zone is rather high.
But it's so cold!
Well then, you're in luck.
It's warmer in the water.
All right, knees bends!
One, two, three, four...
Five, six, seven, eight...
Now from knee bends to bunny hops!
Warm up? What's the point?
What?!
No complaining!
Well, people from Shioshishio get
arm and leg cramps too, don't they?
Two, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight...
You're not going to do them, Hikari?
Like I need any preparation to breathe.
Make sure you state your form.
It can be the crawl
or even doggy paddle.
Tsumugu, what are you going to do?
Crawl.
Then I'll do that, too.
Let's swim together.
Sure.
Apparently Kihara-kun and Sakishima-kun
are going to swim together.
Who are you rooting for?
Wasn't Kihara-kun super fast last year?
Yeah.
But the kid from Shioshishio
might be faster.
Are you two going to root for Sakishima-kun?
Huh? I-I'm not sure...
Um... Kaname? And...
Hii-kun, right?
Yeah...
Yeah, you'd probably cheer
for the other Shishio kids.
Then I'm going to root for Shishio, too.
What the heck?
I'm totally rooting for Kihara-kun!
All right.
Ready...
You can do it!
Huh? Isn't Sakishima-kun a little slow?
Oh, it's probably because
he's not used to it.
To swimming?
Well, it's sort of weird swimming
in between the land and water...
and he's not used to doing the crawl.
Oh, is that it?
Damn it! This isn't easy to do!
If I didn't love them,
I wouldn't be so sad!
I don't want to think that it's
hopeless or useless to love someone.
Ow...
Hii-kun!
What's wrong, Sakishima?
It's nothing.
Hii-kun's hurt...
Shut up, Manaka.
Anyway, come up, both of you.
Let's go out, Hii-kun.
Oh, your nail came off...
Who's on duty today?
I-I am.
Oh, well that works out.
Please take him to the nurse's office.
Huh?
Chi... Can Hiradaira-san
come with us too?
Sensei.
I'll swim next.
Huh?
Nurse's Office
Excuse me...
What are we going to do?
The nurse isn't here.
Why are you asking me?
I know.
Disinfectant...
It's fine. I don't need any.
But the teacher said to...
Ow!
S-Sorry!
Damn it!
Sorry...
that I'm not very good at this.
Hii-kun, are you mad?
No, I'm not mad.
It stinks! I smell like chlorine...
Seriously...
Huh?
He's way too fast...
That's because we don't
do the crawl very often!
It can't be helped!
You'd definitely be faster if
we were in the ocean, Hii-kun!
That hurts.
Sorry...
When you compliment me, it's really...
B-But everyone knows that
you can be really amazing, too.
Chii-chan, too...
Why are you bringing up Chisaki?
Go back already. I'll do this myself.
How lame...
Oh.
Chii-chan!
I um...
You're late!
What were you guys doing
in the nurse's office?
Stop, you perv!
What?!
Nothing happened! Really!
Really sketchy!
What?!
You guys are so perverted!
Mukaido-san, go ahead and change.
Don't worry about cleaning.
O-Okay.
Let me see that.
You don't really seem like you're
from the Village of the Sea, Isaki-kun..
I don't think I seem to be from
the surface either, though.
Oh, that's not what I meant...
Sakishima-kun's pretty scary.
Really?
But he's not, is he?
How'd you know we were here?!
You kids are from Hama
elementary school, right?
We're not kids!
Are you done with school?
W-We thought we'd help out...
So we came here!
With what?
Um, with Ojo...
You guys were still making
the Ojoshi-sama, Isaki-kun?
Were you hoping to help out, too?
Yeah, I was!
U-Um...
Hope you guys will help out, too.
Y-You should totally
let us help you out.
What the heck?
Tsumugu-kun, are you going home?
Yeah. I've gotta help Gramps today.
I see...
Is your foot okay now?
Yeah...
I hauled the veneer.
I would have done it.
That'd be hard if you
can't stand very well.
See ya.
What the hell's with him?
Huh? What?
Never mind.
Oh, there he is.
Sakishima-kun!
What the heck, Sakishima?
Just getting here now...
There's nothing left for you to do!
Nothing!
You're the one who destroyed it.
Boo.
Everyone said they'd help
rebuild the broken Ojoshi-sama.
But you two are totally
after Hiradaira-san, aren't you?
Wh-What the hell are
you saying, you idiot!
W-W-We'll never finish at this rate!
Then you all are my minions.
Like hell! I'm a pro at Ofunehiki!
What do you mean, "pro"?
Well, we have to make offerings,
too, not just the Ojoshi-sama.
Offerings?
Like a dresser, a stand, and a table.
And we need the car.
And a TV and games.
Are they a gamer?
You idiot!
Ojoshi-sama nowadays is totally hip!
Hip, totally hip!
They're totally fitting in.
Fitting in too much.
Ow!
Hii-kun, you shouldn't walk
around on your own yet.
Right, Chii-chan?
Oh, I just remembered.
Sorry.
My mom asked me to stop
by the post office.
What time does the post office close?
4 o'clock.
Thanks, Miuna-chan.
See you guys later, I'm heading out.
Chii-chan, wait!
U-Um, I...
I asked you to forget, didn't I?
I-I'm sorry!
But, Chii-chan, I...
You promised, didn't you?!
Why do you do stuff like that?!
B-But if things stay as they are,
I didn't think it'd be right
for you, Chii-chan...
Why do you get to decide
if it's right or wrong?!
Sorry. I'm leaving.
Hii-kun!
Why...
I hate this!
Aw, too bad, boys.
Hiradaira-san went home.
Oh, shut up.
We just really wanted to help out.
It seems Manaka's not
coming back either.
So suspicious!
So it really is Manaka.
She's our center.
Mukaido?
You're not with Hiradaira?
Huh?
That's rare.
Because...
Because... Chii-chan...
said she didn't want to talk to me...
And then Hii-kun... Hii-kun...
Tsumugu, take her to the wharf.
What about you, Gramps?
I'm gonna go check the
trap on the east side.
Oh, okay.
Why don't you get on?
Gramps...
was saying that today was
a great day for Tomoebi.
What's "Tomoebi"?
Wh-When the weather is really nice
and a lot of saltflake snow falls...
When a cold current comes through,
because of the reflection or something,
it looks like there are three suns.
But I've never actually seen it.
Chii-chan and the others saw it once
when we were in elementary school...
They came to get me,
but I couldn't understand what
Chii-chan was saying at all and zoned out.
Stupid Manaka.
No...
I'm the stupid one...
Stupid!
I'm totally, totally
done with you, Manaka!
It's no good if we don't all see it!
Don't get so mad.
Why? Doesn't it matter to you, Hikari?
Stupid Manaka! Stupid! Stupid!
Chii-chan got really mad,
and that surprised me,
so I started crying.
She didn't talk to me for
a while after that...
Is it something to get that mad about?
She said we all had to see it together,
or it wouldn't mean anything.
I sort of get it.
Huh?
Wanting to share an experience
you enjoy with people you like.
But...
I might not be... someone that
Chii-chan likes anymore...
Why?
Because...
You know...
Huh?
Why don't you finish your sentences?
Finish?
You know, instead of "this
was like this or that,"
and trying to make things ambiguous...
You should always talk
without hesitating
like you did today when
you went to help Hikari.
That was...
That was just natural...
I see.
So that's the real you.
Huh?
You were really cool then, Mukaido.
Tsumugu-kun...
I'm sowwy!
Chii-chan, Chii-chan, Chii-chan!
H-Hurry!
Manaka?
What is it?
Tomoebi...
A long time ago, you went to
get me for this, didn't you?
Did I?
When I took too long and I was the only one
that didn't make it in time to see it...
You got really mad, Chii-chan.
So much that it surprised
me and I started crying.
That's enough.
No, I'm going to finish my thought.
I'm really sorry that I wasn't
able to see this with you that time.
You called me for that?
Because I promised! I said we would see
it together next time no matter what.
If only the Ojoshi-sama
wouldn't be completed...
Wh-Why?
Then it'd always be summer.
Then we can all still be
building the Ojoshi-sama.
We could be together forever.
Always playing together, and
going to school, and talking.
But...
I thought things didn't need to change,
and I don't want to change.
You don't want to change?
That might not be possible...
It might be hard.
But even then...
I don't want to change.
I always want to be together.
It's so pretty...
I wish that Hikari and
Kaname were here, too.
Yeah...
Seeing the same thing,
laughing the same way...
Staying friends forever, like this...
Manaka...
Whenever we realize it,
she always jumps ahead...
Way further than any of us.
Even though she's a scaredy cat...
Even though she's Manaka...
We want to do the Ofunehiki...
This is youth!
Break up with that man.
So careless...
We aren't fish, and they aren't pigs!
Episode Seven: The Ofunehiki Shakes