Nothing. It's nothing.
Touko!
What?
What's wrong, Onee-chan?
Touko-san?
Touko?
Are you okay?
I'll get them.
Don't go.
It's my fault.
No, I asked to watch your
mom play piano, too.
I couldn't hear anything.
But you felt something strong
enough to make you pass out.
So the experiment was a success?
Maybe.
But I might have put you in danger.
I'm fine. Besides—
Whenever I try to stay in one place,
I get other people mixed up in my problems.
Touko,
are you okay?
I want to stay here a little longer.
O-Onee-chan.
You're right. You should
stay put a little longer.
I want to make beads when I get home.
Yeah?
Final Episode:
"Shooting Star"
Are you sure we should
have left Onee-chan there?
I'm sure.
I wonder what happened to her, though.
I wonder.
She's getting to that age.
What? Are you saying I'm the only kid here?
You're almost an adult, too.
It'll happen before you know it.
One more piece?
Yes, please. I'll go home after that.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Um! Something really dramatic.
Okay, got it.
I'm not afraid.
It's not a future that's about to happen.
But Kakeru-kun...
Kakeru-kun will be gone.
Thanks for waiting.
I'm surprised you all
ordered Mandheling, though.
I'm nervous for some reason.
Yeah. I feel weird.
It's bitter.
I wish Touko-san were here, too.
Remember when the five of us used to
get together randomly all the time?
I'll try calling her.
What's up?
I want to meet her by chance.
That's a nice thing to say
for once, coming from you.
For once, yeah.
Sorry, I rocked the boat.
I'll tell you both, too.
You don't have to.
Everyone has secrets.
Well, small ones.
Maybe it's because we all
got together for coffee.
Morning.
Huh, where's Onee-chan?
Dunno.
Is she in the studio again so early?
Hina,
it looks like that girl came home in
a huge hurry to finish her homework.
Don't get in her way.
Fine.
Hey, Hina, it says there's going
to be a meteor shower today.
Brings back memories of that night.
Mari said she wanted to
watch the meteor showers,
so I decided to propose.
Dad, move your newspaper.
Kakeru,
have you decided?
You're a grown-up, now.
You can do whatever you like,
and I'll help out as much as I can.
It was pretty tough until middle school.
You're a kid until middle school,
a grown-up in high school.
That's where the line is for me, anyway.
And not for any real reason.
So you're still hiking, huh?
Yeah, though not so much hiking as
just walking around the foothills.
Remember you weren't so enthusiastic
about it when I first invited you?
Yeah, I eventually got into it.
It's been a while since we
stopped hiking together.
Can you keep up with me, Dad?
That's quite a statement.
Hey, dear, come help.
I'll get it.
Thanks.
Yes?
Takayama.
Let's take a short break.
Hina-chan tells me your
mom held a piano recital.
It wasn't really a recital.
Nothing so grand.
You should invite me next time, too.
Takayama, you're—
Yanagi.
Call me Yanagi.
Do you like classical music?
Actually, I listen to it quite a bit.
Your tea's always so good, Mom.
Thanks.
Say, Touko, have you ever
seen something in a haze when
you're suddenly in a bright light?
That'd happen to me sometimes
when I was young,
and I even thought it
might have been my future.
But it wasn't.
Everything that happened
afterwards was totally unexpected.
I wonder what it was, anyway.
Does that help you move on?
I don't know, but it's
all I can do right now.
You're right. You have
to do everything you can.
You have to fulfill your promise.
I'll remind you if you've forgotten.
I remember.
I've promised you only one thing.
Want to sit?
Tell me later.
I heard the gist of it from Sachi.
I see.
The incident at the beach where I was forced
to make that promise with you,
and this time, when Touko collapsed—
both are my fault.
How much of that am I supposed to believe?
It's hard to believe all of it.
I don't mind, but it's the truth.
Besides, it's true that I
needed Touko to be here.
But if I weren't here,
Touko wouldn't have gone through all this.
I hurt Touko.
I don't even have a clue what Touko saw.
It's not all good,
coming to an epiphany.
What?
Are you talking about Yukinari Imi?
Yeah, it's about Yuki.
He doesn't need to say anything
for me to know what he's thinking.
Yeah, that does sound a bit troublesome.
So,
Kakeru, are you going away?
I get that feeling.
I'm heading out.
Be careful.
Where's she going this
late in the afternoon?
I don't know, but she was pretty excited.
Where's Onee-chan off to so late?
My, my, everyone's worried about Onee-chan.
Kakeru-kun?
Touko.
Can I sit next to you?
Sure.
There's supposed to be
a meteor shower tonight.
It'll be great if we can watch it
again, the way we did the fireworks.
I hope we can watch the
fireworks together again.
Maybe not with this weather.
Fireworks in the winter.
In the winter?
In the fragment of the future,
we decided to watch the
fireworks in the winter.
So did you?
Yeah.
I went alone.
And the others?
They didn't notice me.
I see, so you watched them alone.
It was the first time I ever
watched the fireworks alone.
It might have been a sudden,
expected loneliness.
I wish I saw it, too.
You were watching, too.
With the others.
Did that me seem happy?
Yeah, very.
That's good.
I wonder what the fragments
of the future really were.
Maybe that name isn't appropriate anymore.
Mom said—
Never mind.
There you go with your "never mind" again.
But whenever you say that,
it was actually something important.
Am I that obvious?
Not really.
I see.
I guess.
Something important.
That day of the fireworks
festival, I saw you.
Was that a coincidence?
Not quite.
It wasn't a coincidence.
You saw it because you wanted to see it.
It wasn't the future.
It's something that hasn't happened,
but it's sure to happen.
What? Isn't that the same thing?
Did you mean it to be the same thing?
Maybe not.
Then it probably means something else.
I wanted to see you.
So I saw you?
And the sound and lights from the
fireworks might have made it happen.
It was really loud and bright, huh?
But why me?
I couldn't do anything for you,
even during the fireworks in the winter.
I just felt like I understood
how you feel a little better.
I couldn't do anything for you.
That's enough.
It is?
I'm glad I met you in this town.
I'm glad you came to this town.
Can't see the stars.
Oh, yeah,
maybe these will be stars.
You made all these?
Yup.
Wow.
Ready, and...
Shooting stars.
Yeah.
You see them, too?
This year's meteor shower
comes unusually late.
The peak of the Kappa Cygnids meteor
shower reaches its peak today;
unfortunately there is cloud
cover throughout much of Japan,
and it may not be visible—
I wanted to see it.
I know.
I can see it!
You can?
It...
was a beautiful proposal.
When we first met and when
we went on our first date,
you were so desperate.
You won me over.
Why is Jonathan the only Jonathan?
Are you okay, Yuki-kun?
It's still hot outside.
No,
I mean, the rest of them all
have philosophers' names.
What? Then what about Jonathan?
An adventurer, arguably?
You've been drawing them all
the time. You didn't know?
I didn't know.
Summer break's almost over.
I hope no matter what happens from now on,
my future self will solve it all for me!
You haven't changed at all.
Have you?
He's back on track lately.
Here he comes.
What?
Oh, come on.
It's over.
Hina.
Where's Hina?
Hina, explain, dammit!
Hina!
Adjust focus there.
I see it.
I like the name Touko.
Sure.
But I love the name Hiro, too.
Kazemichi
Should I help with something?
You're a customer for today.
Welcome.
You're late.
Isn't she going to be late?
Huh?
Summer break's over for
us youngins, unlike you.
There's something wrong.
You didn't sleep in.
Did something good happen?
That tragic glasses girl is coming to school.
Ack!
Good for you. I'll give
you a lift to celebrate.
The only way I'd be late today would
be because you gave me a ride.
Tee hee.
This is another benefit of running, I guess.
I'm leaving.
Watch for cars, you two.
Touko.