My head!
My head is splitting open!
Is this a new form of attack
by the dark alliance?
I told you not to get the regular size.
I award you the privilege to enjoy half.
Look here.
And so, our day alone together began.
Our one, precious day together.
Hey, why doesn't he have his dog with him?
Triangle...
of Missed Encounters
Mr. Saigo doesn't come
with his dog in Kagoshima.
How come? This is Mr. Saigo.
Everyone knows Mr. Saigo comes with a dog.
I don't see what all the fuss is about...
...but let's go look at another Mr. Saigo.
What?
Hey, there's a dog way
over there! There's a dog!
Okay, I'm taking the picture.
Say "cheese."
What are you doing here?!
I got separated from my group.
Where did you last see them?
At the souvenir shop.
Try calling them on your cell phone.
She's finally awake.
What a good idea!
Hello?
What is it? I'm on after-exam vacation.
Why are you calling so early?
Did you get my voice mail?
Do not go and use my voice mail system
without permission...
...fake magician.
Oh, be quiet! Never mind, and just delete it.
Delete what? Your existence on this Earth?
No, that page on the internet.
I'm sure you're the one who went and made it.
What are you blithering about?
Just because you're getting fat
is no reason to take it out on me.
Stop talking gibberish!
You can't talk your way out of this one!
Now listen. That page better be gone
by the time I get back...
...or I'll force a gallon
of milk down your throat!
That faker finally returns my call,
and she's full of nonsense.
I thought she was lonely
for the sound of my voice.
Or maybe she was going to ask me
how I was doing.
Internet page?
It really is amazing from here.
We're so close to it.
Resonating frequency perceived
at a radius of five kilometers.
Magical beings detected
near the vicinity of the crater.
It may be the red dragon!
I'm amazed how easily you
come up with those delusions.
Yuta, I fear that the dragon's body
has shattered through the crater.
It may have split into seven parts.
We need to collect them all.
Not!
Wanna cross over to the other side?
Cross? Can we get there?
Yes, I think we can take a boat across.
To there?
Schwartz Schneesturm!
Schneeglöckchen!
I'll go.
I doubt it's anything like
whatever you're imagining.
But we have plenty of time,
and it won't take long.
H-hey, you're Shichimiya.
Hero.
Hero, it's you! Hero!
Oh, I'm sorry! I never expected to
find him in a place like this.
You took the words out of my mouth.
Are you also on a school field trip?
You too, Hero?
You are indeed the Hero with whom
I once trusted my fate.
Wicked Lord Shingan. I'm sorry.
I apologize for grabbing on to him.
I was so startled.
It is far too late for that.
Magical devil girl, Sophia
Ring SP Saturn VII!
You are now treading upon the territory...
...within my Wicked Lord's dark barrier
in which I cannot be defeated.
Wanna make war?
Are you two alone?
Sorta.
You're alone together, are you?
Then I will let you go this time.
Sophia Ring has been tasked
with an angel-finding mission.
I'll wander off that way. Bye!
Hey!
Um, actually...
I hate to ask, but can I borrow 500 yen?
I'm revived!
How could you come so far
only to misplace your bag?
The angel may be running interference.
There are large shockwaves
coming from Area Zero to the south.
Can you make it back to your hotel?
Never fear! I have memorized every route!
Don't lie.
I can tell.
You don't have a clue
which way to go, do you?
I knew it. Is your cell
phone also in the bag?
Yeah.
Come on.
I'll be fine. The whole
world is linked together...
...so all roads lead to
where they need to lead!
I can make it back!
Still.
I will never go near any girl but you.
Take this and begone
to wherever you choose to go.
Don't solve it with money!
Damn.
Hey, Rikka?
I will soon locate it with
the power of Wicked Lord Shingan.
Come with me.
Now.
Rikka.
Come to think of it, I found
a piece of paper inside my bag.
Let's see.
THE WHISPERS OF
MORI SUMMER
Wh-what is this?
I'm busy.
Fake Mori Summer, how do you dare
use the name of Mori Summer?
What's that? You're the one
who made that page, aren't you?
I have never seen this page before!
You made it because you are the fake!
Me? I would never make such a thing,
and you know it.
Then who made it?
You're asking me?
Could it be the true one?
You walked through here?
I was tracking the angel's signature.
Do you remember taking
anything out of your bag?
I got on and off the train with my friends.
Bought some candy and we split up.
Then I walked through here eating it.
So you would have had the bag
when you were in the store.
A spirit tree.
It sure is big.
It must have incredible magical powers.
Agreed!
You two agree about the weirdest things.
Shichimiya, look.
There it is!
I knew it! Good for you.
Yeah! You're good, Wicked Lord Shingan!
That is to be expected with
the power of Wicked Lord Shingan.
The angel!
No, that's a monkey!
A dark follower!
I'm telling you, that's a monkey!
Leave it to me.
The power of the
Wicked Lord Shingan can handle this.
I can easily obliterate an ape being or two.
Don't do it. It'll bite you.
We need to drive it away.
But that could make it attack.
I'll go.
Hero.
Shichimiya, do you remember...
...the split-second formation - revised?
Split-second? Hero!
That's the plan.
Understood.
Rikka, you stand back.
What? Sure.
Split-second Formation - revised!
Yes! Hero!
Shichimiya!
Run for it!
Yuta.
Shichimiya!
You okay?
Yeah. We're rusty, but we pulled off
the split-second formation - revised!
Yeah, I haven't tried that since.
I didn't think you'd actually remember.
But of course!
I have decided to remain
unchanged for all eternity.
Along with the magical power
I cultivated with you back then...
...and the missions I was awarded
as a magical devil girl.
You're quite the weirdo yourself, Shichimiya.
I'm not weird. I won't change, that's all.
Here.
What's that? An arcade token?
I knew it.
Your memories have already
been taken from you.
What?
Yuta? Yuta?
Yuta...
Can you stand?
Yeah. Thanks, Hero.
Yuta.
Oh, Rikka.
Huh?
Yuta, you...
Yuta, you have forgotten your contract!
Rikka? Hey, Rikka!
Wicked Lord Shingan.
This Mr. Saigo doesn't have a dog either.
I told you as much.
Mr. Saigo doesn't have his dog with him
here in Kagoshima.
Oh, you!
Isn't that Takanashi?
Where did she go? I hope she didn't get lost.
She isn't answering her phone.
I'm sorry. This is 100% my fault.
I butted in on your private time.
No, I'm to blame.
I was so wrapped up in the bag hunt,
I didn't stop to consider her feelings.
So I want you to head back.
Prefectural Citizens
Exchange Centre
I can't do that.
It's okay, really. Go.
This is your school field trip.
Look, there's a bus stop right over there.
You can find your way back
if you get to a station.
But I...
Don't worry about it. Bye!
Oof.
You need to lose some weight.
Coming!
Hello, Togashi residence.
It's Shichimiya.
Is that you, Satone?
Sorry, but I need info quick, if you have it.
Bus Stop
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Okay, thanks.
So Shichimiya and Togashi were with you?
Yeah.
How did that happen?
That means they were goofing around
together and neglecting you, right?
No.
But you were all alone.
I was alone because I broke away.
What the heck is Togashi doing?
Received Mail
RECEIVED MAIL
IT'S SOPHIA
Map.
What?
Got a map?
Huh? You ran into Rikka?
Togashi, what are you doing?!
Surely you know that
paying attention to Shichimiya
while you're spending time alone
with Rikka will upset her.
You're right. Do you know where she went?
She glanced at a map and dashed off.
I see. It's okay, I'll take care of it. Bye.
Again? Kuzuha?
Incoming Call
Home
Hello?
Big Brother, what are you doing?!
Not again.
Sorry for making you come all this way.
Relax, I came alone.
No one will get in our way.
I see.
I will give you fair warning.
Wicked Lord Shingan is all powerful.
Even the most supreme level of light's
magical power cannot defeat him.
Quit while you still can.
Huh?
The manifestation of his physical speed
in this world is equally great.
To fully observe it...
...is impossible.
Then find out to your peril just how powerful
the magical devil girl really is!
Which would be fun...
...but I didn't ask you
to come here to make war.
I wanted you to hear me out.
I thought maybe I gave you
the wrong idea about Hero and me.
Yuta, not Hero.
Hero is what I've always called him...
...so he will always be a hero to me.
Grant me that much.
Granted.
Thanks. So anyway...
...you and Hero are bound by the
Lover's Contract, right, Wicked Lord Shingan?
What?
What's it to you?!
I felt like that once.
Once, I also felt my heart flutter
when I thought about him.
And I wanted to always be with him.
What? But...
But once that happened,
all sorts of things began to change.
There is no doubt.
That is definitely the
signature of a magical being.
Y-yeah.
H-Hero?
What is it, Sophia?
Another inter-dimensional quake
through the alternate world line?
No, it's nothing.
I could feel my powers gradually ebbing away.
There!
What's wrong?
Uh, yeah.
I started to think that maybe
I wasn't a magical devil girl after all.
I felt it gradually lose its meaning for me.
And then?
Yeah. Anyway...
I decided that I would stay
just the way I was, forever.
In accordance to the logic of
the world and its natural laws...
...I decided to stay as I was,
as a magical devil girl.
I am magical devil girl,
Sophia Ring SP Saturn VII!
I will forsake all else to live my life
to the fullest with my powers!
I'm saying that Hero's partner is you,
Wicked Lord Shingan.
That will not change.
Say, Wicked Lord Shingan?
Are you going to stay the
Wicked Lord Shingan forever?
Do you really think you can revive
the Dark Flame Dragon?
Why did you give him that token?
I originally owned it.
But I don't think Hero
even remembers that anymore.
Although it isn't my place to say it.
Well, I have an angel to track down,
so I'm gone! Zoom!
Sophia.
Rikka!
Yuta?
Where's Shichimiya?
It's just that she texted me.
She said I'd find you here.
Received Mail
from: Satone Shichimiya
sub: From Sophia
...is at the Waterfront Park.
All right, if you are a fake,
confess your duplicity immediately!
My question is based on the most
complex section of the Mabinogion.
If you are the true one, you can answer it.
It's here!
What is this?!
This is... death!
I'm sorry.
It is not an issue. Sophia
told me everything.
I am the one who should apologize.
I am mortified that I should ever
have questioned you, Dark Flame Master,
with whom I have walked in this guise
for so many months and years.
But the fact of the matter is that
we didn't end up spending much time together.
So I was thinking.
How do I say it?
Maybe it's about time,
or maybe it's a little late...
The timing just never seemed right.
What is it?
Yeah. It has to be today or it's meaningless.
Here.
It's your birthday today, isn't it?
How do you know that?!
I kept that information top secret...
...because there is such a
high probability of being hexed!
It was there for the whole world to see
in your former email address!
Huh?
Just take it.
Is this...?
Your old one is really worn out.
I thought this would make you happy.
It's amazing.
Schwartz Shield!
And this.
I made it at the place we visited
the other day.
It's a bonus.
This is true power of darkness.
Shall we?
Are you going to stay the
Wicked Lord Shingan forever?
Do you really think you can revive
the Dark Flame Dragon?
Yuta.
Do you believe the Dark Flame Dragon
is alive inside of you?
What?
Will you become Ghelzonianses someday?
Don't call me that.
Well, I can't say for sure about
the Dark Flame Dragon...
...but something could
be sleeping inside of me.
I always thought that the
obvious answer to that was no...
...but it's not so bad to believe
that something is in here.
Yuta.
That doesn't mean I can conjure up
the flames of darkness.
You're conjuring them now.
Uh, no. This is different.
Yuta.
I love you.
To Be
Continued