Episode 6   Umaru's Birthday
Umaru, it's midnight. Time for bed.
What? But I'm not tired at all.
You have to go to sleep at a
set time to maintain a rhythm.
Well, goodnight.
Goodnight.
So he fell asleep.
There's no way I can get to sleep yet
since I took a nap after school.
I wish Onii-chan would consider
my rhythm a little more.
Well, whatever.
Now I can enjoy some late-night relaxing time.
Huh?
There's no cola.
And my night's just beginning!
Jeez, Onii-chan.
I wish he would keep up my cola stock
without me having to remind him.
What to do...
Should I just settle for some other drink?
The drinks in the fridge are milk,
oolong tea, and mineral water.
No, it has to be cola,
or my relaxing time is ruined.
Guess I have no choice.
The convenience stores are
open late, so maybe I'll go.
I feel like a spy on some covert mission.
But man, it's really dark out.
It almost feels like a different world.
Wh-What if there's some
weirdo wandering around,
and I run into him?
If it comes down to it,
I'll just have to use the CQC
I learned from Metal Geo Risotto.
CQC = Close Quarters Combat
Oh, it was just a cat.
I totally let out a weird scream.
Wh-What was that scream just now?
Huh?
There's only one person working.
During the day...
Welcome!
...there are about two or three.
What's this guy looking at so seriously,
in the middle of the night?
Colonel, I have obtained the cola.
Returning to base.
Well done, UMR.
It's no time to be doing that!
I have to hurry home and drink my cola.
I always walk down this street
with Onii-chan and Ebina-chan,
but it seems completely different.
It's so quiet, it feels like
everyone's holding their breath.
I wonder what the people
who are awake are doing.
I wonder why the lights at night look blue.
Okay. Make sure Onii-chan doesn't wake up...
Slowly...
Welcome home.
Where were you, Umaru?
I, uh, just made a late-night
trip to the convenience store.
It's dangerous to be out at this hour!
What if some weirdo was wandering around?!
Guys like that don't exist.
Something scary happened last night,
so I didn't get much sleep.
I see...
So sleepy... I shouldn't have stayed up so late.
Poo.
No fair, Onii-chan!
It's Monday, but you've got the day off!
You had a whole summer vacation.
Rargh!
So Onii-san's off today?
Yeah. His summer vacation is a bit
off from ours, so he's off now.
There she goes.
Okay, I might as well clean...
I guess I cleaned yesterday.
Well...
I guess I'll at least vacuum for now.
Damn it. She must have
sneaked these last night.
Are you all right, Umaru-chan?
I did the grocery shopping yesterday, too...
Man, I'm bored.
It's been a while since I had so little to do.
Usually, Umaru would be
saying something to me.
Onii-chan, more potato chips, please.
Onii-chan, buy me some cola.
Onii-chan, look!
Onii-chan, let's play some games!
Onii-chan, dinner's cold!
Onii-chan, go buy me Jumpu!
Onii-chan, I wanna have sushi tomorrow!
This isn't good.
I can't just zone out on
my well-earned time off.
That'd just make me some
old, retired salaryman.
I've gotta do something.
Huh? What did I do on my days
off before Umaru arrived?
I bet Onii-chan's lazing around and having
a great time at home without me.
Grrrr!
I wonder what those guys are up to.
Bomber
Stochastic nao.
Banchou
Stochastic
Alex
[Summary of this season's anime] The safe choice is "Middle Cube."
The girls' soccer theme is timely, and you can see how much the production staff loves nuts...Read the rest
Tenraku Marketplace
Deliver some delicious chashu pork!
Chashu pork, huh...
Now, just simmer on low heat for six hours...
Onii-chan!
Oh, you're alive.
Huh? Did school let out in the morning today?
What are you talking about? It's 5 PM.
It's rare for you to fall
asleep unguarded, Onii-chan.
Didn't you have anything to do?
Th-That's not true. I made some chashu pork.
Taking a nap while you let chashu
pork cook is pretty rockin'.
Oh, yeah!
The chashu pork!
The burner turned itself off automatically.
Welcome
Spreading Bonds
Do you have enough friends?
Let's follow 5 other people!!
Onii-chan, it appeared!
Wh-What?!
Look, look!
It's a rare titan that only has
a 5% chance of appearing!
See? Shincolle!
This was a feat of the gods!
Its rare level is max!
Taiha
I don't really get it, but it's a game thing, huh?
Sorry. Can this wait?
I'm making documents for my meeting tomorrow.
Huh? Why? Come on! Take a good look at it!
No, I only have until tomorrow.
Shincolle is more important than meetings!
My meeting is more important than Shincolle!
From the Next Day...
Onii-chan, look! I got all the characters.
Potato
Chips
Onii-chan, this is a new flavor!
Onii-chan, look at this!
Onii-chan, look!
Onii-chan!
Umaru, I think it's time to divide the room.
The room?
Yeah. This apartment is only one room, right?
So I was thinking about dividing
our spaces with a curtain.
Umaru Zone
Where did this come from?
It's weird for siblings to be
living in a one-room apartment.
You need your private space, don't you?
Huh? I'm pretty indifferent...
Wait a sec.
If I get my own room,
maybe I'll be able to laze around all
I want without Onii-chan yelling at me.
Yeah, sounds good.
Okay, then.
All right. If I have my own room,
my work efficiency will go up.
And if that happens, I'll have time for
housework and time to spend with Umaru.
All right. Let's go buy that curtain.
I want one with a cute design!
There. All done.
Yay!
Woohoo! My own room!
I won't get yelled at for lazing around!
Umaru, is something wrong?
No, everything's fine.
Don't let it bother you. Just work.
Onii-chan, look! Look!
Umaru.
What is it?
Well, um...
I just put up the curtain, but it's kinda
cramped. We can leave it open.
Yeah, let's do that.
The Next Day
Hey, Onii-chan. I want the new
item, so I need some money.
I'm working right now. Hold on for a bit.
2 Hours Before
Yay! A new record!
It's great that we were able to get a Famicom.
The graphics have a certain charm, Master Komaru.
Kirie-chan.
I brought you guys some drinks.
I think she's gotten a lot more used to me,
but she still seems to tense
up when I talk to her.
Kirie-chan, let's play The Game of Life next.
Um, I'm...
quite content with just watching.
Aw, come on!
Uma... Komaru. Don't be so pushy.
Okay...
I'll play.
Huh?
The Game of Life
Okay, whoever finishes
with the most money wins.
I'm playing, too?
With games like this, the more the merrier.
Now, let's start!
I'm gonna go first!
Hamster Sensei
You become a manga artist and create a hit.
Plus 10 million.
Ten million out of nowhere?!
That's amazing, Master!
Manga artists are self-employed,
so if they release a hit,
they can aim to be a billionaire.
I see...
There you go, spouting stuff you
probably found on Wiki again...
Even if this is just a game,
I have to live a proper life.
There!
A chance to change your career!
You have a chance to change careers
from your current "salaryman" position.
Accept? Decline?
Changing careers already?
Changing careers...
He's really agonizing over this.
It must hit really close to home.
Komaru's Life
Hamster Sensei
Hamster
Ninja
Maiden
Komaru creates one hit after another.
Plus 50 million.
However, she becomes unable
to deal with the deadlines.
Minus 30 million.
She buys her own island
and creates her own kingdom.
She changes her career to a king.
Mostly, she lazes around.
Promoted to the Himono King.
Taihei's Life
He works earnestly as a salaryman.
Plus five million.
He gets his chef's license
and becomes an apprentice.
He changes careers to a cook.
A restaurant he opened
independently is booming.
Plus 10 million.
He has three children.
Promoted to Cooking Papa.
Kirie's Life
She trains daily as a professional swimmer.
Plus one million.
Finally, she wins the nationals.
Plus 10 million.
She slips on a banana peel and gets hurt.
She retires from her swimming career.
Under Construction
10m Ahead
She works too hard and catches a cold.
Health minus 100.
The rare character,
the God of Poverty, appears.
Her life savings is down to zero.
Talk about bad luck.
Taihei closes his own restaurant.
Huh? Onii-chan, if you
close your restaurant,
your life savings will go down to zero.
Well, my kids grew up, so I thought
it was about time to close up shop.
Come on, this game is to see who
ends up with the most money.
Then I guess I'm tied with Kirie-chan.
Yeah.
Kirie-chan.
You've still got a long road
ahead, so life's just begun.
M-Master...
Now, let's keep on going.
Th... Th-Th...
Thank—
I-I'm sorry, Master!
The delicate Famicom is...
Wh-Wh-Wh-What do I do?!
Umaru.
Make sure you treat her well at school, too.
Yeah.
Chef Exam
A cook, huh...
Seems he's
interested
in it now
This usually fixes it
September 26th.
Today is my birthday.
Wish List
Wee
Cute plushies
Fun decorations
DraCue 13
All volumes of Damking
Jun Piece's Chomper
figmo Migu
PPS controller
Let's see... What should I have him buy?
This is hard...
I wonder if he'd just buy all of them for me.
Today is my day!
I'll have to get Onii-chan to
celebrate with me all night.
You're up early.
Good morning!
Huh?
Hey, Onii-chan. You're off again
even though it's a weekday, right?
Don't make it sound like I don't work at all.
I've still got some time that I didn't
get to take off in the summer.
Oh, Onii-chan.
Acting like it's just another day
when it's my birthday today...
Maybe his plan is to tease me.
You know what today is, don't you?
Onii-chan!
Huh?
He hasn't realized it?
What, what?
I have to leave for school now...
I-I'll be off, then.
Okay. Be careful on your way home.
9/26 (Sat)
Today is September 26th.
Nope, I wasn't mistaken.
Umaru-chan, happy birthday!
Aw, you guys remembered.
Of course!
Thank you!
Kirie-chan?
For me?
Thank you, Kirie-chan.
What the heck is that?
Umaru-chan's so nice...
Everyone else remembered.
Why did Onii-chan forget?
Okay. Be careful on your way home.
Umaru-san.
Shubaan
We're usually rivals, but on
birthdays, we shall call a truce...
Is that how it works?
Anyway, I congratulate you on your birthday.
I believe these lines will suffice.
Onii-chan...
Onii-chan!
I'm home!
W-Welcome home...
Whatcha doin'?
Huh? Um, uh...
Were you, like, pretending
you didn't know all morning?
And have you been, like,
preparing for a couple days now?
And, like, I totally caught you?
Wha... N-No...
And you, like, weren't expecting
me to come home so early?
And you're like, what the heck?
And you're, like, totally
embarrassed that I found you?
All right! Yes, damn it!
Next Time
Episode 7 Umaru's Onii-chan
UMR, your next mission will be the preview.
Why are you doing the preview, Colonel?
Even I wasn't expecting this.
Well, I don't appear again after this, so...
How sad...
I wish you luck in your next episode, UMR!
Sir, yes, sir!