Something Given (Part 1)
December.
When Christmas was approaching,
I got another call
from my foster sister, Kyouko.
You forgot something? A watch?
Here it is.
Thank goodness.
Gotou just gave it to me.
He gets mad if I don't wear it.
Hey, I might have gotten a cold.
And it's your fault!
I told you to wait
at the Mec in front of the station.
Forget it, that place is way too noisy.
Why couldn't I have gone to your place?
Why?
How about I guess
what you were just thinking? Rei...
I'm just joking. You look so scary.
Hey, what are you doing for New Year's?
You're coming home, right?
No. I have a lot of matches coming up,
so I need to focus on practicing.
Matches?
Your last match of the year is the rank-deciding
one against Mr. Yasui on the 24th, right?
Oh, that's right.
Speaking of Mr. Yasui,
it seems he's finally getting divorced.
He's usually a meek, modest guy. But when he
loses, he drinks, gets crazy, and gambles.
I'm surprised his wife put up with it
for this long.
I feel sorry for his daughter the most.
She must've been scared.
I mean, living under the same roof with
a father who breaks bad every time he loses.
Ah, I hate this.
But I hear the daughter had one wish.
She said,
"I want to be with Papa until Christmas."
I can't stand it.
This...
It brings tears to your eyes. Don't you think?
The way she speaks,
her words sticking to me like glue...
Hey, Rei, are you listening?
But more than anything...
Hey.
...her words that drip with poison...
Sheesh.
Your scarf will blow away.
You should wrap it properly.
...I hate myself for wanting to hear it.
Children have it rough.
After all, they can't choose their parents.
Oh. But come to think of it,
it was different for you.
You chose your own parents.
You chose somebody else's father.
Hey, Dad, can we open them now?
Oh, sure.
Hey, what is this giant teddy bear?!
Pow
Take that!
Jeez, Dad! I'm in middle school now!
A Game Bomb!
For a child of this family...
...or anyone striving
to be a professional shogi player...
...the value of those beautiful pieces...
...their meaning...
...the father's feelings...
...were unmistakable.
What do you think, Rei?
Should I have gotten you a toy, too?
Oh, no. Thank you.
I'm happy with these.
It was unmistakable.
How my foster brother and sister
were very hurt then...
Hey, it's sad, don't you think?
A papa who comes home after winning,
or a papa who comes home after losing.
Well then...
which would be more fitting
as a final Christmas memory?
Aside from P.E. and music, not bad, I guess.
Your grades for math and physics
are awesome.
Report Card
That being said, here.
You need to be in Sendagaya by 9:30, right?
You should hurry.
Morning
Anyway, you're a busy guy, aren't you?
You even have matches
up until Closing Ceremonies.
You barely met
the required attendance days this time,
but you may be in trouble if your matches
increase third term. So be careful.
Ehhh?!
Are you telling me to lose?
But my living is on the line.
1-B Christmas Party
By the way, after the Closing Ceremony today,
the kids in the class
are having a Christmas party, apparently.
Did you know about it?
No, of course I didn't know about it.
Please don't tell me.
Well, I guess there's only one thing to do.
After your match is over,
why don't you come back here?
Dammit,
they didn't
invite me
either.
Why?!
Just us crummy guys,
eating cake while playing shogi...
Answer: You're a teacher.
No one.
I turn around and he's gone!
Eeeeek!
Wait a second!
This just makes me a mean old teacher!
Listen until I'm done talking!
Please, Kiriyama?!
When did it start?
When did Christmas become painful for me?
A certain thought crossed my mind.
"It's like a report card."
From that year.
In that year, how much love did I receive
from friends, family and my parents?
How did they express that love for me?
Yasui 6th-Dan...
The doors are closing. Please be careful.
The daughter said, "I want to be
with Papa until Christmas."
"Until Christmas..."
A papa who comes home after winning,
or a papa who comes home after losing.
Which would be more fitting
as a final Christmas memory?
Well, Rei?
Something Given (Part 1)
Shogi Hall
It's time.
Let's have a good game.
I lost.
Something Given (Part 2)
I get it.
You want to say I gave up
in the middle of the game, don't you?
The match with Mr. Yasui ended all too soon
that late afternoon.
After 8-f-Pawn, I could've surprised you,
taking your knight at 9-e...
Ah, yes, yes.
Could've gone that way.
If I'd noticed, I would've done that.
But I didn't notice, so it can't be helped, right?
You might've seen it, but I didn't see it,
so what good is it?
Mr. Yasui continued muttering,
as if he was talking to himself.
I was unsettled by the faint smell
of alcohol on his breath as he sighed.
The match began slowly and quietly
with a Yagura Opening.
"Carefully... Carefully..."
From the way he played,
I could almost hear him telling that to himself.
"Don't make a mistake. Don't make a mistake."
Shogi Hall
However...
...after the lunch break,
Mr. Yasui made a mistake.
After a short pause, he noticed it, too.
But afterwards, if he attacked the king
from 8-f-Pawn, who knows?
If he then pulled his knight back and
held out, which side would victory tilt towards?
But then I could see Mr. Yasui's silhouette
lose strength and weaken.
Why?
It's not like...
It's not like the possibilities
have all disappeared.
I hear the daughter had one wish.
Wait a second! Why?
Why?!
That easily?
You can't let go!
Your focus, your awareness...
"I want to be with Papa...
Don't give up such precious things so easily!
...until Christmas."
Please...
I'm begging you!
Don't let go!
Shogi Hall
I lost.
I think that's enough for a post-match review.
I've had enough for today.
Mr. Yasui! Mr. Yasui!
He's gone...
Which way did he go?
There he is!
Where's he going?
The station isn't that way.
Mr. Yasui!
Um... Here.
That ain't mine.
Never seen it.
Mr. Yasui!
All right! Shut up, already!
And this was our last Christmas...
Is everything my fault?
Then what should I have done?
Go to hell!
It's your own fault for being weak!
You lost because you were weak!
Practice! I can tell when you don't!
If you say "I know, but I can't," then just quit!
Don't come!
For me, everything's on the line!
Because I don't have anything else!
Nothing but shogi!
Don't drink booze to escape!
I have no use for weak players!
If you're going to run away...
If you can run away...
...then why...
I said I had no reason to fight,
but the truth is,
I know that a beast lives within me.
It's a rampaging beast that would bite off
everything in sight to survive.
When the battle begins, no matter what,
its hand reaches out
towards the path of survival.
Even if it means misery for others.
No matter what kind of world awaits...
Something Given (Part 2)
Next Episode Preview
Episode 11
Yay! Rei's house!
Here, Rei.
Stretch out your neck, please.
Rei? Rei, is that you?
Are you okay?
I'm an idiot.
That's not true.
I wanted you to come over.
You're the one who helped me.
Don't miss the next episode of
"March Comes in Like a Lion".
I hope everyone watches
our great performances!
M-Mr. Hayashida...