It's something very precious to me.
Serinuma-san, I like you.
Sorry, what did you just say?
I couldn't really hear you.
Serinuma-san, I have feelings for—
What?
Senpai, what were you planning
on telling her just now?
Huh?
Don't tell me...
I was going to tell her that I like her.
What?!
Weren't you saying you weren't sure
if your feelings were romantic or not
just a little while ago?
Yup, so I figured it out just a second ago.
A second ago?!
Right. Thanks to my brother,
I finally realized how I felt.
I'm in love with Serinuma-san.
Ni
Iga
Nana
Shi
S-Straight to the point!
Blush
So I have to tell her how I feel
as soon as I possibly can.
G-Get real! We won't let you!
Huh? Why not?
No one gets a head start!
He means we all feel the same as you.
I like her too, and so does everyone here.
Is that right?
Then you should all tell
her how you feel, too.
Totally Logical
S-Straight to the point!
You don't need to tell us! We've already—
Wait.
As far as I know, I don't think any of us
have actually told her how we feel.
Huh? That's not true.
Yeah. That's not right at all!
Nope.
No—
Ni
Iga
Shi
Nana
It's not?
It's Not?
Well, you're all free to do as you like,
but I'm going to tell her how I feel.
W-We were so preoccupied by
Mutsumi's older brother that we...
Yeah. We pushed the person into action
that should never be pushed into action.
We have to stop him somehow!
Kiss Him, Not Me
Senpai!
I have a favor to ask.
What's the matter?
There's an event at the end of the month
and my draft is a bit behind schedule.
Can you please come over and be my
assistant for a while, starting today?
The end of the month?
You mean Comic Village, right?
Okay, I'll help in whatever way I can!
Really? Thank you so much!
Then I'd better tell Mutsumi-senpai
I'm not coming to club—
Leave it to me!
I have to talk to him anyway,
so I'll tell him while I'm at it!
Shinomiya-kun?
I wasn't called "carrier pigeon"
in elementary school for nothing.
Blunt
I'll be sure to let him know!
I-Is that right? Thanks, then.
Appreciate it, Coocoo-kun!
Don't call me weird names!
Coo, coo
Well, let's go!
Let's!
Huh? You too, Igarashi-kun?
What do you want? No one invited you.
As if I'd leave the two of you alone.
Just when I thought I had my chance.
Are you serious?
All right.
Igarashi-senpai, can you
please scan and clean this?
Yeah.
Sorry, I'm going to borrow the restroom.
Sure.
Hello.
Nana, situation update.
I've just arranged things with
Serinuma's older brother.
He said he'll stop Senpai from
making any contact with her.
Really? I'm surprised you
were able to persuade him.
I told him Mutsumi-senpai
was going a bit wild
and Serinuma might be in danger.
You never know what a guy like him could do!
A Bit Traumatized
And there you have it. Mission complete!
Roger that.
Good. That's one thing down.
Nishina, what about you?
Everything's going well here, too!
I've blocked Mutsumi-senpai's
number on her phone!
All right, let's get cracking!
We won't let Mutsumi-senpai
tell her anything!
No matter how dirty we have to play!
This is the History Club.
We're Always Looking For New Members!
The number you are trying to
reach is currently unavailable.
No way! Ono no Imoko was a guy?!
Huh? Are you for real?
Shinomiya-kun, why are you here?
I'm interested in Japanese history! Really!
H-Huh?
Soga no Umako was a guy, too?!
Huh?!
Serinuma-san
The number you are trying to
reach is currently unavailable.
A Few Days Later
So? How are things going?
I've been having her over every
day for the past few days.
For now, she doesn't appear
to suspect anything.
I see.
Yesterday, I got word from Takuro-san.
Apparently, a telegram was delivered!
This isn't good!
Eep!
A telegram?!
And all it said was, "I like you."
W-Well, we've gotten this far!
It's going well.
Hopefully he'll eventually give up.
Where the heck is he going?
I won't let you make it to Serinuma-senpai!
Oh, just the bathroom?
He's taking a while.
Don't tell me—
He actually escaped out the window?!
He got me! And this is the second floor!
What is it, Shino?
I'm sorry, he got me!
I lost track of him!
Wha—
Where could he have gone?!
Serinuma Kae-san from Class 2-A.
This is Mutsumi Asuma.
I need to talk to you.
Please meet me on
the roof today after school.
Mutsumi-senpai?
H-He's done it!
He's just like his brother!
Nothing less from siblings.
Damn!
This concludes this broadcast.
Senpai!
How could you be so bold?
We won't let you make a move!
Tell me,
why are you trying so hard to stop me?
I think you're all free to
tell her how you feel.
Didn't I say so?
So I won't stop you.
Those who want to tell her
can come to the roof.
I'll see you after school.
And so, in this case,
you use the formula to...
What Mutsumi-san said makes sense.
It's not like she'll just return my
feelings if I get in someone else's way.
I have to tell her, or nothing will happen.
But, if I do tell her,
will she still smile the
same way she does now?
Squeeze
If her heart does belong to one person,
what happens if I'm not that person?
Still, the thing I'm hoping for most
is that I'm...
...the only one for her.
Senpai?
Serinuma-san, thanks for coming.
U-Um, what did you want to talk about?
Or more like, why is everyone
here? What's going on?
I wanted you to come so I could
tell you how I feel about you,
but it looks like I'm not alone.
Right?
Serinuma-san.
I like you.
I-I like you.
I like you so much.
Serinuma-san, I really do like you.
Will you go out with me?
Kiss Him, Not Me
Nakano
Oh gosh, Mikkun, you're such a meanie!
Just kidding, I'm totally fine with it!
Sorry, someone's at the door.
Oh, you don't need to
hang up, just hold on.
I'm sure this will just take a—
A-chan!
They all asked you out?!
Yeah.
They were all very earnest, and
want me to go out with them.
Th-That's amazing. So, what
happened? What did you say?
Well, you see...
We don't need an answer right away.
We just wanted you to know how we felt.
I'm sure this came as a shock to you. Sorry.
Huh? Um...
We just wanted to make sure you knew.
This isn't a lie or a joke.
This is how we really feel.
Oh, come on. If they don't need
an answer, what's the rush?
No, they all looked very serious.
That's why I've got to
take this seriously, too.
Which means accepting their feelings,
thinking about them, and
then giving them an answer.
Or, that's what I thought.
Kae-chan...
She's finally grown up!
So, what are you gonna do?
Huh?
Who are you going to choose? What do
you think of each of them, in summary?
Um...
Igarashi?
5x7!
Nanashima?
Mutsumi-senpai?
He's got that soothing presence
that makes him the perfect top!
Shinomiya-kun?
He's such a klutz, and a definite bottom.
But depending on his development,
I think he could switch to a top!
And Nishina-san?
Yokoshima-sensei! A god!
Oh, but, Akane-chan is definitely a bottom!
Enough with the fujoshi talk!
Why do you seem like you haven't
made any progress at all?!
I'm s-sorry!
B-But, honestly, I've never looked
at them in any other way.
I definitely feel for them.
That goes beyond cruel.
What should I do? What can I do
to get to know them all better?
Hmm, if it were an otome game, you
could just follow their character routes.
That's it!
Huh?!
Bam
And so, for each day of the
holiday next week, I'd like to
go on a date with each one of you!
What?
Huh?
And then, at the end of the holidays,
I'd like to give my answers to the offers
you each graciously made me the other day.
I thank you for your patience!
Bye!
Huh? Wai—
What's the meaning of this?
The offers we made the other day? She
means when we asked her out, right?
And if she gives us an answer
after the dates, then...
The dates will decide who wins the fight.
Day 1
Igarashi Yusuke
Wanna go to the aquarium?
Go
Don't go
Wow! Amazing!
It's so pretty! Look, a shark! Isn't it big?
Oh, that fish looks so funny!
Oh, you mean the Asian sheepshead wrasse?
They're females when they're young,
but mature into males as they age.
Amazing. I'm surprised you know all that.
But of course.
Actually, I just Googled it the other day.
Oh, is that it?
Ask me anything!
Can you really answer anything?
All right then, how about that—
Are you all right?
Thank you.
Igarashi-kun is very
engaging in conversation.
He's very considerate and kind.
He's really easy to get along with.
And...
Let's ride the Ferris wheel.
Look at all the lights! It's so beautiful.
Yeah, you really are beautiful.
And, at times, he says things
that are really embarrassing.
Day 2
Nanashima Nozomu
Let's go to Usami Land!
Go
Don't go
Th-This is awkward. I gotta
say something! Something!
Nanashima-kun?
Thank you very much. Have fun!
Here.
Gotta have all the fun you can
when you come to a place like this!
Let's have a blast!
So Cute!
Hehe
Giggle
Y-You're right!
First, we gotta hit the Usami Coaster!
Nanashima-kun was a little
constrained at first,
but he loosened up, and was his usual self.
He really knows how to have a good time.
And I had so much fun!
You're not Mommy!
Wah!
Wh-What do I do?
What's the matter? Where're
your mommy and daddy?
Do you want some popcorn?
She won't stop crying!
Nanashima-kun, what kind of face is that?!
Stop! You're making my tummy hurt!
Eri!
Mommy!
Ecchan! I looked everywhere for you!
What a relief.
Sorry about this. And thank you so much.
Bye bye!
Don't get lost again.
Oh, for some reason, I'm feeling a bit...
You're amazing, Nanashima-kun.
Huh?
I can't believe you made her
laugh when she was crying so much.
Oh. Well, you know I have a little sister.
Oh, you mean Kirari-chan?
Yup. And she's adored my arsenal
of funny faces since she was tiny.
I wonder if this is what you call gap moe?
Day 3
Shinomiya Hayato
Do you know about the alpaca park?
Yeah! I wanna go!
What's that? Not interested.
They're so fluffy. What a view!
Hey. I've got food for you.
Oh, no.
I spilled it.
Munch
Your hair! Shinomiya-kun,
it's eating your hair!
S-Stop it!
Shinomiya-kun is the kind of
guy you can't leave alone.
Did I lose any hair?
You're fine, you're fine!
Please don't laugh at me.
Sorry.
If I had a little brother,
I think it'd feel just like this.
You two over there! Run!
It's a wild alpaca!
Look out, Senpai!
Shinomiya-kun! Are you okay?!
It felt so soft!
I-I see.
I'm sorry. This one
charges any couple he sees.
We're completely fine.
Or more like, a couple?
But sometimes, you can
rely on him just a little.
Day 4
Nishina Shima
Shall we go somewhere good to eat?
Go
Don't go
Welcome
Okinawa
This is our restaurant. I've reserved
the whole place, so feel free to relax.
Borrowed her dress
from Shima-chan.
R-Right.
Shima-chan is a celebrity. Every
single thing she does is elegant.
Sometimes it feels like we
live in two separate worlds.
When I see such beautiful scenery...
It makes me want to put out an
Akane x Lord honeymoon book!
I want to see that! So bad! So bad!
They'd start at the venue stage,
and then, they wouldn't be able
to leave their room for a whole day!
You know it!
Akane-chan would try to leave,
and the lord wouldn't let him!
The lord trying to use
his last chance with him!
And Akane-chan would be all about
fulfilling his lord's wishes!
Squeal Squeal
And Akane wouldn't be aware of the fact
that this would be their last time alone!
Oh, gosh! A tragedy! That really gets to me!
We're soulmates, after all.
She's so fun to be around!
Day 5
Mutsumi Asuma
Shall we take an old map and go exploring?
Go
Don't go
This is where the old Edo Five Routes start.
Yeah? So it doesn't start
at the Imperial Palace.
Is this turn right here?
It hasn't changed at all from the Edo era!
Wow. I can't believe there's such
a forested area within the city!
Well, since we're here, shall we pay a visit?
Senpai, as always, talks in
a gentle voice, very softly.
He's so kind and soothing.
I like you.
Was he really serious about that?
Serinuma-san, what did you wish for?
I wished for the lord and Akane-chan
to live happily ever after!
Babble Babble
Also, for Shion to come back to life,
and for Captain Levi to show his soft side,
and for Miyuki-senpai to notice.
What about you, Senpai?
I wished that you and I
could be together forever.
You know, I probably always liked you.
But, I didn't know there could
be a special kind of like.
Serinuma-san, you're the one
who taught me this feeling.
Thank you.
A-chan
Today
So? Have you made up your mind?
What should I do?
Now I'm even more confused.
They're all good people,
and have their own charms.
They're all kind, and
I think I like them all.
But, there's something just not there.
What's missing is probably...
that special feeling?
Oh, god! Who can figure this out?!
We reached out to the sky...
For me,
that special feeling is...
And gave one devoted prayer.
The one I have special feelings for is...
Slash through the darkness.
No matter who she chooses...
There are no regrets, right?
Of course.
I've found the person that's special to me.
Wh-Who is it?
It's...
Shion from Mirage Saga.
They're going to air another
season of Mirage Saga!
Not to mention!
There was a silhouette
that had to be Shion!
Who else could it be?! It has
to be him! He's coming back to life!
The staff knows what we all love!
I spent all night searching online, and
I was looking through the animators' tweets,
but it looks like production is already going
and they've already started the storyboards.
I hope the staff is the same!
Especially the character
designer, Kakinuma-san!
And of course, the second season will
cover the foreshadowing with Panasharu,
and the dagger given to Terra.
There are too many key things!
Oh, but there're new characters, too!
Like, shota twins? Maybe
they're enemies? That's so hot!
What if a new pairing is born?
No, it's gotta be Terra x Shion!
I've been waiting for so long! The day
they'll be together is finally here!
Mu
Ni
Shi
Nana
Iga
Oh, look at the time!
Anime Ito has an early merch exhibit
today and is taking reservations!
Gotta move! I gotta get going!
So, that's how it is! Sorry! Later!
Wait!
Wh-What just happened?
Wh-What about your answer?!
Serinuma-senpai, wait!
Senpai, is that information legit?!
Serinuma-san looks like she's
having a lot of fun! That's great!
No, it isn't!
The prince should be with the princess.
Who was the one who decided that?
A prince should be with a prince.
Can't it be like that?
It should be like that.
This is the best place
for the princess to be.
The princess had a life
full of joy thereafter.
And they all lived happily ever after.