Well, Kosaki?
What do you think of
our new fall offerings?
You might want to maximize
the sweetness of the chestnuts more.
But really, what's the rush?
Summer's only just started, you know.
If we don't get a jump on it now,
we won't be done in time.
Really, I just can't figure it out.
Why is it that you can't cook when
you have the best taste buds of us all, Sister?
I wish I knew that myself.
Okay, I'm off to let Dad
know what you think.
Oh, by the way, Sister...
I know I'm the one who
asked you to be our taster,
but don't you think you've been
putting on some pounds lately?
Better watch out, or you're
gonna get chubby in no time!
I-I'm fine! I am watching my weight!
Easy enough for me to say, but
I do eat a lot of sweets these days.
And it's been a while since
I last got on that scale.
I'm not getting much exercise, either,
so I'd better take
better care of my body.
No way... No way!
How did this happen after only
a few days of not weighing myself?!
I admit I have a pretty good
idea what the cause is,
but how could I have gained
this much so suddenly?
Outwardly, I don't look
that much different.
But am I the only one who thinks that?
In other people's eyes, does
this tummy look enormous?
After all, Haru did point that out just now.
This is terrible! I've got to
fix this right away!
"I Want to Lose Weight"
Hey, Ruri-chan?
Do you think I've
gained weight lately?
You don't look any
different than usual to me.
Well, yeah. You might want to
be a little careful about that.
I knew it!
I knew it, I've put on weight!
I know they say it's hard to notice
the changes in your own body.
But I really had no clue!
What should I do?
I started off by skipping breakfast,
but to slim down, first, I need to
exercise, right? And also...
Morning!
Hey! Morning, Onodera!
Good morning, Ichijo!
Th-That's right!
The last thing I want is for Ichijo
to find out I've gained weight!
I've got to shed these
pounds before he does!
All right, I'm gonna do this!
Starting today, no sweets whatsoever!
And I'm going to go easy on
meals, as much as I can.
GURRRRR!
Huh? What was that?
W-Well, now, what was
that sound, I wonder?
An earthquake? You think
it was an earthquake?
That's so scary!
Really, now! Why did my
stomach have to growl now?
Sure, I skipped breakfast today,
but there's no need to growl that loudly!
A-Are you all right, Onodera?
You kinda look pale.
What? No, no... It's nothing!
GURRRRR!
I-It's nothing, okay?
Honestly!
I-Is that right?
Y-You've got to hang in there, Kosaki!
You only have to suffer
for now... It's only for now!
Once you've lost those extra pounds,
you can eat like you always did!
Hey! Kosaki!
Hey, you remember about
our date today, right?
Classes can't end soon enough, huh?
Date? What was that again?
You know, what we've
all been talking about.
We're going to that
all-you-can-eat cake place today.
Did we really say
we were going to do that?!
Oh right, we talked about it
Now I remember!
It's that yummy-looking cake shop
that was on TV the other day.
I want to go...
But I've already made up
my mind about this.
S-Sorry...
The thing is, I have an emergency today.
I'm really sorry!
What, really? Too bad.
But it's just as well,
you know, Young Mistress...
You went to have all-you-can-eat cake
yesterday and the day before as well.
You're eating too much cake.
Hey, I just wanted to
compare the shops.
Hey! Kosaki!
What? What? What? What?
It's the same with Ruri, too.
Where does all the food go, I wonder?
I don't understand it!
All this talk of cake is
making me hungrier than ever.
But it's only second period now, so
there's still a way to go before lunch.
But... but...
I don't want my stomach to start
growling in the classroom again!
What are you doing, Onodera?
In a place like that...
I want to die, I wish I could just die.
A girl getting caught
eating lunch early...
How am I supposed to talk to him?
Just as I thought, Onodera's
acting a little weird today.
Wonder if she's under the weather.
Or maybe something's bugging her?
Huh? Everyone's going somewhere...
What was our next class again?
Gym! That's right, I've got to
exercise, exercise!
I don't have time to sit around moping!
I've got to do whatever I can
to lose weight today!
And so I've got to exercise!
I'm gonna exercise and forget
how I messed up just now!
So the girls are swimming today, huh?
But I'm hopeless in the water.
And besides, I'd rather not get into
an outfit that will expose my body.
No, no! No whining, now!
They say that swimming's a good way
to lose weight! I've got to give it my all!
Hey, today you're pumped up, for once.
How about it? Want to
practice with me today?
I can go at your pace, all right?
Sure! I'm counting on you!
I never thought I'd end up drowning.
I guess I was totally weak
from not having eaten.
Well, I toughed it out for one day.
Wonder if anything changed?
Not that I think for a second that
I've lost weight in a single day.
I-I've gained weight!
And so much, too! No way!
But I've hardly eaten a thing today.
Why?!
Onodera, are you okay?
Huh? What do you mean?
I'm totally fine.
What's going on with her?
Is she feeling sick, after all?
And I heard she collapsed
during gym yesterday.
Dammit, I wish I could
help her somehow.
Come on! Muster up
some courage, Raku!
H-Hey, Onodera!
That konnyaku I boiled in soy sauce
the other day... you remember that?
Yes, I remember.
So anyway, this time I asked Miyamoto
what your favorites were beforehand,
and I made these.
Candied sweet potatoes.
Wh-Why did you have to do that now?!
My favorite food is right before my eyes!
What should I do? I want to eat them!
They smell so amazing!
That's Ichijo for you...
One look and you can
tell they're delicious!
Don't tell me he made them just for me?
No, no, I can't! I can't! I can't!
I've already decided
not to eat anything today!
And I gained even more
weight yesterday!
But... Ichijo did go to the trouble
of making them for me.
One bite can't hurt...
O-Onodera?
One bite can't hurt!
Hey, listen...
You don't have to
force yourself, you know.
S-Sorry, Ichijo.
Actually, see, I'm not hungry right now.
I'm so sorry I'm not hungry!
Huh? Hey!
It's so serious she can't even
gulp down her favorite food?
Is she really okay?
I wanted to eat them!
They were delicious for sure!
And Ichijo made them just for me!
I'm such an idiot!
What am I doing, anyway?
I'm just spinning my wheels again.
Because of my selfishness,
I ended up hurting Ichijo.
How should I apologize to him?
I wonder if he'll let me try them again?
H-How about some tea, Onodera?
My bad.
Guess I stuck my nose
where it didn't belong, huh?
But it seemed like you hadn't
been eating much lately,
so I thought it would be easier
if it were something you liked.
I-Is anything bothering you?
If you don't mind talking
to me, I'll be happy to listen.
Ichijo...
So he was worried about me.
I feel so bad about that.
When it's all my fault.
But... what am I gonna do?
That makes me happy, after all.
Thank you for worrying about me.
But it's nothing serious.
You sure? If that's the case, fine.
Oh, but you better make sure
you at least eat right, okay?
You're thin, Onodera,
so you gotta eat right
or you'll pass out.
What's up with that
smirk on your face?
No, no... It's nothing.
By the way, what's been bugging you?
No, no, the problem's been solved.
I hope you know that scale's busted.
You should've told me sooner!
I nearly had a heart attack!
"Good Morning"
My name is Kosaki Onodera.
When I was a third year in junior high,
I fell in love.
I fell in love with my
classmate, Raku Ichijo.
It wasn't as if he was exceptionally
good at schoolwork or sports,
but it was that simple, inner
gentleness that I was so in love with.
When we were second years,
we became classmates for the first time,
and as third years, we finally got to
be speaking acquaintances.
But normally, we had no real contact.
And I hardly ever went out of
my way to talk to him,
but saying "good morning" in the morning,
and "see you" after class...
That was what
I looked forward to everyday.
Otori Girls' High School
All right!
But...
Hey, Raku,
you've already narrowed it down
to just one high school, right?
Yeah. Bonyari High.
You're trying for Bonyari too?
Yeah, you can't beat
the short commute, huh?
Hey, let's hang out
together again, okay?
I'm gonna be stuck with you again?
What's the problem? You don't like it?
Needless to say...
Once we go on to high school, I won't
be able to see Ichijo anymore.
Pretty soon, I won't be able to say
"good morning" or "see you..."
That would be so sad.
I want to be with Ichijo longer.
I want to talk to him more,
about so many things!
Ruri! I'm going to take the exam
for Bonyari High School!
Didn't you say you were
going for Otori Girls' High?
Because there's tons of yummy
cake shops around there?
Well... that's... Yes, I did say that.
Now that you mention it, Ichijo says
he's going to Bonyari High, too.
What's that look on your face?
Then maybe I'll go to Bonyari, too!
But Ruri, I thought you said...
I know which college I want to go to,
but as far as high school goes,
it doesn't really matter which I attend.
But I have to tell you,
even though Bonyari's not
a selective school by any means,
it's still gonna be hard for you.
Since your grades are pretty low.
I'll work on that.
And so I started studying
for the entrance exam.
National High School Entrance Exam
Questionnaire Compilation - English
To go to the same school
as the boy I loved.
An ulterior motive, yes,
but for someone who'd never in her fifteen
years had a clear dream or goal in mind,
there was no greater goal than that.
And I think I studied harder
than I ever had before in my life.
Wake up!
And then...
Bonyari High School Entrance Exam Site
The day of the exam...
O-O-Onodera!
Wait, are you taking
the exam for Bonyari, too?
Uh, yes, actually, I am.
I wish you would've told me...
Is that right... is that right?
Let's give it our best
shot today, all right?
Let's both get in, no matter what!
Okay!
For some reason, I had
the burning conviction that I'd pass.
Huh? I thought you'd be
way more freaked out.
Oh, this is nothing!
It's all right...
After all, I studied so hard!
And Ruri helped me out so much.
Now all I have to do is
give it my best shot.
I'm going to pass for sure, just like him!
I failed.
In the end, all that
work was for nothing.
I can never say
"good morning" to him again.
And he'll never say
"see you" to me again...
How'd it go, Kosaki?
Hey!
Where are you going, Kosaki?
Hey, come back here! Why, you...
Hey!
Mom, this looks bad!
Sister's turned into graffiti!
I can never look Ruri or
Ichijo in the eye again.
This is so sad...
If I'd known this was going to happen,
I wish I'd just told him how I felt...
Onodera?
What are you doing in a place like this?
Ichijo...
Wh-What about you, Ichijo?
What are you doing here?
I was getting ready for
tomorrow's orientation, see.
My heart's flipping and flopping,
even at a time like this!
I must be the biggest idiot on Earth!
I heard about the results.
And Ichijo didn't go into it any further.
He really is kind-hearted, Ichijo...
If only I could go to the same
school as him, I'd be so...
But anyway, aren't you
cold, dressed like that?
Do you want to use my scarf?
Huh? N-N-No, that's okay.
It's all right, use it.
Just seeing you like that is
making me feel chilly.
That's okay. You're going to
catch a cold, Ichijo!
I'll be fine, so just use it!
I'm all right... really!
Okay, then, I'll use it, too.
You'd be okay with that, right?
Now we kind of seem like
boyfriend and girlfriend.
It's pretty long, huh? This scarf...
Someone at the house has
been knitting up a storm lately.
We've got like a huge surplus.
What? This is hand-knitted?
What am I gonna do?
I feel so happy, but could this be
my chance to confess my feelings?
But I could never...
Hey, Onodera...
I...
Hey! Sorry! It's my mom calling!
It's all right! It's all right!
Go on, answer it!
Hello?
I passed?
I got admitted from Bonyari's wait list!
We just got the letter!
F-For real?! All right!
Awesome! Good for you! Yahoo!
He was so happy for me.
As happy as if it were himself.
He almost seemed a bit too happy.
He really is a great person!
All right, so that means we can go to
tomorrow's orientation together, right?
Right!
See you, Onodera!
Yes! See you, Ichijo!
Since that day,
I think Ichijo and I have been having
slightly more substantial conversations.
Even so,
even though we're both
second years now,
my love has yet to be fulfilled,
but the unchanging bliss of
my days also goes on...
Hey, Onodera!
Good morning... Ichijo!