Gonna getcha, gonna getcha!
You're under arrest!
Today we're playing "Cops and Robbers"
to finish out today's gym class.
Cops and Robbers
A form of tag
Some people are cops and some are robbers
Okay, if we're found, I'll distract the cop
and you free the prisoners while
I've got her distracted.
Oh ho, having a secret meeting, are we?
Down you go!
As if I'd let myself be arrested,
dooooooofus!
Wh...What a jerk...
Go arrest Hitoha! Why're you chasing me?!
'Cuz I love running!
You're such a dope!
This is great!
Micchan!
Come out...
Hurry up! Leave here already!
I thought I had her...
It's stuck! What happened?!
What do I do...
Who's there?
Help-
Umm...could whoever's out there help me?
You think I'm gonna help you now?
Hitoha?!
Then call somebody!
You think I'm gonna call anyone?
Fine, you want an apology right?
Yeah, yeah, I'm so so sorry.
You're not bowing.
You're pushing it...
Everyone back to class for our
end of the day meeting!
I arrested everyone!
Micchan, do you have a hairpin?
I do, but you ain't getting it unless
you get me outta here.
Sweet lady freedom!
Where's the hairpin?
I never had one, dooooooofus!
Get back inside!
No way, how dumb do you think I am?
We might just have to wait
till tomorrow morning.
Say something!
Hey...why're you so sweaty?
You have a stomachache?
No...
Aaaah come on!
Bye bye bye Yabecchi!
Bye bye!
Huh, now that I think about it Mitsuba-chan
and Hitoha-chan didn't come in...
Yabecchi, bye bye!
Bye bye!
Eh, it's not the first time.
Open!
Come on, come on!
Break!
Come on, damn it!
Break! Break!
Break!!
Why won't it break?!
What're you girls doing?!
You'll break the door!
It's open Hitoha! We'll be okay!
Doooooooooooooooooofus.
Please get out.
Mitsudomoe...
Morning Hitoha-chan! Feeling better today?
Yes, I was faking.
How can you say that without
any trace of guilt?!
It was a lie.
Don't do it again!
Empty!
Awesome!
What else, Futaba?
Check this out! Go!
He backflipped!
Hitoha!
I took care of Nipples yesterday.
That's crazy, you taught
him that in one day?
Maybe you communicate with
animals better than humans.
Good boy, good boy.
Fuzzy wuzzy fuzzy wuzzy!
He's always well behaved,
thanks to Hitoha's care!
You...you thieving cat!
D-D-D-Did you see her face?
Yeah...yeah...
Huh?
Unforgivable...Nipples...Futaba... Unforgivable!
L-L-Look Hitoha-chan,
I dunno what happened but please stop
brooding over grudges under my desk!
This is between me and Futaba,
please don't stick your nose
in our business sensei.
I'm gonna stick my whole FACE in!
Now tell me what happened, did you
and Futaba-chan have a fight?
I can't believe they got so
close while I was out.
They? Futaba-chan and...who?
It's not like I wanted to be
the only person in his life,
but for them to be fooling around
right in front of me...
Umm...
Boy
Tee-hee
I see...well, you ARE sixth-graders...
I can't believe Futaba-chan's
got a..."friend"...
I mean, I thought I knew Futaba-chan
pretty well, but...
I guess he's forgotten all about
our initial honeymoon time...
She stole him away?!
Futaba-chan stole her sister's boyfriend?!
Just one day and he's submitting
to whatever she says...
Submitting? To Futaba-chan?!
Giddyap!
Wait...maybe it's a love triangle?!
I've never dealt with anything like this!
Just kill me now! Get out! Leave me be!
No.
Get out or I start kicking!
And farting!
And taking off my shoes! My feet stink!
I know...I just didn't want to say anything.
Do you treat all your students like this?!
Principal
Making them smell your feet?!
No-I...Umm...
Hitoha!
N-Nipples is...
Ah, well if that's the case
I guess I understand.
I can't find Nipples anywhere!
I...I don't care anymore...
Nipples!
When did you-
I knew he liked you better.
I'm sorry I was so mean to you earlier...
Thanks for taking care of him yesterday.
You can...pet and play with
Nipples whenever you want.
Ahh, so that was all about Nipples?
Really? I can rub Nipples whenever I want?
Yeah...just be gentle.
Whee, whee!
What the hell are you teaching these kids?!
Principal...
Do all your students compulsively
fondle their nipples?!
No, it's-look...
You sick pervert of a teacher!
Mitsudomoe...
It's no use, I can't snap my
fingers...it's not fair!
Don't pity me...
Dude.
Yabecchi, you had a cockroach?!
It was gargantuan...I touched
it right before bed...
I was so freaked out I only
slept about two hours...
Those creatures may not
be physically imposing
but they're terrifying enough
to destroy nerves of steel!
I hear for every one you see
there are thirty you don't!
Stop...
I hear they drink sleeping people's drool.
STOP IT!
I'll clean up your roach problem!
Futaba-chan...
I'm not going over there again now that
I know it's crawling with roaches.
I never asked you to come over!
How about we watch the brand-new
Gachi Rangers DVD as a thank you?
Really?
Serious Squadron!
Gachi Rangers!
A Gachi Rangers DVD...
Hello!
Hi hi!
Oh? You're here too, Hitoha-chan?
I just...came to keep an eye on Fu-
It got away...
What'd you do?!
I RENT this place!
But I saw a cockroach.
There's another one!
No barehanded extermination!
Use something cleaner!
How's this?
That's worse!
Gachi Ranger action figures...
The paint job is flawless...
What, are you gonna call me a freak because
I collect the action figures too?
No, I...I love them too! I...
Liar.
It's true.
Then...
What're you doing?!
No, there...there was...
Trying to make me lower my guard so
you can smash my figures, is that it?
You're horrible!
No-
This is no ordinary toy.
This is a high-quality collectible!
Well? Don't you like it?
Please...no...
You said you did.
It's...it's...
I knew you hated them!
I...
Whatever, Futaba-chan understands!
You said doing it bare-handed was bad...
I didn't ask for pinned specimens!
Just get them with a magazine, okay?
Adult book
full of boobies
Crap! Hey, Futaba-chan, do that
AFTER you get the roaches!
The Gachi Rangers DVD...
It's got a special edition insert...
Futaba-chan, wouldn't you rather watch the
Gachi Rangers than some gravure magazine?
Wait-
Don't. It's okay. Don't open it!
What do you care? What's with you?
We're going home!
We're going home.
All right, I'll loan you the DVD.
I don't want it!
You don't have to be so cruel!
It's such a great show...but even Futaba-chan
prefers boobies to the Rangers, huh?
I'll watch it over and over
until I feel better...
Mitsudomoe!
Wait, wait!
Oh geez, bad dumbbell!
Did you hurt yourself?
Momma...where's momma...
Oh no, are you lost?
Momma...
All right!
Don't cry, I'll help you find your momma!
I'll jump up and you look around!
Whoo!
Did you see her?
Wow! So high!
Aww, did you like that?
Let's jump some more!
Whee!
Kazuya, Kazuya?
Where did he go? He hasn't even
learned his address yet.
Where'd Futaba go? She hasn't
even learned our address yet.
Why weren't you watching her?
This foot massage is so good...
More, more!
Okay!
That way!
This way!
Okay!
Outside!
Pass him!
Okay!
Topknot, jump over the river!
Ba-ba-baba-ba-ba-baba-BA!
A B C then D E F,
I say that the bigger ones are the best
and they may call me
crazy and say I'm a mess
but there's nothing better
than F-cup breasts!
G H I then J K L,
Always on the lookout
for the perfect mel-lons
flying into action like a Gachi Ranger
there's no danger for me!
If I could just have one wish
granted before my final rest,
I'd wanna play hide and seek
in a bouncy jiggly forest!
A-cup, B-cup, little itty bitty cup,
all the way up to a monster G-cup!
Two bees walking through trees
wearing nothing but pink crew tees!
Who agrees that seeing these
out in the breeze puts you at ease?
Like pineapples they grow on trees
and never ever come in threes.
Bees-bo-bees-bo-bees I'm on my knees!
My senpai sees that overseas or
on the trapeze they always please!
So just say please, my expertise
requires no fancy degrees
I guarantee MY nominees will make
you freeze if you give a squeeze!
Ba-ba-baba-ba-ba-baba-BA!
A B C then D E F,
the first time I saw I was speechless
I'm Gachi-serious
about coffee cups and coff-E-cups!
G H I then J K L,
I'm Gachi-obsessed
with all kinds of breasts!
Someday maybe I will
have some of my own...
Where are we?
I can't see the mall...
Stupid Topknot!
You wanted told me to go outside...
You got mad at me!
Momma!
What does your mom look like?
I can draw really well!
Momma...looks like...
Make her eyes bigger.
How about her hair?
It's brown, like this!
What about her nose?
Umm...
Done! How does it look!
Momma! It's Momma!
Brown
Momma, momma!
Momma...
Lost children
Okay, thank you.
That was the police station in the neighboring
town, they found both of them!
They were both asleep
on the side of a road.
A ROAD?
Sleeping?!
Momma!
Why do you always insist
on embarrassing me?!
I just nodded off...
I'm so sorry I ran off with your son!
Momma, Topknot is great!
She drew your picture on the ground
for me! It looked just like you!
Then I fell asleep!
You drew my picture?
It...wasn't as pretty as the real you...
Thank you for taking care of Kazuya.
Topknot, can we play again sometime?
You bet, kiddo!
Bye now!
Bye Topknot!
You're lucky you found such
a nice girl to play with!
Yup!
I wish I could have seen
this picture she drew.
You can, it's this way!
Look, there!
See! Right there!
You are NEVER seeing that girl ever again!
I can't believe you got lost...how
old are you?
It was fun, though.
Hey Hitoha, we don't have those disgusting
black things in OUR house, do we?
There's something even more fat and
disgusting lurking around, though.
It opens the fridge at all hours and in some
ways, it's a lot worse than roaches.
Episode 9
Santa Claus is my Sweetheart
I had no idea...