Sorry to keep you waiting, Ayato.
- That was a close shave, wasn't it?
- Claudia!
Julis!
Erenshkigal...
Ophélia!
I see.
So then I passed out.
Uh...
So you're finally up, then?
Julis...
Thank goodness...
You didn't wake up
for three days straight.
You had me worried.
For three days?
These two must've really been worried.
They've been hovering
over you every day.
You should show them
your appreciation later.
Also...
I never thanked you myself, did I?
Thank me?
I hear that not only Ophélia,
but even Gustave showed up.
Sorry about that.
Seriously, you saved me.
Hey, don't mention it.
I hope you're not going to say
"I'm indebted to you" now.
No.
I just wanted to make sure
I thanked you.
So...
how about telling me about it?
Your relationship with that girl...
Ophélia Landlufen...
You remember this, don't you?
Sure.
Isn't that the handkerchief everybody
at the orphanage embroidered for you...
and your best friend sewed for you?
She didn't like fighting...
and she was a truly kind-hearted girl.
No way.
Right.
The one who sewed this for me...
...was Ophélia.
Reunion
What on earth is so fun
about doing that?
See, plants are really honest.
If you suffuse them with love,
they'll love you right back,
but if you neglect them,
they'll abandon you.
Abandon? Plants... abandon humans?
Plants that aren't even sick
wither and die
because they've had it with humans.
There was nothing she enjoyed
more than caring for plants.
She couldn't even bring herself
to kill an insect.
Whenever beautiful flowers
came into bloom,
she would get so excited.
Then...
what about yesterday?
That gutted building you saw
on the snowy plain yesterday
was the result of Ophélia going berserk.
It used to be an Integrated Enterprise
Foundation lab called Frauenlob...
...where an Arlequint student
known as the Magnum Opus
once conducted
a certain kind of research.
Namely...
creating manufactured Genestella.
And the guinea pig for this experiment...
was the person they took away
as collateral for the orphanage's debt.
Ophélia!
As a result,
Ophélia, who wasn't even
a member of the Genestella,
is now the most powerful
Strega in the world.
Meaning that the research
was successful?
No.
To this day, the ground below that
abandoned building is rotten.
Not even so much as a blade
of grass will grow there.
The price she had to pay
for the power she'd gained...
...was the inability to even go
near those flowers she loved so much.
When I saw her again in Asterisk,
I could see that she had changed.
It was as if she'd given up on her past
and herself, and abandoned everything.
OPHÉLIA!
I'M NOT ASKING YOU TO COME BACK!
You know what I'm talking about.
BUT... AT LEAST...
Ophélia's uncommonly intense power
is a double-edged sword
STOP FIGHTING
that eats away at her,
the more she uses it.
RECKLESSLY!
IF YOU WANT YOUR WISH TO COME TRUE
I wanted to stop her
from further recklessness, but...
FIGHT ME... AND...
DEFEAT ME...
The result was... well, I shouldn't
have to spell it out for you.
I'm sorry I dragged you into this.
But now I'm going to
finish this on my own.
Otherwise, Ophélia would never get it.
Roger that.
So anyway, you two
playing possum over there...
I'm counting on you, too.
So you were onto us.
Sorry about that!
Never mind.
Anyway, we need to make
Gustave Marlowe our top priority.
Right.
Has he attacked anyone else since then?
No. You don't have to worry about that.
We've raised the threat level
throughout the capital
and we've bolstered
our security forces significantly.
Just in case, I had them send some
forces over to the orphanage, as well.
If he does show his face
somewhere, it would be...
B-B-B-B-Bad news, Princess!
Flora? What's wrong?
Why are you panicking?
R-Right!
Something is wrong with the city!
There are all these giant lizard things,
about this big, flying through the sky!
Are those things attacking people?
N-No, not quite.
Since the entire police force
is dealing with them,
there hasn't been
a lot of damage yet, for now.
What?
The entire force, did you say?
So the police unit guarding
the orphanage as well...
Yes, I hear they've all
gone into the city.
Damn!
Julis, calm down!
Gustave knows what he's doing!
They wouldn't think twice
about forsaking the orphanage,
and that this would be a good
diversionary tactic to draw us out!
I have no doubt
he's lying in wait in the slums.
And if I don't show up, he's sure to...
This is my problem to fix.
Don't come with me.
What are you talking about, Julis?
He's right.
After all, it's not just you
who they're after, Julis.
We're involved in this one, too.
Very well.
In that case, I have an idea!
Will you follow my instructions exactly?
Gustave Marlowe!
Well, well, Your Highness,
Princess Julis...
I am humbled that you would
come all this way to meet me here.
You better not have
touched the orphanage!
Rest assured.
After all, it would be pointless to destroy
the bait before I even get my prey.
My first order of business
is to draw you all out!
Is that a Hydra?
That's exactly right, Your Highness.
Every bit as...
no, even more imposing and striking
than the ones in mythology, eh?
Now, then...
Having lured my prey here,
I have no more use for that bait.
Why don't I finish this off
without further delay?
Now then, if you'll excuse me.
I encourage you to enjoy
yourselves to the fullest!
Come back here!
Julis!
Sorry, Ayato.
Uh, never mind that.
Dammit!
If I want to protect the city,
I've got to stop this thing, eh?
Since the police unit isn't showing up,
our only choice is to do
something about this ourselves!
Julis, I want you to help
the residents evacuate.
Don't tell me you're going off
to stop that thing by yourself?
I'm going to do what I can.
And anyway, Saya should be done
with her preparations soon.
But...
You're more familiar
with this area than I am,
and everyone would listen
to you, wouldn't they?
All right.
But make sure
you don't do anything reckless.
So there's no question about it?
No.
I can send you the evidence
I've gathered if you need me to.
No, that won't be necessary.
That's as far as you're gonna go!
And now I stop you!
So it regenerates, too, like in the myth?
Ayato!
Thanks for waiting!
Thanks, Saya.
Good save!
Is that snake-thing my target?
Yeah.
What's the plan?
Gustave was serious
about reproducing the myth.
Meaning that until we chop off
the head in the center,
the other heads around it
will keep regenerating.
So a swift attack?
Right. I'm gonna have
this monitor on stand-by.
Okay. All right, then...
bring it on.
All right, that's two!
4 o'clock!
That's four!
6 o'clock.
I'm on it!
That makes six!
Saya, let's finish it off
with the next blow.
Gotcha.
Amagiri Shinmei Style...
Twin Dragons!
And that leaves just one!
Ayato! 3 o'clock!
Did it speed up the regeneration
by focusing on just one head?
Not done yet!
You did such a great job, both of you!
I'm done setting up my ploy!
Come out...
Rafflesia Duoflores!
Oh, my.
Now I'm at a loss.
How did you find me?
Surely someone like you
would be watching
from where you could
overlook the entire slum,
somewhere safe and not so far away.
That's how Julis guessed it.
I see... You certainly are a group
of annoyingly smart young girls!
This is Kirin.
I've captured him.
Father?
Gustave Marlowe has been apprehended.
It's been a while
since we last met, Claudia.
A member of Galaxy hires a criminal
to assault a Seidoukan student...
a princess, no less.
Galaxy had nothing to do with it.
I acted solely on my own.
Such an excuse wouldn't work
for a man of your position.
I believe that would also
be my mother's judgment.
Probably.
If she deems it necessary, she won't
hesitate to throw me under the bus.
In other words, none of this
will be of any use to you!
Probably not.
And you know what will
happen then, don't you, Claudia?
If you still insist on competing
in the Gryps Festa...
Please!
At least change your wish!
There's still time if you act now!
As I've already told you
numerous times,
I can't do that, either.
I...
I love you, Claudia...
I am truly grateful for all
that you did for my sake, Father.
Now, then, good night.
Really, thank you
for all that you've done.
Thanks to you, peace has been
restored in our nation.
The people are deeply grateful as well.
In fact, Julis...
the people in the old city
might throw you another parade.
Meaning that your position
will soon become tenuous?
In that case, Brother...
I'm going to take this opportunity
to tell you something.
Oh? What would that be?
I'm going to win the Gryps Festa
and expand the king's powers
in Lieseltania!
This incident convinced me.
That in order to change this country,
I'll have to do something
at a more fundamental level.
Right, the Festa prize money
could expand the king's powers...
If it happens, I'm going to
burden and trouble you.
But knowing all that...
I'm asking you, Brother...
Do you think you could
help me out, for my sake?
Julis...
You've really changed, haven't you?
I never dreamed the day would come
that you'd ask me for help.
This is all thanks to you, Amagiri...
no, all of you, I think?
You got it, Julis.
I promise you.
If you really do manage
to win the Gryps Festa,
then I'm going to go all-in
and stop being a good-for-nothing.
Brother...
Thank you very much.
They're such a lovely
brother and sister, aren't they?
Yeah, they really are.
The Steering Committee Chairman?
Amagiri...
I've found your sister.
Big Sis...
ASTERISK CENTRAL DISTRICT - HOSPITAL
Haruka Amagiri was brought
in here five years or so ago.
Her body's been in a state
of apparent death since that day,
and to this day,
there's been no change whatsoever.
I believe it's the effect
of some kind of power.
According to the doctors,
there's nothing they can do at this time.
This is probably
my sister's own power.
Imprisonment Power.
The power to bind all things.
I don't know why,
but she's cast it on herself.
If this state continues...
would her life be in any danger?
They say that if there's no change,
she'll outlive you by far.
If you can call this living, that is.
I hear they found your sister.
Ayato Amagiri...
I can cure your sister for you!
Who are you, exactly?
I'm Hilda Jane Rowlands.
Chairman of the Tenorio Faction
of the Arlequint Academy Research Institute.
I'm known by the people as...
Magnum Opus.
Once again, I'm sorry that my father
caused so much trouble in Lieseltania.
But why would your father
do such a thing?
Because it would inconvenience him
if I were to win the Gryps Festa.
Galaxy, that is, rather than my father.
But if that's the case, wasn't there
another way to go about it?
My father must have wanted to settle things
before Galaxy made a serious move.
What would befall me
if Galaxy were to take drastic action...
My father was all too aware of that.
Do you realize what you're saying?
Making an enemy of Galaxy is the same
as making an enemy of Seidoukan.
Yes. But even if that comes to pass,
I have no intention whatsoever
of conceding my wish.
Don't you all feel the same way?
Joining my team could mean
making an enemy out of Galaxy.
Even so, I still want you all to take part
in the Gryps Festa with me.
Isn't the thought of this team
alluring enough to seem worth it?
This lineup boasts all the best players
I could hope for now.
Count me in.
M-Me, too... count me in, too!
Ever since I saw you
in the last Gryps Festa,
I've wanted to fight
on your team, President!
My answer depends on Ayato.
What are you going to do, Ayato?
Ayato?
I have no intention of asking
that Magnum Opus for help,
but...
if there's a way to treat Big Sis...
All right. I'll be joining
your team, too, Claudia.
And let's win with this team!
No matter what!