The Third Plate
Eleven
Cutting Edge Cuisine RS
Good work, Ryo-kun.
You listened to what I said
and won, as you should've.
Uh, I guess.
Anyway, we have a win.
We got one back at Central!
Yeah!
That was a good match.
What?
Director Nakiri?!
Seriously?!
Uncle Azami, it's been a while.
Scandinavia, 8 Years Ago
Miss.
What are you always writing?
Letters.
I'm sending letters by airmail to Japan.
Erina wants letters from me, you see.
So I have to send a lot.
Even though it's such a bother.
Huh, I see.
She's really enjoying it.
Bye, Erina.
Letters.
You'd better send me letters.
What?
There are no letters from
Erina today, either?
I see.
It's fine, Mother.
I'll just try to write another one.
Ugh, Erina.
You're the one who said you wanted letters.
Hello, Alice.
Thank you for taking care of Erina.
Uncle Azami...
Food Wars
The Third Plate
Der Weiße Ritter der Tafel
Alice, the chief of Cutting Edge Cuisine RS?
Since when?
See, it's in the official records
of a Shokugeki in the past.
That's why she was targeted
by the survivor hunt.
I wonder if Alice is going to be okay.
You're worried, aren't you?
I-I'm not worried!
But Alice can be reckless sometimes, so...
Well, it's true that she's the one who
took you away from your family home.
Alice-kun seems to be very
concerned about you, too.
What a beautiful friendship!
That's youth in a nutshell.
I wonder about that.
What?
I doubt she feels any friendship toward me.
I've done many horrible things to Alice.
Alice, your Cutting Edge Cuisine RS
was the only one to win a Shokugeki
in today's survivor hunt.
The other 32 organizations all suffered
defeat and will be disbanded.
Regardless of other outcomes,
Ryo-kun won against Central.
Can you still insist that your way of
thinking is absolute and correct, Uncle?
How disappointing, Alice.
I thought you would support my
utopia of true gourmet dining.
The Nakiri family has a responsibility
to advance the world of gourmet dining.
That's what this great revolution is for.
Father?!
Alice...
I can't agree with your methods, Uncle.
Nor do I wish to.
That's all.
What a stubborn child you are.
You even took my beloved daughter
out of the house without permission.
Consider whether you have the right
to speak to me that way.
I don't care!
I am angry.
I will never forget what
you have done, Uncle.
I don't like you, Uncle Azami!
I will not let you do what you want
with Totsuki Academy! With Erina!
I see.
Well, do your best.
For today, I'll just congratulate
you on your one victory.
Erina...
You were listening to us?
If only Uncle Azami had not interfered,
we would've been such, such,
such better friends, Erina.
How rude of him.
Besides, you've been looking
too gloomy lately!
Why don't you stand up straight and proud?!
You've been holed up in your room in
Polar Star Dormitory, haven't you?!
H-How dare you!
You're the one who made
me run away from home!
That's because I couldn't stand to
see you all terrified of Uncle Azami!
You have to show him!
You have to show him that
you're your own person!
That you won't just be someone's puppet!
You can't stay in your shell forever!
Got it?
Alice...
Besides, I intend to hand you
a crushing defeat some day!
I can't have you be a shrinking violet
when I need you to be my worthy foil.
What did you say?!
What?
Everything you make tastes disgusting, anyway!
You said "disgusting"!
I said "disgusting" because it is disgusting!
They're actually really close, huh.
Don't say that to them.
It'll only cause trouble.
Chanko RS
Organizations that suffered defeat
will be immediately disbanded
and forbidden from any form of activity.
Should there be any act of rebellion,
retribution will be swift.
Good day.
Kitchen No. 26
The class format has changed a lot
since Central was founded, too.
Yeah.
There are no more classes where
you come up with your own dishes.
They're all about following recipes to a T.
They really don't plan on letting
us cook what we want.
Even Master Shinomiya gave me
more leeway in the kitchen.
What's wrong, Chef?
I suddenly felt really
irritated for some reason.
79th Generation Totsuki Elite Ten
First Seat
Shinomiya Kojiro
The instructor who had been
in charge of this class
was dismissed due to his claims that
he could not follow Central's directives.
What?!
Dismissed, huh.
They're really ruthless.
Due to that, a substitute instructor
will undertake the demonstration today.
The lesson will be a basis for the
true gourmet dining Central espouses.
Pay full attention, and learn the material.
The instructor will be coming in now.
The First Seat...
Tsukasa Eishi!
What?!
Hello.
I'm the Elite Ten's First Seat,
Tsukasa Eishi.
I don't know if you all know me.
We know!
I'll be preparing a few dishes today.
I'd like you all to model my methods
when you make these dishes.
Seriously?!
The First Seat will be showing us how?!
That's too scary!
Remember the quality of what
he served at the Moon Festival?
They were amazing, weren't they?
Everything we tasted was wonderful.
Oh, and I'm supposed to
have a student volunteer
to be my assistant during this class.
They'll be providing support
while I prepare the dishes.
Does anyone want to step up?
What?!
You go.
No way. I'll just get depressed.
Huh?
Um...
Does no one want to cook with me?
Huh?
Soma-kun?!
What?!
Yukihira Soma...
You attend this class, I see.
I'll be your assistant.
That's fine, right?
I'll ask you for your help, then.
I'll be demonstrating five French
amuse bouche dishes today.
I'll be preparing all of
them at the same time.
Yukihira, you'll be
preparing the ingredients.
Okay.
Well, let us begin.
Yukihira, first, use a food processor
to make a quenelle from semi-dried figs.
Mince the shallots and julienne the carrots.
Add ground cardamom and milk to egg
yolks and sugar to make crème anglaise,
then pour it over the sorbet once it cools.
Got it!
So much information at once!
My head would explode!
Wow, Soma-kun!
Okay, next—
Fry young sweetfish coated
with whole wheat flour, right?
Yeah, thanks!
Senpai, I'm done making the zucchini dish!
The whipped cream will be whipped
into soft peaks in ten seconds, too.
Good.
Almond cuit!
I had all the French culinary
techniques pounded into me when
I did my Stagiaire with Master Shinomiya.
Don't lose focus, Yukihira.
Got it!
Plating, please.
Wow.
So fast.
Unbelievable.
A true collaboration between gifted equals
that denies entry to anyone unworthy!
Yukihira!
Grill asparagus!
Got it!
So fast.
Okay, let's have you all make the same dishes
within the same amount of time.
As if!
Kitchen No. 2
She's so beautiful.
I hadn't seen her attend classes in a while.
I'm glad to see Erina-sama doing so well.
I'm glad I summoned the
courage to come to class.
It doesn't seem like Father will
force me to come back, either.
Well done, Erina-sama!
It was a matter of course that
you were given an A.
It was easy.
How exceptional, as usual, Nakiri-san.
Instructors.
Your father must be proud of you.
We look forward to your
future accomplishments
for Central and Totsuki Academy's sake.
Excuse me.
Good job, Soma-kun!
You too, Tadokoro!
That was amazing.
You handled all that work with ease.
Well, I wouldn't call it "with ease."
Central's not too shabby, either.
Hm?
Now that I'm actually thinking about it,
didn't I just help Central?
The hell am I doing?
Regional Cooking RS
will be in the next round
of survivor hunt Shokugekis!
Really?
I'm going to go call the chief!
Okay!
Huh?
Whoa!
You're still here, Tsukasa-senpai?!
Oh, I'd been wound up so tight
that once the class was over,
I lost all my tension.
That was really scary,
being asked to cook in
front of so many students.
To think, I might've forgotten to
tell them something important.
I wonder if Rindo's going
to get mad at me again
for sounding so unsure of myself.
He sure is a perfectionist.
Anyway, you were impressive, Yukihira.
You're more skilled than I'd thought.
Oh, I had fun.
I learned a lot, too.
You're a capable man.
Would you be interested in
becoming my right-hand man?
Will you join Central?
What?
Women's Changing Room
Erina-sama, I hear the next survivor hunt
has been scheduled for three days from now.
Women's Changing Room
I see.
Many more organizations will
be disbanded, it seems.
But like Alice, there may yet be another
organization who seizes a victory.
Father's—Nakiri Azami's Central
isn't absolute, after all.
What?
Why are you staring like that?
Oh, well...
You seem different than usual, that's all.
It's as though you've had a
change of heart in some way.
That's...
Until now, I've always done what
Father said without question.
I didn't even think of doing anything else.
I just took it for granted
that I was supposed to obey.
But Yukihira-kun and other
Polar Star Dormitory members
refused to change themselves.
They would not bow down before Father.
And Alice told Father how
angry she was to his face.
When I saw her like that, I...
You have to show him!
You have to show him that
you're your own person!
I started thinking as well about
what it is that I want to do...
Erina-sama...
I-It's not because I've been influenced
by Alice and Yukihira-kun, understand?
I just want to make my own decision—
Yukihira?
S-So Yukihira-kun has
nothing to do with this—
Tsukasa-san and Yukihira-kun?!
Why are they talking to each other?
What is the matter, Erina-sama?
Why are we hiding?
Um, I am not sure why.
Are you telling me to join Central?
Yeah.
That's a bad joke, Tsukasa-senpai.
Why would I do that?
I see.
I guess you wouldn't.
Hey, that shouldn't make you feel so bad!
Well, I mean it's honestly nice
that you've recognized my skills.
But I don't feel like presenting
Yukihira Diner's cooking at Central, so...
Oh, that wouldn't be necessary.
Huh?
Yukihira Diner's cooking isn't necessary.
What I wanted was your
supportive capabilities.
With you at my side,
I feel I could further refine my cooking.
Um, so it'd be nice if you
could think it over...
for my cooking's sake.
You're pretty casual about saying
some incredibly selfish things.
Man, chefs are all such selfish assholes.
Nakiri-san, Arato-san...
What are you doing?
Hurry, hide!
Huh?
There will be advantages
for you too, Yukihira.
If you join Central and team up with me,
you'll be able to cook at a level far
above what you currently have access to.
But that's just as your assistant, right?
What's the point if I can't
serve my own cooking?
Oh, I guess that's true.
You really think about nothing
but your own cooking, don't you?
Besides, you've never seen
any of my dishes, have you?
It could be that I'm better
at cooking than you!
I see.
Then let's test it out...
And see whose skills are superior.
If I'm acceptable,
I can face you here and now.
And I'll wager the Elite Ten's First Seat.
The First Seat
First
Are you serious?
Very serious.
But if I win, you'll have to
join Central and work for me.
Will you accept this challenge,
Yukihira Soma?
Great.
Let's do it!
I'll face the first seat!
It's decided, then.
About the topic, how about venison?
We were supposed to use the
venison during class earlier,
so there are many different
cuts still available.
I see.
That's fine by me.
As for the cooking genre...
Let's go with French cuisine!
I see.
Sure.
Let's begin, then.
The match has begun.
The French cuisine I had at Tsukasa-senpai's
booth during the Moon Festival
was a shocking revelation.
But I learned a lot at Master
Shinomiya's restaurant, too!
I'll face him with my own French cuisine!
H-H-H-How's this even happening?!
Well, we don't know, either.
But now that they've
begun their cooking match,
we can only observe what will happen—
how Yukihira-kun will
challenge the Tsukasa Eishi.
Yes, Erina-sama.
But if he loses...
Okay, so venison.
What kind of dish should I make?
What kind of dish will let
me win against Tsukasa Eishi?
Yukihira, I'll get started first.
Wow, that's huge!
That must be venison backstrap.
After rubbing the meat with salt and pepper,
he's using the salamander to
slowly and gently cook it.
He's lined the skillet with diced
venison fat and tendon, so that
the meat will not come in direct
contact with the skillet's surface.
And he's periodically removing the meat
and basting it with the melted fat
to prevent the meat's
surface from drying out.
His care for his ingredients is unbelievable.
He is so tender toward them.
It's almost as if he's
silently speaking to them.
That is why he is the First Seat.
Right now, he is communing with the
ingredients in the truest sense of the word.
Good. Come this way.
Come closer.
That's right. Come.
Now...
Come reside in my dish.
Amazing.
The venison's juices seem to be quietly
rippling within the meat.
We're witnessing the ingredient reach
its full potential as we speak.
I haven't even tasted it, but...
Just by smell and sight...
I can't help but consume...
...the ingredients' energy!
His sensitivity and technique far
surpass the acts of mere mortals.
Der Weiße Ritter der Tafel, Tsukasa Eishi,
has set foot in the divine realm
ruled by gods of gourmet dining.
Yukihira, are you sure you
don't want to start cooking?
As a member of Central, I cannot
allow myself to be defeated,
so I will not be holding anything back.
Tsukasa-senpai, what does Central
want to accomplish, anyway?
Huh?
Why ask all of a sudden?
Is controlling the academy
their only true objective?
I mean, you're such an excellent chef.
I think you'd do just fine on
your own without joining Central.
Th-That's giving me too
much credit, Yukihira.
Hmm, but I guess Central's long-term goal...
is to shut down all the restaurants in Japan.
Huh?
Oh, I hope you don't misunderstand.
Of course, we wouldn't shut down any
restaurant that is truly serving gourmet food.
Here's what Director Azami said.
We must annihilate restaurants that serve mere
animal feed, unworthy of being called food.
It is an absolutely necessary step in order
to advance Japan's gourmet dining.
To do so, nurturing superior chefs
who'll become our army is essential.
The current purge at the academy
and the restructured classes
are all preliminary steps before the subpar
restaurants are shut down nationwide.
Subpar restaurants?
Right.
We'll eradicate all the city
restaurants that cater to the masses
and replace them with restaurants
that provide true gourmet dining.
That is the future Central wants.
The city restaurants that
cater to the masses, huh.
So that means stores like
Mitamura-san's Western restaurant...
Western Restaurant
Mitamura
and my family business,
Yukihira Diner, are all unnecessary?
Yeah, that's correct.
Even if that means there'd be people
who'd lose places they really care about?
Yeah, it would.
I think that's unavoidable.
I see.
I don't think I'm suited to
becoming your second-in-command.
I won't join Central.
I'll win this match!
Totsuki
Food Wars
The Third Plate
Next Episode:  The One Who Aims for the Summit
I hope you savor the next episode!