Where are we going, Coach?
You'll know when we get there.
Youth Volleyball Class
Let's go home and practice!
That was so much fun!
Sorry.
Hey, you made him cry.
What am I even doing here?
Shh, stop that.
The class is already over.
Toru! Show me how to serve!
Hey! How about showing some respect first?
O-Oikawa-san!
Come on! Move those legs!
Nice receive!
One more!
Whoa, I can't get that!
Are you sure you're supposed
I'm tired!
to be moving around like that right
after getting out of the hospital?
What? If they let you out of the hospital,
it means they're giving you permission
to move around all you want.
He's my grandpa.
Huh?!
Gra...
Coach Ukai?!
Haikyu!!
Ukai
So...
You couldn't figure out what to do
Episode 06: "Tempo"
with this weirdo quick attack and
helplessly ran away, eh, Coach?
That's your team, you weakling!
Coach?!
He's the great commander that led
the nameless Karasuno to nationals.
The name "Karasuno's Ukai" was super famous.
They said he owned a fierce pack of crows.
P-Please help me!
With what?
I don't go around smacking random people.
Just weaklings.
You shitty old man...
I-I came here to learn to fight on my own!
You want to master mid-air battles?
When you're only that tall?
It's because I'm only this tall!
I might sound like I'm saying
something weird, but...
What's weird about it?
No matter what kind of genius
setter you're dealing with,
in what we call a quick attack,
the one that's the absolute leader
is you.
Stop spacing out!
You're the coach, damn it!
O-Oikawa-san, what are you doing here?
I'm watching my nephew.
Hey!
H-Hey... What about club?
We usually have Mondays off.
Y-You take a day off during the week?
That's such a waste!
Resting and skipping are
two different things.
See ya.
O-Oikawa-san, um...
Nope! Stupid!
You're stupid! You stupid face!
I haven't even said anything yet!
Oikawa-san—
Nope! Can't hear you! Can't hear a thing!
Please listen to me for a second.
Why should I have to listen
to what my opponent has to say?
Please, Oikawa-san!
Please! Please!
Please!
Takeru.
What?
Take a picture.
Hold it like this... And press this button.
Don't move, Tobio.
Yay! I'll call this, "Tobio is
No Match For Oikawa-san!"
Toru, you're actually happy
about this picture? Lame.
Well, what do you want?
I'm busy, you know.
You said your girlfriend dumped
you, so you had free time!
Takeru! Shut up!
What? But when you came, you said you
didn't know what you did wrong...
I said, "Shut up!"
So, uh, what if you were close
to a tournament, and, uh...
And Iwaizumi-san said he was going
to try some impossible attack...
Hey.
If you want to talk to me about something,
quit with the lame "what if" story
and just tell me flat out.
Hinata said he wants to hit
our quick with his own will,
even though he had been closing
his eyes this whole time.
Oh, really? That'd be pretty
impressive if he could do it.
Why not let him?
Please don't make it sound so easy!
Hinata doesn't have any technique!
So you told him, "Just do as I say"?
You sound like a dictator.
Have you put any thought into it?
Are you giving the shrimp
the exact tosses he wants?
Have you even tried to?
Kageyama...
Give me a toss.
If you're thinking the situation as good as it
can be and you're being defensive about it,
you're basically a coward.
Don't get the wrong idea.
The one who has leadership
in an attack isn't you...
It's the little shrimp.
If you can't understand that,
you're just regressing back
to playing the tyrant king.
Let's go, Takeru.
Are you in a good mood, Toru?
I'm happy that Tobio's more run
down that I thought he was.
I'm totally blurry!
You'll need awareness before
you improve your technique.
What do you personally think
about this weirdo quick of yours?
Um... I go whoosh, and then
jump up as high as I can, like pop,
and then the set comes toward me, like slash,
and then if I wave my arm, like swoosh,
my hand happens to perfectly
make contact, like whack.
Er, what he's trying to say is when
he jumps up with his eyes closed,
our setter, Kageyama, tosses
the ball directly to him—
I get what you're trying to say.
But you're wrong, Shrimpy.
So long as that weirdo quick
is indeed a quick attack,
you still hold the initiative in this.
You need to get that through your head.
Don't think of your weapon
as something that's unknown.
Well, I guess it's faster to just show you.
Shrimpy, try blocking.
You're a middle blocker,
aren't ya? Try stopping it.
You're in junior high?
What school?
I'm in high school!
All right, here we go!
Okay!
Is this height for grade school kids?
I feel a bit taller.
Third tempo.
"Third tempo"?
That's an amazing jump!
Your face was totally above the net.
Well, yeah.
You've definitely got some
spring in your step...
All right, next!
Second tempo.
They're coming faster than before, but...
All right, next!
First tempo!
Well?
It's fast!
Can you block that?
If anything, I don't think
I could do it on my own.
In the three tempos you just saw,
was there a big difference
in how the spiker hit?
No! I don't think...
Then what was different?
The timing of their running approach?
Correct! That's what the tempo is.
Listen. The agility in any attack
is determined by its tempo.
It's not how fast or slow the toss may be,
it's the timing of the
spiker's running approach.
The fastest is the first tempo.
It's the best way to get
around the opponent's block,
and is probably the attack you
were doing without realizing it.
But you need to actually understand it.
You need to start your running approach
before the setter's toss goes up...
The setter tosses to the spiker...
Which means, your weirdo quick is also
an attack where the spiker leads.
First... tempo...
And... I don't know what kind
of attack this weirdo quick is,
but this much is certain.
There's no better toss than one
that the spiker can easily hit.
It can't be one-sided.
Eh?
Hinata, practice here for a bit!
S-Sure...
What a weirdo.
The timing of the spiker's
running approach is everything.
One centimeter,
one millimeter...
One second faster to the top...
But that's not enough.
Up until now, I was only working
to get to the top, but...
So from now on,
you want to fight at the top, too.
In order for that to happen,
your partner's gonna need
some improvement, as well.
Huh?
I'm sure Keishin will
do something about that.
Kageyama's an amazing guy,
so I'm sure he can do it.
I don't want to be left behind...
Please teach me how to
fight when I'm at the top.
Don't get the wrong idea.
The one who has leadership
in an attack isn't you...
It's the little shrimp.
If you can't understand that,
you're just regressing back
to playing the tyrant king.
Yes, hello—
Kageyama! Where are you right now?!
Ukai-san?
I'm heading to the school right now.
What?!
I was gonna see if they were done
with the inspection of the gym yet.
Ah!
Kageyama!
Whoa.
Stop walking! Come with me!
I'm sorry?!
A toss that stops!
Haikyu!!
Shrimpy,
if you're gonna fight at the top on your own,
you're gonna have to start
with the fundamentals.
Therefore, you're gonna be hitting
one quick after another.
You're going to get in all the
practice that you missed before.
Hello!
Heyo!
There you are.
Hi!
Shrimpy, your assignment right now
is to do first tempo with anyone.
Got it!
A newbie?
Your genius setter isn't here to toss to you,
He's in junior... Oh, he's in high school.
so it's not gonna be easy.
Ah...
Right!
Also,
in order to get used to the ball,
you need to always be touching it.
Always.
Okay.
It can be with your hands or feet.
Volleyball is a sport where
you can't hold the ball.
You're only allowed to touch
the ball for a few seconds...
You need to control that moment,
as though ball were a part of your body.
Because your body is small,
use everything else possible
to make up for that.
Right!
Sakanoshita Shop
Tempo?
Welcome.
Well, I have the basic
theory of it in my head,
but I was never able to apply it.
I treated your quick attack as something
special when I shouldn't have,
and almost forgot something very basic.
I think I get the basics of tempo,
but what do you mean by a toss that stops?
Listen. First...
When you're tossing for your weirdo quick,
Point of Impact
it's a toss that passes through the
spiker's point of impact.
Right...
But you're going to stop it right there,
at the point of impact.
So, basically...
You're going to make the spiker's
highest point of impact
the place you're going to aim for.
You're not going to use so much force
that that the ball passes through
the spiker's point of impact,
You'll use just enough force to get to
the spiker's point of impact, and then...
...kill it?
The difficulty in controlling your power
and how much backspin you put on it
isn't going to be like before.
Not to mention B-quick,
D-quick, and slide hits...
The farther out you get, the more
difficult they'll become.
Can you do it?
Are you giving the shrimp
the exact tosses he wants?
Have you even tried to?
Don't Cause a Ruckus
I'll give it a try.
Tanaka-san!
Oh?
I-I'm sorry about the other day!
No problem! Kageyama just came by, too.
I'm sorry for hitting you guys.
Stop!
I got too worked up trying to
stop you guys from fighting.
Your punch really worked, Tanaka-san.
But don't fight in front of girls!
Yacchan's face was as pale as a ghost.
T-T-Tanaka-shan!
They're gonna die! They're gonna die!
What is? You're scary!
Also, don't fight in front of
the Vice Principal, either.
Fight anywhere else.
Right!
Hinata, come here a sec.
All right...
When we're doing practice games, Hinata,
you'll be on the B team for a while.
Sugawara, I'm counting on you.
Right!
All right, let's get this started!
Make sure you stay hydrated!
Right!
Um, Hinata...
U-Um, I was wondering if you were okay...
You and Kageyama-kun, um, uh...
I'm fine.
Year 3  Class 1
Yui! Sawamura-kun's here.
What?
Hey...
Once the girls finish practice,
I was wondering if we could borrow the court
until the gym closes,
even just for a little bit.
Oh, sure. I'll go ask.
Did something happen to
the second gymnasium?
No, it's just...
A lot of the guys are doing their own practices.
so we don't have enough room.
Damn it.
Serving is the ultimate attack...
The only one at Karasuno
who can safely use a jump serve is Kageyama.
I'm not good enough to be able
to use it safely in matches.
But then...
I couldn't call it a weapon!
Asahi-san!
A Match for a Thousand
Mind if I join you?
Oh, yeah. Sure.
He casually scooped it up
upon entering... Damn it.
Would you mind hitting some of my tosses?
Yeah, sure.
Uh, wait, what?
You're going to toss?
Could it be...
He's gonna try what
Seijoh's libero was doing?
I'll help you with your
serves, too, Asahi-san.
I can't be left behind...
Sure. Let's do this.
All right!
First Gymnasium
We'll leave the rest up to you guys.
Thanks!
Mens' Volleyball Brazil Compilation
Views: 4419
World Volleyball Simultaneous Attack From Various Positions Compilation
Views 87872
Oh, here it is.
Is this a video of Brazil's attacks?
They all started moving at once.
Shinzen's attack was like this, too.
Um...
A synchronized attack.
Next, please.
Got it!
Good evening!
Sho-chan.
There you are, Shrimpy.
Um, Coach Ukai,
I've been meaning to tell you...
But I'm not "Shrimpy."
It's a good enough name for
a crappy player like you.
Come on! Let's go, Shrimpy!
I'm ready!
You need to put all your thought
into jumping with all your might.
There you go.
You need to be able to hit the
ball at any time, at will,
regardless of who the setter is.
Right!
Don't try to match them!
You need to jump at your own pace,
not anyone else's.
You need to fight with your own will!
Let's go!
Hey, Tsukki.
I'm gonna head this way.
I'm gonna go practice serves
at Shimada-san's place.
Yeah.
See ya.
Tempo
Veteran
Shimada Mart
Report Card
Karasuno High School
Ice
Woof
Oh, sorry! It might be a bit short!
That's amazing, Sho-kun! Nice cover.
You used to panic so quickly,
even if it was just a little off.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
Shut up!
Up until now, I was able to
hit without thinking too much
because of my amazing setter...
But now, all of your techniques
and habits are different,
so I have to make it work in mid-air.
It's just a little, but I can
see the ball better than before.
Give me a hand, Shrimpo.
It went from "Shrimpy" to "Shrimpo."
He's been promoted!
Is that really a promotion?
You're going to Tokyo the day
after tomorrow, aren't ya?
Nekoma's coming, too, right?
Yes.
Sensei told us that Coach Nekomata's
the one who invited us over.
He's hard to get along with, but
his volleyball sense is second to none.
The players he's leading aren't
going to be easy to handle.
Let the push you to your limits.
Right!
First Gymnasium
All right!
Next, please!
You got it!
Now, that it's summer vacation,
we can practice from morning to night.
And starting tomorrow, we'll
resume the Tokyo away games.
This time, we'll be there for a solid week!
This is the first and last
long-term training camp
before the spring tournament prelims.
Let's make the most of this opportunity,
so we have no regrets entering
the spring tournament prelims.
Noya-san, you started practicing tossing?
Yep! I'm gonna do a running
approach to here...
Then Jumping Thunder Toss!
Uh, wait. Where'd the ball go?
How about you start by
practicing normal tosses?
Episode 07: "Moonrise"
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"Moonrise."