"October 21, 1600"
"Around 2:00 p.m."
"Sekigahara"
Don't mess with Shimazu!
Oorah!
This battle has already been decided.
"Fukushima Masanori--Eastern Army Commander"
Forget Ukita and Ishida--
the entire Western Army is routed.
In this final moment...
...why don't you surrender, Shimazu?
What are you thinking?
D-Don't mess with...
...Shimazu!
Please allow me to inform you!
Commander Fukushima was unable
to withstand Shimazu's fierce attack!
Could you assist us with pursuit?!
"Ii Naomasa
General of the Eastern Army"
Got it.
"Act 1
Fight Song"
"Utouzaka"
Our lives for the commander!
--Toyohisa!
--Please withdraw!
Uncle! Please withdraw!
From here on, leave it to me!
"Shimazu Yoshihiro--Western Army General"
What?! You're returning
to Satsuma, too, Toyohisa!
I do want to go back. If I'm to die,
I want to die in Satsuma.
But even if I and all these troops die here,
as long as you return to Satsuma,
this battle is a victory for us!
Rearguard! Form up!
It's time to die!
Our enemy is Ii Naomasa's Red Devils,
the greatest foe that Tokugawa has mustered.
A truly worthy opponent.
It's time to give our lives... now!
If we let them go back to Sasshuu alive,
it would be a shame on
the Ii Clan of Tokugawa.
Lord!
Stall for time! Hold up the
enemy as long as possible.
Hold back as many as we can!
I'll be waiting for you, Toyohisa!
I'll be waiting in Satsuma!
I'll be waiting! You are not
allowed to die, Toyohisa!
I'm a lucky guy, to have an old man like him.
Well, now! It's time to do a warrior's work.
Let's do it!
Take aim!
Fire!
Fear not! Run them down!
Wow! That was splendid!
I am Toyohisa of the Shimazu
Clan, undersecretary
to the Imperial Minister of the Center!
You're dead!
I am Naomasa of the Ii Clan,
undersecretary to the Ministry of War!
Don't you know you've been defeated?!
I shall have your head.
Heh... what are you
talking about, you old fool?!
My head won't be yours...
Yours will be mine!
Stupid fool!
Commander Naomasa!
Defend our lord!
Ready!
T-This man!
Damn idiot!
You are the idiot, Naomasa,
the Chamberlain of the Ii Clan!
I've got you!
Lord?!
--My lord!
My lord!
Lord Naomasa!
Withdraw! Withdraw now!
Withdraw!
Wait!
Wait, Naomasa!
Don't mess with me, you moron!
Leave your head here!
Leave your head with me! Naomasa!
I'm going home...
...to Satsuma.
"Out for lunch
Be back in a while"
"Please take a number"
"Battle of Sekigahara is over"
"Shimazu Toyohisa"
"Out for lunch
Be back in a while"
Next.
What the hell?!
Where is this?! Where am I?!
Who are you?!
Damn you...! I am going back...
...to Satsuma!
"Shimazu Toyohisa"
Next.
What the hell?!
What is that?!
What happened to it, brother? Did it die?
What the hell?! It's covered with blood.
Hey you! What's wrong?
Are you alright?
Hey you. Are you okay?!
This man is "earless," brother.
Devils. I must've been
sent to hell after all...
Hey, you!
This isn't an ordinary dying man.
This language...
It's a Drifter.
What?! Again?!
Wh-What should we do?
What else can we do?
We have to take him to that deserted castle.
It's sooo heavy!
"Drag drag drag..." "Drip drip"
It must weigh a ton.
We have to hurry up.
If the lord ever finds out
about this, we'll be damned...
Stop!
If you get any closer to
the castle, I'll kill you!
Also, if you scream, I'll kill you!
What do you want?!
This thing is one of you, right?
It's dying!
It took a lot for us to bring it to you!
Slow down. I don't understand. And speak up.
If you don't speak slower, I'll kill you.
Isn't this a Drifter like you? Look at it!
Look!
Leave it there.
I still don't understand them at all.
That's enough. Let's get out of here.
We'll get killed if they find out
we not only entered the forest,
but also met with a Drifter...
We need to hurry and get back.
This man is a warrior. Could he be
from the Land of the Rising Sun?
Who is he?
What happened?
The villagers brought a dying man.
He is from the Land of the Rising Sun.
He is a warrior of some clan.
Is he still alive?
He is barely breathing, but he's still alive.
I see.
We don't have proper medication,
but tend to his wounds.
His strength and fate may keep him alive...
...just like us.
How intriguing life is...
Toyohisa! Toyohisa!
This was your first battle, yet you've
brought back an enemy's head.
Good job! What a fine boy!
--Father!
--Toyohisa!
Father! Father!
Oh, you're up.
You're resilient.
You've just been stitched up.
You'll die if you move around too much.
Who the hell are you?!
You're asking me who I am? Who are you?
Answer me! Who are you
and where are you from?
The Mokkou Crest...
Are you a member of the Oda Clan?
A member?! Don't be so stupid.
I am Oda and the Oda is me.
Who the hell are you?!
I am Nobunaga... the former
Minister of the Right of the Oda Clan.
That was dangerous, you stupid fool.
You are the fool. You
call yourself Nobunaga?!
Lord Nobunaga has been dead for a long time.
That means this must be the next world
and you are impersonating Nobunaga...
...a devil from hell!
Please stop.
You're awake.
Excellent.
"Quack quack quack"
Could you please pluck feathers?
Huh? Sure...
Time on your hands?
Huh? Yeah...
Please pluck.
"Pluck pluck pluck"
What the hell?!
You said Nobunaga had died.
People really do think I died then, huh?
Yeah! He died!
He was betrayed and killed by Akechi's
forces at Honnouji Temple in Kyoto.
That was a full eighteen years ago!
What?!
Don't be stupid! Eighteen years?!
It hasn't been even a half year
since the baldy assaulted Honnouji
and I was thrown into this world!
That's why I've been telling you...
You are either a devil from hell or a ghost.
If not, you are just a madman.
I can't help laughing,
seeing you two making a big fuss...
...over something as insignificant
as ten or fifteen years.
Who are you?
Tell him. Tell him.
My name is Yoichi.
"Nasu Suketaka Yoichi"
Nasu Suketaka Yoichi.
You're lying!
"Rumble rumble rumble"
You are from the time of the Genpei War.
That was over 400 years ago!
That's too absurd!
Whether you believe it
absurd or not, I am who I am.
I must be dreaming!
Without a doubt, this is a dream!
Well, who are you and where are you from?
I am Shimazu
Toyohisa of the Shimazu Clan!
I am the son of Shimazu Iehisa.
Shimazu?
Who?
"Shimazu" "Big City"
Where? Where? Where? Where? Where?
I see! It's in the far edge of Kyushu...
A super hick town!
Oho.
I'll kill you!
I know that clan. A Lord Shimazu
lived in my time as well.
If my memory is correct, he was from
somewhere in the countryside of Kyushu.
I see. Your family must have
been provincial for generations.
I'll kill you all!
If you move around too much, you'll die.
For I've just stitched up your wounds.
You are a resilient man.
Sit down.
You called yourself "Nobunaga," didn't you?
Yeah.
Didn't you die at the Honnouji Temple?
You're supposed to be dead!
As if I would allow myself
to be killed by that baldy.
I took Ranmaru with me and ran around,
trying to escape the temple.
No way in hell you'll kill me, you old fool!
I'm used to betrayals like yours!
Then, I found myself in an unfamiliar place.
There, I saw a strange stone passage
filled with countless doors.
In the middle of the passage
was a mysterious man.
Same here. I met him, too.
I also met the man...
...while I was withdrawing from
the Great Battle at Sekigahara!
Sekigahara?
Is it in Mino?
Yeah. It was a great battle between
Tokugawa's forces and Ishida's forces.
Wait! Wait, wait, wait!
Ishida, as in that little toady?!
Why on earth did Tokugawa
have to fight such a battle?
Because, after the death of the regent,
the country slid back into civil war.
Regent?! Why the hell was
the regent running the state?!
Because the regent gained control of
the whole country!
Regent Hideyoshi!
Wait! What?
Tell me how the hell
that bald rat took over the country!
That's enough! Don't you get it?!
Hideyoshi's the one who defeated
Akechi, destroyed Shibata,
then conquered the country!
D-Did Katsuie die?! How about Oichi?!
--Don't know!
--Niwa?!
Kazumasu?!
Toshiie?!
They're nobodies!
The Oda are now just minions of Ieyasu.
Nobody remembers the clan's sovereignty!
What the hell?!
How about Nobutada?
Tell me what happened to my son.
He died! His Nijou Palace
was attacked by Mitsuhide.
He thought you were dead...
He fought to the bitter end!
My son was stupid!
Idiot... Idiot...
He should have gotten out
of there as soon as possible.
The fifty years of human life...
Everything I did for those
fifty years of my life was in vain.
The world is uncertain.
I was also surprised to hear
from Lord Nobunaga that the
Minamoto Clan was overthrown,
and the Kamakura Shogunate
was destroyed as well.
You told me you were Nobunaga, so...
When I saw this man, I thought
he was the famous Mori Ranmaru.
I wish that would've been true.
I wonder what they are talking about.
From this far distance, it's really...
Semu, respond to me.
How's it going? Did you catch it?
Yes, sir. They are certainly Drifters.
Three of them are gathered.
It's unbelievable.
"Octobrist"
We've got to do something about them.
Otherwise...
...it will be the end of the world for sure.
"Smell of Battle"
"Elven Village under Siege"
"Good!"
"Act 2
Footsteps"