Goodbye.
We're going now.
Tabitha!
Where are you going?
Don't tell me you're...
I'm going back to Gallia.
Why all of a sudden?!
Because if I keep hearing your voice,
I'll lose my resolve.
Tabitha...
He'll really be surprised
if we attack this early.
Oh.
It's the Elemental Siblings.
What are you doing here?!
Isn't it obvious?
We're here to kill you.
Huh?
Shut up and fight!
Elves from the Desert
If we continue straight,
we should come out behind
the barbarian's mansion.
I hope she's still there.
I can't wait to meet her.
I wonder what she's like?
Lukshana! What if the
barbarians see you?
Who's going to see me in the
middle of this huge forest?
Let's hurry up and go.
Your fiancée is just as audacious
and impatient as ever.
She's a good girl.
As long as that unchecked
barbarian lover isn't around...
Don't get in our way.
I'm his champion.
Your hair has the same color
as the royal family of Gallia.
We actually have some ties to Gallia.
Knights of the North
Parterre... I was there...
Well, what a coincidence!
Fly!
Hey!
I'll be fighting you.
Didn't you get caught in Romalia?!
You think there's a dungeon
that can hold me?
But let me tell you,
I didn't enjoy being forced
to eat their stinking dungeon food.
I'll be taking out my anger on you!
Hey, what are you
doing to my mansion?!
Valkyrie!
Saito, are you okay?
Let me handle that muscle brain!
Would you care to find out if
my brain's really all muscle?
I-I would!
He looks awfully strong!
Yeah.
What's all the racket?
M-Miss Vallière!
What?!
Good morning.
It's good to see you again.
You!
Looking for this?
Windy Icicle!
Hardening magic...
Fighting you is more
fun than I expected!
Go!
Saito, help!
Louise!
You're so cute when you're struggling.
No! Stop!
Are you okay, Louise?
Help me, Saito!
She's strange! There's something
not right with her!
I think I'm going to make
this girl into a doll.
Is that okay?
Of course not!
Come closer, and she
loses her cute negligee.
Y-You think you can
threaten me with that?
Stop!
Why?
I don't want anyone else to see!
I feel the same way, but...
Well, I'm taking it off.
Stop it!
What the hell are you doing?!
Um, Siesta...
Miss Westwood!
You're safe!
What's happening?
I'm not sure. These strange
people came out of nowhere.
What are they doing?
They're probably fighting
because they're hungry.
That's barbarians for you.
No better than beasts.
Hey, isn't that her?
It's too dangerous!
But I might be able to stop the fight
with my Mind Wipe spell.
This is truly the working
of a great consciousness.
That was too easy.
What's going on here, Jacques?
D-Damian...
This is just...
How should I say it?
Doudou was saying he
wanted to fight that
Sai-something guy again...
And so I...
So you tagged along to
get some revenge, huh?
Of course Jeanette is being Jeanette.
But I don't believe in doing things that
don't make me money.
I'm going to end this right here.
My older brother Damian?
This is...
Wh-Where did the water come from?!
It's alchemy.
It completely changes the
properties of matter.
Damian...
So you had to come.
I've had enough of your games!
Oh, not bad.
That was Siesta!
Saito, go!
Okay!
Elves?
Half-elf daughter,
you will come with us.
M-Me?
She does look like an elf.
But those are too big for an elf.
Stop!
I don't know whose magic this is,
but I'm going to use it.
Precious water of life,
grant them a peaceful sleep.
Wh-What is this? I feel slee—
Hey, pal! Snap out of it!
Hey!
Let's take them with us.
Yes.
I knew it.
He is the protector of the demon.
You know, the one who
defeated our uncle.
What?!
I would have never expected
to see elves here.
The world is spinning
out of control indeed.
No.
I suppose I should say that the
Void is changing the world.
Th-This is really bad!
Huh?
Where am I?
What is this?
Th-This is a happiness producer!
S-Saito...
T-Tiffa?
I'm so sorry!
Touching them just felt
so good that I...
No... It's not a big deal.
Where do you think we are?
Wait, those clothes...
This is elf garb!
My mother had something similar.
That's right. There
were elves and then...
Oh.
You're up?
I was worried that maybe Ari's
magic had been too potent.
You're an elf, aren't you?
That's right.
My name is Lukshana.
It's nice to meet you.
What is this place?
This?
This is our country.
This is Nephthys.
And this is my oasis.
But what are we doing here?
Isn't it obvious?
We kidnapped you two.
Tabitha's familiar
Sylphid saw everything.
It is certain that the elves
have kidnapped Tiffa and Saito!
A week has passed,
but you're saying Tristain
can't send any help?
Romalia has asked that
we leave this to them.
His Holiness asked this?
We are not very
familiar with the elves.
Romalia has been studying
them for many years.
They are much more suited for this.
But...
Please understand, Louise.
I understand.
Then, if you will excuse me.
Louise...
What happened?
You came...
We couldn't just sit at the
academy and wait for the news.
So when is the rescue party leaving?
The Order of the Undine
Knights is volunteering!
Tristain is not going to send help.
Apparently we're to leave it to Romalia.
Huh?
But he's the hero of this country!
They still won't help him?
Our hands are tied against the elves.
We had all those mages there,
yet still we were
powerless to stop the kidnapping.
I'm sure Romalia will do something.
I'm going back to the mansion.
Louise...
Miss Vallière!
Are they sending the rescue forces?
Please leave me alone.
Saito... Saito...
Saito has always saved me.
Now it's my turn to save him.
Even if I have to do it alone.
The ancestral prayer book...
I'm actually a scientist studying
the barbarian culture.
I asked for permission to keep
you here for my research.
That's why both of you
were able to come here.
Stop making it sound like
you did us a favor.
And why did you kidnap
us in the first place?
Because this girl wields
the power of a demon.
A demon?
Excuse me. I suppose you
barbarians call it a...
Void Mage?
Plus, you're the familiar Gandalbrr.
It's Gandalfr!
And since you are a weak soul
and don't have a familiar,
you were the perfect target.
Weak soul...
The higher-ups of this
country are afraid that
the four demon users will get together.
They say that power could be
used to invade this country.
We just took you because we could.
It was Ari's idea to kidnap you.
They said you were strong
enough to defeat our uncle,
so it was best if we took you, too.
Your uncle?
But now it's my turn to ask!
What kind of food do you eat?
And why do you believe in
this devil called Brimir?
And how do you get a chest like that?
Huh? That's...
Uncle!
Lukshana.
Is there any news?
Yes!
The barbarian world
was very interesting.
Look. It's that half-elf
and the barbarian.
It's been a while, barbarian warrior.
Bidalsha...
Don't worry.
I'm only here to check if my niece
is properly doing her
job in keeping you here.
This time.
Lukshana, I'm going to check
the mansion to see if
everything is all right.
Go ahead, uncle!
You'll find everything in perfect order.
Whatever happened to that
Gallian girl's mother?
The last I heard, Tabitha's
mother had recovered.
I see.
So you're saying our resting place
is now the barbarian's kennel?
Stop pouting.
Anyway, what did the council say?
Well...
There is no reason to
let the demon users
and their familiars live!
The moderate faction rejected the
military party's proposal
that Eshmael delivered.
Right now the council is
split right down the middle.
But this time, I have to
say I agree with Eshmael.
A barbarian is no more than a beast.
Who knows what will happen
if we let them live?
Ari!
If you keep saying things like
that, I won't marry you.
But that's something
completely different!
Can't you be more supportive
of my research?
Miss Vallière?
Siesta.
You're going to the land
of the elves, aren't you?
Please take me with you!
I can't!
It's a very dangerous place, you know.
I can't doom you with me.
I also can't just sit here and wait.
But, Siesta...
Even if I can't help,
I want to be close to Saito!
Please.
Fine.
Then the two of us will go together.
The three of us.
Tabitha! I thought you
went back to Gallia!
I changed my mind.
I'm going, too.
B-But...
Sylphid is here, so we can fly there.
Should be faster than riding horses.
Then let's go, all three of us!
How long does it take to
get to the elf country?
With Sylphid's speed,
we'll get there in four days.
But we can't take any rests.
I see. That's a lot
further than I thought.
Huh? What's that sound?
Look!
It's the Ostland...
Jeez, Louise, what are
you trying to pull?
You know, even Sylphid
is going to get tired.
Join us and let us head for
the elf country together!
Everyone, thank you.
Just you wait, Saito!
We're all coming for you!
I guess this really isn't going to work.
It looks like they've cast some spells
to make sure we can't run away.
I'm very sorry, Saito.
This is all my fault.
But this isn't your fault at all.
They caught me because I'm so weak,
and you got caught up
in the whole thing.
Do you want to go back
to Tristain, Tiffa?
Huh?
Yes, I do!
Me, too.
So let's go back together.
Right now, that's all we need.
Okay!
Saito?
We can work out all the details later.
Right now, let's just have some fun.
Come on in, Tiffa!
Saito!
I'm so glad he's here.
The things barbarians do
might not be so different
from what we do, after all.
Isn't that right, Mr. Talking Sword?
Huh?
Tiffa?
Hey!
Tiffa, don't scare me like that!
I'm sorry! I didn't...
It's all right!
You're my friend. I don't mind.
You're right, we are
friends, but still...
It's fine! If you want,
you can even touch them.
After all, we're just friends.
No, I don't think that's a good idea!
What is it?
Wait right here.
This is from my world...
Saito, I do hope you're safe.
I'm going all the way to
that desert to save you!
Next time: Escape Through the Sewer.
You think you can do that with Tiffa
Escape Through the Sewer
and get away with it?!
You stupid mutt!