OP
Yes.
Nice, Hinata, Kageyama.
Too bad. Shake it off, Ikejiri.
Nice fight.
Karasuno isn't using it.
Their usual quick set,
without looking at the toss...
But, although it's still
rough around the edges,
they've learned to do normal quicks.
Although they're still lousy at it,
they can spot openings in the court.
They must've had good practice matches
in what little time they've had.
They're improving their existing moves,
adding new ones,
and creating the best attacks
for each match.
Before they were a dangerous team
that relied solely on brute force,
but now they have knowledge.
Polish and Refine
But they still make a lot
of common mistakes.
It's impossible to improve
receiving overnight.
Karasuno                       Tokonami
Nice serve, Chaya.
One more.
Noya-san.
All right.
Looks like they're going
to win the first set in no time.
That libero is a pesky one.
Now that the dude with the beard is playing,
Kageyama has even more options.
Don't worry.
Come on. Let's turn it around with this one.
Yeah.
One more.
Hinata, give us a nice serve.
Yes.
Let's score with this one.
Yeah.
Haikyu!!
Episode 16: Winners and Losers
In our last junior high tournament,
we made it through the
first match by sheer luck.
Senkan Junior High
Furusan Kita Junior High
Amado Junior High
Taihaku Junior High
But the second match was
against a powerhouse.
We didn't stand a chance against them.
When we were about to totally
give up, you said something...
They're in junior high too, just like us.
They're not unbeatable.
We'll never win if we don't believe we can.
You never get discouraged, Sawamura.
Of course I'm not discouraged.
This is our last tournament.
Our opponents are junior high students, too.
That's right.
We won our first match,
for the first time ever.
All right. We can win the second match
for the first time ever, too.
Yeah.
All right.
However...
Senkan                                                     Taihaku
...we couldn't instantly become a strong team.
Sorry, Sawamura.
Sorry.
Let's turn it around with this one.
Senkan                               Taihaku
We weren't surprised that we lost.
We weren't all that angry about it, either.
In fact, we felt relieved
because we wouldn't
have tiring practices anymore.
But...
...you were the only one
who seemed upset.
Seeing you like that, I was jealous.
I don't know why.
Do your best! Tokonami Spirit
All right.
Are you okay, Ikejiri?
Hinata, nice serve.
Tamagawa.
Nice receive, Tamagawa-senpai.
Bring it to the left.
Ikejiri-senpai.
Tokonami                       Karasuno
All right.
The rumors about Karasuno aren't true.
Fallen powerhouse? Yeah, right.
They're on a whole other level.
Rankings have nothing to do with it!
"We'll never win if we don't believe we can."
Oh, um...
I was just quoting a friend.
It's starting.
Yeah.
I don't have the charisma to convince them.
That was stupid.
It just slipped out.
Nice serve, Kageyama.
An service ace...
Karasuno has stepped up their game,
even after winning the first set.
Karasuno              Tokonami
Damn.
Ikejiri.
It's high.
All right.
Karasuno                                  Tokonami
Maybe we shouldn't be
so happy about one lousy point.
It's fine.
One point can be the
beginning of a scoring streak.
Everyone...
"We'll never win if we don't
believe we can," right?
We'll hang in there.
We might be weak, but we're stubborn!
Let's go win this!
Yeah.
Aya.
Yui, get it.
Yes.
Out.
Good call.
Shirato                                          Karasuno
Even if we're not confident that we'll win,
even if others tell us we
don't stand a chance, we...
"We must never tell ourselves that."
Nice serve.
Aya.
Score!
Don't mind, don't mind. No regrets.
You could've saved that one, Yui.
Huh?
I'm sorry. I've lost so many of them.
Save the apologies for later.
Get up. It's not over yet.
All right!
Karasuno                       Tokonami
It's Karasuno's match point.
It'll probably be a cinch for them.
But for us...
One more point...
It's not over.
We're ready, Karasuno.
Sakurai.
Ikejiri-senpai.
We're not beaten yet.
It's not over yet.
Left.
All right.
Damn it!
I'll save the next one for sure!
One more! Let's turn it around.
Yeah!
They're serious.
They're taking us seriously.
Everyone in the gym thought
we'd be pushovers, but not anymore.
Because these guys...
...are serious.
Karasuno
Hey. Quit spacing out, airhead.
Let's go－
We won.
Yeah.
Do we play... another match?
Yeah, because we won.
We won.
We won!
We can play another match.
We can stand on the court again.
He was like a little animal,
hungry for victory...
...and now he's tasted it
for the first time.
Yeah.
Do they realize they have
another match this afternoon?
Huh?
I mean, it was impossible for the
other team to make a comeback.
They should've conserved their energyー
I'm glad they didn't.
We got to see them be serious.
Although we didn't get
to see the freak quick.
The match on that court's done, too.
Dateko won handedly.
So it'll be Karasuno versus Dateko.
Who will win?
Let's go.
It won't matter if we don't win.
Prefectural High School Sports Tournament
Girls' Volleyball
Stop crying already.
They aimed serves at me.
They scored so many points off of me.
And we kept the ball in play.
That's volleyball.
They were better at it than us.
That's why we lost.
It is not any single player's fault.
Captain, sensei wants to have a word.
Okay. I'll be back, okay?
Michimiya-senpai is amazing.
She's practiced the hardest of all.
You'd think she'd be the most upset.
No...
She's trying to stay composed,
since she's our captain.
She's waiting until she's out of sight.
I did all I could.
I never skipped practice.
The day I saw that
tournament on TV, I said,
half-jokingly,
"I'm Japan's future champion."
But as soon as we started conditioning,
I began to lose steam.
And now it's all over.
That was fast. It's still only June.
I should've... I should've
trained a little harder.
Running, conditioning... I should
have done it all a little harder.
I would've been a better captain...
If only I could've
been a fiercer receiver.
If only I had gone one step further.
Maybe then, I could've played more volleyball.
Sawamura.
Ikejiri.
Win! Then win some more!
Win for us, too.
Yeah. You got it.
There must be thousands
of guys in this country...
...whose last season gets cut short.
Winning all the preliminaries
and going on to nationals...
If all this were a work of fiction...
The guys who go to nationals
would be the protagonists,
and the rest of us would just be extras.
But, regardless...
We got to play...
...volleyball.
Karasuno was amazing.
Especially that little #10! He was unreal.
I know, right?
His quicks were right on the money.
Wh-What?
I'm happy. What's wrong with that?
No one's ever said stuff
like that about me before.
I didn't say anything.
I'm glad you're getting all the attention.
The more our opponents
are wary of you,
the more they'll bring out
the best in you.
Yeah, I don't really
understand what you mean,
but you're scary when you're smiling.
Ouch, ouch...
Yeah, he's right.
"That little #10" gets a big reaction.
The bigger, the better.
The more Hinata shines,
the more he blinds the defense.
Oh.
So, the starting lineup for the next match
will be the same as the first.
Our next match is at 1:30 PM.
Keep yourselves warm.
Have a light lunch.
Don't fill yourselves up.
Yeah.
Next up is no-eyebrows guy's
Iron Wall school.
It's Date Kogyo.
I know that.
Dateko defeated us in March.
That match made Azumane-san want to quit.
Asahi-san...
Every single spike by Asahi got
blocked in this one match...
They blocked all of Asahi-san's spikes.
Hinata, Kageyama.
Got a minute?
Asahi.
It's time to go.
I'm counting on you.
Date Kogyo is a powerful opponent.
Their blocking devastated us three months ago.
But this time, we have the best decoy ever.
You brought out the best in Hinata.
Asahi...
Our ace needs you to do the same!
All right. We'll win the second match, too!
Go! Go! Let's go! Let's go, Dateko!
Iron Wall of Date
Dateko... fight!
Yeah.
Start running!
You're getting intimidated again.
Dateko's scary. I'm glad
I'm not playing against them.
I felt so sorry for the spiker
up against Dateko in the last match.
He was unable to do anything, literally.
Captains.
All the best.
Go! Go! Let's go! Let's go, Dateko!
Iron Wall of Date
I don't know how to say it...
...but it's like Dateko
has taken over the court.
We're receiving first,
from this side of the court.
Yeah.
Get ready to receive!
Here goes. Keep it in play.
Yeah.
It's only been three months
since Dateko defeated us.
Though our team has made
definite progress,
our second and third-years might
still be feeling the sting of defeat.
We have to fix that somehow.
We can't be intimidated by Dateko.
Rolling...
...Thunder...
Again!
That was perfect.
Noya-san, nice receive.
Perfection itself! Except for the name.
The name is perfect, too!
Teach me! Teach me the Again version, too!
How's that different from the regular one?
What was that?
He saved it.
You're showing off again.
Hey, Nishinoya,
you're gonna make Daichi mad.
All right. There's nothing to worry about.
All of you, keep your eyes forward.
Because you have me guarding your backs.
A-Awesome!
Awesome.
Wow. He restored the team's confidence.
Yeah.
He's a little guy,
but incredibly charismatic.
The libero is not just the guardian.
He also encourages the team from behind.
He's a truly outstanding libero.
Fly
Iron Wall of Date
Line up.
Let's play.
Next Episode Preview
That no-eyebrows guy blocked
you, didn't he, Asahi-san?
Y-Yeah.
He's so intimidating.
But you're older than him. Don't worry.
Huh?
That's enough already.
Episode 17: The Iron Wall
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"The Iron Wall."