Chise!
Chise! Chise!
Looks like the binding of
her ring didn't hold up.
These Sleigh Beggy children
just get weaker and weaker.
Chise's familiar, huh?
How's Chise?
You need to get in her shadows.
Hey, snap out of it, thorn child.
Time passes faster over here.
Come to the other side.
We can't show her to a human doctor, can we?
The land of fairies...
Good.
Silky, we're going to be away for a while.
Watch the house.
The entrance to the land of the fairies.
You refused to enter when
you last came here.
To think that now I'm taking you inside...
What a twist of fate.
It's the failure.
The half-assed.
He smells awful.
The beloved child.
Adorable.
Don't touch.
Don't get so hot-headed.
Don't worry, we just met a good doctor.
She's a bit of an oddball, though.
You can't get up yet.
I'm taking the bandage off your eyes.
Um... Where am I?
This is one of the fairy kingdoms.
It's called The Ant Hill.
Fairy kingdoms?
Here, drink this.
Thank you.
Your skin and veins couldn't withstand the
excess magic that was created in your body.
It's being held back by that charm for now.
Honestly...
You could have gotten more proper
treatment at a human hospital.
The fairy king is so selfish.
He brought you here because he
wanted you here on this side.
Um...
Nice to meet you, Chise.
My name is Shannon.
I'm a fairy, raised by human parents
whose child I was swapped with.
A changeling.
Welcome, Elias.
How dare you show yourself!
Spriggan.
How is your adopted child?
Shannon took off with her.
I'm sure she's fine.
I thank you for your concern.
It's my duty to help when
a child is in danger.
You're covered in blood.
Say, Elias,
shouldn't you two live in this world?
Your Majesty, that's not...
This is my clinic.
Like humans and animals, some fairies
can be ailed by sickness and age.
Um...
Where's Elias?
He's near enough to come if we call for him.
Don't worry.
I've been told that he's your husband.
Are you able to communicate with him well?
The people of this side have trouble
understanding certain things with humans.
H-He's not so much my husband
as he is my magic instructor.
Let's just leave it at that, then.
Shannon!
Shanahan.
Get off me.
But...
I was lonely.
It's only been three days!
I told you, the patients are my priority.
I know, but...
Hey, it's a Sleigh Beggy.
She's so cute.
This patient is critically ill!
Don't touch her so casually!
But...
Shannon!
We're having mushroom soup today.
Come home early.
Sorry he's so annoying.
That's my husband.
He's the former human that
was raised here in my place.
We lived for half a century,
swapped into each other's worlds.
Half a century?
When an ordinary human
spends a long time here,
they become something not human.
The human world is toxic to the soul.
The toxins in the soul
soon consume the body.
That may be fine for you, but Chise...
Say, Elias, she's closer to this side.
If you truly care for her,
she would find happiness if
you allowed her to abandon humanity.
Otherwise, that girl
will surely die soon.
I...
For a while, I worked at a human
hospital, believing I was human.
I creeped people out, though.
That's when Shanahan came to retrieve me.
Which is why I'm here now.
Creeped people out?
It scares people when you age so little.
Sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
It's in the instinct of the weak
to be afraid of the strange.
I committed myself to my work
and lived a proper life.
I have nothing to be ashamed of.
We're here.
A pond?
The water here is effective on wounds.
We need to heal your open wounds first.
Thank you.
Does it sting?
No.
It's cold.
But warm.
As a fae, I'm unconditionally
attracted to Sleigh Beggies.
But I absolutely despise you.
I...
I can't breathe.
I don't understand human minds very
well yet, but I want to learn.
Why?
Your kind always pity or
mock me, do you not?
I don't wish for that.
The humans are the ones who fear me,
but it was always a human who accepted me.
You don't need to keep your head down.
Stand tall, and look forward.
I want her to continue living as a human.
Not bad.
The will of a living being can sometimes
be the most powerful thing of all.
The desire to live can bring you
back from the brink of death.
That's especially clear on this side.
However, even when you'd lost a fatal
amount of blood, you showed no such spirit.
That's why your wounds wouldn't heal.
But you just fought back.
As a doctor, no matter how much you
don't want to live, I will keep you alive.
Because I want you to live.
Your wounds have healed.
Shannon!
Chise.
Elias.
Shann—
Silky, we're going to be away for a while.
Watch the house.
Silky.
We're home.
Look, it's a banshee.
Leave her be.
You don't need to be mean.
It's got to be upsetting for the family
she's possessed to have passed.
Hey, dear, you should go somewhere else.
Your family's not here to
hear your voice anymore.
Hey, hey, I heard there are some
hot guys in that town over there.
What, really? Let's go!
What is a banshee doing out here?
Where's your home?
H-Hey!
I want...
more...
time...
with them.
Get on.
What about that home?
They're a pious family that
observes old traditions well.
They should be good.
Blood inevitably ceases to flow.
But a home, even if a house is to crumble,
is not lost, as long as people live.
As long as just one person lives,
there you will find light.
If there is no light to shine on you,
it's your turn to protect the light.
You have the appearance of a silver flower.
It's much better than seeing
you vanish like foam.
You don't need to thank me.
It's our duty as protectors to aid the weak.
Farewell, Banshee...
Or should I say...
Silky.
Elias, um, I can walk now.
No.
I'm sorry this happened.
Yeah, I was shocked.
Even I could tell I was shocked.
But, as long as you're still alive,
I'm content with that.
We're about to leave.
Haven't I told you?
Time passes differently on either side.
So it shifts.
S-So cold.
My feet...
Hang on, I'm going to light the furnace.
Okay.
Huh?
Things seem kind of different inside.
Silky.
Sorry we're—
Whoa, there.
Sorry we were gone for so long.
I can't believe it's winter already, either.
I'm home.
I'm about to spend my first
Christmas with the mage.
What does the girl find in the town of
London in the end-of-the-year rush?
Let's go look for a present together, then.