No!
I-I'm sorry...
That's enough, Hikari.
Come home.
What's going to happen on the surface?
Episode Ten:
The Saltflake Snow Falls and Falls
Now, then...
Long ago, the Sea God
was saddened by the humans who went up
to the surface and left the sea,
so he went into hiding far below
into the depths of the ocean.
After that, saltflake snow fell and amassed
both in the sea and on the surface,
and the world gradually turned cold and gray.
Then one girl dove into the
sea to see the Sea God.
She wanted to save the humans.
The Sea God's heart was
moved by the girl's wish,
and he joined the people once again.
And now, it's not that the Sea God
kept himself from the people.
The people have forgotten about
the Sea God, and moved away.
Without prayers, the Sea
God loses his power...
Compared to before, the Sea God's
power is much weaker and smaller.
Hikari.
Are you listening?
Yeah.
But it's a fairytale.
This is the story of
humans themselves...
Of the upcoming demise that will happen
in about fifty or a hundred years.
What?
Upcoming demise? Humans?
You mean humans will die?
The only way that humans will survive
is if they can sleep and escape
the upcoming freezing world.
"Sleep"?
From here on, the saltflake snow will
continue to fall and amass.
The world will start freezing,
and people will not be able to bear
the cold that will eventually come.
Therefore, we will go into a
long sleep and let time pass,
waiting until the Sea God is
able to regain his power.
The people of Shioshishio
must sleep immediately.
The longer we wait,
the more people we will lose—
Hold up! Wait, hold up!
Are you both being serious right now?
Are you guys all right in the head?
Sleep?
It's not like we can
hibernate or anythin—
We can.
The Ena that the Sea God
has given all of you
will let you sleep until
the calamity has passed.
Hold on a second.
This is all too sudden.
We have school, and what
about everyone of Oshiooshi?
The surface has nothing to do with us.
They don't have Ena.
We aren't obligated
to tell them anything.
But...
Understood?
You need to be prepared, as well.
Like I can believe that...
Uh... Manaka—
Manaka!
What the heck? It's so messy.
Her body was so warm...
Oh, god damn it!
Hey.
What?
We will be having a feast with
everyone in Shioshishio on Friday.
You need to come.
What?
If we fast, our Ena will thicken
and will be able to protect us.
And that is apparently how
the sleep comes upon us.
So we are all eating to our
hearts' content one last time.
Everyone, children and
adults, will be there.
"Last"?
You mean we're not supposed
to eat after that?
That's right.
Manaka, you need to
apologize to your father.
He went out to look for you.
Are you listening?
Aren't you going to eat?
I'm not hungry.
You say that,
but in order to thicken our Ena, soon
we won't be able to eat anymore.
That's fine!
For crying out loud...
Sleep...
But if we sleep...
They don't have Ena.
We aren't obligated
to tell them anything.
It's sparkly and pretty.
I don't know!
I don't know what to do!
I don't know...
What's wrong?
You're up early, Hikari.
You aren't planning to head
up to the surface, are you?
No.
See? I'm not in my uniform.
Good.
Don't leave Shishio.
I'm just going for a walk.
I'll be steaming some
seaweed for you on Friday.
Sure.
He sure loves his seaweed.
You did come after all.
What do you mean, "after all"?
We heard what happened from Manaka.
What?!
What do you mean, "What"?
You were at Uroko-sama's, too, right?
More importantly, what are you
guys going to do about school?
What? You're going?
If what Uroko-sama said is true,
we have to tell everyone from Oshiooshi.
You think we have to tell
everyone on the surface?
But there's supposed to
be no way to save them...
I think I'd be better
off not knowing then...
The people on the surface are
different from us after all.
You think so?
I think that some people
would want to know.
Like you-know-who.
"You-know-who"?
You know he is.
So...
People meeting their demise or going to sleep
supposedly comes down to the Sea God
not having enough power, right?
That just means we really have to do it.
The Ofunehiki.
That's how we'll get the Sea
God to regain his strength.
But they said it was canceled...
I'll talk to Uroko-sama.
Not to mention, it's not like we can
hear something this insane and be all, "Oh, okay."
We have to do what we can.
Hikari!
Wait right here!
It's not happening.
At least listen to what I have to say!
You seem desperate.
Yeah, I am.
So what if I am desperate?
Wouldn't you be better off if the
sea and the surface drew apart?
What?
Being in love is a difficult situation.
Wha—
Too much to bear, you can't help it.
You can't control yourself, to the extent
that you're sad and in pain,
and your heart is full...
Right?
Shut up!
It's not like you'd
understand how I feel!
But I do.
I am the scale of the Sea God who
fell in love with a human girl.
A part of those feelings are within me.
Not to mention, Hikari,
I don't think you're capable of swaying
the feelings of the people of Oshiooshi.
Wha?
Going through with the
Ofunehiki is not a small task.
You should just give up.
No way!
I'm going to talk to them again!
You don't understand a
single thing about me!
It's just till we go into the sleep.
What harm could it do?
Why allow them to go
to school at a time like this?
Why else?
It's compulsory education, after all.
Hey, are you listening?
You guys on the surface
should do something, too.
Do you plan on not doing anything?
You and Dad should have talked more.
Seriously, that's not
the point right now!
Aka-chan, are we going to die?
Of course not.
What are you doing, scaring
Miuna-chan like that?
But you know,
we've been able to catch a lot of
golden-eyes lately, and it's been cold...
A lot of weird things
have been happening.
If weird phenomena keep happening
the way Hikari-kun's saying...
I'll try to talk to everyone again.
Thanks.
I don't think the guys from Oshiooshi
will listen if it's me telling them.
We'll be doing the Ofunehiki
for sure on our end.
Aka-chan, I...
Don't worry, it's okay.
We'll be together forever.
Seriously?!
That's like super bad.
That sucks.
I still want to go overseas,
get a boyfriend,
and do a whole bunch of other things.
I'd confess my feelings!
To who?!
But you know,
if this happens after we
die, does it really matter?
If everything were going to end
tomorrow, it'd be pretty big, but...
Listen to me!
You guys may be okay with it, but what
about your grandkids and great-grandkids?
"Grandkids"?
Our last resort is the Ofunehiki.
It's not just some little
festival anymore.
Kaname-kun, is this true?
Like everything being
destroyed and stuff.
Do you think he's lying?
But you know...
I think it's true.
Gramps has been saying
something's weird for a while now.
Like how the sea is completely
different from before.
He said the sea probably won't
go back to how it used to be.
I'll give the beaded ring to my mommy...
and I think Nyoppi to my Daddy.
Hey, give me your
strawberry pencil, Miuna.
I'll give you my stationary with violets on it.
Sayu, aren't you scared?
We're going to die.
That's why we're distributing
mementos right now.
We don't know when we're gonna die.
No!
I don't want you to die, Sayu.
I don't want to die either.
But there's nothing
we can do. It's fate.
But there has to be something!
You and Aka-chan and Daddy are
all important and precious.
There has to be something we can do so
all of my precious people don't go away!
But you know...
Kaname... the people of the sea just
have to sleep and they'll be fine, right?
But Aka-chan said she
wasn't going to sleep.
She said she was going
to stay awake with us.
But then, Aka-chan's going to die.
We can be together,
but we'll be dead so we won't
be able to see each other anyway!
Huh?
I-I feel sick...
Sayu?
Hey, Miuna.
How do you keep precious
things precious?
Huh?
What happens when your
precious things go away?
Mementos Distribution List
Kaname: Gloves and the
four-leaf clover I found by Miuna's
Long Hair: Sea Slug Pendant
Boobs: Dolphin Pencil Board
This one deserves nothing!!
I see...
So that's what Shishio's been saying.
Gramps,
do you think the saltflake snowfall
and the cold is just temporary?
Or do you think it's going to stay like this?
Well...
I don't think it's something that can
be helped within a single lifetime.
Weather and environmental changes
can be good or bad, depending on
how the affected side sees it.
There might be something somewhere in
nature that is enjoying the saltflake snow.
It just happens that for
humans, it was a bad change.
Does everyone have a drink now?
Yeah!
Yep!
Now, Tomoru, you should say a few words.
Why?
Because you're the Chief Priest.
Come on!
Sing!
Um... Thanks for...
I'm not good at this, but—
Cheers!
Manaka.
The ends of rolled sushi are good, huh?
Y-Yeah...
You've been weird since the other day.
Is something wrong?
Really? I've been normal.
Could you take care of this?
Oh, thanks.
Chisaki-chan, I have a favor to ask you.
What's that?
If you happen to wake up before I do,
could you feed my sea rhododendrons?
Before?
My late husband really loved those.
If they were wilted when I
woke up, he'd be very sad.
If I wake up before you,
I'll make sure to take
care of your plants.
Sure.
Thank goodness.
At my age, I don't even know if I'll
be able to wake up after all this....
Isn't everyone going to sleep
together and waking up together?
Huh?
You mean that someone might
wake up before everyone else,
or everyone else might wake
up and someone might not?
I'm not sure...
I think Uroko-sama will
probably wake us up, though.
When?
Probably after the saltflake snow stops
and people can survive again.
So when is that?
How would I know something like that?
You didn't ask Uroko-sama, Manaka?
Chisaki-chan, where's the rolled sushi?
Oh, I'll bring it right now.
Why isn't Akari coming?
I don't know.
And I even steamed seaweed...
Why're you eating by
yourself like that, Manaka?
W-Well...
Shishio's future is all up to you guys.
You know that, right?
Um...
When we wake up,
the youngins need to be full of energy
to pop out kids left and right.
"P-Pop"?!
It doesn't matter whose seed it is.
Make the babies.
Make babies from Shioshishio who have Ena!
You need to work harder and fatten
up a little more, Manaka.
You've still got a ways to go.
This is the last. Drink.
Um... I'd prefer some tea...
Come on, just drink!
I think you've had enough to drink.
Look at you, Hikari, all grown up.
I'll drink this.
Like hell!
I'll drink it rather than let
someone like you have it.
Give it back!
Don't believe what those
surface people have to say.
I won't be able to go to the
surface if I'm sleeping.
You idiot!
Want some?
Chisaki made them.
They're really good.
I know.
This doesn't feel real at all, does it?
Yeah...
But you know, this might
be a dream right now.
Huh?
We might already be asleep.
I might just be dreaming that I'm
talking to you and eating rolled sushi.
Dream...
What are you talking about?
Just what I said.
You have bad taste, Kaname.
I wonder if I'll be able to wake up...
What am I going to do if I wake
up and no one else is there?
If we sleep, it might be the
last time we see each other.
I wish I didn't have Ena.
Manaka...
I don't wanna sleep...
No...
I'm sure Hikari will wake you up.
But what if Hii-kun won't
be able to wake up?
Don't worry.
He never has any problems waking up.
Yeah.
He'll be the first one to wake
up and say, "I'm starving."
Not to mention if Kaname
or I wake up first,
we'll definitely wake you up!
I think you've had enough to drink.
Just because our school closed,
doesn't mean the soul of Nami
Junior High will disappear!
I'll make it happen. The Ofunehiki!
We'll find it no matter what!
Why do you have to be red right now?
Hey...
Good morning, Chisaki.
What's up?
Why'd you come to get me...
I'm done with just watching.
What?
I thought it couldn't be helped while
you were chasing after Hikari...
But it appears we don't
really have time anymore.
Wait, Kaname. What are
you talking about?
I've liked you, Chisaki.
For quite a while now.
What?!
You sure it's okay?
I'm going to eat.
I'm going to eat, too!
You're going to get in trouble.
You saw, didn't you?
We seriously are going to sleep...
Episode Eleven:
The Changing Times