I'm Sunakawa Ai,
a college freshman.
Now that I've gotten used to
living on my own in Nagoya,
I went home for the first time in a
while, and I got quite a shock.
Takeo, of all people, now has a girlfriend.
Not to mention, his girlfriend seems to
have a secret she can't tell Takeo.
And Takeo's starting to notice.
Subject: Goodnight
Takeo-kun, I wonder if you're looking
at the Moon and the stars.
I've never seen a shooting star.
I hope we can see a meteor
shower together someday.
Yeah.
Goodnight.
Is Yamato trying too hard?
Ever since we started dating,
I always end each day
thinking it was a great day.
Yamato, don't hold it all in.
I want you to laugh at the
end of each day, too.
My Wish
Shuuei High School
Rose Kiss 2
Why are you reading shoujo manga?
I'm just trying to learn as much
as I can about how girls think.
Are you going to see Yamato-san today, too?
No, I've got no such plans today.
Takeo! I recommend this one, too!
This is a real tearjerker!
My Boyfriend and Me
You'll die from cuteness overload!
All Because of Love
My Boyfriend and Me
Thanks, guys.
Wow!
She's a real stunner!
What's she doing here?
Maybe she has a younger boyfriend?
Maybe I'll go say hi.
Oh, it's Sis.
Sunakawa Ai
Now!
Come with me and don't tell Takeo.
I think I'll go home early.
Sure, I'm leaving once I finish this one.
I'll text you later.
Yamato-san...
Oh, hello!
Koizumi Girls' Academy
Huh? Where's Takeo-kun?
Takeo isn't here.
There's something I'd like to ask you.
Listen, Yamato-san...
You're hiding something
from Takeo, aren't you?
Huh?
Takeo's noticed.
He knows you're hiding something.
But because he doesn't know what
it is, he's worried sick about it.
Takeo-kun...
Tell me!
You're having a hard
time telling Takeo, right?
I won't say a word about it to him.
Sure, you will.
I want Takeo to be happy!
I need him to be happy!
Of course...
Takeo-kun is a good person.
But me? To be honest...
I'm not the good person
Takeo-kun thinks I am!
I KNEW IT
What do you mean?
Takeo-kun has really nice skin.
Yeah.
He goes to sleep early and wakes up early.
He's got great skin.
And his eyebrows and sideburns really get to me!
Yeah, they're so wild.
And his broad shoulders and nice pecs...
They've got great form, right?
They're so muscular.
And his lips are so sexy!
He's the Hollywood type!
You don't find many of them in Japan!
His hands are so big, too.
They make my heart race!
Yeah, I know!
They're very sexy!
But Takeo-kun says
he won't lay a finger on me until I grow up.
Takeo-kun seems to think that
I'm really pure and stuff,
but I'm not...
I really want to cuddle,
and hold hands, and stuff.
When I'm with him,
I have impure thoughts.
But how can I tell him that?
If I did, he'd stop liking me.
I mean, he'd definitely back off...
Even if that's the case, I'll be fine.
It's more important to me that
Yamato's in knots about it.
What are you talking about?!
Listen, Takeo isn't that fragile!
He wouldn't back away, just because
of something like that!
He's the kind of man who'll try to accept
you head-on, no matter what!
He's dense and trusting,
so I don't blame you for misreading him,
but Takeo told me...
He said, "If Yamato won't tell me,
I won't have a clue."
But he also said he'd help,
if only you'd tell him!
I...
I'll go over to his place right now!
Go now...
It'll be fine.
Thank you.
You're a good person!
Takeo's girlfriend is a nice girl.
They're happy together.
I'm happy for Takeo...
Why did you fall for Takeo?
Remember the Growing Child statue
in the elementary-school yard?
Growing Child
Yeah, the creepy one.
I was tall and skinny,
so guys started saying I looked like the statue,
and gave me the nickname "Growing Statue."
It did a number on my self-confidence as a girl.
But when I was in sixth grade,
Takeo, who was in third grade at the time...
Takeo, you're done with practice?
Yeah.
You can have half.
You must be thirsty.
You remind me of something.
Yeah, the statue, right?
Nope.
It's that thing in the flower shop...
I don't know what it's called,
but you remind me of that flower.
Huh?
I'm that pretty?
Yeah.
That's it?
That's it!
It might seem like nothing special
to others, but it's special to you!
That's what it's like to fall in love.
Why didn't you tell him?
How could I?!
We were three grades apart
in elementary school!
When I was a first-year in high school,
he was a first-year in junior high!
Junior high!
I never thought he'd start dating someone!
Of course he would.
He's cool.
I know...
But I was hoping it'd at least
take him until college!
But age difference?
You just said he isn't the type
to worry about something like that.
Let's go home.
What are you doing, Takeo?
Oh, hey.
The cat was having trouble getting out of a tree.
Yamato-san's headed for your place.
She was crying.
Yamato...
was crying?
You know,
I guess I was trying too hard to hide my feelings.
I wasn't trying hard enough to win Takeo over.
If I'd told him,
maybe he would've run that fast for me, too.
He would've.
I'm so jealous!
I wish I'd been born a man!
You're lucky!
You can stay friends with him forever!
What a pain-in-the-butt sister...
I'm a fast runner.
Even though I was in the judo club,
I came in first three years in a row
in my junior high school's marathon,
beating track and field, soccer,
and basketball guys.
I have endurance, too.
I'm glad I'm a fast runner.
I'm glad I can run for a long time.
Yamato!
Takeo-kun?
Sweat
Tears
Suna said you were crying.
You stopped?
You ran all the way here for me, Takeo-kun...
Yeah.
Yamato,
you've been troubled by something, right?
Tell me!
Tell me everything you're thinking about.
Hit me with all you've got!
I won't keel over, no matter what.
And laugh!
I love seeing you laugh!
Takeo-kun...
I want to hold hands with you.
And sometimes...
I do want to snuggle and stuff...
I'm sorry I'm not as pure a
girl as you thought I was.
Is there anything else you'd like to do?
M-Maybe I'd like to walk with
you like this for a bit.
Okay!
Maybe we can go to a nearby park.
Okay.
I'm so nervous!
My hand's sweating a ton!
Me, too.
Yamato,
am I correct in thinking that
if I want to hold your hand,
I don't need to hold back?
Yeah.
Then don't hold back, either, Yamato.
Okay.
She's a nice person.
She's a very nice person!
Then what do you like
about Yamato-san, Takeo?
She's pure-hearted.
Um, Takeo-kun...
Remember how, the day after we met,
I went over to your place?
I know I said I'd asked around at the station,
but I lied.
Actually, I knew from your uniform that
you went to Shuuei High School,
so I went there and asked around.
And about how I forgot my cell in your room...
That was on purpose, too.
It was?
I thought I wouldn't see you again
if I didn't have a reason, so...
I just had to see you again.
You said I was a good person, but...
I'm sorry for lying.
I see...
I had no idea.
Shuuei
She went through a lot of trouble to see me.
Thank you, Yamato.
I'm glad!
I'm so happy you said that!
I was scared that if I told you the truth,
you wouldn't like me anymore!
Now that I'm relieved, I guess I'm crying...
Sorry.
Why?
When I got out of the fire,
I swore a vow to myself
that I'd never make you cry again.
But I...
This is different!
These are happy tears.
So you can't count them!
Think you can go to sleep smiling tonight?
Um...
I'll probably be grinning ear to ear.
I see...
I'm glad.
I'm really glad.
Are you sure you're okay with all this?
Yeah.
You don't have to rush back, you know.
This was for the best.
I now know that Takeo's a happy man.
I wouldn't want him to see
me like this, anyway...
Takeo-kun, the stars are beautiful today!
Subject: Shooting Star
I saw my first-ever shooting star!
I just happened to be thinking about you,
so I made a wish that I could
stay with you forever.
By then, the star had already gone,
but maybe I made my wish in time?
You sure did.
Don't worry, Yamato.
Suna,
I'm coming in.
I have a favor to ask.
What's that?
Let me kiss you.
Huh?
I held hands with Yamato today,
but I kind of failed at it.
How the hell do you fail at holding hands?
Don't sweat the details!
When we kiss, I wouldn't want
my teeth to hit hers.
Let me practice...
Why don't you practice with a pillow—
I already tried that!
I just can't get a good sense
of distance with a pillow.
I need a person!
Try someone else.
That'd be an insult to Yamato!
You're good at keeping secrets.
I can't think of anyone else I can ask!
Quit it. It's gross.
It'll be fine.
I brought plastic wrap.
Stop, you're crossing a line...
If we use this between, there's no problem.
Dude, it's a huge problem—
I'm resolved to do this!
You should be, too,
if you call yourself a man!
Dude, there's something wrong
with your logic for sure...
Don't worry, Yamato.
I'll become a man you can depend on.
Congratulations on Our First Hand-Holding
From now on, go to sleep
with a smile on your face!
My Strength
Next time: My Strength.