Things get WEIRD in 5 seconds
So soft...
C-Cups...
I...It's...
G...H...no, I-cups!
I admit defeat.
Die! Burn for eternity in the flames of hell!
I-cups...
The next day
I can't focus...probably
because I skipped breakfast...
Micchan...
Can't you appear NORMALLY
like the rest of us?!
Check out this ad I found.
The Vibe-Shape Belt II?!
Vibe-Shape Belt II!
The wildly successful "Vibe-Shape
Belt" has been powered up!
3000 rotations per minute
Now with a rotational speed
of 3000 cycles per minute,
High-Speed Vibration
this is true high-speed vibration technology!
Excess fat...
Before                                             After
Results may vary
Melts away!
Just 10 minutes a day!
For a beautiful, tight stomach!
The amazing new fitness machine,
the Vibe-Shape Belt II!
Limited time
Special price!
"Vibe-Shape" search
Now on sale for a limited time only.
Version II...on sale...
That's not cheap at all!
I...I don't want that thing!
Yes I do.
Jackpot!
Stupid Sugisaki
Aah...my abs...my abs...they're
getting tighter...
I'll...use dad's phone when I get home...
I left my phone on my desk,
it was right here!
Someone stole it.
If anyone looks at my stuff I'll...I'll kill 'em!
I didn't mean to steal it...
Uh oh, where did I put it?
I had it right up against my stomach!
Try calling it, maybe it
fell under something.
G-Good thinking.
Lemme borrow your phone, Yabecchi.
Okay.
It's on my back!
What's so funny?
Your stupid face!
Mitsuba! It was Mitsuba!
Calm down.
You're hiding it somewhere! Give it back!
Let go!
I'll help.
Body exam, body exam!
H-Hey!
Let's see...
So soft...
F-Futaba?
What'd she do?
Futaba got KO'ed...
Look!
She's euphoric!
She got hit with some kind
of super-erotic attack!
Very well...
Hit me with your best shot, Eldest!
Nooooooooo!
Wh-What'd you do to them?!
I'll never tell.
I want to feel your technique too!
Not in a million years!
How come? I wanna see!
Do it to me!
No.
But I wanna end up like that too...
"That?" Meaning what?
All...satisfied...
I want you to satisfy me too!
You perverted whack-job!
Please? Don't be stingy...
Pervert pervert pervert!
What about the phone?
Mitsudomoe...!
Do you have this in one size bigger?
I'm afraid that's the only size we've got...
Ooh, this dress is adorable!
Shoot, it's too big for me...oh well.
Why hello there, Mitsuba-san!
Freaking stalker...popping
in out of nowhere...
It's that crazy girl!
Are you Mitsuba-chan?
Excuse me?
You exist!
Mom!
Mom?
Miku-chan's always going on and
on about you, Mitsuba-chan.
I've always wanted to meet you!
She tells me you're a twisted dominatrix
who hands out a constant
torrent of indiscriminate abuse
to everyone you meet!
It's true!
You're just what I pictured...
Don't touch her, mom!
Yeah, she's a nympho! She'll touch
your breasts and stuff!
I'd love to see your dominant
personality in action!
What's with this lady?
I'm not sure why...but she's pissing me off!
Pissing me off
Help me try these on.
Eww, no way!
Mitsuba-chan...Mitsuba-chan!
Mitsuba-sama?
Sh-Shut up!
I knew it, you don't acknowledge people
who don't call you "Mitsuba-sama!"
Just like I thought!
Would you like to dominate me a little?
No thanks!
What're you out shopping for today?
Whips?
Oh my god, I don't need to buy any whips!
I'm here for clothes!
Of course...a true domme can
make use of anything...
What'd you say?
What else do you use?
What do you do?
Trampling? Do you want to step on me?
U-Uhh...
She has some seriously messed
up ideas about me...
Aren't you going to punish me?
It always sounds like being
on the receiving end of your
anger is so much fun!
I, uh...don't even know you, so...
Oh no!
Just look at me, I'm sure there's
plenty to disparage, no?
No...there isn't!
Come now...
Use that sharp tongue to cut my
poor little heart to ribbons!
Insult me, abuse me!
Come on...please!
Do it...do it!
Mom...
Mom gets curious about
the weirdest things!
I never should've told her about Mitsuba...
Hurry up and change!
If I don't do something Mitsuba
will get all full of herself and
turn Mom into her slave!
Oh, I'll abuse you all right, you
worthless, messed-up freak!
Mom!
What's a slave?
Be quiet!
It means she'll do whatever Mitsuba says.
Hey, zip me up.
Forget it.
I'm not your slave!
That's not being a slave!
Lemme go!
I'm a free boy!
What is it, what's wrong?
I don't wanna be your slave!
H-Hey!
Stop it! Stop trying to make me your slave!
Ahh...there IS something.
You raised your kids to be a pair
of snotty brainless dooooofuses,
you worthless excuse for a mother!
You are the lamest, stupidest family in
the universe and you should all die!
She cut my poor heart...into ribbons.
Why didn't you deny any of it?!
Check it!
My mom bought it for me.
Nice.
Now we match.
Stop ignoring me!
That's Sugisaki-san's younger brother...
Hey, you're not wearing yours!
Not wearing "yours?" As in panties?
My sister ruined it.
The loudmouth one?
I'll never forgive her...I'll curse
her for the rest of eternity.
With her, I'd believe it...
Aww, that stinks you're not wearing yours!
Whoa, not so loud!
Who're you?
Sensei...
Were you listening?
S-Sorry...
Man, you can't let that dope
get away with this.
I saved my allowance for so long, too...
Your allowance?
She has to scrimp just to afford
a pair of underpants?
I...treasured every moment...
Hitoha-chan...
At this rate I'm gonna get in trouble!
Hang on a second!
Sensei...is he going to get me a belt?
Who is he?
My sensei, he loves the Gachi Rangers too.
He's an adult, he needs to grow up!
What a lame-o.
No...
One does not "grow up" from loving justice.
One does not "grow up..."
You can have my belt!
I couldn't...
We've got plenty of money,
I, umm...my Gachi-level's a million
times higher than yours,
I can live without the belt!
Gachi-level...?
Shut up!
I didn't say...
Hey, I'm back from the store!
Here.
Umm...I...
You can wear that.
I'm all right now.
I'm sure it'll look good on you.
Look...good?
I look goooooood.
I...
I'm not into that kinda stuff!
Why do you have to make fun of me!
It took all my courage to buy this!
He's...outgrown...the Gachi Rangers!
Mitsudomoe...!
Serious Squad, Gachi Rangers!
Shine!
Take flight!
Now YOU can take monsters down too!
The Serious Squad Gachi Rangers
Deluxe Gachi-Belt!
Second one she got from Ryuuta
I will destroy all monsters!
Micchan Micchan!
What?
What's your problem?
You're acting like a little kid.
She's immune...
A Gachi-belt! Did Ryuuta-kun
give you that one?
Cool, it's got a secret weapon!
She's immune...
Mitsudomoe...
Another day with no serious injuries,
thank goodness.
I heard there've been some weird people
hanging around here lately.
They'll probably come after me
first, I'd better stay alert!
Yeah, you're the type who
gets killed off first...
because you're a nobody!
Wh-
Please don't talk about murderers, okay?
Sh-She's covered in blood!
This is it...this is why I've
spent so many days
training relentlessly...
to create this technique.
Healing Rolling!
She's gonna wrap her in bandages
Go, go, go!
Micchan!
What was that?
Her special move?
Are you all right?
Oh no...I'll take her to the nurse's room!
Oh-umm-
She's a pain in the butt anyway, leave her.
But...
Nurse
I...can't move...
I'm tied up...where am I?
What happened?
I heard there've been some weird people
hanging around here lately.
Kidnappers!?
They're gonna sell me somewhere overseas!
At a high price!
That's right, Sugisaki and the
others were with me,
are they in here too?
They've gotta be tied up
somewhere near me.
Over here?
Maybe...
What'd I fall off of...a bed?
It did feel kinda soft...
I don't hear anyone...maybe
the kidnappers left?
I've gotta escape before they come back!
And I'll save Sugisaki's group if I can.
That would be a wall...
What's that...
Fur?!
Wild dogs!
Go away! I taste terrible! Shoo!
Oww...
Looks like that scared the dogs away...
But they could come back any time...
I've gotta get outta here!
What'd I hit this time?
The kidnapper!
He's back!
"Stop! Please don't hurt me!"
"I'm worth more unharmed!"
What happened...did he fall?
Is he knocked out?
Now's my chance!
Where's Sugisaki?
Another room? I hope she's safe...
Someone's coming...
There's more than one of them.
I've gotta hide!
What...
I'm sorry I forgot my stuff.
I wish you'd noticed a little faster!
Settle down...
Someone help!
They killed Sugisaki!
L-L-Let me go!
Murderer!
She's still tied up...
Oh thank god you're alive!
Anyway, it's a good thing you weren't hurt.
Just tie me back up...
Mitsuba-chan?
Why are you in the preview too?
You haven't abused me nearly enough yet!
Call me a crusty old hag,
tell me I stink like a slug,
Episode 12
It won't reach you
let me have it!
Please...no more!