Gravity wave interferometer has
detected a strong fluctuation.
It's beginning.
The space-time merger...
All of Aura's energy must
be getting funneled into
the space-time merger,
such that no one can use Mana.
We have estimated the
space-time merger perimeter
distribution based on
lepton radiation intensities.
What is the estimated epicenter
of the space-time merger?
The Dawn Pillar, in the Misurugi region.
When the two Earths combine,
everything will be destroyed.
All will die.
We must take back Aura,
no matter the cost, before that happens.
Hilda.
Are you still waiting for Ange?
Of course not.
There won't be a world to
wreck if the Earth is gone.
Let's go, Dragon Princess.
We're going to be your allies.
Aurora, full speed ahead.
Our target is the Dawn Pillar.
Incoming communication.
Switching to speakers.
Aurora? Can you hear?
Ange here.
I'm returning now.
Aurora, respond.
The Warped World
Ange!
Welcome back!
I'm home, everyone.
Dammit! Where the hell were you?!
Isn't this Vanessa's machine?
Yeah. Mom's Arquebus.
So it can still fly.
Momoka-san.
You were safe.
Officer.
You quit drinking?
This is no time to be drinking.
I'm going to join Libertus.
I know the truth about humans and Mana now.
It's...
Ersha came back.
She said she woke up.
She did, huh?
You're the only one that
doesn't know anything, Ange.
Salako.
The People of Aura
have allied with the Norma.
What will you do?
I don't mind joining.
The time's finally come
for us to fight together.
To protect our worlds.
No, Salako.
I just don't want that pervert
to have his way with the world.
Riza.
I heard from Momoka.
You told them where I was, didn't you?
We're going to be busy.
We have to kill that man.
Angelise-sama.
Hilda.
Where's the commander?
I'm the commander now.
Then what about Jill?
I'm glad you've come back.
Yes, thanks to everyone.
So, are you here to mock me?
You're aware you did something
that warrants mockery, are you?
Well, I guess you couldn't tell
anyone that Embryo raped you.
Are you here to pick a fight?
There's something I want to ask you.
Tell me how to kill Embryo.
What?
Every time he dies,
he switches places with a multiplex
entity in undefined space.
Tusk told me.
You said the Villkiss is the only thing
that can defeat Embryo, didn't you?
Somewhere in undefined
space is his true body.
I couldn't make it there, but you
learned the song and released the Villkiss.
I see, okay.
So what about you?
Are you going to just hide here?
I gave command to Hilda.
Quit being a chump!
How many people were screwed
over for the sake of your revenge?
What could I do?
I failed both my revolution and my revenge.
It was Salia that let me go.
She was miserable.
She's chosen to obsess over
Embryo to forget about you.
I'm not letting you say you're not responsible.
Alektra Maria von Loewenherz.
Damn.
You're scary.
It's just that I can't allow her to
run away from her responsibilities.
So you have changed.
Huh?
You, the old Commander,
and the Dragon Princess.
You're born leaders.
You don't even have to say anything
to get someone to follow you.
Hey, you should be the commander.
What?
You're used to being above people,
aren't you, Burn Princess?
I don't mind, but...
I'm better off charging around with a gun.
What are you sulking about, Hilda?
I-I'm not sulking.
If you have something to say, just say it.
Hilda.
You'll hate me if I do.
Huh?
Ange...
You're my prince.
Huh?
But you already have a
friend that's a princess.
And you have a man.
I know.
It's weird, isn't it? We're both women.
The world's about to end, and I'm...
Who says it's weird?
That's the ridiculous world we're
going to destroy together, isn't it?
I'll need you in the new world, too, Hilda.
Ange.
Everyone, retreat!
Retreat to the Tower of Aura!
This is for royalty only!
Just let me on!
The destruction of the old
world is proceeding smoothly.
I need you all to protect Aura until
the space-time merger is complete.
Got it?
Yes, master.
I heard from Sala-san earlier.
Aura and Aurora both
mean "light" in the old language.
Yeah?
Bring light back into a
world shrouded by darkness.
Let's get home alive, Ange.
I promise to protect you.
You keep protecting me.
Is there anything I can do for you?
As long as you're safe, that's good enough.
Don't give me that.
Then, uh, maybe you can
give me a good luck charm
of some kind or something.
I don't really have anything.
Look away.
Got it?
Okay.
This is the best I can do.
It's warm.
No looking!
No pulling it out!
No checking!
Bring it back, got it?
Or I'll catch a cold.
It's not...
I'll have to give it back to her.
Enemy fleet acquired.
Everyone, can you hear?
I'm Captain General Ange.
We're going to attack the Empire of Misurugi.
We'll charge into the Dawn Pillar
to stop the space-time merger.
We Norma, so-called anti-social monsters,
and their enemies, the People of Aura...
Those who follow us,
and the Ancient People...
Isn't it wonderful that
after suffering so much,
we can join forces to save the world?
Let's fight.
So that we can one day live our own lives!
It wouldn't be like us to
go down without a fight.
This is Operation Last Libertus.
Whether he's God or anything else,
we'll kill him, win, and survive.
All of us.
Launch cryo torpedoes!
This one's on me.
Fire all missiles!
Roger. Fire all missiles!
Oh?
We are approaching Misurugi's coast.
Switch all systems in aviation mode.
Set engine output to 80%.
Yes, ma'am.
Deploy quantum field.
Deploying quantum field.
A frontal assault.
How violent.
Ange, they're coming!
All Para-mail units, sortie!
Yes, ma'am!
All units, release arresting gear.
Ange, Salamandinay, ignite and lift off.
Hilda, Vivian, ignite and lift off.
Sink!
Ange?
Let us move out, too.
Dawn Pillar approaching firing range.
Charge cryo beam!
Prepare to fire!
Roger. Cryo beam, prepare to fire!
Enemy spotted forward of Dawn Pillar!
Embryo.
Sink with the old world.
Sing, sing, the two wishes are now,
Strongly, strongly shining in heavenly gold,
It's...
He's after the Aurora.
Charge status?
74%.
It speaks of eternity.
Ange.
Energy charge at 98%.
N-Type Cryo Beam Destroyer Cannon, fire!
Firing N-Type Cold Beam Destroyer Cannon!
Help!
That's the main shaft that leads to Aura!
All units, follow me!
Yes, ma'am!
When did she find such a thing?
Embryo-kun, she's coming.
Hm?
Troops, intercept them.
Yes, master.
Salia, you understand, correct?
Yes.
Princess, to Aura!
You're back again?
Chris!
I'm taking you, if nothing else!
Rosalie!
Welcome back, Ange.
It seems you were
destined to reunite with me.
Embryo.
Go, Ange! To Aura!
Got it.
Oh? You were alive.
Ange's knight is invincible!
Salako!
I've been waiting for you, Ange.
Salia.
Nonna!
All right.
Onee-sama!
Are you hurt?
Jill.
Sorry to show you such a pathetic sight.
I'm going.
To achieve our Libertus.
Jasmine, open the launch deck.
You're going?
Yeah.
Releasing upper hatch.
Air traffic controllers evacuate.
I haven't forgiven you.
So you better listen to
me rant when you get back.
Alektra, moving out.
Jill, ignite and lift off.
Damn, Commander!
I'm in a hurry here!
Hey, Ange, what do you
think the new world will be like?
It's a world where you don't exist!
Embryo-ojisama...
What a sad child.
It was Julio that
killed your father, and yet...
There! Princess Sylvia!
Sylvia-sama, help us!
Aren't there shelters and escape ships here?
We didn't get any warning
from the government!
I don't know anything about that.
Why didn't you royals do anything?
Do something!
I did nothing wrong! Go away!
Dammit, Salia.
Onee-sama.
Sylvia.
It's Angelise.
Help us!
Yeah, take us with you!
Help? Me?
Why?
Isn't it your duty as
royalty to save your people?
It's you Normas that did this, isn't it?
Don't you care if we die?
Nope.
What?
I don't care.
At all.
Selfish pigs.
That's why Embryo can control you.
You'd better run while you can, too.
You know I can't walk, don't you?
It's you that made it so that I can't walk!
Quit being a baby.
You blame everything on others.
The imperial doctor told me
your wounds were fully healed.
You can't stand on your own
because you won't even try.
Help me! Help me, please!
I'm your sister!
Do you need to die to fix
that rotten attitude of yours?
No!
Fight!
Live on your own!
We'll never meet again.
Goodbye, my only sister.
Onee-sama...
You're late, Ange.
I was taking care of some errands.
Then you're prepared to die!
I heard you're Embryo's knight.
I wanted to see how strong you've become.
But I'm disappointed, Salia.
Next Episode
Ersha's back!
I'll do anything to atone, so...
Buy me yakisoba bread!
So... so just let me read the preview!
Ersha's Headbutt of Hell!
Ow.
A Battle With No Tomorrow
Sorry, Vivi-chan.
Next week, on Cross Ange...