I've never found this world fun.
Not even once.
In the end, I'll never hold anything in my hand.
Apparently, they've attacked again.
Are you scared?
Of course not. I do not fear them.
Your voice is wavering slightly.
Don't worry. There's still time.
Globe succeeded in intercepting the
Kiltgang's advance again, didn't they?
Everything is in your hands.
I know that.
I was just surprised to hear
that two of them attacked.
They've entered an Orgonic-oscillation state...
An excess of Orgone energy has shorted
out the Neural Maneuver System.
During trials, they performed better than expected.
I was able to move the manipulators
and engines like my own limbs.
You were pretty rough on them...
The R&D Chief is gonna cry.
We got a little carried away.
How long is it going to take?
To fix them?
What do you think?
At best, two weeks...
Two weeks.
I'm sick of waiting.
Yup.
We still have Setsuna's capsule.
It's only our Machine Goodfellows that won't work.
Then we'll go with Plan B!
Other than ours, all the Machine
Goodfellows are in here.
And Puck's given us the data for the other five.
Let's go and see some old familiar faces.
Sign From the Dark
We've just arrived in Odaiba.
Yes, they're getting ready now.
There will be a high-density libido
event in Odaiba tomorrow?
That's what Pitz says.
Why aren't they acting sooner?
Most likely, they can't.
Alonzo's action-prediction simulation
reached the same conclusion I did.
During the Kanda incident, development of
eight Machine Goodfellows was confirmed.
And the Machine Goodfellow Aramusha
had a man-machine interface
that only Teppei could use.
Amarok and Malkin...
Their Machine Goodfellows were
most likely disabled during the last battle.
Interesting...
If we analyze that, we'll probably
find all kinds of weak spots!
But if there's going to be a high-density
libido event anyway...
They may try to make contact with the other five.
Make contact...
With the other five?
Do you know anything about
the other designer children?
I don't.
I think we were all isolated from one another.
This data says there are two
men and three women...
Do they not have their Kiltgang memories?
I don't know.
But if they do what I did,
and either touch Orgone energy
or come into a certain type of contact
with another avatar who has memories,
I believe their memories will return.
A certain type of contact?
Does the enemy know where the missing five are?
They may be able to sense their general locations.
Since my Ego Block was destroyed,
I've lost that sense.
Anyway, the Earth Engine Impacter is
undergoing repairs, but thankfully,
the Ordinary still functions.
Even if the low-orbit Impacters can repel them,
Earth will sustain tremendous damage.
Your mission is to secretly stop the
others from becoming Kiltgangs.
And so, our first mission is in Odaiba, huh?
I'm coming in.
Okay.
Are you ready?
That's pretty nice.
How about the girls?
Okay!
Akari, this is a little tight.
Captain...
Are you going to keep calling me that?
If Hana's prediction is correct,
a Machine Goodfellow will appear
tonight, in this area.
If they're bringing in that huge machine,
I want to stop it before it activates.
What are you doing?
Gathering information.
Is it okay to leave the Japanese area's
independent attack force to kids like these?
I heard another team is active, too.
They can pull it off.
I'm not the type who believes in
intuition, like the commander.
But given their individual skills, I think
they're appropriate for the mission.
I found it.
This is it!
Look, this is it.
The fruit tart in the Orlando Casino's café.
That looks delicious!
Let's go here first.
Will they really be okay?
It's good!
See?
This was the right place to go, Captain.
Hey, is everyone really going
to keep calling me that?
No more bets.
Now, then... We've come all the way to a casino,
so let's use Pitz's power to make some money.
I don't think that'll work.
Pitz can only instinctively sense
the flow or presence of Orgone energy.
Oh...
Was that why we came here?
Excuse me.
Minors aren't allowed in this casino.
Well...
I told the manager we were
observing for educational purposes,
and he let us in with a smile!
I did have to give him a sizable tip, though.
Tip?
What do you mean by "tip"?
Don't worry about it, Captain.
Just leave it to Akari, and it'll be fine, Captain.
I don't see the problem, Captain.
Seriously, do you have to keep calling me that?
You guys are good friends, aren't you?
I don't have any friends, so I'm jealous.
Zin!
Sir, you can't allow minors on the floor...
They're fine!
Spend as much time observing as you like.
How much did you pay?
Anyway, Zin...
You've got a friend here to see you.
You do have a friend.
In the end, I'll never hold anything in my hand.
Naoko?
Where are Daichi and Teppei?
Looking for the Machine Goodfellow,
as we were ordered to.
Shouldn't we help?
Leave that to the boys!
If anything is nearby,
it's probably here, not in the casino.
Now, there's a coincidence.
What are you doing here, Daichi Manatsu-kun?
I think there must be some fate that ties you...
No, that ties your father and you to me.
I'll tell you something interesting.
I was the one who destroyed the Star Emblem.
In other words, I'm the one
who killed your father.
Did you know that?
Yes.
I did.
I heard gunfire!
I saw Amarok.
So they're here, after all...
Did you fire?
He escaped before I could.
If you don't shoot next time, he'll kill you, Captain.
Seriously, do you have to keep calling me that?
The Neoteny is here.
Do they know what we're doing?
Perhaps it's the princess's singularity?
One unexpected event after another...
But at least it's interesting.
You've changed, Zin.
I don't think I'm the one that's changed.
It's been about a year, hasn't it?
I'm amazed you found this place.
Someone at the facility told me.
Why did you drop out of school?
This is a nice camera, isn't it?
You don't have one, right?
I'll lend it to you.
After school, we'll have a photo shoot.
Let's see who can take a prettier photo of Naoko.
Cameras are great!
They make the whole world more fun.
That looked nice...
Let's take another.
They were nice to me, and that was enough.
Grand Prize
Setting Sun
Takao Takami
Is this the birth of a high school photographer?
That's amazing, Takao...
I had a good model.
In the end, I'll never hold anything in my hand.
At school, I never fit in.
I planned to drop out, once I found a job.
Since then, Takao says he's been a slump,
and he can't take any good photos.
Lately, he's been really angry all the time.
Hey...
Weren't you the one
who actually took that grand-prize picture?
Come on!
It was my camera you took the picture with.
Takao was the one who took that photo.
Isn't that good enough?
Then Hana's prediction was right.
It was Pitz, not me.
I'll confirm the information we have.
The target's physical age is seventeen,
the same as Teppei's.
And tonight, the Machine Goodfellow will activate.
About the same age, huh?
About the same age?
Who is it that wants to see me?
The number two man in the Asanoda Yakuza,
the de facto owners of this casino.
Please make sure not to offend him.
Come in.
You can leave.
Want a drink?
No, I'm underage.
I've heard you're quite good.
Is it true you can make a ball fall in any
pocket, even after you've shot it?
Yes.
What kind of trick is that?
I don't know.
But even after I shoot, it goes in any
pocket I want if I focus hard enough.
Then it isn't cheating...
If the dealer controls the ball,
I think that counts as cheating.
Your talent will be useful in many ways.
If you do what I tell you,
I'll make it worth your while.
Your world will be a lot more fun.
Cameras are great!
They make the whole world more fun.
Come on!
It was my camera you took the picture with.
But it won't be your talent that makes money.
It'll be this casino!
You, and the money you make,
will belong to the Asanoda.
Don't forget that.
It doesn't matter where I am.
Nothing will ever change.
Hi, there.
Who the hell are you?!
Malkin and Amarok...
Good morning, Zimbalt.
How does it feel to be the real you again?
The real me...
The world is about to get a lot more fun.
I feel wonderful.
You know how to control it, don't you, Zimbalt?
Thanks to Moco's telepathic kiss,
it's all in my head.
I'm totally awake.
Abreaction.
MM bus signal detected.
Calculating epicenter of Machine
Goodfellow activation.
The pier next to us!
Activating catapult launch sequence.
Captain, are you ready?
Go.
Earth Engine Ordinary... Go!
Zimbalt, they've seen you!
The enemy mobile weapon is coming.
Escape before the time limit.
Escape?
I'm back to the real me, and I feel wonderful.
Why should I run?
Is the Kiltgang coming?
Right now, there's nothing I can't hold in my hand!
I only need to kill him, right?
Sheesh...
Captain, aim for real!
I am!
I'm counting on you, Brute Force Attacker-chan.
What's that?
A secret weapon.
Here it is!
That dealer was the designer child?
What's this?
This countdown...
I get it!
Earth Engine, can you hear me?
It will take time for them to charge the
energy, and send it to the Kiltgang.
You have a minute and eighteen seconds!
Our system is being hacked!
The Machine Goodfellow is being hacked?
I can keep going, right?
Here, this is it!
Captain, the Orgone energy capsule is in the neck.
That's its weak spot?
Roger!
What's going on?
The avionics went down.
Be careful.
Our system is being hacked!
It doesn't matter what they do.
They can't stop me anymore!
Wow!
Is that his singularity?
I can feel the Orgone energy coursing through me.
I feel like I can do anything!
You aren't the only ones
that can use Orgone energy!
I see...
You're a Neoteny, aren't you?
Our first time, and we're already
cutting it this close?
We're a team,
but I'm the only one who isn't helping.
Can you hear me?
Mission complete.
Good work, Captain.
Can you please stop calling me that?
We encountered and fought a Machine
Goodfellow at Odaiba pier #2.
Code 03, requesting cleanup.
Over.
This is Tanegashima.
Roger.
Code 03, cleanup.
I'd forgotten that he was a Neoteny.
You got too excited, Zimbalt.
That was pathetic.
Yeah, it's pathetic that our Machine
Goodfellow got hacked...
Looks like we've got a nuisance
of a script kiddie on our hands.
They're pissing me off.
I'll devour the libidos of everyone on this planet.
We are the real humans.
I feel like I've awakened from a dream.
I'm grateful to you.
I'm special. I can hold anything I want in my hand.
They're right...
The world really is fun.
Thanks to my magic,
we managed to analyze part of the enemy
Machine Goodfellow's systems.
The Planetary Gears don't like that,
so they try to kidnap me.
And a new Machine Goodfellow
appears in Shinjuku.
Next time, on episode 9 of Captain Earth:
Magical Girl Akari-chan
Magical Girl Akari-chan.
Logical, logical!
See you next week.