The enemy's strategy
is simple in the extreme.
Use the shockwave from the Landing Castle
impact to clear out the area,
which both eliminates our own forces
and gives them a beachhead.
However, we have been making plans
for this attack for the past 15 years!
We will combine
all our forces
and we will surround and annihilate the enemy
before they can deploy any ground troops.
Dismissed!
So that's...
a Martian Landing Castle!
Neutralize them!
Dickhead!
Enemy missiles!
Intercept! RAM!
No, hold on...
Undersea cables Southern Cross,
Concerto 1 severed!
Miami Landing Station
has gone silent!
What about comm satellites?!
They're under attack from the
Landing Castles still in orbit!
Comm links to U.E. HQ and
branch offices are down!
Alpha Leader to all planes.
Will now begin attack.
What?!
The fighter squadron was...
One enemy reading detected.
Silver 22!
Jamming, huh?
Lead Silver Squad appears to
have encountered the enemy.
All units, deploy.
Attack at will.
That's it?
Commander!
Stupid primitives.
Bow down before the
might of the gods.
Swear allegiance or be annihilated.
You have but two choices.
Pathetic...
How can this be happening?!
Those are Martian Kataphrakts!
We can't possibly beat these guys...
We're insects to them.
We're no more than insects...
Child's play.
Count Cruhteo.
We should begin our advance
on Shinawara right away.
If we plant our flag at the scene
of Her Highness' tragic death,
it will solidify the righteousness
of Vers' cause.
Indeed. I had intended
to do so all along.
However, the more pressing matter
at hand is securing the drop site.
In that case, Count Cruhteo,
please allow me that honor.
This is the perfect opportunity to repay you for allowing me
to impose on your hospitality these many years.
Then I shall delegate the
task to you, Trillram.
Apprehend this area's leaders and learn the
details surrounding Her Highness' death.
Yes, Milord!
This is a special report.
Moments ago, major cities around the world came
under attack by Mars' Vers Imperial Forces.
Due to a communication network
disturbance of unknown origin
the extent of the damage to these
cities is unclear at this time...
We have more than enough seats.
Move in an orderly fashion.
Citizens of Shinawara City, an
evacuation advisory is in effect.
Is there anyone here
who has not left yet?
Tell me...
We will be happy to take the infirm
or elderly to the ferry pier.
Why were we roped
into doing this?
We had to, they're shorthanded.
And I can't say no to Inko.
I'll take helping out the
student council any day.
The fighting's ramping up.
Are we gonna get drafted someday?
No way. You're not put in the Reserves
until after you graduate high school, right?
Well, maybe if the fighting drags on
and there's a shortage of troops...
Inko. Family spotted
at 10 o'clock.
Dude, seriously?
Fucking Martians...
Like I said, we got put on standby,
so I can't leave.
I thought the plan was to
leave town in your car, Yuki.
Wait, don't tell me you're
still at our house, Nao!
Why didn't you evacuate
with everyone else?
Oh, right, I could have
done that...
Make decisions as circumstances dictate!
If you have to, trust your gut and make the call!
Isn't that always
my advice to you?
Penivia...
What?
Never mind. I'll get a lift from one of
the transports that are patrolling the area.
Be careful.
You, too.
Excuse me.
You really should
flee the area.
An evacuation advisory is in effect
for the entire Shinawara area.
Are you tourists?
Do you speak—
My apologies.
Ah, you do understand me.
Yes, thank you for
your kindness.
Meaning no disrespect, of course, but might I
ask you a few questions while I have you like this?
Be my guest.
What is this
"evacuation advisory"?
They say that Tokyo has fallen
because of the Martian attack.
This area is in danger, too.
We wish to go to the proper authorities
and inform our people that we are safe.
Your embassy, you mean?
Given the situation,
I don't think they're open.
Ever since the assassination of the Vers
crown princess yesterday, the U.E. has—
Princess Asseylum is—
She is alive. She did not
take part in the parade.
The unaccustomed gravity
of Earth made her feel ill,
and so a double
took her place...
I know how she feels...
That's a novel hypothesis.
A transport will be here soon.
I texted Inko earlier.
You're welcome to join me.
Slaine Troyard... To think that
you will be acting as my pilot.
I was ordered to do so
by Count Cruhteo.
No matter. Just don't
get underfoot, Terran.
You're a lifesaver! I can't belive my
car picked now to run out of gas.
I expect some gratitude, Doctor.
You, too, Inaho.
Sure.
Don't casually
ditch us like that.
Still...
Are they Russian? Northern European?
Don't see many of those in Shinawara.
I don't mind one bit!
Always happy to see a babe! She's a 10!
Thanks.
Boys...
A KG-7 Areion!
What are you people doing?!
The evacuation here is supposed to be finished!
That voice...
Is that you, Yuki?
Inko?! If you're here,
does that mean Nao is, too?
Oh, for the love of... Why?
Hey, if the Kataphrakt squad
has been mobilized,
does that mean the enemy's
on its way to Shinawara?
That's right. High-temperature thermal signatures
are headed this way from Tokyo.
This area is a projected
combat zone! Turn around!
But we have to go through here
to reach the ferry pier!
Whatever! Just find a safe place
and hunker down!
We'll hold them off!
Inaho...
Enemy fighter formation
approaching from 1 o'clock!
So, they've turned up
to die for nothing.
As they wish.
First, a warning.
Target merge.
Now attacking.
All missiles, direct hit!
E-Enemy is intact!
It's unscathed!
Scum...
Slaine.
Milord?
Oh, dear... This boy's upbringing
is sorely lacking, Count Cruhteo!
No matter. I shall take it upon myself
to educate you in the joys of the battlefield!
It's started...
Message from HQ!
Fighter squadron has encountered
enemy flying vehicle!
Currently engaging!
What's wrong?
Our comms reception is bad.
We're being jammed.
They're using powerful EM waves
to disrupt our chain of command.
Just like 15 years ago.
It's one of their tricks.
Like you saw anything
15 years ago, you fraud...
Crap! He's on my 6!
Moving to assist!
What the—?
There is no beauty in the struggle if one
is unaware that one is about to die.
Well, Slaine?
How does it feel to watch from on high
as your former countrymen die so pathetically?
Fighter squadron... wiped out.
Enemy flying vehicle is continuing
its advance towards Shinawara.
Let's hurry.
That's our ride.
Yeah.
And now, as per our agreement, we'll return home
to our motherland of Vers and be knighted.
It's been a difficult mission,
hasn't it, Rayet?
No, Father.
We are above the target area.
All right, set me down.
Yes, Milord.
Nilokeras, disconnect.
Here he comes.
Sir Trillram! We have
awaited your arrival!
Congratulations on completing
this important mission.
It's... the light of Aldnoah!
And now, farewell,
my good rats!
We mustn't have you squeaking at an
inopportune time in the future, you see.
What have we here?
If it isn't an adorable baby rat!
You won't escape me!
Enemy Kataphrakt spotted!
Bastard... It's attacking a civilian!
Commence attack.
We'll make quick work of him.
Keep laser comms open.
Maintain coordination.
But, sir!
I said, commence attack! Fire!
Cease fire! Assisting the
civilian has priority!
What the hell?
Our shells, they aren't—
Warrant Officer Kaizuka!
Secure the survivor. I'll cover you!
Roger!
Lt. Marito!
This is my platoon!
Don't go around
issuing orders!
What are they playing at?
Go!
Get in!
Civilian secured!
Grenades!
I told you not to give orders!
What the hell is the deal
with that thing's body?!
Stay calm!
Cut loose with
everything you have!
What in the world?
The meddlers have been dealt with.
Now, back to my rat problem...
Run, Kaizuka!
Lt. Marito!
Die with cowardice,
or die with foolhardy valor?
Do you think you are making
a noble choice here?
A pity.
Lt. Marito!
HQ, come in! HQ!
Is it just me, or have we been
driving around in circles?
What else do you
expect me to do?!
This is Warrant Officer Kaizuka.
Do you copy?
Yuki?!
Take this girl aboard
and gun it!
Warrant Kaizuka! What's going on?!
Hop to it!
Sergeant!
Old man!
Don't give me any
more trouble, little rat!
Inko! Go faster!
I'm trying!
He's gonna catch up!
We're too heavy!
Brake.
Slam on the brakes.
Come again?
Hurry. Brake!
Now hit the gas!
Right!
Stand still!
Okojo!
We have to save Yuki!
Damn it, it's too dangerous!
Sorry!
I'm fine!
Now leave him in the dust!
Inaho!
Inaho...
Need a hand?
Okisuke...
I toyed with them too long, eh?
Good job.
We're safe now, you two!
He isn't follow—
Hey, Inaho.
Where's Okojo?
No way...
Warrant Officer Kaizuka,
this is Marito.
Do you copy?
Instructor Marito...
Kaizuka!
Listen close. That Martian
is following you.
He hasn't attacked
the ferry pier yet.
Draw him away as best you can.
But don't be a hero.
Make it back in one piece.
Inaho?
He says that that guy
is still following us.
But we might be able to buy time for
the ferry with the refugees to leave port.
If we act as decoys.
Whoa, what are you saying?
If we take the utility tunnels,
we can reach the school from here.
And do what?!
There are trainers in the hangar.
And live-fire training rounds.
Come on, man...
Let's fight. Yuki and the
others tried, now it's our turn.
Let's fight that
Martian Kataphrakt.