The High School National Ogura Hundred
Poets Karuta Championship begins.
We'll win every match
and become number one in Japan!
Chihaya Furu
Verse 8
Which
shines
over
Mount
Mikasa
Wh-Why am I dressed like this?
You're asking why?
Did you forget what happened last year?
Right, right
When you suddenly collapsed last year,
it was because you were overwhelmed
by the heat and your nerves.
So this year, we'll make sure
the heat isn't an issue.
It's okay.
I'm not wearing a hakama this year.
But...
Plus, this is my second time at Omi Jingu.
We're back.
This is our second national championship.
What kinds of matches will we play?
How strong are the other teams?
Hey, Tsukuba!
Stop sneaking pictures of girls!
They'll arrest you!
Don't insult me!
I'm taking pictures of
the pretty Akita ladies
while taking pictures of the karuta
holy land, the Omi Learning Center!
Y-You're not supposed to admit it...
Ooh, I've seen this area
in pictures before!
The Master match takes
place up here every year!
Where do they put the TV cameras?!
Cut it out already!
This is the first national championship
for our first-years.
Okay, let's all get changed...
Into the new T-shirts my sister made!
Winners
Wow!
It's got punch!
So cool!
That's a lovely blue.
Huh? Wait...
I can see something in the dots...
Second Place
Second place...
Second place winners?!
Huh?
What did you expect?
The champions will be
Retro-kun's Hokuo.
Sorry, everyone.
Let's wear our regular T-shirts.
All ready.
Sorry.  We ended up having
to wear our usual T-shirts.
That's okay.  We can focus better
when we're in familiar gear.
Hey, Hanano!  Take a picture!
Geez, what now?
My brothers are waiting at home!
"I'm a starter for the national
championship, of course!"
"Your bro's gonna knock them out!"
You're lying again!
Why would you be a starting member?
We're heading down!
Oh, okay.
I want to be a starter!
I've given up Second Verse Karuta
to focus on mainstream
karuta since spring!
I've learned a lot at
the Shiranami society!
This time, I'll successfully change the order,
show my true skill, and become a regular!
Tsukuba!
The lineups for the first round are up.
What?  They already chose
the starting members?
Huh?
1 Nishida Yusei
2 Oe Kana
3 Ayase Chihaya
4 Mashima Taichi
5 Tsukuba Akihiro
What?!  Tsukuba's really a starter!
That's amazing!
Starter...
The group stage match-ups
were drawn yesterday,
so Komano and I already came up
with the order for the first round.
Why me?  Isn't Komano-senpai a starter?
For the National Tournament
A month has passed since
the Tokyo regional.
You've worked very hard.
In terms of skill, you're even with me.
Don't forget that our goal is
to become number one in Japan!
While the two rounds in the
group stage are taking place,
I'll be scouting the other top schools
to prepare for the
championship bracket!
The five of you have to get us there!
Does that mean you're not
playing in the group stage?!
Are you really okay with that?!
Yeah.
I'll need Hanano to help me scout.
What?
Check groups H and I for us.
Geez...
Fine.
I'm impressed.
You brought your own notepad.
I-It's no big deal...
Then I'll show you which
room you'll be in.
O-Okay.
He's so cool...
Desktomu-kun worked just
as hard as the rest of us.
Could I do what he did?
After putting in so much hard work,
could I accept that someone
who started later
had caught up to me?
If Ayase's serious about her dream for
us to become number one in Japan,
we can't flounder around like usual.
There has to be someone
in a support role.
Yo, Eyebrows!
Should you really be so worked up?
Isn't tomorrow's individual tournament
and your chance to make
Class A more important?
It doesn't matter if I lose
my first match tomorrow.
We'll win every match today.
I want to win...
together.
Our opponent's order isn't up yet.
I believe we were matched up
with a school from Chiba.
It's a strange feeling.
Have I been infected
by Chihaya's greed?
I want us to become number
one in Japan together.
There it is!
Is this...
Don't tell me that...
No way...
Huh?
Chiba International School of Information Sciences
Napa Payakaroon
Rachel Port
Anthony Sorb
Park Kyung Seo
Matt Rowan
Um...
In group C, I need to
pay attention to...
the First Akashi Girls' School from Hyogo.
Make sure you pay extra close attention
to the third-year Ousaka Megumu!
Is she really that special?
She was the west representative
in last year's Queen match.
She lost a close match to Yumin,
Yumin?
but she's still the strongest
girl in west Japan.
Okay...
But how can I tell who's who?
For now, I'll put that they're
all ordinary-looking.
Oh, excuse me.
Sorry!
I got the quick energy boost you wanted.
Thanks, Megumu.
Megumu?
I'm so thirsty.
Here.
Energy boost...
Did something run out of power?
Y-Yeah...  Thanks...
Ousaka Megumu is ordinary-looking
and an airhead.
Megumu-tan!  You're adorable as always!
Megumu-tan?!
I've got the best seat in the house!
Hey, is that a new model?!
This guarantees that I'll capture
Megu-tan's beautiful karuta!
She's ordinary-looking,
an airhead, and popular?!
I'm a little
shocked...
Moreover, she's popular
with old-school freaks!
The three cameramen with
glasses are back again.
We only recently got them to silence
the shutter sound during matches.
They're a pain.
I know.  I wish we could dump
them in an incinerator.
Swoon!
She's ordinary-looking, an airhead,
popular, and sharp-tongued?!
Swoon!  Swoon!
Okay, let's do the best we can.
Yes!
I'm so confused,
but there's a lot more to female
karuta players than meets the eye.
Groups E and F are in the
hall by the main office.
The team that we must watch carefully...
The team we must watch...
is last year's champion,
Fujisaki High School.
They've won the championship 13 times.
With over 50 members and a long tradition,
they're the greatest
obstacle in our path.
I have to collect as
much data as I can.
The first match for group
B is about to start.
Will they be okay?
Mizusawa
High
Chiba
International
High School
of Information
Sciences
Their first opponent,
Chiba International High School of
Information Sciences, is new to karuta,
so I couldn't find any data.
Karuta's never been big in Chiba,
so it should be easy for them to win.
Wh-What should I do?!
I've never been so close
to a foreigner before!
What should I do?
Are we really playing
against these guys?!
Can they play karuta?!
Can they understand Japanese?!
The foreigners are wearing hakama,
while we're wearing T-shirts...
I'm so ashamed!
What do I do?
Everyone's thrown off...
But...
The biggest question
is why you're crying!
It's impressive that there are
so many people playing karuta.
No one wears hakama except us,
but it's lucky to be notable.
Without hakama, we are the most noticeable.
That's right!
Let's make a bet the most card!
Karuta has become a global
game like poker and Othello!
Ignoring Chihaya for now,
I need to calm the others down.
Forgive me,
but your pronunciation is not correct...
Maybe you can more easily speak
Japanese than English, can't you?
I'm so embarrassed now!
They caught us!
Who said that we could put pressure
on them by acting like foreigners?!
I barely know middle school English!
It's not my fault!
I've never left Japan before!
Was it you?!
Just so we're clear,
my English is better than yours!
Listen to yourself!
You've never left Chiba before!
I study hard!
I study hard, too!
But your intonation is totally wrong!
Quiet down!
Please place your cards!
We grew up in Japan
and fell in love with karuta.
Please...
Let's have a good match.
Two more minutes of memorization time!
The media is here?
Yes, it's from a local station in Chiba.
Ah, The Chiba International High
School of Information Sciences.
They're attracting a lot of attention,
since we have foreign high school
students wearing hakama.
Hopefully, it'll be good publicity
for the tournament.
Man, why is their first match
against a Tokyo school?
Those guys are probably strong.
The hosts should have put
more thought into the brackets.
I wanted to do a feature like,
"The blond samurai
forges ahead with karuta!"
Finish them
It's really bugging me...
It's really bugging me that she's
wearing her kimono backwards...
His card placement
is exactly like what I used
when I first started!
The cards are lined up in alphabetical
order by unique syllable!
My opponent's even better!
They're lined up in alphabetical
order by second verse!
It's so unusual, it's actually
hard to memorize!
Time's up!
Thank you for the game.
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
Like the sound...
Yes!  I got it!
He's big...  I-I'm scared...
There weren't any black
people in Hokkaido...
He's lying
I can't beat him...
Is he from Vietnam?  Thailand?  Laos?
In any case,
his card placement is very methodical.
Hundred Poets
Competitive Karuta
Guys, just do what we always do.
They're just a bunch of karuta lovers.
That's impossible!
Karuta's difficult and complicated!
How could foreigners ever love karuta?!
I mean, Japanese people
don't like it, either...
We grew up in Japan
and fell in love with karuta.
Fell in love...
the thistle and brush are
blown by the autumn wind
Though I prayed...
She's fast...  Really fast.
So fast that it's scary...
This is competitive karuta.
At first, I was willing
to try anything.
Tea ceremony, Asian calligraphy,
flower arrangement...
Since my physical appearance
was that of a foreigner,
I thought I might be able to make
friends if I did something
really Japanese.
I first encountered
karuta in high school.
You memorize a hundred cards and
try to take them from each other?
That sounds so intellectual!  So fun!
But as I became more engrossed
in competitive karuta...
Eh, not interested.
No, thanks.
He's just a foreigner.
My Japanese friends grew distant.
It's okay...
I know that everyone
thinks we're strange,
but it's okay!
I never asked to be treated colder
than the winds of Mount Hatsuse
Swift waters parted by the jagged rocks
Yes!  I got the card!
This is my favorite poem!
I'm also a fan of this poem.
No way!
I also like this one,
this one, and this one!
"Feel love deepen," "The storm will soon,"
"The hazed field of"...
They're all love poems.
You're not taking them from me!
are joined at river's end
My own sleeves are like...
None are left...
All alone, I step...
He's got good sense.
So there are people with good
karuta sense who aren't Japanese.
But then there are cards where
he doesn't move an inch.
He's a simple player who only
takes the cards he recognizes.
His hearing is superb.
If he learned more about how
to send and place cards...
They're free.
They're showing us how our playing
style is dictated by competitive karuta.
They don't adhere to certain
theories when placing cards.
They pay extra attention
to the poems they like.
They use whatever form they want.
They're all playing Hundred
Poets in their own way.
One card...
One card at a time, Mizusawa!
Yeah!
Don't get too excited.
Let the Chiba kids have their glory.
After many, many years...
A house left to the weeds...
Amazing...
#36!
One moment please!
This is beautiful...
#17 is over here!
They're moving so fast,
yet they're moving in unison...
This is our love for karuta.
This is the product
of the hard work we put in
every day!
The best karuta is beautiful to watch.
Unfortunately for the Chiba International
School of Information Sciences,
this tournament ended with the first match...
Any comments?
U-Uh, any comments?
I suppose...
We were put in our place.
Er, that's what you want to say?
What are you doing?
Wait, don't erase that!
Sorry, we'll fix it once we're done!
Stop!
Karuta is fun,
but competitive karuta is amazing.
We were shown how a good team
can play competitive karuta.
We'll do our best to promote karuta
at our school, improve ourselves,
and return a better team next year.
Bye, Arata.
Let me know when you're done
watching your friends play.
Thanks, Uncle Motoki!
I'm a little late.
Is their first match over?
Are you going to come tomorrow, Arata?
What?  Just the individual
tournament in two days?!
I was lying.
After I pay my respects, I'll
go watch Chihaya and Taichi.