I think we should use the same members
we've been using for the next match.
I think we should go without Desktomu-kun.
Huh?  Why's that, Porky?
Why?!  Why would you say that now?!
It only makes sense for Desktomu-kun
to play in the playoffs!
He'll be much more useful than
an exhausted Tsukuba-kun!
Bingo
Why would you say that?
Wait, Kana-chan.
I'm okay with that.
Our next opponent is Shoyo
High School from Kyoto.
I was watching Fujisaki's match,
so I don't have much
information on them.
Oh, here we go.
I talked to the team they
beat and found out that...
Why...
Why won't you speak up?
Why aren't you asking to be a starter?!
We've worked so hard together!
Why are you letting a new
member take your spot?!
I'll admit that the first-years have
taken some of the pressure off of us,
but that's wrong!
You can't stop fighting to play.
Once you've lost that drive,
you'll start to lose your edge!
I'll take Tsukuba any day when he's
willing to rewrite the
order so he can play!
Huh?
I'll let the Prez decide.
Porky!
What order do I go with?
Who do I play and who do I sit out?
I can understand where
Nishida was coming from,
but this isn't the mood we
want before the playoffs.
What do I do?
Taichi, give me that.
Um, Shoyo from Kyoto...
There we go.
Sano, Ooka, Kawabe, Tashiro, Sanada...
They're all right-handed.
Two girls and three boys...
Everyone!
You should have lunch now
if you haven't eaten yet.
We only have thirty minutes left.
There aren't any vending
machines, so here.
I need to be more proactive
as their advisor.
The advisor is supposed to
decide on what order to use.
Especially when the going gets tough...
Ayase-san can only be counted
on to play in matches.
There's too much pressure on Mashima-kun.
Okay, I got it.
We'll rest Desktomu-kun and use
the same five from the group stage.
Chihaya Furu
Verse 11
I feel as
though
my body
is on fire
with Ibuki
mugwort
What now? What now?! What now?!
Curry Rice
Why did I have to say that
right before the playoffs?!
Another one!
Back again?!
Don't you have a match coming up?
Sure you won't regret this?
I don't regret it...
If I didn't say something now,
Desktomu-kun would drift
into a supporting role.
He wouldn't be one of
the players anymore.
Hang in there!
Finish the whole plate!
But what now?
If nobody does anything and he's
removed from the lineup...
And if that familiar-looking person
over there really is my sister...
Porky!
What are you doing?!
We've been looking for you!
The match is about to begin!  Hurry!
There's no time for us to talk strategy now.
Why were you in the cafeteria?
We bought three lunches.
Oh, we'll be going with the same
lineup we used in the group stage.
Playoff teams, please head inside.
Really?
So you don't want to play?
Porky!
If you're matched up against
Kawabe, try to stay calm!
I don't need your help.
He's just guessing!
Hurry up.
No, I'm not...
Don't need your help...
Shoyo High School    Mizusawa High School
The playoffs...
Featuring the eight schools
that won their groups.
One loss, and the team is out.
Our opponent is Shoyo High
School, representing Kyoto.
Show you...
Shoyo...
A pun?!
Is it a coincidence that all their faces
resemble ancient officials in textbooks?
Two minutes left.
Let's do this, Shoyo!
Yeah!
Kyoto:
where Wakamiya Shinobu is from.
They look very imposing.
Komano-kun?
What are you doing?
Didn't we tell you to get some rest?
You should grab something to eat, too.
Yes...
Thank you very much.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
Though I prayed to the god of mercy
that the one I love not shun me,
He's fast!
Seriously?
Is everyone from Kyoto this fast?
Like Wakamiya Shinobu?
One loss in this tournament...
and our team is out.
May it be that I...
This is bad.  Very bad.
Empress'
jacket
of love
We should let him sleep.
I'll go see how the match is going.
Can you watch Komano-kun?
But I want to watch the match...
You also need to get some rest.
Okay...
...summer night fully breaks
In the sleepy spring sunlight,
He took another one.
He's really fast.
I have to stay calm.
We'll rest Desktomu-kun and use
the same five from the group stage.
Huh?
Dr. Harada once taught me
that you shouldn't
concentrate on watching
other people play before
your own match begins.
It's more tiring to closely watch
a match than to play a match.
After seeing this, I understand.
Desktomu-kun is much more
tired than the rest of us,
so I'm leaving him out.
The storm blasts...
This is bad...
I can't keep up with his
sporadic bursts of speed.
My arm won't move.
This Kawabe guy is really good...
Kawabe?
If you're matched up against
Kawabe, try to stay calm!
He's just guessing!
to set the Tatsuta River ablaze
After many, many years...
Is this speed he's using the real thing?
Normally, I would have no trouble
protecting the "After many" at my lower left,
but he took it before I heard the "many."
Does he have good game sense?
No.
He's gambling that his
card will be read.
now bloom inside the nine-fold palace
As I wait for someone...
A fault!
A person with good game sense
wouldn't let me goad
them into that fault.
He's just guessing...
Desktomu-kun...
Desktomu-kun!
A mountain village grows
lonesome every winter
According to Desktomu-kun's notes...
Excuse me.
Tashiro-kun likes to stand up a lot.
He does this frequently
to get into a rhythm.
So I should put an early stop to that.
Pout
What?  You're standing up again?
O-Oh, sorry about that.
That makes it harder for
Tashiro-kun to stand up.
I'm throwing him off his rhythm early on.
I should stand up again soon.
What?
That card was mine.
It wouldn't have flown in that
direction if I hadn't hit it.
What?!
I definitely got that one!
Ooka will contest cards that she
obviously lost so she can cool down.
You and I both know
that I won that card.
I'm sending this card.
I always thought that skill
was everything in karuta.
I never thought that data
could be so important.
But...
Sanada-san is a whacker.
He whacks the tatami when
he practices his swing,
but it doesn't scare me.
It means his motions are rough and sloppy.
I can't imagine how hard it was
for him to gather this
information from a team
that just lost their match.
Please help us!
Why do we have to talk
to you about Shoyo?
I'm begging you!
You should know how it feels to
want the team who beat you
to win the whole thing.
Let's get going.
I want...
I want to do whatever I can
to support my teammates!
I'm sure you know how that feels!
So please!
Desktomu-kun has the drive.
That notebook is his way of
saying that he wants Mizusawa
to be first in Japan.
Please...
Huh? I fell asleep?
You scared me, senpai!
I can't tell if you're awake or
asleep because of your glasses!
Sorry for that
What about the match?
It's still going on.
Oh...
I think it's perfectly okay.
Huh?
You're so good at gathering data
that it doesn't matter if you don't play!
It's hard to play in a match.
I know!
It's hard and scary...
I got nervous when Porky called me out.
We won!  Mizusawa won!
You're playing in the
next match, right?
next match, right?!
You're going to join us, right?!
Desktomu-kun!
We worked so hard to get here.
We want you with us as a player.
You should always be a player with us.
Arata!  I'm so sorry!
It's my fault you have
to write this essay!
No, I should apologize.
I can't return this T-shirt yet,
since I had to lend mine
to the drenched Queen.
And
those
pants
And
that
phone
That's no big deal!
You can keep it if you want!
Oh, unless you don't want it...
Wataya-kun, what was
your objective today?
Huh?
I came here to cheer for
my friends from Tokyo.
Then you're no longer
allowed to do that.
Go to the room in the back
and write an essay of apology.
Tomorrow, you will play
in the individual tournament.
Taichi...  Chihaya...
Are you working hard?
One page should be enough, right?
So there won't be any more events today...
Quality over quantity.
Can't they push the individual
tournament back a day?
Why is it?
It seems I only ever run
into them during matches.
Our opponent in the semifinals
will be First Akashi Girls'.
I'm sure that everybody
already knows this,
but our biggest obstacle is
the third-year Ousaka Megumu.
Who's that?
Idiot!
Do you have the mind of an infant?!
She was the West representative
in last year's Queen match!
Didn't you watch Yumin's match with us?!
The girl who lost a close back-and-forth
game to Yamamoto Yumi-san...
the strongest girl in western Japan!
I wanna play her!
Their match was in a different area,
so I didn't get to watch them,
but Hanano-san helped scout them out.
That's where these notes about
bags and straps came from?
First Akashi Girls' all look ordinary
Girl in front (with long hair)
Pink checkered handbag (Ponita)
white hand towel
pink macaroon phone strap
Girl with glasses
(ordinary, sharp-tongued, popular)
black handbag
This has nothing to do with karuta.
It's useless...
I-It's not my fault!
I couldn't see the cards
from my position!
Plus, I don't really understand
how karuta works...
It's okay.
You were very observant.
We can tell from these notes that,
aside from Ousaka Megumu,
the others are ordinary girls who didn't
start playing karuta until high school.
They probably place more
emphasis on the meanings,
so they're probably good at love poems.
Yuube-san is a little
boyish with simple taste.
She might place more emphasis on sound.
There's also their names.
Make sure you check their names.
Names?
In Ousaka Megumu's case,
she's probably good at "While it pains,"
"While it may," "While it brings," and "Long,"
the cards with the starting sounds of her name.
As for their order,
the Class A players
Ousaka-san and Yuube-san
1. Yuube (Third-year) Class A
2. Hayasaka (Second-year) Class B
3. Ousaka (Third-year) Class A
4. Nanase (Third-year) Class B
5. Tanimura (Third-year) Class B
have been in these
positions every match,
so it's likely that won't change.
In that case, the best
scenario for us would be
to avoid matching Ayase, Mashima,
and Porky against their Class A players.
But our ace is aggressive.
She wants to play strong opponents.
Then...
Put me in the s-second position...
I've been in either the first
or third position every game,
so I'll probably end up
against a Class B player
in the second position.
Chihaya's thinking of our best chance to win.
We only need two more victories...
She's focused on being best in Japan!
Okay, we'll go with that.
Ayase,
If you really want to win,
here's my advice.
I've been meaning to talk
to you about this...
At the end of our match against Hokuo,
you surrendered a card because you
both touched it at the same time.
You can't give up when it's close.
If you want to win,
you have to fight for every card.
Mashima!
Win!
We'll have a repeat of the
Tokyo regional finals!
Will the semifinalist
teams please enter.
The semifinals:
Mizusawa High School against
First Akashi Girls' High School.
Fujisaki High School
against Hokuo Academy.
Victory for Fujisaki
I know that Fujisaki's famous, but
their supporters really stand out.
There are so many of them.
Excuse me for a moment.
Could you hold the other side for me?
I'm here to support Fujisaki...
Oh, dear.
What about you?
No good?
I'll hold it.
Oh, thank you!
Hokuo Victory!
Sudo-san...
And all those alumni...
The Omi Jingu Learning Center.
The Urayasu room.
A new Master and Queen
are crowned here every year.
Where I played against
Shinobu-chan last summer...
I saw the Queen!
She was with someone from Fukui.
Listen up, everyone.
I'm putting Chihaya in the
number three position.
Huh?
In the regional final,
Hokuo went with even
match-ups across the board.
Do we really want to
dodge our opponents?
Chihaya, you just have to win.
Bring home the win!
Victory for Mizusawa!
Yeah!
But...
1. Yuube (Third-year) Class A
2. Hayasaka (Second-year) Class B
3. Ousaka (Third-year) Class A
4. Nanase (Third-year) Class B
5. Tanimura (Third-year) Class B
Akashi Girls might
change up their order.
I didn't mention this...
But...
They probably went with the
same order every match
as preparation for the strong
teams they'll face from here on.
They'll switch it up once they
face a strong team.
So the question is whether Akashi
thinks we're good enough.
I will begin reading the order for
Mizusawa High School versus
First Akashi Girls' High School.
Mizusawa High School, Nishida-kun.
First Akashi Girls', Yuube-san.
Good, all according to plan!
Mizusawa High School, Oe-san.
First Akashi Girls', Hayasaka-san.
All according to plan!
Mizusawa High School, Ayase-san.
First Akashi Girls', Ousaka-san.
All according to plan!
Mizusawa High School, Mashima-kun.
First Akashi Girls', Nanase-san.
Mizusawa High School, Komano-kun.
First Akashi Girls', Tanimura-san.
It's so exactly according to our plan,
it's kind of sad...
Are they looking ahead to the finals?
They don't respect us?
Or perhaps...
they have absolute faith
that their ace will win?