Take Chise to the land of dragons?
Yes.
Lindel-sama heard a rumor that the
Robin there has trouble using magic.
So he insists that you make a wand soon.
A wand?
It's a tool for conveying your
intentions to the fae.
He would like you to come see him, Robin.
I've been out all the time lately, though.
Oh, don't worry about that.
He wants the Robin to come alone.
Chise? By herself?
"I want to spend time with my
granddaughter, not with you," he says.
That old bastard...
Granddaughter?
So Elias is his son?
It seems he wants to talk about your wand,
though, so I suppose it's all right.
Take care.
Would you rather not?
No, but by myself?
You have me.
Oh, right.
Are you done talking?
You sure haven't changed at all.
Um...
Come on, have you forgotten me?
We talked, remember?
You wouldn't fly with me, though.
Dragons grow up in various ways.
I wanted to be big enough for you
to be able to ride me, so it works out.
Yeah?
Thanks, Silky.
Okay, I'll see you soon.
Take care.
It's cold over there.
Don't freeze.
Okay.
Elias?
Yes?
It's nothing.
Let's go.
Hang on tight, so you don't fall off!
What's that?
It's a cloaking spell.
No one will find us now.
It's a lot quicker than
swimming through the sea.
The sea?
I'm a selkie.
I'm a citizen of the great seas,
with both a human and seal form.
Are you okay?
We'll be there as soon as
we get through the wind.
Hang on a little longer.
Okay.
I'm sure Elias will be fine.
Yeah.
Lindel-sama!
Lindel-sama, I did what you asked me to.
Yes, you did well. Very good.
Hello, Lindel-san.
Chise.
Long time no see.
You look quite well.
And you've put on some weight.
Good, good.
I'm glad to see you've found a good family.
Lindel-san, where did you get those clothes?
Oh, I went shopping in town.
I'm very handsome, aren't I?
He kind of resembles Elias.
Come on, guys, say hi.
I'll be in your care.
I didn't get to explain last time.
The land of dragons was established as
a nesting ground by the first administrator,
for the few dragons that remained
scattered throughout the world.
So you weren't the one who made it, then?
I used to be a simple nomad.
I didn't even have a name,
until my master gave me one.
All right, we're here.
Nevin's tree.
I'll be preparing supper.
Chise.
It's your wand. You've gotta cut it yourself.
Are you okay?
Y-Yeah.
What is wrong with you?!
Who falls without even trying
to break their fall?!
Ow.
Sorry.
You're so overprotective.
It wouldn't kill her to get
to know the rocks a little.
Shut up!
Should I go?
No, I'm going to be the one using it.
I'll see what I can do.
Thanks, Silver.
Boy, it's quiet.
Even though that girl is not very talkative.
The air feels terribly cold.
Hello, Mr. Ainsworth.
My name is Adolf Stroud. I'm with
the College administration.
College?
I'll get straight to business.
I'd like to speak in depth about
the future of the human child.
Reindeer soup.
I imagine this is your first time having it.
Yes.
It's good.
You've got scrapes all over.
Let me see.
My hands are what's called healing hands.
As long as you aren't mortally
wounded, I can heal you on the spot.
There used to be more of us, before.
But not many have been born in
the past few hundred years.
Have long have you been alive, Lindel-san?
Are other mages long-lived, too?
Oh, that's why you were
making such a fuss earlier.
That idiot!
He hasn't explained anything!
What does he...
Err, sorry, I should have asked Elias.
Chise, the reason I brought you
here alone is because I'm worried.
He seems to want to tame you,
as one would a reindeer.
And Chise, you seem to be content with that.
The person who gave birth to me
told me that they shouldn't have.
My mother didn't need me,
so she ran away. She died.
I think my brother and father
ran away from me, too.
Elias is the only who's kept me nearby.
That's why I don't ask him
anything he doesn't say.
I want to be complacent.
Though it doesn't appear that way at all.
I'll tell you an interesting bedtime story.
An interesting story?
I suppose I'll answer your question, too.
But, half of it is as punishment for that
bastard, for saddening my granddaughter.
Long ago, when the world was still dark,
before the power of steam, and before even
the power of the old, earthen oil...
We mages were all aware that
we were not normal people.
For we saw magical creatures, and worked
miracles that the ordinary person could not.
And at times, we lived very long lives.
We don't know why we're so long-lived,
or possess abilities humans do not.
It may simply be that fate
wanted us to be born so.
But those who were not satisfied
continued to seek an answer.
"Why are we so?"
"Is there a duty that we must fulfill?"
Many of our kind perished in their search.
I wandered alone, sick of that way of life.
One night, there were wolves, and I had
no choice but to stand watch all night.
However, the wolves never came.
Instead, it came.
It came as certain as night on two legs.
You...
What's the matter?
I'm hungry.
Hey!
You're awake, huh?
You were asleep all night.
You're so huge, it was a pain to carry you.
Aren't you going to eat?
Where did you come from?
I don't know.
When I came to, I was in
the forest, and I was walking.
Avoiding people, I walked, walked,
and walked, until I was here.
I'm tired.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You look to be an apparition of some kind.
But you wear flesh, like a living creature.
What are you?
I don't know.
Well, let's go see my master.
She's a strange one.
She may be at the other side of
the world. She may be right there.
She may be alive a hundred years
from now or a hundred years ago.
Being a meddler, she may provide guidance.
I'd imagine it would be less painful than
aimlessly wandering through the wilds.
Who are you?
I'm Lindel.
The ordinary people call us "mages."
What is that?
An ancient technique for finding the missing.
Gather some spruce, tie it in
red string, and set it loose.
The spruce covering the ground is
the dining table of the forest god.
We ask for their help and for directions.
My guide, take us past the
fog, to the one we seek.
The fog is thickening.
Stay with me.
Water.
The sea.
Have a taste.
It's fun.
That's my master's home.
Master.
Rahab.
Are you home?
Is that Lindel?
I don't see your face here often.
A pity, since your name's derived
from that of the tree of gatherings.
That name was your choice, Master.
You need to make an effort to
interact with people more—
Oh?
I found him yesterday.
I wanted you to take a look at him.
Come in.
Though then again, you're pretty big.
Can you become smaller?
Smaller?
That's right.
About human size.
Human...
Like this?
Yes.
Well done.
Come.
You don't know?
Well...
He's as close to a spirit or fairy as you
can get, but there's a hint of human in him.
It would make sense if he were
simply a human who'd gotten
himself transformed trying
to use black magic.
But this seems more like...
Do you remember anything about what
happened before you started walking?
Anything I remember?
Red.
Red?
You don't have to force
yourself to remember.
Lindel, you'll take care of him.
Huh?
Why me?
You've already taken pity on him once.
You ought to take care of
him until he's independent.
I have to follow the reindeer.
It's about time you took an apprentice.
We ought not to live by ourselves.
Remember what I taught you?
I won't tell you to love your enemy.
But the neighbors love us.
We lend a staff to those
who have lost their way.
It's not as if we asked to be loved.
Not me nor you.
We might as well be cursed.
Curses and blessings are
the same in essence, Lindel.
What matters is how you take it.
It's fine.
I'm going.
If you'd rather not have me
here, I'll continue walking.
To where?
I don't know, but you're busy, aren't you?
I don't take apprentices.
So from now on, you're my acquaintance.
I would surely have to provide a weary
acquaintance a place to sleep.
I'm not in need.
You're one to talk. You collapsed!
Oh my, how kind of you.
Shut up!
Now that that's settled, we're friends.
What's your name?
I'm guessing you don't have one.
What should we call you?
Here we go again, with Master's
name-giving obsession.
The gods and the fairies are all with you.
Even if no one takes notice of you,
even if you're sad, suffering, and crushed by
loneliness, they will always watch over you.
So take comfort, and save yourself.
Elias.
Hello? Ainsworth?
Senpai! Stop!
Renfred.
You're going to ruin her if you continue to
do nothing more than let her live with you.
The story of the mage's past.
The girl is shaken by the
truth that had been hidden.
What does the brief parting
bring to the two?
I'll tell you what I haven't
been able to tell you, too.