Space-time fluctuation confirmed.
Bearing 012, distance 4,500.
It's coming.
It's big.
Dragons have emerged.
One Brig-class, 30 Scuna-class.
Brig-class? What about Galleon-class?
There are lots of small ones...
No whining.
Captain to all units.
Open fire and destroy all enemies.
Safeties open.
Yes, ma'am!
Update data confirmed, sight line type G.
Parallax compensation, sight line type G.
Fire.
Eight Scuna-class down.
I'm going in to intercept.
All rearguard units,
begin barrage at distance 500.
Now! All vanguard units, attack!
Roger!
The forty thousand in cash is mine!
Is she splitting off again?
You! Maintain formation!
Emissions confirmed.
All units, scatter.
Rosalie, Ersha!
Ange, come in.
Ange!
Here we go, Villkiss.
My name is Ange.
I will survive.
Kill and survive.
Fallen Princess
The sweat and blood of youth!
The Light of Mana clashes!
It's the Iaria Championship!
Will the grand prize be
won by Floria Academy,
of the Kingdom of Rosenblum?
Or by the Empire of
Misurugi's Ho-o Institute?
I'll take back the lead!
Follow me!
Oh no you don't!
Momoka!
Yes.
Are you hurt?
Angelise-sama!
Let's fly once more.
Yes.
And the game is over!
One point decides this fierce battle!
The victor of this year's Iaria
Championship is Floria Academy,
of the Kingdom of Rosenblum!
For Ho-o Institute, it's an unfortunate end.
Prince Julio and Princess Sylvia
give a warm round of applause
to both teams, for their passionate fight.
I'm sorry!
Angelise-sama, if only we
hadn't gotten in your way...
Remember the promise we made that day?
That we'll aspire to something
more important than winning.
We formed stronger
bonds than any other team.
That is our victory.
Angelise-sama!
Impressive, Princess Angelise.
You've taught us all something
more beautiful and noble than victory.
We'll make up for today
in the fall competition.
I'll be back after the Baptism Ritual,
no matter how busy I become.
Please take care of the
Iaria team until then.
Yes, Captain!
How laughable.
My heart's still pounding.
I thought I was going to have a heart attack
when Onee-sama flew into the sky.
Angelise is a constant source
of anxiety, isn't she, Momoka?
I'm so upset.
Help my friends and win...
That's what's expected of a princess.
Good grief. Our princess is greedy.
The country's full of pictures of Onee-sama.
They can't wait for the Baptism Ritual.
I understand, Onii-sama.
I will show them the future of this nation,
with my Light of Mana.
I look forward to the
Baptism Ritual tomorrow.
Guards, perimeter defense!
Light of Mana, shield!
Please be patient.
We'll take care of this.
It's a Norma, eh?
Let me go, please!
Barrier!
No!
She broke the Light of Mana.
Haven't seen one in person before?
That's a Norma.
Under Article 1, Section 3,
of the Norma Management Code,
this individual is hereby
designated Norma #1203-76.
Serra—
Give me back my daughter!
What are you—
You!
Please forgive us.
She's just a little bad at using Mana!
Please!
But that is the very sign of a Norma.
We cannot ignore it.
Angelise-sama...
What?
It's her!
The Light of Mana,
the ultimate evolution of humanity...
The Norma reject it.
They are instinctively
violent, antisocial monsters.
She must be quarantined immediately.
Please, Angelise-sama! I'll raise her well!
You can't. Norma are not human.
You must forget her,
and bear another child.
A proper child, not a Norma.
Shield!
Princess, are you hurt?
You're too protective.
Serra!
Let go!
You haven't changed since you were little.
Whenever you're troubled,
you come here to sing this song.
It's as if it washes everything away.
My doubts, my anxieties...
The Endless Song.
The lullaby that guides the royal family.
That guides...
Mother,
I love this world.
This world, freed by the Light of Mana
from war, inequality, and poverty.
A world where all darkness has disappeared...
It's peaceful, beautiful and perfect.
But I've always been searching.
There must be a path
that challenges me out there.
So you must have found it.
I saw a Norma for the first time today.
A Mana-destroying mutant...
Why does such a thing exist?
We know nothing.
How it happens, or why only in women.
Indeed. We know nothing.
But I hope to find answers.
If we can exterminate the Norma,
the world should become even more beautiful.
Angelise,
this is for you.
This is the Ikaruga royal family's—
May the Light protect you.
Mother.
The roads are filled with citizens hoping
to celebrate Angelise-sama's 16th birthday.
Angelise-sama will be joined by members
of the royal family in front of the Dawn Pillar,
and the Baptism Ritual will begin.
From now on, Princess Angelise
will be practicing politics.
She will no doubt bring even
greater peace and prosperity
to our Empire of Misurugi.
What's this noise?
Norma alert.
Impossible. Surely the Pillar is...
I disabled the disguise.
Why, Julio?
That would be my line, Father.
Trying to use the Baptism Ritual to make
a monster a part of the royal family...
Are you mad?
O-Onii-sama.
My adorable Sylvia...
And my beloved subjects.
I will show you the truth!
Angelise...
...is a Norma!
To cover up the truth and have a Norma
in politics is a theft of the state!
A grave betrayal of the people!
How could we allow such a monster
to tarnish the Empire of Misurugi?
But at last, Angelise's Baptism Ritual
will reveal everything to the people.
Run, quickly.
Mother, what's going on?
Stop her!
Use live rounds!
Lockdown!
The suspect is fleeing into the Pillar's interior.
Secure it immediately.
Sylvia-sama!
Angelise-sama, this way.
You are under suspicion of being a Norma.
Please do not resist.
What do you mean?
No, Angelise!
She destroyed the Light of Mana!
The princess is a Norma...
No. No way.
Drop your weapon and surrender.
If you resist, we will shoot to kill.
How dare you point a gun
at the First Princess!
Angelise!
Mother!
I wanted to protect you...
From the truth.
Live on, Angelise...
No matter what.
Mother!
Under Article 1, Section 3, of
the Norma Management Code,
you are hereby recognized
as Norma #1203-77.
Take her.
Yes.
You tricked us!
What "bond," you liar!
Mother.
Serves you right!
Mother. Mother!
Prepare a state funeral for Her Majesty.
And have His Majesty restrained.
Sir.
We're about to get busy, Sylvia.
We have to rebuild the tainted royal family.
Just the two of us...
Riza,
from now on I will be in
charge of the Empire of Misurugi.
I shall take the name
Holy Emperor Julio the First.
Understood.
This is 107.
I've brought the waste material.
Requesting permission to land.
This is 107.
Norma #1203-77, Angelise Ikaruga Misurugi.
Born in the Empire of Misurugi. Sixteen years old.
Sixteen, huh?
You'll be enlisted here
in Arzenal from now on.
You will be required to fight as a soldier.
What is this place?
What's happening to me?
As a sixteen-year-old,
you will be educated—
My mother. What happened to my mother?
Let me see her. Now, please!
Wh-What are you—
I will be taking your belongings.
Stop.
And your ring.
Don't touch me!
This belongs to the Misurugi royal family!
A lowly officer like you
has no right to touch it.
How dare you, Norma!
I'll do it, Officer Emma Bronson.
A Norma must be dealt with by a Norma.
I'm the Arzenal commander, Jill.
Sorry about the rough handling.
I'm not a Norma.
This is all a mistake.
The Empire of Misurugi will—
My, my...
I'm impressed.
You made it sixteen
years without once using Mana.
What are you—
Didn't you ever think that was strange?
Not even once?
What are you talking about?
I hear she had a Mana-using maid.
I see.
Sixteen years of effort, all for nothing.
And your mother died in vain.
Died?
G-Give it back.
Why don't you take it back?
Use your Mana.
Light of Mana.
Light.
Light of Mana!
You have nothing now.
Neither the privileges of royalty,
or any rights as a person.
Welcome to Hell.
Officer, some assistance, please?
Why me?
Don't you want to get the
dirty work over with?
What—
It's just a physical.
Stop this.
Stop.
I am the Empire of Misurugi's
First Princess, Angelise Ikaruga Misurugi.
No. From now on, you're Ange.
No!
Next Episode Preview
What did you think of Episode 1?
It's horrible! They did terrible
things to that glamorous princess!
How could they do that to her?
That was totally unconscionable!
And isn't this supposed to
be a bishoujo robot anime?
Unyielding Spirit
I get the bishoujo part,
but where were the robots?