Painful Countdown
Here.
This rod's 37,500 yen.
For the first time, I was trying to buy
something with money I had earned myself.
The reel's 33,000 yen.
The cap's 3,500 yen.
It's 10,000 yen for the polarized glasses.
With the rest of your
wear and life jacket...
Salary
Will I have enough?
All together, your total
comes to 102,500 yen.
I'll give you a discount and
make it an even 100,000.
Thank you for your purchase.
Most of my pay's gone...
but now I can finally
assemble my own tackle.
That's great, Yuki.
Yeah.
Haru, you're not going to buy anything?
Huh?
Yeah, you should buy something.
You got paid to work, too.
I won't fish any more.
Why not?
Because fishing is lame.
And the ocean's dangerous.
I'm not interested at all.
No more fishing! Forbidden!
Absolutely not!
What are you talking about?
You're the one who said we should fish.
No fishing for you, Yuki.
What are you doing? Stop that.
No fishing! Forbidden!
He's a hypocrite now?
What are you talking about?
You're not making any sense!
No!
Stop!
Yamada, is that true?
Yes. I was there to witness it.
I saw it...
I saw it with my own eyes.
Bermuda Syndrome is the work of aliens,
and JF1 is one of their kin.
Do you have proof?
I told you, I saw it myself.
Did you record the event?
Well, it happened so suddenly...
We understand your speculation,
but we are curious about one thing.
Twinkle!
Why did you go fishing with them?
To observe JF1, of course.
Is there a problem?
Not at all.
Stay an appropriate distance
from the target at all times.
Understood?
Understood.
Well, then.
Duck!
Damn it.
They don't believe me.
They would understand
if they had been there.
The Bermuda Syndrome is
about to strike again.
Right here on Enoshima!
I'll make dinner tomorrow.
That's great. You can use
the rest of the whitebait.
Okay. Maybe I'll make a salad.
Yuki, be careful with that.
Oh, sorry.
It feels great!
Having your own pole's nice, isn't it?
Yeah.
Hey.
What's up with him?
Who knows?
He said he's going to play
soccer instead of fish now.
I don't know what he's thinking.
Don't think you can fool me with that.
Akira, why are you dressed like that?
It's supposed to rain today.
Is that right?
Looks like you've really
gotten into fishing.
I've always liked fishing.
Why don't you fish by yourself, then?
I have my reasons.
Just be honest.
About what?
I bet you had fun the other day.
Fishing for tuna with the rest of us.
Ridiculous.
You're not very cute, are you?
So, Natsuki.
What are you going to teach me today?
I'm not teaching you anything today.
What?
Fishing's something you
think about for yourself.
Based on your current
location and conditions,
you come up with your own strategy.
A strategy.
Yeah.
An angler's greatest moment
is when it all comes together.
I see.
Look at that.
Is that...
The sea bass are eating
Japanese anchovies.
Go for the sea bass out there today.
The rest is up to you.
Huh? It's up to me? But...
An angler has to develop
a habit of always thinking
of how to fish...
so you're always ready, no matter
what kind of tough catch appears.
A tough catch.
I will go for the sea bass
with this top water lure.
I see. What about you, Yuki?
I, um...
You'll think of something.
I'll use this sinking lure.
Why?
It's just a hunch,
but I thought sea bass feeding at
the surface must be small.
I care more about numbers than size.
I want to catch a big one.
I have a feeling the big one's
biding his time in there.
I see. Is that the
color you want to use?
The color?
You should match the color of your lure
to whatever the fish are eating.
Then...
This one, I guess.
Now you just have to figure
out how deep their prey is.
How?
With a countdown.
A countdown?
It's a method for measuring how long
it takes for your lure to sink.
But how am I supposed to do that?
Figure it out yourself.
For example, this lure will sink
to the bottom in five seconds.
One... two... three... four... five.
That means it'll be around
the middle at three seconds.
You can measure five levels
of depth this way.
I see.
If you get a bite at three seconds,
you'll know there are fish there.
Of course, the depth of the ocean
varies from location to location.
So I should cast over there
and measure the depth?
Yeah.
What will you do, then?
Once I figure out where the fish are,
I'll bait the fish by making
them think my lure's food.
That's right.
Let's start already.
The first one to catch one wins.
Bring it on!
Eno... shima... bowl!
Damn it.
He won't be easy to beat.
Yuki, why don't you
switch to another lure?
Enoshima bowl!
But I decided I'd fish with this one.
If you always use the same tactic,
your target will deceive you.
He's not doing the same thing.
One, two, three.
He's been testing all sorts of things.
Akira.
What?
Sorry for surprising you the other day.
I won't do it again.
I'm fine now.
What terrible acting, Tapioca.
What?
Onii-chan.
Sakura.
Catch anything?
Not yet.
You just watch.
I'll catch you a huge one.
Hey, listen.
The day after tomorrow's
my brother's birthday.
Huh? It is?
Natsuki, happy birthday!
We're going to go fishing as a family.
Come with us.
What? Aren't you going with your family?
It won't be just my family.
Tapioca!
I want this.
This looks good, too.
I'll catch anything you want.
Come on, come on, come on!
Right, Natsuki?
Is everything okay now?
Did something sad happen?
Sad?
Your chest hurts, doesn't it?
Does your chest hurt sometimes?
Sometimes, but you can't
fix it with a band-aid.
How can I fix it?
You have to try.
What?
Think really hard about what you can do.
You have to try.
Try...
Whoops.
What are those?
They're beautiful.
Is that a present?
Yeah.
This blue one's for my brother,
the purple one's for Dad,
mine's pink, and Mari-chan's is yellow.
They're all our favorite colors.
Did you make all of those?
Yeah, with Dad.
This string is Dad's fishing line.
That's amazing!
What about this orange one?
That's Mom's.
I'm going to put it on our family shrine.
I see.
I'm sure Natsuki will be happy.
But what will I do if he doesn't come?
Sakura-chan, you're worried about him?
I don't think he really wants to come.
All right. Let's all go.
I'll take my boat out.
Really?
Yeah.
Weird things have been
happening around here lately,
but we'll be fine as long
as we don't go out too far.
Thank you, Ayumi-chan.
I have a feeling things
won't go so well.
No.
With everyone there, they cannot fight.
Indian, you say some
smart things sometimes.
Haru-chan, you'll come, too, won't you?
What?
I've got to play ball in a cup that day.
But... I want everyone to come.
But my ball in a cup...
Haru, enough already!
You used to never shut up about fishing.
But it's dangerous in the ocean.
It'll be okay.
The captain will be with us.
That's right, Haru.
Everyone will be sad if you don't go.
Akira.
I don't know what to do.
You have to try.
Try?
That's right.
Don't you remember?
You said it's better for
everyone to get along.
I did.
Tomorrow's our chance for
everyone to get along.
We've got to try to make Natsuki happy.
Sure, got it.
Sakura, I'll try.
It's better if everyone's
friends, so I'll try.
Tapioca, this is our chance
to gather evidence.
Please don't get in our way tomorrow.
I don't like to be sad.
I want to be friends
with everyone forever.
Koko-chan, you came.
Of course I did.
Thanks a bunch.
All right, everyone. All aboard!
Yeah!
Enoshima game!
The loser will be punished!
What?
Let's go!
Enoshima...
Specialties!
Whitebait!
Esca!
Mister Indian loses!
Mister?
One more time and you'll be punished.
Shut up, alien.
Who knew you were so stupid, Indian?
Right, Misaki-san?
Enoshima!
Specialties!
Punishment! Punishment!
Hey, Yuki-san.
When should I give these to everyone?
Just wait.
I'll tell you when.
Natsuki, Tamocchan.
Let's take a picture.
Come on, come on.
Good job, Haru.
Smile, Onii-chan.
Um, okay.
You're making a weird face.
Natsuki, how is that a smile?
I'm smiling.
I know.
I bet you're grumpy because you're the
only one who hasn't caught anything.
You haven't changed a bit
since you were a kid.
It's all right.
Natsuki will catch something.
They don't call him the
Fishing Prince for nothing.
That's right.
My son's gonna be a bass fishing pro.
Thanks to my instruction, of course.
Now.
I'll never be a bass pro.
You know I can't catch
black bass on Enoshima.
I can't become a professional here!
Let's just take a picture.
Then leave Enoshima!
I can't do that.
Why not?
If you really want to
be a pro, you'll do it!
What about the store?
You don't have to take over.
I've been thinking about converting
it into a whitebait carpet place.
We've all been coming up with
ideas and getting ready for it.
I have my own dream.
You have your own.
Why wouldn't you tell me
something that important?
Why didn't you tell me?
That store is mine.
You don't have to force
yourself to do anything.
You've got your own life to live.
But we're family!
You're cold!
I really hate that about you.
Hey, come on. No one likes
this sort of atmosphere.
Shall we head back?
Watch out! A boat's coming!
Hang on, everyone!
Nii-chan, is that him?
Sakura!
Grab on, quickly!
Don't let me down, Seishunmaru.
Hard to port!
Mom!
Sakura!
Akira.
Thanks, Haru.
Are you okay, Sakura?
I'm relieved.
What's wrong?
I dropped it.
I dropped the orange one.
Mom's favorite color.
It's your fault, Onii-chan!
It's all your fault!
I tried to give you your present,
but you had to fight!
Mom... Mom's gone!
Okay. I'll make you a new one.
No! I don't want you to make one!
Why can't you get along with Dad?
Why won't you smile even
though everyone's having fun?
Onii-chan, you're a jerk!
Enough!
You're a jerk!
I hate you!
Do what you want!
What?
Get out of the way!
Apologize!
Apologize to Sakura-chan!
Sakura-chan worked really hard
to make those for everyone!
What would you know?
You don't understand!
Leave me alone.
You've got your own life to live.
But we're family!
What would you know?
That day, I fought with my
friends for the first time.
Natsuki was right.
I didn't understand.
I don't know anything about
parents or siblings.
Where's Sakura?
She's not with you?
I was so frustrated,
I couldn't stand it.
He... He... Hel...
Misaki-san?
It was...
Sakura-chan isn't with you, is she?
We can't find her anywhere!
Sakura-chan's missing?
a long, long night.
And I still didn't know...
what was happening on Enoshima.
Not yet.
Continued in #8