Hm?
Kageyama
What's that?
While Ritsu was mistaking Dimple
for a creepy-looking balloon,
the rumors about Mob,
who kicked around Hanazawa—
Hey, have you
heard about
the shadow
leader at
Salt Middle
School?
The one
in the
white
T-shirt?
Pale
and
skinny?
the shadow leader of
Black Vinegar Middle School,
were starting to take a life of their own.
You mean
White T
Poison, right?
White T Poison...
This was the title given to Mob,
whose identity had yet to be revealed.
Apparently,
he'll do
anything.
A slow-acting
poison?
White T Poison...
I'll be the one to defeat him!
Miso Middle School's
Gang Leader:
Fuji
Bean Paste Middle School
Gang Leader: Kenzaki
I'll defeat him and make him
admit that I'm the best.
Noodle Soup Middle School
Gang Leader: Akagi
So the next target is Salt Middle School...
Mayo Middle School
Gang Leader: Gozu
White T Poison is my prey.
Soy Sauce Middle School
Gang Leader: Bandai
This is my chance to shine.
And thus the fierce battle to fight
White T Poison was about to begin.
Onigawara
Leadership: 1500
Moderate Faction: 4
White T Poison
Attack Power: ???P
Hanazawa
Attack Power: 2800P
Kenzaki
Leadership: 1000
Extremist Faction: 5
Akagi
Leadership: 1000
Moderate Faction: 2
Gozu
Leadership: 1100
Extremist Faction: 5
Fuji
Leadership: 1400
Extremist Faction: 3
Bandai
Leadership: 1300
Diehards: 1
Mob Psycho
Exaltation
~I've Obtained Loss~
Man, thanks for helping me out.
I managed to make it back from
the particle level by myself,
but my spiritual energy is way
less than what it used to be,
so I wasn't able to get into
the house anymore.
It appears that low-level spirits
can't even go near this place
just because Shigeo lives here.
What...
is this ugly jellyfish-looking
thing that talks?
But the first thing that I need to do is...
What? You wanna shake hands?
I have to exorcise it!
Wait!
Stop kneeing me in the face!
I'm Shigeo's friend!
Nii-san's?
You could even call me his mentor!
I'll let you off the hook this time,
because you obviously panicked.
That aside...
How about it, Ricchan?
Wanna pair up with me?
No.
That was too fast.
Wait a sec, just hear me out.
You just awakened to your
psychic powers, didn't you?
What? I have psychic powers?
The fact that you can see me is proof.
I'm Dimple. I'm basically
what they call a ghost.
So are my psychic powers only
strong enough to let me see you?
I see you haven't realized what your
powers are, let alone how to use them.
Go ahead. You should be able to do that now.
I shouldn't get my hopes up.
What's the matter?
It's a world that's out of my reach...
What's with him? Does he
have a complex or something?
Well, it's understandable,
given who his brother is.
It...
It's...
It's not...
It's not bending!
D-Dimple!
Calm down.
What?
Did I do this?
Join me, Ricchan,
if you want to surpass your brother.
Surpass Nii-san?
Is that possible?
I can be like my brother?
If you'll let me use your body.
Huh?
Ritsu's not eating?
He doesn't seem to have an appetite.
I wonder what's wrong with him.
Is he feeling down?
No...
He seemed oddly happy.
How do I get to use my powers freely?
It's better to actually try them out,
rather than explain, Ricchan.
Don't call me that.
Okay, then.
I'll just call you Ritsu.
Close your eyes, and relax your whole body.
Possession!
You fool! Now your body's mine!
What?!
I can't control his body!
Where'd you go, Dimple?
It's because my spiritual powers
have become so weak... Damn it!
I heard that the student council
took care of the problem.
You mean about the perv gang leader?
They're like heroes.
They're the heroes of the school.
Yamazaki-kun from Class 2-4,
I'd like a word with you.
What do you want?
You haven't fully buttoned up your coat.
So what? Buzz off.
I can use them...
I can use psychic powers, Dimple.
It's because I'm controlling the output,
but you've always had
latent psychic powers, Ritsu.
And I'm deducing that
the reason they came out now
is due to your emotions.
Did something stress you out badly lately?
Like shitting your pants in
front of a lot of people,
or getting caught peeping into
the girls' locker room?
Of course not. Are you mocking me?
It's just a joke.
You're so damn serious, Ritsu.
That's right, you're an honor student.
Then, what? Did you do something bad?
I heard rumors that you were
stealing the girls' gym clothes.
What the hell are you talking about?
And so the student council
did a bit of investigating...
What did we find out, Kageyama-kun?
We found some of the girls' gym
clothes in your bag, Yamazaki-senpai.
Huh? What?!
Stop lying!
You can try to say that you didn't do it,
but that might prove difficult.
The school's been very
strict with perverts lately.
I'll give you one way out of this.
Onigawara ordered you to do this, didn't he?
If you admit that,
you're merely another victim.
Oh, and button up.
The whole school had been cleaned up
and turned into the optimal
environment for academics.
However, because of the
considerably immoral strategy
that was used upon certain students,
there would be a deep, black scar
engraved in their lives.
And the two that carried it out would
have to live with that burden forever...
Therefore,
they either became drunk with power and
felt a delusional sense of accomplishment,
or suffered greatly.
Whoa!
Your power's grown even more, Ritsu!
Corruption and guilt...
Those are the things that
become fuel for my powers.
Whatever it is, it's working!
Something eating at you?
Dimple, you just won't stop talking.
If I were able to control
my powers on my own,
would I be able to make you disappear?
Is his personality changing, too?
S-Seriously?
Amazing...
That's amazing, Kageyama-kun!
Do you want me to keep going?
Want me to fold your car
in half, Mitsuura-san?
What?!
What the hell happened?
Can I help you gentlemen?
According to Kamuro, he had you
plant all the evidence on us.
Are you the one who framed us?
I have no idea what you're talking about...
Dimple.
Leave it to me.
Even if I did,
it's too late.
Why, you little...
Who do you think we are?!
You little shit!
That does it! Get him!
Hey, there's a fight.
Scary!
But isn't that guy's hair even more amazing?
You're right!
Seriously?
Hey, you there.
Yes?
Gah! That's...
I think that's enough.
Top of
Teru's Head
If you grow dependent on that,
you're gonna get hurt.
Whoa, what is that?
You've got the wrong idea.
It's so long.
You think you're someone really special.
It's hard looking at someone
who reminds me of my old self.
This is a warning.
Don't try to live relying on psychic powers.
Are you an esper?
I don't know who you are,
but I have no need to take warnings from you.
Don't try to take a bite at him!
He's not someone you can beat!
I'm sure he's not much different from
the people at the Awakening Lab.
I want to compare powers with him.
Ritsu?! You idiot!
Stop!
Why, thank you for the handshake.
I'm Hanazawa Teruki. A pleasure.
Don't try to fight him, Ritsu!
Let go of his hand!
Having trouble staying on your own two feet?
Success
Academy
Ah, you're so young.
Now! Run!
I was surprised at how strong he was...
And...
His brain was so developed.
Is that why he was so strong?
No... That was just because
his wig didn't fit correctly.
Though I'm not sure why he's wearing it.
I'm so frustrated. I can't believe I
lost to someone other than Nii-san.
Dimple.
I want to get even stronger.
So I won't lose to anyone.
Little boy.
Do you have a moment?
Mob Psycho
This is the Vase of Happiness.
A renowned potter put his heart and soul
into making this, a very spiritual vase.
The owner will be blessed just
by having it in their house.
It's actually about 2.5 million yen,
but I'll make it 800,000 yen just for you.
I don't have that kind of money.
Then, I'll drop the price to 500,000 yen.
Uh, I don't have 500,000 yen, either.
So if you did, you'd buy it, right?
Why don't you call your mommy for me, then?
Seasoning General
Bank Note
Seasoning Bank
I don't think my mom will buy that.
This kid's easy bait...
Hey, why don't you touch it?
The texture here is a bit grainy
and it feels rather nice.
Er, I can't really tell.
That was close.
What was that?
You should be careful.
Huh?
Hey, you broke it.
Th-That was...
What? You're going to say it was my fault?
Huh? No...
Say, little boy...
Problems you can solve with money are
better than those you can't. Understand?
Oh, dear... Did you break that, sir?
Do you have a phone?
I-I don't...
Well, that rang at the perfect time.
Why don't you answer it?
What are you doing, Mob?
Calling me out here when I've got a
customer showing up at any moment...
Are you this boy's guardian, sir?
I see...
It's going to cost five million yen
to replace this.
You're telling me that Mob
broke that cheap-looking vase?
What'd you say?
Looks like you don't know
how the world works.
Want me to make sure you never work again?
Ow! Ow! You totally cracked my clavicle.
That's gonna cost you.
Huh?
The hospital bill with reparations
is gonna be a million yen.
Y-You can't be serious, you dumbass!
And now that's psychological damage,
which is going to be another million.
Hey!
Your breath stinks. That's another million.
The hell?!
Your voice is loud.
And that's another million.
Ah. You frayed my shirt.
That's another million for damages.
And now that's equal to what
he owes you for the vase.
That's the kind of business
you guys are running.
Let's go, Mob.
Like we'd let you leave like this!
Give it up!
His misfortune was decided when
he broke the Vase of Happiness.
Perhaps some disaster will befall him.
Misfortune? Disaster?
I was just talking to someone who
had been haunted by an evil spirit.
Apparently, the spirit has
now decided to haunt me.
And when that happens, you keep
hearing strange noises at night
and weird things keep popping up in
pictures, and it becomes unbearable.
Though the spirit might have
transferred to you guys now.
Be careful at night.
Huh?
A ghost?
Doesn't feel too great, does it?
That's exactly what you guys are doing.
A ghost? What are you, a kid? So scary!
That sure shut them up quick.
Ramen
Chinese Soba
That last bit was great, Mob.
Huh?
You shook the building to scare them, right?
No, I thought it was you sending
the evil spirit after them...
Could it be that you couldn't see—
Of course...
I could see it.
You know...
Con artists are really terrible people.
Yeah...
Only the lowest of the low try to take
advantage of someone's weakness...
What? You as well?
Student Council Room
Yes. He said, "So, you're trash, too?"
All I was doing was chewing gum during class.
Kamuro, this school doesn't belong to you.
We still have the smaller
pieces of trash to deal with.
Let's keep it moving.
You're still going to continue this?
Come now...
You're not going to suggest we stop, are you?
No. I just felt like throwing up.
You're just trying to
relieve some stress, right?
I was correct in choosing you
as an accomplice.
If you knew, why did you decide to help me?
Because I was tired.
I think I might have gotten tired of myself.
I just wanted to know what
it felt like to be a fool.
A fool, eh?
But in the end, we're popular.
We've become the heroes of the school.
So that old-looking guy wanted to be popular?
I've obtained a much bigger world.
By the way, President,
did you find any telepaths?
If I'd found any, I wouldn't be here.
Hey, Inukawa! Putting a
bomb there is cheating!
Put on Muscle!
Kurata, could you be a little quieter?
I'm not done talking to him yet.
Oh, sorry.
Musashi, that's enough.
No, it's not! Man up!
Go to class, Onigawara!
I've got no place there.
None of my friends will
even talk to me anymore.
Oh, a visitor...
The student council president!
I see this place is as rotten as they say.
More importantly...
What are you doing here, Onigawara-kun?
Put on Muscle! Burn the Fat!
Infiltrating the school when
you haven't been showing up to class?
No!
But if I stay at home,
my mom will ask me why—
Listen, President.
Onigawara didn't do anything.
Should I have you all dealt with
for being Onigawara's accomplices?
Wha—
President, some weird guy just
showed up at the school gates.
Good grief. They couldn't
have come at a worse time.
Bean Paste Middle School Gang
Leader: Kenzaki Yuuto
Who are you? I told you to
bring me White T Poison!
White T Poison? What on earth is that?
Stop fooling around! He's the
talk of all the thugs right now.
I'll deal with him.
That should settle things.
Th-That was surprising...
That was self-defense.
Not to mention, they were students from
another school, so it shouldn't matter.
To think he was one to fight...
And be that strong on top of it.
Hey, are you the one that got Kenzaki-san?
Huh?
Are you White T Poison?
Wh-What are you... I was just watching!
Then who the hell is White T Poison?!
I don't—
That's enough! It's time to stop!
You look awful.
I became a victim
because you taught a gang leader
from another school a lesson!
Don't you understand that?!
I'm fine with that. It's very much deserved.
A-Again?!
Mayo Middle School Gang Leader: Gozu
Are you White T Poison?
Kamuro
Oh, it's you, Tokugawa-kun.
Shinji doesn't want to see anyone right now.
I see...
What a terrible room filled with garbage.
I think what you should have
cleaned up was this room.
H-How did you get in here?
There are plenty of small pieces
of trash left at school.
I-I'm done with all of that! Get out!
It's too late.
We both did something unforgivable.
No one's going to save us.
The puppet's been broken.
Now the school is clean.
What are you going to do now?
The other schools are gonna show up again.
I can do whatever I want,
as long as I have these powers.
Yeah! You can be a superstar!
Dimple, you're trying to
use me, too, aren't you?
Wha?!
What are you talking about, Ricchan?
We're partners!
Akagi
Noodle Soup Base
Middle School Gang Leader
Bandai
Soy Sauce
Middle School Gang Leader
Mayo Middle School
Gang Leader: Gozu
Miso Middle School
Gang Leader: Fuji
And here they come.
There are quite a few today.
I came to see what was
going on and of course...
Are you the White T Poison that
defeated Hanazawa and Kenzaki?
What?! Is he pretending to be Kageyama?
I think things will be settled
once I deal with you guys,
so let's just say that I am.
Apparently, I'm gonna have to
ask Kageyama about this...
Looks like I found something
pretty interesting.
I've found him. I'll apprehend
him and head back.
But before that, I should watch for a bit
and see how good he is.
Possession.
All right. Go ahead.
You telling us to bring it?
Sounds good to us!
Hey! Don't chicken out now!
That's not it...
We can't move...
Dimple, we're going to go
a bit strong this time.
Chance!
Your magic tricks won't
work on me, White T Pois—
What the heck is going on?
Is White T Poison doing that?
Don't falter! Let's all charge him at once!
I will not judge you people.
Because I know now.
When people stray from the right path,
there usually isn't an actual reason.
It's like that even now.
I'm facing enemies that
have lost all will to fight,
and I'm moving forward
for the sake of violence.
There's no reason there.
This kind of freedom is strong.
I'm much freer than all of you.
Why?
Because I've lost my limits.
I've obtained loss.
Ritsu...
What are you doing?
The brothers finally confront each
other in an alleyway after school.
Then suddenly, an adult esper
we had previously seen appears.
Hey, Mob, that guy's really bad news.
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 Episode 8:
"The Older Brother Bows
~Destructive Intent~"
What do I recommend?
The Older Brother Bows
~Destructive Intent~
The convenient option A with the Blu-ray set!