The enemy is completely falling apart.
Take it! Now is the time to
achieve honor! Take it all now!
--Right!
--We'll give vent to our fifty years of anger!
Olminu!
Tell Yoichi. Extend the firing line.
Yoichi! Nobunaga said,
"Start shooting their rear. Break them."
Roger.
Musketmen! Keep reloading!
Don't let your fuse extinguish!
When Toyo falls back, we provide cover fire.
But since Toyo is Toyo,
he probably won't fall back...
In that case, we will also charge forward.
Can we keep this going?
No, I have a bad feeling about this.
It has the same smell as Kanegasaki.
Abandon the vanguard.
Infantry, temporarily pull back.
Rearguard, spread out.
Break down into smaller units.
Disperse through narrow streets and make
your way towards the Capitol Building.
I'll take care of the shock troopers.
I...
...and the Shinsengumi will end them.
"Act 12
Staring at Shinsengumi
~The Song of the Fervid Kyushu Man~"
Withdraw! Withdraw! Withdraw!
The enemy is falling back...
...with no rearguard.
They are retreating.
So, haven't we won this? We won, right?
The timing of that retreat was too good.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Lord Nobunaga! Lord Nobunaga!
A message from Yoichi on the roof!
The enemy has split into smaller squads and
has started spreading throughout the city!
They are setting the houses ablaze
and obscuring our vision!
Bad... This is really bad.
Hold it... What does that mean?!
But something is still off.
They are adapting far too quickly!
No way! Could the enemy leader...
...know about guns?
Someone is coming... all alone.
Toyo! Toyo! Nobunaga is calling for you!
The enemy... The enemy...
You all return to the main force.
This head is mine.
The Shimazu cross...
I will never forget that crest.
You know of the Shimazu clan?
Who are you?
Hijikata Toshizou Yoshitoyo
of the Shinsengumi.
Shimazu Toyohisa, undersecretary to
the Imperial Minister of the Center.
You are a warrior of the
Land of the Rising Sun, are you not?
The mere fact that you wear that crest...
The mere fact that you are
of the Shimazu clan of Satsuma...
...is more than enough reason to kill you!
You must hold real resentment
towards the Shimazu clan.
Kizakibaru, Mimikawa, Okitanawate,
Hetzugigawa, Sekigahara...
Or was it the Invasion of Korea?
I can think of so many possible reasons.
Just by looking at you,
I can tell you are not from my era.
Aha, I see. What have my
descendants done to you?
Die, Shimazu. You will
never be allowed to live.
Die. Do nothing but die.
Hmm?
They will never pardon you either.
Rebellious Satsuma,
your death shall come to pass!
What should we do, Nobu?
The enemy is...! Nobu!
What should we do...?
Should we spread out, too?
No, that won't work.
The destructive power of muskets can
only be fully brought out in a large unit.
First of all, they are lacking in experience.
If I break the force into squads,
no one will be qualified to lead them.
Should I send them all out together?
No, that will take too long,
and this castle town will be devastated.
What should I do?
What shall we do?
You're heavy, old fool!
This is easy.
We'll do berry smashing.
What the heck has the old man
started to do now?
Don't know. He's just an old man.
Please let him be.
What are you doing, old fool?!
I've had it with you, Lightning of Carthage!
It's much easier to smash them all at once!
They taste better smashed!
Ah!
Yoichi! Yoichi!
We have a situation here, too.
Toyo... and the enemy...
Nobu said to monitor the
enemy's movement from above.
Look down upon the entire city!
Are they rampaging on the streets?
Smoke... Are they randomly setting fires?
Just a moment. Please hold.
"Shake shake"
"Creak creak"
The height of Elves sure comes in handy.
Uh... Umm... Yoichi...
Ah... Abs... My abs...
Indeed, the enemy forces are scattered
and moving in a disorderly way.
They appear to be chaotic at a glance, but...
There's a method to it.
They are making a detour,
but they are probably heading
towards the Capital Building over there.
Is that so?
I see.
I totally see!
I know their intention now.
They haven't given up the
plot to conquer this state.
Their plan hasn't shifted...
...and won't be changed in the future.
They are persistent in executing their plan.
Everyone should leave the building!
Call Toyohisa up! Boobienue,
come over here too, now!
A map! Bring a map of this building!
Y-Yes.
The enemy leader may be an
expert in tactical maneuvering,
but he is an amateur in strategy.
No, that sounds a little strange.
"Conquer the state"?
The Ends are saying this?
Instead of annihilation,
they aim for conquest?
Come to think of it, that man was going
to take over Orte when he first appeared.
Are these the same Ends who seek
the eradication of the world?
What are they doing at the Northern Walls?
The Black King...
Do I know him?
This idiot is smiling.
Shimazu Toyohisa...
What kind of path has he taken?
Are you running away, Shimazu?
Shimazu!
Nyaa!
Plates... Foolish! Are you so desperate?!
You don't follow the way
of the warrior, do you?!
Huh?
This is a war. There's no justification
for taking the enemy's head.
There's no excuse we can make
to the enemy if we don't use
every trick at hand to hammer out a victory.
Shimazu!!
I can't listen to this anymore.
It's probably not intentional,
but Toyo is a genius
when it comes to infuriating his enemy.
No, this should work.
We have the advantage of
three frontline commanders.
That enemy took the bait that Toyo set.
Thus, he is too busy to command his troops.
The enemy forces are advancing this way,
faithfully following his orders.
What a pity for you, enemy leader!
In fact, the fool you've been
chasing around is only our leader.
"Drip drip"
Wait. I don't know what you're talking about.
Are you all set?
As soon as you are ready,
we'll get out of here quickly.
Yes, sir!
Then, we will let all the
enemy forces into the city.
We'll wait in the surrounding
buildings until they all enter.
At my signal, you'll all come out at once.
Olminu, I'll leave the rest to you.
We are here now.
This is it!
Charge forward!
Shimazu...!
You underestimated us.
You underestimated the Shinsengumi.
You won't be able to mess around for long.
Foolish.
Not once have I ever
underestimated you, not even once!
They are not here.
It's empty.
Why?!
This is a battlefield. I'll do
whatever I gotta, even mess around.
What the...?!
Good. Elves! Fire arrows!
Rain fire down on them!
Fire!
These are barrels of oil.
Get out of here!
Run!
Th-The enemy is...!
Wow... They die so easily...
We kill them so easily!
Wh...?! Ah... M-My charm was again...
...used for dreadful things.
What a great feeling to box the enemy
in and fan the flames around them!
This must be how that damn Mitsuhide
felt watching Honnoji Temple burn.
Nobu and Yoichi chose me as general,
but I never thought of myself that way.
After all... above all,
I am just an ambitious brat.
I can never be a warrior
like my uncle or my father.
However, he is different...
Oda Nobunaga, former Minister of the Right,
Demon King of the Sixth Heaven, is different!
If I stake my life to buy time for Nobunaga
to turn the tide, he will definitely succeed.
I'll do anything for that to happen,
messing around included.
You bastard...
Many Shimazu troops died at Sekigahara,
but those deaths became
the foundation of our success.
Even if we die, we don't die.
Thus, we can accomplish anything.
Shimazu!
Even if I am to die here,
Nobunaga will turn my death into
the foundation of our success.
It may take several ruthless steps.
That Shimazu attitude brought death to us!
I truly hate them.
I detest this damn clan who die smiling.
His eyes are almost boasting,
"We Shimazu are the only true samurai."
Those eyes...
I loathe them.
Toyo!
All right! Don't worry!
Go ahead! Fire everything my way!
OK!
What is he?
A fool?
Among all the people I have seen
from Satsuma, he is the greatest fool.
You brat!
You are truly mad!
War is already madness from the outset.
Hijikata...
Hijikata, this is your moment to withdraw.
Not yet! I have not lost yet!
That's right, you still haven't lost.
This victory is yours.
However, beyond this, there is no victory.
You're in the middle of a fight!
Who the hell are you talking to?!
Give up your head, you bastard!
You dead bastard!
Are you a monster?! Die! Hurry up and die!
Ah! Just leave your head, jackass!
Argh... I can't even back him up
in such close combat.
Ahh, greetings.
Shimazu!
Withdraw. That is my order.
Hmm?
Come back down here!
Isn't the true battle just about to start?!
I thought I finally had the chance to fight
against a "samurai" from
the Land of the Rising Sun...
I won't forgive you for flying off like this!
Come back down, so I can take your head!
You bastard!
A little while ago, weren't you the one
running from me and messing around?
Don't mind him. Let's go.
Yes, sir.
I thought I would get to fight a "samurai"
from the Land of the Rising Sun...
Samurai... Samurai...
Me?
Defeated... but victorious.
Toyo! Hey, Toyo!
P-Please forgive me.
Black Lord, before my very eyes,
I let your army...
Yet they didn't die in vain.
We obtained a great outcome
from this probing assault.
We were also able to cripple
the capital of Orte.
I heard that it is called a "test war"
in your country, right, Koreto?
That voice, his manner of speech...
There is no doubt.
I can never forget or mistake it...
Nobunaga... No wonder we couldn't
find his remains at the temple.
If I get to kill the idiot Nobunaga...
I, Akechi Koreto Mitsuhide,
will join your force.
"Encampment"
"Gigant"
"Professional Savior"
"Act 13
Rewrite"