Fire!
Send word to the lords of
every domain in Melromarc.
Ma'am.
As you wish.
That is no ordinary forest fire.
That woman probably started it.
She's trying to smoke us out.
Sister...
The fire will spread here soon.
We're leaving.
The checkpoint's been closed,
and there's an emergency security
deployment along the border.
It's gonna be impossible to cross
over to Siltvelt for a while.
It seems the Devil of the Shield
has abducted Princess Melty,
and is hiding in this area.
Will this be enough?
Sure. Let me get your change.
Huh? Sir?
Have you seen this man around?
Oh, Master.
How'd it go, Naofumi-sama?
We should probably give
up on going to Siltvelt.
Which means...
Shield Hero, you are requested to meet
with Her Majesty the Queen, I daresay.
Is doing as that Shadow
said our only option?
What's the plan, Naofumi?
We're going to meet the queen.
The Rising of the Shield Hero
Everlasting Memory
There are a lot of demi-humans
in this region.
Yeah.
Are we in... I see!
What is it?
A nobleman I know is in
charge of this domain.
He may be able to help us out.
A nobleman?
These days, humans treat
demi-humans like slaves,
but in the past, some of the
nobility tried to mediate
peaceful coexistence between the two races.
The leader of that group
was a wonderful man.
He was the lord of the domain of Seyaette.
But he died in the first Wave,
and the nobles that sided with him
were all shuffled off to remote
regions under Father's orders.
That guy's hatred of demi-humans is absurd.
What's wrong, Raphtalia?
The village I'm from is in
Seyaette's jurisdiction.
I heard Seyaette was attacked
by rioters after the Wave.
That's right.
My village was attacked by a
mob of Melromarc's soldiers.
The more I hear about these people,
the more they disgust me.
I'm so sorry.
It's not like it was your fault, Melty-chan.
As royalty, there must have been
something we could have done.
But we did nothing to help.
Raphtalia-san, tell me everything
you remember about those soldiers.
Once this all dies down, I'll make
sure they're brought to justice.
Okay.
And? This nobleman you
know lives here, right?
Yes.
The question is whether
or not we can trust him.
You are indeed right.
It's been too long, Reichnott.
Welcome, Melty-sama.
Pleased to meet you.
I am Van Reichnott, the lord of this domain.
This feeble guy is the
nobleman she mentioned?
But his stealthiness is off
the charts. What's with him?
This is no place for a chat.
Would you like to join me at my mansion?
I see.
So you reached my domain
after a long escape, is it?
Yeah.
The knights informed me that
you started the wildfires
to cover your tracks, Shield Hero.
That's a complete lie.
The first princess probably made it all up.
Just as I thought.
I was patrolling the area out
of concern for Melty-sama, too.
You must be exhausted from your travels.
Please rest up here for
a while, if you wish.
May I eat, Master?
No, wait.
I don't trust this guy yet.
Ah, this is delicious.
Rest assured, the food isn't poisoned.
Time to eat!
Filo!
Where are your manners?
Ugh...
Let us eat too, Naofumi-sama.
Casting doubts on such gracious hospitality?
How rude can you be?
We shouldn't stay here too long.
We're leaving tomorrow morning.
That soon?
The longer we stay, the higher the
odds of us being sniffed out.
Well, yes...
But I was hoping to rest some more.
You've changed a little, Princess Melty.
You used to force yourself
to act more mature,
but it seems traveling with the Shield Hero
has helped you grow in a good way.
I'm pretty sure you mean in a bad way.
Sh-Shut up!
Don't make a racket while we're eating.
Whose fault do you think it is?!
This bed feels amazing!
So soft and bouncy!
Why don't you sleep for a bit?
We don't know when this
place will get attacked.
I make a point of not sleeping
at times like these.
Naofumi-sama, I'll keep watch,
so you can go ahead and sleep.
All right.
Why do you listen to what
Raphtalia-san says, but not me?
It's not like that.
Mel-chan, I wanna explore this place.
Sure. Let's go.
I wonder if they have any yummy snacks.
Couldn't you be a bit nicer to her?
What's wrong, Mel-chan?
I think I've been acting really
spoiled since meeting Naofumi.
My speech has become cruder, too.
It's like I'm a different person.
Uh...
Sorry. You don't understand, do you?
I love the way you are now, Mel-chan.
I mean, you look so cheerful
when you're talking to Master.
Th-That's not right...
Mel-chan, have him dote on you just like us!
D...
Dote on me?!
Yep!
That's n-not what I'm looking for!
You still haven't found her?!
Know that I'll have your heads
if anything happens to Melty!
Yes, sir!
Please rest assured, Father.
I promise you that I shall rescue Melty.
Please.
Not my family again.
How much will you make me suffer?
Accursed Shield!
You're up?
Yeah. I'll take over now.
It's fine.
I'm not very sleepy.
Really?
Say, Naofumi...
What?
Should I really keep running like this?
As crown princess, there are so many
other things I should be doing.
But I haven't been able to do any of them.
Your life comes first.
You can worry about your
duties after you're safe.
But I feel so pathetic.
Don't beat yourself up
too much. Get some rest.
Okay.
I'm sure there are things
that only you can do.
Thanks.
Huh?
It's nothing. Never mind.
Good night.
Yeah.
Please... Stop...
Is she having that same nightmare again?
Rifana-chan!
You okay?
Y-Yes.
We've got bad news.
Why is the lord being taken away?
Sir Hero! You must get out of here at once!
What happened?
A nobleman from the next town over marched
in here and accused us of hiding you!
Find the Devil of the Shield!
Use the kitchen door and
escape out the back.
Where are Filo and Melty?
Did you find him?
No, he's not here.
This way.
Hey, you there!
What are you doing?
Getting ready for lunch.
Forget that! Get over here!
What do you think you're doing?
I am Melty Melromarc,
Second Princess of Melromarc.
I demand that you cease
this behavior at once!
The second princess?
The real deal?
My, if it isn't Princess Melty.
Aren't you...
Let's wait and see what happens.
I'm so glad to see you're all right.
I rushed here worried for your safety.
Idol Rabier...
I've heard that you fought
with Father in the past.
You heard right.
Are these your troops?
They are indeed.
Have them withdraw from
this mansion immediately.
Before that, where is the
Devil of the Shield?
The Shield Hero isn't here.
Oh?
I asked him to leave me and escape.
That girl...
I plan to speak with Father directly.
And I shall clear the
Shield Hero's good name!
You will take me to the
capital as soon as possible.
I understand.
I'll make arrangements for
your journey at my mansion.
Take her.
Calm down.
Do you want to ruin what
Melty's trying to do?
Filo! Where are you?
Filo?
Filo-chan!
Where are you?
Oh, to hell with it.
Filo!
Get out here now! This is an order!
Master, you meanie!
It's your fault for not showing yourself.
What were you even doing up here?
What?
Mel-chan wanted to play hide and seek.
She said I should hide somewhere
I wouldn't be found
and not come out, no matter what.
But she never came for me in the end.
Huh?
Where's Mel-chan?
I'm going to save Mel-chan!
Wait, Filo!
But if we don't hurry up, she'll...
Abandoning her and running
away is an option.
But she believed in me.
I... don't want to betray someone
who placed their trust in me.
I did make her a promise.
You know that Idol guy, don't you?
Yes.
You can stay behind if you want.
No. I have my sword now.
I want to confront my past!
Got it.
Open the gate!
What's going on?
Demi-humans who love their lord
must've come here for him.
Give back Van-sama!
This is convenient. We'll sneak into the
mansion while they distract the guards.
Let's go.
Right!
'Kay!
Ugh, those damned demis!
What is happening outside?
Just some flies buzzing around. It's
nothing you need to worry about.
We'll get rid of them at once.
Now, will you tell me where
the Devil of the Shield is?
As I've told you several
times, I do not know.
Reichnott?!
Where is the Devil of the Shield?
I know no such person.
The only one I know is
called the Shield Hero.
As you see, we're having a hard time
getting him to spill the beans.
I would very much like to avoid
getting rough with you if possible.
But as a servant of God,
I must punish anyone who
sides with the Devil.
That is my sacred duty.
Intruders!
Go wild, Filo.
We'll go rescue Melty in the meantime.
'Kay!
After them!
Mel-chan!
What's down there?
Rescuing Melty takes priority for now.
We can come back later.
Okay.
Found them!
Over there!
Chimera Viper Shield Exclusive Skill — Venomous Fang (Med)
That's a highly potent venom.
If you don't use an antidote quickly,
you'll die.
But I'm willing to save your
life if you listen to me.
Where is Melty?
Stay away!
I love that valiant look in your eyes!
I want to see it become despair,
and your face warp in agony.
Let me have a good look at you!
Tch! What now?
Idol-sama! It seems the Devil of the Shield
has infiltrated the mansion!
What?
Mel-chan!
Filo-chan?
Raphtalia-san!
Don't move!
Take one step forward, and the
princess's head will fly.
So we just have to stand still, right?
Air Strike Shield!
Naofumi!
Why did you come?
Because I've never heard of a hero
who abandons a child to run away.
Now you've wasted all my efforts.
But...
Thanks.
You dare make a mockery of me?
Torture isn't enough for the likes of you!
You will pay with your lives!
Onee-chan!
Wait.
Lowly demi!
W-Wait...
Don't.
S-Spare me!
So many demi-humans begged for
their lives just like that,
but you...
Raphtalia