Kochi kite hayaku! Kochi kite suguni!
こち来て早く! こち来てすぐに!
Hurry over here! Come over here now!
San-nin mou jishitsuwase
三人も実質わせ
We need all three of us!
Jugyou no ato de Sensei ni Bye Bye!
授業の後で先生にバイバイ!
Say "Bye Bye" to the teacher after school!
Taisou fuku wa motte kaeru
体操服はもって帰る
Get my P.E uniform and go home!
Koutei shuugou asobimasuka
校庭集合遊びますか
Wanna play in the school yard?
Demo demo datte iiwake shinai no
でも!でも!だって言い訳しないの
But but I won't make any excuses
Shukudai nante hottoko yo
宿題なんでほっとこうよ
Who cares about homework!
Tetsubou shuugou mawarimasu yo
鉄棒しゅうごう回りますよ
Just swing around the metal bar in the yard.
randoseru wa sou akai tsuyoi
ランドセルはそう！あかい！つよい！
Our bag is all red and mighty!
hitotsu futatsu
一つ！二つ！
One, Two...
mitsu narabete mujubaku naru
三つ並べて矛盾ばくなる！
The three of us make no sense!
houkago wa dashu!
放課後はダシュ!
After school, you dash!
abarete wasurede genki dashite
暴れて忘れで元気出して
Just forget all about it!
Ignored.
Sen Nou!
セン、ノウ！
One, Two!
Oni-san, achira! sono kado magaru
鬼さん、あちら！その角曲がる！
Hey, its over there! Round the corner!
Koutei Dai-shugo!
校庭大しゅご!
Schoolground big parade!
Watashi wa dare deshou?
私はだれでしょう？
Who the hell am I?
Tanoshii de mainichi ookiku nare ba
楽しいで毎日、大きくなれば
If you have fun and grow up everyday.
asobenaino, shiritai, shiranai, shiritai!
遊べないの? 知りたい、知らない、知りたい！
Dont you wanna play? I wanna know, I dunno, but I wanna know!
Tanoshii de mainichi chiisai na koto de!
楽しいで毎日小さいな事で!
Enjoy all the little things everyday.
warai aidara sore wa sore de ureshii
笑い会えたら、それはそれで嬉しい
Just seeing a smile makes me happy!
sore mou kore mou dore mou
それも、これも、どれも！
Like this one, that one; and that one too!
sanningoko setsuwase wow!
三人五個せつわせ！　ＷＯＷ！
Then it's the fine whether its three or five!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
The triplets are unstoppable
Although it's the start of spring, it is still very cold today.
Is maintaining your image that important to you?
Huh? What's an i-image?
Today sure is w-wa-war-warm!
Are you a special agent or something?!
You're trying too hard!
Geez, your face is all red. I bet you have a fever.
Oh?! You're being rather nice, Mitsuba-chan!
W-What are you saying?! I just don't want to catch anything from her!
Mitsuba-chan! Someone take her to the infirmary!
I don't wanna, she's disgusting.
My nose is all runny.
Today, we will be looking at "averages" and how to find them.
Let's start with...
My nose won't stop running.
If it doesn't stop soon, I might die of dehydration!
Shocking Truth!
Tragedy. A young girl in Grade 6
Killed by a runny nose!
My sister died from
a runny nose!
One million copies sold!
Sis died from runny nose
By Marui Hitoha
So pitiful!
The t-tissues!
Even the tissue gods have given up on me?!
I guess I'll have to use my notes!
I wanna eat boobies
with wasabi and soy sauce.
I can't do it! It's a waste of good sketches!
For some reason, these sketches came out really good!
It's all over.
I don't even have any textbooks with me!
Empty!
Finding averages
So if you divide it by the number of people, you can find the average.
Yabe-cchi!
What's wrong, Futaba-chan?
Sensei, you made a mistake on the board.
Yabe-cchi!
Sensei, your mistake!
Sensei, Yabe-
Geez, one at a time!
Geez...
This is bad! It keeps coming out!
Yabe-cchi, I'll take it all back now!
Stop spinning around and fix your mistake!
Even if you say that...
S-Sorry!
I can't get it off!
The average of the four people is 8.6 seconds.
A-san took 7.8 seconds.
Yabe-cchi is a talented hypnotist.
I can't sleep face down like this!
But I can't beat the afternoon drowsiness!
What the hell? Disgusting!
Sleep while facing forward!
And close your eyes properly!
You stupid, stupid, stupid...
What's with this dirty arm?!
How noisy...
I can't believe it; it's all sticky and wet!
Geez, face forward!
Huh?! If you sleep in a place like that, you'll catch a cold.
S-Someone take her to the infirmary!
I don't wanna, she's disgusting.
Infirmary
I'm really sorry...
My students are always causing trouble for you.
No, it's fine. It's great to be energetic!
Okay, let's sterilize it.
Mit-chan, that lump looks like a huge plum!
That stupid Futaba!
Let's see who gets hit - rock, scissors, paper!
Go away!
How many times are you going to try and kill me in this anime?!
Calm down, Mitsuba-chan.
I'm from Class 4-1.
I've brought back the urine samples.
Okay!
Thanks for your help!
Zoom zoom!
Woah! It's urine from thirty people?
Yeah.
Ah! The urine!
She tripped over nothing!
Is this the legendary klutz?!
O-Oh no!
Kuriyama-sensei, your knee! It's squashing them!
Nooo!
The urine! The urine!
Kuriyama-sensei, are you alrig-
It reeks of urine!
Ah, please be quiet. There's a girl sleeping at the back.
It's all your fault!
And hurry up and stop my bleeding! Are you going to let me die?!
C-Calm down.
Don't touch me after you touched the urine!
I-I'm so sorry!
I'm really ashamed of myself.
Everyone makes mistakes.
I'm not even worth pitying.
Geez.
That stinks! Isn't it urine?!
I mistook it for the disinfectant!
Who would mistake it with urine?! Are you just trying to kill me?!
No I'm not! I'm really sorry!
I'll do it myself! I don't have enough lives for this.
Here, have a drink.
Thanks.
Futaba you idiot!
It's all your fault to begin with!
Don't get too depressed over it.
Maybe I'm not fit for this job after all.
Urine! That's urine, sensei!
I've mistaken it for the milk!
I'm sure you're just too tired.
Maybe that's it.
Like I said! That's urine!
No! I've had enough of this!
That's my line, you idiot!
Sensei, I've brought the urine samples from Class 3-4.
Steady...steady!
Stay calm!
Watch your step!
O-Okay.
I'll clear the way for you!
You can leave all the obstacles to me!
Thank you so much.
Umm Futa...Mitsu...Hito...Mitsuha-chan!
It's Futaba.
Please remember it next time.
Is this where you store the samples?
Gently... Gently put it down.
O-Okay.
I-I did it!
Congratulations!
Good work, Kuriyama-cchi!
They're getting squashed again, Kuriyama-sensei!
T-This is the battle of the United Urine!
Be quiet.
Why did you put them on a sleeping child?!
I didn't know she was there!
This stress is going to kill me.
Saturday Morning
Kuriyama-sensei, I didn't expect you to be this bold.
That tickles, Kuriyama-sensei.
N-No, not there!
There're people watching!
P-Please, just spare my l-life!
Help! Please stop, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Eh?! Hitoha-chan! Sorry, I thought I saw a demon or something!
Good morning to you too.
Wait, why are you here in the first place?
I came to see Nipples.
Oh, that's right. I look after it when there's no one at school.
W-Wait a second! I locked my door right?!
I made a spare key during handicraft class.
You made it yourself?!
T-That's amazing, but you can't just copy someone else's key!
Hitoha-chan, it's alright to come here...
but it'll be nice to make an appointment with me.
Nipples doesn't accept appointments.
No! An appointment with me!
I'm only here to see Nipples.
Don't mind me, read as much porn as you want.
As if I'd read them!
Even though you always ignore me at school.
Only at times like this...
Ignore? I don't ignore you!
That's a lie.
I've always been here every morning on weekends and holidays.
You never notice me.
I'm not lyin-
Every morning?!
That's all there is to my existence, huh...
That's not true!
It's always bothered me; and I've always been looking at you, Hitoha-chan!
Sensei...
I've always been looking at you, Hitoha-chan!
Here's Nipples.
The stuff you said just now, I wonder what would happen if the police heard it.
I'll be back tomorrow.
Next Morning
She's not here yet?
Well, it is still five in the morning.
Nipples is gone!
D-Did it sneak out at night?!
What should I do? At this rate-
Hitoha-chan's coming!
Where's Nipples...
Where is Nipples?
M-My life is going to be ruined!
Nipples, where are you?!
Nipples...Nipples...Nipples...
Nipples...Nipples...please answer me!
Satoshi
Sensei... I know you're in there.
I-I'm scared!
I'll copy the tape and release it everywhere...
and of course, I'll give Kuriyama-sensei a copy too.
Nipples...Where are you?!
Ah! There it is!
Wait!
At this rate, it'll escape outside!
Hitoha-chan, close the door!
Nipples, I missed you.
Umm... Can the Marui family look after Nipples on weekends and holidays too?
I've already told you, it's too dangerous at our house.
Oops, I nearly stepped on it!
Squishy little animals...squishy little animals!
You're right...
Kamohashi
National Park
Mit-chan, thanks for helping me catch cicadas. You sure are nice today.
You're welcome. I am your older sister after all.
It's only because I want to see that innocent face...
distorted by despair as I squash them!
I can't wait for that moment!
Is that high enough for you?
That hurts. Wait! St-
Can you stop it?!
Just you wait... I'm going to show you what despair is!
I caught one!
Look! It's an American crayfish!
Cool! You're good!
I found one!
Futa-Futa-Futaba!
Fu-Futaba!
Where the hell did she go?
I-I need to calm down!
If I keep edging towards the tree...
The cicada from before!
Y-You're in the way! I'm going to squash you if you don't move!
I-It's not like I feel sorry for you or anything!
I just don't want to get my hands all dirty...
That's why I'm hesitating!
W-What the hell is that?
T-That voice is...
These are... a pair of legs?
It's Satou and Chibara from my class!
H-Help m-
Judging from her panties...
She's probably a five-or-six-year-old in kindergarten.
Kindergarten?!
I'm supposed to be the most powerful person in grade 6!
If people found out that I wear the same panties as a five-or-six-year-old...
No!
Everything that I've built up, the respect and honor...
What kind of judgement is that...
Hey!
I don't know who you are; but I'll help you down now.
Ouch!
Satou! Hey! We said we're going to help you!
I'm just some random five-or-six-year-old!
Get away from me!
What's the hell is with her...
That kick definitely wasn't from a five-or-six-year-old!
Hurry up and get away!
Get the hell away from me!
You idiot, just stay there forever then!
Satou, let's go.
That was a waste of energy.
See ya, sis!
Let's play again some other time!
I sure caught a lot!
Even the crows are gone, time to go home!
Zoom zoom!
I caught a lot! I caught a lot!
At this rate, I'm going to be stuck here till night-time!
Should I just fall; or should I squash it?
Oh that's right, cicadas only live for around a week anyway.
Compared to a stupid bug, I'm obviously more important...
I'm home...
Hito, we went crayfishing today!
We sure caught a lot!
I peeled the skin off live frogs and used it as bait!
Ah! Welcome back Mit-chan, where did you go?
Y-You demon in sheep's clothing!
You went home without me on purpose didn't you?!
Oh, I forgot...
Die! Go die in a hole!
I'm sorry! I'm really sorry!
Mit-chan, you're all dirty, get out of our house.
I'm injured! At least ask if I'm alright!
Geez. Just die, all of you!
Kotei ni yuuhi ga ochite
校庭に夕日が落ちて
The sunset reflected on the schoolgrounds.
te wo futte ie ni kaeru
手を振っていえに帰る
Let's hold hands and go home.
bedo no naka de mata konya
べドの中でまた今夜
Laying in my bed tonight.
kyou no kimi ni aitetara ii na
今日の君に会えたらいいな
It would be nice if I could meet you again.
ikou! Nemurou!
行こう！眠ろう！
Let's go! Let's sleep!
Asa made matte nai
朝まで待ってない！
I can't wait till morning!
totemo suteki sa
とても素敵さ
It's really wonderful,
sora motomeru no sa
空求めるのさ
just wishing upon the sky.
kimi to te wo tsunai de
君と手をつないで
Just holding hands with you,
Mune ga itaku nata
胸が痛くなた
makes my heart beat.
Yume no naka demo
夢の中でも
Even though it's only a dream,
Yume iro no Koi
夢色の恋
it's a lovely dream.
There used to be plenty of empty space around here.
As more and more people moved here, there's not much space to play anymore.
It was where I used to find lots of porn!
Next Episode: There's lots of intruders!
Damn it!
That's what you were after?!