No...
Please...
DON'T!
Senketsu!
Good grief.
How many times am I going to have to
tend to you after you've passed out?
How about changing careers and
becoming a Nudist like me?
Spout off any of your lame
jokes, and I'm gonna kill you.
Ah, sorry, sorry. So, who took you out?
It was Nui Harime. Nagita was Nui.
Oh, so that's what happened.
You found me unconscious,
dressed like this?
Yeah. If I had arrived on
the scene a little later,
you would've been arrested by
the cops for indecent exposure.
Do you have a death wish?
Snippy, aren't you?
Of course I am. I...
I lost Senketsu.
To Nui Harime?
That's right. He was
chopped to pieces by her.
I was weak and couldn't summon up any
of his power, either,
and he got shredded...
I haven't been lost!
If you try any lame impersonations,
I mean it, I'm going to kill you.
Hey, cut me some slack.
I'm not doing anything.
Ryuko, calm yourself.
See, you're doing it again!
I have him right here.
Senketsu, you're alive?! What a relief!
Only because you held
on to me so tightly.
And the rest? Where's the rest of you?
The sleeves? The shoulders? The skirt?
Huh?
I didn't see anything
else when I got there.
Just you, lying there
unconscious, clutching that
scarf like your life depended on it.
Ryuko, my shredded body
has been divvied up
amongst the School Raid Trip students.
So the rest of you is in Kansai, huh?
Exactly. It was Satsuki Kiryuin's doing.
Damn that Satsuki, always
screwing with me...
Huh? What're you doing
here, Mr. Mikisugi?
Unfortunately, I'm no longer a teacher.
The time has now come.
Today, I bid farewell to
my cover identity as the
homeroom teacher for Honnouji
Academy's Second Year, Class K.
Today, I return to being
my unadorned self!
A Splendid Naked Officer, the
nude warriors of Nudist Beach
who do battle against the
threat of Life Fibers!
Aikuro Mikisugi! Let's begin!
NUDIST BEACH SPLENDID NAKED
OFFICER AIKURO MIKISUGI
Come on, Nude Shooting Star!
Farewell, students of Honnouji Academy!
What the hell was all that about?
EPISODE 14
RIDE LIKE THE WIND
I have selected students with
high Life Fiber tolerance,
and am dividing up the various
parts of Kamui Senketsu among them.
They will be affixed to their
School Raid-spec Goku Uniforms,
and I will ascertain whether
they can be employed
as a power-up item that
will boost their abilities.
Good.
KYOTO
The Kyoto Raid Trip Brigade
under Nonon Jakuzure,
KOBE
the Kobe Raid Trip Brigade
under Ira Gamagoori
and the Osaka Raid Trip
Brigade under Uzu Sanageyama,
OSAKA
have each arrived at their
respective destinations.
TRI-CITY SPECIAL INTELLIGENCE
UNIT HOUKA INUMUTA
The Tri-City Special Intelligence
Unit also stands ready.
The info-nets of each city's
academies have already been seized.
The information networks of each
academy have been isolated,
and all phone and net connections
are under our management.
Good.
This operation's success will
place all of Kansai's high schools
under our umbrella in one fell swoop.
TRI-CITY SCHOOLS RAID TRIP
Tri-City Schools Raid
Trip... commence operation!
Kami-Kobe High School Armed Faction
Alliance Representative Kyuji Obayashi!
KAMI-KOBE HIGH SCHOOL ARMED FACTION
ALLIANCE REPRESENTATIVE KYUJI OBAYASHI
Deputy Armed Faction Alliance
Representative Kenta Sakuramiya!
DEPUTY ARMED FACTION ALLIANCE
REPRESENTATIVE KENTA SAKURAMIYA
We won't let them take
a single step past here!
Molotov cocktails! Cut loose!
We got help from the
American School, too!
We'll drive 'em out with the power of
their Armed American Football Corps!
I am Ira Gamagoori, Honnouji
Academy Tri-City School
KOBE REGION SCHOOL RAID TRIP
BRIGADE LEADER IRA GAMAGOORI
Raid Trip Kobe Region School
Raid Trip brigade leader!
If you engage in armed resistance,
we are prepared to retaliate in kind!
Enhanced Disciplinary
Committee Members, deploy!
What the hell?
We're gonna feed you to our
armored protective gear!
All hands, charge!
Let's go!
Fire!
Oh, My God!
What the—?
To a student, school regulations
are heavier than stone!
The Disciplinary Guidebook
in which these rules
are inscribed is harder than steel!
HONNOUJI ACADEMY DISCIPLINARY GUIDEBOOK
Honnouji Academy's school
regulations are as steel!
Ironclad rules!
Do you believe that such armor
can stay our ironclad rules?!
Taste our Full Metal Disciplinary
Guidebook Regulation Hurricane!
FULL METAL DISCIPLINARY
GUIDEBOOK REGULATION HURRICANE
I-Impossible!
Do you see now the might
of Honnouji Academy?!
This is the might of Student
Council President Satsuki Kiryuin!
Let's play this fortissimo, everyone!
KYOTO REGION SCHOOL RAID TRIP
BRIGADE LEADER NONON JAKUZURE
What's up with this?
Welcome, warriors of the East.
Abekamo Academy, which has stood for a
thousand years here in
the ancient capital,
is the linchpin of Kyoto's defenses!
If you wish to avoid a painful
fate, begone at once.
Fail to do so, and
you will be baptized in a
flood of demons and monsters.
Listen to you, trying to sound big!
It's not like your school has
stood for a thousand years!
What are these things?
They're monsters!
They're gonna eat us!
Guardian Student of
the North, Taro Genbu!
GUARDIAN STUDENT OF THE NORTH TARO GENBU
Guardian Student of the
South, Jiro Suzaku!
GUARDIAN STUDENT OF
THE SOUTH JIRO SUZAKU
Guardian Student of the
East, Saburo Seiryu!
GUARDIAN STUDENT OF
THE EAST SABURO SEIRYU
Guardian Student of the
West, Shiro Byakko!
GUARDIAN STUDENT OF
THE WEST SHIRO BYAKKO
Do you see? This is the
Divine Four Formation,
the impenetrable defense
of Abekamo Academy!
You Kanto barbarians cannot defeat it!
What're you talking about?
It's so obvious that these
monsters are all illusions!
Stay calm, everyone!
This is just a psychological attack!
What fascinating people.
Would you mind if I
fought them for a while?
Inumuta?! I thought you were in Osaka!
What are you doing here?
Don't be startled.
This is merely a hologram
projected by the Film Club.
Armed Arts Club! Advance!
This is a non-Euclidean space creation
ritual calculated by the Math Club.
Art Club members, use this as
a basis for a Paradox Painting!
Our barrier! Impossible!
ESCHER TOPOLOGY ATTACK
An Escher Topology Attack.
What's that?
The Divine Four Formation
employs geomagnetism
to envelop this location in
special electromagnetic waves,
thereby causing disruptions in the
nerve signals of the human brain.
The picture they just drew
altered this area's phase space
and disrupted its geomagnetism!
In short, they have
negated their barrier!
I didn't understand a word of that,
but I guess one obnoxious jerk is
effective against a bunch of obnoxious jerks.
In that case, you should have no
trouble "pwning" them now. See?
You uncouth boors and
your strange words!
You leave us no choice but to fight!
This isn't my scene. I leave
them in your capable hands.
Thanks for nothing.
Okay, let's get jazzed up!
Armed Wind Instrument Club!
Combat Orchestration!
Pomp and Circumstance 'em!
NANIWA KINMAN HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
COUNCIL PRESIDENT KANEO TAKARADA
I'm surprised you came, worthless
slime of Honnouji Academy.
I am Kaneo Takarada, Naniwa Kinman
High School Student Council President!
You may have thought you were
hot stuff in Kobe and Kyoto,
but you're not so tough here in Osaka!
OSAKA REGION SCHOOL RAID TRIP
BRIGADE LEADER UZU SANAGEYAMA
Well, well, you've heard
rumors of the other cities?
I thought that we had cut off
your information network.
I hate to break it to you,
but I have powerful allies in
the form of Osakan grannies.
They'll spread rumors
in the blink of an eye.
Even if you lock down the
net, you can't stop a rumor.
Listen up, I'm gonna tell
you the rules of this town.
Osaka here is a merchant town!
It's money that makes
this town go 'round!
He who has the most coin wins!
Money? Philistine.
We have come to bring down those
like you who reek of the old system
in order to create the
new world order that Satsuki
Kiryuin strives to achieve!
You're adorable. You naive, naive thing.
A guy who don't know the
fearsomeness of money
shouldn't be offering up
opinions about society.
I'm gonna wake you up to reality
by smacking you in the
face with wads of cash!
All right, people! Let 'em have it!
I'm gonna kill ya!
Guns?
It's bills, sir!
They're shooting at us, using
wads of bills as bullets!
They're literally using
money as a weapon!
I put my money where my mouth is!
If I've made my point, get lost!
Judging from the feel, these aren't
Bank of Japan notes, are they?
Counterfeit bills, huh?
They ain't counterfeit!
They're Takarada Bucks!
Takarada Bucks?
Exactly. They're redeemable
paper currency.
As wealthy people, the name
of the Takarada Conglomerate
is as good as gold here in Osaka.
They have more value than the
debt-riddled national currency.
But a northern Kanto hick like you
wouldn't understand any of that!
How dare you!
If you go on mocking northern Kanto,
I'll grind you up with our
konnyaku root harvest!
Not if we turn youse jerks
into takoyaki first! Get 'em!
Armed Ping Pong Club! Step forward!
As well as the Sumo
Club! Sumo Stomp Attack!
Armed Archery Club and Armed Track Club!
Ultra long range squads! Salvo attack!
Not bad, kiddo!
Now, storm the school building!
Over my dead body! Force 'em back!
You can withstand Goku Uniforms?!
The Kiryuins ain't the only
conglomerate around here.
Don't underestimate the might of
the Takarada Conglomerate's money!
It's gonna break my heart
if I came all this way
to Osaka and all I got to do was
this stupid ball bucket brigade!
Hey, that's--
It's the veritable symbol of Osaka!
Jumbo takoyaki sold by a street vendor!
It just isn't a trip to Osaka
without eating some of those!
OSAKA
But I've got no money!
I got dragged here without knowing why,
so I'm flat broke right now! Penniless!
Boy, I sure wish somebody
fire some money my way!
There is! There's a guy who's
spreading money around with a gun!
Bastard! I'm gonna send
youse straight to Hell!
Not to Hell! It's Heaven
that I'm going to!
Go on, shoot me!
You don't toy with Mako Mankanshoku
when she sees something she wants!
Who the hell are you?
No way...
Bye!
Hi, Mister! Takoyaki, please!
I've got plenty of cash!
That's the Osaka-style
okonomiyaki that you eat with
a spatula instead of chopsticks,
and that's kushikatsu, which
you're not allowed to double dip!
And ketsune udon, not kitsune!
And best of all is the butaman, the
ikayaki, the negiyaki, and more!
Now this is Osaka! A
Victory Road of food!
You are all that remain!
Attack!
Sorry, did I surprise you?!
This is a little something we had
the Russian mafia smuggle in.
I don't know 'bout no Goku Uniforms,
but can clothes stand up to a tank?!
Don't make me repeat myself!
Our ironclad rules will tear through
the armor of a mere tank like paper!!
What do you think of this?!
The very latest in Kobe's specialty
product, composite meat armor!
KOBE SPECIALITY PRODUCT,
COMPOSITE MEAT ARMOR
Your hard "ironclad rules"
or whatever get swallowed up
by that beautiful Kobe beef marbling
and melt away into nothing!
No, be a good boy and
surrender, Gamagoori.
Laughable! If you think you can
make me, let's see you try!
Dumbass... Fire!
Fortified Disciplinary Unit, forward!
Discipline!
Oh crap! It's coming back!
That's hot! Hot!
Ow! It burns!
The meat is burning! Nom!
It's so good!
A Kamui power-up is most
impressive, all right.
Magnificent... Now, finish them!
So, you seem to have lost
your final trump card.
Surrender peacefully, Obayashi!
You! Matoi!
I came to get Senketsu back!
Lovely, what a beautiful sound!
Adding a Kamui lets you play
such beautiful music together!
I guess that about does it.
Transfer student! What
are you doing here?!
I don't have time to
mess around with you.
What's with that attitude?!
Why?
My bamboo sword is more than
enough for the likes of you!
It sounds like Gamagoori and Jakuzure
have wrapped things up on their end.
How are you coming along?
Most of the Kinman High
students have been dealt with.
Tell Lady Satsuki that Osaka
will be under our control soon.
I wouldn't be so sure about that!
Takarada?
Buddy, you're underestimating my power.
The students aren't my only pawns!
Thank you, come again! How's
business?! Not too bad!
You're making the common masses
fight for you too, you bastard?
I am indeed.
But it's not quite accurate
to call them common masses.
They're all Combat Citizens who
have been blinded by money.
Everyone in this town right
now is itching to fight!
They're tough!
That's the newest Osakan
spot, the Naniwa Sky Tower!
Right! Let's climb it!
When you see a high place, you get
an irresistable urge to climb it!
What'cha think of the attack of
Kaneo Takarada and the
I Heart Osaka Brigade?
If you want to take Osaka, you'll
have to kill every last one of us!
In the end, it's money
that motivates folks.
You "heart" it, eh?
What's the sense in
destroying your own city?
We'll just rebuild it afterwards!
The contractors will love all
the extra work thrown their way!
Okay, people! Kill that man,
and I'll give you a
million Takarada Bucks!
Make him suffer!
How are you gonna deal with
all these people, then?
That's—
What's that light?
L-Lady Satsuki!
Ow...
Huh?
Hey, that's Ryuko's Senketsu!
Hey, you're Mankanshoku,
the second-year!
What are you doing here?
You deserted in the face
of the enemy and have
been goofing around, haven't you?
What do you think the Raid
Trip is about, anyway?
Purge her!
I'm sorry!
Ryuko!
I see you're taking things easy and
taking in the Osaka sights, Mako.
Am I glad to see you, Ryuko!
Senketsu's all chopped to bits!
Yeah, but I'll get him back.
I'll take back every last piece
and make him good as new.
Oh, I get it, Ryuko.
You're going to these lengths
'cause he's your only uniform.
There is only one left, Ryuko.
Really? How are you feeling?
Rather well. You're
different, don't you think?
How so?
The only part of me that is giving
you power right now is this scarf.
But in spite of that, you are
insta-killing the Goku Uniforms
that have had my fragments
attached to them.
You are even stronger than
before, don't you think?
I'm getting stronger?
It's because what you
desire is almost in reach!
You're so desperate cause you're
fixated on your desire to
get Senketsu back to normal.
I get the same way, but with money!
Thanks. The way you get
fixated is pretty hardcore.
Yeah! You gotta be hardcore
about "fixated rates"!
Okay, one to go.
Can you tell where it is, Senketsu?
Yes, I can tell. However...
What is it?
The person holding the final
fragment is Satsuki Kiryuin.
Satsuki, seriously?
Fine. I don't care who has
it, I'm getting you back.
But in my current condition,
I am unable to transform into
Life Fiber Synchronize mode.
How do you intend to fight
an opponent like Satsuki?
Don't worry. I'll make up for the rest.
I'm not the usual Ryuko Matoi right now.
I'm a Ryuko Matoi who's fixated by
seeing what she wants almost in reach.
Isn't that right, Mako?
Yeah!
Ryuko...
I'm coming for you, Satsuki Kiryuin!
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Osaka, a town where money
talks! Money-mad Osaka!
OSAKA
SCATTERED
In search of her scattered Kamui
Senketsu, Ryuko dives in, too!
KAMUI SENKETSU
IN THE END
Will Kamui Senketsu be revived?!
Oh, this is talking about me...
KAMUI SENKETSU
ABOUT ME
Next time on Kill La Kill,
"Don't Stop Me Now"!
EPISODE 15
DON'T STOP ME NOW