Rule the Court
Go, go, let's go! Let's go, Date Tech!
The Iron Wall of Date
Let's play!
Yeah.
Now, now. Don't be so tense.
You guys still have next year.
That doesn't matter.
Positions and such don't matter
once you're on the court.
I know, right?
Heads is Seijoh, tails is Date Tech.
It doesn't matter if you're
a first-year or a third-year.
The strong are the strong,
and the one who drops the ball loses.
All right!
It's pretty simple, actually.
Haikyu!!
Episode 18: "The Losers"
It's out!
Don't mind! Next, next!
I'm sorry.
I haven't even hit that many,
but I've managed to miss
three spikes this set.
Wakunan                            Karasuno
Oh, man. What's up with him?
I think it's because he's on the right,
and he's not used to that.
But I think the biggest
factor could be pressure.
One more!
Got it.
All right, one touch!
Damn it... They're pretty good, after all.
Wakunan                               Karasuno
All right!
Wakunan's Nakashima's really
stepping up his game.
On the other hand, seems like
Karasuno can't get it back.
Hey!
You got a look on your face
like the world's going to end!
It's too early for the world to end.
I'm the Earth Defense Force!
I do not look like that!
All right! Chikara's back!
If the ball gets blown away,
there's not much you can do,
Calm down. I can't keep dwelling on it.
but there are still some
that you can pick up.
I've got to do this! Like Daichi-san!
Your attacks are getting
in there. Keep it up!
Right!
Coach!
Huh?
So the Little Giant was like Wakunan's #1?
Well... His play style is probably
the most similar in the prefecture right now.
Hey, don't try to duel with him.
He's better in mid-air
battles than you are.
Just play like you usually do!
Why do you have to break
my heart like that?!
That was just some kind advice!
Kind?!
I know that they're good!
H-Hinata, calm down...
That's why I'm trying to
figure out what to do!
Don't try to use the brain you don't have!
What did you say?!
Wakunan                            Karasuno
Takeru!
What a narrow straight!
He's so good!
Takeru
Nice kill!
Your height doesn't even reach 170cm...
You're definitely strong,
Tabi, one more nice serve!
but I'm not going to lose, either.
Yeah, leave it to me!
I'm the one who's going to
surpass the Little Giant.
Wakunan
Nice serve!
Look out!
Hinata, get the last!
Yeah!
I'm going to go for a wipe.
That's a king-sized homerun!
I'm sorry!
As Kageyama said,
Don't mind, don't mind!
I told you not to try to
match him, you dumbass!
right now, we're definitely no match
for Nakashima's personal skills.
Tabi! One more, nice serve!
All right!
It's up front!
All right, we picked it up!
Two blockers!
Ah, again!
So fast!
Look out!
It's a counter!
Your skills are no match for Nakashima
or the Little Giant's right now...
But...
You can fight with everything you've learned!
Yeah!
Are you all right?
I got too enthusiastic.
Be careful! Seriously, be careful!
Bumping into a guy this light is nothing.
That was awesome! Nice kill!
Even if we're backed into a corner,
we still have the firepower to break through.
That's our weapon.
Kageyama's saying something decent?!
I think you said something like
that before, Ennoshita-san.
Oh, yeah...
Yeah.
S-Sorry. Are you all right, Sensei?
I totally flipped backwards.
You wouldn't believe he'd been having trouble
with diving receives with that one.
Yeah.
Go! Killer serve!
Karasuno's #10... What
reflexes and maneuverability.
Wakunan
Shiro!
A feint!
Nice receive!
Out, it's out!
The toss was low! Sorry!
I could see the feint, but
I couldn't move fast enough.
If it were Daichi-san,
he would have been able to get
it to the setter properly.
I'm sorry.
What's that supposed to mean?
Trying to do the same moves
that Daichi-san would do...
You're ten years...
Well, that's a bit too long...
You're about a year away from that.
No matter how you look at it,
that was a nice receive.
Let's not mention any realistic
numbers like "one year"...
Karasuno
Cover! Cover!
Takeru!
All right!
Damn it!
We've got to do something about that wipe,
That was close! Don't mind!
or it's going to be rough.
I don't have time to wallow
in my failure now.
Playing on par with Daichi-san
won't be possible right away.
I know that they're good!
That's why I'm trying to
figure out what to do!
Hey, may I have a moment?
When their #1 goes for a wipe,
I'll pick up the ball.
Tanaka and Asahi-san are way better
at receiving powerful hits than I am.
If you two defend the straight sides,
I'll go deep in the middle and pick up
any balls that go over there.
I can't guarantee that it'll work, but...
Yeah, let's give it a shot.
Th-Thank you very much.
Like I'm any better at getting
powerful hits than Ennoshita...
Got it!
All right!
Takeru-san!
Mine!
Two blockers!
I can't guarantee that it'll work, but...
Yeah, let's give it a shot.
If I can't pick this up...
I don't have the right to be on this court!
Ennoshita!
Damn...
Connect!
Haikyu!!
Ennoshita!
Damn...
Hinata, get the last!
Three blockers!
If I hit, they'll get it.
I'm going to regroup.
He...
All right! Got it!
What?! He hit the block on purpose?!
A rebound.
Huh? When did he learn that?!
During the summer training camp.
But he just got lucky.
One more!
With Daichi absent,
our defense is weaker than usual.
Whether intentionally or subconsciously,
Bring it!
Hinata's trying to deal with this situation.
That was awesome, Hinata!
I feel like someone's complimenting me!
You're imagining it.
Where did you learn that?
Actually, Bokuto-san taught
me during the training camp...
I knew that Karasuno had an amazing shrimp,
What? No fair!
You lucky bastard!
but I thought that was only
because of the setter.
You should have told me earlier!
And yet...
All right, Hinata, Tanaka, nice kill!
Chikara!
Nice receive.
No fair... Getting one
from Noya-san is no fair.
Getting a compliment from
Nishinoya about a receive
would cheer anyone up.
He's in.
Pardon?
He's just a substitute,
and he can't completely blend
in with the vibe on the court
since he doesn't belong.
I think that's how Ennoshita felt.
But I think that play just now
banished that feeling.
That play just now?
He thought of it on his
own, told the team,
and carried it out.
Plays like that give you confidence.
I see.
It's difficult.
All right!
Karasuno...
Up until recently,
they were an average team
that didn't stand out.
Truly, the Little Giant!
That match showed me that
there was a path like this when
This is a good course!
He can see so well!
I was starting to worry about my height.
Karasuno's #10...
The guy who wears the same number
as the Little Giant did back then.
One more!
Takeru!
First, I'm going to defeat you.
#1's doing a back attack!
Karasuno                                        Wakunan
All right!
We caught up!
Sorry, the toss was low.
Ennoshita, nice serve!
Got it!
Nice!
All right! Thank goodness.
Isamu-nii and Takeru-nii,
the oldest and second oldest brothers...
Are you sure you're not backwards?
You're gonna make your brother cry.
Karasuno                                                      Wakunan
Asahi-san, nice serve!
Sorry! That was long!
It's going over the net!
Takeru-san!
Kageyama, push through!
It's at times like this
that I'm reminded
how high that wall is.
Nice cover, Tabi!
Connect!
Karasuno's #10...
I'm not going to lose to you!
Takeru!
Not me, or my team's bravery!
All right!
Karasuno                     Wakunan
Hang in there.
If you keep it up, they're start making mistakes.
Not to mention their captain's absent.
Hang in there until they break.
Right!
And...
Go show them who's really the
Little Giant in this match.
Right!
Hinata, serve!
Ukai-san...
Huh?
He was saying that it might be okay
to start giving tosses to Azumane-san
since the match is almost over.
Right.
The quick's coming!
Nice receive!
Now that Hinata's in the back,
they're definitely all going to
start being cautious of Azumane-san.
When it's best to set
the ball to Azumane-san...
Right now...
It should be this.
All right!
It's in! Thank goodness.
Chikara!
He set to their #6, who's only gotten
Ennoshita, nice kill!
a few hits in, despite this chance
coming in the last part of the game.
That first-year setter's definitely gutsy.
Damn it! Not sure if
I should be happy or sad...
Karasuno
Asahi-san, nice serve!
Give 'em a fierce one!
Now's the time to get the lead!
It's out!
All right!
Nice call!
I'm sorry...
Next! One more!
Karasuno                     Wakunan
Don't look at the score...
Matsushima, nice serve!
Calm down. Stay calm.
Crap!
It's out!
Nice call!
I-I'm sorry...
Right, let's change it up!
There's no problem if we get the next one!
Hey, Matsushima!
The next time you're up front,
if you get depressed again,
I'm going to make you buy me a popsicle.
Right.
Karasuno                Wakunan
Karasuno's at match point.
And here comes Karasuno's #10.
Wakunan's in trouble.
Got it!
All right!
They targeted the spot Yu didn't cover?
They're calm.
Kawatabi-san, nice serve!
Tabi, get this one!
So if we miss this, it's all over.
You'd look really cool if you hit
this one with everything you've got.
It's up! Nishinoya, nice!
It's off! But a quick isn't impossible.
Kageyama!
Got it!
Or should I let Tanaka-san have it?
But we can go with a quick.
It's a bit high?
He panicked.
Hang in there... Until the opponent breaks.
Chance ball!
Hinata!
Don't flail!
A good jump...
...starts from good footing!
I guess we really don't
have an advantage with
Karasuno's captain missing.
Watch the ball!
Yeah.
It's too late!
All...
...right!
All right!
Show Your Tenacity
Karasuno                       Wakunan
Thank you very much!
What?
One-on-one, I couldn't beat their #1.
He was more of a Little Giant than me.
Of course. You've still got at least
100 years to go, you dumbass.
Hey! What are you guys doing?
Come on, line up!
Show Your Tenacity
Bow.
Thank you very much.
Today was just our second match.
Our next opponent will be even stronger.
Daichi-san!
Uh, um...
I'm sorry.
D-D-D...
Daichi!
Daichi-san!
D-Daichi-san! A-Are...
I'm fine.
No, seriously. I got some rest, and honestly,
I'm better than before the match.
I'll work twice as hard in the next match.
You guys must be exhausted
from playing a full set.
Come on, rest.
Oh, our next opponent's playing right now.
I was watching from around
the time the score was 20.
At first, I wanted to get back
at soon as possible, but...
I saw you guys and thought you'd be okay.
I thought I'd actually destroy
your rhythm if I showed up.
That last one... Nice receive, Ennoshita.
Right.
Sorry, could you go on ahead?
Doesn't Ennoshita seem a bit down? We won.
Yeah.
Half of the spikes I hit were misses,
and I only got real
receives in the last half.
I somehow feel this was the first time
I got to fight properly to the end.
And yet...
Don't you dare relax now!
You need to think that you're gonna defeat
the next opponent that
comes around, you idiot!
You idiot, idiot, idiot!
That was amazing!
I was watching the last
bit with Sawamura-san.
We're gonna win the next one, too!
Doesn't Yamaguchi-kun seem down?
Sorry... I'm gonna go to the bathroom,
so go on ahead.
He's really pumped about
going to the bathroom.
He must need to take a shit.
Say "poop!" You're so vulgar, Kageyama-kun!
I don't think he actually
went to the bathroom.
Hey, Takeru. It's meeting time.
You know...
Huh?
That last bit was in slow motion.
I met eyes with their #10 at that moment,
and I could tell that he figured out
where I was aiming for the wipe.
That was the first time
I was able to see that much.
It gave me chills.
Once more...
Let me do it once more.
Aoba Johsai
Push it, push it, push it, push it!
Push it, push it, push it, Seijoh!
Rule the Court
Go, go, let's go! Let's go, Date Tech!
The Iron Wall of Date
Hey, don't eat too much.
Now...
I wonder who our next opponent is.
Lately, I've been conflicted as coach
because everyone's doing so well.
And Nishinoya keeps scolding me, too.
Want to join me?
Uh, I'm a minor!
Next time on Haikyu!!:
Episode 19: "The Iron Wall Can Be Rebuilt Again and Again"
"The Iron Wall Can Be Rebuilt Again and Again."