My lord, you must return.
Enough, Tsunamoto.
Kojuro will look after the castle.
But what if Ieyasu's men
come while you're away?
I'm going because that old man's useless.
But more importantly,
why is he sending the priestess
he's been hiding back to Izumo?
Sanada Yukimura knows
more than he lets on.
What's so important in Izumo that
you and Sanada are doing this?
The Kushimitama.
The Kushimitama?
It's a relic that houses
the soul of the gods.
The gods?
I suppose someone interested
in the popular foreign deities,
like Buddha or Kannon, wouldn't
know what I'm talking about.
What do you intend to do
with this soul of the gods?
I will acquire it and turn
this world upside down.
Upside down?
I will make the winds of change blow!
My lord seeks to bring
misfortune to this world.
He is the...
...Rising Dragon of Oshu!
The Souls of the Gods
That's Izumo Shrine?
Yeah.
I'm glad we made it here safely.
Is there really anything
left down there?
Burnt to a crisp...
It looks completely destroyed.
Sorry.
Let's go check it out!
To destroy all of this...
They must have been desperate to
get their hands on whatever it is.
Let's split up and look.
But we don't know what
we're looking for.
Carefully examine anything
that appears suspicious.
Isanami?
Hey, Isanami!
Right.
I'll go look over there.
Hey! Don't run off on your own!
I'll call you if something happens.
I'll go look around the perimeter.
You keep an eye on Isanami.
I'll fire a shot if I find anything.
Sheesh. That woman...
This pillar used to be a beautiful red.
The walls were a brilliant green.
It used to be such a colorful
and welcoming place.
Isanami, you're so good at that.
You really are a great dancer.
Sisters...
I'm sure you will become
Izumo's best dancer.
Master...
They're all...
Isanami.
I told you not to go off on your own.
There's nothing over here.
Looks like it.
Saizo, why don't you go
look somewhere else?
What's wrong with you?
You're always saying
we should go together.
Hey.
I was actually afraid to see Izumo again.
As long as I didn't see it, I still had hope.
Hope that, maybe, someone survived,
and would be here to greet me.
But it's...
It's all gone, isn't it?
It hurts...
Wipe your nose.
It's filthy, so keep your
face hidden for a while.
Thank you...
Yeah.
They should be arriving
in Izumo about now.
Won't they go after Isanami?
Probably.
If you sent her there knowing that,
you must have a plan.
A plan?
There must be something in Izumo you needed Isanami to retrieve.
Is that not what you thought?
There are things about Izumo
that only a local would know.
That's all.
I will bring you more tea.
However, I do think they might run
into someone along the way.
Who will it be this time?
Hey, Saizo.
Why'd it have to be Izumo?
Why'd it have to be here,
and not Kasuga or Ise?
We're here to figure that out.
You're right.
Besides, we can't bring
the dead back to life.
And you can't pretend it didn't happen,
but at least you can figure out why it did.
It might not make you feel any better,
but isn't it the most the living can do?
Thank you, Saizo!
Get off of me.
Get off.
Just for a little bit! It makes me feel safe!
What?
But if not for this thing we're looking for,
this place would have been peaceful.
Kakei-san's signal.
Kakei-san, did you find something?
No, nothing.
Didn't you say you'd fire your
gun if you found something?
I thought I should let you
know I did not find anything.
I see.
I searched everywhere,
but it had all burnt down.
This trip has been worthless.
What's wrong?
Why didn't this burn down?
It appears to be made of bronze.
That must be why it survived the fire.
It should at least be covered in soot.
Saizo?
This symbol...
Did you find something?
It looks familiar...
Let me see. Hey, let me see.
That's it. It's a yin-yang symbol.
But...
But?
It's a little different
from the actual symbol.
Let me see!
There must be some sort of trick.
Yeah.
Maybe we're supposed to
make the correct symbol.
Can those stones be moved?
Hey!
Don't push yourself too hard.
I am shamed.
I think it moves.
It moves?
Th-That's impossible.
I just tried to move it.
I think...
...only the center piece moves.
Hey, can I give it a try?
Sure.
How do I know this?
Have I seen this before?
Incredible!
It opened!
It's pretty deep.
I heard a tall staircase was constructed...
...at Izumo Shrine long ago
to reach the heavens.
A stairway to Heaven?
These stairs seem to be the opposite.
You mean these stairs
go to the netherworld?
Yeah, right.
There's no such thing as Heaven or Hell.
You don't believe in them?
I believed we'd be together in the
netherworld even after we died.
I'd like to live a quiet
life in the other world.
What's that supposed to mean?
Hey, I think we're here.
It seems to be a dead end.
We came down here for nothing.
Wait. There's something written.
Huh? What is that?
I think it's Izumo script.
Izumo script? Can you read it?
No.
It's worthless if we can't read it.
Saizo?
It seems you've found it.
I must thank you.
Now I don't have to look for it myself.
Who are you?
Bastard.
Now, hand over the Kushimitama.
The Kushimitama?
That's right.
It's your very own protective charm.
Keep it with you always.
Just for me?
You must never remove it.
You're after my hairpin?
So that's what they wanted after all.
Well, I can't say I was
expecting a hairpin.
Now, if you'll hand it over.
We'll never let you have it!
If you intend to take it by force,
we accept your challenge.
We're surrounded.
What?
What are those lights?
They're snakes!
Bastard!
No, Kakei-san.
They'll explode if you kill them.
What? I can't cut them?
If I could, I would've
done that already.
Damn snakes!
Leave the older one to me.
Mushikugutsu Hiki Jagyokuken.
Kakei-san!
My hairpin...
Hey.
You idiot, what are you doing?
Hey!
It's my fault the priest and sisters...
If you must interfere with my job,
just like our meeting at Ueda Castle,
I will not hold back.
He's as bloodthirsty as always.
I... It was my fault...
No turning back now!
Missed by a hair.
How long can you avoid my blades?
G-Get off of me!
Your efforts are futile.
You're trapped inside my technique.
I have all the power here.
An illusionist?
I'll lick you clean.
Too slow.
Don't bore me!
I thought you'd be more of a challenge.
Let's finish this!
You want a challenge...
You got it!
You... You bastard!
Now you're symmetrical.
What would you like next?
Enough of your vulgar nonsense!
Vulgar?
It is not proper for a
woman to straddle a man!
Nothing excites me more than
breaking prudish men like you.
Ougi Kashozanmai.
Saizo...
Shit...
Stop!
No more.
I don't want anyone else
to die for me, Saizo!
Gimme a break.
No one's dying here.
I can't die.
Saizo.
What can you do in that state?
It's over.
No!
This wind...
Who gave you permission
to play with my toy?
I'll kill you, bastard!
"My toy?"
I'm the only one allowed to shed blood
fighting to the death with him!
What?
And he's the only one allowed to
push me to the edge and kill me!
Pervert.
I don't wanna hear that from
some gross, masked bastard!
You can't do shit.
Behind you, idiot!
Bastard.
I've had enough of you and your swords.
You dumb-ass, you just suck at fighting.
What? Who're you calling a dumb-ass?
If you don't want both
of us to die, assist me.
You can't order me around!
Once we're done with him,
I'll play with you until
you cry, so come on.
Until I cry?
You're serious?
All right! Bring it on!
What an unromantic child.
I can move.
That wind must have torn her
barrier and broken the illusion.
A hidden gun? That's no fair.
I, Okatsu the snake charmer,
will constrict you myself, like a snake.
Now you cannot fire your gun.
Prepare yourself.
You shot through your own arm...
What a strong man...
Yuri Kusarigama Ougi Fujinsho!
This ends now!
Shunko!
We did it.
Your crappy fighting made
me waste my energy.
Shut up.
Your support just sucks.
I'm sorry.
Everyone got hurt because of me.
It was nothing.
Besides, no one asked
this guy to jump in.
Don't worry about him.
What'd you say?
You would've been screwed
if I hadn't shown up.
But...
I'm just glad you are safe.
It was my fault Izumo was attacked.
It wasn't your fault. It was that hairpin.
I did not expect that to be their target.
My hairpin... The Kushimitama.
So that's it?
Let go of her! Who are you?
Date Masamune!
Date Masamune? The lord of Oshu?
Let go! Let go of me!
Isanami!
Saizo!
Go home and tell your master.
I, Masamune, have taken
the Kushimitama!
Wait...
Saizo! Saizo!
Damn it!
Saizo, when are we gonna do this?
What?
Y-You said you'd play
with me until I cried.
When are we doing it? I'm ready anytime!
I don't have time for that now.
I've got to recover.
Yes, recover!
You're right.
You'll need all your strength
for a really good fight.
Don't worry, I'll go get you something.
Leave it to me.
What's wrong with that guy?
He's so annoying.
The next episode of Brave 10 is
"The Heart of the Dragon."
Bring it on!
The Heart of the Dragon