I must be aware...
of the ball,
the blockers,
and the spikers.
I can't overlook even the slightest movement.
With perfect timing, I must find
the highest point of the spiker's strike...
And capture it!
Again.
Another point!
They've turned it around.
Kageyama-Hinata     Tsukishima-Yamaguchi
One more point and
they'll take the first set.
His tosses get more accurate every time.
We're seeing Kageyama's
true abilities as a setter.
Score.
That was awesome, man.
But the one who pulled it all out of him...
...was Hinata.
Scored again!
Haikyu!!
Episode 5: A Coward's Anxiety
He sure hung in there...
I've never seen anyone take
a toss to the face.
You're not scoring any more.
Come to me!
He's untouchable when he spikes free.
Damn.
How do you like me now, Tsukishima?
Weren't you going to crush me and Hinata?
That's right. That's right.
Try it if you can.
Try it.
Why are you bragging the most, Tanaka?
That's right. You're scoring
thanks to the first-years.
You have a big attitude.
Don't take off your shirt, baldie.
Who's trash-talking me over there?!
Frankly, if they can't stop
Kagaeyama and Hinata's attacks,
Tsukishima's team is going down.
They lack conviction.
Starting the second set.
Let's go.
Right.
Tsukishima-Yamaguchi     Kageyama-Hinata
All right.
Kageyama is amazing,
but it be really taxing to keep
making such accurate tosses.
Hinata's looking tired
from moving around so much.
Yeah, but...
Yes.
I think they're having fun.
Tsukishima-Yamaguchi     Kageyama-Hinata
Good job.
Da... Daichi-san, Suga-san,
did you two know
those two could attack like that,
when you said what you said?
Huh?
If we can utilize that combination...
Karasuno will make explosive improvement.
Can't we use it to our advantage, some how?
Of course not.
I just meant he should give Hinata tosses
he'd have no trouble spiking.
I thought maybe Hinata could get used
to Kageyama's somewhat reckless tosses...
But that isn't exactly what happened.
I was hoping they would
simply fight together,
but they actually made
each other stronger.
Hinata is raw, but he has
natural speed and jumping ability.
Then Kageyama perfectly utilizes
Hinata's abilities with his finely-honed skill.
The two of them bring out
the best in each other.
Why? We don't have to.
As a duo, they may exceed all expectations.
Yes, we do.
All right. Let's go.
Tsukishima.
What?
We're supposed to shake hands
before and after a match.
Though we didn't do that at first today.
Besides, we're teammates now.
Though that doesn't make me happy.
Hurry up.
Don't you know?
They'll kick you out the gym
if you don't show team spirit.
The reason why you two got kicked out
was because you ignored the captain,
started your own competition, and finally,
blew the dean's rug off his head.
N-Never mind the minor details.
Shake hands.
Wh-What are you doing?
What are those first-years doing?
Are you all right, Tsukki?
Tsukishima.
How did you like the three-on-three?
It made no difference to me.
He's a king from an elite school, anyway.
There's nothing strange about
commoners losing to him.
Hmm...
But then again,
you played pretty seriously.
Here.
Captain.
What?
Club Application
Volleyball
First-Year, Class 3
Kageyama Tobio
Club Application
Volleyball
First-Year, Class 1
Hinata Shoyo
Shimizu.
The stuff is here, right?
What?
Karasuno High School
Volleyball Club
I think they should fit, but
let me know if you need anything.
Thanks.
Come on. Put it on.
No, I'll do it later...
Are you shy or something?
Never mind. Wear it.
Wear it. Wear it. Wear it.
Looks good on you.
Yeah, looks good. Looks good.
We're the Karasuno Volleyball Club
from here on...
Ready, and...
Good to have you with us.
Thanks!
Anyway, got that out of the way.
Suga, you and Tanaka helped
them out, didn't you?
Oh? No, not really.
Anyway, it all worked out.
Thanks.
Good job.
What? Hey.
Hey, Hinata, are you rested?
You ready to go?
Let's practice "quick" again.
Let's do it while you're still in the zone.
Yeah.
Tanaka-san, please bring the balls.
You're moving around already?
It's decided! It's decided!
The practice match.
It's against one of the top four teams
in the prefecture.
Aoba Josai High School.
The one nicknamed Seijo?
Yikes.
No way.
A practice match with
one of the top four!
Aoba Josai...
Oh. You two are the controversial
Hinata-kun and Kageyama-kun.
Who's he? A teacher?
I dunno.
I'm the volleyball club advisor
starting this year.
I'm Takeda Ittetsu.
Hello.
I have no volleyball experience,
so I can't help with your technique,
but for anything else,
I'll do my very best.
It's good to meet you.
Yes.
Sensei.
Ah.
I've been running around everywhere
setting up the practice-match.
I haven't had time to drop in here.
But, sensei, how did you get
a powerhouse like Seijo to agree?
You didn't get on your knees
and beg again, did you?
No, no.
I'm good at getting on my knees and begging,
but I didn't do that this time.
But they had a condition.
A condition?
Kageyama-kun must play setter
the entire game.
What's that about?
Sounds like they're not
interested in Karasuno.
They just want to assess Kageyama.
Are they underestimating us?
Are they?
Well, that's not quite how it is.
Sounds good.
We don't get chances like this that often.
You're going to agree to that, Suga-san?
You're the official setter
of Karasuno, Suga-san.
I...
I want to see how effective
Hinata and Kageyama's
attack will be against
a top four team.
Sensei, may we have the details?
Sure. Um... the schedule is rather sudden,
but it's set for Tuesday next week.
It'll be after classes, so there
will only be time for one game.
We'll rent the bus after school...
A match.
It's going to be my first
official match at Karasuno,
with a full team!
So make sure you're not late.
Yes.
Good job.
Sugawara-san.
I have to play setter by default this time,
but from now on I will earn my place.
Huh?
Oh, I thought you weren't
concerned about me at all.
I wasn't expecting that.
Why would you say that?
Because you're superior to me
in athleticism and talent.
You can't make up for a lack
of experience that easily!
And also...
Suga-san.
Suga.
Sugawara-san.
I h-have to earn...
...the t-t-trust of the other team members...
That junior high match he was in
must've really gotten to him.
Therefore,
I will never give up.
Yeah. I won't give up, either.
Suga-san.
Daichi-san said he'll buy us pork buns.
But you know, Kageyama,
Foothill Store
Aoba Josai is where most of the athletes
from Kitagawa Daiichi move on to, right?
Yeah, you could say that.
That means Kageyama's
former teammates are at that school.
I'm just wondering if you might
be uncomfortable with that.
I might be if they were on the same team.
But if they're my opponents,
I'll fight with all I've got.
I see. I suppose you would.
But are you all right with it, Suga-san?
I... I... just can't accept it.
Sure, I'm a little mad about it...
But...
I also want to show them that
Kageyama's completely different
from his junior high days.
That's true.
Plus, we'll show them that Kageyama's
not the only one they need to worry about.
Right, Hinata?
Why are you eating first?
Are you kidding?
Hey, volleyball club!
Don't make a ruckus in front of the store!
Sorry.
"Volleyball club"... that's right.
All five of us are
in the volleyball club.
We're on the same team.
Excuse me. Is there a curry pork bun?
Eat your dinner properly.
Hey, you guys come and eat, too.
Thanks.
We're all on the same team.
Kageyama, after you're done eating,
could I ask you something?
Sure.
Don't make a ruckus.
I was wondering about Hinata's position
for the upcoming practice match.
What do you think?
Now, concerning the positions
for the practice match...
I think this is how we'll do it.
WS Tanaka               MB Hinata            WS Sawamura
S Kageyama           MB Tsukishima        WS Ennoshita
S Sugawara
MB Yamaguchi
WS Kinoshita
MB Narita
I want to use Kageyama and Hinata as a set,
"Set"...
and Tsukishima is one
of our few tall players.
I want to see how
you'll fight against Seijo.
Yes.
I'm the only first-year out of the loop.
You're using Hinata in a
position where height matters?
Middle blocker?
I'm in the same position as
the lanky jerk Tsukishima?
Volleyball
HOW
TO
Oh, j-just a second.
Can I read up on the positions?
Setter (S)
Setter:
The control tower that tosses for spikes,
and organizes the offense.
Wing Spiker (WS)
Wing spiker:
An all-around, well-balanced player
who attacks the core of the opponents.
Middle Blocker (MB)
Middle blocker:
He defends against the opponent's offense,
and scores points, mainly using "quick."
Furthermore, he plays the decoy
to draw the opponent's blockers away.
Would you say these are right?
There are other exclusively
defensive positions, too,
but for now, those are all.
Listen, Hinata...
You're the ultimate decoy.
The ultimate...
...decoy?
There's something uninspiring about that.
We'll let you score lots
of points using "quick,"
and direct the opponent's
blockers' attention to you.
That's when the other spikers
will come into play.
Oh.
Big guys like Tsukishima will fall
like idiots to your movements...
That'll feel good, won't it?
I like it. I like it a lot.
Hey. Are you calling Tsukki an idiot?
Shut up, Yamaguchi.
Sorry, Tsukki.
On the other hand, if you're not effective,
know that the other attacks will all fail.
Hey...
Don't put so much pressure on him.
All fail... all fail... all fail...
All fail     All fail
You see?
What about blocking, though?
Even if he can jump high,
the taller players will reach
the highest point of their jump faster.
Yes, the reason we want Hinata
to be the focus of blockers
isn't to smack down the opponent's spikes,
but to touch them.
With Hinata's crazy reflexes and speed,
he can touch the opponent's spikes,
and slow down their momentum.
We'll set the pace to our advantage,
and make our counterattack.
It's not going to go that smoothly
right off the bat.
It probably won't.
Huh?
Right off the bat, anyway.
But we should still try it.
Maybe we'll learn something as we go along.
It's a practice match, after all.
Fine.
Anyway, for in-air battles,
we've only got Tsukishima and Kageyama
who can match Hinata's jumps.
So, Hinata, have confidence, and...
Yes! I'll do my best!
I'll score lots of points. I'll be a decoy.
I'll serve. Block. Quick. Everything.
Hey, hey, calm down!
He blew a fuse!
Hinata blew a fuse!
Sawamura.
Hey, Michimiya.
What?
I heard you're having a match
against Seijo tomorrow?
I'm surprised they agreed to it.
Yeah. Takeda-sensei did
the hard work for us.
But aren't you scared?
Hm?
Seijo was in the prefecture's
top four last year, weren't they?
Won't they beat the crap out of us?
Well, we actually have some rather
interesting first-years...
I heard about them.
As soon as they joined the club,
they blew off the dean's rug...
D-Don't!
Shh.
They're still imperfect, but if
those guys start playing their part,
I feel Karasuno is going
to improve explosively.
That's what I think.
Wow...
Are first-years allowed to use the club room?
Of course. It doesn't matter.
Hey.
Hello there.
Oh...
There's nothing impressive about this place.
It's just an ordinary club room.
I've never been in a club room before.
The Little Giant used
this room, too, didn't he?
Tomorrow's finally your
debut battle, Hinata.
Even though it's a practice match.
Seijo's gym is huge.
Their players are huge, too.
Don't get intimidated.
Hey.
Hello.
In...
In?
Intimidated? Of course I won't be.
I'll do great. You'll see...
Hey, Hinata.
You're putting your jacket on first...
What's that? A fashion statement?
Kageyama, is Hinata going
to be all right tomorrow?
Who're you trying to look like?
Will he be all right?
What do you mean?
Hinata's only experience is at
that one match in junior high.
Is that how you get dressed?
No, it's not. I was daydreaming. That's all.
I think he's really anxious
and worried because of that.
That's why I think he
might be quite nervous.
But everyone feels nervous...
You make light of the
anxiety we cowards feel.
No matter what I say, it adds pressure.
Hinata.
Here's the key to the club room.
Don't worry. I'll bring it with me.
I never told you where to keep it,
so I brought it with me.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You can't help it at first.
I think it's best to leave him alone.
I wonder...
I have to do it right tomorrow...
This isn't going to be like junior high,
or like the three-on-three the other day,
because I can be replaced.
I don't want that.
I don't want to be replaced.
I'm finally going to stand on the court
with a full team.
I want to be out there 'til the end.
I can't goof up. I can't goof up.
I can't goof up.
Whoops, sorry. You're so
small I couldn't see you.
I can't goof up. I can't goof up.
What's that all about?
Who knows?
Hey, Kageyama.
Don't make any wisecracks
that'll put more pressure on him.
Wisecracks?
Have I ever made any wisecracks?
I have no recollection whatsoever.
He has no self-awareness.
Hinata.
You're wearing my pants!
What are you doing Tanaka? You pervert!
Are you stupid? You're the worst.
I can't sleep.
Nii-chan, you're too noisy.
S-Sorry.
Kitagawa Daiichi
Volleyball Club
Line up.
Let's play.
Yes.
Hey, Hinata. I'll give you something to eat.
What is that look on your face?
I couldn't sleep last night...
The window... can I open the window?
Stop the bus!
Uh oh...
This is...
...worse than...
...we expected!
Next Episode Preview
Daichi, is Hinata all right?
Y-Yeah...
Daichi? You're looking pale...
The smell is... making me feel dizzy...
The windows! Open all the windows!
Episode 6: An Interesting Team
Next time on Haikyu!!
"An Interesting Team."