At that moment, I heard
a terrible noise.
Shiina Mashiro-sama
I get it. This is how it works...
I heard something
snapping inside me.
The world isn't fair.
My body creaked...
No matter how much I want to
catch up, it's still not enough.
I felt like my heart
was being ripped in two.
Even if we give it everything
we have, it's pointless.
The only thing I could
do to protect myself...
was to take my pain
out on someone else.
There was nothing we could do!
I didn't want to say those things,
but...
Maybe that's who I am.
Graduation Ceremony
#22 Run Through Those Sparkling Days
Good morning, kouhai-kun.
You're up early, Senpai.
The graduation ceremony's today!
Let's show some enthusiasm!
The graduation ceremony
really is happening today.
Wait, Misaki. I'll come after
I have something to eat.
Okay.
You should wake Mashiro-chan soon.
She won't have time
for breakfast otherwise.
We can't have that, kouhai-kun!
Food is the source of our power!
Let's stuff ourselves silly!
Kouhai-kun looks down.
That's why we've got to keep it together.
Right, right.
Mashiron's Room
Please Knock
I...
Kanda-kun.
Aoyama, good morning.
Good morning.
Are you okay?
How about you?
Of course you're not, huh?
Thanks to you, I feel a lot better.
Really?
Try not to remember how
I looked when I was crying.
Because you looked grody?
I don't like you when you call girls ugly.
I wish I could forget about
what happened yesterday...
I wish I could relive yesterday.
Kanda-kun?
Sorry. Forget I said anything.
Sorry... I've got to wake Shiina.
Okay.
Shiina.
Shiina, I'm opening the door.
Get up, Shii—
Shiina?
Shiina?!
What? What's wrong, Kanda-kun?
Shiina's missing.
Mashiro left this morning.
Why?
Sakura Hall is being torn
down because of Shiina.
It's obvious.
Mashiro knew?
Why? Why didn't you stop her?
I asked her if she talked it over with you.
When she first arrived at Sakura Hall,
she wouldn't have cared how you felt.
Thanks to you all, Mashiro has changed...
Even if it's for the
worse in this situation.
It's all my fault.
Her GPS says she's at school.
Mashiro-sama: Locked on!
Are you sure?
Leave it to me.
Let's go, kouhai-kun!
Huh? What?
Let's go to school!
Why am I going, too?
See you later.
Shiina Mashiro-sama
29th Suimei University of the Arts
High School Graduation Ceremony
Mashiron!
Which way?
30 meters to Mashiro-sama.
30 meters? In which direction?
That's the art room.
All out dash!
Mashiro!
This is Mashiro's...
Did Mashiro-chan paint this?
She must have.
Is this me?
Yeah, it is.
And the rest of us.
Mashiro's amazing.
She really is.
Not even...
Not even the most...
famous painters throughout history
could have painted this.
This painting is the love
Mashiro feels for Sakura Hall.
But...
Why? Why?!
Why are you the only one missing?
But that's why I understood...
I will protect Sakura Hall.
Just how strongly Mashiro felt...
when she said those words that day.
Mashiro-chan planned to
protect Sakura Hall...
by leaving if we failed to
get enough signatures.
This isn't right!
This isn't the Sakura Hall I love!
What kind of goodbye is this?
There's no point if it ends like this!
Kanda-kun.
In that case, Sorata,
you'll have to tell her that.
Yes!
Okay! Operation: Search for Mashiron begins!
Knowing Mashiro-chan,
it's unlikely she's returned
to England on her own.
Has she ever even ridden a train by herself?
Let's check out places in the
area Mashiro might visit.
Misaki-senpai and Jin-san,
search the school and
the surrounding area.
What?
I'll search the station.
I'll go with you.
Make sure you're back for
the graduation ceremony.
I'm determined to get you to give
me the most magnificent send-off!
I'll bring Mashiro back!
Let's look for her, too.
Mashiron!
I guess I'll search around
Sakura Hall just in case, then.
Kanda-kun, you take the area from
the shopping mall to the station.
I'll check the area around
the convenience store.
Gotcha.
Call me if you find Mashiro.
Kanda-kun!
What's wrong?
Your promise to listen to...
what I had to say once I got the
results of my audition...
Yeah, I remember.
I...
I've always... always...
I've always been grateful
I got to meet you.
Aoyama...
I've been able to work so hard
up to now because you were there.
Looking at your face gave me energy.
Hearing your voice made me optimistic.
Before I knew it, I was
always watching you.
Hearing you compliment my clothes
and hair made my feelings soar.
The days we talked a lot...
made me feel like I could
try that much harder.
So...
Thank you for giving me
the will to work so hard!
I feel the same way!
Because of you...
I know. That's why...
You should tell Mashiro how you feel!
Thanks, Aoyama.
The reason I've been able
to work so hard until today...
is because I'm in love
with you, Kanda-kun.
Mashiro-chan!
Mashiron!
Baumkuchen
Did the girl who always
buys these come in today?
Mashiro!
Searching on foot is ineffective.
Why am I doing this, anyway?
How can I help?
Send an email to the former freeloader.
"Shiina felt responsible for Sakura
Hall being torn down and ran off."
"Do you have any idea where
she might have gone?"
Request received.
Incoming Call
Former Freeloader
Where are you?
That's your first question?
It's only natural for
me to be suspicious...
since this isn't an international call.
Where could I be, hm?
A hologram?
Want to touch me and find out?
S-Stay away from me!
That's no way to treat someone
who was worried about you.
Don't patronize me.
Isn't there something
you'd like to say to me?
I'm grateful.
I can't hear you.
Nothing, forget it.
Still, I was surprised.
When you emailed me
saying you wanted to do...
something for Jin and Misaki...
Sorry about that.
I like how you can't admit your feelings.
E-Enough of your jokes!
Let's look for Shiina.
Mashiro's fine.
How can you be so sure?
Mashiro doesn't give up so easily...
on something once she's
decided she wants it.
Despite how she looks,
she's actually the world's most
selfish and stubborn sore loser.
Burnable
Someone already came asking
me to subscribe to the paper.
Hey.
What a warm welcome.
You know why.
You shouldn't act so immaturely
in front of children.
I came to apologize for that.
I feel badly about what
I did to Kanda-kun.
No one told me another team
was trying to hire Shiina-san.
No matter the circumstances,
isn't doing something about it your job?
There's nothing I can say.
Kanda isn't here.
This place hasn't changed.
And your habit of ignoring
everything you don't want to hear...
hasn't changed, either.
I heard they were going
to tear Sakura Hall down.
What did I just say?
Is there anything I can do to help?
Nope.
Even if there were,
we don't need your help.
Why not?
They'll do something about it themselves.
You didn't find her?
I even checked around the college, but...
Let's go look outside the school.
No.
They left us at school so we wouldn't...
be late to our graduation ceremony.
Let's trust them with this.
Besides, there's something
we have to do.
You're right.
You two always get along so well.
Not as well as you two,
who we always see together.
W-We're not...
Here.
For you. It's a love letter from me.
You're not going to look at it?
If you're serious,
there's no need to read it.
Hau-hau, your boyfriend is so cool.
Of course he is.
Just as we planned, Mr. Former
Student Council President.
Sorry.
If you're really sorry,
don't get me involved.
Misaki, you can do it.
I'm looking forward to
your video, Hau-hau.
Mashiro!
Hey, it's Kanda's boy.
Have you seen Mashiro?
She was heading towards the
station about ten minutes ago.
Thank you.
I don't know what's going on,
but you can do it!
Youth is for exploding!
I always thought it was kinda boring...
that every day was the same.
I pretended it was someone
else's fault that nothing happened.
But when I met Mashiro
that fall, I realized...
that if you put your mind to it,
you can change the color of
the world in an instant.
Hey...
What color do you want to be?
I...
I'm...
Mashiro?
Hey, you!
I'll pay later!
Mashiro!
What are you doing?
Sorata...
why?
Because you suddenly disappeared!
But Sakura Hall will
be torn down if I stay.
I don't care! It's fine!
It's not fine.
Today is the graduation ceremony,
but we didn't fill the whole notebook.
Mashiro...
We have to fill it.
It's okay.
It's all my fault.
I worked hard, but Sakura
Hall will be torn down...
It's because of me! I hurt you, too...
You hate me. I...
No...
I don't want to stay at Sakura
Hall if it will make you hate me.
I don't. I don't hate you!
You do!
Just listen!
Sorry. I think what I said
yesterday was how I really feel.
I'd been thinking it
for a long time now.
I was jealous of you because
you had everything I wanted.
I wondered, "why is it always you?"
I was so frustrated,
I almost thought I hated you sometimes.
But that's not all!
Because of you, I was
able to find my own goal!
I worked hard, but I failed
and was disappointed.
But all of that made for
the greatest of days!
If I hadn't met you, I never
would have known these feelings!
That's why I love you for
teaching me all of these things!
I love you!
I'd never hate you!
Don't go!
No...
Sorata!
Mashiro?
I...
I want to be with you.
You can.
I want to stay at Sakura Hall.
But if I stay,
Sakura Hall will be torn down.
I'll cause everyone else
trouble, and I'll hurt you.
You can hurt me.
I made Nanami endure so
much after the audition.
I don't want to stay at Sakura
Hall if it will hurt someone.
What are you talking about?
Aoyama.
Don't act like my
frustration is your own.
Failing the audition is my own problem.
Mine alone.
This experience is all mine.
But...
Ignoring Kanda-kun's warnings...
and pretending I was fine
were my own decisions.
You shouldn't feel responsible for me.
Hey, Aoyama. You don't
have to be so harsh...
Kanda-kun, shut up.
Nanami, are you mad?
Do I look like I'm not mad?
But, Mashiro...
I'm really happy you
were worried about me.
Nanami.
Thank you.
It makes me really happy.
So I won't let you just leave.
Nanami.
You're such a handful.
But it's my fault Sakura Hall
is going to be torn down.
I don't want to go, but I have to.
We told you, you don't have to go.
I've never felt like this before.
I don't understand.
My chest hurts.
I always feel terrible.
It must have been painful.
Yes.
Kanda-kun, if there's anything you
want to say, you can tell her.
Just because she's crying,
she's not going to break.
Oh, right...
You're powerless against
Mashiro's tears, aren't you?
Mashiro.
What?
You don't understand Sakura Hall at all.
I understand.
No, you don't.
I do!
The Sakura Hall I'm talking about
isn't that rundown building.
It's Sakura Hall because
Misaki-senpai and Jin-san,
Aoyama and Chihiro-sensei,
Akasaka and you are there.
Sorata...
It's Sakura Hall because
everyone is there.
In any case, what I'm
trying to say is—
I understand.
Really?
Yes. Sakura Hall is Sakura Hall
because everyone is there.
We're all Sakura Hall.
Yeah, so...
I'll always stay at Sakura Hall.
Nanami.
Thank you.
You said I made you happy.
Yeah.
I'm happy, too.
Thank you.
Of course. We're friends.
Yes, friends.
W-Wait. That hurts, Mashiro.
Hey.
You'll be okay, Nanami.
What are you talking about?
Sorry to interrupt,
but you should probably
head to school soon.
What?
Rita?
How do you do, everyone?
What are you doing here?
Kanda-kun, the time!
The graduation ceremony is starting.
Oh, no!
Let's go!
Mashiro.
Ryunosuke.
I'm coming.
I don't want to go!
Hey, Mashiro.
What?
I still don't know what
color I want to be,
but today is a specific color.
Even if today's the last
day we're all together,
I want the graduation ceremony to
be the color of cherry blossoms.
I love the color of cherry blossoms.
Graduation!
Laughing with everyone
at the culture festival!
#23 Graduation Ceremony
Running at the pool
with everyone at night!
I don't want to graduate!
Kanda, why are you running?
Come back!