Hey! Kirie!
The hell? Where did she run off to?
Well, whatever. I've got nothing to do,
and I'm broke after going shopping yesterday.
Maybe I'll just go to Taihei's place...
These custard cakes sure are yummy!
Yes! And there are still plenty more left!
Thank you, Kirie.
No, I don't know why, but these were just
lying around the house. So please, go ahead.
Huh? She "didn't know why"?
Oh! That's incredible, Master!
Hey, hey! Bada-bing, bada-boom!
That's just rude!
Huh? Who's that?
Coming!
Dude, it's REALLY cold out here. Hurry up and let me in!
Huh?
Ah! Kirie!
Hey! Those are the custard cakes I bought yesterday!
I was looking forward to eating those tonight...
So she basically thieved them, huh?
This has gotten sort of awkward, hasn't it?
Even though they're brother and sister, yeah...
Oh, hey.
You're always coming here to hang out, aren't you?
It's good that you haven't just been staying home alone.
I'm glad that you've made a good friend.
Yeah!
And thanks for those custard cakes, Bomba!
Huh? Well, I bought them for Kirie anyway.
Let me get you some cola to say thanks!
Ooh! Thanks, Tanukichi.
T-Tanu...kichi?
I mean, she looks like a tanuki, right? So, "Tanukichi."
You call my Master a TANUKI?!
If you see my Master's cuteness and think
that she's a tanuki, something is wrong with you!
Well, they look sort of the same, don't they?
THEY DO NOT!
If anything, it's weird that you call her "Master."
A master of friggin' what?
L-look! What makes you think
you have to worry about the friends I keep?!
I had a good time when we were at the beach,
without you being around.
You didn't even pay any attention to me...
Why would you not pay attention to your own sister?!
Uh, well, I...
Th-this is bad. We have to do something.
Just die, you idiot of a brother!
Looks like Bomba's already done for.
Kirie.
Yes, Master?!
Let's relax and have some cola.
You too, Bomba.
ZO GUTE!
So cute!
Yeah, they're related all right.
Hey, how about the four of us play a game?
Ooh, nice! What do you say
we play on the same team, Kirie?
G-give me a break! I'm not teaming up with YOU!
Umaru, I'm going to the Nyaon Mall
to buy groceries for dinner. You need anything?
This week's issue of Fanitsu! It's got all the latest! news!
Huh? Wait, the bookstore?
It's supposed to rain. I wouldn't want it to get wet.
Nah, it'll be fine. Going by this weather,
it's not gonna rain.
You think?
I need to go over today's route!
It's currently 1:00 pm.
The groceries will get heavy, and there's also
the problem of keeping them fresh...
I'll do the bookstore first. I'll wrap up my purchases
at the 3rd-floor bookstore by 1:30.
After that, I'll hurry down to the 1st-floor ATM.
I'll take note of the crowds and act accordingly,
making a careful selection of requisite ingredients.
The weather will likely make a turn for the worst
between 3:00 pm and 4:00 pm.
So, I'll finish up my purchases and get home before then.
Still, this is the same route as always,
with the exception of the bookstore.
This is the first time I've come to the 3rd floor.
Where do they keep the Fanitsu?
Somewhere near the kids' section?
No, it wouldn't be with the storybooks...
I know, right?
Oh, Kirie.
H-hi!
You buying something?
N-no! Just browsing! Well, see you!
Maybe that was a bad time to try to talk to her again...
What was all that about?
The same thing happened last time too.
Huh? Kirie...?
Oh, I get it. Because of the rain.
It's not gonna rain!
It's freaking pouring down, Umaru...
Hi, Kirie.
Oh, Taihei!
Looks like you don't have an umbrella ei...
Huh?!
Wh-what's the matter, Kirie?
N-no, it's just...
Come to think of it,
she seems to get a little down on rainy days.
I... There's something I'd like to do. In the future.
I came to the bookstore to do a bit of research, but I...
you always made the best grades in school, didn't you?
But I'm nowhere near as good as you.
There's no way I could make my dream come...
Ah! I'm sorry. You don't want to hear
about any of this, do you?
No, that's not true at all.
I think you're pretty great, Kirie.
H-huh?!
True, all I did in high school was study...
and, yeah, it paid off. But I never
thought about what I'd do in the future.
I just stuck to the "route" that was right in front of me.
I guess it's still sort of the same.
I-I... want to be a storybook author.
I'm writing a book about my Master.
Huh?
M-meeting her has made me so happy,
and has given me courage.
That's why, I want to share that with people everywhere!
To tell people about my Master, through storybooks!
You'd be the only one who could do that huh, Kirie?
Yes!
Hey, Big Brother!
Umaru!
I-I feel bad. I told you
that you wouldn't need an umbrella...
Don't worry about it.
And I'm glad you brought one for Kirie.
Hm? You happy about something, Brother?
I guess. I was just thinking,
it's nice to take a different route sometimes.
Huh? We're going down the same street as always.
That's not what I mean. Like, the bookstore...
Oh, that's right. My Fanitsu!
Oops.
Eh? You didn't buy it?!
I was so concerned about Kirie that I forgot all about it...
Hey, c'mon what the heck?!
Okay, now listen close, Ebina!
O-okay!
We've used various means to make yourself more
appealing to Taihei, but it's gotten you nowhere.
H-have we really used that many...?
But now, I have devised a plan
that will bring you two together!
Kirie, you seem way more fired up than usual...
Hey, Kirie. Ebina.
Did your skate shoes fit okay?
Y-yes!
Th-they did!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Hey, Umaru, it looks like some pros
have come to practice today.
Things could get kinda dangerous.
No, it'll be fine! They separate
the pros and the amateurs.
But it's not like it's walled off or anything, right?
I'm telling you, it'll be okay!
P-please, I'll be counting on you today!
Same here, Ebina.
Yes, simple cause and effect: The thrill of
skating practice will lead to the thrill of love!
Through teaching Ebina how to skate, those two will...!
And as their relationship progresses, Umaru and I will...!
It's... it's so perfect, it's almost frightening!
Shpaaaaaan!
Skating is quite fun, indeed!
This is my first time at a Japanese skating rink.
Let's all enjoy ourselves!
O-okay...!
Still, Sylphin is something else.
She was the only one not invited, and yet...
Very well, let's begin!
When people skate on their own, well...
This is going to lead to something!
This is skating, indeed!
The pros are skating over here too!
Looks like it'd be best to stay in the middle area.
Yes, Taihei! Take Ebina's hand!
Well, you guys have fun!
You're not going to skate?
Big Brother CAN'T skate!
Uh, yeah...
Oh, no! I'd just assumed that he could!
O Brother of Umaru! You'll be fine!
It's quite easy, indeed!
R-really?
C'mon, Big Brother. I'll teach you.
But, what about Ebina?
S-skating is scary!
Kirie, lend me your hand!
Whaaat?
H-how did this "cause and effect"
lead to me and Ebina getting together?
The only thing to do is teach him how to skate,
and fast! That way, the two of them will...
Are you okay, Ebina?
What kind of move was that?!
Just let the strength go out of your body.
Putting too much strength into your feet
will make you lose your balance!
I-I'm sorry!
You see, Big Brother?
I-I guess, but...
But, this could be bad
not just for me but other people here.
Y-you'll be fine if you just relax and skate.
That is true, indeed!
You'll be fine if you think of it merely
as a surface you are sliding upon.
Whoa! A triple spin!
Sylphin, you're incredible!
That was as beautiful as a pro figure skater!
You think so? Goodness, you're making me blush!
Figure skater...
An incredible performance from Umaru!
She's just set a new world record!
Umaru, your jump is far more beautiful!
Eh?
Umaru! Let's challenge each other!
Huh? No, that's too dangerous.
It shall be fine!
You can do it.
T-Taihei!
The strength is draining from my body...
H-huh? Taihei, what's happened?
Ebina, look out!
O-oh nooooo!
I-I'm sorry! She's an amateur! Amateur coming through!
Huh? Brother, you're going into the pro area?!
That was fun, huh?
I would like to go again, indeed! I never thought...
Thank you for inviting me to go skating, Kirie!
Um, Ebina? This didn't help
improve things for you at all...
Huh?
All done, Hikari!
It's cream stew!
It's cold outside, so it's good to have something hot.
Let's eat!
Let's eat.
This cream stew is creamy!
This is much tastier than what my big sister made!
Huh?
Hers was all burned.
A-ah...
Sis, are you going somewhere?
I'm gonna to buy something.
You shouldn't eat that, Hikari.
Kanau's cooking, huh? I saw her in action once...
B-Big Brother...
Hm? What's the matter, Hikari?
It's just, when it comes to cooking...
Oh, there's no more bread.
Please make dinner at our house!
Big Brother, we need more bread!
What? You've eaten it all already?
I'll have to heat it up, so hold on a minute.
Huh? Did you say something just now?
No. Nothing really.
Don't be lying. You said something!
I said nothing whatsoever.
Wait, hold on. Something's not right.
Okay, it's ready.
Aah, this belly is full.
That was delicious.
It's gotten pretty dark outside, huh?
It sure gets dark soon in the winter.
Hikari! Where have you been?!
I suppose I should get going.
Will you be okay? Is someone coming for you?
Big Brother! Please see me home!
Of course.
Umaru Dive!
The heck?! What's with you?
I just... I thought I'd take a look outside.
Outside?
Well, LOOK! The stars are out and they're so pretty!
You're right. You can really see them tonight.
Hm? Do you want to have a look too, Hikari?
Yes...
Which one's Altair and which one's Deneb again?
What, you forgot? I've told you twice already.
Oh, you did?
Hm? What's the matter, Hikari?
Oh, now I remember!
It was YOU I taught about the stars.
When I...
When I was young, I always just stayed at home.
I'm back!
In those days, my sis was like...
You're eating sweet bread AGAIN?!
No, I am not!
Liar! Eating only bread is not healthy at all!
And here I was thinking you'd be lonely at home
by yourself and got you a present...
A present?! Yes, I want that!
Here. It's a stuffed toy cat.
It's cute, right?
It is?
Huh? Wh-why wouldn't it be cute?
Did you buy this?
O-of course I did.
My sister is a little strange.
THIS is the sort of thing she likes?
I'm home.
Welcome back...!
Sorry for the intrusion.
Th-this is my little sister, Hikari.
You'd mentioned you had a sister.
She looks just like MY little sister.
It's nice to meet you, Hikari.
Hey, look, Taihei! Here's that recipe book,
the one you said you wanted.
Thank you. What are the odds
you'd have this very same book?
I-it's my pleasure! My way of thanking you
for that stuffed doll!
I looked around, but just couldn't seem to find this book.
I can't believe you had it.
Oh, it was pure coincidence!
So this is...
my sister's type!
Well, I don't want to inconvenience you
by staying too long.
Oh, w-well, okay!
Um!
Please have some of my sister's cooking!
Her cooking?
I never knew your sister was good in the kitchen.
Looks like this will take a little while...
The stars are so pretty!
Oh, you're right. You can really see them, huh?
Well, how about I teach you
the constellations' names to pass the time?
Huh? Their names?
Yeah.
First off, that's Cassiopeia.
The stars are lined up in a "W" shape, see?
My sister is strange...
and she brought home a strange guy.
First off, that's Cassiopeia.
The stars are lined up in a "W" shape, see?
My sister is strange...
and she brought home a strange guy.
He's my big brother!
Blgh!
I'm sorry, Hikari. I'd totally forgotten.
No, it's okay. I'm really happy.
Thank you for remembering... Big Brother!
I've missed you so much!
Jeez! How long are you gonna keep this up?!
This is MY big...
Um...
Huh?
With the both of you on me, I can't really move...
Yeah, that's right! The "Dive" is MY technique!
It's a technique?
I have my own technique, the Hikari Dive!
The Hikari Dive?
First thing's first: Get off of him!
No. Rotation-wise, this is my turn.
How dare y-?!
I dare!
I guess this is what a mother feels like...
It's really okay? Just taking you this far...
Yes, I've got someone coming for me.
All right then, Hikari.
See you soon.
Okay!
This will be the last episode, huh everyone?
Looking back, it's gone by so fast.
Indeed, it feels like a mere three months have passed!
It's a little sad, isn't it?
Okay, let's finish this out, everyone. One, two...
See you again, indeed!
See you again!