That was loud.
Haru, are you okay?
My late grandma used to say
that you sneeze when someone
else is talking about you.
Here.
It must be Rin-chan!
No, I'm pretty sure he's just sick.
It's because you were swimming
in the pool in April.
I'm not a baby that gets sick from swimmi—
It's too early for swimming in outdoor pools.
We'll just have to work out until it's warmer.
Oh, I heard from Gou-chan
that Rin-chan joined the
Samezuka swim team.
Huh?
Is something wrong, Mako-chan?
No, it's nothing.
But this means we might run
into him in a tournament.
Yep, we should enter tournaments!
Then we can do relays again.
I only swim freestyle.
Does that mean you can't swim relays?
Don't say that!
Come on...
Besides, we can't swim a
relay with three people.
That's true.
Which means...
We have to find one more member?!
Theoretical Dolphin Kick!
We need one more member.
But it'll be hard to find one now.
I was turned down by everyone
I asked last time.
Physical Training
Ryugazaki-kun?
You go to school by train?
Yes.
Oh, by the way...
I wanted to ask you a favor, as a classmate...
I won't join the swim club.
Huh? How did you know
before I said anything?
It was easy enough to guess.
Huh?
Considering the recruiting posters in your bag,
and those swimsuit Iwatobi-chan straps
you probably plan to give to new recruits.
As I mentioned before,
I already joined the track team.
Goodbye.
Huh? Why?
The school is the next station!
Wow!
He runs the last stretch every day!
I want to swim already.
Wow...
We can swim here in the off-season?
A free environment where you can
reinvent yourself at your pace.
Spring Recruitment Campaign
Awesome!
Right?
I'm thinking that schools like us
without indoor pools probably
use facilities like these.
Way to go, Gou-chan!
Our super manager!
You're supposed to call me Kou!
Haruka-senpai.
How do we pay for it?
With our club budget, of course.
Ah, I see.
This gym is pretty expensive to join.
If our club budget will really cover that...
This is the real reason
we started a swim club.
That's probably what you're thinking.
Shut up.
This means we can swim year round!
That's not happening.
What? Why?
The school isn't going
to give that much money
to a brand-new club
with no accomplishments.
There is an aphorism from the Bible.
He who does not work,
neither shall he eat.
I don't think you're using that correctly.
You can't eat a pool.
So we'll get the money if
we deliver accomplishments?
I suppose.
That's the best way to secure
lots of money for your club.
Accomplishments...
So what if we can place
in a summer tournament?
Your request might be approved
at the second term budget review meeting.
But you'll need at least four
swimmers to bolster your case.
Swimmers...
So it's meaningless if we
can't find another member...
One more...
...and I can swim all I want!
Huh?
Haru?
Haru-chan sounds motivated now.
Oh, he stopped.
That was a trick question.
Yeah, I thought the same—
Hey.
I'll give you this.
So join the swim club.
No, thanks.
Ouch.
It's hopeless.
That's the best Haru can manage.
Don't let it get to you, Haru-chan!
Fun! Iwatobi Swim Club
Should the posters be flashier?
Ah.
Wait, Ryugazaki-kun!
Let's go home together.
We can talk about swimming.
I have practice now.
Deodorizer
And there's nothing you can say
that will convince me to join the swim club.
Ryugazaki-kun...
You're so cold.
Ryugazaki
This way!
What is it?
I found the perfect person!
The track team?
He can't join us, then.
Look. Over there.
It's his fate!
Was he on the swim team in middle school?
Does he hold a record?
It's his name!
His name?
Yep.
It's Ryugazaki Rei-chan!
Ryugazaki Rei
He's the same as us!
A boy with a girly name!
That's your reason?
But I have to agree.
Look at those deltoids...
That's your reason?!
You really think those reasons are enough?
My reason is very good!
Next, Ryugazaki.
That's right, Mako-chan.
Okay.
Go with your gut on these things.
Hey, it looks like he's about to jump.
Bar height: 4.20 meters.
Set takeoff speed to v.
Set acceleration to a.
Gravity is g.
If the center of gravity after taking
into account pole length is h,
then the angle of approach...
His form was beautiful.
He's probably a great diver.
Absolutely!
And his biceps are also beautiful!
Is that all you care about?!
I miscalculated the angle of approach.
Hey, Rei-chan!
Rei-chan?!
Oh, you can call me Nagisa.
I won't.
We aren't that close.
We can get closer once
you join the swim club.
I'm not going to join.
I'm only interested in
sports that are beautiful.
Like track?
Yes.
It's a sport known for beautiful
events such as pole vaulting.
You can attain the perfect form
through theory and calculation!
That sounds too hard
for me to understand,
but you can be in both
clubs at the same time.
You use your arm muscles
for pole vaulting, right?
So doesn't swimming sound perfect?
I'm not going to join both.
After all, humans evolved to live on land.
Why would you go backwards
and play sports in water?
It defies reason!
Don't forget that water has 12 to
13 times the viscosity of air!
No luck.
He wouldn't say yes.
I don't think Rei-chan likes water.
We don't need anyone like that.
Don't let him in the water.
If you say that,
nobody will join!
We'll have to spend all winter
lifting weights and jogging!
Are you okay with that, Haru-chan?
Are you really okay with that?!
No.
I think we need to ask Ama-chan
to strip down for us.
That won't happen.
She said that she won't wear a swimsuit.
Then we should reverse it!
Reverse it?
If you join, you get to show
off your swimsuit to Ama-chan!
Does anybody want that?
Wait, don't write that down.
Excuse me, boys.
We're sorry!
Hey, Haru.
It sounds like we'll be entering tournaments.
Are you really okay with that?
Even if you end up racing Rin again
and beating him?
Who told you?
I happened to run into Coach
Sasabe the other day.
It's in the past.
Besides...
He's swimming again.
That's enough.
Bar height: 4.30 meters.
Set takeoff speed to v.
Leave a, acceleration, unchanged.
But factor in the potential energy
from any shifts in the
pole's center of gravity.
Ryugazaki.
Are you running calculations
in your head before jumping?
Your form is perfect,
but that's all you have.
You're too focused on the technical side.
But I...
I understand that's your style,
but you're not going to
improve at this rate.
I have good news for everyone today.
Amazingly enough, I was able to schedule
a joint practice with Samezuka!
What? Really?!
Did you ask Rin?
My brother won't listen to me,
so I went straight to their captain.
Joint practice?
Yes.
That sounds great! Let's do it!
That's our super manager, Gou-cha—
It's Kou.
That means we have permission to swim
in Samezuka's indoor pool now.
But...
Since it's a joint practice,
we need to bring four
members at a minimum.
That means we have to recruit a
new member before the practice.
Especially since Gou-chan used her
sex appeal to get us this chance.
I didn't use sex appeal!
Huh? You didn't?
Of course not!
Nobody told me there would
be a joint practice.
The captain made the call.
Your little sister is a member
of the Iwatobi swim club, right?
Their members are Nanase Haruka,
Tachibana Makoto, and Hazuki Nagisa.
They all have girly names—
Sorry.
How do you know?
I participated in that tournament.
I believe that was your
last tournament as a
grade-schooler, Matsuoka-senpai.
My team lost in the prelims.
That race was amazing to watch.
Somebody's talking about me.
Wait, Rei-chan!
What do you want?
Can I run with you?
If you can keep up.
Okay!
This brings back memories.
I used to run with Haru-chan to the
swimming club like this in grade school.
Haru-chan always played
it cool and said,
"If you can keep up."
Who's this Haru-chan?
Oh, you go this way?
What do you want?
What do I want?
I want you to join the swim club.
We really need another member
before our joint practice.
Why does it have to be me?
Because you're a boy with a girly name?
That's your reason?!
Yeah.
But the main reason is because
you looked beautiful.
Huh?
When you were pole vaulting.
Your jump looked really beautiful, Rei-chan!
Well...
I was just
following theory and calculation.
That's not something everybody can do.
I suck at that stuff.
So I want you to use theory and
calculation to look good swimming.
That's impossible.
A swimmer must flap his
arms and legs underwater,
while struggling to break
the surface for a gasp of air.
You can't look good while doing that!
Really?
But...
Haru-chan is a beautiful swimmer.
Haru-chan again?
Hey, wait!
What are you doing?
Haru-chan,
Mako-chan.
Oh, Rei-chan.
You're Haru-chan-san?
Don't put -chan and -san on my name.
Is something up?
I'm willing to participate in your
joint practice as a trial member.
What? Really?!
But only on one condition.
I won't do any swimming.
Samezuka Academy
Indoor pools are so nice!
Easy to see they're from a champion school...
But ours are just as good!
It's been a while.
Hey, thanks for coming.
Thank you very much!
Sure.
You're Nanase-kun, right?
You won a bunch of regional
tournaments in grade school.
Yeah...
Oh, Senpai.
I've heard a lot about you.
What's wrong?
You may not remember,
Nothing.
but when you won the Iwatobi
regional, I was second.
I still remember how you beat
me on the 50 meter turn.
Samezuka Academy
Oh.
Big brother!
Gou, what are you trying to do?
Rin-chan! We get to swim together again!
Let's have fun today.
Together?
You guys are a waste of my time.
Big brother...
What's his problem?
Yeah, there's some history there.
I was thinking that you could practice
with our first-years today.
Okay!
Let's start with individual time trials.
You there.
Get in your swimsuit.
Uh, I'm not...
Sorry!
He forgot to bring his swimsuit!
What?
Why is he here, then?
You can use one of our spare
swimsuits, so go get changed!
Huh?
Hey, Nitori!
Yes!
Come with me.
Uh, I'm not...
Hurry up!
Hey!
Uh-oh...
You'll get in trouble again!
I'm not swimming!
The deal was that I wouldn't have to swim.
Don't worry.
These time trials are just for practice,
so it doesn't matter if you're slow.
That's not the issue!
Oh, it's Mako-chan's turn.
Are you listening to me?
So he's curious.
I'm up next.
Ready!
Keep it coming!
Next swimmer, get ready.
You're up next, Ryugazaki-kun.
I told you, I'm not—
Hey, next swimmer!
Move to the starting block!
Can the next person get over here?
Well...
You might as well.
Fine!
Don't underestimate the water.
I'm not!
It'll be fine.
It's about 50 centimeters from
the surface to the starting block.
Set acceleration to v.
Set entry angle to theta.
Assuming that the water
viscosity is equal to r...
Calculate the power I should
use when kicking off...
Ready!
His form is beautiful.
Set!
What angle should my arms be at?
What?!
U-Uh...
He hasn't come back up.
Um, this looks bad...
Is he okay?
Whew...
So Rei-chan...
You can't swim?
Yeah...
Are you saying it's my fault?!
I told you I wasn't going to swim!
You should have said something earlier.
I wasn't going to admit I couldn't swim.
That would go against
my sense of beauty!
Rei-chan...
I'll clear things up with Samezuka.
Sorry about forcing you
into this situation.
Oh, it's Haru's turn to swim.
Ready!
Set!
It's so beautiful to watch!
Is something wrong?
No, it's just that...
See? I told you so.
Haru-chan is an amazing swimmer.
He doesn't use theory.
No calculation, either.
He has something much stronger
that I do not.
Much stronger...
Can I...
Can I learn to swim like that?
You haven't given up yet?
Of course not.
But it looks like Rei-chan...
Ryugazaki!
Yes!
...is feeling much better.
No theory... No calculation...
Be free!
What?!
He fell.
Huh? He's coming over here.
I want to be like you, Nanase-senpai.
What do you mean?
I want that kind of freedom.
It's not freedom.
It's freestyle.
Fr-Freestyle...
Anyway, I would like to formally
join the swim club!
What? Really?
If you want to swim, go ahead.
That's that, then!
Yep!
Haru-chan!
However, you were the one who
initially invited me to join.
I expect you to take responsibility,
Nagisa-kun.
Sure! You can count on me!
Hey! Watch it!
Hey, so why can't you swim, Rei-chan?
That's a foolish question.
The fluid mechanics of human
physiology show that...
Enough of that complicated stuff.
I'll show you what to do.
Come with me.
Haru-chan's fired up!
This is how you hold a carving knife.
He's teaching him how
to make Iwatobi-chans.
You're not done with those yet?!
Next time: Captive Butterfly.
Captive Butterfly!
That's easy enough.
I'll have the theory down by next week.