The time is upon us.
Our long-held wish shall be fulfilled.
Thank you for bringing us this far, Fitoria-san.
And for the new wagon.
Filo really loves pulling one.
It's mine now, okay?
No, it's not.
Fitoria...
Is another hero nearby?
Yeah. I sense one.
I see.
Shield Hero...
Take care of her.
And keep your promise.
Yeah, I'll do what I can.
The Rising of the Shield Hero
A Conspiracy Linked
If only we could get past that wall,
we could cross the border.
Any other routes we could take, Raphtalia-san?
Taking a detour would
cost us a few more days.
Fitoria-san said there was
another hero nearby, right?
It might be better to take a detour anyway.
What will we do, Naofumi-sama?
Did you really try to make up with them?
If you don't tell them they're wrong,
you're basically admitting your guilt.
Shield Hero... keep your promise.
We'll head down to the checkpoint.
If it's Itsuki or Ren there, we'll talk
to them and have them let us through.
And what if they refuse?
Then we'll force our way through.
Okay.
What?
Well...
I thought you'd try to stop me because
it could make my reputation worse.
There are guys like Idol who want to kill you, even if they have to summon a monster.
This isn't the time to be
worrying about appearances.
True that.
Get ready. We're leaving.
Okay!
Th-That's...
Master...
I see the spear guy.
I get the guy least likely
to hear me out, huh?
What now?
It's too late to turn back.
Keep going.
Motoyasu, listen to me.
We're not here to fight.
All we ask is that you let us through.
Is that all?
Huh?
Is that all you have to say,
Devil of the Shield?!
Naofumi-sama!
Who attacks someone without
even listening to them first?
You're still using your brainwashing shield
to enslave Filo and Raphtalia-chan.
How despicable!
That shield doesn't exist!
Don't try to talk your way out of this!
Heroes are supposed to work together.
Hear me out, Motoyasu!
I don't want to fight you!
Hell, even last time—
Maybe I was summoned to this world...
to stop you!
Meteor Thrust!
You still won't go down?
You're stubborn if nothing else,
you damned devil.
Master!
Naofumi-sama, you can't talk
anything out when he's like this!
This guy...
Why is he doing this?
Hey, Motoyasu.
Why are you so mad?
Is it because I ran away last time?
Did it piss you off that much?
To you...
Were Ren and Itsuki that
insignificant to you?
I finally understand that
you really are a devil!
What?
You tricked us by saying
we were on the same team
as heroes, and then...
You...
You are the scum of the earth!
I will make you pay!
Hey, what did I even do?
Search your feelings!
You'll know!
He's seriously trying to kill me!
I'll make you pay.
I'll make you pay for
killing Itsuki and Ren!
I killed them?
What are you talking about?
Trying to play dumb, you accursed devil?
You should know why I'm so angry and hurt!
You killed them both!
And yet, you...
What is the meaning of this?
The heroes of the Bow and Sword were killed?
You used your brainwashing
shield on Princess Melty, too?
You filthy swine!
Again, I have no such thing!
If Motoyasu is telling the truth...
If even one Cardinal Hero is
missing when a Wave hits,
fighting it off will be
exponentially more difficult.
Listen up, Motoyasu.
I haven't killed Ren or Itsuki!
I have no need to!
What?
Did you see their bodies for yourself?
You didn't, huh?
Then it may be a lie—
It's reliable information
from an agent of the Church.
They said the Devil of the Shield unleashed
a monster sealed in the center of town
and killed Itsuki-sama and Ren-sama
while they were distracted.
What?
Motoyasu-sama, be wary of
his brainwashing shield.
Don't let the devil sway you with his words.
Yeah, I know.
I won't be fooled!
Why is she always like this?
Mel-chan?
Sister, you didn't.
Did you kill Ren and Itsuki?!
Now, it is time to battle.
What's this?
A Lightning Cage?!
Indeed. An item that seals caster and target
in an impregnable lightning prison.
You're not getting away!
I will avenge their deaths!
Calm down and think this through, Motoyasu!
Are you going to believe something
without confirming it for yourself?
I believe in my trustworthy friends!
What a clown!
He's dancing in the palm of her hand!
Here I come!
Shield Prison!
Our levels are too far apart!
Filo!
'Kay!
Oh no, you don't.
As source of thy power and the
next queen, I order thee.
That's one haughty incantation.
Decipher the laws of creation and
drench my targets in a rain of flame!
Zweit Fire Squall!
Nullify the flames raining
down upon my targets!
Anti-Zweit Fire Squall!
Naofumi!
You ready, Filo?
Yeah!
Not so fast!
Zweit Air Shot!
Amazing.
That's the move she picked up in
the duel with Fitoria-san.
She's already making good use of it!
Forgive me, Filo-chan.
I must fight for Ren and Itsuki,
even if it means hurting you.
Meteor Thrust!
I'm not done yet!
Chaos Spear!
Myne! Guys!
Zweit Fire!
Zweit Air Shot!
Behold this combo skill involving
fire, wind, and my spear!
Air-Burst Flare Lance!
Naofumi-sama!
Zweit Air Shot!
Zweit Aqua Shot!
Melty...
Naofumi-sama!
Is this... a combo skill?
You saw their attack just now, right?
Right.
Raphtalia-chan.
If you continue to side with him,
I won't show you any mercy, either.
As source of thy power, I order thee.
Decipher the laws of nature
and conceal my target.
First Hiding!
Hiding Shield!
Change Shield!
Motoyasu-sama!
He drained my SP?
Who do you think I am?!
I don't need to use any skills!
Filo!
High Quick!
Motoyasu-sama!
You're wide open.
You will not get in Naofumi-sama's way!
A damned demi-human thinks she can
strike me not once, but twice?
How dare you!
How could you force Filo-chan and
Raphtalia-chan to attack others for you?
You still don't get it?
What?
Filo! Melty!
As source of thy power, we order thee!
Decipher the laws of nature and
bring forth a raging wind!
Bring forth a pelting rain!
And produce a storm that
blows our targets away!
Typhoon!
That was great, Filo-chan!
We were in perfect sync!
Yeah!
Damn...
How can you be so strong when
you haven't upgraded classes?
Is this because of the
brainwashing shield, too?
While you were having fun playing superhero,
we were out here fighting
and acquiring skills.
Lies!
You think I'll believe
that trite explanation?!
It's the truth.
We did what we had to do,
no matter how trite or trivial.
And that's why you lost to us.
Give it a rest, Motoyasu. Hear me out.
Even so...
Even so, I must avenge Itsuki and Ren.
If I give in here, Princess Melty,
Raphtalia-chan, and Filo-chan
will never be freed from
the Devil of the Shield!
I will never accept that!
Because I'm the Spear Hero!
That's my Motoyasu-sama!
Bring me the Devil of the Shield's
head and my dear Melty!
How can I talk this thickheaded buffoon
down when he's got a hero complex?
Filo-chan?
This is odd.
All those soldiers are gone now.
Filo, what are you doing?
The shield, Master!
Bring out that dark shield!
And place a bunch of stuff above us!
Or else we're done for!
What are you saying...
Hurry up! Now!
Shield Prison!
More!
Up top, too!
Air Strike Shield!
Second Shield!
What are you playing at?
Shut up, Sister!
Here it comes!
Naofumi-sama...
Are Filo and Melty okay?
We're fine.
What?
What just happened, Myne?
Th-That power...
Don't tell me...
My, how wonderful.
You take the high-class multi-caster
ritual magic, Judgment,
head-on and remain standing?
I'd expect nothing less from the Shield Devil.
The Pope?
You're that guy from the
capital's cathedral!
Oh? You remember who I am?
Then you must be aware of your sin as well.
My sin?
You not only showed no gratitude for
the holy water God bestowed upon you,
but also deceived the people and led
them to turn against the country.
Hence,
I shall purify you all in the name of God.
Pope Balmus!
Do you realize what you have just done?!
You nearly killed the Spear Hero
and the next queen!
The Spear Hero's party and the next queen
were killed by the Devil of the Shield.
Or, well, that's how the script goes.
In other words, you are
all walking corpses.
What?
Myne, what the hell is he talking about?
And if walking corpses become
real corpses,
that just means all is right in the world.
It is all as God desires.
Nonsense!
That's some messed-up logic.
Reminds me of a certain someone.
Oh, you may rest assured.
We have already planned a system of
government to take the royal family's place.
Wha...
Ridiculous!
No one but us can rule this country!
Royalty that abuse their power
and mistreat the Church,
apostles of God Himself?
Neither the country nor its people
need such blasphemies.
If anything, you are a pestilence.
And the same goes for you heroes.
We worship the ones who save the
people and the world from the Waves.
But...
The Spear Hero released a sealed
monster upon the world,
the Sword Hero caused an epidemic,
and the Bow Hero tried to
conceal his standing and hide from his duty.
Heroes who cause harm across the country and
damage the people's belief are nothing but fakes.
I... I did it because I thought
it would help the world.
Ren and Itsuki were trying to help, too.
And you call us fakes?
Your foolishness speaks volumes.
As did theirs, when they started
investigating something beyond them.
Investigating?
That is why God's Judgment fell upon them.
God's Judgment?
W-Wait a second! Didn't Naofumi kill them?
You've put on quite the
amusing farce, but enough.
For the false Spear Hero
and for the Devil of the Shield,
clinging so desperately
to life like a cockroach,
let there be the purification of Holy Judgment.
And...
For this country, righteous order!
Watch out, Naofumi!
That sword is...
The Four Cardinal Heroes