You have visitors.
Pardon us.
What the hell do you want?
Please let us accompany you,
at least during the Waves!
Can you arrange for class upgrades?
You can simply get it done at another
country's dragon hourglass.
We won't get there before the Wave.
Once all the Waves are repelled,
you'll go back to your own world, won't you?
The next Wave is coming.
Will the heroes be able to overcome it?
It's almost time.
Along with the potions, I also packed
some leftover weapons I had.
They'll make for decent backups.
Thank you so much.
Still, I'm impressed you managed
to stock up on so much medicine.
Even this may not be enough.
There's no telling what'll
happen during the Wave.
If you're being that careful,
you'll be fine this time, too.
Oh, right. Hold out your hand, Raphtalia.
Huh?
What is this?
It's imbued with a spell to
boost your mana generation.
Not much of a present for a lady.
Boost my mana generation?
I'm so happy!
Thank you!
Only she gets one? No fair!
You get this.
It'll increase your agility.
It's very cute, Filo.
What? Really?
Yay! Thank you, Master!
And a hairpin won't fall
off when you transform.
What brought this accessory-making spree on?
It's just to boost their stats.
Really, now?
The time has come.
Register the Ake Squad
to be teleported with you?
Now you'll be teleported along with me.
Right!
It's time.
We're off.
Be right back!
Yeah! I'll be waiting in the shop!
Y'all better come back alive!
Yeah.
The Rising of the Shield Hero
Catastrophe Returns
The other villagers have already evacuated!
Get out of here now!
G-Got it!
That should do it for the evacuation.
That took a while.
We should get back and...
Go!
Yeah!
So strong...
They took down a lizardman in a flash.
Stay alert! There are more monsters around!
Right.
She killed them in one hit?
Thank you very much for your
help before, Shield Hero.
You know her?
Are you that same old lady?
Thanks to you, I'm all better now.
Here.
As you can see.
Wow!
Small fry like these are no match for me.
I swear on these fists, which fought many a
formidable foe back when I was an adventurer.
What the hell did I feed her?
Sir Hero!
We've finished evacuating the villagers!
Great.
Now focus on keeping the enemy out.
It's been three whole hours.
What are those guys doing?
Please go, Sir Hero.
Putting an end to the Wave as soon as
possible will also help the village.
But...
Leave the village to ol' Gran
here and these whippersnappers.
Got it.
Just don't push your luck, Gran.
Raphtalia, Filo, we're going.
Right.
'Kay!
Naofumi-sama!
What a big ship!
Don't let up!
Where are the others?
They're on the ship.
I told them attacking that statue and
spawning the Soul Eater came first, but nope...
How irresponsible can they be?
What are you doing, Motoyasu?
We need to take out the skeleton first!
No, the kraken comes first!
The Soul Eater won't spawn otherwise!
What are you saying?
You morons...
Say what?
This is no time to be bickering!
Naofumi...
Go defend some village or something.
Indeed.
An incompetent hero who can't fight should...
Who's really incompetent here?
As long as you don't put an end to
the Wave, the monsters will keep coming.
I can't defend a village like that.
But...
Instead of working together, you three
are doing whatever you want!
If we lose, all the villagers
will die, and so will you!
Quit thinking this is some game already!
I know, I know!
That's why I'm hitting the skeleton
to spawn the Soul Eater!
Huh?
You killed it earlier, but nothing spawned.
We need to kill it several times!
I don't know about that.
These morons...
It doesn't have any special
parameters or resistances.
Is there a way to spawn a Soul Eater
other than killing that monster?
Raphtalia! Cast light magic!
Light? Really?
Now!
O-Okay!
As source of thy power, I order thee.
Decipher the laws of nature and
illuminate my surroundings.
Fast Light!
Attack the shadow by its feet!
So many of them were hiding?
Look!
Soul Eaters are spawning
from all over the ship.
Dimensional Soul Eater
Thunderbolt Slash!
Thunder Arrow!
Lightning Spear!
It's sturdier than I expected.
Are our attacks even affecting it?
We'll get nowhere with only
lightning-element attacks.
Filo, cast wind magic.
'Kay!
Fast Tornado!
Hurry! Or else it'll use a powerful skill!
Got it!
Raphtalia, Filo...
Get behind me.
Filo!
'Kay.
High Quick!
Can't touch me!
This strategy will kill it eventually.
But...
If we take too long,
the village will be in danger!
He's not taking damage!
Don't complain. We have to kill it.
Raphtalia...
Yes?
I'm going to use the Rage Shield.
Forgive me.
Didn't I tell you?
I am your sword.
I will follow you through
fire and brimstone.
Take care of Raphtalia
if anything goes wrong.
I'll remain by your side until the very end.
Come forth, Rage Shield!
...will pay.
You will pay!
What was that?
For humiliating me by defeating
me as a puny human...
And for humiliating me by taking my
bones and turning me into a tool...
Is that the dragon zombie
I absorbed back then?
You will pay...
You will pay!
Growth affected by Zombie Dragon Shield
"Grow up"?
A seething rage...
It's not the flame from before.
It's his hatred!
What happened to him?
H-Hey!
Filo's being affected by
the dragon zombie, too?
He's basically a wild beast.
That isn't how a hero is supposed to fight.
What the hell are you people
standing around for?
H-How dare you, demi-human!
Naofumi-sama is fighting in our place!
That's right.
If only I weren't so useless...
If only I were stronger...
I wouldn't have to put him through this!
You have the power, so why won't you fight?
How can you call yourselves the
world's heroes like that?!
Crimson Sword!
Thunder Shot!
Motoyasu-san...
Why should I have to help that bastard?!
I hear you, but we have no
other choice right now.
Damn it all!
Motoyasu-sama? You mustn't help the Shield!
Can you kill that thing, then?
How do you like that?
Very cool, but you're not
doing much damage.
Naofumi-sama...
You will pay.
Shut up.
Settle down!
I will make you pay!
I believe in you.
Didn't I swear to protect Raphtalia, Filo,
and all the villagers?
Shield Prison!
Not so fast!
Change Shield!
Within this virgin of cold ore, who shall
swallow even your screams with her embrace,
suffer in anguish as your entire
body is stabbed and skewered!
Iron Maiden!
It's over.
Huh?
What happened?
Naofumi-sama! Filo!
Are you all right?
Yeah, as you can see.
Is that what the Shield is capable of?
It's basically a cheat.
Things will be different next time!
Hey...
Sore loser, much?
Th-That's not it, Filo-chan.
I'm, uh, just saying I could've one-shotted
that thing if I'd gotten serious.
Really?
R-Really!
Motoyasu never lies.
Then why didn't you?
What's there?
Another one?
This wasn't in the game!
How very disappointing.
You have trouble with weaklings like these?
Are you really the heroes who hold
the world's fate in their hands?
It seems only one man here is
worthy of even being called a hero.
What is your name?
You're supposed to introduce yourself
before asking for someone' name.
Oh, pardon me.
My name is Glass.
Feel free to consider me your enemy, hero.
Enemy?
I'm Naofumi.
Naofumi, is it?
Then, shall we begin
the true battle of this Wave?
The Raven Invader