You've got some nerve, calling for our help.
Thanks to you, Ange escaped,
and we lost the Villkiss.
You ended Libertus.
You, the Knight of the Villkiss!
Ange isn't your tool!
Without the Villkiss, we can't defeat Embryo.
Your father was the one who taught us that.
You let it all go to waste.
Quite the dutiful son, aren't you?
Libertus isn't over yet.
We ought to go help Ange.
When we can barely escape ourselves?
Well...
Besides, it's no use helping her.
She won't take my orders anymore.
Take us to Arzenal.
I'll inform you of our
plans after we resupply.
That's all.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry,
Embryo-sama.
Soul of God
Let Ange into the Diamond Rose Knighthood?
She can pilot the Ragna-mail.
She's needed in order to change the world.
You can't!
Ange won't listen to you, Embryo-sama.
Worse, she'll...
Are you jealous?
I just need her to use, like a tool.
You're the one that's most important to me.
Embryo-sama.
Would you let me through?
Leave.
Now.
You'll get in trouble if
you don't obey your master.
Then refuse, no matter what he says.
Not to worry.
I'd never join your
Daikon Radish Knighthood, anyway.
It's the Diamond Rose Knighthood.
Darjeeling, second flush.
"It's so good!"
Is that what you wanted to hear?
The tea Momoka prepares for
me is hundreds of times better.
Well, then.
You didn't call me to brag
about your stupid tea, did you?
Fine.
I'll get straight to the point.
I'd like to take you as my wife.
What?
You're stronger, more intelligent and
more beautiful than anyone I've ever met.
You're the goddess of the new world.
You are perfectly suited to be my wife.
So naturally, I want to
grant my wife's wishes.
Huh?
Let's destroy this world.
The people of the old world
were barbaric and warlike.
When they wanted, they stole.
When dissatisfied, they grew angry.
They were like animals.
In order to save the species,
I had to recreate humanity.
And I made this world.
I made an intelligent humanity, connected
through advanced information technology.
I made a world of abundance,
filled with light.
But this time, they stagnated.
They became used to being given things,
and they stopped thinking for themselves.
You've seen it, too.
They will hate and slaughter upon command.
You've seen their true, rotten nature.
Humanity hasn't changed at all.
They're fundamentally evil and foolish.
But, Ange, with you...
I'm certain that a humanity that we
created would be upright and good.
How?
Destroy the world how?
The flames of countless lives...
The Endless Song!
Unification theory.
It's the laws that govern the universe,
fashioned into a melody.
By amplifying this melody through the
Ragna-mail and using Aura's energy,
we can merge the two worlds...
And recreate a single world.
What you saw on the DRAGON
world was merely a test of the process.
What do you think, Ange?
Would you cooperate?
A new world, huh?
That'll stop your weird magic tricks, right?
Angelise-sama.
I have nothing to lose!
I'd rather die than become your wife...
Mister Tuner.
So you're the one to die!
W-Wait.
Angelise-sama!
You're a violent one.
But that's what makes you
worthy of being my wife.
Angelise-sama!
It seems even you can't handle
pain multiplied fifty times.
Then how about this?
Princess, are you all right?
Don't touch me.
Princess.
Princess!
Touch me more.
More...
I turned all of her pain into pleasure.
Ange, it's easy for me to manipulate you.
If you don't want to suffer anymore,
you'll accept my proposal.
Bring her back to normal, please.
Right now!
Rosalie.
Come on.
It's been a while.
Sorry.
I'm not in the mood.
Are you leaving again?
I have to help Ange.
If the commander isn't going to, I will.
Hilda.
I made a promise with her.
That we'll destroy this world together.
You love Ange, don't you?
I can tell. We've known
each other for a long time.
I'm the same, too, after all.
I can't seem to handle being without Chris.
She was always so scared.
I always felt like I had to protect her.
But she's so strong without me...
She's fine.
But I'm still a total loser.
I was the one who needed Chris.
Let's go get them back.
Chris, along with Ange.
Hilda.
All normal here, too.
Commander.
Hey,
Want me to get you out?
Wha—
But in exchange, there's something
I want you to help me with.
You haven't done it with Ange yet, have you?
If it all works out, I'll let you do me.
Stop it!
I'm Ange's Knight.
My first time will be with Ange— I mean, no!
Huh?
I mean, well, I'm not indulging in
sexy times until we're done fighting.
Like, as a knight, I want
to avoid anything amorous.
I heard you had your face
in Ange's crotch all the time.
That's a misunderstanding!
Those were accidents!
I wasn't being a pervert!
So you're just a loser.
I see.
Ange's knight, huh?
Assist me, Tusk.
I want to go help Ange.
Huh?
Something's wrong with our commander.
I can't really trust her.
Alektra?
Mei, what's going on?
Maggie.
The bulkheads have shut down.
We can't get out of the residential block.
Oh my, Commander.
Going out?
All dressed up, too.
You!
Are you going to Embryo-sama's
place or something?
I overheard.
You were talking in your sleep.
"Embryo-sama," you moaned.
Dude, what's going on?
I nailed it.
Let's do it, everyone.
I won't let you go!
You!
Now, Rosalie!
All right, it's open.
What is this?
Angelise-sama.
Where are you?
Princess.
You're useless!
You have such a defiant attitude for a slave.
Think about what you've done!
Princess...
Why?
I haven't forgotten what you did with
Julio-sama to hurt Angelise-sama.
So please apologize to Angelise-sama.
You mustn't die until you do.
Underground the west wing
of the royal palace,
in the dedicated royal shelter.
She must be there.
I was Embryo's doll.
He manipulated my mind
and took everything from me.
My pride, my duty, my chastity...
I was scared.
The cause of Libertus,
the duty of freeing the Norma,
my bonds with my friends...
All of it was replaced by his love,
by my dependence upon him,
and by the pleasures he gave me.
Why didn't you tell us?
How was I supposed to explain?
That I went to kill Embryo,
but instead he took my body and mind?
It's all my fault.
That Libertus failed,
that my friends died... All of it.
They all died trying to
help a filthy woman like me.
No.
No!
There's only one thing I can do to grieve.
I have to kill Embryo.
Nothing else.
I'm sure he's obsessed with
his new toy about now.
This is our only chance to kill him.
It hurts!
That's why you tried to go alone.
And I failed again.
I came along because it was you.
I followed you because you were my friend.
And I was just being used the whole time.
Say something, Alektra!
Now!
That's enough, Maggie.
Now that we know what happened,
we can't let you continue being in charge.
I relieve you of command.
Understood?
Yeah.
Hilda, you take over.
You won't make my mistakes.
Yes, ma'am.
It is quite enjoyable to see beauty
oppressed, suffering, and in despair.
Are you more accepting now?
Yes, Embryo-sama.
Go to hell, you shit!
Impressive.
It's hot!
Help!
Tusk!
Let's begin.
Where's Salia?
Well...
Never mind.
Pathetic.
Salia.
This is what happens
when you defy Embryo-sama.
Idiot.
You're the idiot who fell for that slimeball.
Embryo-sama is all I have left.
But that's not true of you.
You have the Villkiss,
your friends, and your own place to be.
You have everything.
You're strong enough
without having to transform.
Don't take anything else from me.
Leave, before Embryo-sama gets back.
If you keep resisting,
he'll end up destroying your mind.
Do you want that?
It's not like I'm trying
to help you or anything.
I just don't like seeing you be so pathetic.
Sing, sing, the two wishes are now,
Strongly, strongly shining in heavenly gold.
It speaks of eternity.
Thanks, Salia.
This is for helping me.
You'll be less trouble
if I make a daring escape.
I don't need your sympathy,
you macho gorilla.
Angelise-sama!
The preparations are complete.
All units, to your Ragna-mails.
Guard the Dawn Tower
until the mission is complete.
Yes, Master.
Where are you going, Ange-chan?
Embryo-san is looking for you.
Can you run, Angelise-sama?
Yes.
Oh, dear. I suppose I'll have to handle it.
Villkiss!
Momoka, get on!
Yes.
Chris-chan.
I know.
You're not getting away, Ange.
Angelise-sama!
I'm here to repay you, Ange.
Salako.
Salamandinay-sama.
Next Episode
I'm going to be so unlucky next week!
Me, too! My fortune's really bad.
Next week, could we end up...
Don't worry about it!
The previews are never right.
I thought this might be a death flag...
The One Left Behind
They won't kill us off! Right?