Customer service in Japanese style inns
is inevitably focused on emphasizing the individual
traits of the proprietress and employees
Episode 23
Compensation for the Dream
You awake, Minchi?
Do you really think this place
will be shut down?
Do you suppose there's anything
we can do about it?
She's up before me, as usual...
This place really is going
to be shut down...
Can't you go and persuade
the Madam Manager, Mr. Ren?
I think she'd listen to you, at least...
Time sure flies.
I came to this inn when
I was about your age.
I've known the Madam
Manager ever since.
She's made such a big decision this time.
Nothing anyone can say
will change her mind.
Morning, Nako!
Nako?
Good morning...
You should already know this,
but the morning greeting
is one of the most basic
requirements for a job.
I'm sorry...
Minchi...
I don't think we'll need
that much white radish.
The only customers are in the Wave Room,
which Nakochi is in charge of.
You're going to be fine, Minchi.
You can peel white radish like a pro.
You can work anywhere.
Yeah, you and Tohru are fine.
Rotary slicing, not peeling.
Huh?
No matter what happens,
I plan on becoming a fine chef.
I see...
Yeah.
You have a goal set in mind.
I...
Oh, there you are!
The Madam Manager is
calling for you, Ohana.
It's ready!
Delicious ginger tea!
I wonder why Mom said something
like that out of nowhere.
I guess that's the inn's financial state...
Enishing.
Yes?
Do you remember the catchphrase
I've been using since college?
"Time is money," was it?
Or perhaps it was "killing
two birds with one stone."
Or maybe, "always have a smile on"—
"Never give up!"
I'm going to get back the money that
you were stupidly tricked out of!
What?
Couldn't you put it a bit nicer?
What do you plan on doing now?
Well...
Let's see...
I'm coming in, Madam Manager.
Enter.
I will be heading to
Tokyo now, Madam Manager.
I see.
Well, great timing.
Take this girl along as well.
Huh? M-Me?
Meet up with your mother
and discuss future plans with her.
But I need you back here
in two days, no later.
The busiest time for the inns
in Yunosagi is during
the Bonbori Festival,
which starts next week.
Um...
Get ready quickly, okay?
I'm leaving in an hour.
Okay.
So I hear you're heading to Tokyo, Ohana.
Yeah.
The Madam Manager told me
to go and meet with my mom.
What are your future plans, Jiromaru?
Oh, she said she'll let
me off the hook here.
Which means you'll be a free man again!
I feel like I'm the only
one happy, though.
It's a bit awkward.
And where do you plan
on living from now on?
Huh?
Well...
Yeah, let's see...
Where am I going to live?
Have a safe trip, okay?
Thanks.
Ohana.
Yeah?
Are you going to see him?
Huh?
Your crush.
Well... I haven't decided yet.
What do you mean?
You need to meet up with him.
Do it!
You cheered me up a bit, Nakochi.
Thanks.
Oh, right. I have
something from Minchi—
What's taking you so long?!
I'm leaving you behind!
Coming!
Come back soon!
Ohana's got a lot on her
hands, doesn't she?
Why don't you worry about yourself
before you worry about others?
W-What's your problem?
Oh yeah, where's the young master?
No idea.
Maybe he's off crying somewhere
since he's all alone, after
having just been married.
What's wrong?
Beanman!
Takky went off to Tokyo, Beanman!
She said she'd do
everything by herself.
I should go after her, right?
If something were to—
Young master.
I know it's not in my character,
but allow me to speak my mind.
I think Takako considers this Tokyo trip
her first task as the next young
Madam Manager of Kissuiso.
The next young Madam Manager?
That's right.
It's also a man's duty to sit and wait.
Yeah.
Oh.
Looks like it found itself a
companion for today's trip.
I didn't expect to be
babysitting a high schooler.
I don't give old aunties trouble—
"Old aunties"?!
No, I mean my mother's brother's wife.
Which makes you... my aunt.
So that makes you my niece.
Technically.
Call me "big sis," then.
Balut.
Huh? What was that?
Oh, nothing!
Thanks so much!
Thank you for waiting.
Huh? Is that you, Ko?
Long time no see!
Eat up.
Oh... Thank you.
You're as well-mannered as ever.
Um...
In case you're wondering,
it's no longer the mother's
problem when a daughter this age
gets dumped or gets knocked up.
Besides, there's no way a healthy
boy can stand being so far apart.
Um...
In other words,
you have no reason to feel
awkward just because
you had a long distance
relationship with
my daughter and then
proceeded to dump her.
Is Ohana doing okay?
Do you really think a woman
who got dumped is doing okay?
I didn't dump her.
The food cart lady sure is
taking her time in getting here.
Uh...
What?
I've got lunches that Minchi made for us.
Why didn't you say so earlier?
This looks good.
You're the Madam Manager's
one and only grandchild.
Yeah.
Were you hoping to become
the Madam Manager someday?
I've never wanted to
become the Madam Manager.
I see.
Yup. It is good.
Aren't you going to eat?
It's delicious.
The spinach has been
seasoned very well.
You're right.
Minchi tasted these before she
served them to us, right?
What do you mean? Of course she did.
Yeah. Of course she did.
She also peeled the skin off
of these potatoes so neatly.
This is good, too.
Yeah.
Do you suppose you two would
have been doing well together
if I hadn't decided to flee that night?
There's nothing I can say, really.
Besides, it's not uncommon for children
to have to move because
of their parents.
And since she is being fed,
maybe there was no other option.
That's... how Ohana probably felt.
So you do know a lot about her.
No, I don't.
Please tell me more about her!
I've never even seen her
working at the inn.
I don't know anything...
Okay. Follow me, then.
So, what are your plans now?
That's what I'm going to
talk with my mom about.
Didn't you come to Kissuiso in the hopes
of living with your mother again?
No, that's not...
Come on, you're young, so
you've got it easy.
You've got a boyfriend waiting
for you back in Tokyo, right?
What?! You don't need
to be such a crybaby!
Did I say something to make you cry?!
Fine, I get it!
You didn't come to Kissuiso
because of that,
and even though you're young,
you've got it rough.
Also, you don't have
a boyfriend in Tokyo.
Happy?
Excuse me, may I have a can of beer?
Yes, of course!
And what would you like?
Cola.
And a cola, as well.
Oh, and some black tea.
What?
I'm an only child.
So am I.
What do you think of this distance
between an aunt and her niece?
It's hard to say.
I enjoy it.
Yeah. My aunt was absolutely correct.
I didn't come to Kissuiso
because there was
something I wanted to do.
I'm not struggling that
hard in life, either.
And yeah, Ko is in Tokyo.
But he's not my boyfriend.
He's just a crush of mine.
How are you going to
find that producer?
I actually have some information
given to me by my sister-in-law.
Yeah?
Wait, sister-in-law?!
Yup. The person you're
going to meet.
Your mother.
She is so reliable!
I'm coming with you.
It's an important matter
regarding the Kissuiso,
and I can't just leave everything
to my mom and you, aun- big sis.
Is that so?
Is it okay for you to
take off from work?
Yeah, I had a coworker cover my shift.
Is it okay for you as well?
I've already done everything
I need to for today.
Well, all I really "did"
was stand someone up.
For me?
No, of course not.
Come on. This way.
Bingo.
There he is!
There's nothing better in the world
than a cunning older sister.
Watch the elevator.
W-What?
Watch... helevator...?
He's a fast one, all right.
I lost him.
Did you see him?
No.
Which means he's still on this floor.
Um...
Keep running and I'll tell
everyone what you did!
Killer!
My new auntie, I mean, big sis,
seems to be pretty capable.
What, you nervous?
N-No!
Okay.
I'm borrowing this desk.
Since it's Sunday, there's
no one in the office.
Oh.
You'll be fine with coffee, right?
Um...
I... can't drink coffee.
O-Okay.
Then you can have green tea.
Um...
I love green tea.
Good thing you have the same
tastes as an old man.
Er...
I'm not about to watch porn with you.
Stop worrying.
Oh, good...
You were actually worried?
Oh, that's not what I...
Am I really that
unattractive of a woman?
No, absolutely not!
You're the most beautiful
of all my friends' mothers.
Okay, whatever.
Is this...
The Kissuiso. Where I grew up.
It's where Ohana works.
Wow.
It seems like a nice place.
It is.
There was some talk about a film
with the Kissuiso as its setting.
It was called off in the end,
but this is footage
from the camera tests.
I guess the producer of the film
wanted nothing more to do with it
after the plans were called off.
So he sent it to me asking if I'd like
to use it in my next article.
It pisses me off even more
that he thought he'd be
forgiven after doing that.
It's also my first time watching this.
This?
Yes.
This is sweetfish, and this is mackerel.
Two additional servings of
sashimi in the Wisteria Room.
Do you mind answering a few questions?
S-Sure.
Relax. Act naturally.
Okay.
Do you find work difficult, Miss Ohana?
I love festing it up,
err, working my hardest
with everyone, so...
That was Nakochi.
Mind telling us a bit more?
You came from Tokyo
on your own to be trained
as a waitress, right?
I'm not sure about "training"...
And you're only in high
school. Isn't it difficult?
Aren't your friends
and family in Tokyo?
Oh, did you leave your
boyfriend behind as well?
No, I didn't!
I didn't leave him behind.
Ko's also working hard.
It wasn't a matter of leaving
behind or being left behind.
U-Uh...
Sorry for these sudden questions,
but do you mind telling us
what your job is here?
My name is Majima Tomoe, and I
work as the head waitress here.
Miss Tomoe, you're not acting like usual...
Wow, that seems like a long time.
About 6 years, maybe.
Can I have some coffee, please?
And your age?
Huh? I thought you couldn't drink coffee.
Twenty...three.
Huh? Oh, twenty-three...
Coffee...
The last time I had some was with
your daughter- with Ohana.
Oh?
The kind they served at the restaurant
was bland and not very good,
but I kind of wanted to keep
that taste in my memories.
I didn't want to forget it.
I haven't had coffee since.
How's it taste after not
having it for so long?
I'm going to excuse myself now.
Okay.
Let's meet again.
Yeah.
I'm so honored to have our inn
stage Mr. Matsuura's next film.
Thank you so much, Ms. Matsumae.
I had almost given up on Ohana...
Ohana, you're nothing
like a bland coffee.
I'm not too swift on the uptake.
But this is obvious enough
for even me to understand.
Ohana...
Episode 24
Sui Shijima, the Final Boss
Don't say all these things!