King Joseph of Gallia's recent attack
came completely out of the blue!
It was an unspeakable attempt
to turn Romalia and many
innocent people to ash.
We have been shaken by fear.
Being turned to ash is unbearable!
If you're turned to ash,
you can't even admire a woman's rear!
And that is boring!
Truly boring!
However,
these heroes stopped King
Joseph's delusional plans.
They are the ones who
saved Halkeginia, no,
the entire world!
Long live Tristain!
I'm truly relieved that
you made it back alive.
Now let us eat, drink, and be merry!
Let us enjoy these hours of peace.
This way, please.
That's it?
Not even a reward?
If anyone's getting a reward,
it would be Saito.
After all, he's the one
who saved Romalia.
Oh, come on.
I'm serious.
Even an estate wouldn't be too much.
An estate...
I can't buy you a real mansion.
Maybe not now,
but someday.
The Queen's Reward
Sir Guiche, I'm so glad you're safe!
Are you hurt anywhere?
Thank you, I'm fine.
I'm sure it was your prayers
that delivered me home safely.
You're just going to let that go on?
I'm used to it.
You just have to look at it
like some sort of disease.
Well, it seems to have gotten worse.
You've got some nerve!
M-Montmorency...
How dare you kiss another
girl in front of me?
That's not what happened!
I had something on my face
and she was just helping
me get it off...
That's the lamest excuse ever!
This is it, I won't
forgive you this time!
Thanks for saving us in Romalia.
It was nothing.
Saito is very grateful, too.
He is?
I hope I'll find my familiar soon
and have a relationship like you.
Oh, but we fight all the time.
Excuse me...
Tiffania, may I ask you for a dance?
You want to dance with me?
I'll leave you two alone.
L-Louise!
Good luck, Tiffa!
What am I going to do?
I can't dance!
Tiffania, please!
Well, you see...
It's sad when people
don't know their places.
Have you seen your face recently?
Go wash your face and then come back!
Tiffania, you deserve a lord
with much higher standing
than that scum.
B-Beatrice!
I swear on the honor
of my family, Guldenhorf,
to find you someone much better.
U-Um, you really don't have to do that.
I was wondering where you were.
You should try some
of this food, Louise.
Wow, this all looks good!
Hey, Saito.
These were really great, too.
I know you're a big fan
of melons.
Melons?
I-I don't know what you're
talking about, Malicorne!
Bye then, little lemon!
What was he saying about melons?
It's nothing.
Are you sure?
I'm sure!
This song...
This was the first song we danced to.
Your hair and your dress
are the same as that night.
Took you long enough to notice.
You can be so dense sometimes.
Sorry.
I'm happy we can dance like this again.
Oh, don't be dramatic.
I'm not being dramatic.
I felt like my heart would stop
when I heard that they took you.
I kept wondering what I'd do
if anything happened to you.
Saito...
That's when I truly understood
how important you are to me.
Saito...
I never want to leave your side again.
I want to be with you always.
It doesn't have to be big.
Let's buy a house together someday.
One for just you and me.
You mean it?
Yes.
Well, if you really insist, I suppose
I can go along with it.
Of course I insist.
I want to be with you forever, too.
Louise...
Saito...
Sh-Shall we go?
Y-Yeah.
Louise...
Now, hang on, you can't...
Saito!
I'm never letting you go.
We're together forever now.
Saito...
Siesta!
You!
You were going to try to
get him in his sleep again!
You know me too well, Miss Vallière!
I warmed your bed for you.
But if you would like it to be warmer,
I will warm you.
I'm fine, but thanks for
your concern, Siesta.
Concern, my eye!
You've got this totally perverted grin!
I don't, I don't...
But, I mean, I am a guy, after all.
Uh oh...
Jeez. Why are all guys like that?
It's so idiotic,
the way they run to this
girl and that girl...
What's so funny?
Nothing.
I was just thinking that
this is so peaceful.
We've really made it home.
Yeah.
The only one missing is Tabitha.
I wonder what she's doing now.
We had just gotten back here,
and then she took off for Gallia again.
She did receive a letter asking
for her immediate return quite urgently.
I hope she's not getting
mixed up in some trouble.
She can take care of herself.
You're right...
Can this really mend her broken heart?
Take this.
This is the medicine that will
mend your mother's heart.
I have a question.
Why did you become his pawn?
There was something I had to do.
That's all I can say.
My Lady!
Lady Orléans!
Charlotte?
Charlotte... It's you, isn't it?
Mother!
One, two! One, two! One, two!
It doesn't have to be big.
Let's buy a house together someday.
Oh, Saito!
That reminds me!
What?
With Saito?
Tiffa's so bad!
Yeah, she was on top of Saito like so
and trying to kiss him!
Really?
And when Malicorne saw them,
he started talking about melons.
If she's melons, would I be coconuts?
I can't stay idle!
And I'd put the living room here.
This would be the banquet hall.
And here I'd have our dinner parties...
We'll need to have
some guest rooms, too.
And then...
The master bedroom.
Saito!
Louise...
No, I can't think about that!
That has to wait until we're married!
But we're going to live together!
No, no, I can't think about that!
Miss Vallière,
something terrible happened!
Wh-What's wrong, Siesta?
What's the big rush?
Have you heard about how Miss Westwood
made a move on Saito?
What? Tiffa?
That's right!
They were saying something
about melons!
So that's what the whole
melon thing was about.
Well, I guess I can live
with my pineapples.
I know I've got lemons!
What's this?
Don't look at that!
What is this supposed to be?
Can't you tell by looking at it?
It's the house where Saito
and I are going to live.
That's it, Miss Vallière!
You should buy a house
with Saito to prevent
Miss Westwood from seducing him.
A house with Saito?
Yeah!
You want to eliminate as
many rivals as possible!
Y-You're right!
I've got to find a house where we can
both live before something bad happens!
You've got to come look!
This mansion's kitchen looks
so spacious and convenient!
Your cooking is great
no matter what, Siesta.
Oh, Saito!
I don't like it.
But this mansion was designed by
that one very famous architect.
If I don't like it, I don't like it!
What's wrong with it?
Why don't you just say it?
I agree.
Why are you here anyway, Siesta?
This house is for me and Saito!
This is none of your business!
But if Saito moves,
I have to move with him.
Who decided that?!
Her majesty did.
Queen Henrietta made me
Saito's personal maid.
Which means you can't fire me.
Let us three
just continue to enjoy each
other's company, Miss Vallière!
If you're looking for a
place for three people,
how about this?
Siesta!
So that was your motive
for looking for a place!
Why can't Siesta come
live with us anyway?
It's hard to find a
good worker like Siesta.
I know that, but...
Oh, this is so wonderful!
Saito, come look at this!
That does look good.
It's got a big bath.
Big enough for two.
For two? Oh, you...
What's so great about this room?!
I hate it!
So you're saying you
didn't find anything?
Yeah, first she insisted
on finding a place,
then she did nothing but complain.
Of course we couldn't find anything.
I am the master!
What's wrong with looking until we find
something I'm happy with?
It doesn't matter where you live.
You should just go ahead and make sure,
before you get married.
Make sure of what?
That you're physically suited
to each other, of course!
I'm not going to do that!
Then I'll do that first.
It's not easy to be popular
with the ladies, huh, Saito?
I wouldn't say I'm popular, exactly...
We all heard, Saito! That's amazing!
Spectacular!
Wonderful!
Uh... huh?
What's going on?
They're talking about that...
The Queen's Knight?
That's right!
The play is extremely popular
with the townspeople.
Come at me, evil and
cruel army of Gallia!
Here I come!
Damn you, Incompetent King Joseph!
Our beloved Queen has sent me
to face any enemy of the Brimir faith!
I am the Swordsman of the
Wind, Hiligil Sartom!
Silence, Hiligil Sartom!
Take this!
Is Hiligil supposed to be me?
Looks like it.
Go, Saito!
I'm done for!
Now for the final blow!
I finished him!
What a horrible play.
You were wonderful, Saito!
Truly great!
By now, Saito's the hero
who saved His Holiness!
All the town girls are in love with him.
The town girls are...
...in love with him?
We've got to find a mansion...
...before we get even more rivals!
Yes!
Me? Be queen?
Yes.
Castelmore thinks so, too.
Castelmore was loyal to your father,
the Lord of Orléans.
Right now, Gallia has
forgotten its pride.
It lies in confusion.
The people have forgotten how to smile,
and nobody knows what to do next.
This country needs you on the throne
to make itself whole again.
Charlotte.
Let me tell you something your
father told me long ago.
He said, "We must make this land better."
This land?
Yes.
And I would like to honor that memory.
You will agree, won't you, Charlotte?
We've been searching
for three days now. Jeez.
How far do we have to go
to find a decent mansion?
It's because you have to
bicker about everything.
It's no wonder we haven't
found anything.
A-Are you saying this is all my fault?
Saito.
Miss Vallière.
Agnès?
I've been looking for you two.
Queen Henrietta wishes to see you.
Please go to her court at once.
I got you into danger in Romalia.
Oh, but it's fine.
This is not to make up for that, but I
wanted you to know I was sorry.
Thank you.
That reminds me.
I received a message from Gallia.
It looks like Tabitha will become
the new ruler of Gallia.
Tabitha?!
Yes.
I suppose officially it
will be Queen Charlotte.
I wonder if that's what
she really wants.
I worry about that as well.
Then again, it was Tabitha's decision.
I'm sure she gave it plenty of thought.
I'm sure she did...
Shall we enjoy this
while it's still warm?
I'm honored that you
received us like this.
Indeed. It was delicious.
Now, Saito, for all you
have done to help,
you would be entitled to a reward
worthy of your status as chevalier.
However, right now...
...the Tristain coffers...
It's fine. I don't need a reward.
No, I must insist.
I know it's meager,
but I'd like to give you
a small fiefdom from my own holdings.
F-Fiefdom?!
What's a fiefdom?
If you are given a fiefdom,
it would mean that you would become
that holding's king! Its lord!
A lord? Me?
There's a piece of land in western
Tristainia called De Ornierés.
I hope you will like it.
But isn't this too much for you?
I would feel guilty not rewarding
him in some way.
Right now, this is all I can do.
There's absolutely nothing here,
as far as the eye can see.
Could there possibly
be a mansion out here?
Excuse me.
We're trying to find
De Ornierés fiefdom.
Then you've found it!
You mean this wasteland is it?
What about the mansion?
Where is the mansion?
It looks like a haunted mansion.
The princess sure likes to joke.
They do say your home is your castle.
Well, the princess did
give it to me out of the
goodness of her heart.
Now hold on!
Don't tell me you actually
want to live here?
You can go back if you don't
like it, Miss Vallière.
Saito and I can live here all alone.
I will live here!
Of course I am going to live here!
Would you rather sleep on
his right or on his left?
There are a million other rooms,
so go sleep somewhere else!
But I'm scared to sleep here alone!
What if a ghost comes?
Can't we all just get along?
Tabitha!
What are you doing here?
Moving in.
You put the coronation on hold?!
I'm going to sleep.
Wait, Tabitha, that's...
Looks like she's really tired.
Let's just leave her.
It is very late.
Goodnight, Miss Vallière.
Louise, calm down!
We're finally in our own mansion!
This is even worse than
being at the academy!
Jeez, this stinks!
This mansion was supposed to
be just for me and Saito,
but all these people keep
getting in the way!
Tune in next time for
"The Maidens of De Ornierés."
Is that the princess kissing Saito?!
The Maidens of De Ornierés