How do you like the pleasure
of being enveloped by Junketsu?
I had no idea...
In all the world, only you and
I can savor this pleasure.
Enjoy it to the fullest.
She's right, not even I know it!
I'm so jealous, Ryuko!
The Life Fibers within Nui's body
repel other fibers,
so even if she puts on a Kamui,
she can't draw on its power.
Yep. That's why I chose to
become Grand Couturier.
I'll make the ultimate Kamui
with my own two hands.
As you are now, you must know
perfectly well what I'm thinking.
Humans exist to serve clothing...
Indeed. Life Fibers are
the pinnacle of all life forms.
C'mon, Ryuko,
hurry up and show me!
Let me see what you look like
in your finest!
Life Fiber Override, Kamui Junketsu!
Wow, how beautiful!
Lady Ragyo, Lady Satsuki
has escaped.
She what?
I will let you deal with her.
Understood.
You still want to avenge
your father's death?
For luck.
I see that she is still unable
to keep her emotions in check.
For someone with so little experience,
she has better technique than I expected...
Lady Ryuko has completely
awakened, hasn't she?
When the life of its host
is in danger, it causes the
Life Fibers to become even more active.
No matter how hard Soichiro
tried to seal them away,
it'd be child's play to
reawaken her by making her
experience intense existential terror.
Hououmaru, have all company
employees gather at REVOCS.
I will return to the mansion.
We're fast approaching
the endgame, Nui.
My heart is pounding!
I'd better work fast, then!
EPISODE 21
INCOMPLETE
Ryuko Matoi, to think
you were my little sister...
Don't get all big-sisterly on me now!
You're making me puke.
I have absolutely no intention to.
I'll crush anyone who's become
a puppet of the Life Fibers,
no matter who they may be.
Let's begin, Senketsu!
Life Fiber Synchronize, Kamui Senketsu!
KAMUI SENKETSU
Synchronizing with Senketsu
right after putting him on, huh?
That's our little miss Satsuki.
I can watch no longer!
Let's get in there, too!
We're gonna support Lady Satsuki!
Wait!
What do you want, slacker?
We're a little busy!
I have a message for the Elite Four
from Lady Satsuki!
Let's do this, Satsuki!
That's Bakuzan, huh?
You can't let go of something that
Mother smashed? Talk about clingy!
It's not clinginess,
it's vengeance!
Even if smashed to
a million pieces,
if a single fragment remains,
the whole can be reconstituted!
These two blades so lovingly
protected by my Elite Four
are the symbol of my tenacity
of purpose towards the
victory of Satsuki Kiryuin
and Honnouji Academy!
When will you shut up?!
You talk louder than your actions.
You couldn't even control Junketsu
and you're not gonna be able
to summon up that knockoff's power.
You think Satsuki Kiryuin
to be all talk, do you?
Then I'll have to prove otherwise!
Senketsu Senjin!
Senketsu Shippu!
How dare you, little bitch!
I'm only getting started!
Senjin Shippu!
Interesting! Senjin Shippu!
Kay... I think that's enough
for today.
So you aren't
entirely useless.
Ryuko, take off that outfit
and put me on.
No way. As if I'd stoop to looking
that ridiculous ever again.
I look ridiculous? Do you really
mean that, Ryuko?
Damn straight. What else would
you call it but ridiculous
when you can't tell if you're
wearing anything?
To access the Life Fibers' power, while at
the same time ensuring the wearer
is not inadvertently enslaved,
by minimizing the surface
area in direct contact.
That is the purpose of
Life Fiber Synchronization.
You should call it
a stroke of human genius.
Genius, my ass! All I see is fear.
You want the power of clothing,
but you don't want your
soul to be taken over.
That getup is that half-assed
mindset in a nutshell.
All it is is pathetic!
That isn't true.
When we were synchronized,
you wore me and I was worn by you.
As it stands now, you are only
being worn by Junketsu.
And what's wrong with that?
Being worn by it feels so
amazing I can't stand it!
Humanity was born to be
worn by Life Fibers.
Being worn by them
is the ultimate bliss.
That is the bliss of slavery.
If they have a problem with it,
they're welcome to die.
"Submit or die." That's the sort
of line you love to say!
Ain't that right, Satsuki Kiryuin?!
Senketsu Senjin!
Don't hold back!
Oh, I get it now.
So that's what's going on.
I knew it, you haven't mastered
wearing that Kamui properly.
Senketsu Shippu!
Too slow.
Senjin Shippu!
That one's slow, too!
Lady Satsuki!
What's she doing?!
What's the deal, huh?
You can't fight back?
You can't, can't you? 'Cause I've
seen through all your moves!
Come on!
Synchronization, my ass!
You and Senketsu aren't synchronized at all!
You shout out your instructions, and Senketsu
attacks using his own strength!
That's why there's a split-second
delay in your transformations!
You're the one who's just
being worn by her Kamui!
You haven't advanced one damn bit
since the time you wore Junketsu!
I am so freaking sick
of your empty talk.
Aw, what's the matter?
Aren't you gonna look down
on me like you always do?
If you can't stand on your own,
how about I put you on your feet?
Feel better now,
Little Miss Satsuki?
But you're not standing
on anything.
You're a sad little princess who's
standing on top of a sand castle.
The instant a wave comes,
that castle comes crashing down.
Stop it, Ryuko!
I admit, Satsuki cannot
hear me when I speak.
Our synchronization is
makeshift, as well.
And yet, our hearts are one.
We are of one mind in our desire to
bring you back to your senses.
Shut up.
Can you imagine how much of a strain
Satsuki is bearing to let me fight?
No other human could do that.
No one but Satsuki Kiryuin!
So what? It don't change the fact
that she's a loser!
I'm sick of hearing you yammering
on and on, you dishrag!
I'm gonna chop up
both you and—
Don't you dare mock Satsuki!
Satsuki's sand castle
is made of is steel!
It won't collapse that easily!
Butt the hell out!
If you can't see what is in her heart,
you can't see anything!
Quit pissing me off, human!
What can you do with that little knife?!
What can he do?
Lure you into
my firing range, I suppose.
Did you think that would
do anything to Junketsu?
No, but it did allow me
to get in close.
What the—
I'm going to rip Junketsu
off of you!
Satsuki, you bitch!
This was your plan all along?!
Indeed!
Senketsu and I cannot defeat you
in your current state.
However, if I give the Elite Four
a fighting chance, it is possible!
Son of a...
Yes! It went according
to plan!
I still can't believe that Satsuki proposed
a coordinated operation with the Elite Four.
But what's most
surprising of all
is that you were able to accurately relay
such a convoluted message, Mankanshoku.
She wrote it on my hands!
That girl thinks of everything.
I can't believe you'd
use yourself as bait.
I'd do anything to win.
Did you forget that that
is my modus operandi?
And now we're going to
pull you out of Junketsu
and make you come back
to your senses!
Why can't it separate Matoi?!
Run! Gamagoori!
Nui Harime!
You little—
Nope, nope, nope!
Gosh, you humans sure like to waste time
on things that don't work, don't you?
Those bullets are never
gonna hit me!
Ryuko will never be able
to take off Junketsu.
Why not?
Cause Junketsu's Life Fibers are tightly
linked with the ones inside Ryuko's body!
If you try to pull Junketsu off, they'll snap,
and she'll die from the shock!
What?!
Why, you—
The Kamui's been stitched
to her body?
That's so mean! What kind of
penalty game is that?!
Mako Mankanshoku
is on her way!
As a result of our recent successful buyout
of China and India's garment factories,
REVOCS now controls 100% of
the world garment market.
This means that every
human being on the planet
is wearing our clothing
in one form or another.
Congratulations, ladies and gentlemen,
Life Fibers have now spread to all humanity.
And now, I ask you to perform
one last task for me.
After it arrived on Earth
and gave us clothing,
the Original Life Fiber,
the cause of human evolution,
has remained asleep until the human race
reached a suitable level of evolution.
Keeping it safe has been
the duty of the Kiryuin clan.
Only one family head may
bear witness to its awakening.
I am grateful to time for allowing
that family head to be me.
Because I will be able to
witness the amazing event
that is about to transpire with my own two eyes!
What is that?
The beginning of the Cocoon Sphere Birth that
will soon make this world the Life Fibers'!
COCOON SPHERE NATIVITY
Congratulations.
Kuroido, do you and the others
also wish to take part?
May we?
Yes.
Thank you!
Magnificent!
It feels so wonderful!
Lady Ragyo!
Now, let us be off.
To where it will all begin.
Chew on this!
Senketsu!
You're dead!
Don't!
I understand why
you're angry, Ryuko!
I mean, if you can't take that outfit off,
you can't take a bath or wash yourself,
and you can't get
dressed up for a date!
But even so, that doesn't mean it's
okay to go on a rampage like this!
What are you talking about?
Mankanshoku, run! This isn't
the Matoi you used to know!
Ryuko is always Ryuko!
Even if you've got
Life Fibers inside you,
even if you're mad that you're
not human, you're still Ryuko!
And Senketsu is your Sunday best,
same as always!
That girl is such a pest.
Mako?
MAKO!
Would you look at that!
I am taking your blood.
Just don't pass
out from blood loss, all right?
I hate girls who try too hard
by wearing clothes that just don't suit them.
It's so pathetic
it makes my skin crawl!
I told you, that won't work!
Haven't you figured it out yet?
No ordinary human can beat me!
Perhaps, but the blade of my
heart isn't broken just yet!
Oh, brother... you're so stubborn!
I'm telling you,
Ryuko belongs to Lady Ragyo.
We'll see about that!
Are you trying to appeal
to her feelings, too?
That'll never work!
You've gotten soft, Satsuki!
It's because of you that I believe
it is possible to turn the tables!
Because of me?
Yes, you!
If Ryuko Matoi has truly gone over
to your side body and soul,
why haven't you given her
that Scissor Blade?!
That blade is the ultimate weapon
to fight against Life Fibers.
The reason you still carry it
is because you still harbor
doubts about her loyalties!
And it is in that uncertainty
that our victory lies!
Your agitation has made me
more convinced than ever!
We will be victorious!
Leave this one to us!
You see to Matoi, Lady Satsuki!
You are our hope!
I'm counting on you.
Ryuko! Destroy her
along with Senketsu!
That's what Lady Ragyo wants, too!
Give these softies with their "hope" nonsense
a dose of cold, hard reality!
You got it.
Move it.
Stop this, Ryuko!
You're protecting that woman?
I will protect Mako.
But I will protect you, too, Ryuko.
Me?
Yes, you. If you killed Mako here,
the one who would be hurt
most of all would be you.
That is why I won't let you
lay a hand on her!
What?
It's because you've been selfish
that Senketsu is being worn by me!
This isn't right!
The Ryuko I know
can take off that outfit.
So let's hurry up
and get changed, okay?
God, your voice is so annoying!
Now, Mankanshoku!
Jam Senketsu into the wound!
Senketsu! Use your strength to shake
Ryuko's Life Fibers loose from Junketsu!
Right!
On it!
Ryuko, I'm coming!
I'm going to force myself onto you!
Learn the power
of the Sunday best!
Ryuko! We're here to
bring you home!
Ryuko!
I'll kill anyone who ruins
my happiness.
This isn't happiness,
not even close!
This isn't you, Ryuko!
Shut your mouth.
Snap out of it, Ryuko!
Shut up!
Dummy, dummy, dummy!
Fine, go ahead and kill me!
If you're so intent on
staying cooped up in here,
kill me and give up on being my Ryuko!
Ryuko!
Matoi...
Oopsie, looks like they
failed to win her over.
Ryuko, let's sink this tub!
What?
Give your crap a rest!
Impossible!
How dare you bastards
put me into this outfit!
Ryuko!
I'm tired of all of this.
I want it off!
- Matoi!
- Transfer student!
I WANT IT OFF!
Stop, Matoi!
If you tear it off, you'll die!
I'd rather be dead!
I have to take this off
even if I die!
Because if I don't...
I won't be able
to wear Senketsu again!
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Someone once said that each
person's life is a tapestry.
A TAPESTRY
The time has come for two
woven tapestries that
WOVEN
can never intermingle to overlap and become one.
OVERLAP
The impetus for this... is croquettes?
IMPETUS
CORQUETTES!?
Next time on Kill la Kill,
"Tell Me How You Feel."
TELL ME HOW YOU FEEL
EPISODE 22