Are you nervous?
No, it's just a track meet.
Right, just a track meet.
Episode 5:
"Hinode Bridge"
He's smiling.
Ready...
Hey.
Long time.
How've you been?
Not bad.
How was it?
Must be hard to get back into it.
I'm here.
Is that—
I'm jealous.
I'm Matsuda. I'm run sprints.
I'm Nagai. I do hurdles.
I'm Hyouno.
I'm Yukinari's—
Who cares, Yanagi. Let's go.
They call each other by their first names.
Yukinari, don't use up all your energy.
You guys should
get some release, too,
or it'll hurt your performance.
The fireworks were awesome the other day.
I wish I saw it.
Next year, for sure.
They're really huge up close!
Are you sure you should have said that?
They're going to start rumors.
Let them.
I just remembered I have
something to do. See you.
Hey,
is Hiro-kun on another...
A date, I think.
If you don't mind me asking, whom's he with?
I wouldn't know.
That's right.
Of course you wouldn't.
Touko-san, was it?
Yes.
You've become even
more of a lady lately.
Summer is the season of love, huh?
Excuse me, I've said too
much to a dear customer.
No, it's fine.
Let me bring you a cookie
to make up for it, on me.
Thanks.
Sacchan
No way.
But, then...
Who? Who?!
Thanks for earlier.
You chased me down all
out of breath just to say that?
I wanted to talk to you about something.
I bet you've done it before, too.
Talking to the plaster figure in the art room
to gather your thoughts.
Not really.
Touko says she has.
So are you saying I don't have to respond?
Hello. Is Sacchan in?
Touko-chan's here.
She was coming today?
Yeah.
Touko-chan.
Is it okay?
I'll be right there.
Come in.
Thank you.
No problem.
What's wrong?
Nothing. Come in.
Okay.
Huh...
I think it's Mom.
I'll go say hi.
There's no hurry.
Hm?
Yuki hurt his leg during
the summer of first year.
He's rehabilitating.
There was a joint middle-school
and high-school track meet today,
but it didn't go too well.
Hiro-kun has
a date today.
I thought it'd be with you.
But I was already supposed
to come over today.
Sacchan, are you going out with Hiro-kun?
He was here until earlier.
So many surprises today.
I didn't think you'd be going out.
I didn't know.
Touko-chan, you've got it wrong.
I never said I'm going out with him.
We were just reading together.
Oh, right. Of course.
I guess it wouldn't be anything more.
And you? Have you met with
that guy since then?
Yeah, about that.
Okikura-kun seems stern,
but I thought maybe he has a nice side.
Ah.
And he's cute.
Oh. No, no, no. It's not like that.
Nothing like that.
I'm going to be in the
hospital for a while soon.
It's just for tests, so it's
nothing to worry about.
Oh really?
There's somewhere I want to go
with you when I'm discharged.
Where?
I can't tell you yet.
I wish I could see the future.
I think Yuki's really worried.
Everyone wants to know the future, right?
Are you seriously not going to say anything?
Nah,
I won't see it.
Okikura residence.
Okikura-kun? It's Fukami.
Can we meet up for a bit?
I know. What you said
to me the other night...
I thought about it.
Kakeru is out right now.
Excuse my late introduction.
I'm Kakeru's dad.
I'll let him know you
called when he gets home.
I'm sorry. Good-bye.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
You would do that!
What is this?
Nothing, nothing!
I just thought maybe I'd read for once.
So you bought it?
Y-Y-Yes!
No, you didn't.
There's no chance you'd read Camus.
Camus. Camus! The Myth of Sisyphus!
It makes no sense!
It's that tragic glasses girl.
Hello, Fukami here.
Hey. Sorry, I was out earlier.
It's fine. I—
My dad said he's sorry for
troubling a young girl.
I'm sorry, too.
It was my mistake.
Do you want to come over now?
If you have time,
my dad says he wants to cook
for you to make up for it.
Cook?
Dad's been living alone for a long time.
He's good at cooking.
But—
Didn't you want to talk to me?
Yeah, but...
There's something I need to tell you, too.
Do you know how to get here?
I don't.
Come in.
I'm Touko Fukami.
Thanks for having me.
I'll make something.
Think of it as a light snack.
Okay.
Kakeru, make Fukami-san
at home in the meantime.
She's half my guest today, after all.
All right. I'll keep her company.
I'll show you to my room.
That's my room.
Hey...
Yeah?
When it rained the other day,
on the road to Kirinkan...
You saw.
I wasn't hugging her.
I just caught her.
"Hugging"...
She'd hurt her leg.
You know about that, don't you?
It's okay. I'm done talking.
She nearly fell over on the steep road.
Anyway, it's nothing.
But the reason I wanted you over today
is to talk about her—Takayama.
Takayama is going to
confess to Yukinari Imi.
Eh?
I said, Takayama is going
to confess to Yukinari Imi.
What? What? What?
How do you know that about her?
Did you see the future?
She told me herself.
She told me to tell you.
I want you to tell Touko about this.
Because—
I won't ask why.
Don't talk, statue.
Crap.
It's good.
Say, Kakeru,
this is a good opportunity.
Why don't you get a cell phone?
It'd be useful.
Are they really that useful?
Yeah. Well, I might die without one.
Would anyone ever call me?
Is Yana-chan's leg all better now?
I think so.
That's good to hear.
Seriously, I know your boyfriend's there,
but you've seriously got
ears all over the hospital.
How often are you there?
Three days a week.
They were such a cute couple.
They're both remarried and have kids.
There they are amidst
their complicated family,
like leaves in a cold blast, like a boat,
their hearts tossed in a storm!
Go away.
Friendship punch!
I had such a treat today.
Thanks for having me over.
See you.
I found an interesting place the other day.
It's nearby.
When I found it, I knew
I had to take you there.
I've been meaning to ask you.
Do you want to go now?
Sure.
Wait here. I'll get ready.
Thanks for everything today.
The meal was delicious.
Say hi to your dad for me.
I'll be heading home now.
Bye.
She still hasn't told me what
she wanted to talk to me about.
Yanagi. You haven't made it home yet?
I'm resting here.
This is where I take a break,
eat, drink some water,
and get ready for the rest of the trip.
You don't have any water.
There was something I wanted to tell you.
I...
like you.
I know you like Touko.
I know you confessed to her, too.
I know it's going to be painful for me
to live with you after you reject me.
We're family, as you said.
I know what your answer is.
I mean, I would have been really
happy if you gave up Touko for me,
but I would have lost respect for you.
Still, I wanted to tell you.
I don't know what's going
to happen to us now,
but this is where I move forward.
I wanted to tell you that here.
I'll head home first.
If I see you there, I hope we can
keep things the way they were.
I overheard something some high school girls
said at the station.
One of them said, "1221, year of the Joukyu war."
High school girls are busy, too.
Hina, can you set up the
chopsticks and stuff?
Okay.
Onee-chan, come help.
Onee-chan, dinner!
Okay.
I wanted to tell you myself.
That doesn't explain anything.
I'm a total idiot.
What am I?!
Come to the school yard.
Let's put an end to this.
Episode 6
"Punch"