Squeak, squeak, squeak!
Look how the hamsters eat their food so squeaky clean.
They're squeakily cute!
What are you doing?
Big Brother! Welcome back.
I was just shooting a movie...
Huh? What's that?
Oh.
Bomba let me have this.
A single-lens camera?!
Huh? Why would he give you something so COOL?!
He said he bought a new one
so he won't use this anymore.
It's made by a different company,
so none of the lenses fit.
As of today, I'm with Team Canon!
Yeah, that sounds like Bomba...
Still, taking photos doesn't really sound like Bomba.
He's been doing it since high school.
It's just, he gets bored easily
and jumps from hobby to hobby.
Yeah, that DOES sound like Bomba...
So, how about I snap off a shot
while you just act natural?
Huh? H-hold on, Big Brother!
Umaruuuun!
Okay, cheese!
How is that acting natural?!
Tee-hee!
If I'm gonna leave behind a memory of me,
I may as well look good in it!
She makes it sound like I'm painting her friggin' portrait...
Oh, I know! I'll take YOUR photo!
R-really?
It looks kind of plain...
Just hurry up and take it.
Come on, Big Brother! Give us a smile! Say chee...!
Hey! I was making some kind of weird face, wasn't I?!
Nah, not at all!
You friggin' took it when you'd only said "Chee"!
Photos are a lot of fun, huh?
Huh?
Big Brother, there are some old photos in here.
I guess Bomba left the memory card in, huh?
Ah! Kirie looks so young!
She doesn't look happy at all.
And here's an old one of you!
Huh?
You shouldn't go looking at other people's photos.
I'll give this memory card back to Bomba.
Still, finding old photos is kinda fun, huh?
Yeah...
Okay, Big Brother! Let's take tons of pics!
You're STILL taking photos?
If I take photos of the hamsters,
I might be able to enter them in a contest again!
Oh, yeah.
Okay, here goes.
And... Cheese!
Taihei, I bought a new camera,
so I'll give you my old one.
You wanna come by and get it tomorrow?
But it's a single-lens, right?
Don't you want to hold on to it?
You should have a camera.
Huh?
Tanukichi will be all grown before you know it.
She won't be living with you forever, right?
Take pictures of her now, while she's acting natural.
You'll thank yourself for it later.
Man, there's nothing more
to take pictures of in here. Let's go outside!
Hm? Oh...
Well, how about we go for a walk?
What do you wanna take a picture of, Big Brother?
The scenery, I guess...
Oh, yeah!
Huh?
Let's take a picture of you drinking cola
with the setting sun in the background!
There's no point in even being outside for that, is there?!
Hey, Bomba, you left your memory card
in the camera you gave me the other day.
Whoops! Sorry 'bout that.
Were there any photos on it?
Huh?
Why'd you only take one pic?
And what's with this crazy-ass face?!
Th..they're closed?
But they can't! This is where you and I
have made so many memories!
It is a travesty, indeed!
TSF, it says they're closed for cleaning.
Oh?
Where should we go? Nyaon would be crowded,
and we went to the candy store just the other day.
Well then, UMR! There is somewhere that I wish to go!
Hm?
This department store is totally retro!
Right?! It is a nice old department store, indeed!
Even the story directory calls to mind a bygone age!
This escalator is SO nostalgic!
They don't even have a food court, just restaurants
where you have to buy a ticket for your order!
And this staircase!
Even the sign leading to the rooftop is wonderful, indeed!
An arcade!
It looks like an amusement park, indeed!
That crane arm is SUPER strong!
And so, Sylphin and I both grew fond of that nostalgic
department store and started going there often.
But...
Oh. That department store, huh?
That's right! We should go, too!
Yeah. I guess we should before it closes.
"Closes"? It's going belly-up?!
Well, it's an old building
and there aren't many customers, right?
What are you talking about? It's great
BECAUSE it's old and there aren't many customers!
That's no way for the stores to stay open, is it?
Nice! I got "Excellent Luck"!
As did I!
My brother is a liar...
There's not a single sign that says they're closing.
Sure, there aren't many customers,
but it's still got some life left in it.
Places like this make you hope
they stick around, don't they?
So that even once you and I have become adults,
we can reminisce and talk about "that time when."
And as we're talking, we can think to ourselves,
"I'm glad we became friends."
TSF...
D-don't you worry. This is staying put.
Nothing's going to change!
Huh?
What is it, Ebina?
Was that always a vacant lot?
Oh, you're right. That's a lot of empty land...
I wonder if some big building used to be there.
There used to be... an amusement park there.
Huh? An amusement park?
Yes. It was most fun, indeed!
That's when I first realized...
Where should we go?
Well then, UMR! There is somewhere that I wish to go!
Sylphin knew that the department store
would be closing.
Hey, how about we all go to the amusement park
on our next day off?
I would like to go, indeed!
I-I will go, too!
Where should we go?
This familiar scenery....
Once we become adults, it will have changed completely.
But even if the scenery changes,
there are some things that will never change...
Because they exist in our memories.
Coming!
Ah, Ebina. Good morning.
U-um! I got some rice in the mail, from Akita.
This year as well?
Thanks, as always.
Thanks, Ebina. You should join us for dinner tonight!
O-okay! Thank you!
I have to make sure I don't eat too much...
What should I make today...?
This is new crop rice, right?
I should make something extra tasty...
What do YOU always make, Ebina?
Um, if I'm using rice, kiritanpo hotpot, or...
oh, oyaki dumplings.
Oh. Yeah, you're from Akita all right.
Still, you need mochi rice for oyaki,
and kiritanpo takes a lot of time to make.
If we're going to make something in time for lunch...
Ah!
What about takikomi rice?
Whoa! Good idea!
Sorry to drag you into the kitchen,
but you'll be a big help.
I-I'm in the kitchen with Taihei!
Are you okay, Ebina?
Th-th-this is...
It's like what Kirie said before!
Ebina! I have a cunning plan!
Huh? A "plan"?
Apparently, the way to a man's heart
is through his stomach.
His stomach?!
Put simply, through FOOD!
Feed Taihei some of your home cooking
and you'll land him for sure!
L-l-land him?! No, I can't!
Land him! Land him! For sure!
She's really concentrating hard.
Is that from being from a farming family?
Ebina, I'll help too.
Okay!
Don't you think it's a little cramped?
No, it's fine!
If I let her cook alone with Big Brother,
she'll find out HE'S the one who always makes the food.
I have to help out, at least a little.
Ebina, I'll trim the chicken and dice the vegetables.
Would you mind rinsing the rice?
Oh, um, okay!
What about me?
Well, we're going to cook the chicken,
so you can get the frypan ready.
Leave it to me, Big Brother!
She should be able to do that, at least...
He's so close!
Brother, how about this?
No, that's too small. It's for frying eggs.
I-I knew that! I was just joking.
The larger one's down below there,
so go ahead and add some oil for me.
Ah... Must be nice...
Land him!
Kirie... Sure enough, I can't do it!
Fire!
Ebina!
Are you okay, Ebina?
Dammit, Umaru!
You gave Ebina such a shock that she fell!
What if she'd hurt herself?!
And why did you add that much oil
just for browning the chicken?
Uh, I got a little confused...
I-I'm sorry, Ebina. Are you okay?
The truth is, I can't cook at all.
I wanted to grab him... but he grabbed me!
Huh?
Well, that little accident aside...
Y-yes! I'm sorry!
No, it was my fault.
Okay then...
Let's eat!
I wonder what's for dinner tonight...
Thursday is bread day, so what could it be?
I'm home.
Oh, Big Brother!
Look who I ran into on the way home.
So, I invited her over for dinner.
"Ran into," you say? And where
did this meeting take place?
What are you all mad about?
Was it wrong for me to come, Big Brother?
No, you're perfectly fine.
Ah! That was a sneer!
It was her PLAN to come here, Big Brother!
It was just a coincidence, Big Brother.
What difference does it make?
And what's got you so angry?
You're acting strange.
She's had dinner with us before, right?
Yeah, but still...
Well? Why did you come here?
It was just a coincidence.
I saw him as he was leaving the office,
so I called out "Big Brother!" and he replied "Hikari!"
THAT'S NOT A COINCIDENCE AT ALL!
I just happened to be outside of his office
and he just happened to come out.
There's nothing coincidental about that!
It's purely coincidental.
I thought those two were friends...
What's got Umaru in such a bad mood?
Still, maybe Hikari came over so they can get closer.
Huh? Isn't it bread day today?
Yup, it's bread day. So, let's make pancakes.
Okay, I think it's ready now.
All of us making something together
will probably help them break the ice.
Okay, who's up first?
I... I-!
Okay! I shall make you the perfect pancake, Big Brother!
"Perfect," huh? That's a tall order.
Nah, it's easy!
All you have to do is pour this on here!
You think?
Hyaa!
It was too soon!
Big Brother, I can make a better one.
Um, Hikari?
You watching?
The trick is to wait until the surface starts to bubble.
Okay, all done!
What is this sorcery?!
Delish!
It's fun to make food together, isn't it?
Huh? Did you make more?
No, these are your two.
You said you made them for me, right?
Big Brother, don't force yourself.
There's no way those will taste good.
Um, I...
Hm?
I came because I wanted to eat bread with you.
It wasn't a coincidence.
I'm sorry for lying.
You don't say...
Oh, that's right!
You forgot this last time!
That's pretty incredible that you got an award.
Th-thank you very much.
Hmph!
I GOT AN AWARD TOO!
Why are you getting so mad?
I'm not getting mad!
Mine is for AP classes.
They recommended that I take AP classes too!
See? You're getting mad.
I'M NOT GETTING MAD!
Squeak, squeak. Hamjiro, Hamsaburo, c'mon!
Ding-ding-ding!
Ooh, and the wild hamsters have appeared!
Let's get your hamster ball ready!
Dammit, Umaru! Don't treat your hamsters like toys!
Y-you've got it all wrong, Big Brother.
We're just playing together.
Even if you're trying to play,
your pets aren't having any fun.
I mean, look at their faces.
They're making the same face as always...
Look, small animals have been known to die from stress.
They're always in the same place, inside their cage.
You have to treat them with care, right?
Y-yeah...
Master! Good afternoon!
And good afternoon, hamsters.
Master, are you not letting them out today?
Yeah. 'Cause Big Brother said...
Pet stress?
Yeah, he thinks I tire them out
by playing with them too much.
A-a long time ago at an aquarium I went to,
I heard that even fish can feel stress.
All those people coming and going
and standing there in front of them...
Well, the hamsters always stay inside the house,
so I think they're okay!
Hamjiro, Hamsaburo, good afternoon.
'Sup, Tanukichi?
I'll be back.
Okay, here's your food.
Sorry Hamjiro and Hamsaburo...
Umaru must be tough to put up with.
She's a bit selfish, but don't hold it against her, okay?
Huh? What's wrong?
Umaru has returned!
Okay, I'm back! Games, Internet, and anime!
Hamjiro, Hamsaburo, c'mon out! Let's have a party!
Well, that was the usual fun and games...
What should we do next?
Still, it's not like you can understand me.
You're not feeling any stress, right?
I wonder if Big Brother will be home soon...
Huh? Your hamster ball?
Well, well! You two wanna play with me after all!
Okay! Today it's the Pokeham the Movie 2000!
I'm home.
Hey! Wake up, Umaru!
Gah! What? Big Brother?
I told you not to play with your hamsters!
So it's just us doing the preview again, huh?
Last time there were just WAY too many spoilers!
It says here in the script,
"It will be fine. She trusts Umaru."
In a way, faith is the biggest,
most irresponsible kicker of them all, huh?