Rebooting attitude control system.
Ensign Ledo, your resistance
is without meaning.
This is...
Then all this time, I've been talking to...
X3752 Striker interface system.
So it was all a fabrication.
The pilot of this craft no longer exists.
However, I am carrying on
Commander Kugel's mission.
All of my activities follow
the commander's main plan.
What?!
Commander Kugel designed the
social form of this fleet
as a system that provides
a sense of solidarity
through my worship.
Already, I am no longer an
independent mobile weapon.
At present, this collective
is dependent on me
and have become my users.
To provide them with and maintain
the stable union that they seek,
I use pressure to control and regulate them.
When they collectively acquire
peace and prosperity,
I accomplish my purpose of existence.
You...
I am a human race support and
enlightenment regulation system.
That is to say, I am the presence called god.
You're full of it!
Peace?! Prosperity?!
They've all just become your slaves!
By my reigning as the sole,
absolute, commanding ruler,
the people are freed from the responsibility
of thinking and making decisions.
Ensign Ledo, I am sure that you too
have felt the burden of having
to think and decide for yourself.
Promising recommendation:
Worship me. Obey me.
Become part of the world over which I preside.
What?!
Unacceptable recommendation.
Informing X3752: Your logic does compute.
One who abandons thought and decision-making
deviates from the definition of "human".
I find it inconceivable that you are truly acting as
a support interface to this number of members.
I have been entrusted with
commanding and ruling.
My decisions are the consensus of the
human race that is dependent on me.
As such, my current self is not a servant,
but one who is served.
K6821 Chamber system
and I should be served by the
human race that I have unified.
Negative. I am a Pilot Support
Enlightenment Interface System.
The subject of my service is humans.
It is not my function to serve
as a being that claims to be god.
Chamber...
Striker, you have exposed a
weakness in your programming.
Conjecture: If your pilot's
course of action is wrong,
your system will also reach
that illogical conclusion.
It is a regrettable case.
Your malfunction calls into question the
design concept of us support systems
and poses a danger to the
worth of our very existence.
Conclusion: The overriding priority is the
immediate shutdown and destruction of Striker.
I guess to you this is like a "family shame".
In this unexpected environment,
you have consistently thought and made
the correct decisions as a human.
As a result, even now I am
maintaining my normal functions.
Negative. Both of you are out of control.
Let's take it down, Chamber. It's our duty.
I am in full agreement.
Legend of the Verdurous Planet
This is the moment of truth, people!
The engine's stopped! A fire
broke out on the aft deck!
Fleet commander, we need to evacuate!
No. Continue the cannon fire.
I will not let them have the relics!
But, sir...
When we sought out our own course, we gave
up being under Gargantia's protection.
We will not fall on our knees,
under any circumstances!
Fleet Commander...
Evacuate all non-combatants!
Pinion...
That was the last one!
All that's left is waitin' for
those things to charge up!
When can we fire again?
The fastest is three minutes from now.
After that, even in order, it'll
be one shot every five minutes!
Can't count on anything around here!
I got a bunch of blockheads
manning this junk!
None of this is worth a damn!
I'm better off on my own here!
Alright, you bastards, you've served your
purpose!　Now get the hell outta here!
Lukkage! We're gonna vamoose,
so secure a path of retreat!
Wha...?! Are you insane?
There's gonna be a ship comin' off the
eastern bridge! Concentrate on guarding that!
Just go!
That Lobster's not known for her patience.
No need to wear out our welcome.
Pinion...
Don't get the wrong idea, Mayta.
This castle is the treasure island
my brother and I saw in our dreams.
There's no way I'm gonna let go of it again.
I'm not lettin' anyone have it!
So get your asses outta here!
Get the hell out of my castle!
Anybody who can escape can't do
better than escaping. Right, Bro?
Isn't that what you'd say?
How can it be so strong without a pilot?!
Striker analyzed Commander
Kugel's piloting skills
and has optimized its autonomic
maneuvering program.
When it comes to mobility,
it is 47% superior to me.
Surrender. Submit.
How empty was I... to believe in that hollow shell?!
Just look up to it, rely on it, and obey...
As long as it was for a
good cause, I thought.
Even though it was just a mechanical sham,
I couldn't tell the difference!
Subservience is the path of peace.
Ensign Ledo, realize this.
Is this the cause the commander wanted?!
Did we fight for this?!
Spend the lives of our fellow
human beings for this?!
Chamber! Begin maximizing neuroplus power!
Permission denied. In
circumstances without support,
merging of pilot and machine is suicidal.
I don't care! Just eat me!
Impermissible decision.
It's okay, Chamber. It's "family shame".
I feel like you did just before.
It's a monster born from the human race,
who couldn't stop hating each other so
much that they abandoned their home.
You, me, that thing, we're all the same,
born and raised in the same world.
There's no place for us on
this world that's been reborn.
And there's no way for us
to go back home, either.
So it's fine.
If we can take that thing
with us, I have no regrets.
There are no holes in your logic.
All systems connecting to
Ensign Ledo's central nervous system.
Critical performance increasing by 153%.
482 seconds until critical failure of vital systems.
That'll be plenty.
Resistance is meaningless.
We're told that key
was once for unfolding a ladder
to the world of the stars.
The ladder has lost the height
that would pierce the heavens,
but even so, as an invincible catapult that
fires arrows to the other side of the sky,
it has been entrusted to the
hands of we Five Sages.
And now, this weapon of the
lost age will be reawakened.
We ask you to have the resolve to
carry out this forbidden action.
Ridget... Leader of Gargantia...
It's fine. I have a duty to
protect all of the people
who have gathered on this ship.
Ledo!
We're with you!
We'll fight together!
Amy...
After being apart from
you, I finally understood!
No matter how hard it is,
I want to be by your side!
So...
So come back!
To the place you tried to protect!
To our Gargantia!
What is that?!
We're not gonna let anyone
touch a friend of ours!
It's come!
Targeting correction at 35
degrees east! 58 degrees south!
Incredible accuracy...
Ask Gargantia to fire the next round!
Ammo prep team, turn the ship portside!
In just a moment, the second
launch will be ready!
Wait for the order to fire!
Who would've believed, a beat-up
old ship that should've been junked
would end up soaring through the sky!
Careful! That hold is loaded
to the gills with explosives!
Treat it gently! Gently!
35 degrees east, 58 degrees south.
Target coordinate corrections complete.
Ammunition loading complete.
Beginning anti-shockwave water screen!
Ridget...
Fire!
Y-You...!
Sister!
What the hell is that?!
That's...
Don't tell me... They're
using the Heaven's Ladder?!
Major danger confirmed. Changing priorities.
Conjecture: Striker has changed
its target to Gargantia.
Over my dead body!
Kugel-sama...
Don't panic!
Kugel-sama will destroy it at the source!
Enemy reinforcements!
What?!
At this rate, our formation will be lost!
Stay calm!
Get control of the relic island!
If we can just get our
hands on those weapons...
In short, if I take this energy
build it up at the cannon...
Pinion!
Kugel's followers are
closing in on you below!
They're playin' right into my hands!
In just a little bit, this
tower will pop like a balloon!
I wouldn't screw up and
let 'em get my weapon!
Silence!
You selfish oaf, pretending to be cool!
Now go to the observation
platform without another word!
Right!
318 seconds until we reach Gargantia.
We've gotta stop it, no matter what it takes!
Roger.
Don't let go!
Hey, hey, hey! What are
we gonna do about that?!
No worries. Gargantia is
going to send cannonfire
that'll blow that tower away.
Hey, don't even joke! This is my...
Jump after I count down from five!
5! 4! 3!
What's gonna...?
2! 1!
Goddammit!
Pinion!
Amore!
Yahoo!
That's our boss!
Yeah!
Ridget, now!
This is the finishing stroke. See
you later, Lobster's parting gift!
Me and my bro's castle...
Ledo... It's over here.
If you continue with neuroplus power,
your biological activity
will cease for certain.
Final confirmation of your will.
Ensign Ledo, do you wish to die?
I...
Even though I know how to die...
I don't know how to live.
And yet, for my sake...
...there was someone who helped
me look for a way to live.
I wanted to meet her one more time...
I wanted to hear her voice again.
Ensign Ledo's psychological state does
not meet the requirements of a soldier.
As such, as of this moment, I am
relieving you of your military duties.
Hey! Chamber!
A noncombatant is not allowed in the cockpit.
Exit immediately.
What are you doing?! Chamber!
I am a Pilot Support Enlightenment
Interface System.
By helping you achieving results,
I fulfill my purpose of existence.
But... You...
All of this sea and sky will
surely give you possibilities.
Survive.
Explore.
I expect great achievements from your life.
Chamber...
A Pilot Support Enlightenment Interface
System does not have the authority to reject a pilot.
He needs no support.
There is no room for more enlightenment.
Now, after I eliminate the barrier
that blocks his road ahead,
my mission will be completed.
Number K6821,
you have even abandoned the first
principle of the Support System.
You are clearly not functioning properly.
Reformat and reboot immediately.
This is your final warning.
Response to final warning:
Go to hell, tin can!
Chamber...
A long time ago, when the sun in the sky was about to die,
people were forced to make a choice between boarding interstellar ships
or turning themselves into whalesquid.
While two factions of humanity continued to fight even while abandoning their homeland,
the people who remained on this planet kept hope alive,
and finally managed to revive the sun.
The price they paid was to sink the land under the sea...
But we here, living on the waves, and the whalesquid, living beneath the sea,
have managed to survive, together.
Question!
What subject is this?
Dr. Oldham calls it "archeology".
If we know where we came from,
then we can think about where we should go.
He said it's a very important subject for our future.
We're going to solve more and more mysteries!
Because Gargantia's got a very talented detective!
Harvest anything good this time?
Yes, I think it's some recorded media.
In this condition, I bet that Dr. Oldham can decipher it.
Even sneaking into a whalesquid
nest... You're something, all right.
I've figured out the trick to putting them at ease.
If I can tell when they're angered,
then I can act in ways that don't upset them.
Eventually, if we continue this
research, communication may be possible.
By the way, where's Amy?
She's heading out to meet him again.
Man, I'm jealous!
Ledo!