D-Don't...
Don't...
If Tanigawa-san hadn't said
anything back then,
I'm sure I would have...
I was so close back in Okinawa...
Just a little bit more...
A little bit... more...
Oh, crap.
On shoot in Okinawa! All of us together
But...
I must not forget...
...the reason I came to this planet.
Another problem?
Rinon?
Rinon!
What are you doing?
Thump, thump.
Roar.
You giant monster!
The alien sent you here!
MIA missiles, fire!
Whoosh. Bang. Bang.
Grr!
Zap, zap, zap.
Ah!
Shyeeew. Boom.
Zoom, zoom, zoom.
Bam.
Hi-yah!
Hey, Tetsuro.
What was this movie about, again?
Don't ask me.
How many times have
you died in this movie?
I don't know that either.
I thought so.
Good work.
Want to take a little break?
Here you go, Ishigaki-kun.
Thanks.
Here's yours, Kaito-kun.
Huh?
Thank you.
Y-Yeah.
Oh, yeah. I was in the
middle of doing laundry.
A-Anyway, keep at it, you two.
Did something happen?
What do you mean?
Did something happen with Ichika-senpai?
No... Not yet.
Not yet?
Oh, yeah, I have to go get the camera.
I'm going upstairs for a sec—
Tell me the details.
Rinon?
Oh, yeah. Where were you yesterday?
You've been acting weird
since we went to Okinawa.
The terminal's been acting up, too.
Are you sure you're okay?
Really?
Umi
Maybe we should have
Salisbury steak tonight.
It's Kaito-kun's favorite.
I-I like it, too, you know?
Rinon?
Huh?
A k-kiss?!
Idiot, you're being too loud!
Senpai's here, you know?
You kissed her?
No... It was more like I was about to.
Like, I was almost there...
So you didn't, then.
I was so close.
I see.
I feel bad for Kanna.
She's headed straight for a dead end.
I can't do anything about that.
I don't even know if what you said is true.
It's true.
Kanna likes you.
Do you want to get
Tanigawa and I together?
If that's what you want,
then I'm sorry, I—
Hey there!
Hey.
Over here.
What are you doing over there?
Nothing important.
I brought the developed film with me.
Thank you.
They said it took longer because there
was some high-iso film in there, too.
K-Kitahara?
Your hair...
Oh, it was hot, so I just thought
I'd change things up and cut it.
Does it look weird?
No, it looks good.
Right, Tetsuro?
Y-Yeah.
R-Really?
I'm glad.
Kitahara-san?
It really is you, Kitahara-san!
You cut your hair!
It looks really good!
Those clothes are really nice, too.
Thank you.
Wait just a second.
I'll bring you some tea right away.
Don't worry about it.
Come on in.
We put together a test reel of the film,
with just the special effects.
I wanna take a look.
Thanks for having me.
Where is it?
Today...
Right here. We only did a little bit.
Today I made sure I'm good.
I-I see.
What's wrong?
Oh... Nothing at all...
No, nothing's wrong.
Here you guys go.
I have ice cream today.
Cool!
Did you make it yourself?
Yeah, it was my first time making
it, so I was worried, but...
It looks really, really good, though.
Yeah, really.
I didn't even know you
could make ice cream.
Yeah!
Manami-senpai, it's been a while.
You're still in high school?
I'm forever seventeen.
Right.
If you're here, that means you had
another fight with Ogura-senpai?
He beat the game I bought before I did.
And then he spoiled the end.
I can see you two are getting
along as well as ever.
How?
Anyway, what did you need
to talk to me about?
This.
Secret Notebook
Things have gotten quite complicated.
There's something I want you
to help me out with, Senpai.
Kaito, Ichika,
Tetsuro, Mio, Me
What are you planning now?
Do Not Enter
See you later.
Be careful heading back.
Mio's kind of changed.
I don't just mean her hair.
Yeah.
I ask her what's going on,
and she just says "stuff."
Tetsuro, do you know?
If you don't know, what
makes you think I would?
Yeah, I guess you've got a point.
Kaito-kun's kind of changed, too.
You think so?
I just know.
You know—
I'm really excited.
Huh?
The day after tomorrow's
the festival, right?
We should all go together,
like we did last year.
We'll invite Takatsuki-senpai
and Remon-senpai, too.
Y-Yeah.
I actually had Mio's
mom make me a yukata.
The sash is pink,
to match Mio's.
They're really cute.
I see.
Don't just touch a girl's hair like that!
Stop touching me!
I see.
Hey!
This is when I first saw her...
At that time, I was probably already...
What's this?
That's the night sky.
Must be from back then.
It's showing up pretty well.
What's...?
Kaito-kun, food's ready.
Okay!
All right.
Episode 8
Senpai's pinch.
They're late...
What are they doing?
Tetsuro!
Tada!
So that's the yukata you
were talking about.
Not bad. So you can look good with—
Owww!
If you say another word, I'll kill you.
Damn, I can't believe her.
I think it'd be better
if you were more honest.
I think I'm being honest enough.
If you're not, she won't understand.
We're here.
Sorry.
I wasn't really sure how to wear
one of these, so it took a while.
Pretty attractive, senpai.
You really do look wonderful.
R-Really?
It's my sister's again, though.
Do you have everything on right?
This again...
Yeah, I read a book.
Hey! What are you doing—
Everyone's here. Let's get going.
Yeah.
Let's get going.
I told you not to touch my head!
Yeah.
Th-This is a festival!
So, should we walk around once to—
What are you saying, Kaito-kun?!
There's one thing we
have to do at a festival!
Yeah.
You're right.
Huh?
This right here!
Now try a bite!
What is this?
Mwrunderful!
Mwrunderful?
Festivals are mwrunderful!
She's really excited.
Seriously.
Mwrunderful!
Senpai, is there something
else you want to see?
I couldn't pick. Everything's
so mwrunderful.
Good evening.
Remon-senpai?
You seem to be enjoying
this summer festival.
Yeah, Remon!
Festivals are really mwrunderful!
No.
Not yet.
You can't say you've enjoyed
everything to the fullest yet.
Are we missing something?
What are you talking about?
You see...
We need a test of courage.
What's a test of courage?
What's the best way to put it...
It's a simple game.
You go up those stairs
and leave something...
...in the temple at the top and come back.
I see.
U-Uh...
I don't really like scary stuff.
It's okay.
We'll make up pairs through a lottery.
Kaito-kun!
Let's do this!
I'm glad you're on board.
Now then...
G-God, thank you very much.
Now I just need to time
everything perfectly...
S-Sorry.
A bug landed on me, and...
Ah, sorry!
This is going differently
than I thought, but...
Let's go.
This might work!
Yeah!
There's nothing there.
B-But I think I saw something!
But...
Monsters, ghosts,
souls of humans who have passed...
They wander the earth.
There are folktales and eye-witness
accounts claiming their existence,
but it's yet to be proven scientifically.
So they're basically imaginary beings
that humans have created...
...due to their fears
and superstitions, right?
Re...mon?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry I said they were
created by superstition!
Wonderful reaction there, Ichika.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
Now, on to the next one.
Shortcut
Okay, we're done.
See? Nothing happened.
Y-Yeah.
Anyway, let's head back.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry you had to be with me.
You wanted to—
Hey, your hair...
Wh-What?
No, I thought...
That was Tetsuro's team, right?
Are you okay?
S-Sorry. Just for a little while, okay?
Yeah...
I-I wonder if everyone's okay?
Wh-What was that scream just now?
Where did Remon go?
S-Sorry...
Hey, are you okay?
Sorry, I didn't think
you'd get so scared...
That's rude!
It's me. Me.
N-Nee-chan?
Manami-san?
What were you thinking?!
I thought I'd help out.
Stop messing around!
Don't get so upset.
Sorry about that, Mio-chan.
No, it's okay...
Sorry won't cut it!
I apologized, okay?!
Nice, Manami-senpai.
Uh, Tanigawa...
Could you, uh...?
Kai-kun.
I...
Tanigawa...
Remon, where are you?
I...
I, uh...
Someone...
Kaito-kun...
That was...
This is...
Tanigawa, don't move from there!
Huh?
W-Wait!
Kaito-kun...
Kanna!
That was Takatsuki-senpai
who just screamed, right?
Where's Kirishima-kun?
Kanna?
Senpai!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Rinon?!
Why are you...?
Why are you saying sorry?
The distress signal started broadcasting?
You can't turn it off?!
Why didn't you tell me
something so important?!
So when is help coming?
What was that?
A federation unmanned rescue pod...
Wait.
There's been a mistake.
The distress signal was a mistake.
I still have things to do on this planet!
Rinon, jump me.
A linkage anti-field?
This can't be...
Senpai!
Wai—
Kaito-kun?
Wh-What is that?
Rinon, can you call Rinna?
Senpai!
What are you doing?!
Hurry up!
Kaito-kun, keep running away.
Why?
Just do it! Run!
I can't... do that!
Listen to me!
I—
Please!
I can't...
Senpai!
Kaito-kun!
I can't run away...
...and leave someone I love behind!
Run while you can!
Rinna!
What's going on?!
Rinon?
Senpai!
Senpai!!
What's going on?!
Huh...
I know this...
Kaito...kun?
Senpai?
What's going on?!
What's going on...?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
Episode 9
Senpai
So, Senpai's an alien!
Now that I look closely,
I see a zipper on her back!
No way...
What's inside?