Vitya!
Don't go! Stay here!
Yakov, you were the best coach I ever had.
You always will be.
If you walk away now,
you can never come back!
Dasvidaniya.
I'm sorry I can't do as you say this time.
You don't get to say that when you've
never done as I said in the first place!
You should come visit Japan, Yakov.
Second Skate
Two Yuris?!
Drama at Yu-topia
Two Yuris?! Drama at Yu-topia!
Yuri! Why aren't you answering your cell?!
What's wrong?
Everything's wrong!
There's a rumor that Victor's
going to be Yuri's coach!
Oh, Vicchan's here already.
What?
Vicchan's sound asleep.
Hello! I'm Katsuki Yuri!
Top Certified Athletes
I'm in a bit of a slump right now,
but I'm a top figure skater certified by the JSF!
Back home for the first time in five years,
I was thinking of how to keep my career going...
when my idol, Victor, suddenly appeared!
I'm still in denial that this
is actually happening!
By the way, Victor Nikiforov is a
living legend in figure skating.
I never dreamed he'd be interested in me, but...
Starting today, I'm your coach.
I'll make you win the Grand Prix Final.
What is he saying, standing there buck naked?
Yuri!
Why is Victor sleeping in one of the inn's robes?!
He soaked in the hot spring and
had dinner, then fell asleep...
It's big news in Russia.
He's taking next season off and
is considering his next move.
They're also saying that when he saw
the video of you skating his routine,
he was struck with inspiration, and that's
when he decided to be your coach.
Huh?
Victor came here because he chose you, Yuri.
You brought him here!
That's incredible!
Huh?
Victor went to Japan to become
Yuri Katsuki's coach?
Why that fatso?
Did he forget what he promised me?
Yakov! Where are you?
Explain this to me, damn it!
Victor wants to take time off until
he finds his motivation again.
Personally, I doubt he'll be able to
return if he takes a break now.
He's going to coach Katsuki Yuri in Japan—
That man only thinks of himself!
He'll never be anyone's coach!
Hasetsu Hot Springs
Yu-topia Katsuki
Oh, he's awake.
I'm starving.
Hungry...
Huh?
He still wants to eat?
Um, what would you like to eat?
Hmm...
As your coach, I'd like to know
what your favorite food is, Yuri.
What?
Wow! Amazing!
Our specialty, the pork cutlet bowl, extra-large!
Vkusno!
Delicious! Too good for words!
Is this what God eats?!
I'm glad you like it.
Yuri gains weight easily,
so he was only allowed to eat it
when he won a competition. Right?
Oh? So have you eaten this
pork cutlet bowl recently?
Yes, yes.
I eat it often.
Why?
You haven't won anything.
With that pig's body of yours,
lessons would be meaningless.
You need to get back to your weight at
last year's Grand Prix Final, at the least...
or I can never coach you.
Until then, no more pork cutlet bowls.
Okay, little piggy?
Huh?
I feel like I should be offended...
Hey, this luggage is in the way.
Can you take it to the room
where I'll be staying?
Staying?
Wow! What a classic, tiny room.
Is there a sofa?
No...
I'm sorry it's so small. We only had
an unused banquet room available.
You look anxious.
You can pay the coaching fee
after you achieve success!
I'll bill you later.
Th-Thank you.
Yuri, tell me everything about you.
What kind of rink do you skate at?
What's in this city?
Is there a girl you like?
Before we start practicing,
let's build some trust in our relationship.
What? Why are you running away?
Uh, no reason...
I'm still scared to be close to him.
Yuri, let's sleep together.
As your coach, there's so much
I need to learn about you.
No!
Yuri!
Yuri?
We've barely ever spoken
because I always put him
on such a high pedestal,
and now he's right here...
I get it now.
My heart's pounding
because of how happy I am.
Hello!
Hi!
I'm Victor Nikiforov.
I'll be Yuri's coach from now on.
Huh? What? What?!
Victor's really going to be Yuri's coach?!
Wow!
A quadruple flip!
Mom, I've got this!
I'll take the video!
Can I upload this?
It's not for the public, you skating otaku trio!
Seriously?
Yeah.
He says he'd like to use this rink
as our home base for now.
Is that okay?
Okay, sure!
I'll talk to the higher-ups.
Victor teaching you himself...
It's like a dream come true!
Yeah...
By the time I was twelve,
Victor, four years my senior,
was already number one in the world.
Junior World Championships, Gold
Victor Nikiforov
Sofia, Bulgaria
I've imitated him for years,
trying to catch up to him.
How could seeing the video of me
skating his routine inspire him?
How did I inspire you, Victor?
The little piggy can't enter the rink
until he drops some body fat.
Are you really serious about making me win?
Okukawa Minako Ballet
Maybe he just wanted
an excuse to take a break.
Please don't say that.
That's what I suspect, too, but...
You decided to keep skating, didn't you?
You need to take advantage of Victor!
Okay, let's get you slimmed down!
O-Okay.
Minako-sensei is a ballet instructor.
She used to travel the world as a dancer.
When I was younger,
I spent more time in her
ballet class than at home.
I even started skating because
Minako-sensei urged me to.
She's always cheered me on,
but she likes to meddle, too.
Do you have feelings for Minako?
What?! No way!
Do you have a girlfriend?
No.
Any ex-girlfriends?
N-No comment.
Let's talk about me!
My first girlfriend was—
Stop!
Yuri, what's that castle over there?
Oh, that's Hasetsu Castle.
Inside is ninja house.
Really? Ninjas?!
Hasetsu Castle!
Let me see! Let me see!
Who's that good-looking foreigner?
Hashtag "#ninja"!
Yes!
What the... (lol) Victor's photo?!
So it's true that he's going
to be Katsuki Yuri's coach...
"Hasetsu Castle"?
Does he want to become a ninja or something?
I finally found you.
Just you wait, Victor.
Oh?
Is it true that Victor is here?!
Comment, please!
Can we share a bath with him?!
Mari
It's been a long time since
we had so many customers!
Congratulations on Advancing to the
Grand Prix, Skater Katsuki Yuri
Victor's here, right?
Excuse me! We'd like to film a special feature!
I want to learn how to skate, too!
Wh-What the hell?
Me, too!
Oh...
Victor!
Oh my God! He's super hot!
C-Can I take a photo with you?
He's really good-looking.
Please let us interview you!
Apparently Victor's at Ice Castle.
Oh, wow!
One Week Later
Hasetsu City
Hasetsu Float Statue
Photos are best taken from right here!
Wow. Creepy.
Crap, no!
If I post this, Yakov will know I'm here!
Victor's been uploading tons of
pictures with this city tagged...
Hey! Where's Victor?!
Victor!
Tiger Sweatshirt
1,300 Yen
Wha—
My God...
That's awesome fashion!
Yuri!
Why are you in Japan, too?!
Oops, you found out?
You know how important this time
before your senior debut is, right?!
I told you!
I'm not coming back to Russia until
Victor makes good on his promise!
That geezer's such a nag!
I have my own plan, okay?
I'm supposed to do a triple Salchow next.
He'd better not...
I can do it!
A quadruple Salchow?
See that, Yakov?
You idiot!
I told you repeatedly that quads are off-limits
because your body's still developing!
If you can't follow orders, then quit!
Yakov!
You should praise him more.
Don't butt in! It's none of your business!
I used to get scolded for doing that, too.
You can win, even without quads.
I'd bet money on it.
You can win the Junior World Championship.
Okay, if I win without quad jumps,
then choreograph a program just for me!
Sure.
When you win the Junior World
Championship, come see me.
I'll give you the best senior debut ever.
Where am I?
Victor!
Oh? Are you a fan of Victor's?
There's a skating rink below
the castle. Try there.
Come on, let us watch.
It's reserved, and it's a
private practice session!
Go home!
Hey! You can't go in there!
Huh?
Yuri Plisetsky!
He's the junior world champion...
Victor's inside, isn't he?
Come in, come in.
Finally here... I'm exhausted...
Yuri...
Hey, get this!
My weight's back to what it was
before the Grand Prix Final!
Now I'll finally get Victor's
permission to skate.
Ow!
It's all your fault.
Apologize.
Why is he here?
U-Uh, sorry, sorry.
And why's he furious at me?!
Hey, pig!
Ow! That hurts! Stop!
The Japanese Yuri and the
Russian Yuri are both here.
Fatso!
Pig!
This means...
We can go ahead with that, right?
Right!
He promised me first that he'd
choreograph a program for me.
What about you?
Huh? We haven't gotten to talking
about programs or anything.
What?!
You make him take a whole
year off, and to do what?
Isn't getting him as a coach enough?
As if a guy who'd sob in a toilet
stall at the Grand Prix Final
can change at all just by
getting Victor as a coach!
He's...
Just retire already.
He's totally underestimating me.
Stop smirking, fatso!
I don't really get the whole picture,
so you should ask him yourself.
Victor came all the way to
Hasetsu because he wanted to.
Just to become my coach.
Huh?
Those moves...
They're for the short program Victor
was practicing for next season.
What?
Victor was already putting together
routines for next season.
But he was really torn.
Surprising the audience has
always been his top priority.
He had the whole world in his hands.
But now, no matter what he does,
no one's surprised anymore.
He knows that better than anyone.
If you don't have any inspiration left,
you're as good as dead.
If he's going to take next season off,
I wonder if he'll let me use his program.
I know I can surprise people more.
I need Victor's help if I'm
going to make my senior debut
and win the Grand Prix Final.
Huh? Win?
You look like you're doing great, Victor!
Yuri, you're here?
I'm surprised Yakov let you come.
What do you want?
Judging from that look,
I'm guessing I forgot some promise I made.
Welcome, Victor!
Welcome Back, Katsuki Yuri
Sorry, sorry.
I totally forgot.
But you knew I was the forgetful type, right?
Yeah, I'm painfully aware of that.
But a promise is a promise!
You'll choreograph my new program, Victor!
Let's go back to Russia!
Okay, I've decided!
Tomorrow, I'll choreograph
a program for both of you
to the same music I'm
using in my short program.
Huh?! The same music as him?!
What?! With the same choreography?!
No, this piece has several
different arrangements.
I was trying to decide which one to use.
I'll think of a different program
for each of you, of course.
I'll reveal the programs in one week!
You'll compete to see who can
surprise the audience more!
Whoa! Let's take a step back here.
I don't want to be punished for losing...
Victor will do whatever the winner says!
If those are the terms, I'm in!
Great! I love that kind of thing!
Wait just a minute!
Will you let us organize the event?
A face-off between
Yuri of Russia and Yuri of Japan!
Let's throw...
...a huge party!
Hasetsu Exhibition
"Hot Springs on Ice"
Presented by Victor Nikiforov
One week from now, the "Hot Springs
on Ice" show will premiere
News Department
at Ice Castle Hasetsu.
Please come to the event.
Talk about a hovel.
Where's my room?
You're staying here?!
If you get Victor to yourself all
the time, it won't be a fair match!
I'll stay here, too! All right?
It's not like you care what I think.
The hot spring is great.
I can't take a bath with other people!
I'm going to sleep!
Growl
Give me food!
And a bath!
This is great!
The pork cutlet bowl is good, isn't it?
You have another visitor, Yuri?
Huh?
Huh?!
No way!
Ba-Dump
He looks just like my
idol, The Blond Takao!
Takao?
His name is also Yuri.
What? That's confusing.
Okay, you're Yurio!
Yurio
What?!
Where will Yurio stay?
Upstairs in—
The storage room?!
Oh, no! I need to clean it up!
Yuri, come help.
Good for you, Yurio.
Shut up!
That's not my name!
I see...
Of course.
That Yuri has more potential than I do.
Yuri, where are you going?
He's pretty confident, saying he'll win the
Grand Prix Final on his first run as a senior.
Above all, he's comfortable in front of Victor.
Compared to me, he's much more...
Huh? Where's Yuri?
He left a while ago.
At a time like this, he'd be at
Minako-san's place or Ice Castle.
He's always been that way.
Huh? Yuri?
Kachu
Snack Bar
He's not here.
By "my place," she meant my ballet studio.
Whenever Yuri gets anxious,
he always wants to practice.
I usually go along with him.
Ice Castle lets him skate anytime
if it's not booked already.
Yuri was able to grow because he had a place
where he could practice alone
whenever he got anxious.
He's no genius,
but he was gifted with more free time
than anyone else to practice.
He's always come here to practice by himself.
It always made me think
he really loved skating.
He didn't even play with his friends.
Well, he was never very good at making them.
Skating aside, he's not good
at putting himself out there.
I don't want this to be the end for him.
Me, neither.
He actually hates losing.
I hope Victor will bring out a side of
Yuri-kun that we've never seen before.
So, a magic spell to change
the little piggy into a prince...
Huh?
Nothing.
Thanks. I know a lot more about Yuri now.
Good morning.
Morning.
You say hi too, Yurio.
I'm not Yurio!
Private Practice Session
Reserved All Day
Apologies for the Inconvenience
"Hot Springs on Ice" Is a Go!
Katsuki Yuri & Yuri Plisetsky
Location: Ice Castle Hasetsu
Victor will finally start teaching me today.
Whether this is my last
season or not rides on this.
I'll never win if I wimp out here!
I can't lose this "Hot Springs on Ice" match!
And then I'll aim for the Grand Prix Final!
First, let's have you two listen to the music.
This piece comes in two arrangements,
each with a different theme.
"On Love: Eros and Agape."
Have you ever thought about love?
Nope.
All right.
Then what do you feel when
you listen to this music?
It's very clear and innocent,
like someone who doesn't
know what love is yet.
I don't like this piece.
This innocence crap makes me wanna barf.
Okay.
It's like a completely different song.
Victor!
I want to skate to this one!
The first piece is "On Love: Agape."
The theme is unconditional love.
And this piece is "On Love: Eros."
The theme is sexual love.
I'll have you two skate
to these opposing themes.
This is how I'm assigning them.
Yuri, you'll skate to "Eros"!
Yurio, you'll skate to "Agape"!
What?!
Switch them! That piece isn't me at all!
You have to do the opposite
of what people expect.
How else will you surprise them?
That's my motto.
Actually, you're both far more ordinary
and mediocre than you think.
You need to be more self-aware.
I'm surprised you think you can
choose your own image.
From the audience's perspective,
you're just a piglet and a kitten.
Hasetsu Exhibition
Hot Springs on Ice
Victor Nikiforov Presents
If you aren't up to my standards by next week,
I won't choreograph either of your programs.
Both of you are my fans,
so I'm sure you'll manage.
Fine.
I'll skate to "Agape."
My senior division debut depends on it!
You'd better give me a
program that'll let me win!
It's up to you whether you win or not.
If I skated the program, I'd win for sure.
If I win, Victor, you're coming back to Russia.
And you'll be my coach!
That's what I want!
Sure.
Yuri, what about you?
What would you like to do if you win?
I want to eat pork cutlet
bowls with you, Victor.
I want to keep on winning,
and keep on eating pork cutlet bowls!
So I'll skate to "Eros"!
I'll give it all the eros I've got!
Great!
Hasetsu Exhibition:
"Hot Springs On Ice" in 7 Days
That's exactly what I like!
To Be Continued!!!
I wonder, which of you will
be able to satisfy me?
I'll satisfy you for sure!
Fine! Bring on the fight!
Don't underestimate Russia!
Next time, Third Skate:
The Third Skate
I Am Eros, and Eros Is Me?!
Face-Off! Hot Springs on Ice
Hot Springs on Ice.