In life, you need vacations
where you can be yourself,
away from your hectic everyday life.
When I get away from skating,
two "L words" come to mind:
life and love.
I've been neglecting both
for over twenty years.
Tenth Skate
Gotta Supercharge It!!
Pre-Grand Prix Final Special!
Even Barcelona's cold in December.
I thought, other than me, only a Russian
would be stupid enough to get
in the pool this time of year.
I guess I was right.
Chris!
Hi, Coach Victor!
And here I was hoping to go skinny dipping.
Don't let me stop you.
I'll even take photos for you.
My name is Victor Nikiforov.
I was kidding about being on vacation.
I just arrived in Barcelona, Spain, for
the Grand Prix Figure Skating Final.
He's Christophe Giacometti from Switzerland.
Since you left, I'm one of the oldest...
And I'm only 25.
Nowadays, Chris is sexy
both on and off the ice,
but when I first met him at the
European Championships,
he was like a little boy running
through the Swiss meadows.
I've shared the podium with Chris
at many a Grand Prix Final,
European Championship,
and World Championship.
I can't imagine a skating season without him,
and he has said that
he wouldn't be motivated in a
season without me, either.
Despite all that, he was savvy enough
to make it to the Grand Prix Final.
Yuri!
At least check yourself in.
You do it, Yakov.
I'm tired.
Yuratchka!
Autograph, please!
Can I get a photo with you?
You ug—
Yuri Plisetsky, don't use unattractive words.
From Russia, we have Yuri Plisetsky.
At just 15, he's qualified for the GP Final
first thing in his senior debut.
He's a tomboy cat under my former coach, Yakov.
After visiting Japan,
Yurio
he's been called by his nickname, "Yurio."
It's well-known that he has rabid
fans called "Yuri's Angels,"
Meow
who appear at every competition.
Wow, he's so popular.
Yuri's Angels are famous.
Huh...
But JJ Girls are better about following the rules,
and we're cuter.
Don't diss my fans and call
them ugly, you ugly-ass bitch!
So scary.
Help, JJ.
Oh, he's just jealous because
my fiancée is so beautiful.
I think he's the one named
Jean-Jacques Leroy, from Canada.
He's a strong gold medal candidate,
but he has a certain unapproachable
quality the other competitors don't.
Any guy who wears sunglasses
on his head is scum.
Find someone better, ugly-ass bitch!
Hey, don't be so uppity.
Scary!
Otabek!
Where are you going?
Out to eat.
Otabek Altin from Kazakhstan, age 18.
He rushed into the GP Final at full speed.
Ever since he shared the podium with me
at Worlds last season, I've sensed
a certain presence about him.
But people don't know much
about his personal life.
Eating alone?
You're still an odd one, huh?
Want to join us for dinner?
Thanks, but I'll pass.
It appears he's not interested in
socializing with other skaters.
Huh?
What's with you, asshole?
Yuri's not answering.
Ugh, I can't wait any longer!
I'm going to Sagrada Família!
Just go.
Okay!
Phichit Chulanont from Thailand.
He won the Cup of China,
becoming the first Southeast Asian figure
skater to qualify for the Grand Prix Final,
but I feel he's also peerless when
it comes to skillful selfies.
He was Yuri's rink mate in Detroit,
and Yuri says he's the only foreign
skater he considers a friend.
And among the six qualifiers for the Final,
Top 6 Men's Singles Figure Skaters
the last one, who made it by a hair's width,
is this jet-lagged sleeping beauty,
Katsuki Yuri from Japan.
I've come here with him as his coach.
After the Rostelecom Cup,
Yuri spent his few remaining days
Congratulations on Qualifying for the GPF 2 Years in a Row!
Thank You, Katsuki Yuri and Coach Victor Nikiforov!
until the Final maximizing his practice time.
When I think about it,
it's already been eight months
since I first came to Hasetsu.
I can't remember when I last spent
this much time with Maccachin.
Every day, I've been able to bathe
in a bath bigger than any tub,
and I can eat all the delicious
pork cutlet bowls I want.
This is heaven on Earth.
Yuri's life and love have taught me
about a brand new world that
I'd never known before.
Huh?
Where's Victor?
Oh, he's at the pool with Chris.
Oh! Phichit-kun's...
JJ...
Yurio...
Wow.
"Now that I know what love
is and am stronger for it,
I'll prove it to myself with a Grand
Prix Final gold medal," huh?
Help me, Victor.
Yuri!
I'm freezing!
Please draw a hot bath!
Yuri, can you make coffee, too?
You were still asleep?
Whoa!
Y-You're freezing!
Quit clinging to me! Both of you!
The aggressive jump composition
Yuri's planned in order to win
includes a quadruple flip, which he's yet
to land, as his final free skate jump.
If he sticks with his old jumps,
even if he skates a flawless program,
JJ has a higher base score.
Okay.
I'm done with practice!
Off I go!
Yuri, let's go over it one last time.
Yuri, what do you want to do now?
I recommend a good night's rest to
prepare for tomorrow's short program.
Don't be such a model coach now.
This is my first time in Barcelona,
so take me sightseeing.
Leave it to me!
Yeah!
Salud!
Perfecto!
Yeah!
I haven't shopped in ages. This is fun!
Hey, let me take a breather.
I would've liked to shop when
the Euro was weaker, though.
You don't want anything, Yuri?
Oh... Nah.
Every competitor has a different
way of winding down.
It's unusual for Yuri to suggest sightseeing.
It might mean he's just that
nervous this time around.
Okay, then...
Yuri!
I'll buy you a suit for your birthday!
I think you should burn the suit and tie
you wore at that press conference.
Huh?
Wait, you don't have to!
I kind of like that suit!
Hey, Victor!
Where's Yuratchka?
We're about to have a fan meeting.
I can smell Yuratchka!
It's coming from over here!
Oh, this hair is Yuratchka's!
Crap...
How do I get myself out of this?
Yuri, get on.
Huh? You're...
There's Yuratchka!
Huh? No way!
It's Otabek Altin from Kazakhstan!
Huh? What?
Are you coming or not?
I'm sure athletes aren't the
only ones who are sensitive
to tailwinds that can take
one to worlds unknown.
News that the hero of Kazakhstan
kidnapped the fairy of Russia
The fairy of Russia, Yuri Plisetsky, rides off on
a motorbike with Otabek, the hero of Kazakhstan
spread across the world like wildfire.
However, the hero didn't lure
the fairy out on a mere whim.
Yurio thought they had nothing in common,
but five years prior, they had
actually trained together
at Yakov's summer camp.
Really?
I don't remember that!
At the time, I was in my first
year in the junior division.
But I couldn't keep up with
the Russian junior skaters,
so I was put in the novice class.
That's where I met you.
Yuri Plisetsky had the
unforgettable eyes of a soldier.
A soldier?
Me?
I had just moved my home rink
from Moscow to St. Petersburg.
I was desperate.
I'd decided that I wouldn't complain
until I was good enough.
After that camp,
I moved around to train, from Russia
to the US and then to Canada.
I only managed to return to my
home rink in Almaty last year.
Now, more than ever, I want to win
the championship for Kazakhstan.
Otabek, why did you talk to me?
I'm a rival, aren't I?
I've always thought we were alike.
That's all.
Are you going to become friends
with me or not?
Yurio had never been asked
to become friends before!
Now, back to the main story
where I'm shopping with Yuri.
Here, the mood had turned sour!
It's not here, either.
Yuri, calm down and remember.
It's the bag of nuts we just bought.
It's a brown bag with green print.
Sorry.
I have no idea where I dropped it.
I'll go back to the shop and get another bag!
It's okay, Yuri.
The nuts shop would be closed by now.
Let's head back. You're tired, right?
You don't have to say it like that!
Well, I'm tired.
We ended up walking in silence, looking
around at the nearby Christmas market.
Victor, your birthday is Christmas Day, right?
Yeah.
What would you like for your gift?
In Russia, we don't celebrate
before the actual birthday.
We don't really celebrate Christmas, either.
I see.
Do you want some hot wine, too?
Ah, I try not to drink before a competition.
Oh, right.
When Yuri's searching for an answer,
his eyes sparkle, even if he doesn't say anything.
He's looking for something
right now, like a dowsing rod.
I'll just watch over him
without making conversation.
Victor!
Let's go in this store!
Can you show me these two in front?
I've always wanted a lucky charm.
I-It's a lucky charm so that I
can do my best in the Final!
It's also a thank you gift to
Victor for all of his help.
This one, please. I'll pay in installments.
Sometimes, when backed into a corner,
athletes can act completely unexpectedly.
Thank you for everything up to now.
I... I couldn't think of something better.
But, um...
I'll try my best from tomorrow on, so...
Tell me something for good luck.
Sure.
I'll say something you won't
even have to think about.
Tomorrow, show me the skating that
you can honestly say you liked best.
Okay!
That's the only shortcut to
a gold medal that I know.
I'm hungry.
Let's go grab a bite.
I have absolute faith in what you decide, Yuri.
AGHHHHH
What's wrong, Mari-chan?
Yurio looks like he's enjoying
having tea with someone!
Whoa, really?
It's Otabek from Kazakhstan!
Oh, Minako-sensei, Mari-neechan.
You're already here.
Crap, crap, crap.
Yuri, we need a huge favor!
You're way too happy about this.
I could just die right now!
Why did we all have to get together?
How much should I pay you?
Hello, ladies.
Still, it's kind of weird for us
all to be here like this
Yurio, have some shrimp!
Picture, picture!
Oh, sure.
before the Final starts.
At last year's Final,
I was always by myself, even at the banquet.
I couldn't even talk to Victor.
Yuri, you don't remember?
What?
Yuri, you got drunk on champagne
and started dancing.
Everyone saw it.
Huh?!
That was disgusting as hell.
I was dragged into a dance-off
and got humiliated, too!
A dance-off?
With Yurio?
I did mine with a pole dance, half-naked.
I start going off the rails
when I drink, just like my
Kyushu born-and-bred dad,
so I was trying to lay off, but...
The banquet refers to the party
held after the competition.
Learning proper social skills and etiquette
is also important for skaters.
What's wrong, Yuri?
Last year, Yuri suffered a
crushing defeat in the Final.
You look so glum.
Have you had anything to drink?
He looked like his coach had
dragged him to the banquet.
To eat?
There's pizza...
At least, at first.
Since he couldn't mingle
well with other skaters,
he kept drinking champagne, and...
I still have videos of what happened.
I do, too.
Wait, what?
Yuri, that's so dirty.
I want to see!
Don't look!
W-Wait... Cut it out already!
Isn't this amazing?
What's with the rings, you two?
Huh? Rings?
I don't remember you wearing that.
U-Um, this is...
They're a pair!
Congrats on your marriage!
Wait, no...
Um...
Everyone!
My good friend here got married!
N-No, this is, um...
It's to thank him for all his help...
And lots of other things... Yes, other things!
Yeah, don't get the wrong idea.
This is an engagement ring.
We'll get married once he wins a gold medal.
What?
Right, Yuri?
V-Victor!
A gold...
...medal...
...huh?
Uh, well, um...
Wait a second!
I'll be the one who wins gold
and gets married, of course!
That's right, it'll definitely be JJ.
Sorry we can't congratulate you
on that future marriage.
Well, tomorrow's an early start.
Better call it a night.
Huh, what?
Hey, wait a second.
I was just joking!
Kick Kick
Victor Nikiforov is dead!
Why do you look so happy to be
looking after that damn pig?
Did you want to compete against me?
Don't be so full of yourself.
Not all skaters look up to you.
Just go away already, geezer.
The ring you got from that pig is garbage.
I'll win just to prove how
incompetent his owner is.
Let me go!
If I'd stayed in Russia as a competitor,
Yurio wouldn't be this motivated to fight.
And neither would I...
This place reminds me of Hasetsu's ocean.
I thought that, too.
Yuri, you may not realize this,
but many others besides me
got their "L words" from you.
Wow!
It feels like it's really happening.
Mari-chan, take my picture!
Sala!
Why are you here, Mickey?
I'm the one who made it to the Final!
I'm standing guard to make sure
the hyenas don't touch you!
Let's go to a club after this!
Not her again.
Guang-hong, can you watch it on your end?
Nope, the live stream isn't working for me.
Grand Prix Final in Barcelona
Katsuki Yuri Cheering Party!
I'll be the head cheerleader
at tonight's public viewing!
The Grand Prix Final is here
in Barcelona, Spain!
Tonight, it's the Men's Singles Short Program.
Victor...
After this season ends,
my family runs a hot spring
resort, so please come.
If I win this dance-off...
You'll become my coach, right?
Be my coach, Victor!
To Be Continued!!!
Hola! I'm the figure skater Oda Nobunari!
Oda-kun!
Nobu-kun, over here!
Vic-chan! Yuri-kun!
Huh? What's with those rings?
Next time, Eleventh Skate:
Gotta Super-Supercharge It!!
Eleventh Skate
Grand Prix Final Short Program
Grand Prix Final Short Program.
Oda-kun! Let me take a picture!
Okay!