Hina-chan!
Welcome home, Hina-chan! Perfect timing!
I wanted to ask you a little favor.
You see, the wind yesterday knocked down
our scarecrow and broke it.
And, you know, animals have
always liked you, right?
I know it sounds funny to ask you
to take a scarecrow's place,
but if you'd stick around near the field
and attract the animals to you,
it'd be a great help.
It's this way...
Oh, my!
I guess I startled you when I just
showed up and started talking to you.
There you go.
All you have to do is stay right here.
Thank you so much.
Take a scarecrow's place?
Oh, Hina-chan's taking the scarecrow's place?
Yep.
All the animals go straight
to her. It's a big help!
She's much more reliable
than any real scarecrow.
She sure is.
Hina-chan, thank you for
being our scarecrow today.
Thanks a bunch.
You're such a sweet girl.
I wish we had a scarecrow
as cute as you in our fields.
It's not often we see
such a quiet girl, is it?
She never says a word. Just like a doll!
She really is just like a scarecrow.
She has the spirit of a pro!
This is just the way I've always been...
Standing in the field
every day is exhausting.
There's nothing to do out here...
But I can't just tell them
I'm quitting now...
Thanks for always helping out.
Thanks to you, the animals
don't come close anymore,
so we can concentrate on working
in the fields without worrying.
Take these to eat with your family.
Th-Th-Than...
Than?
Than...
Mom, I'm home.
Oh, Hinako. Welcome back.
You were out late again, huh?
Here, use these for dinner tonight.
Oh, thank you...
Lately, Hinako's been bringing
vegetables from somewhere.
And she's been getting home late.
Sh-She couldn't be stealing
from the fields, could she?!
No, no! That can't be it!
I trust my little girl!
I'm sleepy...
It's so warm out today.
It's making me sleepy.
Oh, it's Hina-chan.
Oh!
She's here to be our scarecrow again today?
What a big help she is!
Oh, right. I'll get her vegetables for today.
She'll catch a cold
if she stays out here like this.
Wow! There are so many!
H-Huh? What is this?
Am I a jizo statue now?
When did this happen?
Oh!
Hey, Hina-chan!
Thanks for being our scarecrow again today.
You were a big help.
U-Um... These... I... I should
also... tha... than...
Hurry on home before it gets dark.
Come by again, okay?
Wow!
This is great, Hinako!
Thanks for always bringing these!
I know. I still haven't been able
to thank them for the vegetables.
What should I do?
Yeah, you're right. All I can do is practice.
I'll try my best.
Hina Mama
My daughter is currently wearing
a costume and talking to a bird...
Tanuki-san, you can be the old man, okay?
He and his wife are always very kind to me,
so I want to be able to thank them properly.
Help me out, okay?
Here I go. Let's see...
"Hey, Hina-chan!
Working hard again today, eh?"
"Hello, sir. Thank you
for all you've done for me."
"Here are your vegetables for today."
"Eat them all up."
"Thank you very much, sir.
I always enjoy your vegetables."
"Is that right?"
"Yes. My mother always
looks forward to them, too.
Recently, when she sees the
vegetables I bring home,
she starts planning our meals
for the week with them."
"Oh?"
"The vegetables from your fields
are so delicious!"
There! I practiced!
I said everything perfectly!
Hina-chan.
Y-Yes?!
You did great work again today. Thank you.
Here, take this.
U-Uh...
See you again tomorrow, okay?
The vegetables...
The vegetables... are delicious.
Th-Thank you for always giving them to me.
I should be thanking you.
I'll be counting on you again, I'm sure.
Y-Yesh! I'll try my besht!
Better try your best to get better
at speaking, too, eh?
I'm...
That's right. I'm in Tokyo now.
I have to try my hardest here.
I have to try hard so I can stand on a stage
and learn to talk skillfully to people.
Oh, yeah...
It Begins Here
The high school's
theater club is on hiatus...
Morning, Hina-chan!
Oh, good morning.
Morning.
Oh, Miss Landlady. Good morning.
Good morning.
Oh, Kuu-chan's here, too.
I'll get breakfast ready right away.
Go on. Eat up.
Let's eat!
What do you think, Hina-chan?
It's really delicious!
By the way, are you really going to
start a theater troupe, Hina-chan?
Huh?
Um, Miss Landlady...
Yes?
The theater club is on hiatus because
the advisor left on a theater trip, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Why did the advisor leave, though?
Because...
Sensei, why?!
As I am now, I'm not fit to be your advisor.
I'll come back when I am!
She said she suddenly felt that
her skills had reached a limit.
Sh-She sounds like a passionate teacher.
What are the other members of the club doing?
They're all keeping active in their own ways,
going out for TV auditions and such.
But you've just been practicing by yourself
at the park all this time, right?
I want to act with everyone.
Miss Landlady...
She really loves acting.
Hina-chan.
Why do you want to get into theater?
U-Um... I...
Are you already an actress?
Is there any role
you're particularly good at?
Obviously, that would be a scarecrow.
Cue Card
Coffee Shop Hitotose
So that's why you want to be in theater.
Yes.
As you can see, I get so nervous
in front of people, and I want to fix that.
That's why I want to try theater.
B-But I'm never going to get
anywhere this way, am I?
Don't worry. I was nervous
at my first performance, too.
I couldn't say my lines very well.
R-Really?
Yeah. I was four years old.
F-Four?!
That's right, you were a
child actress, weren't you?
My dad was a stage actor,
so it happened naturally while
I helped at his rehearsals.
Chiaki-chan.
Yes?
Can you grab those props for me?
Okay.
We've got trouble! The girl
playing Girl A suddenly got sick!
Oh, no! Will we have to cancel today's show?
Wait, I know!
Chiaki-chan, can you be a stand-in?
Huh?
Uh... um...
That's what happened.
That would make anyone nervous, child or not!
Is your father still a stage actor?
You're so cute! Is that food yummy?
No, my dad became a guitarist after that.
Oh, really?
He travels the world, playing and singing,
while he manages an apartment building.
Right now, he's apparently
playing the maracas.
Sounds like quite a free spirit...
1) Slice the apple into rings.
Leave the peel on!
2) Coat the inside of a pie pan with butter.
Lay the thawed crust in the pan and trim any excess.
Poke a few holes in the bottom with
a fork and chill in the refrigerator for 30 minutes.
Use a cookie cutter for cute and easy core removal!
Let the slices sit in salt water. Don't forget to peel them!!
Butter the pie crust!
30 minutes!
Cooking Drill: Apple Pie
Ingredients
1 frozen pie crust
1 apple
30g sugar
1/2 tbsp. lemon juice
Small amount of butter
*Thaw the pie crust at room temperature.
Oh, it sounds like it's going to rain soon.
Huh? But it's so sunny.
Aw, man...
And I thought we'd be able
to dry the laundry...
Hina-chan, can you talk to animals?
Oh, no, um...
It's more like just intuition...
Wow!
Animals have always been drawn to me.
Like rabbits, tanuki, boars, deer...
After a while, it just came naturally.
I think she'd be more suited to
the circus than to theater...
Is something wrong?
Hina-chan, why don't we try
forming a theater troupe after all?
Huh?
What you said earlier made me see
that you really want to be in theater.
But there's no telling when the school
theater club will start up again.
B-But...
Let's do it!
Kuu-chan...
How about we make use of your talent
to put on a play with real animals?
Like The Three Little Pigs.
But that story wouldn't need
any human actors, would it?
That's true... Okay, then...
Maybe Little Red Riding Hood?
Whoever played the grandma would be killed!
She'd get eaten by the wolf!
Actually, didn't Little Red
Riding Hood get eaten, too?
We can't do that!
This is harder than I thought.
Um, Miss Landlady...
Do you really think I can be an actress?
Maybe you can start behind the scenes
instead of jumping right into acting.
Behind the scenes?
There's a lot of work to do in a
theater troupe besides just acting.
Like makeup, set design, script writing,
and putting together props and costumes.
Oh...
They also need someone to
book venues for after-parties,
and people to prepare meals.
That's the most important thing!
I want to work behind the scenes!
I'm good with my hands,
and I can make clothes!
No, Mayu-chan, you need
to be front and center.
Why?
Because you're as cute as a doll.
She's right. You have a nice
voice, too. It carries well.
Mayu-chan, you'd look great
in a princess role!
I'm telling you, I can't!
In the first place, we haven't
even decided we're going to—
I'm up for it.
Hearing them talk about it
made it sound kinda fun.
I've always been interested in
things like scripts, anyway.
And above all,
I want to support Hina-chan.
Kuu-chan...
Also, I want to see Mayu-chan
playing a princess.
I told you, I'm not going to be an actress!
I think you'd be a perfect fit, though...
Jeez!
I'm getting hungry.
But we just had breakfast...
It's a little early, but shall we have lunch?
The new fabric softener I bought to try out
the other day smells so nice too...
Buying that was a good choice!
I'll definitely be buying it again!
The weather's nice today,
so it's a perfect day to do the laundry!
We can dry the bath towels
and sheets quickly and fold, fold, fold...
Today's Opening Time
12:30
Please Bear With Us
But even if we do start a theater troupe,
is there a place where
we could practice acting?
I was thinking we could make a stage
at the back of the coffee shop
and use it as a theater.
You've thought that far ahead?
You're really into this idea, huh?
I always thought it'd be nice if we could
hold regular stage productions here someday.
If we could do that...
...we'd draw more customers here, too.
You're more shrewd than I thought...
It would conform with the
apartment rules, so why not?
Oh, that's right...
Yep! Residents have to work here in the shop!
If you don't want to be in the troupe,
would you rather work in the coffee shop?
W-W-W-Wel...
W-Wel...c-co...
Or would you rather work
in the used bookstore?
I-I-Is... Is th-this...
the book you're l-looki—
The Setting Sun
I-I'd like to be in the
theater troupe, please.
Then that settles it!
Let's do our best.
Looking forward to it, principal.
A-Actually, about that...
I think you'd make a better principal.
I only jumped on board with your idea.
B-Besides, Aki-chan has to deal
with her work as landlady, too.
Is working as a landlady really that busy?
Just accept it!
Me as the principal of the
troupe... I couldn't...
Don't worry.
I don't think anyone wants this theater
troupe to happen more than you do.
You can do it.
O... O... O...
Okay! I'll try my best!
I-I'm inexperienced, but I'll be
counting on your support!
We're looking forward to it.
Buy for Tomorrow:
Coffee Beans
Filters
Let's work hard, Hina-chan!
Can't wait, Principal!
Today's Opening Time
14:00
Please Bear With Us
If we're going to start a theater troupe,
we'll need to come up with a troupe name.
Anyone have an idea?
Since it was her idea, it should
include Hina-chan's name!
Yeah, good idea.
How about the Hinako Troupe?
Or, for more impact, maybe Hinako Deluxe.
Or maybe Hinako and Her Merry Band?
What do you think, Hina-chan?
Huh? A-A... A...
A?
The apartment's name, Hitotose...
So, the Hitotose Troupe?
The Hitotose Troupe... I like it!
The Hitotose Troupe...
Yeah. I guess it's settled.
The Hitotose Troupe.
Okay! Now that our troupe has a name,
I need to open the shop.
U-Um...
C-Can I get all of your contact information?
Oh, right.
An SNS might be better than email.
Which SNS do you use?
W-Well...
I'm sorry... what is an SNS?
We're starting there?!
Now touch here.
That's it! Now press this, and...
Something popped up!
Mom
Kuina
Chiaki
Mayuki
That's all of us. You can contact us anytime.
Thank you!
Now, then...
I'm going to open the shop, okay?
Huh?
U-Uh... C-Can I have more pasta?
You want to eat more?!
Mom
Kuina
Chiaki
Mayuki
I got all these new contacts in just one day!
Kuina
Are you awake?
Eh... Ah...
Yes, I'm awake!
Hello?
Kuu-chan, you're here!
The others are here, too.
Mayu-chan! Miss Landlady!
Mind if we come in?
U-Um, what brings you all here?
We were wondering if you'd decided
what we should do with the troupe.
No, I don't even know
where we should start...
I guess you don't have
any stage experience yet.
So we did some research on theater troupes.
And we found that there's a famous place
in Shimokitazawa called Suzuran...
It's this.
Theater News
It's a very historical theater that
everyone dreams of performing in.
Really?
Yep.
Why don't we try to get there?
To someplace that amazing?
I'm in. It's always better to dream big.
I'm all for it, too.
Let's work hard together.
Okay!
Then Suzuran will be our goal.
Let's put together a great act!
Yep.
Right!
Yeah!
Leave the script to me!
I can't wait!
Yeah!
I'm excited.
Mistaken Friend
It's always better to dream big!
Bigger taiyaki and dorayaki
are always more exciting, too!
School's about to start, too.
Just thinking about what awaits
in our future makes me so excited!
Next time: "Mistaken Friend."