Excuse us.
I am the General.
From now on, you will be taking orders from me.
Did something happen to L?
That's none of your concern.
You both did well on this last mission.
I would like you to move right on
to your next assignment.
Assignment... Sir?
Her.
That's...
You will assassinate Princess.
What is going on here?
Why kill Princess now?
I believe that was always
the purpose of Operation: Changeling?
But Princess is currently our ally.
There is no need to kill her.
She's a royal.
There's no telling when she might betray us.
We have yet to see any sign of such intent.
Can't we wait until we KNOW she's danger-
We don't like taking risks.
And we did not ask for your opinion!
I understand.
The mission: assassinate the princess.
It will be accomplished.
Are you sure about this?
About what?
Don't play dumb with me.
They want us to kill Princess.
We're spies.
We just follow orders.
Well, I don't want to kill her.
We may be spies.
But we're human beings first!
Can you ignore your feelings?
I am from the Black Lizard Planet.
I'm not human.
Liar.
Report.
Sir.
We have a roster of 42 men, all present.
Very good. Contact the Wall unit.
Tell them we've arrived in London.
To a world without barriers!
You go on ahead.
I've been running her too long.
She needs maintenance.
Alright.
Dorothy.
Thank you.
Who's there?
You on the roof.
Ange le Carre, I'm a friend.
You won't need that gun.
Miss Zelda?
Is something the matter?
Ange's here.
Welcome back, Ange.
Do you always come in through the window?
I'm Zelda. Control sent me as Princess' bodyguard.
They didn't tell me.
Then ask them.
I start today.
I was just about to make some tea.
Have a cup with us?
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
From now on, our team will be made up
of eight agents, including Princess.
We're reorganizing the Operation: Changeling team.
I have been appointed its new commander.
Commander?
What about Dorothy?
When this place is finished,
the Queen herself will come see it.
Wow.
Ain't that something.
There are agents here that they haven't told me about.
Which means they don't trust me, either.
Ange!
How do you do, Ange?
Out for a stroll?
Oh, no.
Actually, the housemother wanted to see me.
Excuse me.
Her guards include the Duke of Normandy's people
and a Commonwealth spy.
Just one?
This is going to be troublesome, isn't it?
You are so kind, Princess.
Kind?
I finally figured it out.
You love all your people,
and work to defend your nation.
Because that is your royal duty.
Winter has been especially cold this year.
Yes, it has.
The ice on the pond has already...
Be careful not to touch items you don't recognize.
Do you think it's a joke?
I'll look into it.
So it's too dangerous to risk contacting her.
What do you think you're doing?
You know agents aren't allowed to contact Control.
And yet here you are.
What do you want?
What happened to L?
There were changes at the top.
We're led by the military now.
That's all.
So there's been a shakeup.
This new operation... it's too heavy-handed.
Like they WANT to be discovered.
How is this supposed to play out?
Stay loyal to the mission.
If you want to survive.
Chise.
What are you doing?
I've been assigned to a different school.
My Lord's orders.
Our time together was short,
but I thank you for all you've done.
I see.
Is there something troubling you?
In my country, we believe that
a debt of hospitality must be repaid.
No, I'm fine.
I see.
Take care.
How is Seven doing?
We execute the mission tomorrow.
The plan is to take her outside the school
to dispose of her, but...
I'll do it.
Operation: Changeling was my idea.
I will kill Princess.
Alright.
Construction will be complete by this weekend.
In honor of the new royal temple's dedication, we
will be holding a service to pray for our nation's victory.
We ask for your Majesty's honorable presence.
The lords and ambassadors in attendance
would be honored to hear a few words from...
Excuse me.
This won't take long.
What?
I've received intel that part of the army
began gathering in London last night.
Who is their leader?
We haven't identified one.
But we believe that most of them were born
in overseas colonies.
Call back the Home Office forces stationed in Rouen.
And be discreet about it.
And Her Majesty?
I will decide whether or not to tell her.
Princess, you remember, don't you?
The day we first met.
I never told you where I was trying to go.
I had heard there was a dry well
in a corner of the gardens.
And I was planning to disappear forever.
Then I met you.
I didn't like people, and I was afraid of everything.
You were the first friend I could ever confide in.
The revolution came, and I lost everything.
But I didn't give up on living.
I wanted to see you again.
That was the only thing...
...that helped me keep fighting.
I wanted to apologize to you.
But...
I told you.
I want your help to make me Queen.
In the end, I only got you caught up
in my selfish wishes again.
And I'm sorry.
But this is one time...
...I can't protect you.
I think this is a first!
Going shopping, just the two of us.
Yeah.
There are so many people!
Yes.
Oh, Ange!
Look, look!
Come on, Ange! Hurry!
Coming!
They aren't hiding their watchdogs.
So they don't think I'll do it?
Of course they don't.
What's the matter, Ange?
You're not having fun.
Oh, no, I am.
Really? I couldn't tell by looking at you.
Is this a good idea?
Leaving the princess' assassination to A.
This is a test of loyalty.
If she tries to pull anything funny...
This will be something to see.
You're right.
I didn't think my guards would follow me in here.
So Princess.
There's somewhere I have to take you,
just the two of us.
Let's ditch the security.
Like we used to do when we were kids.
Yeah!
How do I look?
After her!
She's onto us!
She got away!
Princess.
Where do you think you're going?
What's going on?
Stop!
This way!
Ange!
Let's go!
Yeah!
It's like old times!
Just like when we would tease Mrs. Crawford!
Yeah!
We were running then, too.
Where are we?
The passenger airship, the Good Hope.
It's headed for Casablanca.
Casablanca?
What do you mean?
Is that where you had to take me?
I told you, remember?
There's a white house there, waiting for us.
Where is this coming from?
You've been acting strangely
ever since Zelda came along.
Just what happened?
We were given orders...
to assassinate you.
Assassinate?
For Operation: Changeling? But that was...
There've been changes at the top.
I tried to get around it somehow,
but I've run out of options.
What about Miss Dorothy and Miss Chise?
They've both been removed from the team.
Oh no...
I always planned to abort this operation
as soon as I made contact with you.
I can't afford to put you in any more danger-
No.
I still have things to do in this country.
I told you.
I'm going to get rid of the Wall.
Princess...
There are still so many people here
who have been torn away from each other!
As long as I am the princess, I can't run away!
On the day of the revolution, I swore to myself.
I swore I would create the world you wanted to see,
with my own hands.
So please, Charlotte.
There must still be SOMETHING I can do!
After the scene we caused back there,
there is no going back.
Please understand, Princess.
If you were going to run away anyway,
I wish you'd left me out of this from the start!
My life is not yours to play with!
Princess?!
Wait!
Princess, open the door!
That's right. I am the princess.
If Operation: Changeling means that
one of us has to disappear,
then you can disappear without me.
Princess.
You were the one who was always scared,
always crying, always making trouble.
I was always cleaning up your mess.
From the day we met,
I've always hated that about you.
Goodbye, Ange.
Never let me see you again.
Princess...
Thank you for your undercover work.
The truth is, I've heard some unsavory rumors,
which is why I have called you back.
Which is to say...?
You are aware that the majority of the Royal Army
hail from the colonies, yes?
Yes.
Something about a deployment of colonial soldiers
against the Commonwealth.
There has been some unrest among a faction of
colonial soldiers who are unhappy with the Kingdom.
And that is why you summoned me back here?
Yes.
If the information is accurate,
then your friend is at the center of that unrest.
We have split into four teams to search the airport.
We had a tip that they escaped into the airport lounge.
Wait, you're...
An... ge?
I'm sure you have an explanation.
What exactly did you think you were doing?
Trying to gain the princess' trust.
She believed I was on her side to her very last breath.
Really.
I have arrived.
I understand there was some commotion downstairs?
Don't worry. It's all according to plan.
Zelda, is...
Is that...?
Yes.
This is Princess Charlotte.
It is an honor to meet you, Princess.
Princess, this is Major Yngwie.
He laments the state of this country just as we do.
As we do?
Though it pains us to do so, we are prepared
to strike down Her Majesty the Queen.
And we would like to make you our new sovereign.
We're going to war.