Izanami no Mikoto.
Drawing on negative human
emotions for strength,
she is the goddess of
death who threatened...
...to kill a thousand men in a day.
That's Isanami?
Hello again.
Is everyone here?
If you've gathered us here, then...
It's time.
The world is about to shift dramatically.
Tokugawa and Toyotomi will clash soon.
And one of them will rule the world.
Whoever claims the throne,
we'll be the ones ruling from the shadows.
That goes without saying.
However, we'll need power to do that.
A power great enough to turn
this world on its head.
We tried to gather all the information
we could to take that power,
but we have enough.
We must simply capture the
priestess and the Kushimitama.
We'll eliminate the worthless
eyesores guarding her.
The Start of Tragedy
Isanami is Izanami no Mikoto?
I cannot believe the Kushimitama has
been suppressing Isanami's power.
Does Isanami know?
She overheard us.
Isanami!
Don't worry. Saizo is with her.
B-But!
Only light can hold back the darkness.
Nii-tan!
What should I do as her older brother?
Am I being tested?
Are you telling me to endure this
pain in my heart and keep going,
gods?
Is that supposed to help him think?
I'm pretty sure it'll just make him dumber.
Ben-chan!
Miss...
Excuse me.
You have guests.
Guests?
They wish to see you immediately.
Unbelievable. Who's visiting me now?
Quiet, Yukimura.
Excuse the intrusion.
Mitsunari, Kanetsugu?
What are you doing here?
I told you to be quiet.
We didn't get the chance
to talk in the capitol,
and you never respond to my letters.
I thought it'd be quicker to come
here and speak to you directly.
This place lies between
Aizu and Sawayama,
and Ueda's a well defended
backwater country.
It's the perfect place for a secret meeting.
What are you calling backwater?
It's a compliment.
How is that a compliment?
Now, now. There's no point in
arguing since it's the truth.
If you came here to mock me, go home.
What are you so mad about?
Wha—?
Your words are too much
for me, Kanetsugu.
Well, what do you want?
Keep it short. I'm in the
middle of something.
Whether or not this will
be short is up to you.
You are the Light, Saizo.
Is this as far as you'll run?
Good afternoon.
You bastard.
Hattori Hanzo.
I bet you thought I died at Izumo.
Unfortunately for you,
I'm quite resilient.
Are you thinking you've led
me far enough away?
Don't worry. You're my target today.
Me?
There's something we have to do
before we take the Kushimitama.
Kill all the braves.
I must thank you...
...for protecting the Kushimitama
and the priestess for us until now.
Of course, your exceedingly
tight defenses...
...prevented us from taking
Unno Rokuro's eye.
You're the one Ana's working for!
I will kill you with all the
gratitude and hatred I have.
I have decided to murder
you most brutally.
You're starting your killing
spree with me, then?
Starting with you?
No, it has already begun.
The tragedy of the Five
Iga Ninja and the Braves.
The Five Iga Ninja.
Speed, strength, deception,
sorcery, and mercilessness.
Against the five of us who have
mastered the five ninja techniques,
the braves are nothing more
than a flock of fools.
Killing all of you will be no trouble at all.
I'm sure you understand.
You're an Iga ninja.
Sasuke?
What is going on?
We were lured out here.
What do you mean, lured?
Caught two bugs in my trap.
I've been looking forward
to meeting you.
I'm so excited.
What is that monstrous spider?
Who are you?
One of the Five Iga Ninja.
Kaio, master of insects.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Five Iga Ninja.
You know of them?
Secret ninja. Identities unknown.
Unusual techniques.
Ninja who specialize in killing other ninja.
What are they doing in Ueda?
I will answer that.
Our leader instructed us to kill...
...the Sanada Braves protecting
the Kushimitama and priestess.
Of course, I have my own reasons
for wanting to kill the two of you.
Personal reasons?
I know not of what you speak.
I assure you, I do.
I must avenge my sister Okatsu.
Get it now?
On your guard!
That's it. That's it!
All gods are the same.
The more you believe,
the more you will be saved.
Whether she's a creature
of the underworld,
or Izanami no Mikoto, she's still a god.
I simply need to have faith in my sister.
My sister is my true god.
How splendid!
I'm not sure I get it,
but it sounds like he does.
What's so bright?
Isanami, there is nothing
to be sad about.
Your brother will...
Seikai!
I thought he'd dodge it. How slow.
Mister Seikai!
A midget with messy orange hair.
Kid, you're one of the braves.
Then you'll die, too.
Benmaru, are you all right?
Are you?
How disgraceful to disrupt
my moment of enlightenment.
I must lecture you.
Identify yourself!
One of the Five Iga Ninja, Byakugun.
Go to hell!
I despise unnecessary killing.
I don't know your intentions,
but if you retreat now, I'll let this slide.
Let it slide?
The hell does that mean?
Don't tell me you think
you're stronger than I am.
We'll kill all you braves, every last one.
Every last one?
Isanami's in trouble!
I said every last one!
Ieyasu's tyrannical
behavior is outrageous.
We have to do something
about that old raccoon dog.
He accused Uesugi of
plotting against him for...
...constructing fortifications
within his own territory.
Nothing could be more obnoxious.
I see.
I've had enough of his insolence.
You're as foul-mouthed as always.
I considered sending you a letter
describing his actions,
but I couldn't fit all my
thoughts on a single scroll.
I see.
I have secretly gathered
my soldiers in Sawayama.
We have many allies.
Uesugi will fight with us.
You're ready to go, aren't you?
I...
I cannot forgive him for
slighting Toyotomi.
That raccoon dog must be doing this
because he believes he stands a chance.
What I thought was a raccoon
dog turned out to be a mouse.
If we act blindly, we'll play
right into his hands.
If only we had some earthshaking power.
You shouldn't wish for such things.
But...
A power that large...
...would only bring trouble.
What?
What's wrong?
You moved a lot better when
I fought you at Izumo.
Shut up! I'm just getting warmed up!
Saizo!
Isanami!
Isanami, stay back!
Watch from over there.
Isanami!
If you don't focus on fighting, you'll die.
Stop!
I'm the one you want.
Saizo has nothing to do with this.
Shut up, you idiot!
Let Isanami go!
Oh, I will. I'll be taking
her with me, anyway.
Right after I finish toying
with and killing you.
You bastard.
You're disgusting!
Where did she go?
She blended in with the
bugs and disappeared.
Their wings are covering her sound.
I cannot sense her.
Jump!
Sasuke, leave this to me.
Okay.
You can't get close to me that easily.
Iga Insect Technique.
Sengoku Doro!
Praying mantises now?
You are the prey caught in my web.
You cannot escape now.
Oh my. You're more
capable than I thought.
Leave here at once.
I'm afraid I cannot.
We've been instructed
to kill all of you.
Then you will die.
How dare you reject my kiss?
Terrible.
Sasuke!
Once he's in your body, it's over.
He will eat your heart.
Sasuke!
Does it hurt that much?
Ants?!
Insects may be small,
but they're the servants of death
who return flesh to the earth.
May you be eaten alive
from both inside and out,
and die painful deaths!
Juzo.
Koga Tenshin Technique.
Kamaitachi!
Sasuke!
Sorcery?!
It's payback time.
How does that taste?
I'm not finished with the two of you yet.
I hope you'll entertain me even more.
You'll be eaten alive by
insects if you don't get up.
How long can you keep
dodging these rocks?
Her strength is unbelievable.
In front of you!
Gotcha!
A girl's attacks are nothing!
Mister?
You're all talk, monk.
No matter how faithful you are,
you can't save anyone.
If you believe, you will be saved.
You will be saved!
The gods protect us humans.
Life and death depend
on your own strength.
Only you can protect yourself.
Pitiful. What pathetic thinking.
If not for Isanami, I would
take my time converting you.
Isanami? Is that the priestess?
I bet she's our leader's tool by now.
Take that back!
Mister, let's go now!
No. I will have her pay
for slandering Isanami.
And how do you intend to do that?
Show me.
Did she get bigger?
How absurd to think you can
fight me hand to hand!
You're weak.
Rokkon Shojo!
In the name of the gods and the spirits,
repent!
That's all?
Why? My fists have no effect.
It's my turn!
Seikai!
Stay back, kid!
Benmaru!
We're not done yet, monk!
Over already? You're pathetic.
I must go.
I must not let Isanami feel sad.
I must...
Why? Do I lack faith?
Isanami, I am sorry.
I cannot save you...
Saizo...
Saizo, stop.
Please stop.
You'll kill Saizo.
Isanami.
Didn't I tell you?
You'll die if you don't focus.
Stop!
Don't hurt Saizo any more!
This is all my fault.
Well, this is interesting.
Does your sadness awaken the
power of the Kushimitama?
Shunko!
You're too slow.
Kasho Zanmai!
No!
That's right. This is all your fault.
If he had never met you,
or never had anything to do with you,
this never would have happened to Saizo.
My...
You hurt him.
Isanami, don't listen to him.
It's not just Saizo.
All the other braves should have
drawn their last breath by now.
It's all your fault.
Isanami...
Good to see you all again.
Don't tell me you thought I died at Izumo.
I'm not one to die so easily.
I'm actually quite strong.
I actually did everything I was paid to do.
I was just so tired of
working for those morons,
so I thought it'd be
easier to fake my death.
You thought you defeated me, didn't you?
What a shame.
Bet it hurt, though.
Well, enough excuses. Let's get on with it.
The Wail of Darkness
The next episode of Brave 10 is
"The Wail of Darkness."
Bring it on!