It seems Romalia has already
dispatched a fleet to counter ours.
The stage will soon be set.
What do you mean by that?
You can't possibly be
planning to declare war?
War?
Wars are started by those
who wish for gain.
I wish for nothing. I just want to try it.
Begin the preparations, Sheffield.
As you wish, my lord.
Wh-What's that?
As you know, I'm a Familiar of the Void.
Myozunitonirun, the Mind of God.
I am the only one capable
of releasing the power
locked within the Founder's Round Mirror.
Those runes...
When I use this mirror,
I can transfer a Void
Mage's power to another.
I needed your destruction
spell, Explosion,
so that I may use these
fire stones at will.
The Incompetent King Gone Mad
The Gallian fleet has stopped
1200 meters from our border.
Keep that distance and set
up a defensive perimeter.
Yes, sir.
What are you plotting now, Joseph?
What does this mean?
It's no small thing, that's for sure.
So I guess you're over there, Louise.
What is happening, Your Holiness?
This is most likely one
of Joseph's feints.
He's trying to make sure the Void Mages,
besides him, do not get any closer.
I don't think he will
make an actual attack.
Do you really think so?
But then, why did he take Louise?
Aeor suhn fil jarnsaks,
os suhn uriu rad...
What are you using my spells for?
Stick around and you'll see.
Beozus yul sviel kan oshel,
jer isa undun hagal,
beocun ir...
Explosion!
My lord!
Unexpectedly, I feel nothing.
Ready the next fire stone.
Yes, sir.
He's destroying his own men, too!
What is he thinking?
Tabitha! Please, let me ride Sylphid.
Saito!
Julio?
Don't even try to stop me.
I have no intention of stopping you.
There's something I wanted to give you.
R-Retreat!
Retreat at full speed!
Come about 180 degrees!
H-Hey. What was that?
It's a bomb!
Run for it!
Where are we going?
I'm not certain.
But it's over there!
Tiffa!
You're all here!
Where are Saito and Louise?
Tabitha's gone, too.
That's...
Hey...
What's that over there?
A gargoyle?
This is terrible!
We've got to get the
townspeople to safety!
Why? Why are you doing this?!
What is your objective?!
Objective?
My objective is death and destruction.
That is all.
I want to find out what level
of cruelty will actually
make me feel remorse,
and if I am capable of
shedding tears, like you.
Just for that, you'd...
It's quite a problem...
...for someone like me, who had to kill
his emotions as he grew up in the
shadow of a superior younger brother...
My little brother, Charles...
It was fun when we were young.
I've got to do something.
But when your gift for
magic was awakened,
everything changed.
Since then, my soul has
only thirsted for more.
No matter what riches I amassed,
no matter how many people I killed,
I could find no peace.
What do you think, Charles?
Do you think destroying a city
can make my heart start beating again?
Sheffield.
Right away, my lord.
What?!
Impossible!
Bring it back at once!
Saito, Saito, Saito, Saito!
No!
Saito, Saito, Saito!
Louise!
Louise...
Thank God.
We've got to stop the explosion!
I've retrieved the fire stone
safe and sound,
but it appears the girl's life is forfeit.
I doubt it will be that easy.
Full speed ahead.
Saito, please!
So that's Joseph, King of Gallia!
I guess all I have to do
is keep him from casting.
It's been too long, Gandalfr.
I won't let you get in my master's way!
Shut up!
I will stop that explosion!
Everyone, please remain calm!
Please take shelter in the cathedral.
Is it really all right for us to use
the cathedral as an evacuation shelter?
I don't care!
I will personally take responsibility
for those useless priests.
I nailed that one.
Guiche... Behind you!
I thank you for your swift decision.
Please help us lead everyone
into the cathedral.
Look!
It's Tabitha and Louise!
Air Cutter!
It's fast!
It looks like they're
chasing the gargoyle.
The gargoyles caused that
explosion a while ago.
I'm afraid that one will do the same.
Those two are trying to stop it!
Why you...
Hey, pal, this is never going to end.
I know that, but...
The gargoyles get their
power from Myozunitonirun.
I won't get anywhere,
until I can get some hits on her.
This is one of those "out of place relics"
that are kept in Romalia.
Make good use of it, Gandalfr.
Okay...
Th-That's a...
I don't have time to fight you right now.
They're having a hard time of it.
I can't bear to watch
knowing that I can't do anything.
Miss Westwood!
There is something you can do!
Wasn't there that time when you
made everyone forget all
those things with magic?
I understand.
I'll try!
Naucid is eywath,
hagraz yul beog,
nied ees algihz,
berkana man ragu!
You did it!
I'm going back to Joseph's ship.
You should get off here.
No, I'm going, too.
I want to be at Saito's side!
Fine.
Beozus yul sviel kan oshel...
Joseph!
Stop casting!
Gandalfr.
Are you going to kill me?
You won't be blowing up anything else.
I'm going to protect the
city and everyone in it!
That's all there is to it!
There's so much honesty in
your eyes, it's almost blinding.
I was like you once.
I suppose there's no going back now.
What?
That thing is useless against me.
This is the Void Magic
that was bestowed upon me.
It's called Acceleration.
For what purpose did God
grant me this spell?
It's as if he's urging me to hurry.
Now...
I must be getting back
to the task at hand.
Pal, if he gets you with
that, you're done for.
Pal...?
In my world, we have an
expression, "the mind's eye."
I'll use that to track
your movements, Joseph!
Why don't you try it?
So, is this the great "mind's eye"?
Gotcha.
I don't have to be Gandalfr
to learn how to use this.
Which do you think is faster,
your sword, or mine?
Explosion!
Windy Icicles!
Saito!
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
I've gotten worse from you.
You're such an idiot.
Charlotte.
I see you inherited your
father's magic powers.
You killed my father and you
broke my mother's heart.
I will never forgive you for that.
As you shouldn't.
Then do with me as you like.
That is your right.
Tabitha, you shouldn't!
There's no need for you to
have his blood on your hands!
But...
I...
I can't forgive him.
Saito, you've got to stop her!
This is her decision.
But, Saito!
Even if she sullies her hands,
she has to decide this for herself.
Isn't that right?
You're the one who has to decide.
Either way, I'll respect your decision.
I'll hand him over to Romalia.
If you're treated right away, you'll live.
Live, and atone for your sins!
Tabitha!
I won't allow King Joseph to be
subjected to something so degrading!
You!
Stand back!
The incantation was almost complete.
From here, even my own power
is enough to make it explode.
My lord's life is rapidly fading away.
Please, leave me alone with him...
Damn it.
We had them cornered, and
then we let them get away!
It's better this way.
Let's go home, Saito.
Louise.
We haven't kissed since
the contract, my lord.
I'm returning this to you.
For your actions, I'd like to
thank you from the bottom of my heart,
Miss Vallière,
Miss Tabitha,
and you, Saito Chevalier de Hiraga.
How are your wounds, Saito?
Great, thanks to your
healing magic, Princess!
That's good to hear.
Julio, that pistol you
gave me came in handy.
Did it?
I'm glad to hear that.
But you gave me that because you
wanted me to defeat Joseph, didn't you?
I couldn't help but think,
you make Louise into a shrine maiden,
she gets kidnapped by Joseph.
I go to save her, and then
I take Joseph down in the process.
Seemed like everything
was going right according to your plans.
Saito! How can you say such a thing?!
Am I wrong, Your Holiness?
Saito!
Indeed, I can't deny it outright.
We made a Void Mage
into a shrine maiden,
not to convince him, but to provoke him.
We expected Joseph to do something.
No, we hoped he would.
If that happened,
we would have a reason to
launch a holy war against Gallia
and get rid of Joseph.
But you must believe me when
I say that it was never our intention
to put Miss Vallière in
such a dangerous position.
Nor did we expect Joseph to
cause so much destruction.
I hope
you can forgive us.
Louise, wait!
Don't you think you should
say something to them?
If King Joseph is dead,
then another Void Mage will be born.
I'm sure, then, it'll be easy for
the four of us to join forces.
You're saying that makes it okay?
You were almost killed in the process.
But you were there to protect me.
I knew back then that you would
definitely be coming soon to save me.
I felt it, too.
It was like I could see
you waiting for me.
I know you'll always be
there to protect me.
That's why I'm not afraid.
Louise.
Shall we go?
They're all waiting for us.
Let's go.
What a strong bond they have.
How could I ever think
that Saito might be my familiar?
It's impossible.
It's the saint of Aquileia!
And the hero!
This is so wonderful!
What is...?
What are you doing?
Everyone is praising
the saint of Aquileia
and the hero!
Long live the saint of Aquileia!
Long live the hero!
Y-You lecherous dog!
Just because you saved
Romalia doesn't mean
I will let it slide that
you're drooling over other women!
Next time: The Queen's Reward
The Queen's Reward
After this, let's look for a
castle just for the two of us.