Somebody!
Isn't there anyone around?!
Whoa! What's going on, Ms. Kyoko?
Ichijo, huh? Where are
the other students?
Everyone's gone home for the day.
I'm the last one.
Whaaat? So I was too late.
Hey, I know!
All right, Ichijo, do something for me.
You look like the kind of guy
who has a lot of friends.
The thing is, see, I was supposed to
pick some students to clean the pool,
but it totally slipped my mind.
And so you see, Ichijo...
Tomorrow, Saturday, round up some
friends and clean the pool, will you?
Whaaaat? Hold up!
Why does it have to be me?!
I'm begging you, Ichijo!
I'm in a real bind here!
I'm always, always taking care of
those animals on holidays, aren't I?
So the least you can
do is return the favor!
Well...
All right, I'm counting on you!
The rest is up to you!
"Cleanup Day"
So?
You were at the end of your rope,
so you came crying to me?
You really are a handful
for a bean sprout!
I owe you big time.
But you know what, cleaning the pool
sounds kind of exciting to me!
Sounds fun!
Talk about thinking positive...
Who else did you ask?
The thing is...
Basically, I called on the guys,
but aside from this one
they all turned me down.
Looking forward to this, Kirisaki!
Don't you have any friends?
If you'd said some girls' names,
they all would've come running.
Like I could take advantage like that.
Ichijo!
Sorry to keep you waiting! I'm
looking forward to working with you today!
Onodera... Hey, thanks for coming!
Huh? Who's this girl?
How do you do?
I'm Haru's friend.
Haru calls me Fuu-chan.
What are you doing here?
Now, now...
You came, too, Haru? You're so cute!
Did you really think it would be so easy?
You're not getting
anywhere near my sister!
Of course I'm not.
Young Mistress!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Getting changed into this held me up.
Morning, Tsugumi!
Hey, that looks great on you!
Didn't you have anything
that wasn't quite this sparse?
I know I shouldn't say that
when you're lending this to me.
Hey, so you came, too?
It's Paula-chan, right?
Don't give me that "chan"
treatment - it's creepy.
I'm here because the Black
Tiger summoned me.
Young Mistress Chitoge?
I'm pleased to make your acquaintance.
I'm Paula McCoy of
the Beehive Hitman Team.
I have offered my life and pledged
my fealty to the organization.
Should you need anything,
please feel free to let me know.
Y-Yes... N-Nice to meet you.
What do you want me to do, Black Tiger?
First, let's inspect the equipment.
Master Raku!
I've missed you so—
Whatever do you think
you're doing, Kirisaki?
I can read you a mile away!
I guess we're all here, then.
You guys, thanks for coming today.
Once we're done, we're free
to have fun as we want,
so let's get this over with
as soon as we can!
Right!
Take that!
If I could just turn all this into
a DVD, I bet I'd make a killing...
Forget it.
These are all people you definitely
wouldn't want as enemies.
Let's dig in!
Wow! Looks yummy!
This is soooo good!
Did you make all this yourself, Haru?
Well, I did leave
the presentation to my sister.
My intent was to whip up
a conventional meal,
but before I knew it they'd
become posh box lunches.
Alchemy!
Paula! Aren't you going to eat with us?
Would you mind setting
some aside for her?
I'll hand it to her later.
All righty, how should I go about
provoking the Black Tiger next?
Shall l toss that boy into
the girls' locker room, maybe?
Whoops-a-daisy...
Hey... what do you think you're doing?
That's dangerous!
But you climbed up here, too, Paula.
And besides, I thought I'd enjoy
my lunch more if I ate it up here.
Here you go! This is your share, Paula!
I don't want it.
But it turned out so tasty!
What's this girl's problem?
Hey, Paula, you're always
looking at Tsugumi, aren't you?
What's your relationship to Tsugumi?
Oh, did you go to the same
junior high, maybe?
That's none of your business!
Well, you see, I've got an older sister.
See, over there!
My sister's name is Kosaki,
and she's always been sweet and
a little ditzy, but she's really dependable,
and she's my beloved,
precious big sister!
I was wondering if maybe you felt
the same way towards Tsugumi, you know?
I told you, it's none of your business!
Why are you paying so much
attention to me, anyway?!
What's the problem? You're so stingy!
Everybody's starting to
jump into the pool!
Young Mistress! You forgot to stretch!
Why don't we go in, too, Paula?
We've got floats and
water pistols and stuff!
Do whatever you want.
Hold up! No way!
Amazing!
Jeez, talk about acting too buddy-buddy.
What do I care about relationships?
They're sure handling those
water pistols like amateurs.
If it were me, I'd go like...
What the...?
What's the big idea, damn you?!
No, what do you think you're doing?
It's so obvious that
you're dying to join in.
If you want to play, then just play.
What... Wh-Who wants to...?
I have absolutely no desire to play!
Dummy, you can't hide it.
It's written all over your face.
Didn't you say you were trying to
learn more about this world?
But I don't have a clue...
I've never played with
so many people like this,
and I have no idea what expression
I should have when I join in.
Idiot!
Who cares what your expression is -
if you don't join in, you'll never know!
You do have some interest in why
Tsugumi changed after coming here, right?
Then come on.
Everybody's waiting.
Paula! Thank goodness, you came back!
Hey, hey, wanna swim together?
No... I...
You're not gonna swim?
Just let me make one thing clear. I'm not
here because you told me to come.
I just felt like taking a break, that's all.
Yeah, sure, gotcha.
Come on, come on, don't be shy!
Let's swim!
I told you, I...
M-My legs...
Paula... you can't swim?
Oh, shut up! You got
a problem with that?!
Whaaat? No way! Who knew?
So you do have some
endearing aspects!
Shut up! Shut up!
I'm never getting into the pool again!
Hey, don't be like that, all right?
How anyone finds this fun,
I'll never know! Jeez, I'm so wiped!
Youth, eh?
"Visiting the Sick"
Onodera's got a cold?
That's right.
I want to go see her myself,
but I've got something to do.
Ichijo, would you mind
going in my place?
But are you sure it's okay for me to go?
What are you talking about?
Kosaki says she wants you
to come over.
Whaaaaat?
ONODERA JAPANESE CONFECTIONS
And so I did end up coming,
but is it really okay?
A guy visiting a girl at home alone?
"Closed for the next few days"
Huh? The shop is closed.
Come to think of it, Miyamoto did
tell me to go in from the back.
Yes?
Yes? Who's there...?
Huh? Wait... Onodera?
What's wrong, Onodera?
Open up, will you?
Okay? Come on!
I-Ichijo... what are you doing here?
Well... Miyamoto said she had
an errand to run, so I'm here in her place.
She never said anything to me!
What the hell, Miyamoto?
Giving me false hope!
Thanks to you, I've
come to see her, but...
Hey... My fever's going to spike!
All right... All right, why
don't you come in for now?
Are you sure?
How are you feeling?
Yes, it's fine.
I still have a fever, but
I've got some medicine.
Come to think of it,
the shop's closed today.
Yes, the thing is, Mom's away on a trip
with her friends from the shopping arcade.
She won't be back
for another few days.
What? Meaning that...
could it be that today
I'm here alone with Onodera?
Hello? Is this the police?
There's a prowler inside my home!
Hold up, hold up, hold up!
Who are you calling a prowler?
What are you doing here
in our home, Senpai?!
Just get out of here right now!
Hey, Haru!
Ichijo came here
to check up on me, you know?
You shouldn't be rude to him!
But there's no need.
For him to check on you.
You've got me at your side, Sister.
All right, Senpai, thank you for coming over!
There's nothing to worry about anymore!
Hold up, hold up, Haru!
Uh... If you like... Here!
You did tell me that you loved
the strawberry rice cakes from Suzumiya.
Dangling a carrot in front of me...
did you really think that would work?
Well, I guess I'll let you stay
for a little while, but...
Thanks.
Then would you mind
if I borrowed your kitchen?
I'd like to make some
rice gruel or something.
You don't have to do that.
Oh, then I'll give you a hand.
Sister, you rest up, all right?
So...
What are you plotting, anyway?
Are you planning to take advantage of
my sister when she's vulnerable?
I'm not plotting anything.
I find that very hard to believe.
Coming here when
you already have a girlfriend...
won't that gorgeous
girlfriend of yours be pissed?
Well, it's...
It's really complicated, you see...
How interesting.
A situation where you're allowed to be
a two-timer? What could that be?
It's no good.
Far from being alone with Onodera, it doesn't
look like I can even have a nice talk with her.
Could it be that you're after that locket?
I'm not handing it over.
I'm going to give that
back to my prince myself!
No, although I do admit I want it back.
Don't let your guard down, Haru.
Now that Sister's so vulnerable,
I've got to protect her!
Sister!
Your rice gruel is read—
Why are you cleaning up, Sister?
Come on! You're sick,
so you've got to stay in bed!
I couldn't help it.
Who knew that I'd ever get to
enter this room again.
Here, Sister, we made you
some rice gruel. Have it!
Okay.
Sister? All right, say ahhhh!
It's all right, I can eat on my own.
What do you say?
Aren't you jealous?
Th-This kid!
Um...
Yeah, I think your fever totally broke.
Looks like you're going to be all right!
All right, Sister, drink lots of
water and get lots of rest.
Just call me on my cell phone,
and I'll come anytime!
Right.
Come on! Let's go, Senpai!
I know, I know!
Huh?
But I am still running a temperature.
All right, there's nothing else
you can help out with, Senpai.
Why don't you take your leave now?
Sorry, Haru.
Hey! What are you
doing, all of a sudden?!
That was totally sexual harassment!
Haru, you've caught
Onodera's cold, right?
I-I did not catch it.
As you can see, I'm fit as a fiddle...
Go to bed!
No!
If I collapse, too, what's
going to become of my sister?!
I don't have any plans today,
so I could look after her,
if that's okay.
Why would it be okay?!
Something like that!
If it means leaving
my sister in your care,
I'd rather just pass out myself!
Hey, that's enough!
If you were to push yourself
too hard and collapse,
who'd end up feeling
the most responsible?!
Hey, I don't want to make
Onodera feel uncomfortable, either,
and I don't intend to.
And I don't have the guts to do
what you're so worried I will.
Understood.
Seriously...
Pushing herself so irrationally
for someone else's sake...
I can see that she's
Onodera's kid sister, all right.
Coming in!
Haru,
you still haven't eaten, have you?
I did make you some rice gruel.
I don't want it, really.
It's not like I have any appetite.
Come on, don't be so stubborn.
You need to eat while you can.
Or is it something else?
Want me to feed you
like you did Onodera?
Here... ahhhh...
Sorry, I shouldn't have done that.
I just have to eat it, right? Right?
Yummy!
Well? Is it good?
What is this?
It wasn't the least bit good!
You can't even make a decent rice gruel.
Your ineptitude is enough
to make me drool!
Oh, is that right?
All right, I'm gonna
leave this drink here,
so be sure to keep sipping it
and get some rest, okay?
See you.
What's up with that?
Pretending to be a gentleman...
When he doesn't give a second
thought about two-timing.
Well, but that rice gruel was good.
My body feels so hot.
I was all tensed up till now...
so the fatigue just hit me at once.
I think... I'm in agony...
What's this?
Something cold on my forehead.
It feels so good.
When did I fall asleep...?
I-Ichijo-senpai!
What are you doing sleeping here?
A cold compress?
Is that what felt so good?
Have you been changing
them all this time?
For me?
But why?
This guy... He's not the kind of
person to do such a...
He's really gentle, you know... Ichijo.
Whoa, my bad! I must've nodded off.
Who knew I'd fall asleep here?
It's all right, don't worry!
I swear I didn't do anything to you!
So everything's fine, okay?
Hey, that's right,
how's your fever?
Yes, thanks to you, it came down a lot.
Is that right? Thank
goodness. Hey! Not good!
I've got to go change
Onodera's compress, too.
Whoa... Whoops, whoops, whoops!
Oh, crap, I went and did it!
My bad, I'll pick that up right now!
Wh-What's so funny?
Well, but Ichijo-senpai,
you're somehow even
weirder than I thought!
You haven't smiled at me like that
since we first met in the hallway.
Wh-What's that supposed to mean?
Is there a problem?
No... there's no problem.
Ichijo-senpai, if you please.
A lot has happened between us, but...
You're giving it back to me?
No, I'm not!
I'm just leaving it in your care.
When the day comes for me
to be reunited with my prince,
please give it back to me.
Until then, I'm granting you
special custody.
But in return,
please let me see my
prince again someday.
Or else I'm going to
stick a needle in your eye!
Right... Roger that.
But see, that's...
I admit he's just a tiny bit different
than what I thought, Sister.