I'm late, I'm late!
I gotta go, I gotta go!
I'm off!
"The Search"
Man, what a close call.
I came this close to being late.
Hey, pretty unusual, Chitoge.
Even if it was just barely,
for you to get here before me...
Chitoge?!
You lost your ribbon?
I didn't notice till I got to school.
Since you were in a hurry,
the knot might have been too loose.
So you're not even sure
where you might have dropped it?
I'm gonna go look for it now!
Hold up, hold up! Class is about to start!
Come on, calm down, will you?
I'll help you look for it
after school, all right?
But that ribbon...
Yeah, I know.
It's your cherished ribbon that
you got from Ms. Hana, right?
I promise you that I'll find it.
Well, that's one thing, but...
That's the one that y—
Huh?
No, never mind.
Never fear, Young Mistress!
I, too, shall help with the search.
We'll pitch in, too.
You guys!
For now, let me tie this up for you.
Thanks.
I thought it would
come in handy one day, so...
My hair/makeup kit!
All right, what kind of
style should we go for?
Honestly! Over a ribbon...
how pathetic you are!
I can't imagine that anyone would
turn in that strip of cloth.
By now it might well be discarded
along with the trash, no?
Marika Tachibana! Why, you...!
You think so?
You really think that's
what happened to it?
Kirisaki!
That's not at all how you'd usually react!
I implore you not to sob so hard!
Very well, very well!
I, too, shall lend
a hand in the search,
so for goodness sake,
please stop crying!
Is she okay? Chitoge...
I wonder where it could be?
Chitoge's ribbon...
It doesn't seem like anything resembling it
was turned in at the police station.
Are you all right, Young Mistress?
Come on, cheer up, Chitoge.
We'll help you look again today.
Yeah...
Man, what am I gonna do with you?
All right, today, as a special treat...
I'm going to buy you some ramen!
That limited-edition ramen that you love
came back on the menu lately, right?
When we find your ribbon,
let's all go out for...
No, thanks. I'm not in the mood.
Did she just turn down ramen?
I-I-I mean it's ramen!
She's never done that before, not once!
Dammit, look how meek she's gotten.
It's not a matter of being thrown off...
I just can't stand to see her like this!
Yeah, but what is this?
Maybe I'm imagining
things, but somehow...
...is she like, a stunner now?
No.
Normally, it's hard to forget, but
she's always been a stunner, right?
Somehow, together with that meekness,
she looks more feminine
than usual to me...
Hey, Chitoge!
Wanna arm-wrestle with me?
Why?
Never mind why.
Let's go!
Ready... set...
Master Raku!
I was a fool for getting my faint hopes up.
Are you all right? Master Raku!
Are you okay, Ichijo?
You really are a moron.
Yeah, but if we never do find that
ribbon, what's gonna happen?
Could it be that she'll
stay this way forever?
We just can't seem to find
your ribbon, Young Mistress.
Where else can we look for it?
We might have to
expand our search area.
Look at her, mired in depression again.
I really can't take this anymore.
I wish I could somehow cheer her up,
but that ribbon's nowhere to be found.
Thank you very much!
Like Tachibana said, even if
someone did pick up that ribbon,
it's doubtful that they'd turn it in.
I have no choice.
It's killing me to trick her like this, but...
Hey, Chitoge!
I found it! I found your ribbon!
Whaaat?
No way! Did you really?
Where was it?
Oh, well, it got blown away
into some alley, see...
Here. Try not to lose it again!
Oh, wow!
Thank goodness! Thank you so...
...much.
It smells different.
Smell?
You can tell something like that?
It smells like it's brand-new.
Raku?
My bad! I'm sorry I tried to trick you!
But see... I didn't
mean you any harm.
No... that's okay.
You did that for me, didn't you?
Thanks.
What's up with that?!
The normal you would totally kick
my butt, bury me in the ground,
and stomp off, shouting
all kinds of abuse!
Who the hell are you, anyway?
But no matter how you look at it,
that one's the awful Chitoge, right?
It just might be better
for her to stay this way.
No, no! No way would that be better!
I came this close to being
deceived by a gentle lie!
No choice, then. I'll just
start all over and look for it...
Is that...?
What's the matter?
Hey, Chitoge.
You've got great eyesight, right?
Over there...
That thing caught
in the telephone pole...
Found it!
Found it, found it, found it!
You're not getting away!
Well, I guess I should be glad
that you've cheered up.
Oh, crap!
I've lost sight of it!
But I'm gonna find it, no matter what!
Found it!
I'm gonna catch it this time for sure!
Hold up!
Not there!
N-No way...
Hey, hey.
What's all this crying for, huh?
Raku...
Because... my ribbon...
No, that's the ribbon that I bought.
My ribbon just got
blown away by the wind, too.
You were chasing after the wrong one.
And just now, I picked up your ribbon.
Here.
You can tell by the smell, right?
Go on and make sure.
This is the real deal!
I'm relieved!
I'm so relieved!
Seriously... Next time, be sure to...
Thank you!
Why are you glomming
onto me, moron?!
I'll never lose you again, all right?
Oh, man...
So she's finally back to
being her usual self, huh?
It seems just a little too bad.
What's your problem?
No... this feels more natural, after all.
Hey! Why are you smiling?
Nothing.
Hey, come on!
"Just Testing"
A LITTLE LOVE HERE!!
Confess...
...huh?
No, no, no... Not
happening, not happening!
But...
If... If I did...
I wonder what would happen?
As for how I feel about him... Well...
I like him.
But as for whether or not
I want to date him...
To be honest, I'm not sure.
What is it that I want to do?
How do I want this to end up?
If I did confess my feelings,
would it change anything?
Should I do it? As a test.
Just as a test?
Not for real.
Just see what it's like to say it.
What's going on?
Staring at me like that...
Impossible! Absolutely impossible!
Just the thought of confessing my
feelings to him makes my head explode!
Because if he turns me down,
what am I gonna do?
We still have to keep up
this fake love afterwards!
No way could I take that!
I'd totally die!
But if I really did tell him how I feel,
what kind of look would he give me?
Would he be happy?
Would he be disgusted?
I bet he'd be disgusted!
After all, he doesn't even
see me as the girlfriend type.
Why are you pondering this
so seriously, Chitoge?!
Just testing!
You're only testing out this thought!
No Confession
Can't Say It...
If I can't tell him directly,
why don't I write him a love letter?
That seems like it would be much easier.
Wait, what am I supposed to write?
"I love you, please
go out with me!" I guess?
Yeah...
I...
No Way
Can't Write That
Impossible
It's no good! I can't write that!
Even if I know I'm not
really handing it to him,
it's so embarrassing, I can't take it!
My heart's pounding harder
than I'd ever imagined.
Did all the couples in the world get through
these rituals to become couples?
Aren't they all beyond heroic?
That's it. No letter!
For now, let me practice.
Um...
Let's see...
You see... Um...
"I..."
"I love you! Please go out with me!"
I managed to say it.
Although it was horribly embarrassing,
Well, I guess if I'm
talking to a doll, it's no...
What are you doing, Young Mistress?
It's not...
That was just me practicing!
Actually, I was just
mimicking some TV show!
Anyway, Tsugumi, would you
mind knocking? Knocking!
I did knock, but...
Pardon me.
Confessing your
feelings is hard, after all.
This was just practice, and look at me!
If it were for real...
Totally Impossible (>_<)
Impossible
I wonder how everybody else does it?
Hey, Dad.
Who confessed their
feelings first, you or Mom?
Hmm, let's see.
Well, long story short, it was me, but...
Come to think of it, I never
told you how I met Hana, did I?
Hana and I met when I happened to
be here in Japan on business, you see...
It happened one day when we were trading
gunshots with an enemy organization
in an abandoned factory...
Looks like the pressure's on us, eh?
What do you want to do, Boss?
W-What's up with that woman?
Who the hell is she?
Is she out of her mind?
Walking right into a hail of bullets...
This woman stood right in the crossfire,
and this is what she said...
Which of you people called in
the order for this pizza?
You mean that was Mom?
That's right.
Back then, Hana was
a struggling student, you see.
She was juggling seventeen
part-time jobs just to get by.
Seventeen? What's up with that?
At that moment, Hana was so beautiful.
Looking just like an angel
who'd descended onto a battlefield.
In spite of myself, I was
captivated by the sight of her.
So what did you do after that, Dad?
Right... I proposed.
Will you marry me?
Why would you...?
Immediately afterwards, I got
the living daylights kicked out of me.
Mom's something else, huh?
In other words, it was
love at first sight for me,
but I had my work
cut out for afterwards!
I kept making moves on her,
but she'd always shoot me down,
and in the worst cases I'd end up with
broken bones during the rejection.
No good, this is too
atypical to be of any help.
But the thing is, despite all that,
I couldn't stand not to tell her how I felt.
That's how alluring she was to me.
I was sure she was the one
I was destined to be with.
So Dad was really in love with Mom.
I wonder if I can
pull that off just like he did?
It doesn't seem like I can even pretend
to confess my feelings for him, so...
Can I really tell him that I love him?
Hey, Chitoge! Ahead of you!
Wound
What a child.
Oh, you shut up! Just leave me alone!
Spacing out and crashing into a sign...
How scatterbrained is that, anyway?
Oh, back off.
Something on your mind?
Lately you've been brooding over
something, am I right?
If there's something I can do,
I wouldn't mind being
your sounding board.
He's been worried about me...
That kind of makes me happy.
No, no, I'm fine.
Is that right?
Right now, we might have
the tiniest bit of chemistry.
No, no... is that
a reason to confess?
Impossible!
But if you're in love with him,
that's what you should do!
If you do it, something might change.
Do you really love him?
This might be your chance!
I don't know!
But...
Now that I think of it...
Since you came to Japan,
and we started
pretending to be dating...
It's already been
more than a year, huh?
Amazing, huh? I'm used to it now.
The fact that I'm used to such
an abnormal situation scares me.
What's up with that? Are you
complaining about the status quo?
No, nothing like that.
It just blows my mind, that's all.
So much happened, huh?
Getting clobbered by you,
clobbered by you, clobbered by you...
Hey, you! It was all
your fault, you know!
It was mostly beyond
my control, remember?
Anyway, how about you?
I mean, you were so pissed
about this whole thing...
But of course I'd resign myself!
Since I'm an adult.
Where's this adult you're talking about?
Can't you see the lady before your eyes?
Nope, not seeing her!
I'm gonna clobber you.
Hey, but you don't
mind me now, right?
Well, but we still have more than halfway
to go before we graduate, you know!
Well, no use thinking about
what's gonna happen in the future.
Let's just take our time with this.
We'll figure it out somehow!
Take our time, huh?
Right.
It's not like I have to
do it right this minute!
What are you talking about?
That's private!
That's right...
I want to spend more time with him.
Right now, that's
how I feel towards him.
Why don't we head back now?
Yeah.
If my feelings of love
for this guy don't change,
then someday I'll want to
confess to him like my dad did.
If that day ever comes...
Hey, Raku!
Never mind, it's nothing.
What's up with you, anyway?
Actually, it wasn't nothing.
Shall I treat you to some ramen today?
Me, treat lowly you?
What's the matter with you?
You got a fever or something?
Wh-Why would your
mind go there, huh?
Because normally, that would
never happen in a million...
Why, you... shut up!