23rd - Summer Break
25th - Summer School Starts
x becomes 4. Substitute this value in the
formula to calculate the value of y.
Now you can derive the coordinates at the
top, enabling you to draw a graph.
31st - Gala Concert
You're totally distracted!
I'm doing what I'm supposed to.
You were playing reluctantly! It
sounded like your heart wasn't in it!
Listen... Do we have to play
this piece for the gala concert?
What's that? Is there a problem?
For a gala concert, we should be
playing something more glamorous.
Let's change it to
something more major...
No way! This is the
song I want to play.
Don't worry, don't worry. If you and I
play it, it will sound glamorous enough.
I wonder why you're
so reluctant to play it?
When the score was overflowing
with so much love for you?
Kreisler's... Love's Joy.
Love's... Sorrow.
Love's Sorrow, the companion piece to Love's
Joy by Kreisler, was written for the violin.
There's a piano version of this
song arranged by Rachmaninoff.
Huh? Did I stick it here?
Falling asleep under the piano again...
You're going to catch a cold.
You've gotten heavy, haven't you?
Kousei...
This is your punishment.
The piano isn't responding to you, is it?
I wish you would just die.
I can't hear! Help me, Mom!
I wonder why you're
so reluctant to play it?
Why? Because it reminds me of my mother.
Hiroko-san, I've got to practice...
No sweat, no sweat! It's good to have
a change of scenery, to take a breather!
Cotton candy! Frappes!
Hey, don't get lost on me.
Rachmaninoff's Love's Sorrow.
Saki used to play that all the
time since we were students.
She used to play it a lot as a lullaby.
This piece just reeks too much of my mom.
So raw... and vivid... It closes in on me...
My mother must've
had despised me, right?
No mother on earth
despises her own child.
That day...
That was the moment you grew up,
both as a person and as a pianist.
There's no way that
wouldn't make Saki happy.
There you are! Sorry!
But it is just a little
bit sad, you know.
To see your kid grow away from you...
My mom...
Do you think she'll forgive me?
For trying so hard to forget all about her?
Is it all right for me
to play the piano?
If that's how you feel, play.
If there's something holding you
back, then play with conviction,
and try to hear Saki's voice.
Voice...
"Don't sit there brooding over ridiculous matters,
it's high time you manned up!"
Play. You and I are
pianists, you know.
A candy apple.
You don't like candy apples?
It's not like that. It's just that
I've never had one before...
Don't cry! I'll eat it!
I'll eat it, okay? Thanks!
Am I being too harsh with
him? But he's got to play.
So that he can
mature as a pianist...
So that he can say goodbye.
Jeez!
31st - Gala Concert
Look how late it is!
Yeah, because you
wouldn't give up. What a baby!
What about you, you
kept whining about the piece!
Since we're so late coming home,
I wonder if your folks are mad...
Hey, look up there! At the sky!
You're ignoring me?
The stars are so beautiful.
It's like the stars are speaking to us!
Twinkle, twinkle, little star,
how I wonder what you are.
Up above the world so high,
like a diamond in the sky.
Twinkle, twinkle, little star,
how I wonder what you are.
A cake shop?
I'm home!
Hold on a sec!
I'll be heading home now.
What do you want with my daughter?
Uh... I...
Arima-kun?
Hey, if it isn't Arima-kun!
These are just leftovers,
but have your fill, all right?
Th-Thank you very much!
We've got some test samples, too, right?
Oh, but I've already had more than enough...
My parents are fans of yours.
When I was little, they
came to hear you a lot.
I heard all about it, Arima-kun!
You shouldn't abort your performances.
That's like flushing all your
struggles till now down the drain!
It's like baking a
moist sponge cake,
only for it to be totally ruined
by some horrible-tasting cream!
Sorry about that.
But I like a young man
who does the unheard-of!
Good for you!
Once it's inside your stomach,
there's no difference.
Since the ingredients are all the same.
Thank you very much!
Want to see some pictures of
Kaori back in grade school?
She was so adorable!
We have some from
kindergarten, too!
Don't show him!
Here, for your folks.
Thank you very much. And
thank you for all the cake.
We'll be going to the gala
concert to cheer you on.
Good luck!
Right, I'll do my best.
I'll walk you to the street.
So that's Arima-kun, huh?
He's got manners, and he's
a good kid, don't you think?
Yes...
Really! They even hauled out
the pictures of me as a newborn!
Stark naked, no less! I can
never get married now!
You sure have cheerful parents.
My mom's always stuffing
starving dogs with food.
Starving?
Huh?
Hey, did you get taller?
Huh? I don't know...
Oh, I see. It's because you're
not looking down anymore.
Anyway, it sure is hot this year.
A meaningless conversation.
Familiar scenery.
It's so humid! It's so deplorable,
it's really muggy, don't you think?
Even so, the reason I remember
it so well is probably...
Oh, but I do like summer
because there are fireworks.
...I'm sure...
...because of that summer night.
31st - Gala Concert
I...told...you!
Make that part flow more elegantly!
But the accompanist can't
just ignore instructions!
Or else the violin won't stand out.
It will too stand out!
Because I'm gonna be playing it!
It's peaceful.
You're so arrogant!
Follow what I'm doing!
Where's my green tea
and red bean shaved ice?
It's not that simple!
You runaway horse!
Huh? I'm eating it.
You monster!
That was my shaved ice! I've had enough!
I don't want to go to summer school!
I want to play!
I want to go to the festival!
I want to watch fireworks!
It's peaceful.
Done!
The year's first fireworks!
So pretty!
You sure we won't get caught?
Sneaking into the pool area
and lighting firecrackers...
Oh, no worries!
I mean, the teachers have
all gone home anyway.
And as for water, we've got a
whole boatload at our disposal!
But lay off the rockets, okay?
Kashiwagi-san?
Oh, crap! Summer
school again tomorrow!
Well, just suck it up.
It's your fault for being a moron.
Shut up, you lousy
scholarship student!
What are you two gonna do?
I mean high school. You're not
attending summer school,
so does that mean you two
are on the music college track?
I'm...
...not even thinking about the future yet.
For now, let me just say that I'm
going to rock the audience at the gala,
and claim the spotlight!
Because we're the
almighty duo, after all!
That's the spirit,
that's the spirit!
So glorious!
Yeah... those two look great together.
What are you gaping at?
Why? Why?
It's totally dark at the bottom...
I can't hear a sound...
It's like my...
Help me... please help me.
I can't hear anything.
It's dark... it's dark...
The fact that you can't
hear the notes means...
...that you're not bound
by auditory sounds, I think.
Not bound by sound?
The images you have within you.
The sounds that rise up
from the bottom of your soul...
You've been letting them
override all else without realizing it.
The sounds within you,
the imagined scenery...
Wasn't there ever a
moment when you sensed...
the notes suffused
with your desires and emotions?
Losing the ability to hear the
notes. I'm sure that that's a gift.
A gift?
Close your eyes, cover your ears,
and play as you feel for now.
You have the technical
ability to pull that off.
The ability to trace the sounds within
you, the sounds you imagine.
And those are the memories Saki left you...
Did you get taller?
Oh, I see.
It's because you're not
looking down anymore.
It's because you're
looking up now.
Kousei!
Kousei...
He's alive!
He's in pain!
That's proof that he's alive!
How could you...?
How could you drown in such a shallow pool?
Everyone's gonna blame me!
He freakin' slammed his head
right into his savior's face.
Not bad.
Is it because it's a pool?
Is it because the moon's out?
Maybe... just maybe, the light can
reach even the bottom of a dark ocean.
31st - Gala Concert
Miyazono-san's playing, too, right?
Yeah, that kid who
stopped playing midway.
The people who run this
are reckless for sure.
I think she'll actually
make an impact. Can't wait.
Wonder if she'll play it right today?
She'll probably go bonkers again.
Well, I came today just to see her.
Curse
All right! There's nobody
I know around here.
Emi?
Aren't you going to take your seat?
Ms. Ochiai?
Uh... did you call me Emi?
I'm the one who told you about
Arima-kun being an accompanist today.
N-N-N-Not that I came here to see Arima...
I'm just here to enjoy some violin music...
Here's your program.
Let's go. It'll be starting soon.
You witch!
No judging at gala concerts, so we can
just sit back and enjoy ourselves.
With this level of talent, we can certainly
afford to listen like everyone else...
Now then, is it almost
time for my favorite?
Kaori Miyazono
Sumitani Junior Highschool
What does she think she's doing?
The violinist a no-show?
That's just insane!
Who is she, Michelangeli? Pogoreli?
The show's started.
Kao-chan's not here yet?
What am I supposed to do?
Is Kaori Miyazono this unpredictable?
I've been calling her cell,
but she's totally not picking up.
Watari-kun
This is serious. I can't...
Let's go in and get prepared.
So we'll be ready whenever
Miyazono does show up.
Please, keep calling Miyazono's cell.
Right! Onee-sama!
I'm counting on you.
Ma'am!
Good luck!
What should we do?
I'll go ask if they'll move
you guys down in the order.
Since it's a gala concert, they
might be a little more flexible.
As long as we can get
the performers to agree...
We can wait on Miyazono
till the last possible second.
Why...
If that doesn't pan out,
we'll just have to forget it.
Yes... you're right.
But why?
What will you do?
This is the song I want to play!
Weren't you looking
forward to this?
I was an idiot for
getting carried away.
It's almost Kaori Miyazono's turn.
Wonder what she's going to do this time?
It's been a while since
I've felt this excited.
That's unacceptable.
Please! She's on a bus
right now, on her way here!
Be that as it may,
I don't have the authority to...
What's going on?
Miike-kun?
Miike-kun... He's the final
act of the junior high division?
That's right, being that
he won the competition.
Nice timing!
Sorry, but could you
let them play after you?
Our violinist's running late.
Running late?
Her name's Kaori Miyazono.
I'm sure she'll be here soon.
You think you could
let her play after you?
Miyazono-san's playing, too, right?
Can't wait!
Absolutely not.
The final act of this gala concert...
The starring role... it's mine.
Well, of course it is.
It is your moment of triumph, after all.
We only have ourselves to blame.
I apologize for being so presumptuous.
Looks like we're going
to have to withdraw.
A-Anyway,
it's her own fault for being
late on a day like this.
Her playing's such a mess, no wonder
her lifestyle's all messed up too.
She thinks she's special just because
the audience kind of liked her,
so she shows up late
without a second thought!
You don't have to go that far...
But isn't that a fact?
The music is written in the score.
What she produces is disastrous.
It's not music or anything at all!
You little brat, who are
you to talk like that?
All right, then. Sorry for causing
a disturbance before you perform.
Come on, Kousei,
aren't you pissed at all?
He insulted your partner!
Let's go by the program.
Please perform the final act of
the junior high division, Miike-san.
However...
The spotlight!
Today's spotlight belongs to us.
The promoters' choice for the junior
high division, Ms. Kaori Miyazono.
Here she comes!
At last.
It's Miyazono.
She got here in time?
It's Kaori Miyazono.
Isn't he the accompanist?
Where's the violinist?
Where's Miyazono-san?
Arima, surely you're not playing alone...?
Unprecedented.
Kousei...
Twinkle Little Star
Episode 13
Love's Sadness
Watch Again Next Week!
Two People on a Bike is Forbidden By Law