Wh-Who are you...
I'll just tell you.
It's Megumu-san.
Trip.
Why did you tell him, Ruri-chan?!
I thought it'd be better if
we didn't let this drag out.
Megumu, why are you...
My sisters came and are staying nearby,
so they snuck into our place and
switched all my clothes for girls clothes...
Oh, I see.
Well, I'm sorry for worrying you, anyway.
No, I'm glad you're okay.
If Her Flag Breaks
Flag 7
I Learned Something Amazing. I'll Hide Myself Before I can be Erased
So you agreed to be brother and sister...
That's right.
I'm now Souta-oniichan's little sister.
That's nice!
Little sisters are nice!
I want one, too!
What are you doing?
No!
It's a bad thing to care more about
little sisters than older ones!
You like little sisters better?!
You traitor!
Hey, Okiku-nee, calm down!
Indeed.
If you wanted a little sister that badly,
why not just be with
your little android sister right here.
Not you, too, Ruri-chan!
Don't make things worse!
I'm sorry.
It doesn't really matter how
happy I am to have a brother if
I'm just going to hurt his
older sister in the process...
If you're my brother's little sister,
then you're his older sister's little sister.
That's why I need to be
the older sister here,
and recognize you as the little
sister of my younger brother.
Hug, hug, hug.
So I'd like to take Kurumiko back with
us to Hatagaya Academy, if possible.
Well, let's see...
Little Souta's asking.
Do something for us, Little Mimori.
I'm not taking no for an answer.
When did you start spoiling him?!
Please, President...
Hatate-kun...
She's the chairwoman's granddaughter,
so she's always pulling a lot of stuff,
but that sometimes comes in handy.
Yeah, but...
Sorry for introducing myself so late.
Here's a present for you.
Thank you.
What? This doesn't taste like anything!
Well, I guess we'll have to
use "give and take" here.
Hm... As compensation, how about
during tomorrow's free period,
Souta goes on a date with you?
A-A date?!
Now you're just making light of me.
A date with Seiteikouji
Mimori doesn't come cheap!
Guess you'll just have
to buy her a juice box.
A date with me's worth less than a juice box?!
A date'll be fine. I want the date.
I've kind of wanted some
good summer memories.
Guess it's settled, then.
Huh? Wait...
Um...
Come on...
If you fall in love with me,
Hatate, it's not my fault.
Roar! Gawo!
What's wrong?
You know it's not like I'm really
excited because it's our first date.
Oh, right.
That's fine.
R-Really?
Okay, let's go.
There's a beautiful stream
deep in the forest.
Oh, right.
That's cold!
It's kind of nice to be
with a girl whose flag I
can't get in an instant.
I'm boring, aren't I?
Huh?
Don't worry about it.
I know myself.
No normal guy would want
to go on a date with me.
Sorry for making you spend time with me.
I'll do what I can for Kurumiko-kun.
I don't really dislike you or anything.
You're kind.
I'm a loud person.
I know I'm not really that girly.
But I can't stop being who I am,
nor do I want to.
That's because I'm Seiteikouji Mimori.
Is something wrong?
It feels like
you're living earnestly, unlike me.
Hm?
You might cause a lot of ruckus,
but you're just enjoying life.
You really stand out to me,
since I've given up on everything.
Mimori,
I'm envious of you.
You shouldn't be.
I mean, everyone thinks you're
far better than I am.
You might always be causing trouble,
but that means you're living life to the
fullest, standing out to everyone.
That's why you should stay the way you are.
But I wonder if
I'm really here,
if I'm really living.
You're at the center of everyone.
That's something to be proud of,
and I'm sure everyone loves you.
That's what it means to be alive, isn't it?
Don't make that face.
You're alive, too.
Everyone alive must become happy.
Hatate-kun, I'll...
I'll make you happy.
Is this a flag, too?
I...
I'll do what I can to help you.
I mean... You can depend on me. Yeah.
If everyone turns against you,
I'll be there for you, Souta-kun.
I'm sorry. I called you by your name.
It's fine. I don't really mind.
Really?!
I mean, really?
Cool.
Souta-kun. Souta-kun.
I'll take care of Kurumiko-kun, okay?
I'll...
I'll do what I can for you.
Okay, everyone, get on the bus.
Stay in line and don't fight.
I see...
I'm sorry.
I told you to come, and then...
Hatate-kun isn't the one at fault.
I wasn't able to do anything...
I'm sad I'll have to be away from you,
but our hearts will be together.
Right?
Yeah.
I'm glad we were just able to meet
and become brother and sister.
Kurumiko...
Souta-kun, the beach was fun, wasn't it?
Y-Yeah.
I guess so.
I want to go again with you.
If Souta's going, I'm going, too.
Me, too.
W-Well, if everyone's going,
I guess I'll go, too.
Yeah.
I guess we can go if we
don't have to go to the sea.
What does that mean?
Welcome back.
Huh? Kurumiko?
Why are you here?
A nice girl brought me.
Hello there.
Daimyouzamurai Mei.
What's going on?
I just altered the
school's data, that's all.
I didn't think of that!
You're useless when it matters.
I did my best!
How mean!
So why are the student council
president and Granny here?
That's because we're going to
live here at Quest Dorm, too.
We already completed the paperwork.
What was that?!
Are you trying to get me to
owe you a favor?
Not really.
I just didn't like what was
happening, is all.
Huh?
I'm glad everyone's here.
Kurumiko-chan, the
student council president,
Granny, and Mei! All four
of you are moving in!
Why me?
I have no plans on getting
friendly with you all.
Are you leaving?
I'd like it if a nice girl
like you was around...
I'll live here, too.
Okay, then let's sleep together tonight.
Wait. Why?
I won't be able to sleep by myself.
Just ask Hatate Souta for—
Fine. Just today.
She doesn't look it, but she was easy.
Okay, I'm off.
Tell me, Daimyouzamurai... You—
Call me Mei.
You can see flags, right?
Yes, but my power is
artificial and limited.
However, you're different.
The ability to alter flags...
You were given that power by the sacraments.
Sacrament?
You mean Sakura?
It's something which a human would
normally never be able to possess.
A power which allows one
to alter fate itself.
The Angel Boat.
What's that?
It travels all water in existence,
a boat of fate capable of
controlling all there is.
You have a power on that level, Hatate Souta,
and what do you wish to do with it?
First, I'd like to rid
myself of this death flag.
First?
Yes.
The second is a request from Sakura,
I guess.
I will give you my power.
And in exchange,
you must learn the ultimate
truth of this world.
The ultimate truth of this world?
I see.
So that's it.
Huh? You know something?
Those who seek will find happiness,
for you learn the most when you
realize how little you know.
Very well.
Phase shift, clear.
Spacial link, clear.
Gate release.
I'll shall show you
part of the truth of this world.
We didn't go anywhere?
Hey, wait. Mei!
We're in the Hatagaya
Academy building, right?
What are you trying to do?
You'll understand soon.
S-Sorry.
Okiku-nee?
What's up with you?
Another first year trying to
do something to Kikuno?
R-Rin-kun...
How dare you?
I never said you could call me by my name.
Huh? What's going on?
Sorry about my friend.
It seems we mistook you for someone else.
I see.
Be careful.
It seems the girls in this world
don't know you.
This world...
In order to put it into
something you'd understand...
We're on an Earth from a parallel universe.
Parallel universe?
The Council of the Seven
Virtues watches the worlds.
The Council of the Seven Virtues?
Right now we're currently watching
the Sacraments and you,
Hatate Souta, the closest.
It is my job to figure out if
you will bring harm to the worlds.
I couldn't...
Your power is far greater than you realize.
We're...
Nanami...
No...
This is...
We're on the Premium Ambriel...
I... I see.
In this world, I...
You're not going to run?
Everyone died.
If I'm going to be alone,
then I might as well...
Wh-What are you doing?
You might think it's
better to die here, but...
Then...
I still want you to live.
You will meet people.
People who will be happy you lived.
Just like I
met everyone at Quest Dorm.
Huh?
M-Miyuki-sensei?
I didn't think I'd hear about Quest Dorm here.
Huh?
Just a little before the Second World War,
my great grandfather went
missing underground there.
Under Quest Dorm?
Could that be...
Sorry, who's you great grandfather?
I think his name was Hatate Souta.
I forgot to mention it,
but my name is Hatate Miyuki.
Crap.
Miyuki-san!
I'm fine.
I have a reason to live now!
That's the main character flag...
Your words have given me power,
and I just like you, I...
Where am I...
This is the world you started in.
I see.
I'm back...
That world will revolve
around Miyuki MacKenzie, no,
Hatate Miyuki.
That's right, as the main character.
You have an enormous power,
capable of altering they
very core of a world.
And using that power, you...
Huh? Is something wrong?
You look pale.
I'm fine.
I'll be fine, after I rest a little.
Huh?
I finally got closer to the ultimate
truth of the world, and I...
Wait...
Is the activated death flag in
you making you say all of that?
At this rate, he's going to...
I guess I'll have to do it!
This is death...
This is fear!
The truth behind the power to change flags.
You must bear all the fate in the world by yourself.
What despair!
I'm afraid!
Afraid! Afraid!
But he's born this burden for so long...
I won't let him die!
This person will save
the Council of the Seven Virtues, and the world!
Please! Mother! Father!
Everyone! Help me!
I've only delayed its activation temporarily.
You're so weak, so naïve, but
I'm so proud I saved you.
I didn't know your warmth
could be so endearing.
The Sacraments!
I'm sorry.
I can't have you doing all of this.
The apostles of the seven virtues
know too many things
that he can't be allowed to know.
I'm sorry. I really am.
He will find the ultimate truth
of the world on his own.
Hm? Are you awake?
Mei?
Wait. Why are you...
I don't know...
The next thing I knew I was...
What are you...
Complete
The conquest completed flag?
What are you saying?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Mei, can you see flags?
What about the Council of the Seven Virtues?
Flags? The Council of the Seven Virtues?
Her memory's
gone?
Roar! Gawo!
You're half-Japanese, right, Miyuki-sensei?
It turns out I am.
I'm not sure why you said
"it turns out," but whatever.
There's a big difference between you and me,
even though we're both half-Japanese.
I'm sure your boobs will get bigger.
I was talking about our height!
Kids grow fast, so I'm sure you'll look
different by the start of summer break.
That's the "I'm totally
not getting bigger" flag!
Flag 8
Yellow blue green. Pink yellow pink green blue?
Roar! Gawo!
If Her Flag Breaks
Hope you watch next time.
Illustration: Mizu Asato