Thanks to you, I've awakened.
This time for sure, see.
So now I have a favor
to ask of my partner.
Do you mind?
Let's hear it.
Could you buy me
just a little bit of time?
There's something I want to try out.
All right. I'll see what I can do.
But...
I can't sustain it for too long.
Well, well, Glühen Rose,
what are you doing here by yourself?
Never Back Down
Surely you're not planning
to take us on alone?
Is that a problem?
I see we're being grossly
underestimated.
Yes... What a sad thought, Shenyun.
If I were you, I wouldn't
underestimate me too much, either!
Burst into bloom, Ranunculus!
I see.
So she was after the talismans.
But are you sure about this?
Can you protect your partner
while you're focusing on that move?
I won't let you get in Ayato's way!
All right, then what do you say to this?
Go!
So it's an illusion!
I see.
Letting the illusion go past
is a wise way to endure them.
All right, then I'll take this
opportunity to target your partner.
Sorry...
Damn!
Of course it hurts.
That's where I got a direct hit on you
with my Gossamer Attack earlier.
You know how you should be aware
of your opponent's breathing
and smallest gestures during a battle?
You expand your senses to your
surroundings, not only your opponent.
Well, under the Amagiri Shinmei Style,
we call this state Vijñāna.
Vijñāna...
Since humans tend to hit a wall
when their outlook grows narrow,
it's important to look at all kinds of things
from all kinds of angles.
Why didn't you go after my badge?
My aim was a little off, that's all.
I see!
Then I'm going to make you regret it!
Come out...
Semiserrata!
You're blowing yourself up?!
I really wanted to keep this
under wraps a little longer, but...
So you can resist your own powers.
Really, now, I'm astonished!
The rumors don't
do you justice, Glühen Rose.
You were too careless
just now, Shenhua.
I'm sorry, Shenyun.
What do you say
we wrap this up now?
I do need to thank you for making me
break out in a cold sweat.
What's wrong, Glühen Rose?!
Aren't you going to fight back?!
What a one-sided attack!
B-But...
since she's unable to move,
shouldn't she just target her badge?
This is way too...
Looks like she's trying to win
by rendering her unconscious.
But I can see that Shenyun is holding back
somewhat in her attack.
Apparently, she doesn't intend
to let her black out so easily.
You love to feel pain, don't you?!
Ayato!
When you're in trouble,
you should lean on someone else.
Aside from me, I'm sure there are other
people who'd help you out.
Well, then,
who's going to protect you?
Look at you now!
Why don't we end this now,
Glühen Rose?!
What's going on?
Sorry to keep you waiting, Julis.
You're late, Ayato!
Were you able to break
the seal completely?
No. I just managed to get
to the second level, I think.
And it's not like it gave me
a power-up or anything.
But this amount of Prana...
It's just that I can store
all my leaked Prana internally now.
But I think it's extended
my limit by that much.
How long do you think you'll last?
Let's see...
Probably over an hour.
I see. In that case,
can I leave the rest to you?
To be honest,
I've reached my own limit.
Sure.
You two are one surprise
after another, aren't you?
Now, then...
All right.
Impossible... you can see them, then?
In that case...
What do say to this?!
What the...
Amagiri Shinmei Style
Hidden Technique...
Banish Evil Spirits...
No way...
Now that it's come to this...
That's an explosive sphere woven
from all the talismans I had!
Hope you enjoy it!
Needless to say, this is an illusion.
Only one is genuine.
Well, I'm sure you can
see right through them now...
But what about this one?
Ayato! Don't worry about me!
Just focus on getting her!
Would you mind keeping quiet
for a minute, Glühen Rose?!
Ayato!
True to form to the bitter end,
huh, Shenyun Li?
That's right!
That's what I like to see, Murakumo!
Both of you can just get blasted to hell!
There's no need to dodge.
What the...
I-Impossible...
I have to say,
you did piss me off a little.
So at least let me do that.
Shenyun Li has lost consciousness!
Therefore, Ayato Amagiri and
Julis-Alexia von Riessfeld are your winners!
Now that was an enjoyable match!
Ayato Amagiri...
I would be thrilled to meet you.
Congratulations, Your Highness!
Mr. Amagiri!
You were totally, totally amazing!
I was so excited!
Thanks, Flora.
Calm down a bit, Flora.
I see you're as spunky as usual, Flora.
That sets my mind at ease.
Did you know Flora from before, Claudia?
Yes, I've met her as Julis's
maid-in-waiting several times.
Lady Enfield is always so kind!
- I see.
- Now, then...
Congratulations to you both
on reaching the semifinals.
Seidoukan Academy has more points
than we'd projected.
As a representative of the school,
I'd like to express my joy and gratitude.
Hey, it's nothing
you need to thank us for.
Of course,
I'd like to express my heartfelt
congratulations and gratitude to you,
not just as a representative of the school,
but personally, as well.
Now, then, please come
to my room tonight.
- Come along!
- H-Hey, wait!
Right, then! Away we go!
H-Hold up!
What kind of proposition
is that, all of a sudden?!
In order to restore Ayato's vitality
before tomorrow's semifinal match,
I've prepared to offer him
some hospitality.
Don't just drag him away like that!
Ayato and I are going to discuss
our strategy for tomorrow!
No, no, what Ayato needs
right now is rest!
- No way! Strategy meeting!
- It's not fair, Julis!
H-Hey, come on... both of you!
This year's Festa has a greater
popularity than we expected.
At this point,
we've already surpassed last year's figures
for both the box office and attendance.
Permitting Arlequint's surrogates
to compete was a masterstroke!
Haruka's younger brother, huh?
What?
No, never mind.
Thank you for your report.
Excuse me, sir.
Now, then...
On to the semifinals!
What is that?
This is my good luck charm.
It's a magical ticket that will
grant you any wish you desire.
How wonderful!
Oh, then were you just wishing
for victory in today's match?
No.
This is just a good luck charm.
Today's victory is something you
and I are going to achieve on our own.
You're right.
Sorry about that.
Kirin?
Uh, yes? What is it?
Thank you.
What? Wh-What's this, all of a sudden?
I only made it this far because of you.
I'm grateful for that.
P-Please! Don't say things like that!
I'm the one
who should be thanking you.
Because my wish to save
my father is about to come true.
Your father...
This is something
I want you to know, Kirin.
Yes?
My father lost most of his body
in an accident at the lab where he worked.
Fortunately, his brain was unscathed,
so now he's hooked up to the nerve center
in the workshop he built at home.
You don't have to feel bad for him.
Now that he's free to research
what he wants to,
my father says he's happier.
What he wants to?
Making guns for me.
For you, Saya?
That's right.
So in a way, what Camilla Pareto said
was on the mark.
Because this power wasn't created
for others, but for me alone.
And that's precisely why I can't forgive
anyone who would reject that notion.
Hey, there, girls!
Long time no see!
What do you want?
Oh, my, that's pretty cold!
Camilla says there's something she just
has to tell you before the match, so...
It's been a long time, Saya Sasamiya.
What can I say? It seems
that I misread you slightly,
so I thought I'd tell you.
Misread me?
Yes, I realized it when I saw your match.
When viewed separately,
those Luxes of yours are all defective.
But when you look at them,
including yourself, as a single weapon,
I must admit
that they're without peer.
Then...
However...
That actually means they're prone
to causing more organic instability.
Like I said, they're not
for actual combat.
Then, I'll make you acknowledge them
by taking out your clones.
That's impossible.
S-Saya!
That said...
If, by any chance,
you two should win,
I'll take back
what I said the other day.
Ferrovius and I have poured
all the technology we've developed
into AR-D and RM-C's equipment.
So if you do manage to defeat them,
I can't say your Luxes
aren't suited for actual combat.
See ya!
Let's go, Kirin.
Right!
Listen to me!
We're going to grant you...
a one-minute grace period today, too!
There it is! He said it again!
AR-D's trademark declaration!
After making this same declaration
in all of their matches,
they've won within
approximately one minute!
A team that's reached the quarterfinals
and is also riding a wave of momentum...
Let's see if the Sasamiya-Toudou duo
can hold its own here, too!
- Kirin, I'm leaving that one to you.
- Right.
You show them a thing or two.
Phoenix Festa Semifinals,
Match #1...
Battle start!
Kirin Toudou... here I go!
Kirin Toudou, huh?
What about it?
If your intent is to breach
my defensive barrier,
then it would make sense for Saya Sasamiya
to take me on with her Lux.
This is just my advice.
You can switch now, or else
launch a two-pronged attack—
Then...
Would you like to try me?
Whether or not this Senbakiri
and I are no match for you...
Please find out yourself.
Very well. If you insist,
then go ahead and try it.
It's futile.
So long as you're human, you can never
hope to surpass me in terms of reflexes.
I see, now it's clear.
That's enough for me.
Didn't you hear me say
it was futile?
What?!
Whoa, whoa!
How incredible is that?!
At last, at last,
AR-D has come under attack
for the first time in this tournament!
Ridiculous... It's not possible!
Please take back what you said earlier.
What?
And let's fight fair and square.
What's that supposed to mean?
Please don't mock us...
That's what I mean.
If you're planning
to keep that up until the end...
I'll put an end to it with my next strike.
C-Can you believe it?!
Now AR-D's on the attack!
It's been 56 seconds since his
declaration! The minute isn't up yet!
Splendid!
As far as this matter is concerned,
you've defeated me soundly.
Allow me to retract what I said!
If you don't mind, I'd like you to explain
to me what kind of technique that was.
It worked because you're a machine.
What does that mean?
You used my data and movements
to predict how I'd attack,
and threw up that
defensive barrier, didn't you?
Yes, that's exactly right.
The Toudou Style features a technique
in which you lead your opponent on
by reading the breathing,
sight lines, distance
and muscle movements.
When two experienced
swordsmen meet in battle,
they try to get various reads
on each other in a split second.
But because you're a machine, you tend
to merely react to my movements.
In other words, your lack
of combat experience is fatal!
That's my Kirin.
I don't understand it.
The fact that you didn't launch
a single attack during this minute.
Wouldn't it be fair to say
that you're the ones mocking us?
All I wanted was to fight you
when you were going all-out.
Otherwise...
it would be pointless for me.
41-type Lux, Twin Particle Cannons,
Waldenholt!
Burst.
U-Unbelievable!
A single shot from Sasamiya ends
in a clean hit against RM-C!
As you can see, I'm ready to go, too.
Give me your best shot.
Both Lady Sasamiya
and Lady Toudou are amazing!
Hey.
Now, then, Ayato,
if you're spent from fighting,
come to my room...
Just you and me...
- Kaboom!
- Oh, my!
This is how you greedily usurp
what little screen time Enfield has...
Episode 17
The Tyrant’s Puppet Strings
As Ayato's childhood friend,
I'm the true heroine!