Soccer Tournament
Go, 1-6!
Okay! Go, class 3!
Go, go, go!
There's no one in front of the goal!
Oh—
I am Gouda Takeo.
I will protect this goal!
Takeo's the goalkeeper? That's cheating!
I can barely see the goal!
He's way too quick!
Crap!
His throw is like a speeding bullet!
My Grades
The guys are advancing to the finals!
Wow!
Won't they be up against third-years?
I'm totally intimidated by that goalkeeper.
He's so tall, he's screwing up my perspective.
I doubt we can get any shots past him.
First Half 0-0
Second Half 1-0
Congratulations, class 1-6.
Takeo, we did it!
Well, we'd already given up
before the fight even began.
Using Gouda is cheating...
It's thanks to you, Takeo!
Nah, we all did this.
Congrats, guys!
Congrats!
Takeo-kun, congratulations!
Yamato...
I wonder what she's up to.
I hope she's okay.
You Have A New Message
View
Oh.
Takeo-kun, how are you?
I'm fine.
I'm going skating with friends.
If you aren't too busy, want to
join us, with your friends?
Guess she's fine.
Yamato, I'm fine, too.
Who wants to come with me today, to go
skating with Yamato and her friends?
Me, me, me!
You just went!
It's my turn!
I have a shift,
but I'll just call in sick.
I'll go, too!
Me, too.
I don't like cold places.
It'll be fine.
I've never skated before.
Me, neither.
Takeo-kun!
I'm free.
Five buddies can come along.
Is that okay?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
No, I wasn't waiting long.
So this is what it's like...
Triple Axel
leading into
an Ina Bauer.
Wow, who is that guy?
Did he just do an axel?
Oh, there he goes again.
I feel like I'm watching human
evolution on fast-forward.
Takeo-kun!
You can hang on to me.
Eh? Okay.
Take it slow, Yamato.
Takeo-kun, this is your first time, right?
Why are you so good at it?
Put one foot out at a time.
So warm!
Want anything to drink?
I'll go buy something.
Hmm, what do they have?
Oh, let's just go together.
Yeah?
Come on!
scritch scritch
What's wrong?
My thighs are all itchy because
we switched here, where it's really
warm, and my blood got flowing.
I love her.
Takeo, I thought I saw you accept
a business card earlier.
Oh, yeah.
Someone was trying to recruit him.
Crap, that's unbelievable!
Yeah, back there, what you did was unreal!
Oh, that was just a coincidence.
I was turning around, when I lost my balance.
Huh?
That was fun!
I'm sorry I was late today.
I had to retake a kanji test.
You aren't good at kanji?
No, I am, actually.
But I skipped a question in the middle,
so all my answers were off by one,
so I lost all my points.
You didn't notice the extra
answer space at the end?
I did, but I just thought it was extra.
Guess you didn't think too hard about it.
No, I didn't.
Oh, but Rinko's pretty good at school.
Yeah, she's a good student.
She's one of the smart ones.
I see.
Suna's good, too.
Oh, I knew it!
Stop it.
I'm just normal.
What about you, Takeo-kun?
I'm below average.
Oh, okay.
Below average, huh?
I might be even lower than that.
Today, we had a soccer tournament.
Takeo was the goalkeeper, so we won
without getting scored on at all!
Wow!
Nice, I wish I'd seen that.
I can see why.
I'd have thought you were super cool.
Are you good at all sports, Takeo-kun?
He sucks at basketball.
Yeah, horrible.
He falls for all the fakes.
He sure does!
He sucks at dance, too.
He does!
Every step he takes is huge!
Nice...
Come to think of it,
at the last gym class...
I wish we were in the same school.
Later!
If we were in the same school, huh?
Takeo-kun, where are you going for college?
I don't know.
I haven't given it much thought.
What about you, Yamato?
I've been considering Murasakifuji University,
but if you're going to college,
maybe I'll change my mind.
I want to attend the same college as you!
The same college...
Then I can watch you being badass all the time.
Oh, but Rinko's pretty good at school.
Yamato, you don't need to change
what college you want attend.
Huh? But...
I just have to study.
I'll study to catch up with you,
and then we'll go to the same college together!
Takeo-kun...
Don't worry!
You can count on me!
There are still more than two
years till entrance exams.
I'll make it work somehow!
Takeo-kun...
All right!
From now on, I'm going to study every day!
I want to attend the same college as you!
World History     Math I     Japanese History
All right!
Certain Victory
Suna!
I have a favor to ask!
I don't have anyone else to ask!
What?
Help me get into Murasakifuji University!
Huh?
Please!
Well, I'm glad it's a perfectly respectable request,
but you'll never get into Murasakifuji University.
I see...
I've only ever studied right before
exams in my life, after all...
You didn't study much right
before exams, either.
Why Murasakifuji University?
That's where Yamato wants to go.
Oh...
I thought she'd go to some cooking
school or something, for baking.
But she was saying how she'll change
her college picks to match me.
Ah...
She said she wanted to attend
the same college as me.
If there's anything I can do,
I want to do it, you know?
Yeah, okay.
Want to try English first, then?
Whether you pick humanities or the sciences,
you'll need good English grades.
Sorry, Suna!
No... It's all good.
Okay, let's see how much vocab you know.
Right, come at me!
What does "get" mean?
Like this!
I guess that's about right.
Yeah!
What about "escape"?
Like this!
Yeah, okay.
"Forget"?
Like this...
Yeah, you're right...
Oh, it's Yamato.
Takeo-kun, even if Murasakifuji
University isn't an option,
Aobeni University and Maccha
University are close by.
I'm looking at private universities
strong in the humanities.
There's a benchmark exam coming up.
I wasn't thinking of taking it,
but I will if you will.
Want to try it together?
What about Aobeni and Maccha?
They won't be easy, but they're more
realistic targets than Murasakifuji.
Murasakifuji's the hardest one.
I see...
I'm gonna gun for Murasakifuji!
Okay, well, just try your best.
A benchmark exam, huh?
For now, let's aim for that.
Okay!
Takeo,
you're too loud.
Let's have fun!
Shh...
Huh?
Takeo's studying?
Suna, it isn't looking good.
I can't see my enemy's face at all...
Imaginary Enemy
The Benchmark Exam
I'm trying to throw him,
but he won't even let me get a decent grip...
You can get a decent grip, Takeo.
You have to face him first.
How many do I have to face?
Suna, want to come over today?
If I start having a crisis, say "Yamato."
Oh, Makoto-kun. Welcome.
Gouda!!
Thank you.
Yamato-san.
Muoh...
Ku...
Yamato-san.
Grrr...
Coming!
Math I is a formidable foe...
Fierce
This might be your limit.
I can keep going!
Sorry to bother you.
Oh, not at all.
Take, you have a visitor.
Hello.
Yamato?
Your text said that you'd be studying today,
so I made chocolate.
Stare
I thought your brain would need sugar.
Oh, I didn't actually make
chocolate from cacao beans.
I mean, I made chocolate,
but I didn't make chocolate...
Um, I'm not sure what I'm getting at.
I'll prepare some tea.
Make yourself at home.
Take, come help.
Okay.
Thank you.
Take...
Is she your girlfriend?
She is.
This tea is no good!
I'm going out to get some good tea.
You don't need help?
Of course not!
Where's your mom?
She went to buy some tea.
Oh, no!
I'm sorry to be a bother.
I didn't intend to come in.
Oh, I got really nervous talking to your mom.
I told her you were my girlfriend.
Huh? Oh, okay.
Was that okay?
Yeah, I'm glad.
I see...
Studying isn't so bad.
Oh!
You're using the same world
history textbook we do!
Oh, math I is the same, too.
Guess we can talk things through.
You can do the memorization stuff on your own...
Yamato-san, do you like tea?
Oh, yes!
I love tea.
Thank you!
Here you go.
I've never seen this cup before.
Did she buy it?
Where'd you pop this out from?
Stay as long as you'd like.
Okay!
Oh, but I haven't told my parents I'll be late,
so I'll go home after tea.
Oh, really?
That's too bad.
Takeo, make sure you see her home.
Don't work yourself too hard, Takeo-kun.
I know I said what I said
the other day about wanting
to go to the same school
because I was listening to
what you all were saying.
But it'll still be fun, even if we
aren't in the same school.
No, that's what I'd like, too.
I've wished Yamato were in
the same school as me...
Yeah!
It'd be great to be together.
Okay, let's try this, Takeo-kun!
Yeah!
I'll try hard, too!
I'm also going to study on weekends,
so come over if you're free!
Okay!
I thought how nice it'd be if Yamato
were always with me...
Let's study together!
Yamato will come over tomorrow.
Yamato-kun?
Yamato-san.
Take's girlfriend.
A girlfriend, huh.
What's she like?
She seems nice.
I see.
That's good.
Yep!
What's wrong, Mom?
Oh, I woke you up?
I woke up, myself, so...
Go back to sleep.
Gouda!!
My parents are better dressed than usual...
Welcome!
Make yourself at home!
Oh, is this room different somehow?
Mom cleaned up because you were coming.
Oh, I see!
I'm sorry.
But I'm flattered, too.
Just take a seat wherever you want.
Okay.
World History          Math I
All right, let's start.
Okay.
I'll focus on my own studying!
I'll try my best not to talk for
the next thirty minutes.
Okay, starting now.
Ready, set... Start!
Takeo, may I come in?
I haven't introduced myself yet.
I'm Takeo's father.
Oh, hello!
I'm Yamato. Nice to meet you.
I hear you've been very good to my son.
Yes!
Oh! I mean, he's been good to me!
Please take good care of him.
Okay!
Excuse me.
That was nerve-wracking!
I thought you probably took after your mom,
but you take after your dad, too!
I do?
Okay, so thirty minutes from now.
Okay!
Are you hungry?
Yamato-san, do you like rice crackers?
Yes!
Oh, then I'm glad I brought something sweet.
We can have both kinds.
Oh, my.
You made these, Yamato-san?
That's impressive.
Oh, they're delicious.
How long have you been dating Takeo?
We're going to study.
Leave!
Yamato-san, do you want to watch some golf?
Oh, golf?
My dad watches it at home.
Your dad plays golf?
We'd get along.
Wait one second.
Yamato-san, would you like more tea?
Yes, thank you.
This is a golf magazine. Ishikawa-kun's on it.
Thank you!
Sunakawa
Sure.
My parents aren't home today,
so you can do whatever.
Your room's always tidy.
Pardon the intrusion.
I was just studying, too.
Takeo-kun, I'll quiz you.
Sure.
When did World War II begin?
1939!
Wow, you got it right.
Yamato-san, ask something
a little more challenging.
Um, okay...
Language Arts
I don't get it.
Why is this guy going back and forth
between two women?
I don't get it at all.
Takeo, tests don't want to know your opinion.
You're right.
I was thinking the same thing.
Why wouldn't you know which one
you have real feelings for?
He's being rude to them.
Not you, too.
Takeo, wouldn't you be unsure if
there were two of Yamato-san?
Yamato-san, if there were two
of Takeo, you would be, too.
Yamato!
Takeo-kun!
Which one's the real one!
I am!
No, me.
What about Takeo-kun?
Me!
I'm Takeo!
That's horrible!
I would be uncertain.
Oh, no!
Okay, keep going.
Takeo-kun?
Oh, he's passed out.
He's been studying hard for a long time.
I think it's the first time I've ever
seen him study so much.
Takeo-kun...
Let's let him sleep.
I'll go make some tea.
It'd be fun if we end up
in the same university.
But even if we don't,
I want us to stay together forever.
Do you want coffee or roasted green tea?
Wait, wait! Sunakawa-kun!
No, carry on.
I didn't see anything.
No, please don't tell Takeo-kun.
Don't tell him everything I was doing
to him while he was asleep.
"Everything"?
I won't, seriously.
Oh! I was asleep!
Oh, he got up.
Sunakawa
Okay, good luck!
I can go home fine on my own.
It's still light out.
Okay!
Later!
Suna, are you going to college, too?
Well, sure.
Oh.
I've never thought much about the future.
Suna, do you want to attend
the same college as us, too?
Why?
Oh, I just thought it might be fun
if you were with us, as well.
Okay...
I don't plan on matching your scores,
so I'll need you to study a ton.
O-Okay.
Studying is for people to get the knowledge
they need to not mess up in life.
I guess that's why you don't need it.
Why not?
If you don't understand, it's fine.
I feel like you might get into Murasakifuji now.
Really?
I don't really get this deep stuff...
I'm not good at studying...
But if it'll let me have good times with them,
I want to get past this roadblock...
National General Benchmark Exam
Administration Site
Takeo...
Don't talk to me.
I feel like what I learned is going
to leak out of my ears.
Watch out.
I just lost about ten things I learned!
Pick them up for me!
Takeo-kun!
Yamato!
Calm down, okay?
Okay!
Do you have your pencil?
Your eraser?
All right!
Okay, see you later!
Okay!
Begin!
All right!
Mark
Defeat!!
This problem...
I think this will come up.
Oh, this is the one Yamato...
I made flashcards for all the important years!
Okay, I'm getting some...
No, a pretty good chunk!
There! There! There!
I've got world history nailed down!
Last one!
The answers are off!
...so all my answers were off by one,
so I lost all my points.
Where?
Where'd it happen?
What'd I miss?
I won't give up!
I'll fix my answers till I run out of time!
What's wrong, Takeo-kun?
His answers were off by one.
Huh?
I fixed them as long as I could,
but I'm not sure how far I got.
You both helped me study, too.
You encouraged me...
I'm sorry, guys.
I'm glad it wasn't the actual test.
Yeah, it's only just beginning.
Right.
This isn't my last chance.
Okay!
I'm going to nail the next subject!
I don't care if it's Mark or Billy!
Let 'em come!
Who're you talking about?
Let's do this!
Benchmark Exam Results     Shuuei High School: Gouda Takeo
Assessment
Murasakifuji University     X Indeterminate
Aobeni University               D
Maccha University             D
What's this "X" rating?
Not sure if it's an "X" or a cross mark.
It says "Indeterminate."
Indeterminate
Indeterminate...
I'll go call Yamato.
I see...
I guess Murasakifuji wasn't possible, after all.
Yeah.
I guess not.
I didn't make it, either.
Um, if it's Hakutou University, I think
we can all go together, if we try.
So let's aim for that.
I'll keep trying.
You're okay with not going to Murasakifuji?
Huh?
Oh, no, it's okay.
I mean, we couldn't ever go together.
It's a women's college.
Women's?
Yeah.
I don't know why, but I thought you
might be able to go there anyway.
I guess it's impossible, though.
You tricked me, Suna!
Huh? Sunakawa-kun?
Today Is on Me
Next time: Today Is on Me.