Touko, I saw
what you saw that day.
What she saw?
What are you to Touko?
Hey—
You came all the way here
to see Touko again?
Yeah.
"Yeah"?
How did you know to look here?
Kazemichi
This is where you hang out, isn't it?
Yeah, so?
I'll see you at the Kirinkan lookout at 11.
What?
Hey, wait!
You don't have to go.
What does it matter to you?
That dude was so collected and curt.
So what's your relationship
with that "David"?
We talked about chickens at school.
Huh?
How do you get from that
to "let's meet tomorrow"?
Well...
He was pretty hot.
Never mind that.
You should go if you want.
But I think it's what
inside that makes a man.
Seriously, it's not like that.
Is something bothering you?
I'll go too, then.
Sacchan?!
He didn't tell you to come alone, did he?
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Why don't we all go then?
That's not very thoughtful.
You really don't understand girls.
Why?!
Episode 2
"Bench"
What's there not to understand about girls?
You want me to tell you?
Ow!
I told you not to come
in without asking.
It seemed like you called.
Obviously not.
A guy who understands girls is
someone who's tall, rich,
and smart.
Psych, it's actually a guy who can tell
a girl's lying when she says that.
Good luck!
Focus, focus.
Have you found your fragment?
I slipped up.
Sorry,
I couldn't get the room ready in time.
I'll get it done by the end of the week.
It's fine. I'm enjoying it.
You mean camping out in a tent?
Not much for me to do
as your dad, then.
Thanks.
Oh,
I'm leaving soon, so I won't need lunch.
Yeah? A date?
Yeah.
It's pretty.
I messed up a bit, so I had to fix it.
Doesn't look like it.
Will you keep it?
Really?
For sticking with me today.
Thanks.
Is that—
Your first piece.
Does that sparkly thing have something
to do with why you're here today?
Hey.
Hello. We met yesterday.
It's Nagamiya.
Did you come here because
you're worried about Touko?
What can I do to earn your trust?
Don't come near Touko-chan.
That's not easy.
What if I told you I could
solve one of your problems?
Touko, you see things on
certain occasions, don't you?
Sacchan.
I want to talk with Okikura-kun.
But...
Sorry.
You're going to help Touko-chan, right?
I believe so.
I'll wait downstairs.
Okay.
Oh yeah,
we don't allow dating in our group.
Eh?
I don't think those kinds of things last.
Touko, what do you think of your skill?
My skill?
Your ability, you might call it.
Your hallucinations.
Umm...
Let's go outside.
So hot.
I want to apologize to you.
Oh yeah, you didn't even
ask me if I could come.
What if I hadn't shown up?
I would have gone to see you
as many times as I'd need to.
I got caught off-guard today.
I heard your voice.
Sorry.
I don't get it.
I heard your future voice
without your permission.
My voice from the future?
Yeah.
Are you apologizing because
you heard me singing in the
bathroom or something?
Or—no way...
I wasn't talking about
my exam grades, was I?
Neither.
Oh, good.
Are they bad?
Huh?
Your exam grades.
Why would you even ask?
You figure it out!
So you believe me.
I'll forgive you if you tell
me you're kidding now.
Three-second rule.
I'm not kidding.
On the day of the festival,
for the first time,
I both saw and heard a fragment.
Fragment?
I've finally found you.
That was the first time I heard a voice.
My voice from the future.
I call it a fragment of the future.
A fragment of the future?
What you're seeing is the same.
I can see the future?
I believe so.
How?
Whenever you see things—
there's a trigger, isn't there?
Yes.
That probably makes it easier to see.
You just need glass?
Yeah.
Anything shiny, but especially glass.
Then just
focus on the glass.
I want to see the future, too.
Was that me?
I knew it. I can see something
when I'm near you, too.
I've never seen anything so vividly.
And voices, too.
But how do you know that
this is from the future?
Because it was for me.
See, when we're together,
we can both see and hear.
What do you do, knowing that?
Hold on to this number.
Is this... You're kidding, your landline?
I don't think he's a bad person.
But I can't seem to like him.
He didn't pull anything weird, did he?
Of course not.
Okay, then.
If anyone ever caused you grief,
I would never forgive them.
It's my last chance.
I gotta let her know.
Confession
For I am a man!
Oh? "A man" you say?
I won't tell you not to just barge in,
but can't you at least
think about the mood?
Oh yeah, I saw that girl earlier.
That one you like.
Stop it!
I saw her in the hospital.
Is there something wrong?
She goes there routinely.
Star-crossed with a sickly beauty, huh?
Sounds like your thing.
No star-crossing us!
Hey, we met yesterday.
Yo.
I'm Yukinari Imi.
Kakeru Okikura.
That was quick!
Hey, are you pacing yourself?
Here, drink up.
You idiot, don't just ignore me!
You were getting better.
You really should pace yourself.
Also, Hiro sent everyone an email.
Take a look later.
What?
I saw David.
David?
Oh, from yesterday.
And?
I don't want to lose.
What? I couldn't hear.
Hello?
Touko? It's me.
Yeah, what's up, Yana-chan?
I wanted to talk about something.
Sure.
I'm thinking of confessing.
Yeah?
Do you know who to?
Umm...
Guess.
Yuki-kun?
You knew, didn't you?
I always thought you'd
be cute together.
Yana-chan and Yuki-kun.
But I think
there's someone he likes.
Yana-chan, of course!
Maybe you should get ready
for him to confess to you.
Say what? Get ready how?
Um...
I don't even know if it's me.
I swear, it'll be fine.
If it doesn't work out,
I'll have to leave the group.
That's not true.
Yeah?
Of course not.
Take control. You're awesome.
I'm rooting for you.
Thanks, Touko.
Hey, bath's open.
Bath?
No, no, not like they're bathing together.
How would you get ready
to be confessed to?
Onee-chan, dinner!
Okay.
Getting ready...
Let's eat!
Fried chicken, huh?
I had a craving.
We bought too much chicken.
The freezer was packed.
Onee-chan, you went to
Kirinkan today, right?
How was it?
I wish the balcony had a cooler, too.
Kirinkan is a special place
for us, isn't it, Marie?
Twenty years ago,
Marie was frantically copying
the display pieces.
She forgot to breathe and collapsed,
and it was Dad that came to the rescue.
I don't get it.
I propped her up, and when
she came to, she said,
"You climbed all those stairs for me."
So I said,
"Nah, it was like going down stairs."
Man, I'm embarrassed.
Mom, is that true?
Don't remember a thing.
Hey, Hina-chan,
if... if you could know the future,
what would you do?
That's so random. Well...
I'd make a killing on boat races.
Huh?
Like, if you're married or
whatever. That kind of stuff.
What would be the fun in knowing that?
How about after you grow up, then?
She says she can't make it today.
Her lesson's taking a while.
How was yesterday, Sacchan?
He wasn't any different from
when he was here last time.
I think they were just talking.
What do you mean, you think?
I left the room.
You left them alone together?
I'm finally here!
Huh, what's wrong?
So as per my email,
we're going hiking tomorrow.
First, about our meet-up time—
Before that, there's something
I want to announce.
Proceed.
We're open to dating.
We were banned from dating?
Yup.
But from now on—
Hold up!
Wait, never mind.
Yuki-kun,
I'm ready, too!
Welcome.
Huh, Yanagi-san.
Everyone left already.
Oh.
I finished early,
so I thought I'd drop by.
I'm going to chill for a bit.
Ask Yukinari about tomorrow.
Okay, thanks.
Your order?
Apple tea.
Roger.
Oh, and an announcement from Touko-san.
We're open to dating.
Sorry, I just remembered something.
Okay, Yuki-kun, see you.
Yeah.
Touko.
Yes?
Can we talk?
It's so hot again today.
Yeah.
Sorry, what were we saying?
Erm, well, you were with David yesterday.
Yesterday?
Oh yeah, did you get it already?
Get it? What?
Oh, I mean, a talk.
Talk? You did?
Yeah,
maybe you can't be nice to
girls straight-up because
you're so shy, but...
No, I mean, you're nice,
but some things you can't
get across without saying.
It hasn't gotten across, has it?
Why not try being honest with
the people you care for?
You're right,
I have to say it out loud.
Yup, yup.
I—
Touko, I...
Wait, why are you telling me this?
Touko!
Yes!
I like
you.
I like you, Touko!
Th-Thanks.
U-Um...
Thanks!
Yuki.
What's wrong? You look all doofy.
Why are you here?
What? Seriously? I'm on my way home.
Yeah?
Yeah. Sorry.
You're weird. Come on, let's go.
What do I do? What do I do?
I have to do something.
Oh!
Okikura here.
Hey, um...
Hi, it's Fukami, from school.
Oh, it's me.
Oh, Okikura-kun, hey,
I want to see the future.
I want to see the future, too.
Hey, Yana-chan...
A token of our friendship.
Huh, really?
But they're someone I like.
Everyone, stand back!
Episode 3
"Utility Tank"