Good morning, everyone!
It's a beautiful day!
Huh? Takako?
What? It's four in the morning...
The early bird catches the worm!
Not only do you have
your regular duties at
the inn to take care of,
you also have to help with the
preparations for our wedding!
Thus, I've concluded that
cutting the sleeping time
of you young ones, will be
the first step to making this a success.
What?
Anyway, you now have a meeting
with Enishing you must attend.
Here we go, to the staff dining room!
I wonder why Takako's
so fired up suddenly.
Episode 22
A Determined One-Sided Crush
Good morning, Ms. Tomoe!
Let's begin a wonderful day!
Hey!
Oh... sorry.
Come on, have a seat like
everyone else, Ms. Tomoe.
We'll now begin the meeting.
Let's get fired up!
Are you ready?
Anyway, what led Ryunosuke
Akutagawa to write Rashomon?
His wedding with Yayoi Yoshida,
a girl he'd known since he
was a child, had been called off...
Hey!
Oh... I'm sorry!
It never rings, so I...
Huh? What about
your boyfriend?
Now's not a good time
to bring up stuff like-
I'm sorry.
What were you thinking?!
I can't believe you called
me in the middle of class.
Sorry, sorry.
I just have this image of
you constantly at work.
I forgot that you're
a high schooler.
So, what do you need?
Oh, I received an invitation.
Enishi's getting married, huh?
Yeah!
You're coming, right?
It isn't that simple.
What? You're busy with work?
I've got a lot to take care of.
I'll send him a congratulatory
message, though.
Enishi, huh...
He's streaked ahead of you, huh?
Hush.
Hey, your relationships with your
boyfriends last too long, don't they?
What?
What does it mean to you when
you go out with someone?
What? You've gone and caught
yourself another boyfriend?
N-No!
Hmm...
Maybe it's because I still have a
one-sided crush on your father.
What?!
A one-sided crush?!
You didn't have to scream at me.
I thought I said something
nice for a change.
A one-sided crush?!
I didn't expect those words
from my sex crazed mother.
Jeez...
I want to find a new love because
I can't forget my old one.
I couldn't get anything out of that love.
But, well, it's been 15 years
since your father died.
Recently, I've been thinking that maybe
I don't need to get anything out of it.
Why not?
It's once in a lifetime that you
meet someone you love so much.
Maybe the fact that I met him
was lucky in itself.
Huh?
Ohana?
What?
Hearing her talk about
her one-sided crush made
my heart beat so fast!
Jeez!
One-sided crush?
Why...
Why did I try to forget about Ko?
Minchi is so serious about Tohru...
Why did I think I couldn't have
a one-sided crush on him?
Home Economics Room
Okay, it's done!
Wow! Amazing!
Yeah!
It's not bad for an amateur's work.
All that's left is for
someone to try it on,
so we can make some minor adjustments.
Could you try it on, Yuina?
What? I don't want to.
I hear that putting on a wedding dress
delays your marriage in the future.
If I tried it, I'd be
dragging the bottom...
I feel like this is déjà vu...
Not a pleasant déjà vu either...
C-Can I take this off now?
What should we do...
Tomoe is doing our share of the
duties at the inn right now, so...
Oh, we should ask Tsurugi to try it on, then!
She may not be as...
big as Takako there,
but as long as hers aren't
bigger, she can try it on!
As long as hers aren't bigger!
Right?
Looks like we're done for today.
You're going to start practicing
making the dishes for the party now?
Yup.
I sort of have an idea, but...
Minko...
Umm, I...
I told you, I don't need your help.
Hey...
It's fine. I've decided
to stop spoiling her.
Huh?
I noticed that you have to be hard
on them when they're in a slump,
in order for them to overcome it.
Just like how you were
ruthless with me back then.
R-Ruth... less?
Minchi sure is late...
Yeah...
Minchi!
We all made this together,
but there are some minor
adjustments we need to make, so...
No, I refuse.
What?
I hate wearing things with frills.
B-But, Minchi...
Shut up!
Wait, Minchi!
I don't mind that you dislike me,
but we made that dress
together with Yuina for Takako and
the young master's wedding!
We worked really hard on it!
How could you-
Shut up!
"Worked really hard"?
So has Tohru!
But you stepped all over
his feelings for you!
What? T-Tohru?
I-I've decided that I have a
one-sided crush on Ko!
I'm going to be direct
like you, Minchi!
So I'm-
Cut the crap!
Die!
Why do you have a crush?!
Just go out with Tohru!
Die! Die! Die!
No!
If I die, I won't be able
to go out with anyone!
Besides, I've already decided
that I have a crush on Ko!
I've decided!
Why?!
He's just some loser!
M-Minchi!
You've never even seen him!
Anyone's a loser compared to Tohru!
Minchi!
Tohru's so handsome! He's perfect!
Both of you, stop already!
Minko, you...
Wait, Minchi!
What are you? Stupid?
What?
Well... you're right.
I'm kind of interested in Ohana.
Perhaps I do like her.
But it's not like I
want to do anything.
I just get excited watching her,
trying to imagine what kind
of crazy stunt she'll pull next.
On the other hand, you
keep me in great suspense.
H-Hey...
Sorry, did I just say something awful?!
No... No, it's just...
I'm happy...
You're willing to watch over
me without even liking me...
You really are stupid, aren't you?
I've got most of the dirt off.
Ohana!
Wh-What?
I was really moved!
I've never been in love before,
but I thought what you
said was wonderful.
Wonderful?
Yeah, about continuing your crush.
Fighting isn't nice, but I
think both of you are wonderful.
You're both able to
love someone so much.
I'm so moved!
Nakochi...
What do you mean, "I'm moved"?
Minchi!
Okay.
Wow! It looks great on you!
Hey, we should get
her to hold some white flowers!
I've seen it on TV!
It's supposed to make it
more appealing, right?
I'll borrow the flowers by the staircase!
N-Nakochi?
Is your nose okay?
Y-Yeah, absolutely.
See-
I won't give up.
What?
I'm not giving up.
A-As in you're going to try and
force me to go out with Tohru?
No!
I...
I want to go out with him, so...
I'm not going to give that up.
I want to go out with him,
so I'm going to continue my crush.
Minchi...
I'm going to be direct
like you said, so...
Balut!
O-Ohana? Did you two fight ag-
"Balut" is back!
And after that, the preparations for
the wedding went smoothly.
I sort of decided...
that I'd confess to Ko after the wedding.
Wow, amazing!
Perfect!
You decorated in even
the smallest of places!
Thanks. I have the
feeling that this will
Thank you so much!
be a wonderful wedding
thanks to you all.
This is wonderful!
I think so too!
Minchi, this way!
Please excuse us!
You're so pretty, Takako...
Of course!
This is the day a woman looks
the prettiest in her life!
In a woman's life...
I have a favor to ask you.
About the bouquet toss...
All right!
I haven't seen you since college.
When did you start dating Takako?
W-Well...
We've become bride and
groom on this day,
and we're so happy to be able to announce
this to you all this afternoon.
We swear to work
together as a married couple,
and to start up a warm, happy family.
Okay, bring it on!
The wedding ceremony's over!
Now we're in a race against time!
Okay!
What should I do...
I'm nervous about being
the master of ceremonies...
Hey, Oshimizu,
does my hair look fine? Is it weird?
It looks fine! Later!
Oshimizu looks so nice
when she's hustling!
A kitchen is a battlefield! Let's go!
Yes, sir!
Good!
Tohru, give me some orders.
Huh?
You're in charge today.
Okay!
Could you parboil those vegetables,
descale the carp,
fry those,
and decorate the dishes
with the cucumbers?
Th-That's quite a lot of work.
Okay, I'd like to read the
congratulatory greetings now.
This is from the groom's older
sister, Satsuki Matsumae.
"They always say that a relationship
gets better after a stormy fight,"
"but I'm not sure what the
weather is like today."
"Either way, you need to make
sure she's wet, all right?"
Oh, Mom...
What about the next dish?
The previous one was the last of them.
Great work today, everyone!
Invitations?
We're invited to the wedding too!
You look so pretty, Takako.
Thanks.
Wow, these are all so delicious!
It's the first time I've tasted
Tohru's cooking like this.
This is...
Sorry... I couldn't stop
him from doing this.
So, for our next performance...
Where art thou?!
Oh, where art thou, my destined love!
There you are!
My beloved... Takako!
Wh-What in the world?!
Now, for the baiser amor!
W-
Wait-
Don't react, or you'll lose.
On a morning without clocks,
two lovers smile and laugh while
being embraced by the white clouds.
Sunlight shines through a tiny gap,
and birds are singing freely
beyond the windowsill.
Time will extend as long as
their hands are held tight;
a short eternity is born.
I didn't help out with this wedding at all.
But these two, and the young workers at Kissuiso,
have created such an incredible ceremony.
I apologize for boring you
with stories of my past,
but 40 years ago, I created Kissuiso
with my late husband,
and with Denroku...
No, with Mr. Denroku.
That's what it means to be young.
Even if you stumble and get lost,
you challenge yourself to new things.
You'll be able to create something new.
I look forward to seeing
the new things these two,
and the rest of Kissuiso create,
while I'll sit back and enjoy
my tea from the far distance.
Everyone's future?
Watching from afar?
It ended without any troubles.
Yeah.
Looks like everything's
just about cleaned up.
Madam Manager,
about that speech you gave earlier...
The reason why I asked you all here...
is because Mr. Denroku
told me the other day...
This...
that he wanted someone
to succeed the logs he
kept for over 40 years.
Does that mean you're
quitting Kissuiso, Beanman?!
But, why?
These logs are like a
history book of Kissuiso.
The tears, the laughs...
everything is written in here.
Look how worn it is.
I'm thinking about sealing
Kissuiso, along with these logs,
after the Bonbori festival this year.
You going to see him?
What?
Your crush.
Oh...
A man is responsible
for waiting patiently.
Ohana, you're nothing
like a bland coffee.
Episode 23
Compensation for the Dream