Teppei!
The Earth Engine Impacter...
Delicious.
The Kiltgang has broken through defensive zone 1.
About to make contact with Earth Engine.
I've found a new feast...
Can you hear me, Earth Driver?
U-Uncle?
Daichi?!
Daichi?
What are you doing there?
What am I doing?
The consultation system isn't working yet!
We can't assist the Earth Engine!
What's wrong, Daichi?
Answer me!
Daichi!
This is Peter Westvillage.
Code Papillon, can you hear me?
This is Code Papillon.
I'm aware of the situation.
Who is that?
No idea.
Impressive.
Then, I request your help with flight
direction for the Earth Engine.
Roger that.
I'll borrow your communication line.
Earth Driver, you can hear me, right?
Who's there?
That doesn't matter.
I'm a magical girl who's on your side.
Right now, you're on a battlefield.
Do you understand that?
I don't know if I understand it or not.
But...
I know that if the thing in front
of me reaches Earth, it'll be bad!
That's good enough.
The Earth Engine is currently filled
with the power of Livlaster...
That is, your life energy.
You can pilot it, right?
I don't know.
Wait... Then how did you get up there?
Was the gun controlling you?
That's not it!
It's my own will telling me I must defeat it.
I believe the gun only helped me.
Then, what are you now?
Just a high school kid.
Oh, come on...
Fine, I'll take control.
You can provide the power.
Grip the Livlaster tightly.
You stopped moving all of a sudden.
Are you scared?
You're too slow.
I can't hit her...
I guess it's hard without direct control.
If you die, sorry.
Hey! Are you okay?!
Die? Me?
If your dad ever dies...
He'll die with a smile on his face.
I don't want...
to die.
I just need to hit it, right?
Hey, what are you going to do?
That light...
Orgone energy?
Hey, wait! Hey!
Impossible!
I hit her!
That's not the issue!
I hit her...
You're interesting. I like that...
Kiltgang interception successful.
What an ugly fight.
But we won.
That's right.
Code Papillon, thank you for your help.
It was the Earth Driver that did all the work.
It was fun, Globe-san.
I know I acted without consulting you,
but given the urgency of the situation,
I hope you'll forgive me.
In my experience, she is the
only flight director capable
of assisting the Earth Engine in that situation.
Who is she?
Someone I was thinking of
bringing to the base soon.
I'll show you the documents later.
It's clearly different than the
one we saw nine years ago.
It seems the active phase of the Kiltgang
that we feared has begun.
I've raised all satellite bases to DEFCON 1,
and all Impacters in defensive zones
will be ready at a moment's notice.
That aside...
I hadn't heard anything about the Earth Driver
being stationed at Tanegashima already.
Who is it?
Earth Engine has activated feathering system.
Set to return to Tanegashima on autopilot.
This is Salty Dog.
The area around the airport is cordoned off.
Begin operation immediately.
This is Tanegashima HQ. Roger.
So you're the Earth Driver, huh?
The Name of the Gun Is Livlaster
I don't see any physical abnormalities.
Not at the moment, at least.
It seems a second Livlaster has appeared.
You said nothing to us of this possibility.
You said nothing to me...
Well, it doesn't matter.
We'll have plenty of time to discuss it now.
Looks like your fever's down.
I'll have to talk to you, as well.
About that rainbow you were
probably responsible for...
On the outside, Globe is an
international organization
devoted to space development
for peaceful purposes...
But in truth, it is a defensive organization
here to fight those alien invaders.
Naturally, this is a secret.
Then when my dad died...
It wasn't an accident, after all?
Where did you get that gun?
I don't know.
All of a sudden, I was holding it.
This toy isn't a problem.
You can have it back.
Those two...
Those guys!
Who gave you permission
to use the lead gears?!
I knew it...
Of course we're using them.
If they were all as quiet and obedient
as she is, it wouldn't be a problem.
But some of them use their
singularities without warning.
Teppei!
You're Teppei, right?
Daichi?
Hey...
Isn't she the girl
we saw back then?
Is he the boy who was
there when Hana awoke?
Did I not forbid the use of the lead gears?
Salty Dog does not only inspect Globe.
I got even better at this.
We are also its internal police force.
Ah... Daichi!
You're exceeding your authority!
In an emergency, I am authorized to
take any steps I deem necessary.
I'll keep the promise I made that day.
Let's go.
You, too, Teppei!
Daichi!
Stop it!
Are you okay?
What are these things?
What's going on?
Don't let that animal out of its cage!
I'm sorry about earlier...
It hurt, didn't it?
I'll make sure those people
never touch you again.
I don't think he fired the gun.
I think the gun made him fire it.
I believe Livlaster, that energy generator,
is more like an extra-dimensional life form
in the shape of a gun than an actual gun.
Yes, it has a will.
And that will activated the Earth Engine.
That's the obvious conclusion.
In other words, the Livlaster used
him to activate the Earth Engine?
Then, once the investigation ends,
we have him swear an oath of secrecy,
and send him back to the mainland?
Now that the Kiltgang's active phase has
begun, can we get away with that?
Technology and Research Division 3 is
complaining that they can't set a schedule
for the Machine Goodfellow
demonstration experiments.
Yes, that's fine.
Why are they letting the designer children
determine the development schedule?
That's my policy.
Something wrong with it?
Isn't allowing them too much freedom dangerous?
What about the Ego Block?
It's fine... It was unharmed.
In Ego Block form,
we can use the Entangle Link
to travel through hyperspace.
But if we materialize in Ego Block
form too close to Earth,
it causes a libido burst.
Final approach must be
through normal space via the Kiltgang.
If they knew how this worked
when they designed their defense system,
they can't be underestimated.
Life never goes the way you
think it should, does it?
So, what was the Impacter that
shot down the Malkin like?
A manned Impacter, using a Livlaster?
Well, I'm told letting them do what they want
is the most efficient way to develop
the Machine Goodfellows.
Told?
By whom?
Good evening, CEO Kube.
Something seems to have happened
aboard the Tenkaidou.
I'm impressed you're aware of that.
Very impressed.
Stop talking like that.
You don't like it?
I think it's really cool and computer-y.
Your secretary, Hitomi-chan, was wearing
a very attractive suit today.
You should ask her on a date.
The Kiltgang won't reach Earth sooner
than anticipated, will they?
My simulation's predictions are perfect.
Globe will buy the required time.
And if you'd gone for it, you could
easily have had Hitomi-chan tonight.
She was totally up for it.
Humanity will survive.
The chosen humanity...
No, the humanity I choose.
What is the Macbeth Revolution's
present likelihood of success?
One hundred percent.
You're certain?
Puck doesn't lie.
I refuse to accept this method!
He's still a kid!
I can't have him behaving as he did yesterday.
Science Chief, do it.
Good morning, Daichi-kun.
I saw you yesterday...
I'm this base's science chief, Peter Westvillage.
Today, we'll be discussing the Livlaster,
so I had these two accompany me.
What's that girl's name?
That is none of your business.
There are many things in this world
that you don't need to know.
That's kind of exciting.
The gun you had is the second of its kind.
We believed the Livlaster you
had to be a type of weapon.
But its bearer, this girl...
Hana Mutou cannot fire it.
So we trained this boy, Teppei Arashi, instead.
Hana Mutou...
Your name's Hana!
Science Chief, you're talking too much!
It doesn't matter.
He'll be working with us on this plan for a while.
Where did you plan to take
these two yesterday?
I just...
Come out of there.
I'll show you my boomerang.
Boomerang?
I just wanted to show them my boomerang.
Your boomerang?
Long ago, I promised her.
Promised...
Then he's just an idiot?
Why were they suddenly in
so much pain yesterday?
They are under our protection and observation.
As a necessary safety precaution,
they wear lead gears on their heads.
If they try to leave the base's quarantine zone,
that sensor tower will detect it
and inflict a minor degree of pain.
Did they do something wrong?
That isn't it, but they're dangerous.
They have a special power...
And that means you'll be wearing
one starting today, as well.
I've sent a request to HQ for permission.
We're going to investigate why you
were able to fire the Livlaster.
Just be grateful you survived
firing that gun's first shot.
It didn't feel like that kind of thing...
Hey, where is my Livlaster?
You seem to have the wrong idea.
There is no such thing as "your" Livlaster.
We're done here!
Teppei... Hana.
I'll wait at the coast.
Daichi Manatsu is Taiyou Manatsu's son.
His father came up with the name "Earth Engine."
The power of a captain...
Somehow, it feels like fate that
he boarded the Earth Engine.
Is it out of character for me to speak of fate?
What's wrong?
Daichi Manatsu's lead gear has
gone into warning mode.
This is rough...
There's a strong Orgone signal
from the Livlaster in storage!
What's happening?
We're losing it!
What?
Hana?
Come here, Pitz.
You think you're going outside, Hana?
But...
But I want to see the boomerang!
The boomerang?
Let's go!
Got it...
Hey, why did you come back to this island, Daichi?
I told you.
I came to fulfill my promise.
Also, I remembered...
How good the wind on this island feels...
I'll be living with Uncle Nishikubo...
I mean, the commander.
It'll be Teppei and me, and Hana and Akari.
But the Kiltgang attacks again!
And because of Salty Dog's plot,
I launch in a malfunctioning Earth Engine.
Next time, on episode 3 of Captain Earth:
The Rainbow of Albion.
The Rainbow of Albion
Earth Engine, expand!