I made contact with him last night,
but he ran away.
Don't underestimate Bugbear.
His combat abilities rival, or exceed, my own.
Even before he awakens, there could
be trouble if you aren't careful.
Also, we don't currently know
what singularity he has.
Then getting into the ring was a mistake.
It seemed like so much fun,
I couldn't help myself.
Well, we went through all the trouble
to bring the Bakuretsujuu here.
Let's finish this today.
If we lure him out, it'll be fine.
The Magus incident...
Was this a year ago?
What have you been looking at?
I was just thinking that it never hit the news.
Didn't I kill a guy with my singularity last night?
Are you really okay, Haruhiko-san?
Hey, Vice Commander...
Late last night, was there an earthquake?
I haven't received any information about one.
A strange vibration shook the arena last night,
just as the lights went out.
Does that mean it was this
designer child's singularity?
According to our investigation,
that arena has a number of
illegally collected boys.
How powerful is a Planetary Gear's singularity?
You know, you have a singularity, too.
Before your first launch,
weren't you able to sense how
terrifying the Kiltgang are?
I think that's a type of singularity.
That's the Livlaster's power.
Why do you call your Livlaster "DC," Teppei?
It isn't short for designer child, right?
"DC" stands for "Dream Catcher."
Dream Catcher?
Like the talisman that keeps nightmares away?
Thanks to it, I've stopped having bad dreams.
Do you still have bad dreams?
Yes, every night...
But I have nightmares when I'm awake, as well.
Having Haruhiko as my fiancé is one of them.
It was your father's decision.
My father sees people only as tools.
To me, the biggest nightmare is the fact
that my father is buying and selling children!
I'm sorry...
I don't have any right to say this, do I?
Because I am
the one who bought you.
I did the same thing as my father.
I'm grateful to you, Miss.
You gave me a place to belong.
Baku...
This city is where you belong.
Baku, please.
Will you show me that trick again?
This was my only picture of my mother...
My father found it, and tore it up.
Baku?
Here.
What did you do?
A magic trick.
Please... You can do it, right?
Hey, would you be able to use that trick
to restore the ace of hearts alone?
Unfortunately, I don't have that level of control.
Hey, that isn't really a magic trick at all, is it?
My Town
Well done, Teppei!
Hitting a stationary target is nothing to brag about.
But...
It seems even that's difficult for the captain.
Sorry.
I've never practiced shooting.
You're doing pretty well in real fights, then.
Hey, Captain...
Would you try it with the Livlaster next?
It's strange, no matter how often I see it.
The Science Chief says it isn't
that you're firing the Livlaster,
but that it's using you to fire itself.
How does it feel to shoot it?
It doesn't feel like the Livlaster
is controlling me or anything.
Right?
Yeah.
It feels more...
Natural, I guess.
Natural?
Well, you don't look at your right hand
and think, "This is my right hand," do you?
Your right hand's a part of you,
so it's natural for it to be there.
It isn't like it's me and the Livlaster.
It's like both of us comprise "me."
When I fire the Livlaster,
it feels more like throwing a boomerang
than shooting a handgun.
That certainly is a singularity.
Yes, this is Rita.
Yes. Yes...
Got it.
That was Akari.
Hana had another premonition.
Tonight, a Machine Goodfellow will activate.
That arena seems like the first place to look.
Yeah.
Isn't the Nebula Engine at Haneda,
aboard the Regenbogen?
For strategic reasons, we're
preparing it to be sent here.
Right now, we'll have to rely on the captain.
Roger.
C'mon, let's go one-on-one again...
Hey, that's against the rules!
Oh... H-Hello, Kariya-san!
Business seems to be booming.
Yes, thanks to Baku.
He's our cash cow.
I see.
Tonight, have him earn as much as you can.
Huh?
This will be our last time seeing him in the ring.
Starting tomorrow, have someone replace him.
Does... that mean...
Roger!
Of course! I'll do as you say!
Hey, Teppei...
What? What's wrong?
I'm going to run to the bathroom.
Are you okay, Captain?
Bathroom, bathroom...
Hey.
This corridor is off-limits to unauthorized persons.
Sorry, I was looking for the bathroom...
You're the champion, right?
You're strong...
But aren't you afraid of fights with no rules?
I'm not afraid of fighting.
I'm afraid of not being able to
protect what's important to me.
And there's the gong!
Our undefeated emperor, Baku,
faces off against Great Ramdes!
A fierce battle has begun!
Amarok and Moco aren't here...
Maybe we were wrong?
Whoa!
Great Ramdes has started by
bringing out wooden swords.
But non-ranged weapons are not against the rules!
He grabbed the swords in mid-swing,
with his bare hands!
His strength is amazing.
Maybe it really is him.
He seems different, somehow.
The strength to want to protect something, huh?
Anything you want to say, Baku?
I have one thing to say to you.
This is my town!
That was Miss Kumiko's voice...
You bastard—
Baku!
Thanks for coming.
Let her go.
Hold on a second.
Agree to our terms, and we'll release her here.
I promise.
What are you after?
Who are you people?
You'll know soon.
Baku...
All right.
Don't move, Bugbear...
It'll be over soon.
Now, let's continue what we started last night.
You're free to go, Miss.
So that's what you've been up to.
Miss!
Sir!
Hey, why is he alive?
I was shot, but I'm alive...
My wounds are nearly gone.
I see...
So I was right.
I always wondered about that
strange magic trick of yours.
This is weird.
What do you mean?
Do you remember the Magus incident?
When a ship was blown up in Yokohama, right?
Yup.
An Asanoda ship was blown up.
What's strange?
Most of the Asanoda were aboard
the ship when it exploded,
but no one died.
Is that possible?
Someone's feelings activated a singularity.
Someone's singularity.
I was in the depths of despair at
the world that surrounded me.
At least go out and say hello, Kumiko.
Miss, isn't that a bomb?
That's right.
It was in our basement.
Don't do anything stupid.
Tonight, everyone's aboard the ship.
I can put an end to your child trafficking with this.
Stop it!
The dream I have each night is true, after all.
You're the reason I'm alive, aren't you?
But it's okay now, Baku.
I just wanted to protect you.
Please, Baku...
Release me from this nightmare...
What is this?
What kind of trick was that?
When the Magus exploded,
everyone in the Asanoda Yakuza actually died.
To revive her, Baku brought back
everyone else who died.
I know you are a special person.
Live in a way that lets you see the true light...
They're like an illusion Bugbear created.
You can't bring back the dead with a singularity.
They die because they aren't completely human.
You remember now... Right, Bugbear?
Let's do this!
Yeah, I understand!
Fine...
This planet is a nightmare.
I'll devour it all!
Machine Goodfellow Bakuretsujuu, activation.
Abreaction!
MM bus signal detected.
Identifying epicenter.
Initiating launch sequence.
Captain, ready?
Go.
Earth Engine Ordinary, launch!
It's time for the face-off between the
Bakuretsujuu and the Earth Engine.
Looks like Earth Engine's starting
off with a deadly weapon.
But ranged weapons are against the rules.
Way to go, Bugbear...
He's overwhelming the Earth Engine.
The way he's fighting...
It's the champion!
He's strong...
If you keep running, you'll run
out of time, Daichi Manatsu.
I have nothing left.
He's very fierce, but...
Why?
I don't feel any strength...
I have nothing left to protect!
Good work, Captain.
Sorry, I broke it again.
I'm glad you're safe, Captain.
Do you know who the designer
child on board was?
I think it was him.
Him?
The champion.
That strong person?
He was tough, but...
I don't know...
It almost felt like he wanted to die.
Was it Bugbear?
What's this? It's cute.
Don't touch it!
What's with the attitude?
What are you looking at?
My town.
Huh?
My town, huh?
A premonition says there won't be any
Machine Goodfellows for a while,
so at Akari's suggestion, we take a vacation.
But the Planetary Gears attack Tanegashima
in a way none of us expected.
Next time, on episode 14 of Captain Earth:
A Maiden's Tear That Sparkled Through the Night.
A Maiden's Tear That Sparkled Through the Night
Earth Engine, scramble!