Death?
My death?
Sleigh Beggies are treasures, in that you
create an unending supply of magic,
but your bodies are very fragile.
Just being alive, you relentlessly
absorb and generate magic.
Eventually, your body will buckle.
You're well-versed in the matter, Alice.
Not really.
He keeps you alive without taking any
measures to help you out of danger,
just to satiate his own curiosity.
That dizziness...
Chise-kun, he has no feelings.
You can't expect human kindness
from a sham of a human.
He bought you with money and
tied you down with that thing.
He has a tracking spell on it.
You must have suffered.
We'll set you free.
Ariel!
Master!
This place is our territory.
I won't have sorcerers
wandering around here.
Are you all right, Ariel?
Yes, I'm fine, as long as
I'm not touching metal.
Why?
Don't you want to be set free?
From what?
If you mean from Elias, you
probably wouldn't understand.
Even if he was lying, he was the
only one to ever call me family.
I don't care whether you were
lying or telling the truth.
He was the first person to value me.
So until Elias lets go of my hand,
I belong to him.
Alice!
Have you forgotten?
I am shadow.
I lurk in the shadows of thorns.
I am what you call the Pilum Murialis.
Are you all right, Chise?
Yes.
Can I see your wound?
My wound?
That was reckless of you.
Ouch...
You humans don't last very
long once you're injured.
You're late!
You're a pale shadow of a shadow!
Chise was here.
What could I do?
Its bonds are coming loose.
Chise, I'll take care of things here.
I'll leave the cleansing to you two.
Yes.
I'll come with you.
King!
You don't have to worry about it.
Chise and I are going to handle it.
It's the final duty of the king to
see that the corruption is gone.
Is it not?
Chise!
Are you all right?
Where are we?
A tavern from long ago.
A place to eat.
The neighboring town was beautiful.
I heard there are a lot of
beautiful women there, too.
I can see through myself.
It looks like we're inside
the corruption's memories.
That man...
Thank you very much.
Hey, are you the wandering sorcerer?
Yeah, that's me.
Are you surprised that I'm so small?
Did you need some help?
You can tell?
People everywhere depend
on me when I'm traveling.
Bad harvests?
Trying to win a special lady's attention?
No, my wife's always been frail.
She always ends up bedridden.
I want her to become healthier.
Do you have medicine or
anything that'll help?
You must care a lot about your wife.
Obviously!
That was a fast reply.
You're an embarrassing man.
May I see your wife in person?
Yes, please.
Come soon.
He's no good.
Thank you.
Get some rest.
I'll go talk to your husband.
Okay.
Thank you.
So, how is it?
Tim?
Tim.
What's wrong, Tim?
I don't think she'll get
any better than she is.
She won't last more than a few years.
She was born that way.
Can't be helped.
No...
M-Mina couldn't even play
outside as a child.
She's hard-working in spirit, but she
can't do much because of her health!
She deserves better!
I'll do anything for her!
Please!
I couldn't bear to see her die!
Does your wife like cats?
Cats?
Sure.
I see.
That's perfect, then!
Have you heard that cats have nine lives?
More rats!
Is it just me, or are there
lots of rats lately?
I suppose the cats aren't doing their jobs.
Mina.
Are you sure you're well
enough to be up and about?
Yes, the weather's nice today.
Have you seen Matthew?
I went to bring him a meal,
but he wasn't in the field.
Maybe he's out meeting a woman.
Don't be silly!
Everyone knows Matthew's all about Mina.
I saw him go into the forest with an axe.
I was just joking!
The forest?
Matthew!
Chise, are you okay?
You look really pale.
I have a really bad feeling about this.
A shed?
Was there always a shed here?
No!
What's that Matthew up to?
Matthew?
No!
Matthew.
Don't look inside!
Mina.
Ah, you're doing well today.
Perfect.
I just finished making this.
It's your medicine.
Medicine?
Matthew, what are you...
What are you talking about?
Remember we had a sorcerer see you?
He told me that this potion
would make you better.
Th-These cats...
Where did these cats come from?
They're ingredients.
They say cats have nine lives.
Apparently it's true.
He said I could make you
medicine out of the cats' lives.
How unfair is it that these
beasts have so many lives?
Matthew!
Hey, what happened to you?!
How could you do such a terrible thing?!
You aren't the kind of
person who could do this!
I can.
Because...
It's for your sake.
Matthew...
I can't move.
You don't have to be scared.
Drink that, and you'll go from
being weak to able-bodied.
You might even be able to live forever.
You...
What have you done to Matthew?!
I just had him trust me a little.
Don't worry, it's a magnificent drug.
So...
Be a mouse for me.
Mina, it's okay.
He said it only hurts in the beginning.
Hang in there, Mina.
You'll be well after this.
I'll be with you.
So...
Mat... thew...
Oh dear, it failed.
She lost her form.
I suppose beasts are just beasts after all.
They're easier to process than humans,
but I guess their strong instincts
means they have strong curses, too.
Looks like I'll have to go back to
figuring out how to condense souls.
Thanks for the valuable
research data, Mister.
Why?
Mina...
Why, Mina?
Whoops, he broke.
Love's amazing, huh, Miss?
Why?
Why?!
I know.
It wasn't enough.
I still need more.
More...
More,
more.
I need to gather more.
I need to gather... more.
Tim.
I'm glad you're here.
Your precious Mina is in trouble.
So...
Okay?
You aren't human anymore.
You're a demon.
You were deceived by a demon into
becoming a pitiful demon yourself.
I can't let you live,
and I can't let you die in peace.
I was chosen to be the king.
I also do this for those who died.
Mina...
Where is Mina?
I'm so lonely without you.
Mina...
Chise.
I've made you see something
terrible, haven't I?
I only intended to have you erase us,
but you have a powerful gift of sight.
I'm sorry.
What do you mean by "erase"?
I mean what I said.
Make us not exist.
The souls of all living
things are part of a cycle.
But Matthew and I have
forgotten how to return.
As have the cats.
The cats?
The souls of the cats who bore
a curse from their murder.
We've all forgotten how to return.
So, I want you to erase us.
I can't.
You were only deceived.
You don't deserve to be erased!
You must.
You have to.
All that waits for us if we lose our chance
now is an even more painful, endless void.
You're the only who can help us right now.
I'll lead the way, then.
King.
This is my ninth life.
I'll be returning soon.
I should be able to guide
you to where you belong.
No!
You can't! That girl will be sad!
Death is always sudden.
Sooner or later, it comes to all.
The last king, and the one before,
all sacrificed their souls
to hold off the corruption.
Compared to that, being
a guide isn't difficult.
I have good memories with her.
That's all I need.
Thank you.
What should I do?
Wait.
Ariel, with your power, with the
wind to carry seeds far away...
You're right.
Seed to soil, flower to seed.
That is the pact of the soil and the wind.
Those whose time is to return, to
the place where they must return.
Humans sure are silly and
clever. You're amusing.
That's why we can never get enough of you.
We won't erase you.
Don't worry.
She'll take you there.
So picture it in your mind.
Dandelions, sending their
seeds off into the air.
There, they set root and sprout.
The wind blows toward where you need to go.
Matthew!
Mina!
Mina.
Where were you?
Matthew.
Let's go, Matthew.
Thank you, Chise,
the little mage.
I pray that you don't come
here any time soon.
I was an unnecessary child.
No one wanted me.
I was kicked out, and I wandered
endlessly. And finally...
I might've found a perch.
When am I going to die?
The guiding of souls came at a great cost.
A girl, on the brink of sleep,
and a mage watching over her.
The two were met by...
Would you introduce me to your wife?