(Respiration)
Haruno-san, quick!
The others will come for
us if we can make it out.
Naomi-chan, are you sure the
detectives will come help us?
We have my brother.
I'm certain he'll come.
This is a great lodge.
We can make a nice orchard
here, once we till the land.
How do we capture them?
You'd just rip their heads
off, with your ability.
Let's go with my grapes.
There you are.
What was that?
Something's got the car.
I can't open the door.
Tree roots?
We're going to get crushed!
Sorry about that, ladies.
Do you know how grapes are made?
Grape vines are adept at attaching to
other plants, so their scions are grafted.
Like this.
By merging my grape vine
with the other plants,
I can use all the plants around
here as an extension of my body.
And since I'm sharing my
senses with all the plants,
it's easy for me to find you running off.
Don't look so upset.
I just need you to do me a favor.
When a villain asks for a "favor,"
it's something along the lines of
"Take advantage, exploit, and discard."
The Guild isn't an evil organization.
Of course...
I have a sister back
home who's about your age.
It's a huge family.
The dinner table is a warzone.
My sister loves pie.
She'd always take my share.
But she's so cute, I let
her get away with it.
Then let us go.
Sorry if I gave you the wrong impression.
The Guild's work is treacherous,
but the pay is good.
If I were to get fired,
my family would starve.
Please, stop.
I don't care what happens to
you, if it's for my sister.
Snow? In this season?
Naomi, run!
Brother!
A passenger train is passing
by in five minutes.
I'll convince them to wait
for just one minute.
Jump on.
Now, run!
Don't look back!
I thought this might happen.
My sources weren't very reliable.
Given his ability as I saw it earlier,
as soon as he connects with the woods,
he'll be able to manipulate the roots at
the base of the hill and stop the train.
I can't let him touch any trees
for five minutes so our staff can get away.
Kunikida-san!
You just thought, "I'll win if I don't let
him touch any trees while the girls run away."
Simplify your understanding
of the battlefield too much,
and your behavior becomes easy to read.
Indeed.
I'll have to write that
down in my notebook later.
By the way, did you just have this thought?
"Slap away his pistol, and he'll
have no means of attacking me."
Doppo Poet!
Simplify your understanding
of the battlefield too much,
and your behavior becomes easy to read.
Write that down later.
A secret organization from the
superpower abducting people abroad, I see.
That hurts to hear.
My boss told me, though, that the Guild
isn't an organization that does good.
It's an organization that
does what needs to be done.
Kunikida-san, behind you!
What?!
Do his abilities make him immune to bullets?
You're late, Lovecraft.
What were you doing?
Sleeping.
Oh, you.
Sorry.
Tanizaki! Use your Light Snow to hide!
What is this ability?
It's way too powerful a gift.
Do we kill them?
I don't know.
Let's catch the girls first,
and then ask for orders.
There it is.
Haruno-san!
The train.
All right, job's done.
Let's pull out before the
local police arrive.
There's no point hiding
myself with Light Snow now.
What can I do?
I'm borrowing your sister.
What are you doing with Naomi?
I'm not assigned to her, so I don't know.
Confine her... Torture her, I guess.
Don't think you can get away with this!
This is work.
You moralists would never understand.
Morals?
A truck.
Things could get nasty if they saw this.
Sure, the Agency has a sense of morals.
But Naomi is different to me.
Justice, morals, ego...
She's so much more to me than any of
those things that I can't compare them.
Hasn't that truck noticed us?
No.
Do we look like part of
the road to the driver?!
For Naomi, I'd gladly burn the world.
They stopped moving.
Haruno-san!
That was unexpected.
Where'd they go?
I don't sense their presence.
It seems they hid themselves and escaped.
Freeze!
HQ, we've found the suspects
in the reported abductions.
So they reported us ahead of time.
That train is late, the one
they're supposed to be on.
Mori-san from the Port Mafia is the human
manifestation of streamlining.
He controls the situation with
cold, mathematical detachment.
You can count on him to take advantage of
the fact we're letting our guard down.
We'll be safe for a while now.
Uh-huh.
Sorry.
Sorry?
I'm sorry, too.
Are you hurt?
Atsushi-kun.
Yes?
I have an unavoidable item on my agenda.
What is it?
I'm going to the bathroom.
I'm not going to make it!
There's no one watching us here.
You ought to come out.
Hey, Gin-chan.
You've grown taller.
So you knew we were watching you.
I was the one who created the Port Mafia's
surveillance techniques, after all.
So, what do you want from me?
Don't you think this gun
tells you what we want?
I don't.
For a group of assassins,
you've recruited some lousy members.
Gin-chan, would you please put
this away? It's dangerous.
You're right, that's not why we're here.
I have a message from the boss.
From Mori-san, huh?
I wonder what it is.
The message is this:
Dazai-kun, are you interested in coming
back to the Port Mafia executives?
Ah, what a pleasant invitation.
I've looked at your records.
Your blood is mafia black.
More so than anyone in this nation.
People change.
I mean, Gin-chan over there was
a dainty little girl, this tall.
Don't change the subject.
And she has
a sweet voice.
G-Girl?
Haruno-san.
Naomi-san.
You were safe.
Yes.
I never thought they'd come
after the staff, though.
You're safe now.
We'll escort you to the extraction point.
Something doesn't add up, though.
Why would Mori-san set people
aside for this charade?
In order to protect you.
To protect me?
The boss has set Q free.
Oh yeah, let me introduce someone to you.
We got acquainted on the train.
Whoa.
What the?
There are razors taped
The slightest bump would hurt him.
Let's play.
Impossible.
Do you have any idea what he's unleashed?
Q is a walking catastrophe.
He'll doom everyone, friend or foe.
The Port Mafia doesn't choose its
means to reach its ends.
Why do you think Q was
imprisoned in the first place?
It was because he has the most abhorrent
ability of them all. Mind control.
You better do something,
or he's going to die.
The enemy's gift...
I have to protect them.
You can't protect anyone.
What do you think you can protect?
No.
I'm not the same person I was before.
I have power.
I'm sorry, Haruno-san.
Q's curse attacks the minds of
his victims with hallucinations.
They begin to attack the people
around them indiscriminately.
The curse is triggered by the destruction
of the doll at the root of the curse.
But only a receiver is
cursed when that happens.
In order to become a receiver,
one must hurt Q.
Receivers show a bruise that looks as
though they were grabbed by someone,
which makes them easy to distinguish.
You mentioned that you
came here to protect me.
Damn!
Stop, Atsushi-kun!
Look carefully!
Atsushi-san...
Stop.
No...
I was the only one being
manipulated this whole time?
I was only trying to protect them.
It's all your fault.
It's in your nature to be swept up
by power and hurt others.
That will never change.
No!
It's your fault.
I want to change.
Be gone from this world.
I just want to protect people.
Stop!
Now do you understand who you are?
Be gone.
Ability: No Longer Human.
Your new friends are so fragile, Dazai-san.
It's okay, though.
I still look forward to breaking you.
Q
Yumeno Kyusaku
Ability:
Dogra Magra
In return for making me suffer, I'm
going to hurt you and break you lots.
I won't capture you next time.
I'll rip your heart out.
Let's play again, Dazai-san.
Let's go, Atsushi-kun.
Get up.
I'm no good!
I shouldn't have existed.
Atsushi-kun.
Listen to me, Atsushi-kun.
I'll give you some advice for
once, like a proper senpai.
Stop pitying yourself.
Pity yourself, and life becomes
an endless nightmare.
Now, then...
We don't have the luxury of choosing
our methods anymore, either.
If the enemy wants to play their
trump card, we'll do the same.
Early next morning
Another strategy proposal?
Ability:
Little Women
Guild Apprentice
Louisa A.
I, um... Yes.
Did you have to write an epic novel?
Umm...
I'm sorry.
I'll redo it.
I'll read it along the way.
Where's our next mission site?
I-It's too dangerous.
The cruise ship just fell.
I'd like you to stay put
inside, Lord Francis.
The Guild's site is wherever I am.
Is it not?
Hello, young lad.
Are you here alone?
Why are you here?
I made a deal with Dazai.
If he is to find and save Kyouka,
I will stay patiently here.
Don't you want to be with Dazai?
Dazai-san went to negotiate
with a government agent.
How long has it been, Dazai-kun?
I was surprised when I received your call.
Hey, Ango.
You're looking well.
Glad you came, Ango.
Why did you think I'd have forgiven you?
Just kidding.
I bet you left this thing unloaded.
What do you want?
I see.
The Gifted Special Operations Division
is the most powerful secret gifted
organization in the nation.
Get them on your side, and they'll be sure
to become the Agency's greatest weapon.
Then Kyouka-chan can come
back to the Agency soon.
I wonder.
Say, young boy, do you truly believe
that a young girl of fourteen can,
with just a few months of training,
kill thirty-five people?
It's her gift.
So long as her gift is bound to her soul,
she'll never escape the darkness.
Just as I never was able to.
Boy,
please take care of Kyouka.
Isn't it the Special Operations Division's
job to crack down on gifted crime groups?
You shouldn't neglect your duties.
We're aware of the Guild's
activities as well.
So you knew about it,
and let them off the hook?
They applied pressure on diplomats
to grant their members the
same immunities as them.
They're above the law.
Law enforcement can't even take
the Guild into custody anymore.
Dazai-kun, please, escape.
Immediately.
And tell your subordinates that
their lives are in danger.
Dazai-san's taking a while.
Did I keep you waiting?
What a predictable reaction.
Boring.
He's too strong.
Does he have combat abilities?
But if I can take him down, the war is over!
That was a nice kick.
It was worth at least ten thousand bucks.
But...
The bounty we've placed on you is seven billion.
I can't buy you for that much.
But don't get bummed out.
You're valuable for other reasons.
Now, come with me.
It's the same thing all over again.
Not again.
Wait.
Kyouka.
Episode 20
Though the Mind
May be Wrong
So then...