One, two, three, four.
One, two...
Sorry, Kuu-chan...
No problem. Are you okay, Hina-chan?
I sort of got dizzy as I was
going through the steps...
How did she end up being the heroine?
I'm a better actor,
and my face is cuter, too.
Okay, from the top.
Yes, ma'am!
A Kind Girl Who Isn't Kind
All right, that'll be enough.
Let's take a break.
Yes, ma'am!
I'm hot after all that practicing.
There we go.
Hina-chan, you're wearing
that practice outfit?
It looks great on you.
Wow, it does.
That's the one I lent you, right?
Yes!
It's really comfortable!
It breathes well, too!
Thank you!
Not at all. I'm glad.
In any case, you really
do have remarkable proportions.
I'm glad I asked you to be the heroine.
I-I'll try my best!
What good will it do to try any harder?!
One day, I'll also...
All right, now we'll work
on the steps for part 2.
Three, and...
One, two, three, four.
What's with her?
She can't even get this down?
One, two, three, four...
How can she play the heroine
if she can't master something this basic?
Hina-chan, you do this here.
Okay... One, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four.
I did it!
If you just stay relaxed, you'll do fine.
Okay! Thank you!
You did it, Hina-chan!
Yeah!
Jeez! Chiaki-senpai won't
look at anyone but that girl!
Why? I respect Chiaki-senpai
so much more than she does!
Okay, once more from the top.
Three, and...
One, two, three, four.
One, two...
Yua-chan!
Ow...
I'm perfectly fine! This is nothing!
I just slipped a little!
Are you okay, Yua-chan?
Ch-Chiaki-senpai is looking at me!
Want to go to the nurse's office,
just to be safe?
Wh-What should I do? I have to answer her...
But I'm all choked up...
Can't breathe...
Yua-chan?!
Don't die, Yua-chan!
You and I only just became friends!
No, Yua-chan!
For crying out loud,
stop shaking me! You'll kill me!
Thank goodness!
Want to leave early today?
N-No! I can practice!
Okay... Just try not to overdo it.
Okay!
That will be all for our group practice.
You should all practice on your own now.
Yes, ma'am!
I have to work harder so Chiaki-senpai
will recognize my abilities!
Hey, Yua-chan.
Huh?
Do you want to practice with us?
Huh? Why?
I thought it'd be more fun
if we practiced together.
Let's see... There's me and Kuu-chan and...
Wh-Why should I practice with you?
And the landlady.
O-Oh, fine, then. But just for today.
Yay!
One, two, three, four.
Like this... and this...
One, two, three, four...
And for the next step, do this...
When I see her up close like this,
she's actually pretty devoted to learning.
And then this... And next...
She's clumsy, but at least she's eager.
Huh? Whoa!
S-Sorry! Are you okay, Yua-chan?
I-I'm perfectly fine.
One, two, three, four.
Sorry, Yua-chan!
What do you think you're... doing...
Are you okay?
Y-Yes, totally fine.
I'm glad.
I really am sorry.
Jeez... She may be eager,
but she's still a failure.
Okay, that's all for today.
Thank you!
Today's practice was just awful.
Yua-chan, wait!
What?
Today was really fun, huh?
I'm sure it was for you.
I'm never going to practice with you again.
Huh? Why not?
Don't you "Why not?" me!
I'm all banged up after all the times
you knocked me over!
I'm really sorry.
But I admit that you're eager—
Miss Landlady!
Thanks for lending me
your practice outfit today!
I got sweaty, so I'll wash it
before I return it.
No, that's okay.
It's old, but you can keep it if you like.
Huh? I can?
Thank you!
I'm never going to approve of you!
Yua-chan?
What should we do for the cultural fair?
A café? Food stall? Or there's always the classic haunted house.
A haunted house? Like this?
...I wonder what'd be best.
We have to all think of something by tomorrow...
If it involves food, will there be rice balls?
Hmm... What will be best?
What are we going to display? Like photos?
If we do a display, it'll be easy but it's sort of lonely...
Then again, if we do a café, the preparations will be hard...
Actually, everything will be hard.
I wonder what kind of café... A maid café?
Okay, time to clean the store.
Let's work hard.
Beginning Theater
A theater book?
It has all kinds of different
practice methods.
There's even a way to practice
by becoming animals.
Animals...
There!
Would a bird look something like this?
Or maybe like this?
Or this?
Or how about this?
Hina-chan, how's the cleaning... going...
And this!
Is that self-defense training?
No, just imitating a bird...
It doesn't look like one?
Not a bit.
Why are you imitating a bird, anyway?
Beginning Theater
My movements are too stiff,
so I always bump into people.
I was hoping to do something about it.
I see.
Wouldn't a bird look more like this?
Huh? Oh...
L-Like this?
Do it like you're actually going to fly!
Like this?
Higher!
The dust...
Weren't you guys in the middle of cleaning?
I see.
So you were imitating animals.
We practice that way in the
theater club sometimes, too.
It broadens your range of expressions.
Would you give us a demonstration, then?
I want to see that, too!
Me, too!
O-Okay...
For example, a cat would look like this.
A dog would look like this.
You mimic their behaviors and try to
capture their unique characteristics.
Why does this seem
just the slightest bit erotic?
Why, indeed...
Hina-chan, why don't you
try imitating something?
U-Uh...
I want to see you imitate a rabbit!
It's sure to be adorable!
A rabbit, huh?
Okay, I'll try it.
What is that?
Was this a quiz of some kind?
No, no, no, no! That's what
rabbits really sound like!
Is it?
No idea.
Rabbits sound like that?
Yeah! They make that noise
when they attack you!
That's scary!
But that's true.
Some animals have cute faces,
but are actually vicious.
Come to think of it,
a guard dog my family used to have
had a cute face, but a really scary bark.
Oh, try imitating that.
I'm not sure I can get it right...
So cute!
Wait, but you said it was scary.
What was that an imitation of?
It was the dog leaping at an intruder
and saying, "I'll kill you!"
That is scary!
There.
You don't keep any pets here in the store?
Shop pets are popular these days.
What kinds of animals
were around in your hometown?
Well, let's see...
Dogs, rabbits, monkeys, tanuki, deer...
Oh, and eagles.
It would've been perfect if there were
bears and wild boars, too.
I don't think that would go
over well at this store.
They seem a bit vicious.
No, they taste really good in hotpot.
Huh? You keep them
on the premise of eating them?
Th-That... seems kinda...
...tasty...
You've seen all different kinds
of real animals, huh, Hina-chan?
Yeah.
Then why not try to recall them
while you practice?
Animals from the countryside?
Yeah.
Animals from the countryside...
Um, so how was that?
It was good. You seemed to be
soaring like a bird.
Really?
Yeah.
Yay! You think I can perform at Suzuran now?
That's jumping the gun a bit...
Used Bookstore Hitotose
Used Bookstore Hitotose?
Come to think of it, I've heard
she lives at a used bookstore.
Could this be the one?
And this is a penguin!
It looks just like one!
Pen, pen!
Pen, pen, pen!
What the heck?
Pen, pen!
There's one week left
until the culture festival.
We've got all of our costumes
and props together.
The one thing I'm concerned about is...
Ugh! Keep your eyes forward during practice!
If you keep that up, I'll never
approve of you as the heroine!
I-I'm sorry!
One, two, three, four! Come on!
Hina-chan's movements are
still as stiff as ever.
Sorry!
I couldn't get my acting
right today, either.
I bet Yua-chan hates me now...
I wonder how you can stop bumping into her.
Maybe by just looking around you?
I just can't seem to see anything
around me when I'm focused on acting.
But when I become conscious
of my surroundings,
I get nervous and become a scarecrow...
How about squinting while you act
so that you're only
somewhat aware of your surroundings?
That would take both my hands...
Then how about wearing a cute mask?
That would hide my face.
Hina-chan, I'll practice with you.
Let's do our best.
Okay!
Used Bookstore Hitotose
We're back.
U-Um... Have you been
practicing for the play?
Why don't you practice at the park?
O-Okay...
Honestly! She can never play
the heroine at that rate!
I'll have to tell her—
Huh?
I'm gonna feed the ducks.
I get it! There's lots of room, so I can
practice without bumping into anyone!
Hina-chan, were you practicing
dancing earlier?
Oh... Yeah.
In that case, I think it'd be best
for you to learn from Mayu-chan.
Huh?!
She always practices so she
can dance with a prince someday.
Wow...
Don't tell people that! It's embarrassing!
You're really small and cute, Mayu-chan.
You could get a princess role easily!
A-As far as that goes,
you're cute, too, Hina-chan...
I could never do it.
I'd step on the prince's feet,
or trip and end up tackling him.
Prince
That wouldn't be a dance.
It'd be a fighting competition.
I need to learn how to dance
without bumping into people soon!
Then maybe you should try to be
more aware of your center of gravity.
Center of gravity?
They're practicing out here?
Right, center of gravity.
Like if you put something on your head
and try to walk without dropping it.
Um... Like this?
That's great!
Thank you!
This is the same posture I'm in
when I become a scarecrow!
I never thought my talent
as a scarecrow would come in handy!
Did being complimented
make you so happy, you had to cry?
Wow! That's great!
Yeah. I think the dancing should work out.
Do you have any advice for her, Aki-chan?
Anything she can use to improve her acting?
Well, let's see...
Being used to it?
Used to it?
Th-Then, is there anything she can
keep in mind when she's on the stage?
Um... Maybe to take advantage of
the pauses left by your co-actors?
How can I get the hang
of reading their pauses?
Intuition?
Something
Like a
Genius
Wh-Why don't we start
by going over your lines?
Oh, that's a good idea.
You can't act if you don't know your lines.
I'm a bit more confident about my lines!
I've been reading the script
with Toritarou every day!
Okay, can you act out the heroine's part
in the beginning of the first chapter?
Okay!
I once had someone important
that I wished to protect—
That's wrong? "Someone precious"?
Oh, right!
I once had someone precious
that I wished to protect!
This person was more precious
to me than my own life—
Oh, that one is "important"?
R-Right!
This person was more important
to me than my own life,
Wh-What kind of crazy cheat skill is that?
and was irreplaceable.
It's been five years since that person died—
Huh? They're still alive?
Well, ready to head back home?
Not yet! I want to practice
just a bit longer!
I want to conquer my stage fright
with this play!
I want to change so I won't be
a failshrimp anymore!
All right.
Let's keep working just a bit longer, then.
Okay! Thank you!
When all is said and done, she's serious
about this. I just can't hate her.
Okay! I've got the basics
of the dancing down,
and I've memorized all the lines
through the first chapter.
I still have more work to do on acting,
quick changing, voice projection,
and some other important things.
But I'm better than I was before!
I think this might work out!
What?!
Do you actually think you'll be ready
for the culture festival at this rate?
I won't allow you to mess up
any play that I'm in!
Since it's come to this...
I'll just train you personally!
We're going to make this play a success!
H-Huh?
Wait, how long have you been here?
Don't worry about that!
Let's do this, Hinako!
R-Right!
I can't do it!
I can't reach!
-Prefixes and suffixes
-A prefix is an affix placed in front of a word to modify its meaning.
ex) "ex" (outside) in express, and "inter" (between) in interview.
-A suffix is a morpheme added at the end of a word to form a derivative.
ex) "ish" in boyish (making it an adjective)
-Prefixes that express numbers.
-uni = 1. Examples) uniform = uni+form->"one piece of clothing"
unicycle = uni+cycle->"unicycle" | universe = uni+verse->"Space, the whole world"
-multi = many Examples) multinational = multi+national->"many countries"
multipurpose = multi+purpose->"many uses"
media = multi + media->"multimedia, using various forms of media"
Gulp, gulp
Dribble, dribble, dribble
-Question: Circle the correct word for the following definitions.
1: Impossible to do: A) able B) unable C) enable
2: A vehicle with three wheels: A) bicycle B) tricycle C) unicycle
-Suffixes that create adjectives:
- -ful: <verb or noun + ful> turns it into an adjective meaning "filled with [word]"!
Examples) powerful = power+ful->"powerful, strong"
hopeful = hopeful = hope+ful->"filled with hope"
-If you add -ful to a container noun, it becomes a noun indicating "1 (container) worth."
Examples) glassful "1 glass worth" | spoonful "1 spoon worth" | saucerful "1 saucer worth"
Practice with Yua-chan was really tough.
My whole body hurts...
Are you okay?
Hang in there, Hina-chan!
Yeah! I can still keep going!
You'd better believe it!
We've still got a lot to do!
I can't have you keeling over on me now!
R-Right! I'll try my best
with you, Yua-chan!
Let's work hard, Yua-chan!
Uh... W-Well, of course!
I'm so glad.
I thought maybe you hated me now,
so I'm really happy.
Huh?
You're really kind, Yua-chan.
D-Don't get the wrong idea!
This is all for the play! Only for the play!
What did I tell you? I won't allow mistakes!
Yeah! I'll keep working my very hardest!
Hmph! You'd better!
Okay, I'm gonna do my best!
Together with Yua-chan and everyone else!
Maids, Ghosts, and the Stage of Dreams
I swear, you're such a handful, it's ridiculous.
But you're serious about this,
and you're eager, if nothing else.
I'm willing to admit that much, at least.
All right, Hinako!
Show 'em everything I taught you,
and leave nothing out!
Next time, "Maids, Ghosts,
and the Stage of Dreams."