What are kyoshi?
Walking corpses.
You can ask Theo for the details
when we're back outside.
We can get back outside, right, Sakaki-san?
Of course!
Right!
Shit! Who put this obnoxious ritual here?
Himeduka-san?
Kanoichi?
Hey, Chiyoda Ward's here.
Senda requested backup.
He said to pay you back
for borrowing your new kid.
That's Reiji-kun for you. We're saved.
Himeduka-san, you really
found a kyoshi ritual?
Yes. The stolen izuna tails in Aichi,
the stolen hair of the family god,
the fairy dust, the mermaid scales...
and the centuries-old grave
dirt from Toyama Park.
It was all...
For the ritual to create the kyoshi...
The kyoshi?!
Theo, what are you doing here?!
Kyoichi! You're safe?
Y-Yeah, I guess.
What's that Another behind you?
I've never seen...
Long black hair...
Golden, shining beast eyes...
It's that thief?
He took Suzu-chan's hair?
How rare to see you with humans, Seimei.
I suppose it has been a long time,
so I guess you've changed, too.
Well, it doesn't matter.
Now, Seimei... Entertain me.
#3 "Trickster with Amber Eyes"
Th-There's a ton of them!
So they're kyoshi?
Section Chief Yamashiro, are they okay?
I don't know.
But for now, we need to deal with this.
Seal all entrances to the park.
Don't let a single one out.
S-Seriously?!
Be careful, Miyako!
Kyoshi eat living humans!
No luck, huh?
Kyoichi!
Got it!
I thought we were dea—
It's safe now.
What was that for? I really
thought I was gonna suffocate!
Kyoshi attack humans
by sensing their breath.
So you kept me from breathing?
No luck. I can't get signal.
A barrier?
Probably.
If only I'd noticed sooner...
Um, what is a kyoshi?
You said something about walking corpses.
That's right.
They used to be human corpses.
Meaning even normal people can see them.
You could say they're artificial Anothers.
So, someone created them?
What differentiates them from zombies
is that their bodies are still intact.
Why would you make something like that?
In China, the ritual was used
to send those who had died
far away from their village back home.
Judging by their clothes, those bodies
date back to World War Two.
Someone prepared the kyoshi
ritual to use in the war,
but it was abandoned when the war ended.
And that Another used the bodies down there
and the materials he stole to finish it?
Sheesh...
Every country turns to the occult
when they're about to lose a war.
And they just left this
dangerous stuff down here!
So, is there a way to deal with them?
Sunlight.
It's night, and we're underground!
Flamethrower? Shotgun?
We don't have either of those!
Think for yourself a little, Seimei.
He's back!
He's just toying with us.
Hey, you keep calling me Seimei, but...
Seimei? What are you mad about, Seimei?
I told you...
I'm not this damn Seimei!
Oh, he snapped.
You're not?
You're not Seimei?
Really?
I see. I thought you were.
If that's not the case, oh well.
Well, if you understand now—
I'll just kill you, then.
I prepared all this for my friend,
but it's gone to waste.
I don't like the fact that you resemble Seimei.
Die.
Shit.
I'm Seimei!
I'm definitely Seimei!
Right? Good.
Now we can play.
They're here!
Get back, you two.
They're half-human,
so blows will work on them.
That won't get us anywhere.
Find the altar!
Th-The altar?
Keeping this many kyoshi moving
would require a fairly powerful device.
The Chiyoda team above us
will call for reinforcements.
While we wait for that, we need
to find a way to stop the kyoshi!
Not bad.
This place is pretty creepy.
So this is where they were
doing research on kyoshi?
The string's coming from this way.
String?
How do you think kyoshi move?
They've already lost their human abilities.
There should be no way
for them to move at all.
Some strange power that
emanates from the altar?
That's right. Negative energy. Yin.
I see.
So he's using these threads to supply the Yin
energy the altar generates to the kyoshi?
Then if we cut them?
You can't.
You'd need something magically
enchanted to do it.
Is this...
Yeah. The stolen hair from the house god.
If we can't cut the threads,
we'll have to stop it at its source.
So unless we destroy the altar,
we can't stop the kyoshi?
Okay. Let's go.
Will it be that easy?
Um... what is your goal here, exactly?
I don't know what all this is for.
Why get us involved in this mess?
If you see a big machine in front
of you, don't you want to turn it on?
I just wanted to surprise you with it!
If I take it to the surface,
I'm sure the humans will panic.
I-Is that all?
Yup.
He's just a child...
Like a child pulling a fire alarm.
All he's interested in is having
fun and fulfilling his curiosity.
What are you, really?
Coyote, your friend.
I kept correcting you, but you
kept calling me a "black fox."
How rude.
This is not a job for a guy who
works at the ward office!
Call the cops! Or the riot police!
Weren't you always saying you wanted a big job?
I was wrong!
We're done!
Okay, all that's left is the Shinjuku entrance.
Are we going through them?
Look at that!
This is it.
Girls?
Threads coming from their mouths? Then...
That's right! They're the altar!
You said you were going
to destroy the altar, right?
That means killing them.
Now, what will you do, Seimei?
May 14th
Threads?
I've heard there's several
ways to control a kyoshi.
Threads that supply Yin energy to the bodies.
If we can cut them...
But, can we?
I brought this from Suzu-sama's shrine.
I think it'll work.
Okay, got it.
We're breaking through.
Right!
Huh?!
These girls are the altar?
That uniform... Osen Girls' Academy?!
You've heard of it?
They were on the list of missing people.
Unsolved Missing Girl Cases in Tokyo
Did he kidnap them?
You seem to have the wrong
idea. I just set them up.
A friend of a friend of a friend is a nasty
demon who loves to collect girls.
He says he traded with that demon for them.
So it all comes together here, huh?
Now, what will you do, Seimei?
If you destroy the altar,
the kyoshi will stop moving.
But if you don't kill the girls,
they'll keep killing people.
They might eat you, and your friends.
He's saying something really aggravating.
Shit! There're just too many!
Take this!
Kanoichi!
Save the few, and the many die.
Save the many, and the few die.
Now, what will your choice be, Seimei?
You're stupid if you think
I'm gonna negotiate with you, idiot!
All this crap you're spouting...
I'm not picking either of those bad endings!
At times like these, humans pick
the option that saves the most people.
So, there's only one answer!
I'm gonna save the girls,
and the people of Chiyoda Ward,
and go home alive!
Don't mess with humanity!
That's the first time I've seen
anybody call an Another an idiot.
Well said. I agree.
So, that's your answer?
But how about now?
Sakaki-san?
H-How are they so strong!?
Teenage girls shouldn't be this strong!
What will you do, Seimei?
Kill them?
Or forsake your friends?
Stop it! They have nothing to do with this!
If you want to annoy me,
then only focus on me.
If you want to surprise me,
then I'm really surprised!
That's enough, right?
What do you want me to do?
To tell the truth,
I didn't mean to go this far.
We've reunited after so long,
but you act like you don't know me.
You refuse to say my name.
Y-Your name?
So I guess I just kept going...
Oh, the name you gave me!
The name that only you had for me!
If you call me by that
name, I'll save everyone!
N-Name?
What?
People's lives are at stake and
he's acting like an pissed-off girlfriend.
I'm not even Seimei...
M-Miyako!
Sakaki-san! Theo-san!
Think! Think! Think!
Akane-san!
Looks like we're just in time.
Get back!
Are you okay?
We got word from Shinjuku and rushed over.
It's not stopping them?
We need to put a stop to this at the source.
Where is the source?
Underground, probably.
I think the guys from Shinjuku
Ward are on their way there,
but I don't know what's going on.
Think... Think... Think!
Coyote, your friend.
I kept correcting you, but you
kept calling me a "black fox."
Didn't Grandpa say something
about Seimei and a black fox?
A yokai?
That's right. Seimei-sama
commanded many yokai, but...
I remember...
A story of a yokai friend Seimei had,
whom he named but never forced to serve him.
He took the name from his deep golden eyes...
A black fox named...
Kohaku!
That's right, Seimei!
You finally said my name!
The name for me that only you possessed!
It's over?
W-What is this?
They stopped the Yin energy.
Looks like we're safe.
May 15th
I'm glad everybody's safe.
Thanks for your help, Chiyoda Ward.
I didn't expect you to bring
in a police helicopter.
I don't have power, but I do have connections.
With your help, we were able
to get Suzuka-sama's hair back.
Thank you so much.
Now we don't owe you anything
for borrowing Miyako.
Okay, let's go.
Ah, please wait!
Sheesh...
Looks like we managed to keep
it from getting out of hand.
Yokoyama-san.
You know him?
He's a detective.
He specializes in Another incidents.
You even found the missing
high school girls, huh?
These Anothers are always up to no good.
Senda-san, I'm free to deal with
the rest of this myself, right?
Perfect.
"Missing girls discovered in spooky facility
from World War Two" goes way beyond
what government workers should deal with.
You're just being humble.
At least help me put together
a convincing story.
Of course.
Yokoyama-san.
We made our calls.
The girls were picked up by an ambulance.
Thanks.
Now then, what do we do to explain this?
The usual gas leaks, maybe?
You just used that.
Unexploded shell, then.
The Ichigaya crew will complain again.
A detective specializing in Anothers?
Don't expect too much.
Can you arrest invisible Anothers?
Put them on trial?
Their job is to come up with a plausible
story that the victims can accept.
That's kind of...
Okay, Miyako-kun. Let's hear it.
What's that thing floating behind you?
This is Coyote, I guess.
He's the one who stole all those
things, and Seimei's friend.
Coyote?
Do I need to introduce myself?
I'm not interested in any name
but the one you gave me, though.
But most people who serve me call me this:
Huehuecóyotl. Pleased
to make your acquaintance.
Or so he says.
Huehuecóyotl?!
Huehuecóyotl, The Old Coyote
Huehuecóyotl...
The god of music, song,
and dance in the Aztec religion.
But he was also a trickster god,
who caused men and gods to fight,
and brought chaos and murder
for his own amusement.
A... god?
Yes. A god of disaster!
If something like that's haunting you,
they'll exile you from the country!
How rude.
I don't kill that many people.
Get off me!
Jeez... A god, huh?
Sakaki?
That Another said he got the
missing girls from a demon he knew.
Unsolved Missing Girl Cases in Tokyo
After over 10 years I've finally
run into a clue about my sister...
I said, get off!
Aw, you're so cold, Seimei.
About that, my name is Miyako Arata!
Don't call me Seimei!
My name is Abe no Seimei.
Make sure you call me Seimei.
Do you understand that, Kohaku?
Yup! I got it, Arata!
#4 "Fixed-Point Observation in Kabukicho"