This is...
We've been gathering what
are thought to be weapons
from among the sacred relics
that have been brought up.
I-It's a mountain of treasure!
Their restoration is your sacred duty.
Easy for you to say! I'm good, but what
am I supposed to do without any clues...
What's this?
I can see their insides!
How awesome is that?!
You may do as you wish with the
items that are of no use as arms.
What?!
Alright! Y-You can count on me!
We will.
This is really somethin'!
You come at a cheap price.
Did you say somethin'?
I said that you come at a cheap price.
Satisfied with what you're given...
I thought you were a man with
a little more backbone...
What's this now? What do you wanna say?!
That flying Yunboro...
What about the tin can?
I need to be able to borrow its power, you see...
I'm not seeing where this is going...
Actually, I've grown rather
tired of this fleet's methods.
I'm returning to the pirate trade.
Right after this fleet's at the bottom of the sea...
Commander.
Would you cancel the
attack against Gargantia?
Why?
Well...
If you feel an affinity towards them,
then you had best enlighten them
without a moment to lose, yes?
To increase territory for
the prosperity of humankind,
we need superior people and resources.
But...
Ledo, our mission is to bring a
new sense of order to this world.
Then that's no different from
the Galactic Alliance...
If we can't return to the front line,
we'll make this Earth into
our utopia, a second Avalon.
Our rightful cause hasn't
changed. Don't waver now.
Yes, sir.
Moment of Decision
This is incredible too.
Pinion-sama. Someone would like to see you.
Oh, sure. Come on in.
"Pinion-sama"?! Pretty high and mighty!
Oh, it's you...
They searched through all my packages without permission!
When did you become a VIP?
It's not like I asked for it.
Here.
Avalon...
Utopia...
We'll make this Earth into
our utopia, a second Avalon.
Don't waver now.
Grace!
Hey!
That's right...
Grace is on Gargantia with Amy.
Amy...
Here he is.
Pinion!
Keep it short.
What the devil is wrong with
the people of this fleet?
They all act like ghosts.
It's like their eyes are glazed over. It's weird.
Yeah, well...
At this rate, I'm sure the same thing is
going to happen to the residents of my ship.
I'm wondering why we ever left Gargantia.
You don't mind the way things are going?
Someone's plotting a rebellion.
What?!
Really?!
The red lobster that came to pick me up.
The Great Pirate Lukkage?!
T-Then let's work with the lobster...
She's counting on the tin can,
but there ain't no way Ledo would go for it.
But then... then we're supposed to
live like this the rest of our lives?
Spread it out to collect the water!
You're soaked. You're gonna catch a cold.
Hey!
What the hell is this?
Chamber, what's happening?!
The weather phenomena called rain,
which we have observed before.
I cannot detect any particular abnormalities.
What is this?
What?!
We have received a great
blessing from our divine god.
They shall now make the journey to god.
We give our blessings to those who die for the sake of the living.
W-What?!
Stop! What are you doing?!
They shall be eternally honored for
the salvation of the human race.
People? Those are people, aren't they?!
I didn't come here to see this.
They're insane...
Yes, that's right.
And this insane fleet is heading next for...
...Gargantia.
What?!
Yeah, this ain't for me.
I came here to protect
everyone from the Hideauze.
Amy... Bebel...
To protect them all, I...
You have received orders
from Commander Kugel.
Ensign Ledo, prepare for war.
Board and assume battle command.
I await your decision.
Decision, huh?
I make the decisions and you carry
them out. That's how it always was.
But maybe I never really
made any choices at all.
Meaning of your utterance is unclear.
Response to the commander's order is...
Chamber! How does your fighting
strength compare to Striker's?
Unable to calculate due to lack of data.
Unable to comprehend point of the question.
Can you fight Striker?
Well?
Currently, the actions of Striker X3752
would not be classified
as Alliance military duty.
It is possible to authorize
engagement in battle.
I see. In that case...
...can I fight the commander?
Chamber!
The answer to that question is
beyond my support system function.
In any case, combat policy formulation
is in your hands, Ensign.
Please. If we use a wireless,
it will be intercepted.
The only way is to go over and tell
them directly. There's no time!
But there's no way I can carry out
an important role like that...
Right now, you're the only one
who can fly over to Gargantia.
Please! Save everyone!
Fine, but you owe me one!
Chamber, prepare for war.
Roger.
Gargantia...
Melty!
It was you!
Amy... Amy!
Gargantia is... gonna be attacked...
Melty!
Can you believe it? She flew all
the way over here on a surf kite.
Melty!
Saaya... Amy...
In order to protect Gargantia,
we have no choice but to do as Melty
said, changing course and evacuating.
From my point of view, I'd have to say...
Wait!
Amy!
Melty told me!
She said Ledo is gonna let
us get away and then fight!
What?!
He's gonna fight on his own, in our place!
He's even gonna turn against an
old friend to protect Gargantia!
And we're just gonna run away?!
You're okay with that?!
But...
If that's what he's chosen,
we have to make a choice as well.
Dr. Oldham...
Ridget, it seems the time
has come to use that key.
Heaven's Ladder...
Are you serious?!
As this fleet's resident
sage, it is my responsibility
to offer counsel to the fleet commander.
That time is now.
Amy, I request your assistance as well.
We will make the world aware of my
great will and the grand power of god!
Here I declare the beginning
of a new holy war!
We will be victorious.
To bring absolute order to this planet...
To create a peaceful, glorious
utopia on this planet...
...follow me!
It is the only path that will
lead to eternal happiness.
Ledo...
Ensign Ledo. What foolishness is this?
You're the one that's
acting the fool.
Hardly proper language for
a soldier of the Alliance.
This is Earth! It's not
the Galactic Alliance!
But the human race resides on this planet.
And their fate is our responsibility.
Responsibility? Wrong!
The people living on this planet have
already built their own society!
We have no reason to destroy it!
Our rightful cause hasn't
changed. Don't waver now.
Stop! This is a battle between the gods!
How is it so powerful?!
Conjecture: Instead of an internal
generator, its energy is from an external source.
So it's been conserving power?!
Ledo.
Our mission is to bring a new
sense of order to this world.
Pinion?!
Pinion, withdraw! This is my fight!
Up yours! You may be birds of a feather,
but the one pretending to be a god
pisses me off 10,000 times more!
Ready for the next one!
Kill him!
What's this?!
Citizens not participating in the
battle, take shelter behind the bulkheads!
Prepare the lifeboats!
The main ship is this fleet's mother ship!
Be prepared for it to become a target!
No tolerance for a rebellion! Anyone
who stands against us is the enemy!
H-Her!
Oh my. I apologize if I
have to get a little rough!
You're more of a man than I thought!
My opinion of you is revised upwards.
Shut up! Just scatter those
bastards and get over here!
My pleasure.
Having difficulty securing
strategic advantage.
Suggestion: Hit-and-run tactics.
Concentrate attacks on enemy's head.
I don't wanna kill the commander!
Warning: Enemy maneuverability
is superior to mine.
The strong and the weak support
each other through rationality.
That's what humans are. Am I wrong?
Ledo!
Now!
Hit 'im!
Pinion!
Yeah!
Maximize generator power!
Hey, Ledo, how about trying to change
this planet with me?
Approaching the enemy.
Input emergency release number.
It helps that you're here.
Well? Will you follow me... again?
Commander...
Rebooting attitude control system.
Ensign Ledo, your resistance is without meaning.