From the Starting Sky
It wasn't a dream.
The saucer over the city,
Noel, who watched over us from nearby.
All of it was real?
Yes.
Nonoka.
Thank goodness.
No one remembers Noel.
There's nothing I can do.
But I'm glad you remember.
Just knowing I'm not the only one...
Are you really satisfied with that?
This girl I knew, Nonoka,
would never give up on anything
she set out to do until the end.
She was honest and true.
Before we knew it, she'd have
changed everyone's minds.
Shione.
That's what this friend of mine was like.
Am I wrong?
Thanks, Shione.
But it's...
I'm one of the people who was
changed by Nonoka's willpower.
Have faith in me.
Shione, can I ask you to do something?
Yes, of course.
I want to get together with
our observatory friends once more.
Okay.
Why you little...
Yuzuki.
Nonoka.
Excuse me.
Sorry, I've been looking for you.
Shione, is that you?
Koharu.
I want you to come with us.
Nonoka's back, and to
think Shione's back, too!
That's not quite it.
My school's still on summer break.
Vacation, huh?
That's a bit disappointing.
I was hoping we could
be together again.
Thanks.
S-Sure.
What're you up to this time,
getting Shione involved?
Let's all get together at the
observatory one more time.
Like last time.
This again?
We did try to call the saucer
like you wanted us to,
but the saucer never came.
How would I know
anything about Noel?!
Souta.
Come on, let's let it go.
I don't know anything about Noel.
Yet...
I can't ignore it.
Me neither.
I can't get what Nonoka
said out of my head.
I'm always looking for memories
of a girl I don't even know.
Even though there's
no way I'd find her.
Over and over.
Sorry, but—
I can't take it anymore!
Yuzuki.
I know.
Something's totally missing.
Right, Koharu, Souta?
Yeah.
I know we lost something important,
but I can't remember what it was.
I can't stand it.
I'm relieved.
That we're all the same.
Yuzuki, Koharu, Souta,
me, and Nonoka.
We must all be connected
by the same thoughts
since that time
seven years ago.
We have to find it again.
Before we completely
lose something important
within us.
Nonoka.
Let's call the saucer.
What's this?
I don't remember it being so wrecked.
I know, right?
The time we spent here as kids
will never change.
Noel loved seeing us smile.
So...
I'm a bit embarrassed, aren't you?
Of course.
I am, too.
Really?
You used to be pretty
bold in public, Yuzuki.
What?
I'm curious, too, about
what the other Yuzuki did.
I want to meet Noel.
Yeah.
I want to meet Noel-chan, too.
To be with Noel one more time...
Noel, can you hear?
We all want to see you.
That's what we're all wishing for.
Let's do it.
Shione's hat.
But we finally got to see you.
I'll be here for a little longer.
Where are you staying?
Well...
I asked if she wanted to stay at my place.
See you later.
Bye.
Come to the shop, too.
I will. Bye.
But are you sure?
Dad will be fine with it.
He was totally fine with Noel, even.
Shione?
Nonoka,
make me a promise.
From now on, you're going to grow
up experiencing many things.
Of all those things, some of them
are going to be sad or painful.
But at times like those,
especially at times like those,
you have to have the
biggest smile you can.
That way, you can get over anything.
Anything?
Yes, you're my Nonoka.
I promise!
Shione.
What's up?
When I was a kid, I saw a
girl sitting here alone.
And I thought to myself,
I'm going to be friends
with her no matter what.
And that if I didn't become her friend,
I'd regret it for the rest of my life.
I'm glad it was you I met that day.
Yes, me too.
Nozomitei
Kirigon
Shione?
Morning, Dad.
Morning.
You're finally up.
Where's Shione?
She had business in Hokubi City.
She left a while ago.
I see.
There, done.
Omelette rice?
Yeah.
I had a request.
From Shione?
No, what was her name?
Huh? She was here until just now.
Was she sitting in Mom's chair?
Huh? Yeah.
I'm going out!
H-Hey!
So no one's going to eat this?
If I'm the only one
that remembers Noel,
then if I forget Noel,
she might really disappear.
So
I'm going to record everything
I know about Noel.
Hokubi City High School
Orientation
We'll always be friends.
Such a nuisance.
What are you doing?
Okay, it's decided.
Saucers Welcome
How is it, Souta?
You're going to ignore me?
"No saucer" was better.
Come on, Onii-chan, you idiot.
Can I help?
It'll get better right away.
You're a boy.
All set.
Monster-san will be always be well.
I'm glad.
Souta.
Want a ride?
Yeah.
Take care of the rest.
I have to go find your lost friend.
There's still so much
more I want to tell you.
So many memories I want to make.
Noel, I miss you!
We'll see each other.
Nonoka.
Welcome back.
Welcome back, Noel!
I'm back!
The End