10 MINUTES / 100 YEN
You're finished!
How about this?!
Senketsu Shippu!
SENKETSU SHIPPU (GALE)
10 MINUTES / 100 YEN
The kid gloves are off,
you stinking bitch!
STARDUST ELECTRONICS
Attagirl, Ryuko!
Get her, Ryuko!
Gosh, everyone seems to
be having so much fun!
I'M NOT YOUR CUTE WOMAN
EPISODE 11
Listen close, Heaven and Hell!
My performance can't be stopped
just because she can fly now!
"Performance," my ass! All you're doing
is taking potshots with missiles!
Ryuko, our only option
is to get close and attack.
We have the edge
in maneuverability.
Where'd she go?
Senketsu! We're going
to cut that thing down!
Hey! What's the big idea?!
You little bitch!
Now, now, why are you
losing your cool,
little lady Jakuzure?
Oh, wow! You're flying, you're flying!
Ryuko, that's so cool!
Mankanshoku!
Get off of me!
Whew, that was a close call...
I almost made Gamagoori angry.
No, he's pretty angry already.
What?!
She stole air superiority from you with ease!
I'm disappointed, Nonon Jakuzure!
Oh, no! Oh, no! I've gone
and made Gamagoori mad!
Ryuko, I'm in a pinch
down here too!
Where are you going, Ryuko?
We can fly. We have the option of
going straight for our real target.
Ah, I follow you. Thinking outside
the box is your signature move.
Here I come, Satsuki Kiryuin!
Like hell you will!
How dare you try to get
between me and Satsuki!
Bitch! You're way outta your league!
To hell with your opinion!
I'll take my own path no matter
what anyone else says!
You're a sour note, all right!
I'm going to erase you!
Have a taste of this!
Listen up!
Symphony Regalia, Musical Barrage!
SYMPHONY REGALIA
MUSICAL BARRAGE
Ow!
Stop that!
If anything happens to
my laptop, you die.
Inu (dog) at the front gate,
Gama (toad) at the back...
You can do it, Ryuko!
I'm fighting hard, too!
Ouch... I can't believe
she did that.
Ow!
Hey, what's up with your performance?
Can't you fly anymore?
Cause if you can't...
...that's gonna be awfully
inconvenient for you.
Your butt is ours now!
She's all yours, Senketsu!
Yes, leave her to me!
Flying through the air is rather fun!
Wait! If I can't fly anymore, isn't the cliche
that you come down here to challenge me?
You gotta go all the way when you win
or it'll come back to bite you!
Finishing Move: Sen-i-Soshitsu!
SEN-I-SOSHITSU (FIBER LOST)
- She did it!
Boy, that was over faster
than I expected, you know?
What's wrong, Senketsu?
I have not achieved
Sen-i-Soshitsu yet.
I was unable to absorb
her Life Fibers.
Underestimate the Elite Four
at your peril, Ryuko Matoi.
Encore!
- Encore!
- What the hell?
Encore!
En— What's that?
THREE-STAR GOKU UNIFORM
SYMPHONY REGALIA DA CAPO
Symphony Regalia: Da Capo!
For our encore, let's go
with one of the standards!
- There's more?!
- There's more?
What you are about to witness is the true
power of a Three-Star Goku Uniform!
Jakuzure never knows when
to end a performance.
They drag out
after the encore.
For my finale, a tune known to children everywhere!
Beethoven's Symphony No. 5: "Fate"!
The sound on that thing!
I'm just getting warmed up!
What's wrong, Senketsu?
Your connection is weak!
I don't know.
But your voice is faint.
My voice?
Yes. And that music
sounds incredibly loud.
What?
I see you are confused,
transfer student.
The rhythm blasted out
by my Goku Uniform
resonates with the targeted Life Fibers,
manipulates them, and inflicts damage.
That is the power of my
Symphony Regalia Da Capo!
You've been reduced to a wooden doll that can only
sit there and bear the brunt of my baton's attacks!
What are you doing, Matoi?
You're supposed to fight me and
fall before my bamboo sword!
Whose side are you on?!
Pipe down, wild monkey!
It's bad manners to talk
during a performance!
Everybody around here keeps
running off at the mouth...
Shut out all the extraneous noise, Senketsu.
As much as I'd love to,
every last Life Fiber in my body is vibrating to that music.
All right, then...
And now, it's time for the
encore to come to an end!
Here's your finale!
Your "fate" ends here!
Ryuko!
My music isn't ringing out?
It's not that it isn't
ringing out.
Whatwhatwhatwhat?
What is it?
Matoi is taking the rhythm
emanated by Jakuzure
and using that technique to make it
resonate and turning it into a pure tone.
Pure tone?
She's altering the frequency of the waves
Jakuzure is giving off to match her own.
Oh, I see!
Although the sound
is muddy on impact,
it eventually matches her own natural
frequency. Just like a tuning fork.
So what you're saying is,
Ryuko is really awesome!
Mankanshoku has boiled down your
complicated information to its essence.
This is what you mean
by pure tone?
This is what I mean
by pure stupidity.
Can you hear now, Senketsu?
Yes, loud and clear.
This is your heartbeat, Ryuko?
That's right, ignore
every other sound.
Just focus on mine.
It is most pleasant.
So this is your sound.
Impossible! My attack isn't working?
No, it's much worse
than that.
Time to... send it back!
SENKETSU MUBYOSHI (SOUND NEGATION)
Senketsu Mubyoshi!
She's trying to drive me back?
Over my dead body!
What's that? I can't hear a
single note you're playing!
Y-You stinking, stinking,
stinking bitch!
Give it a rest, already!
No way!
The frequencies emitted by the Kamui,
which is made of 100% Life Fibers,
are far more powerful than
Jakuzure's Goku Uniform!
Her sound is being negated!
M-My Symphony Regalia!
Let's do it!
Scissor Blade: Decapitation Mode!
It's curtains for you!
Finishing Move: Sen-i-Soshitsu!
SEN-I-SOSHITSU (FIBER LOST)
I see, that girl is
wearing a Kamui!
That's so cute!
Did you see that, Iori?
I did. I have located the problem areas in
the Shackle Regalia and Probe Regalia.
Examination of Symphony Regalia
is still underway.
Very good. See to it.
Understood.
All right, let's get
to work, people!
Let me tell you two useful
pieces of information.
One: Clothing that develops rips
must be taken off.
Two: you should also take off that depressing
getup, the sooner the better!
It's a disguise, a disguise!
If I paraded in front of them in all
my nude glory, I'd draw attention.
I'm keeping up appearances.
You're as big a pain
in the ass as ever.
Here, this is the item
you asked for.
This is the only one,
so use it carefully.
Sorry for making you
bring it all this way.
They were nervous
back at HQ.
I can't believe you're going to
be the one to use this bullet.
Is Matoi that strong?
In mere hours, she's absorbed
two Three-Star Goku Uniforms.
Compared to the Ryuko you fought,
this one's on a whole different level.
WINNER: RYUKO MATOI
She did it! She did it,
she did it, she did did did it!
You're here too, Jakuzure!
I managed to collect excellent data.
Thank you.
Bite me.
The next time you butt in, I'm gonna switch out
the lenses of your glasses with non-prescription ones.
Oh, how fascinating. I'll file away
that bit of snide commentary.
Excuse me, aren't you going
to chew out Jakuzure?
Y'know, like, "Why are you
wearing a tracksuit?"
I'm not that sort of
shameless wretch.
Oh, girls get a free pass!
So, it's finally my turn, is it?
Come at me, Sanageyama. Time to finish
our fight from the other day.
I ain't gonna run this time!
You wouldn't be Ryuko Matoi
if you did.
The woman who took my eyes
and gave me the world.
This time, I will take you down!
I'm going to take the liberty of
putting her down, Lady Satsuki.
Very well.
Round 4, begin!
Senketsu Senjin,
and then Senketsu Shippu, eh?
Your evolution
is astonishing, Matoi.
But it's no match
for my growth!
Let's go!
Three-Star Goku Uniform:
Blade Regalia MKII!
THREE-STAR GOKU UNIFORM
BLADE REGALIA MKII
Life Fiber Synchronize:
Kamui Senketsu!
KAMUI SENKETSU
W-Who are you?
Sanageyama! Get back!
Lady Satsuki has lost her cool!
I've never seen that
happen before.
That girl is totally cute, though!
But her identity is unknown.
Who the heck
is that girl?
Just when it was getting good!
Time's up.
You lousy skinflint!
Honey! More money!
We're flat broke.
No other choice, then!
Let's roll, my family!
To where?!
To the Honnouji Academy
fighting arena!
If it's come to this, we'll sneak in
using any means necessary!
You got it, Dad!
Who the hell is that?
Why have you come here,
Nui Harime?
NUI HARIME
KIRYUIN MANOR BATHS
RAGYO KIRYUIN
Now, which of you will
adorn me today?
REI HOUOUMARU
Sorry I'm late, Hououmaru.
No, Ma'am, you are
right on time.
However...
However? What is it?
The Grand Couturier is currently
visiting Honnouji Academy.
I'm aware.
You are such a scamp, Ma'am.
I am simply playing along
with her whims.
Shall I take us to Honnouji Academy?
No. It's time for the regular
worldwide branch meeting.
Take us to the home office.
At once.
NUI HARIME
This isn't fair,
Lady Satsuki, doing something this fun without telling me!
I'm not obligated to
tell you anything.
Gosh, how cold! I thought you and I
were two hearts beating as one!
Both day and night!
Don't be insincere.
You associate with no one.
You're as breathtaking as ever!
Your icy stare and icy skin are simply too much!
My fingers are tingling!
Stand aside, woman.
I won't tolerate any further
interference in my fight with Matoi.
I'm sorry, I can't do that!
After all, I'm the one
who's gonna fight her!
I told you to get
out of the way!
Hup!
What?!
She blocked a Three-Star opponent!
Without a uniform?!
Who the hell is that girl?!
I have a bad feeling about this.
A bad feeling?
Yes, overwhelmingly bad.
Gosh, this won't do.
You're no fun at all.
Eat this! Finishing move:
Isshin Zenzanken!
Hup!
Go on back to being
a naked ape!
Impossible!
Hup!
Oopsie, he fell!
Oh, well!
A Three-Star Goku Uniform unraveled
by pulling at a single thread!
How can that be?!
Isn't it your job to explain exactly this
sort of thing at times like this?
Impossible. I cannot analyze
something without data.
It's the red thread of fate!
The invisible thread that connects the pinkies
of people destined for each other!
Where are there pinkies
on clothing?
But it turned red just now!
Quit bugging me, underachiever!
"Goku Uniform," was it?
Lady Satsuki's vaunted combat uniforms.
The stitching is a bit weak,
don't you think?
She severed its Banshi?
BANSHI
Impossible! No one can spot the Banshi
at a glance and sever it in an instant!
What is a Banshi?
What happened, Iori?
A Banshi is a Life Fiber that has been imbued
with the will to become clothing.
The thread that is the key
to creating a Goku Uniform.
It has multiple layers of defenses to prevent it
from feeling the effects of an attack.
Even when Matoi's Kamui absorbs Life Fibers,
the Banshi is the very last one to go.
It's inconceivable that she could have
pulled it out in that instant and cut it!
See? It really is the
red thread of fate!
Don't pat yourself
on the back, underachiever!
It's Mako!
Mako Mankanshoku!
UNDERACHIEVER
MAKO MANKANSHOKU
I may be an underachiever,
but I do have a name!
You voluntarily admit
to being an underachiever?
That's the spirit, Mankanshoku!
Damn it, who the hell
is that woman?
We have a real bigshot
on our hands.
FIRST ANNUAL
NATURALS ELECTION
Nui Harime,
the Grand Couturier herself.
Grand Couturier?
Revocs'?
Who else has one?
The home office's
High Order Tailor is here.
In other words, the one who sent her here
NUI HARIME
is none other than Revocs' top dog and Satsuki's mother:
Ragyo Kiryuin.
Oh, man. Things are getting
more complicated by the minute.
You're okay with this,
right, Lady Satsuki?
You're asking for my permission?
Yes! I've never disobeyed you, have I?
Whatever, let's just get to it!
Ryuko!
Satsuki Kiryuin, if I have to go through her
to get to you, I don't care who she is.
Suit yourself.
Please gather your
composure, Milady.
Thank you.
For Harime to show up now,
of all times...
How very like her.
You mean Mistress Ragyo?
Who else could it be?
It's in your hands now,
Ryuko Matoi.
RYUKO MATOI VS UZU SANAGEYAMA
RYUKO MATOI VS NUI HARIME
Where's your Goku Uniform?
I don't wear such crude things.
Enough about me,
show me your Kamui.
Are you holding back
because I'm dressed like this?
Didn't you see? I defeated
that Goku Uniform just now,
so you can cut loose with your
Kamui's power all you want!
Having trouble? In that case,
I'll show you something neat!
Here we go!
Ta-dah!
That's...!
Yep, the other half of
your Scissor Blade!
I pulled this
out of your dad!
Wait... It was you?
Yep! It was me!
I was the one
who killed your father!
BITCH!
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Shouting, "Up yours!" out towards
the sea, that's youth!
UP YOURS
THAT IS
Getting dumped by the girl
you like, that's youth!
THAT IS
RAGE
Giving in to rage and destroying
the entire school, that too is youth!
DESTROYING
THAT IS
No, wait, that's bad!
Calm down, Ryuko!
THAT'S BAD
MANKANSHOKU BACK-ALLEY ON-CALL CLINIC
Next time on Kill La Kill,
"Spit Your Sadness Away"!
EPISODE 12
SPIT YOUR SADNESS AWAY