Five, four...
Three, two...
One, zero.
It's taking you too long
to line the pins up with the shear line.
I'm sorry I have to keep asking you
to help me with this, Miss Dorothy.
Oh, it's not your fault.
I mean, the other options...
Watch.
All right.
Um, how did you do that?
Watch closely.
See?
No, I, um...
There. Now you try.
They're just not cut out to be teachers.
I believe they are saying rude things about us.
I think it's fair to get angry.
Maybe we should go with something simpler.
You really like that song, don't you, Miss Dorothy?
Was I singing?
Yes! You hum that tune all the time.
Do I?
Not him, either.
The Kingdom Foreign Office's cipher?
Yes. It's been planted inside the liaison's body.
Inside the body? And you want me
to grab the liaison and remove the cipher?
He's already dead.
He should be taken to the morgue in the next few days.
You want me to raid a corpse.
It's better than killing, I'd say.
Numbers one and two
on my list of least favorite spy jobs.
What's the target's name?
We don't know.
Don't tell me you want me to clean out
every corpse in the morgue?
The Duke of Normandy has an accomplice there.
He knows who to look for.
I'm supposed to be working Operation: Changeling.
Why did you choose me?
Because that accomplice is someone
with whom you are well acquainted.
Danny MacBean.
Your father.
Oh, it was just a cat.
Sorry to drag you along for this.
Not at all.
If anything happens, I'll need someone to act as liaison.
Of course.
But what IS this place?
We call it Ghost Street.
They say half the people
who go down this road never come back.
Half?
Why is that?
Because it leads to the morgue.
We're always shorthanded here.
I'll have you get right to work.
Yes, Ma'am.
The work is nothing too complicated.
When the bodies come in,
you remove their clothing and wipe them clean.
Then you look for anything that might identify them.
If no one comes to claim them,
we put them on the carriage to the graveyard.
Every day it's more of the same.
Damn you, you were laughing at me!
No, I was...
That's right! It wasn't about you!
Defending her, are you?
I bet you two are friends in bed, too!
You're joining giblets, ain't ya?
We are not!
That's quite enough, Danny!
No, I can tell! The bitch and the studhorse!
For goodness' sake, not him again.
He's as low as they come, isn't he?
Er, um...
Daisy!
Daisy, is that you?!
Too stubborn to pop off, eh?
That's my girl!
Yeah. It's been a while, hasn't it, Dad?
Oh, my. The morgue?
Yes, dead bodies from all over London end up there.
I didn't know so many people died every day.
Oh.
And Control is so awful.
They know about Miss Dorothy's situation,
yet they're making her spend time
with that horrible father.
Father?
N-never mind.
Wh-what tea would you like to have tonight?
How about Uva? Or would you prefer Keemun?
And what brings you here, Young Lady?
Eh?
Is it debt? Or are you an immigrant?
Um, well...
Oh, you don't have to tell me if you don't want to.
Everyone here has their reasons.
This place is largely ignored by the rest of the world.
And that's exactly what some of us want.
Even you, Sir?
My leg was ruined in the War.
I killed too many people.
And all my friends are gone.
Maybe that's why.
I feel right at home working with the dead.
If we steal the cipher, then Dad will...
Why? Of all the possible...
My luck is changing, I swear.
You want me to pay back what I owe, don't ya?
I'm a lot of things, but I ain't a liar.
Just taking a bit longer than planned, is all.
So...
You still have work to do.
I'm taking a break, Love.
Danny.
Who is this woman?
My daughter, Daisy.
By pure coincidence,
she came to work with me just the other day.
Ooh, a touching reunion.
A looker like you must have any number of men
dying for your hand.
I want to earn my own money.
I'd be up the creek if my future husband
ended up like my dad.
Daisy! What do you know about anything?!
It's true, isn't it?!
There are plenty of people out who've gotten hurt
and are still doing what they can!
You're just using your injury as an excuse to run away!
Daisy!
Wait, Daisy!
Ah-ah-ah. Our discussion isn't over.
Miss Dorothy-
Well, you should listen to your daughter and get to work.
I didn't lose my hand 'cause I wanted to!
Damn it all to Hell!
Damn you all!
Little brat ain't lived half as long as I have!
What does she know?!
She's got no idea how much I've... how much I've...!
Please stop it!
You should be ashamed of yourself!
Taking your anger out on everything around you!
Who the Hell are you?
You're her father, aren't you?
Then maybe you should start to act like it, Sir!
What did you say, you little brat?
What's this thingamajig?
Please don't do that!
You're an interesting little girl.
No, stop!
Stop that!
Huh?
Daisy...!
Are you all right, Beatrice?
Y-yes.
A-a friend of yours, is she?
We... we were just having a little laugh.
Weren't we?
Don't touch her!
Let's go.
Wait.
Wait, Daisy!
Don't...
Please don't leave me!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, Beatrice.
He can't control himself.
He used to be an expert steam engineer.
But he got hurt in an accident, and it changed him.
Oh, his right hand...
He hates everyone around him, envies them.
He blames all of his problems on everyone else.
Why're ya looking at me like that!
If you have something to say, then say it!
You think I'm a laughingstock, too!
What's wrong?
Why don't you run out on me like SHE did?!
That's dreadful!
He's a weak man.
He would beat me within an inch of my life,
then he'd always...
I'm sorry, Daisy. I'm so sorry.
I couldn't take it anymore, so I ran away.
To what is now the Commonwealth.
The Revolution came that same day.
So you could never go back.
Pretty much.
It was a relief, actually.
I figured I'd never have to see him again.
Mum ran out on us both, so I'm grateful
that he didn't abandon me, too, but...
Why are you telling me all this?
I thought spies didn't reveal their histories.
That's definitely true of Ange.
I think...
I'm weaker than she is.
That, and...
...I thought if anyone would understand, you would.
Sorry.
Well, if that's how you're going to talk, Miss Dorothy,
this isn't just a cover anymore... we're real friends now!
What? Did I say anything to imply that?
Do you really believe that?
That you can change the world?
Yes.
But even if you could become Queen...
I want to stop having to hide our relationship, Charlotte.
So do I!
But we're not the only ones who feel this way.
Parents, siblings, lovers, friends...
So many people have been torn apart by that Wall.
One day, their voices will all come together.
Like a giant wave.
And you're going to wait for it?
I've waited ten years already.
Besides, it won't be like those ten years anymore.
You're not alone anymore.
I can't believe you're already drunk.
Ugh, you're getting old.
Eh, shut up! I'm still...
Come on, we're here!
Well? Brings back memories, don't it?
Come on in, Beatrice.
He won't be waking any time soon.
All right.
He must have some way
to contact the Duke of Normandy.
It should be in here somewhere.
I'll help you look.
This is...
The Moon is beautiful.
And we fell...
Like he hasn't a care in the world.
Owww...
Are you all right?
Dorothy?
I'm Daisy.
Oh, right. Of course.
You know Mum would never come back here.
Want some water?
No, I'd rather be drunk, thanks.
Anyway, we need to talk.
I'm not interested in a walk
down our rubbish memory lane.
It's about money.
A body's gonna show up at the morgue.
One with a cross carved into the palm of his hand.
And there's a note hidden in his tooth.
What's the point of that?
It doesn't matter.
The important thing is that
if we take it to a certain person, we'll be rich.
Got it, Daisy?
A cross on the palm of his hand.
When you find the body, you tell me straightaway.
All right, Dad. I got it.
Have you found the cipher?
We are currently searching for the body.
I've made arrangements at the morgue.
A scavenger, eh?
Can you trust him?
The man has debts to pay.
Those motivated by money
are always the most predictable.
W-wait, please!
I'll be getting the money soon, all of it!
Then I swear I'll pay you back!
And you expect me to believe that?
Oh, I know!
If YOU can't pay, maybe we'll ask
your daughter to get us the money.
She really is quite a beauty.
Say the word, and I could consider your loan repaid.
That's...!
What happened to your face?
N-nothing. Get back to work!
I bet it was just another drunken brawl anyway!
Miss Dorothy!
So that's the cipher?
Yes. I'm going to copy it.
We can't just take it with us?
We don't want the Duke of Normandy to find out.
Besides...
This will help my dad.
Never mind. Let's hurry.
Right.
Not him, either.
Owww. Dammit.
If I just had the money, I'd kiss this place goodbye.
Dad!
What? What do you want?
I found it!
Here.
You did it, Daisy!
That's my girl!
Ugh, don't get carried away.
Get away from me, you reek of booze.
Don't say that!
You'll be drinking with me tonight! To celebrate!
Uh, wait!
Dad!
Oh, pardon me.
Wait for me at the pub on Ghost Street!
Bring your friend!
I'm kissing this rubbish life goodbye!
Money, money! I'm rich!
I'm here, my lovely.
Do you have it?
I wouldn't be here if I didn't.
Let me make sure.
Ah-ah-ah, terms first.
You need it, don't you?
So let's see a little more money in return, eh?
The pub on Ghost Street?
Yeah. Dad told me to meet him there.
That's wonderful.
You patched things up with your father.
Oh, I don't know about that.
What's this?
Goodness gracious, she came with a bonus!
I didn't think he'd give me TWO.
What surprisingly good service.
What are you talking about?
Oh, no, didn't he tell you?
Your father owes me a lot of money.
She's a nice bit of skirt, too.
That'll cover interest and then some.
I don't follow.
It's only logical that the daughter
would shoulder her father's debt, isn't it?
Don't hate me. Hate the fact
that you had that louse for a father.
Wait for me at the pub on Ghost Street!
I'm kissing this rubbish life goodbye!
Dad...
You just have to face facts.
And you, too, Little Lady.
Wench!
Hey, stop! What is wrong with you, woman?!
Sorry, but I am beyond furious right now.
I can't hold myself back!
What are you doing?
Get up and show her what for!
Beatrice!
G-got it!
Damn you!
Why did I ever think SHE was a looker?
You she-devil!
Ow, that hurt!
No, stop! Stop!
Y-you came here alone, so I assumed
he'd given his seal of approval!
What do you mean?
I told him to give us his daughter to pay off his loan.
And he...
Soon! I'm getting a lot of money soon!
Let go of me!
I swear I'll pay you back!
So please, not my daughter! Anything but that!
We hit him, we kicked him, but that's all he would say!
Like a broken record.
Dad...
Took quite a lot of work getting this.
Searching corpses with my daughter, day in and day out.
Your daughter?
That's right.
That's why I want you to pay both of us.
I wouldn't recommend getting too greedy.
She's a beautiful girl.
I'm gonna buy her some clothes,
and we'll walk around town together.
I'll say, "Look at that? Ain't she a beauty?"
to everyone we meet.
Because it's a miracle.
I never thought I'd see her again, but there she was.
So we need some funds to start over.
I'm gonna say goodbye to this rubbish life,
and turn over a new leaf!
Really.
Then I'll help you.
I'll put an end to this "rubbish life" of yours.
No, I...!
What a busy pub!
There aren't any other good pubs in the area.
And they serve a pretty decent stout, if nothing else.
I'll excuse myself as soon as your father gets here.
Assuming he ever does.
He's not exactly the type to keep his promises.
But he really does care about you.
Oh, stop it.
If he had been even a little more decent a human being,
I wouldn't have run away.
And you wouldn't have become a spy?
I might be hawking bread for a baker somewhere.
Then I have your father to thank
that I got to meet you, Miss Dorothy.
Even if he is the weakest,
most worthless father of all time.
He was a good dad, back when he was still an engineer.
He used to sing me to sleep.
Dad and I both loved that song.
The Moon is beautiful
And we fell in love
Come on, stop it!
On just a dazzling summer's night
That's pretty good, Miss!
Nice singing!
On just a dazzling summer's night
We dance the light steps of a merry melody
Laughing as we go
Exchanging kiss after kiss
So on nights when the moon is beautiful, remember
Although we're so far apart now
You are dearer to me than anything in the world
You're late.
Dad.
You are dearer to me than anything in the world
And I am here
Singing