"Want to commit double suicide with me?"
Just kidding... I just thought I'd say it.
You see, I...
Are you going to forget?
Kousei, do you feel sick or something?
I'm okay.
I'm asking because you don't look okay.
Why don't we go visit Kao-chan?
We haven't been able to go together lately.
It's been a while, let's go!
Hey, good idea.
I'm not going.
Did he have a fight with Kao-chan, maybe?
You okay with that? Saying such a thing...
What thing?
Like rubbing salt into your enemy's wounds.
Enemy?
If he's having issues over music,
then I don't know how to help him.
I just think that Kousei will
cheer up if he sees Kao-chan, so...
Well, I don't think it'll
kill you to dial it up a little.
For whose sake are you
studying against your will?
For whose sake did you choose
a higher-ranked high school?
Choosing a high school near
Okutsu Music College Affiliated High...
Who'd you do that for?
Oh! W-Well, you know! Kousei's
totally helpless on his own, so...
If only you'd be that honest
and tell him that yourself.
The truth is, I wish he wouldn't go at all.
It makes me feel anxious, and I get frustrated.
I feel like being snarky to him, too...
When he said he wasn't going,
I know I felt relieved. And full of guilt.
And since I don't want him to see me like
that, I'm doing my darnedest to put on an act.
Have I always been so horrible?
I'm discovering all these different sides
of myself that I never knew I had...
Facing all these different sides of me.
I guess that's also... What you call...
...being in love?
Your head is miles away.
Let's call it a day. Go on home.
I'm sorry.
Oh! Um, Seto-sensei, I have an emergency!
Sorry! I'm counting on you, okay?
Totsuhara University Hospital - 890m
Huh? Arima-sensei?
I was able to catch up to you
just walking at a normal pace.
You walk too slow. Your posture's terrible!
You need to get a grip, or you'll look like a slob!
May your dreams come true!
So this Kimoto dude, he goes, "I'll play my
oboe for you at the culture festival, Nagi-kun."
How deluded is that?
But wouldn't that be pretty thrilling?
Depends on who.
Comes down to...                                              probably their face.
You're such a realist!
Finally got you to laugh!
Thanks. Sorry to make you worry.
N-N-N-Not at all! Worry
about you? Are you crazy?
It would be a bore to have a wuss
for an enemy, that's all.
That guy, he's unbelievable, you know.
Everyone's freaked out because he's got the
whole score memorized perfectly,
but he doesn't even bat an eyelash.
What is he, a gunman out of a Western?
Sounds like a die-cast robot
with that heart of steel, huh?
Like a hero, right?
Dammit!
What am I... supposed to tell him?
Good luck... Don't let him beat you...
How irresponsible is that?
Kousei Arima
Sumitani Junior Highschool
So...
Instead of thanking him, my selfish way of
compensating for being so powerless...
...was only for self-satisfaction.
I'm an ugly phantom.
Kimoto-kun's gonna be a
great performer, you know.
What? You think so?
It's more important than you'd
think, playing for someone else.
What are you going to play the
piano for? For someone else's sake?
You said you started playing
the piano for someone else, right?
That's when you're able to play well.
When you've shared those
sounds with tons of people,
when you've reached tons of
people with those sounds,
when your hearts come together...
It might be that music
transcends words.
That's just a cliché. Women are realistic.
We only believe in words.
May your dreams come true!
Ravel...
Welcome!
I don't want to hear it!
I don't want to hear Ravel!
Commit double suicide with me.
Welcome.
I don't want to hear it. I don't
want to think about anything!
I wish I could just stop hearing everything!
Music Preparation Room
Yo.
We're on our way to visit my Kaori-chan
in the hospital. Come with us.
I'm gonna pass on that.
No need to hold back because
of us. Come on, let's go.
I said I'm not going!
What's wrong with you?
Listen, you... don't you
think you're being callous?
After Kaori-chan did so much for
you, why are you running away?
Look at me!
H-Hey... Kousei...
Watari...
What am I supposed to do?
You see, I...
It doesn't look good for me.
It's not true. It's not true.
I'm so sorry.
...I made you remember something
you don't want to remember.
I guess maybe we never
should've met, huh?
I couldn't say a word.
What could I have said to her?
How should I act when I see her?
Listen, Kousei.
This is just my opinion, but... I think
you should go see Kaori-chan after all.
Sure, if she was okay with me, I'd do
anything in the world.
If it was for a girl I liked, I'd even drink muddy water,
just slurp-slurp-slurp, you know?
But you know what, I think for
Kaori-chan, I'm not the one, you know?
When she wants her own way
or needs to lean on somebody...
Whenever she wants
somebody to do something for her,
it's you she always turns to, Kousei.
Enter a competition!
Be my accompanist!
I wish I could have a canelé.
Please support me in this moment
that I'm about to lose heart.
But I just don't know what to say to her.
Don't sweat it... you'll know once you're there.
A man can only take action!
But for me, it's impossible.
Whether or not it's impossible,
the girl will let you know.
"I didn't think you'd ever come again."
Because I promised to bring you some canelés.
Have you been practicing the piano?
Yeah.
How's school?
The same as usual.
How's everybody doing?
So-so.
What kind of answers are those?
You don't even want to be here, do you?
Yes I do!
I do, but I don't know what to say, that's all.
Just go back to the way things were before.
You can just forget about it all, like
you've pressed the reset button.
Tap, tap, tap... like that.
Why would you...
I won't forget.
And that will make your heart lighter.
There's no point in remembering, anyway.
A violinist who can't hold
her own bow... that's pointless.
Why would... why would
you say such a thing?
After all that howling, slapping me around,
forcing me up onstage against my will...
After carving so many scenes into
my mind that I don't want to forget...
That's my canelé!
Like I'd let such a cranky whiner
have it? I'd feel sorry for the canelé!
But I'm the one who asked for it!
I'm the one who bought it!
What's that?
That's that!
Not again...
You're irresponsible!
I wash my hands of you!
Wait–
You really are a weird one.
I feel so bitter... so bitter...
And it's just so sad.
You gave me so many things...
Isn't there anything I can do for you?
If it was for a girl I liked,
I'd even drink muddy water.
I want him to notice... that
I'm here... with my playing.
I drew this...
Whaaat? You want to perform
at the culture festival?
A bolt out of the blue? I don't
get it! What are you thinking?
You're really pushing it.
Please!
Fine.
No way! But it's your big moment.
What am I gonna do? Are you really sure?
I only asked because
I had nothing to lose.
Grovel some more, Kousei Arima!
I don't really know where this is coming from,
but since I was struggling to
come up with a program...
and I think it'll be intriguing...
Thanks.
Arima-sensei... why do you want to
perform at the culture festival?
Hey, there, my princess.
Wanna discuss The Knight
of the Rose with us?
We reserved a booth at a diner for you.
Nagi, let's have a crepe on the way home.
Can't do it.
You have a date?
Make it sound more springy.
Use your wrists to play softly.
Maybe you should wait an extra beat.
Speed up the intro and vary the pace.
No way! How many times did you go over it?
It's even more accurate than yesterday.
You're not eating?
No. I'm not really hungry.
I'm gonna go practice.
She's pushing herself too hard, don't you think?
I made a mistake! I'm sorry!
Don't worry about misplaying the notes
sometimes. Let's hear you play it through.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
Good luck! We'll be there, no matter what!
You're this year's main draw!
Ibata-sensei will be in the audience.
So turn in a perfect performance.
If he acknowledges your
talent, you'll be set for life!
I hear they're sending a reporter.
They're doing a feature on
"a beautiful young female pianist."
Four more days.
I'm looking forward to this.
Four more days. I only have four
more days to make this piece my own.
We have high hopes for you!
She gets extra points for
her looks, don't you think?
The magazine writer's
coming just to see Nagi.
She'll own everyone
else without even trying.
Lolicon bait!
Your parents must be so proud.
Good luck!
She's nothing but a pretty face.
I've got to endure this
suffering for another four days?
Hey! Nagi!
Help me, Mom... My hearing...
Once again, I'm a failure as an instructor.
I'm about to let history repeat itself.
Nagi...
I...
I'm afraid. Even though
it's just a school event...
even though it's not an
important competition.
We're all afraid. Even me, even Kousei...
And I'm sure even Takeshi Aiza-kun...
Your whole life is condensed
into a scant few minutes onstage.
Sure it's scary, and it
makes no sense, either.
Then why are you still a pianist, Seto-sensei?
Once you get past that, there's a
moment when the slate gets wiped clean.
All the months of agony,
screaming, suffering, and struggling...
There's a moment when
you're rewarded for all that.
When you've reached tons
of people with those sounds,
when your hearts come together...
music just might transcend words.
Maybe we're creatures who just
can't help ourselves... possessed by that moment.
It's a little like being in love.
We...
Gotcha!
Don't monopolize the bathroom!
I give up!
Koharu, at least take the left leg!
Your place is not here in the bathroom.
You're afraid to go out onstage
because you practiced so hard.
You gave your body and soul to the piano,
and that's why you're afraid to expose them.
If anyone calls you a "mentally unprepared
coward," I'll kill them myself.
Throw out that non-existent chest of
yours. You're Kousei Arima's apprentice!
No, I'm not! He's my enemy!
That's the spirit!
Now let's settle this
once and for all, onstage...
Watari?
Huh?
I want you to do something for me.
Sure.
But I haven't told you anything yet.
If it's you who's asking,
it's cool.
Kurumi School Festival
Kuru School Festival
This is the scent of pure, musical maidens!
The place is packed
with cute girls! Woo hoo!
You're like a walking hard-on.
Hey! This way, right?
Looks like it's already started.
Too bad they're plodding along like
that when they've got those costumes on.
That's what makes them cute.
Nagi-chan will be up soon, right?
How did that turn out?
Who knows? She wouldn't
even tell me a thing about it.
Could it be that she's outgrown
her big brother complex?
Must be sad for you, Big Bro!
Nah, it's a relief.
Good job, Komugi!
I think I did a good job!
Huh? Where's Nagi?
Namahage?
Bad kids will...
They're getting huge laughs?
That's gonna make a serious act
like ours stick out like a sore thumb!
This school festival is a terrifying event!
Are you okay?
O-O-O-Of course I'm
okay, why wouldn't I be?
You're quite calm yourself, Arima-sensei!
Lose your head more!
I'm so overwhelmed, I don't
have time to be nervous, I guess...
That's right. The first time I met you,
your hand was trembling, too.
What do you think you're doing,
you pervert? You sexual harasser!
If you squeeze my hand so
hard, your fingers will lock up.
Now open up your hand... and relax...
We're all afraid. Even me, even Kousei...
Were you driven into a corner, too?
Are you afraid, too?
The same way... I am?
A friend of mine told me once.
"Just play with sincerity, give the performance
of your life with everything you've got."
But... I've only lived for thirteen years.
Even if it's only been thirteen years... for you,
and for everyone who's watched you till now,
it's thirteen years that can't be replaced.
Let's believe in it, the time
you've devoted to music.
Performer No. 8,
please take the stage.
That's us...
All right, let's go!
Right.
Twilight
Episode 18
Watch Again Next Week!