On the night of Christmas Eve,
I made up with Shiina,
and passed the "Let's Make
a Game" proposal screening.
If things had gone well between
Jin-san and Misaki-senpai,
it would have been the
perfect Christmas Eve.
But...
So, how did it turn out like this?
Idiot.
#15 Where is My Usual Self?
Hey, Shiina, you remember
what I said, right?
Chihiro-sensei's going on vacation
to Australia over winter break,
so we can't stay in Sakura Hall.
I know.
Then, why haven't you asked
Rita to come get you?
You realize we're all going home, don't you?
Aoyama-san, don't tell me you...
I-It's not like that!
My head's been full of other thoughts,
and I completely forgot
about going home.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm really sorry.
Forgetting that is a huge problem!
I can't go home anyway, so I'm sorry...
S-So, what about you, Misaki-senpai?
I don't want to go home.
My hometown's full of
memories of me and Jin.
I don't want to go home.
Senpai...
In that case, you'll all have
to go stay at Kanda's place.
What?
S-Sensei, what are you saying?!
I'm leaving this afternoon.
Make sure you're packed
and ready to leave by then.
Sorata, strike while the iron's hot.
What?!
It's already been decided?
Komachi, this is a bullet train.
It's fast, isn't it? Whoosh!
I'm glad we found people to
take care of the other six.
Yeah, only Komachi was left behind.
Look, it goes 285 kilometers
per hour! Zoom!
Do you regret it?
Worrying about the past
doesn't do any good.
I want to focus on the future.
That's some backwards optimism.
You can have this.
I prefer bamboo shoots...
I gave my last bamboo shoot to Nanami.
Sorry, I already ate it.
You rushed to eat that, didn't you?
Misaki-senpai, do you
want some mushrooms?
I like bamboo shoots.
Okay, that's enough!
I'll eat all the mushrooms, okay?
We will shortly be arriving in Hakata.
Thank you for using the
bullet train today.
What?! Wh-Wh-What are all
these people doing here?!
Uh, th-thanks for letting
us stay with you...
I can't do it! I can't stay at a boy's house!
You're saying that after coming this far?!
And there're even more
sweet and fragile girls now!
Nice to meet you. I'm Kamiigusa Misaki.
Huh? Um, nice to meet you.
She's right...
Oh, my. Welcome, everyone!
You must be the friends Sorata
mentioned on the phone.
You're all such cute girls.
Huh? What?!
I'm the only one who didn't know?
I thought it might be more fun that way.
Successful Surprise!!
Mom's teasing me!
Sorata, you're back.
Y-Yeah...
I'm home.
I don't recall allowing
you to be polygamous.
Not even the country's laws allow that!
Come on, everyone.
Dinner's ready. Come on in.
E-Excuse us...
This'll be a fun end to the year.
I think I understand how you
adapted to life in Sakura Hall.
I'm starting to feel the same way.
I wonder if Jin's had his dinner...
Did you suddenly get an urge
to hear my voice?
That's exactly it.
That's nice of you to say.
Do you understand my situation?
I'm currently in Fukuoka with everyone...
Chihiro-chan told me.
I respect you. So, what do you want?
What happened between you...
and Misaki-senpai on the
night of Christmas Eve?
I told Misaki I love her.
I confessed my love to Misaki.
Wh-What are you talking about?
If that's the case, why is Misaki-senpai...
I asked for more time because I love her.
Time?
College Entrance Examination Series
Osaka Art Schools
I'm going to college in
Osaka to chase my dreams.
Just because I love Misaki...
No, exactly because
I'm in love with Misaki,
I can't become a worthless
man who's abandoned his goals.
I want to move forward for once, too.
"Let's Make a Game"
Rhythm Battler Vol. 1
Rhythm Action Battle Game
Entry No. 06848860
Kanda Sorata
Well, there you have it.
Take care of Misaki for me for a while.
She'll get jealous if I talk to you
for too long, so I'm hanging up.
Are you at one of your
girlfriends' homes?
I broke up with them all.
I'm staying with my friend,
the Student Council President.
Who are you calling your "friend"?!
See you later.
What?!
Mitaka, you...
Hey, Student Council President...
That's former Student Council President.
Do you think I'm wrong?
Yeah, you're wrong.
I see.
But you're also equally right.
Starting tomorrow,
I'll make dinner every night.
Every night?!
What do you want to eat?
Just get out of my house!
I'm stuffed!
Motsunabe, chanpon, mentaiko...
That's a real Hakata dinner right there.
Thank you, Nanami-chan.
It's like Sorata found himself a bride.
What?!
Y-You think I could
be Kanda-kun's bride?
What are you doing, Onii-chan? Hey!
Sorata, do you want a wife?
You'll have to defeat me before
you can marry my brother!
Get off me.
Sorata, you're too close.
I can't defeat Yuko like that.
Don't accept her challenge!
She's serious?!
In that case, I have to get into Suimei...
and face Mashiro-san
in an all-out battle!
I will have to use my Plan C on Yuko.
No annihilating!
But, Yuko, your father is opposed to
you taking the Suimei entrance exam.
I know! That's why I need
Onii-chan to convince—
No.
Instant rejection?!
Convince him yourself.
I'm busy during the break
preparing for my presentation.
Presentation? What's that?
Does it taste good?
Delicious!
I'll never let you take
the Suimei entrance exam.
I absolutely will not allow it!
That's final.
Oh dear.
Hey, Yuko-chan.
Do you want to start studying
together tomorrow?
Huh?
If your father sees you studying hard,
he might change his mind.
Aoyama...
What am I going to do, Onii-chan?!
Nanami-san's such a good person!
She's totally the one I need
to keep my eye on!
What are you talking about?
Jin! Did you finish writing the script?
Yeah, here.
Yeah! Thanks, Jin!
Okay, I'll start working
on some layouts!
Sure.
Misaki?
In other words, I shouldn't just
focus on giving the presentation,
but also put myself in the
shoes of the listener...
Presentation Techniques Lecture
Grab the attention of your listener!
That's right.
I believe it's important
to include information...
the screening committee
will find interesting.
I see. Maid-chan, thanks.
If you're truly grateful, why don't
you take a quick trip to England...
and take care of someone for me?
Sorry. I don't do those kinds of jobs.
I look forward to hearing the results.
You mean the results of
the presentation, right?!
Genre: Rhythm Action Game
Something interesting, huh?
Now I just have to figure
out what that is...
Game
Pitch Contents
Fun
Target
Concept
Benefits
Something the listener
will find interesting?
How to play
System
Controls
Appeal of the product?
I've written all the necessary
points in my pitch document.
What else would the screening
committee want to hear about?
Onii-chan, help me study!
Huh? Where's Aoyama?
She went shopping with Mom.
So, while she's gone, teach me.
That's a lot of books...
This magazine...
I was thinking about reading
it over my break.
You came here planning to take a break?
This is my oasis.
A manga I like is serialized in here.
It's written by someone called
Shiina Mashiro-sensei.
The art's really beautiful.
Oh, but there are some
weird characters.
These two.
Those are based on Jin-san
and Misaki-senpai...
Their expressions of emotion
leave something to be desired.
They won't get together,
but they won't break up either.
Who knows what they
really want? No, no!
Honestly, I don't understand it.
Don't understand...
Now that I think of it, Mashiro-san,
you've got the same name.
You're her?!
Yeah.
That's amazing!
I'm a huge fan!
Can I have your autograph?
That was a major change of heart.
Yuko-chan, there you are!
Sorry for making you wait.
Let's work hard together!
Mashiro-sensei, I'm cheering for you.
I look forward to next month's volume.
By the way, are you
going to meet your deadline?
You won't be able to use a
computer over the break...
I already did it.
What?
I gave it to Ayano.
I injured my finger.
I did it after it healed.
I see.
Is that right?
Huh?
Is that what you like about me?
Wha—
Since then, I've liked that about you.
Answer me.
Y-Yeah, that's right.
Good.
What? Is this for my presentation?
Use your abilities by hitting the
buttons in time with the rhythm!
Use combos to score lots of points!
Will you stop liking me if I
draw things that aren't manga?
I-I won't!
Good.
I've got to work hard.
No, really...
Thanks.
This concludes my pitch.
Thank you very much.
That was amazing, Onii-chan!
You've become a truly competent man!
Yeah, it's gotten a lot
easier to understand.
Sorata, you've grown so much.
That was so cool! I want to hear it again!
Aoyama, did you make these?
I thought Mom did.
She used to make them
for me all the time.
Y-Yeah, she taught me. Are they good?
Yeah.
They're great, thanks.
I-I see.
That's good.
You're so focused on your work,
you don't even eat dinner.
It's already New Year's Eve.
The presentation's right after the break,
but it took a while for it to take shape.
It was really good.
But I still feel a little uneasy.
Aoyama, if you were on
the screening committee,
what would you want to hear
during a presentation?
Who, me?
I don't know much about games, but...
Let's see...
If I worked for a company,
I might wonder if a game
would make money or not.
Sorry. That might be obvious.
No, I was so caught up in
whether it'd be fun or not,
I had completely forgotten about that!
That's amazing! Thanks, Aoyama!
You're always helping me out, Aoyama.
You made me rice balls for my
first presentation, remember?
Thanks for everything.
And you've got an audition coming up.
Sorry for being a burden.
No, it's okay.
I'm doing this because I want to.
Besides, doing other things
takes my mind off of it.
The only thing I can do until the script
arrives is prepare myself mentally...
Aoyama...
Oh, yeah...
Once my script gets here, I'll get you
to help me practice for my audition.
Here.
You don't have to do that.
I'd help you in any way I can.
What? Why?
W-Well, because I want you
to pass your audition.
I've been watching you work hard
since we were first years.
I... see...
But the truth is, I might just
actually want you to prove...
hard work is always rewarded.
Sorry, I shouldn't have said that.
No, it's fine.
Let's both work hard.
Yeah.
I'll work hard, too.
I want to work hard with you.
Shiina, you always work hard.
I-I think so, too...
There have been lots of things
I don't understand lately.
It's nothing.
Shiina?
There are lots of things
I don't understand.
Mashiron?
Misaki, how do you want
things to go with Jin?
Who knows what you want? "No, no."
Huh? What does that mean?
In my manga, you're together.
Is that wrong?
What's right?
What's...
I want to be with Jin.
If I were hurting Jin by making
animations, I'd stop animating...
I see.
Would Jin like you if you did that?
Sorata likes that I love to draw manga.
What does Jin like about you?
Do you have enough
chopsticks on that side?
Yeah, um...
Hey, do you have a minute?
I've never seen her study so hard.
But Dad opposes her applying to Suimei.
If you talked to Dad,
he'd allow it in an instant.
But Yuko asked you to do it.
Fine. Tell Dad...
that I need to talk to him
when he has a moment.
Okay.
Come on. Your noodles will get soggy.
I know what I told Mom, but...
How am I supposed to convince Dad?
Opportunity waits for no man!
What's wrong with you?!
What are you doing?!
If you make excuses by
saying you're not ready...
and let opportunities pass you by,
you'll never get another chance!
D-D-Don't get so close!
N-N-No!
You wanted to talk to me, right?
Your mother told me.
What?! That's why you came in here?!
Spit it out.
I wish you'd waited until
I got out of the bath.
There's one thing I need to teach you...
about life while I still
have breath in my body!
Opportunity waits for no man!
I got it already!
I wanted to talk about Yuko!
She seems to be taking studying seriously,
so can't you at least
let her apply to Suimei?
If she tries and fails,
Yuko will accept that, won't she?
Then, if she ends up attending a school
here, won't that put your mind at ease?
You've grown, a little.
Hey! Who are you talking to?!
My son.
Please just die already!
So, which girl are you serious about?
You just don't give up, do you?!
Why are you asking me questions
like we're kids at a sleepover?
You shouldn't be so indecisive!
I don't remember raising such a girly-ass son!
Can you just stop now?!
But it's your life.
Live it how you want to.
If you intend to go to college, don't worry.
I'll make enough money to pay
for your and Yuko's tuition.
I won't say it again.
Dad.
Well, in Yuko's case, it's probably...
impossible for her to get into Suimei.
I think so, too.
Hey, Sorata.
What?
I stayed in too long,
and now I can't move. Help me.
Apologize first!
Apologize for making me think
you were even a little cool!
It was probably a mistake to drink.
Don't get into the bath drunk!
Don't be stupid.
What man could talk
to his own son sober?
You're the girly-ass!
Sorata...
There's more?!
Happy New Year.
I'm not in any mood to
celebrate the new year!
Staying up to watch the sunrise is a bit
over-the-top for a New Year's celebration.
And the man who suggested it passed out.
What does Jin love about me?
Onii-chan, thanks for talking to Dad.
It sounded like he would have allowed
it even if I hadn't said anything.
Yeah, but thanks anyway.
I'm glad you're my brother.
Wh-What's that supposed to mean?
Mashiron, thank you.
I can't stop animating.
I just end up doing it.
Even now, I want to go back to
Sakura Hall and make more.
My head's full of thoughts of
background animations for this shot,
and original screen
splashes of that character!
Jin said he liked that about me!
I like you the way you always are, too.
S-So do I!
Me, too!
Yeah! I love myself, too!
Sorry for making you all worry!
But I'm okay!
Misaki-senpai.
I'll make Jin's anime!
Using the script Jin wrote,
I'll make an animation myself!
Let's do this!
I'll make Jin look at me this time!
I'll make my presentation a success!
I-I'll pass my audition!
Huh? Oh!
I'll get into Suimei!
Meatball beam, meow!
Don't use your special ability!
I like meatballs.
I hope Jin gets accepted.
All right! Let's sprint
towards the rising sun!
Misaki-san, there's a cliff over there!
Let's shout Geronimo and take the plunge!
Is she a monster?!
A paratrooper?!
A superhero?!
This girl's just plain weird!
The three days after Misaki-senpai's
revival flew by...
And the day came for us
to return to Sakura Hall.
Onii-chan, I'll be coming next
month for the entrance exam!
Kashiwameshi Bento
Our winter break's finally over.
Yeah.
Are you nervous?
Are you?
Things are just getting started.
Yeah.
I'll have to face that nervousness again...
But this time, I'm even
looking forward to it.
Both of us living together.
It's my job to make dinner.
#16 I've Always Loved You...
She stuffs her face with my
potato and onion miso soup.
Every time I see that smile, I...