Fast as Wind
Quiet as a Forest
Daring as Fire
Immovable as a Mountain
I'm hungry.
Dinner?
Dinner works.
I can offer to feed her.
Okay!
Hey...
Sour!
Get accepted to your first choice!
She brought food...
The Yamaguchis'
Son, Kenji-kun
I am very pleased with who I am.
I never wanted for anything as a child,
and I easily accepted and met
the expectations of my
parents and others.
I sound elitist?
If I'm not considered elite,
who is?
So then...
Why am I in this stuffy prep class?
Listen up!
College exams are a battlefield!
Fast as wind! Quiet as a forest!
Bold as fire! Immovable as a mountain!
Damn, the more I see her,
the harder she's studying.
How could I possibly be attracted to...
Sasaki Seminar
Pass Before Graduation
The pictures are ready.
That was fast.
Put a mark on the back
if there's one you want.
I can make copies.
That was lots of fun.
Next year!
Next year, we only invite
people who are really close!
People who are close?
You should bring your
family then, Natsume.
What?  M-My family...
Why are you so surprised?
Seriously...
Why does it have to be all or nothing?
Are you a robot?
You must have done a lot
of spying to take all these.
Hey, that's uncalled for.
I've got even better ones.
How many pictures did
you take, Sasayan?
Oshima-san happened to be there.
My face looks really round.
Hey!  What was that for, Yoshida?
I didn't want to see that.
You shouldn't take it
out on the picture.
Natsume-san, what are you doing?
Wait, what was I clapping for?
Shizuku, Shizuku.
Your underwear's showing in this one.
You're seeing things.
This one, too.
I want love!
I want love!  Passionate love!
Up for another group date?
Wait, you have class again today, Yamaken?
Yeah.
Don't tell me that
you're seriously interested
in the study bug.
I know it's almost Christmas,
but that's just wrong.
Idiot, I'm not like you fools.
Hey, Joji.
Christmas with
Everyone at RFC
See ya, Yamaken.
Don't look for girls on the Internet!
Oh, there you are!  Yamaken, lookit!
Lookit?
From: Yumi-chan
(No subject)
Sorry...
I'm not coming if
Yamaguchi-kun isn't there...
So don't talk to me.
That girl from Oto Girls'
wants you to ask her out.
Oto Girls'?
Screw that.
Tell her to come ask me out
if she's so interested.
What?
Otowa Girls' Academy?
I think she was pretty cute.
Oh, Yamaken, the door's not that way.
It's this way.
Be careful.
There you go.
I have no trouble getting women,
and that will never change.
Wha—
Damn!
Yamaken-kun.
Hello.
So plain.
No difference from that woman I saw earlier.
Don't tell me that you're seriously
interested in the study bug.
Am I supposed to hit on her?
I won't let myself sink that low.
Hey.
Excuse me.
Oh, thanks.
Get away from her, Yamaken.
Haru.
That hurt, bastard!
I hate it most when people touch my head!
Don't touch Shizuku.
You had a dirty look on your face.
The hell are you on?!
Haru.
I told you to stop following me.
I wasn't following you.
I was just passing by.
Yeah, this is stupid.
The hell you were!
Didn't you promise to care about
the things I care about?!
Why is he so upset about this?
That's different.  Doesn't count.
Does he have no pride?
Anyway, my response was made under
the assumption that I
would be able to study.
My grades are still more important!
"I love Haru."
It wasn't easy for me
to confess my feelings.
I didn't want any more mistakes.
I wanted him to understand...
But then...
Th-That means you won't
take the winter prep course?
In other words...
We won't get anywhere
if I'm the only one
doing the right thing.
Sasaki Seminar
Man, there's a bump now.
Damn, he's too strong for his own good.
Is that where Haru hit you?
Does it hurt?
Not really.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean for you to get involved.
Huh?
Why are you apologizing?
I decided to tell him how I feel,
but for some reason,
he was jealous of you
and derailed the conversation.
Dammit.
Did I do something wrong?
I told her to wait.
Well, you make a nice couple,
since you're so similar.
There are two types of people.
Dumb people and smart people.
You dumb people can only focus
on one thing at a time.
You can't see the big picture.
I'm on this side.
You guys are on the other side.
What makes us so different?
You wouldn't have to worry about
any of this if you went out with me.
What was that?
It sounded like I was hitting on her.
How can he be so confident?
Ow.
Oh, wow.
Ah, there's a bump.
You should put some ice on it.
Let's go.
I feel partially responsible.
Huh?
Oh...
No, it's okay.
Really?
If you say so.
Why did my heart just skip a beat?
Well, you should stay away from Haru,
and stay away from me.
Why should I give a damn about him?
You said that he's jealous?
What?
Are you bragging?
Bragging?
That wasn't my intention.
It just shows how much appeal you have.
Sasaki Seminar
Did you bring an umbrella?
Why?
It just shows how much appeal you have.
So she thinks I'm appealing?
Crap...
I can't stop smiling.
Yes!
Y-Yuu-chan, hold on.
I just saw someone
grinning like a fool.
He did some kind of victory pose.
Huh?
What are you doing here, Yamaken?
Isn't your class over?
Are you lost again?
Buzz off.
Why are you still hanging around here?
Are you a stalker?
Not really.
I kinda spaced out and
now it's dark out.
Wait, I just remembered...
He was definitely about
to push me off.
Am I in danger here?
Come on.
Will the bus stop work for you?
Or are you scared of me?
Idiot, don't insult me.
Stop following me.  It's creepy.
You probably think you're
special because you
got a higher grade than me.
That's why you get bullied,
and I'm the one bullying you.
Got it?  So watch yourself, newbie.
Got it, Yamaken.
Show some respect, Curly.
Curly?
And never walk in front of me.
You okay, Tomio?
Look out, Mabo!
Hey, aren't you guys finished yet?
Nice, Joji!
That's what you get!
Ow.
Hey.
Which one of you threw this guy?
You hit me.
Wait, aren't you...
Was it you?
Hey.
Huh?
You've changed.
Yo-Yoshida-kun thinks you
guys are his friends.
So, if you consider him a friend,
you should be honest with him!
I've changed?  Really?
I haven't changed.
Nothing's changed.
Shizuku's the one who keeps changing.
I can only wonder if she's going
to leave me behind one of these days.
Makes me consider tearing
off her arms and legs.
Your ideas are scary.
Yeah.
Well, I wouldn't do it.
No kidding!
That's why...
I'm always looking up.
Bye.
Yeah.
Yamaken.
I wouldn't do that to Shizuku,
but everyone else is fair game.
Ow.
That was a lame threat.
Jealousy, huh?
I don't think it's simple jealously.
Whatever.
You just sit tight.
Wow, Haru!
You can become an entomologist
when you grow up!
We don't have a choice.
It's what we have to put up
with to stay in this house.
Why did you run away from home?
Did you think you could
go back to Tone?
You're so dumb.
You and I have no place to go back to.
Yuzan!
Do you hate me now?
I wish I could.
Did you know, Haru?
You're the reason we were
brought to this house.
I'm guessing you've never
even tried to imagine
how I feel when I see you.
I've always wished that
you didn't exist.
What are you doing, Haru?
Were you waiting for me?
H-How am I supposed to react?
Should I be happy?
You're my hero, Shizuku.
You're always there when
I want to see you.
Huh?  Weren't you waiting for me?
I love you...
...Shizuku.
So why am I the only one
who has to show restraint?
You've been restraining yourself?
When and where?
I have.
I've been restraining
myself like crazy.
I wanted to storm in your
class and mess everything up.
If you do that, we're finished.
See?
Why do I have to suffer so much?
I love you.
I don't want you to hate me,
but I don't want you to
leave me behind, either.
Huh?  What?
What is he talking about?
What am I supposed to say?
I always believed
that if I told him and
showed him how I felt,
everything would work out.
I need some peace of mind.
I want proof.
I want you!
That's...
That's not happening!
Why...
Why do we keep clashing?
I'm guessing that we're
out of sync somehow,
but I don't know how to fix it.
I don't know the right answer.
Misawa Batting Center
Fierce
I feel like spaghetti tonight.
Pasta!
She can't bring pasta from home!
Would you be interested in—
Get accepted to your first choice!!
I see.
That keeps it warm.
Sasaki Seminar
Pass Before Graduation
I hate girls who are too domestic.
Next Episode
The Year Draws to a Close