Back then, I didn't
know what was going on,
or what they had talked about.
I didn't have any idea.
I didn't even know how I felt.
Senpai...
We were, uh...
I...
S-Sorry!
Senpai!
But I really didn't want to see it.
Huh?
Takatsuki-senpai?
Back then, I...
...was scared of facing...
...how I really felt.
Hm?
Tetsuro-san!
Huh?
He's so shy.
Actually, why am I...?
I think we're far enough away now.
That girl is way too aggressive.
Don't tell anyone!
Please, don't tell anyone!
T-Tell anyone what?
Tetsuro—
Let's head back.
If we don't get back soon,
Remon-senpai's going to be mad.
Um, I'll...
...head back to the room.
O-Okay.
I see. I'll head back first, then.
Hey, you're finally back!
S-Sorry.
What were you two doing?
We were—
He was giving me acting tips.
Umi-chan's such a perfectionist.
Really?
Yeah, it wasn't really
that big of a deal.
Anyway, where's Senpai—
Hey, there. Sorry I'm late.
That took a while.
Did something happen?
N-No, nothing really.
Anyway, where's Ichika-senpai?
I'm right here.
Huh? When did you come back?
Senpai, about what happened—
Let's start filming.
And action.
Give yourself up!
L-Listen to what I have to say.
You're a criminal.
Kinoshita started crying all of a sudden.
Does it have to turn out this way?
I have some money, if...
Then Senpai suddenly showed up.
And I just filmed, not knowing a thing.
In that case... Oh, a UFO!
I thought things felt kind of awkward...
Huh? Where? Where is it?
Over there!
Huh?
Right there!
...and that it couldn't go on like this.
Where?!
It's right there! There!
Here's my chance!
Please, let me go.
Then answer this question.
Why did you come to this planet?
And... And...
And what's your true goal.
Do you like Umi-chan?
Huh?
Wh-What?!
Cut.
S-Sorry.
Senpai?
Let's shoot that scene again,
from a different angle.
Okay.
Tanigawa, help me out.
Right. Mio, we're moving stuff.
Did I surprise you?
Okay!
Remon-senpai, you help out, too.
What about you?
I'm communicating with
the movie gods right now.
They're descending upon me now...
Kaito-kun...
Tetsuro-san!
Huh? Chiharu?
That girl's pretty aggressive.
Arisawa-san was her name, right?
She's cute. Tetsuro should
just date her already.
Don't say that to Tetsuro-kun.
Huh? Why not?
Just because.
Kitahara-san, could you hold up
the reflective board for now?
Sure...
We're going to continue filming.
Oh, okay.
Umi-chan!
Make sure I'm pretty.
Right.
Ichika, are you ready?
Y-Yeah, I'm fine.
Tetsuro-kun...
This should be far enough.
Far enough from what?
Tetsuro-san!
Tetsuro hasn't come back yet...
Mio disappeared once we finished, too.
Takatsuki-senpai isn't around, either.
K-Kaito-kun, you there?
Excuse me...
Huh? He's not here.
Kirishima-kun left in a
hurry just a minute ago.
I'm pretty sure he was
off to see Kinoshita-san.
I knew it. Kaito-kun likes Kinoshita—
No, he doesn't.
How do you know?!
Just by watching him,
I can tell what he's feeling.
Just by watching him?
That's right.
Then could you tell me...
Tell me how he feels...
Very well.
Let's have a long chat.
Kinoshita-sama in room
703 is currently out.
I-I see...
You're Kirishima-sama, correct?
We have a message for
you from Kinoshita-sama.
Okay...
You're late.
Wait up, Tetsuro-san!
How many hours is she
going to keep me running?
Is she some superwoman or something?
Wait!
Tetsuro-kun!
Mio?
Tetsuro-san!
Don't be so shy!
Tetsuro-san! Where are you?
You saved me again.
Thanks, Mio.
I'm just paying you back.
You didn't say anything.
About what, again?
You're really nice, Tetsuro-kun.
Yeah, I guess I am.
Just to cute girls, though.
I mean, uh...
Found you!
What?!
That was mean, Tetsuro-san.
Running around like that.
Not that I don't like
messing around like that.
Anyway, let's have fun
on the rest of our date.
W-We were on a date?
Of course we were!
Wai—
Huh? What?
No.
No!
You ask me to come here
and you show up late.
And now you're keeping quiet?
I'm sorry.
I couldn't get my thoughts together.
I wanted to ask you how you
really feel... about Kaito-kun.
I like him.
What would you do if
that was my answer?
A-Are you teasing me?
Sorry, I'm just a little jealous.
Huh?
I was dumped.
Hey, what are you doing?
T-Tetsuro-kun doesn't
like what you're doing.
And why would that be?
Right, Tetsuro-san?
I, uh...
See!
B-But...
Oh, I get it.
You like Tetsuro-san, don't you?
Huh?!
Huh?
Uh... Well...
Don't you think that's weird?
You're just some exhibitionist!
Now, wai—
I saw it!
When you came diving at us,
you weren't wearing any panties!
I mean, that's weird, right?
Really weird, right?!
I bet you're just a perv that
likes walking around
without anything on down there,
having fun imagining how people
would act if they caught a glimpse!
Tetsuro-kun wouldn't like
it if a girl like you—
Hey, that's enough—
I'm a nudist!
Huh?
I'm... a nudist!
Y-Y-You were dumped?
By Kaito-kun?
No, no.
By my senpai at my school back in Tokyo.
I came to Okinawa to get away.
Oh, I see.
And when I got here,
I ran into Umi-chan by chance,
and acted all happy to
distract myself from...
...how lonely I was after being dumped.
I ended up causing a lot of
problems by doing that.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
So that's what's going on.
Why?
Why were you crying?
Umi-chan said the same words my
boyfriend did when he dumped me.
It reminded me of that,
and I couldn't help but cry.
Umi-chan told me...
...that he likes someone else.
I think he was talking about you.
What are you say—
I can tell just looking at him.
I mean, I have known
him since he was small.
And you like him, too, don't you?
I-I...
So I wanted to apologize.
K-Kinoshita-sa—
See you tomorrow for the movie!
Apologize?
Huh? Senpai?
Kaito-kun...
Kinoshita told me to come here...
But why are you here?
Uh, Senpai?
I knew the whole time.
Knew what?
I'm sure I had known.
Senpai...
Could you tell me how
Kaito-kun feels now?
Let's see...
If you put this outfit
on, I'll think about it.
What? That again?
Episode 7
Senpai's feelings.
A nudist?
A nudist...
You mean a person that walks around
naked at home all the time, like that?
Yeah...
My family's like that, and I've been
like that since I was little.
I just thought that's what
you're supposed to do at home.
When I started elementary school,
I started realizing that wasn't right.
I mean, I can't really
tell anyone about this.
Uh...
I know you're supposed
to wear underwear.
But I've got really low blood pressure.
I kind of space out in the mornings,
and sometimes I forget
to put on underwear.
I end up going to school
and other places like that.
It's really embarrassing.
I know it's wrong for me to be like this,
and I've tried to lose the
habit over and over, but...
I ended up screwing up sometimes.
So I thought it'd be best if
no one knew who I was,
and I tried to avoid standing out,
but then Kanna started talking to me...
Tetsuro-kun and Kirishima-kun, too.
They all became my friends.
I was so happy...
It was so fun with them.
That's why I didn't want
them to find out.
I'm not a pervert!
Are you stupid or something?
If you forget so often,
then why not put a
spare pair in your bag?
Y-Yeah, but...
Then you could just pretend to go
to the bathroom and put them on.
I mean, you carry around
your PE clothes, right?
But...
Getting all worked up isn't
going to solve a thing.
You didn't want anyone
to know who you were?
That's being way too negative.
I know, but...
If you're having trouble, just
talk to everyone about it.
Everyone will help you out.
Kanna would, Kai would, even I would.
But...
No buts.
But if everyone hated
me because of that...
They won't hate you.
Really?
You can't trust us?
There you go.
So, just say what you
want to say, okay?
I like you.
Tetsuro-kun...
I love you.
I see.
So that's what happened with Kinoshita.
That's why she was so...
She said she was sorry.
I'm so pathetic.
Huh?
I knew she was forcing herself.
But I didn't really try
to talk to her about it.
You ended up taking care of it.
I think Kinoshita-san tried to tell you.
Huh?
But I ended up telling her
I wanted to talk first.
You mean Kinoshita?
Uh, yeah...
Did you have a reason?
Yeah...
Oh, so that's why you
found us this afternoon.
Was there something you
needed to tell her?
W-Well...
I...
That's pretty.
Yeah.
Things looked like they were
going really well for them,
and I was just in the way!
Tetsuro-san said he didn't
have someone he liked!
I just made a fool out of myself!
You came with me on this trip so
I could escape my heartbreak.
And now the same thing
happened to you.
It's not fair! I can't believe she
was actually just kind of an airhead.
Things just aren't going right.
That's the second one this summer...
It's pretty late.
Yeah.
I wonder if everyone's worried about us.
You don't have to tell me how you feel.
I already know.
I wonder how Ishigaki-kun's doing.
He's probably still being chased
around by Kinoshita's friend.
So if a girl chases after a
guy that aggressively,
I guess it puts the guy off, huh?
I guess a little bit.
Was it the same with Kinoshita-san?
Don't tease me.
Sorry, sorry.
Senpai.
What is it?
I don't want to be chased
after by someone,
I want to be the one chasing.
I want to chase after the person I like.
But if my feelings are going
to make you uncomfortable...
They won't!
I'm not uncomfortable at all.
D-Don't...
Don't...
What are you two doing, meow?
T-T-Tanigawa-san?!
We weren't doing anything at all!
Wait, why are you wearing that?
Where did the two of you go, meow?
Wait...
Where were the two of you?!
Hey, what's going on?
The two of us were having
a little girl talk.
Huh?!
Tanigawa-san, are you okay?!
Oh, Takatsuki-senpai!
Kiss!
What are you doing, Tanigawa?!
One for Kaito-kun, too...
Wai—
No!
Stop it!
Kanna?
Tanigawa-san...
What are you guys doing?
Tetsuro-meow and Mio-meow.
Where were you two, meow?
Meow?
Wait...
Where were you two?!
Wh-What?
K-Kanna!
Totally not fair!
I was the only one left behind!
And I'm tired.
Y-You can't sleep out here.
What's going on?!
Wake up!
Meow!
You... protected me.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Cut.
Now Kinoshita-san has
finished all of her scenes.
We're done filming.
Good work.
You, too.
I have a plane to catch,
so I'll see you guys.
Sorry to keep you here
until the last minute.
It's fine.
Good luck filming.
When it's done, let me see.
Sure.
Kinoshita-san, here you go.
Thanks.
If you don't make a move,
I'll take Umi-chan from you.
Huh?
See you!
Going to miss her?
A little.
She was your first love, after all.
I told you it wasn't like that!
Our flight is in the evening, right?
It's at 5 o'clock.
We're done filming today.
As soon as we clean up the set,
let's enjoy the Okinawan ocean.
Agreed!
Hey!
Senpai!
I...
I realized.
How I feel...
...about Kaito-kun.
Episode 8
Senpai's pinch.
Kitahara-san, Remon wants
us all to go to a festival.
That's dangerous.
Why?
I smell a plot!