Tsukuba-kun, please win for me.
Kana-chan?!
Did this happen during the last match?
It's really swollen.
Good thing it was me.
Good thing it wasn't Chihaya-chan
jamming her finger.
What are you talking about, Kana-chan?!
We should consider ourselves lucky!
It wasn't our ace who got hurt.
We have first-years to sub in!
Luck is on our side.
Mizusawa is set up to win.
Did you notice that Oe-senpai
was injured, Tsukuba?
O-Of course!
I was watching Oe-senpai the whole time!
Yeah, you're lying.
You always lie.
I was worried about her stamina,
and I never noticed her injury.
That was a lie.
Tsukuba-kun, please win for me.
Her lie was completely different from mine.
I'm amazed you were able
to win your game like this.
It may be sprained.
The swelling could get worse.
It's okay.
Her hand is so small...
Yet Oe-san and Komano-kun
are able to lead the others?
But...
In the process, they're also providing a push.
Chihaya Furu
Verse 15
No
matter
where I
stand
We're sorry...
We're sorry...  We're sorry...
We're sorry, Sudo-san!
Please don't spank us!
Spank?
What?
Oh, one of the hosts...
Members of Hokuo,
too bad about that match.
Do you need something?
Uh, do you know who
Wataya Arata-kun is?
From Fukui...
Wataya Arata?!
He is my eternal rival!
Back in the winter of sixth grade,
when we were almost equals,
we had a fateful encounter in Tokyo!
Oh, I just wanted to know
if you were acquainted.
Wataya-kun came here to cheer for you,
but due to a mishap, he
wasn't able to watch in person.
Once the third place match is
over, you should go see him.
He's in the room at the
end of the second floor.
Wataya Arata came to cheer for us?
Doesn't matter.
I don't have time to worry
about another school.
Because...
Bastards...
Are you ready to bunny hop down
the Tokaido on the way home?
Just kidding.  I was a fool.
I was convinced that you
would make the final,
so I wasn't watching the last match.
I was convinced that you
would make the final,
so I wasn't focused.
This time, I'll be watching...
Huh?
Hokuo must end the
tournament with a win!
The third-years are so good.
I want to know what lineup
we'll use for the final.
There's no reason to change lineups.
They're our best players.
Stupid.  Don't you know
Coach Sakurazawa's style?
She always switches in a
younger player for the final!
Who will be dropped?
Will it be me for being the
single loss against Hokuo?
This is the best lineup we have, Coach.
Suzuki Manata.
You're out.
Wow, she's breaking up
Fujisaki's Mana-Kana,
Manata-senpai and Kanata-senpai!
They're even, ability-wise,
but she only removed
one from the lineup.
Evil!
C-Coach, why me?!
Your knees.
You've put a lot of strain
on those knee supports.
Thank you.
We wouldn't have made it to the
finals without your hard work.
Yamashiro Rion, you're in.
Yes.
A second-year in the lineup...
I knew it'd be Yamashiro.
She's confirmed to be the
next core of this team.
I've heard rumors that the
reader for the next match is—
Stop chattering.
The finals are the best opportunity to learn.
Watch carefully and consider
the meaning of each card.
Yes!
Yamashiro Rion.
I figured she would be chosen.
Frightening...
The third-years are all in love with her.
Plus, she's copying my hairstyle.
Frightening...
Makoto-senpai.
I was watching Mizusawa's match,
so I'm familiar with each player's—
You think you can give advice
to the third-years?!
And why did you agree
to enter the lineup?!
You must know how hard
Manata worked to get here!
You should have refused to play!
Hey, Makoto.
We don't need you to win!
Stop it, Makoto!
Why are you all so soft on Rion?
Don't you find it creepy how
she never shows any emotion?!
But if I play, we can win for sure.
Also, I wasn't the one who took
Manata-senpai out of the lineup.
I know that, you iron mask!
I know that...
The scariest person in Fujisaki is...
We will be fine this year.
The problem is the year after next.
The third-years we have now are so good
that our team is no longer balanced.
There are only a few first-years
who show any promise.
I suppose I could have taken out
another third-year to let a first-year play.
Ms. Sakurazawa.
Mr. Mochida.
Congratulations on advancing to the finals.
I was very impressed.
I just saw that you took out one
of your third-years for the final.
He was the player who defeated
our Kameda very quickly.
Coach Sakurazawa is really something.
Most people would never take out
a third-year for the final.
I know, but you have to
admire Manata-senpai.
He's not hiding the fact that he's upset.
Manata, your knees aren't
bothering you that much, right?
We can go appeal to Coach.
Kanata...
Ma-Manata?!
I-It's okay...
I was just remembering all the
grueling practice we went through.
Yes, Suzuki Manata is
an excellent player.
I expect him to perform well in the
individual tournament tomorrow.
It's my fault that Hokuo lost.
I'm not as strong as she is.
I don't have her kind of
strength and conviction,
to utilize the hopes of the
third-years to win the final.
Retro, pay attention!
Yes!
Give it everything you got left.
The senpais, who hated how
our red T-shirts stand out
and swore to never wear them again,
are wearing them now
as they watch us play.
One of those isn't a senpai...
Forget it!  Don't mention that!
Self-
made
replica
She's still here to support us.
We're not alone here!
May my sighs be blamed upon the moon,
or do my tears come from
the feelings it invokes?
Oe-san?
How did the Monk Saigyo feel
when he looked up at the moon?!
I-I'm glad to see that
you're doing okay.
Listen up, everyone.
I'm confident that I can guess our
opponent's lineup with 100% accuracy.
What?!
Fujisaki has multiple players
who are highly skilled.
Think of it as playing against
five of Hokuo's Sudo-san.
What?!
He said that like it's nothing!
None of the players stand out
for individual performance,
1. Emuro Ryoga (Captain)
but they have a vague order that may
be based on their personalities.
1. Emuro Ryoga (Captain)
2. Ichimura Mitsuki
3. Suzuki Manata\Kanata
1. Emuro Ryoga (Captain)
2. Ichimura Mitsuki
3./4. Suzuki Manata\Kanata
?. Yamai Makoto
Why do you have a question mark here?
I'm not sure where to put him.
They'll be changing the
lineup for the final, anyway.
One of the twins will be
dropped for a younger player.
Wait, a third-year Class A
player's getting dropped?!
Yep, and he'll probably
be replaced by a girl.
How do you know that?!
In Fujisaki, the girls are
scarier than the guys.
I watched three of their matches.
Also...
He reminds me of Arata.
He's about the same build
and wearing glasses.
Huh?
I'd forgotten Arata until now.
He kept popping up before...
Was it because I was concentrating
on the team match?
Time's up.
Will the players please enter the room?
Nationals edition
I've done all I can.
I doubt I'll be able to win my game.
But...
Nakayama!  We'll barely make the
train if we watch this match!
Can we make it?  Can we make it?
Did you really want to play that badly?
Of course I did!
If I'd known about this, I would
have insisted on playing!
Huh?
I'm so glad that she agreed to come.
This is a wonderful present
for the high school students.
The certified reader,
Yamashiro Kyoko, grade 7.
We're so lucky to have her
read for a high school match!
She's one of the best readers out there!
The world of karuta is too
deep for me to understand.
This really is the final...
In Omi Jingu, on the ultimate stage,
with the ultimate reader.
I wanted to play!
I'm actually a greedy person.
Huh?  We know.
Compared to becoming Queen, becoming
the strongest woman in Japan,
it's much harder for us to
become best in Japan together!
Let's do this!
Mi!
Zu!
Sa!
Wa!
Fight!
I will now read the order
for the final match.
Fujisaki High School, Yamashiro Rion.
What?  Yamashiro?
Mizusawa High School, Ayase Chihaya.
They took out a third-year
Class A player.
The first game is between
two second-year girls.
Wait, isn't that certified reader
Yamashiro's granddaughter?
She's a student at Fujisaki?
Is that why she agreed to come?
You'll have a lot to answer for
if you lose in the number one seat.
I don't know which girl they'll put in,
but your goal is to become the
strongest girl in Japan, right?
Fujisaki High School, Suzuki Kanata.
Mizusawa High School, Nishida Yusei.
I'll avenge Manata's anguish!
I'll avenge my anguish!
Fujisaki High School, Emuro Ryoga.
Mizusawa High School, Mashima Taichi.
The two leaders are against each other!
That's how a final should be!
This was the biggest surprise.
I'll play their captain.
That Mashima, not Ayase, was the
one who took the challenge.
I won't run away.
If it's a team match,
not even Arata can scare me!
Fujisaki High School, Ichimura Mitsuki.
Mizusawa High School, Tsukuba Akihiro.
If I win here, I'll look so good!
I'll be a true hero!
Fox-eyed creature?
Huh?  What?
Is that a nickname?
Wait, you've got fox eyes, too!
Fujisaki High School, Yamai Makoto.
Mizusawa High School, Komano Tsutomu.
Oh?  You actually made it
to the final, Mr. Spy?
That's impressive,
but you shouldn't expect to win.
That goes for your whole team...
You should stop blowing at your
bangs when you're in trouble.
Next, we have the third place match.
First Akashi Girls' vs. Hokuo Academy.
Huh?  Where's Retro?
It should be dry by now.
Stop it!
Why are you facing us?!
Don't change in front of us!
Give us a warning first!
What?!
What are you?! Who are you?!
Strangers should stay out!
Retro-kun?
Hokuo...
The first place team from Tokyo.
Retro-kun's still playing karuta?
It doesn't matter if I lose
my first match tomorrow...
...as long as we win every match today.
Mashima's so stupid...
Working hard to win team matches
won't get you anywhere.
You want to make Class A
more than anyone else...
Maybe even more than I do.
Wataya-kun...
Aren't you going to cheer them on?
Mashima and Chihaya are playing
to become the best in Japan.
He's talking about becoming first in Japan
when it's a match between
high school students.
I'm very impressed.
They must all be very good.
Don't you think so, Arata?
You're still not going?
If I go, I won't be able to play
in the individual tournament.
Oh, so you care more about
the individual tournament.
Arata, don't worry.
The room's so packed that
no one will notice you.
Go on.
Isn't that why you came today?
If I don't accept my punishment
after breaking the rules,
I'll be incurring the
wrath of the gods, Shoji!
Mashima and Chihaya are playing
to become the best in Japan.
Not your pants!
I wish I could be as relaxed as you are.
I'm so nervous about the
tournament tomorrow.
I need to go home.
Goodbye then.
Shinobu-chan.
Won't you watch some of the team match?
Your presence will encourage
some of the players.
You must be joking.
This is...
U-Ugly!
So many three-syllable cards...
There's only one one-syllable
card on the field.
No "Impassion—" cards.
This will be a tough match for Chihaya.
Excuse us.
They're leaving after placing their cards?
Did they already finish
memorizing the cards?
That's crazy!
That's how Fujisaki plays.
This way, they always set their own pace.
Don't panic, Mizusawa.
It's no big deal.
We had to play five matches
to reach the final.
The third-years on Fujisaki are also tired.
I think they'll leave their seats
to avoid memorization overload.
The girl who hasn't played yet
will probably remain.
Master Komano, you're incredible.
Karuta is about memorizing and
forgetting over and over...
Memorize and forget...
Forget...
Forget everything...
If I don't forget everything,
I won't be able to defeat a fresh
player in her first match.
Where's Rion?
She's memorizing.
What?  Is that okay?
She's not very strong to begin with,
yet she's not going to stretch?
This is optional.
You guys are too soft on Rion.
True, she has incredible talent,
but isn't it creepy how she
never shows any emotion?
Why is she so popular?
Plus, she's still stuck in Class B.
Sure, she's kinda cute.
Hey, Makoto.  I have a girlfriend, you know.
Huh?
Me, too.
Seriously?!
Good luck, Senpai
I've been dating the first-year
Mano Misaki since spring.
I've been with Shining Rainbow-chan
since the spring season.
Anime character
No way!
What about Eromu?!
You're in love with Rion, right?!
Rion has the breasts of an infant.
I need an E-cup at least.
Emuro...  I forgot...
Stop it with the hands
The bigger the better.
You're called "Eromu" because
of your erotic nature...
The ass is also important.
I've been thinking.
Isn't it because you're in love with Rion?
Thump
Huh?!  Huh?!  Wh-What's that?!
Th-That's disgusting, Kanata!
Who would love that poker face?!
Well...
That girl who just has sharp ears
and no sense of teamwork!
Who was that?
I didn't hear any footsteps.
Scary...
So this is the extent of the
ears of the best team players.
They have fun fooling around together,
so far away from the cards.
Today is a day for teams.
Arata...
Why, Arata?
Like cards...  Check for like cards...
"May the time we," "May the time spent"...
Excuse us.
Even his motions remind me of Arata.
Do all karuta players end up like this?
The grand finale of the team tournament.
I'm up against Fujisaki's Class A captain.
I chose to play against him.
If I beat him, maybe things will change...
I remember you.
You played against one of our
alumni last year in the Class B final.
I remember you.
So...
You're still in Class B?
He drew a line.
He gauged my skill.
Yes, it's such a pity.
I was hoping to see those H-cup
jugs bounce before me,
but it's not meant to be.
Then I'll go with pattern A, where I fantasize
about Coach Sakurazawa letting me
feel her F-cup boobies if I win.
Kanata actually thinks
I'm in love with Rion?!
With Rion?!
Manata...
Watch me play, Manata!
Which one should I use next?
Saint?
Rider?
Fighter?
What's going on?
Why is Fujisaki so relaxed?
We will begin now.
Thank you for the game.
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
It's completely different.
This is the sound of
a certified reader.
This is the final.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
This is our grand finale!