Hey, isn't he super hot?
Oh, wow. He's so my type.
How often do you see someone that hot?
Maybe I'll try talking to him.
Huh? You're just going to get burned.
Hey, that guy looks super strong.
Oh, wow. He's so my role model.
How often do you run into someone that built?
Maybe I'll try sparring with him.
Huh? You're just going to get burned.
Hey! Suna!
We were on the same train.
I didn't realize you were on it.
I could totally see you, though.
They're friends?
No way!
My Boyfriend
I'm Gouda Takeo, a first-year in high school.
This guy's my friend, Sunakawa Makoto.
I've known him since we were three.
Suna, it's spring.
Yeah.
It's spring in Japan, but I'm
experiencing spring, too.
After all, for the first time in
my life, I have a girlfriend!
Spring's awesome...
Oops.
You should watch where you're going.
Yeah.
Huh?
Wait—
My baby!
He's just helping you get to the top.
Huh?
Oh... Thank you.
You're welcome.
Th-Thank you.
That was a huge help.
It isn't like I did anything.
Thank you.
Take care!
Oh, right.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
You were a huge help!
Thank you.
Takeo-kun...
Takeo-kun, you're so strong!
This year's spring is the true spring!
Oh!
You made these, Yamato?
Yeah.
I decided to try making Japanese
sweets for the first time.
I thought these cherry blossom petal
shapes and stuff were cute.
They're delicious!
You're so loud.
You're great at making Japanese sweets, too.
Really?
It makes me so happy when
you say that, Takeo-kun!
I really like her!
It's springtime.
Spring's nice.
Earlier, I was thinking the same thing, too.
Oh, really?
I see.
Summer's good, too.
Yeah, summer's good.
Fall has its own charms.
Yeah, it sure does!
I like winter, too.
Of course I like winter.
It wouldn't surprise me if you two keep having
this convo, even when you're old and wrinkly.
That's your reaction?
Then can I go home now?
Yeah, Yamato...
It'd be great if we could stay like this forever.
Hey, Takeo-kun?
Yeah?
Can I take a selfie with you?
Of course.
Really?
Can I use it for my lock screen, too?
Like this?
Is that okay?
I'm going to take it.
Sure.
Oh...
I messed up.
I'm so nervous!
I feel like my heart's about to explode...
Okay, that worked.
Good.
Send that to my cell, too.
I want to use it for my wallpaper.
Okay!
I really like her!
Oh, sorry.
Can I take this?
Hello?
Yeah?
I'm out right now.
Huh? Yeah, that's right.
I'm with my boyfriend.
Boyfriend!
With my...
I'm about to burst!
But why is she so happy that I'm her boyfriend?
Yeah?
Huh?
Okay.
Um...
What's wrong?
Oh, um...
You can tell me.
U-Um, my friend wants to do a singles' meet.
I have five friends who don't have boyfriends,
and they want to meet you and your friends.
I see...
Okay, got it.
I just have to get my friends together, right?
It's okay?
No problem.
He said it's okay.
Yay!
Was that your boyfriend just now?
He has a nice deep voice.
Don't worry, Yamato.
Yeah.
Shuuei High School
When it comes to guy friends,
I have more than most.
Morning, Takeo-kun.
Takeo! Hey, how you doin'?
Yo, Takeo!
Hey, morning!
Morning, Takeo!
Oh, hey, Takeo!
Takeo!
Takeo.
Yo, Takeo!
What's wrong, Takeo?
Something happen?
Well... I have a girlfriend.
Those among you—
Seriously?
Congrats, Takeo!
That makes me super happy, man!
Okay, time to celebrate!
Hup!
Those among you who don't have a girlfriend,
raise your hand.
Me.
Those among you who want to do
a singles' meet, raise your hand.
What? You're going?
I want to!
I'll go!
Rock-paper-scissors time.
Me, too!
Only four can come.
A singles' meet?
Huh... Good luck with that.
What?
You're coming, whether you like it or not.
Sure, but I probably won't talk at all.
I'll ruin the mood
There may be a nice girl there.
They're Yamato's friends.
They must all be great girls.
Takeo...
Just because someone's friends
with a nice person
doesn't mean they're nice, too.
Sometimes, they're friends because the
person's nice enough to have them.
Suna...
What you said just now was really complicated.
Takeo-kun, they're the friends who'll be
coming to the singles' meet tomorrow.
They're all cute.
I'm feeling really shy about
introducing you to them!
Yamato's laughing...
She's always herself, no matter where she is.
Hello!
I'm Yamato, Takeo-kun's girlfriend.
The other girls here are all friends from my class.
Hello!
Nice to meet you!
Wow, they're all cute.
So who's Rinko's boyfriend?
This girl talks about her boyfriend every day.
Eh? No, I don't!
Yes, that's what people call what you do.
So, who is it?
U-Um...
This is Takeo-kun, my boyfriend.
Hello!
A bear...
Oh, you're just as tall as Rinko said...
I almost mistook you for a bear.
J-Just like Rinko said, you have big hands.
Salmon
Singles' Meet
Here we are!
Okay!
Hey, hey!
The restaurant's this way.
Whoa!
Sorry...
You were lighter than I expected.
No worries, thank you.
He's way too strong.
It's dangerous to leave boxes here.
Maybe I'll move them out of the way,
so people can pass through.
Oh, god.
The emergency exit's locked, too.
Maybe we should tell the restaurant staff?
That sort of thing should be reported to the
management company, not the restaurant staff.
So cool!
Suna, you're smart.
Uh, is that one of the bear's friends?
Yeah?
What a surprise.
Okay, let's order drinks!
Who wants orange juice?
Me!
I want coke.
The more you look at him, the hotter he is.
But he isn't talking at all.
Want to try talking to him?
You go...
Did you make the reservation?
What?
I actually thought he had to be Rinko's boyfriend.
You did a lot of work.
Oh, it's no big deal.
I wonder why she went for the bear.
Yeah, right?
Takeo, your girlfriend's real nice.
I'm happy for you, Takeo.
I'm really glad for you, man.
And why does everyone like
her boyfriend so much?
We should toss you in the air again tomorrow.
Let's aim for three tosses next time.
Yeah!
Everyone got their drinks?
All right, let's start with a toast.
Oh, we don't have a bottle opener.
Excuse me.
It's open.
Huh?
Wow, you opened it with your bare hands!
You're amazing, Takeo!
Wow!
Do mine, too.
What was that?
Takeo, that isn't how you're
supposed to open them.
Hey, so you all attend an
all-girls' high school, right?
So you don't have any guys?
Uh... Well...
Nope.
Don't ask Yamato's friends stupid questions!
Sorry, sorry.
You'd better not do them any wrong!
Takeo-kun,
it's fine.
Huh?
So none of you girls has a boyfriend?
Nope!
We don't have any opportunities to meet them.
Yeah, none.
Well, we're co-ed, but we don't
have any opportunities, either.
Yeah, none.
All the girls go for the popular guys.
If there are any, there's only our school festival.
Oh, the school festival.
Can we go to that, too?
Sure, come!
Sure thing!
Our last festival in junior high, we ran a café.
A café ?
What was your getup?
Um, that question's super dated.
Hey, can I come sit with you guys?
Did you run a café, too?
Sure.
Okay, let's swap seats.
I baked stuff for it.
I made a lot of pound cake in different flavors.
Oh, I would've liked to have tried them.
I'll bake some for tomorrow!
Looking forward to it.
I wouldn't be surprised if you
ate a whole cake in one go.
Oh, oops, my contact lens shifted.
Sorry, I'll go fix it in the restroom.
Okay.
I'll come with you!
Nanako and Ayu still haven't come back.
I'll go take a look.
I'll come with you.
Where's the restroom?
This way.
He's way too tall, you know?
Yeah!
I can't believe he's the boyfriend.
He's barely human.
Rinko kept going on about how cool he was,
so I thought he must be this hottie, you know?
Yeah, I almost had a heart attack!
He's a gorilla.
I wouldn't have the guts to be seen with him.
Just because someone's friends
with a nice person
doesn't mean they're nice, too.
And she says he's cool.
I wonder if Rinko's right in the head.
Oh...
R-Rinko...
Takeo-kun is...
cool!
He's super cool!
Yamato!
Yamato...
I'm sorry, Takeo-kun...
I'm so sorry.
Sorry about what?
My friends said mean things
about you, Takeo-kun.
I'm sure they hurt your feelings.
I'm sorry.
My feelings are just fine.
But...
I'm okay, Yamato.
There are all kinds of people.
You don't need to worry about me.
You're the one who got hurt.
It's because there are all kinds of people
that I was able to meet you, Yamato.
I don't like seeing you cry.
You're not hurt?
Really?
Not a scratch.
More importantly,
I found out that you've been saying really
nice things about me to your friends.
Thank you.
You're amazing, Takeo-kun.
Hmm?
I really like you a lot, Takeo-kun...
I like you so much!
I know! I bet I just didn't explain very well.
I must have been so vague,
they didn't get how cool you are.
Yamato...
When I go back, I'll try to explain it in
a way that's easier to understand.
I don't need you to do that for me.
But I want to.
They just don't know the real you, Takeo-kun.
Yamato...
Every day, I'm thankful that I met you.
I hope things can stay this way forever.
Fire!
Suna!
Takeo!
I called the fire department when
a fire suddenly broke out,
Rinko!
but they're not here yet.
Where is everyone?
Do we have everyone?
What should we do?
I can't find Nanako and Ayu!
They haven't come back from the bathroom.
They're still inside!
Wait here!
I'll bring them out, I promise!
Takeo-kun!
Don't worry, Yamato!
I will save your friends!
Takeo!
Nanako!
Takeo...
You okay?
Nanako!
Call an ambulance!
Don't worry, already done.
Just one more!
I... feel like I was carried out...
by a really strong wild animal.
It was Takeo-kun!
Yamato...
You looked really happy in the
photo you sent my phone.
They're all good friends.
Rinko... Sorry.
I'm sorry...
Are you okay?
Hang in th—
Can you stand?
Yes...
Go.
Huh?
Go!
Ayu!
This way.
Where are the firefighters?
This is serious.
Rinko...
I'm so relieved.
But your boyfriend...
H-He might be in trouble...
He helped me and got left behind.
I guess this is really it...
I guess I've been too happy lately.
Takeo-kun!
Yamato, it's all thanks to you.
If I can die helping you,
it isn't such a bad way to go.
My cell?
I guess it still has a signal.
Takeo?
Can you hear me?
So, Yamato-san's this close
to jumping into the flames.
Takeo-kun!
Let go!
Let me go to him!
Now that you've grasped the situation,
Takeo-kun!
can you get back here ASAP?
Life's pretty boring for me, too,
if you aren't around.
Takeo-kun!
Takeo...
Hey, can you hear me?
Takeo-ku—
Don't cry, Yamato.
Don't cry for me.
You don't need to worry about me.
Please laugh.
I hate it when you cry, more than anything.
Yamato...
I'll...
live...
I'll live,
and then...
I'll make Yamato happy!
Takeo-kun!
Takeo-kun...
Yamato...
I swear that I will never make you cry again.
Um...
Thank you.
Blush
What was that just now?
Is this the suspension bridge effect?
No way!
He's not my type at all!
Hey, so I think I wasn't clear enough
about how cool Takeo-kun is...
So I'm going to try to explain in a
way that's easier to understand—
It's okay, Rinko. We got it.
Actually, I'm really sorry.
We were wrong.
Your boyfriend's awesome!
And you're awesome.
Yeah, seriously.
D-Don't steal him from me!
No way we would!
I mean, there's no way we could.
He only has eyes for you.
I have a feeling the only way
you'd die is from old age.
Really?
Yeah.
Man, Takeo's really awesome!
Feeling major respect all over again!
Takeo's awesome!
All right, toss him up!
Yeah, let's do it!
Takeo-kun, thank you so much for today.
Yamato Rinko
Subject: Thank You
Everyone understands why
you're a good person now.
You were super cool today, too!
If you became a firefighter or something,
I think you'd do a lot of good work,
even though I'd get worried...
Night, Takeo-kun.
See you soon.
It's spring...
Spring's great, Yamato.
I'm Dense
Next time: I'm Dense.