"Operation: Infiltrate a Planetoid Base"
They're fast! I can't process
their data quick enough!
My unit feels heavy!
Did it get fat?! Did it?!
There is gravity since we're on Earth!
Crap! I can't keep up with them!
Guys, get your acts together!
Your controls will go
bonkers if you panic!
Right back at you!
Isn't that Team Rabbits?
Supposedly their AHSMB
units are under repair.
Since they're still considered students,
they're getting a supplementary lesson.
Is it just me, or do they
suck even worse now?
Who're the other three?
Probably teachers.
Students can't pull
off moves like those.
I've gotta do something!
Now that it's come to this...!
Shining Miracle Turn Smash!
What gives?
What the hell was that?
And here I put my faith in you!
Fine! I'll charge ahead!
Whoo boy...
Their formation is a mess...
What the heck was that Miracle-whatever?
My secret move.
Yeah, figures. Most heroes
have a secret move, don't they?
I know, right?
We don't need one!
But heroes use secret
moves to save the day.
I was sure I could pull it off...
If all we needed was confidence,
we'd get 100's studying by ourselves!
I never got to show my stuff...
Yo!
You weren't looking too
hot out there, huh?
Freakin' out after
that string of losses?
Your training session is over.
Team Rabbits, everyone
is to submit your
own personal analysis on why you lost.
Assemble in the Meeting Room in 30 minutes
with Team Doberman.
Over.
See ya later.
Sirs, thank you for the lesson!
That's Team Doberman for ya!
They're scary!
Weren't they also students here?
Supposedly they were
highly accomplished.
A joint meeting...
Does that mean we're working with them
on our next mission?
That'd be super awesome!
All three dudes are stud muffins!
I'm amazed you can act so carefree
after nearly getting killed in that last mission.
Fear and romance are
two different things!
Man!
I guess the Fail Five are
still the Fail Five, huh?
How come they get to pilot
cutting-edge fighters?
My entrance may come
surprisingly soon...
I thought my Likeability Stats would go up
after becoming a wee bit famous.
You can't blame them
for feeling that way.
When you get down to it,
our team only won that very first battle.
They're blasting us on
the internet again...
Don't bring that up.
You'll give me another ulcer.
Your AHSMB units have
been fully repaired.
You will be transferring
to Star Rose tomorrow.
Upon arrival, we will
commence a co-op mission.
What's the matter?
Ma'am, what if we fail again...?
Thinking like that will only hinder
your performance!
You'll be fine!
This time you've got
Team Doberman with you.
Lt. Commander, I have a question!
I've been meaning to
ask this for some time.
Go ahead, Lieutenant.
Please tell me your personal address
and when you're off duty.
Randy, we're in the middle of a meeting!
You shouldn't ask such
shameless questions.
Don't be such a stiff!
If ya don't ask stuff
like this when you can,
you could forever miss the boat!
With you as our clown of a leader,
people keep calling
us the "Bummer Three,"
the "Comedic Three" and "Trio Dobermans."
The "Bummer Three"?
Just what I'd expect from our seniors!
What's wrong with being
the Bummer Three?!
And why do you always act
like you're better than me?!
Just because we're classmates
doesn't mean you can walk all over me!
It's the sub-leader's job to guide
the leader down the right path.
What are you, the
disciplinary committee?!
Pardon?
Why must you always act so cool?!
What are you going on about
in the middle of a meeting?
Do you think you're on
the Cool Committee?!
Sorry, but I don't have time to play.
You should try to act a
bit more like a leader!
Wh-what?!
If there are no further questions,
this meeting is adjourned.
I'm sorry. My team
always acts like this.
I-I see...
Quit acting like you're
excluded from our antics!
Ow, that hurts! Randy!
I give up! Uncle, uncle!
Thank God they aren't
as scary as I thought.
What was that? I couldn't hear you?
In fact, they're funny.
You want me to stop?
But they're still cool!
And they saved our hides!
They're totally the hero type!
I'll really let you have it next time!
I swear, you never change!
Neither do you!
Excuse me! Thank you
for saving me the other day.
Uh, aren't you Red 5's pilot...?
I'm Izuru Hitachi.
It feels like ages
since I was here last.
You've got it rough, huh?
They're sending you out hunting
when you're still just a student.
People are gonna say what they're gonna say;
don't worry 'bout it.
But I do!
Whenever I get sent to battle,
I wonder if I'm doing enough.
You've survived this far!
Isn't that good enough?
But I want to become a hero!
A hero?
So? Why do you want to
be a hero of all things?
Because I think they're great!
I-I see...
All right.
I'll tell you what it takes
to be a hero. You must be...
...good looking!
Good looking?
Right, it's all about the looks!
To be a hero, you gotta
be the best looking
member in your group and get all of the girls.
Aren't I a prime example?
Y-yeah...
For the record, you...
Yeah, you aren't as handsome as me,
but you're plenty good looking!
Don't worry, you'll
become an amazing hero.
I guarantee it!
Is-is that right...?
Let's see, what else is there...?
Well, I suppose you could say
that a hero has three jobs:
Making decisions, never giving up
and believing in your comrades.
Do you trust them... your friends?
I watched the footage from all of
Team Rabbits' battles so far.
You try to do everything yourself while
desperately fighting to protect your friends.
You can't keep a team together
if you don't believe in your men!
Now putting that aside!
The pilots for Unit 2 and Unit 3...
Which do you have your sights set on?
Pardon?
Aren't they both adorable?
Which is your type?
Or are you already dating one of them?!
I-I couldn't possibly!
We're a team, so that
sort of stuff is taboo!
What?!
I can't believe my ears!
Just how old are you guys?
Kei, Suruga and I are 16.
Asagi is 17. Tamaki is 15.
These are the best days of your life!
You gotta fall in love,
squabble and then break up!
I really can't do that!
I know! Swap teams with me.
As of today, you're Team Doberman's leader;
I'm taking Rabbits.
What?!
Of course, I'm just pulling your leg.
Your eyes looked kinda serious...
Listen.
In our line of work, you never know
when you're gonna die.
Wouldn't you like someone to remember
who you were after you're gone?
Interact with as many people
as you possibly can.
And make sure you remember
each person you meet along the way.
You can borrow this.
Study this with the pilots
for Unit 1 and Unit 4.
Does it contain footage
from our battles?
Close enough.
Watch this and put your
best foot forward!
I will!
Let's watch this together!
What is it? Does it
contain video records?
Yep! He said to only watch it
with Asagi and Suruga,
but I figured we could
all watch it together!
What is this...?
That hurt...!
What the hell are you thinking?!
Well, this isn't exactly
what I was expecting...
Pro wrestling?
Wh-what? What?
Wh-what's the big deal?!
This is a bit much for me...
Why are you freaking out when you're
the one constantly flirting with the ladies?
B-but this is on a totally
different level...
I'm gonna pass!
Damn it! If we get caught,
reports will be the least of our worries.
But I didn't mean-
Enough! This is truly ridiculous.
I just realized something important.
What is it?
This actress resembles
Instructor Suzukaze.
Now that you mention
it, I can see that...
I can't bear to watch!
The mission's name is
Operation: MacLean.
You are to infiltrate the enemy base on
Planetoid RA221 and blow it up.
Concentrate!
Sir, what do you think
has gotten into them?
Beats me.
We don't know what to
expect once you're in.
Although it isn't terribly big,
we believe the base's
artificial gravity device is active.
We have outfitted your units
for fighting in gravity.
Was our training on
Earth before the mission
meant to serve as a simulation?
It is far enough away from the battlefield
that we expect minimal security.
However, with weak transmission signals,
it will be impossible to communicate with us.
Gold 4 will be in charge of the bomb.
You will also use Gold 4's
computer to detonate it.
This mission came out
of nowhere, didn't it?
I can't believe we're destroying
a base that's on the sidelines.
They're probably trying to make
the other team look good.
That's what it'd take
to save the MJP's face.
At any rate, they want evidence
that we're winning.
I bet this is a co-op to increase
the chances of success.
Yeah, but do you think
we can handle this...?
Did you end up watching
that video last night?
Not me! I didn't watch it!
Kei, are you going to
tell the instructor...?
No, I wouldn't do that!
D-don't worry, Kei!
I'm sleepy after staying up all night,
but it was really refreshing.
Well? Was it a good picker upper?
Yeah, but I wound up showing it
to Kei and Tamaki...
What?! Y-you've got some balls!
I'm amazed you've treaded grounds
far more dangerous than I have!
G-gee, thanks...
Identifying the enemy base.
I'm forwarding the image.
What's going on here?!
Weren't we expecting minimal security?
What should we do?
Withdraw and request new orders?
We can't reach our commanding officers.
We'll have to make the
call for ourselves...
Let's carry out the mission!
If the base is crowded with enemies
when it shouldn't be,
it means they're up to something.
We can't go back empty-handed!
Roger!
Crap! They found us.
But how? Do they have eyes and ears?
We'll take them on!
My team will draw the enemy fire
while your team carries out the mission!
But will you be okay?!
Don't worry about us!
There should be a gravity reactor
at the center of the base.
Set the bomb there.
You'll do fine as long
as you remain calm.
They want us to infiltrate
the base by ourselves...?
My feet absolutely refuse to move!
Don't run away!
Use your willpower to rein in the
JURIA-SYSTEM's survival instincts!
Go!
Y-yes, sir!
Let's go, Red 5!
L-let's fight!
Follow me, Purple 2!
H-hey, wait!
What'll we do if they find us again?
Doberman is attracting all
of the enemy's attention.
We'll be fine... I think... maybe.
It looks like the base's guards
still don't know we're here.
I bet we could get in through there.
Rose 3 can't fit through that entrance.
What?!
What should we do, Izuru?
Leave Tamaki behind?
Make up your mind before
the gate closes!
I'll stay behind.
Asagi...!
We'll probably need to shoot down
any enemy fighters that come back.
Don't worry. We can handle it!
Thank you.
Kei, Suruga, let's go!
So this is a Wulgaru base...
I'm detecting a reactor located
250 meters below us.
If we blow that up, it should
take out the entire base.
And the route?
Straight ahead.
Enemy fighters incoming at 2:00!
Suruga, protect the bomb!
Kei, can you activate
the defense shields?
I could, but they'll make scanning
and analyzing the area that much harder.
Got it. Then we'll plow
through without them!
Good thing we trained on Earth!
Take the upcoming 90°
turn to the right!
Next drop 90° vertically down!
The heat values are higher
than I had anticipated.
The sudden fluctuation in heat is beginning
to interfere with my sensors.
Can you at least tell
what direction it's in?
If we follow the artificial gravity pipeline,
we should reach the source.
Doesn't that mean we're gonna keep
falling for who knows how long?!
They aren't holding back even though
we're inside their base!
That's a given!
If we destroy this reactor,
it'll send the whole base sky high!
It got hit somewhere along the line!
Crap! I can't set it like this.
What?!
The mission's a failure!
We gotta retreat. Retreat!
What should we do, Izuru?
Izuru!
Suruga, can you fix it?
I don't think it's beyond me...
Then do it!
We won't make it back alive
if we don't destroy this base.
This is our only option if
we hope to survive this!
Are you serious?!
Suruga, you can do it!
I believe in you!
Izuru!
Kei, use your shields to protect Suruga.
I'll distract the enemy!
Darn! I guess this is the only way.
We're going to survive... Everyone is!
I wonder if everyone's okay...
Yeah...
They'll come back safe and sound.
Otherwise my stomach will kill me!
Hurry up, Suruga! Izuru is...!
It's all set! I'm a genius!
Great! Now let's withdraw.
It worked!
Sweet!
The secondary explosions
are going off fast!
We'll get caught in the
blast if we don't hurry!
Why?! What type of
energy are they using?!
We won't make it...!
I suddenly accelerated!
The instinct to survive
means serious business!
Tamaki, thank you!
Honestly, you three are lost without me.
Is everyone okay?
Asagi!
I was so sure I was
gonna die this time...
Lookin' good there...
Hero of the Day!
"Graduation"