My name is Furuya Hotaru.
Today is my first day of high school.
I have an awesome brother.
My Brother's Girlfriend
He's the class representative.
His job is to take care of his whole class.
It's too bad he's so serious
that he can't get a girlfriend.
Onii-chan!
Furuya-kun!
We're in the same class again.
M-Minagawa-san. Get off me.
Onii-chan.
Ho-Hotaru?
Your sister?
Yeah.
Th-Thanks for taking care of my brother.
My, you're so polite. Thank you.
I'm just being polite.
Onii-chan, who is this?
Is she just a classmate?
Are you close?
Do you have more girl friends?
Stop it, Hotaru, that's rude.
You love your brother, huh?
Huh? The hell are you talking about?
I'm normal!
Sorry, she's really attached to me.
What's wrong with that? She's adorable.
And what are you to my brother?
What am I, huh?
Huh?
What is she?!
I'm sure I'm wrong, but to be really sure,
you two aren't dating, are you?
No.
We're just friends.
O-Of course.
I thought so—
For now.
Hotaru, you're hurting me.
I confessed to him, but he hasn't
given me an answer yet.
So not yet.
Onii-chan, she's trolling me.
The answer's obvious, right?
Well, um...
What's wrong?
Hurry up and reject her.
You'll hurt her if you lead her on.
H-Hotaru...
She's right, Furuya-kun.
Reject me if you have to.
Well, I...
It's not that I...
Go, go, Onii-chan!
It's not that I don't like you.
You idiot, Onii-chan!
Can't you tell I'm worried for you?
She's just toying with you.
You'll only get hurt if you go out with her.
Hotaru...
I'm not thinking of dating her or anything.
Have I just been rejected?
Exactly!
You don't need a girlfriend, right?
You have me.
Sorry, Minagawa-san, I can't go out
with you without thinking it through.
I mean, if we did, we'd have
to think about marriage,
and finances, and then kids...
You've been that serious about me?
N-No, that's not what I meant.
Of course not!
My brother's always serious!
You're right.
He really is serious.
That's why I like him.
Maybe I'll give you some more time.
Y-Your choice.
You'll be rooting for me, right, Hotaru-chan?
No!
You can't have my brother!
It's all right.
I'll adore both of you together.
I freaking hate you!
There isn't really anything
that I'm drawn to.
I have no interests or hobbies
that keep me engaged.
I know that I'm a boring person.
But is anyone really interested
by what they say they are?
Hey there.
You look like you'd like stars and stuff.
Wanna join the astronomy club?
Thanks, but no thanks.
I'm not interested.
Grab!
Come on, at least hear me out.
What's your name?
Kaga.
Have you chosen a club yet?
No.
Then want to join me in watching
an orchestra of stars?
Huh? Did I mess that up?
Huh?
Is it any fun watching the stars?
Of course it is!
They're pretty!
Don't you get bored just watching them?
Sweat
You do?
Is there anything else interesting about it?
For sure!
Club members are popular. Bam!
So far, 100% of its members have hooked up.
Well? What do you think?
Liar.
You don't really like stars
that much, do you, Senpai?
So why are you in the astronomy club?
Well, y'know, I like the vibe of it!
Yeah?
How many other members are there?
Sweat
Don't tell me zero.
Please.
You aren't interested
in any other clubs, right?
But...
Let me tell you a story
that'll make you like stars, then.
Bam!
Look over there.
There's a star called Spica
somewhere around there.
It looks like one big star,
but it's actually two stars
spinning around and pulling each other.
Or something.
Two stars help each other
and become one big light.
Isn't that philosophical?
Sure.
Are you interested now?
Not really.
That's so weird.
I ripped off
Senpai's story...
Is that all you've got?
I feel like he taught
me all kinds of stuff...
Mars!
I had delicious takoyaki while watching Mars.
My senpai, who just graduated, was, like,
"Martians look like octopus, don't they?"
So I made takoyaki as we watched Mars.
But Senpai stared at Mars the whole time,
so I scarfed them all down by myself.
This isn't even about stars anymore.
She must really love the astronomy club.
I wish I could be absorbed
by something, the way she is.
Come on, Kaga-kun!
I'm sure you'll enjoy it!
There isn't really anything
that I'm drawn to.
I was sick of being such a boring person,
so I'd been looking for something to like.
Is this what I've been looking for?
I don't know.
But I felt the need
to see more of this smile.
Okay.
Spring
Kamine sits next to me.
She avoids me a lot.
Why?
Contact
Kamine, aren't you going home?
I-I will, soon.
She won't even look at me.
Did I do something wrong?
I'll just go home.
G-Gouda-kun!
Wh-What's wrong?!
W-Well...
I just lost a contact lens.
So, um...
I see.
I'll take care not to step on it.
Don't worry.
I want you to help me look for it!
All right.
Let's look for it.
I guess she doesn't really hate me.
Do you lose your contacts often?
Sometimes.
Like when I wipe away my sweat.
You are sweating a lot.
Kamine, is there something
that you want to tell me?
I intend to answer to your wishes
to the best of my ability.
So you can tell me anything.
You must already know,
considering what you've said.
I'm not sure what you might mean.
Did I do something?
Remember how you lent me your notebook
when I was having a hard time seeing
in class because of my eyesight?
What about that?
I mean, you're so kind.
I guess that was uncalled for.
Sorry, I didn't notice.
No, you don't need to apologize.
Let's find your contact.
If I can at least find it for you...
Gouda-kun.
Did you find it?
What's your answer?
My answer?
Nothing.
I just wanted to tell you how I feel.
Are you asking me to own up?
No way.
I just want to know how you feel.
All right, if that'll make you feel better.
I'm sorry.
It's me, not you.
Honestly, it's not easy for me
to understand how girls feel.
No, it's fine.
I'll surely cause you more trouble
if I were to be near you.
If you'll accept me nonetheless, then please.
I found your contact!
Why are you crying?
Does that mean you'll go out with me?
Go out?
Of course, that was implied
by what I just said.
Thank you!
Are you all right? Kamine?
Am I crazy?
No, I'm sorry, too.
I still haven't confessed properly, have I?
What?
If there's something you
want to tell me, go ahead.
I like you.
It wasn't supposed to rain.
Takano.
No umbrella?
Sugawara-kun is in my class.
Rain
I've never really talked to him before.
Have mine.
I'll run.
But...
I felt bad, so we walked
home together part way.
Sorry.
It must be embarrassing,
walking home with a girl.
N-No, it's fine.
Not with you.
I guess he means no one would
suspect anything if it's just me.
That's good.
Your shoulder's getting wet.
Don't worry about me.
Come closer, then.
Sorry.
A little closer.
A-Aren't you embarrassed
doing this with a guy?
Not really.
No one's looking.
B-But I mean, what if your
crush saw you or something?
I don't really have one.
Why are you grinning?
I don't know much about dating.
What if someone confessed to you, then?
No one would do that.
Hypothetically.
What if someone confessed to you?
I think I'd turn them down.
Wh-Why?
There has to be something wrong
with anyone who'd confess to me.
I'm not cute. I'm gloomy.
Th-That's not true.
You're always helping people clean,
and you take care of the pupfish.
I know.
That's why I...
I'm taking the bus here.
Weren't you about to say something?
Oh, no, it was nothing.
Okay.
See you.
Dating, huh?
I don't think I can.
Sugawara-kun's really nice.
I'm sure he's popular.
Huh?
What's wrong?
I was about to say something.
I figured I'd finish saying it.
S-So, um, Takano...
I-I like you.
Thanks.
You're trying to cheer me up, right?
No?
No, I...
I am.
Well, this is my stop.
Oh? Bye.
Sugawara-kun's really nice.
Maybe I'll bake him cookies
as thanks for the umbrella.
Next episode: Short-Distance Relationships
Short-Distance Relationships