Keep quiet!
Hands behind your back.
What'd I just say?
December 21st
The bus that was hijacked by armed
men is still headed towards Tokyo!
Huh? What?
Please! Let me out! If you
want money, I have plenty—
Sacrifice               Bus hijack
It's the Neomugicha incident all over again      How scary!
Where are the cops?       Copycat criminals
Terro? Terro? Terror? lol       This is pretty bad...
Live broadcast? lol     Seriously? It's the next Neomugicha
I can't believe they're streaming this
Hey, what are you doing?!
Shh, be quiet!
Squeeze the souls of evil!
The cuisine of your heart!
The hero of justice,
Strange Juice, is on the scene!
How cute!       She's here!!!!      lololol
Get rid of her.
Is that...
Look out! Behind you!
What...
Rabura!
Stop the bus!
How do you know my—
Just do it!
Huh?! Wh-Why isn't it working?!
Pumpkin Chair here!
You're late. What kept you?!
Sorry, I had some trouble.
I'm okay now, though.
I'll stop the bus now.
How?!
I'm going to control the tire
killer at the tollbooth.
The taiyaki?
Tire killer!
When?
Um...
Three seconds!
Everyone, hang on!
It stopped!
The bus has just stopped!
Are the passengers safe?!
Masked men hijack bus headed
for international airport
As you can see, everyone is safe.
We can't use the front door.
Everyone, let's head out the back!
I see. The mastermind shows himself.
I would have preferred to stay in my seat.
Hey, what do you think you're—
Now, get on your knees and put
your hands behind your head.
What are you going to do?
I'll get rid of anyone who interferes.
Sorry, you're up first.
First?
What's wrong?
Why don't you shoot?
Goodbye.
Are you all right?
You rescued me?
Huh?! Hey, what's wrong? Get a grip!
Hey!
What happened?!
This is bad! Wake up!
Punch Line
So, Iridatsu Yu-tan, your soul has left your body.
My apartment building?!
Indeed.
And why is a cat talking?
Now, calm down, Yu-tan.
How do you know me?
How else?
I-I don't have legs!
Oh, never mind.
My name is Chiranosuke.
I'm a spirit entity, like you.
"Spirit"? Then...
It's okay, don't worry.
You haven't died yet.
Just look at this.
Hey!
That's my room.
Room 103.
Yeah.
We're in room 203, so that's
the room right beneath us.
Wait, there's someone there.
Let's change angles.
It's me.
I'm in the video.
Oh, just so you know, this is Nico Live.
[Room 103]  A Laid-back, Leisurely Broadcast 1
Current Viewers
It's a Niconico Live video.
It's live, so obviously, it's real-time.
What the hell is this?
How do I stop?!
I stopped.
All right...
Here I go!
What is this?
It's a barrier.
There are talismans all around
the room to ward off evil.
Who put these here?!
Whoever is possessing your body.
You didn't just leave your body.
A spirit entity took over your body.
It possessed you.
As a result, your spirit got kicked out.
Who, exactly?
Sake?!
I'm getting sick of explaining.
Just go find the Nandala Gandala.
What the hell is that?
Huh? You really don't know?
The Nandala Gandala is a
sacred book of ancient India.
It's said that inside, there's a secret
ritual to take back a possessed body.
A secret ritual?
Where the heck would I find such a thing?
Actually, it's here.
In someone's room here at Korai House.
What? Who's?
I don't know.
Well, good luck!
Hey, wait!
What's with him?
Nandala Gandala?
Well, it sounds sketchy, but
I guess I have to go look for it.
The most suspicious room would be...
Sorry, Ito, I'm coming in.
Ito's not here, huh?
Man, this room's always so messy.
I thought if it was anywhere,
it'd be in Ito's room.
You can easily imagine the damage
that will be caused if we...
This is the hijacking.
Ito...
Oh, yeah, I have to grab some more shampoo.
Room 102: Hikiotani Ito
Ito, I didn't mean to!
Sorry!
What the hell just happened?
Oh, yeah.
I forgot to tell you.
When you get too excited
and lose consciousness,
an asteroid comes down and
exterminates humanity.
What are you talking about?
I'm saying it's all your fault that this happened.
When you see a girl's panties,
you reach peak excitement,
and you gain superhuman abilities.
But a peak is a peak.
There's nothing higher.
Therefore, if you're stimulated even
more while you're already excited,
your limiter breaks and
you lose consciousness.
I don't get it.
How does that have anything
to do with an asteroid?
You don't have to overthink it.
If you don't want to end
humanity, don't get excited.
That's all that matters.
But...
Just redo it, Yu-tan.
Go back to the past, and start again.
The past?
The laws of temporal physics
don't apply to spirit entities.
You aren't physical to begin with, after all.
H-Hey, wait a minute.
What are you going on about?
Now, go, Iridatsu Yu-tan!
Go back through time,
and create a supremely
happy and peaceful future!
This is... Ito's room?
You can easily imagine the damage that will be...
I'm back.
Oh, yeah, I have to grab some more shampoo.
Crap!
I can't find it. What did I do with it?
Room 101: Narugino Mikatan
Where did that book go?
Maybe it's on the top shelf.
Don't look...
Don't look!
Oh, right, the book.
Maybe she's talking about
the Nandala Gandala.
Under here, maybe?
Did I leave it under the bed?
Nine months ago...
Sorry! I wasn't paying attention!
Man, I messed it all up.
Um, have we met before?
What are you talking about, Narugino?
You're a member of the popular She's Mei.
Room 201: Daihatsu Meika
You can't blame him for staring at you.
Isn't that right, Iridatsu?
Come on, at least say hi.
You're going to be living under
the same roof from today on.
Nice to meet you.
U-Um...
So, Narugino, what's that thing you've
been holding onto so carefully?
I'm sorry!
It's not here, either.
Coming!
Room 202: Chichibu Rabura
Hey, could you lend me some salt?
Salt?
Do you need it to make dinner?
Y-Yeah, if you want to call
a ghost hunt "dinner," I guess.
Ghost Hunt (Yuurei Hanto)
Dinner (Yuuhan)
I got a request earlier.
I'm going to do an exorcism tomorrow.
Does normal salt work for that?
Sure, it's fine.
It's all in the mind, really.
Is this medium going to be okay?
Hm? Did you say something?
No, nothing.
Oh, yeah.
Meika wanted me to give this back to you.
I was looking for this!
Could that be...
But why did Meika...
"Y-You mustn't, Ryunoshin-dono!"
"Aw, what's the problem, Torahachirou?"
Said Ryunoshin, as he extended his
arm towards Torahachiro's third blade...
This isn't it!
Oh, did we get the wrong one?
The wrong one?
It must've been when we ran into each other.
Then...
Mother stayed up all night...
to count all the money in her secret stash...
Is that...
Damn it!
Too bad.
Your spirit power level is too low.
Spirit powers are the powers
possessed by spirit entities.
With higher levels, you can move heavy objects
and cause poltergeist-like phenomena.
However, at your current level,
you could maybe roll a pencil at most.
That sounds like a game.
I guess I'll try it out.
Move. Move.
Move!
Aw, look what I did.
Beginning Spirit Power User
Huh? Words just popped up.
That's your designation.
Designation?
Here we go.
What's this?
Maybe I forgot to put it away
when I cleaned the other day.
Grandpa...
This brings back memories.
It's just an album.
This just in.
We have just learned that an armed group
Suspects barricaded in movie theater,
audience held hostage
claiming to be of the Qmay Group has
taken hostages in a movie theater in Tokyo.
The Qmay Group is suspected
of being associated
with the bus hijacking that
happened this afternoon.
Qmay Group?
Oh, no! This song!
Hey, what's going on?
The apples of Tsugaru are ripe with nectar...
You're singing?!
Narugino, let's go—
Oh, Rabura.
Hey, Kamenishi-kun escaped, you know.
What?!
Rabura-san, your salt!
Thanks!
I found it!
But why was it here?
Punch Perms and
Chirashi Sushi
She was talking about a lyrics book?
That song earlier was a sign
that there's been an emergency!
Strange Juice, move out!
Roger!
Strange Juice?
Strange Juice, rush up!
Actual footage
You know, I've always wondered...
Is that dance really necessary?
No way... Narugino is...
I'm a hero. I have to transform.
Heave ho, heave ho, there we go.
Crap! I looked!
But as long as I don't see it again...
Changing
Hero of Justice, Strange Juice!
I've transformed!
Let's go, then.
Damn it!
What the hell is going on?!
What're you holding, Pumpkin Chair?
Oh, this?
It's, uh, a lucky charm.
I was going to give it to you.
But it's not fini—
Thanks.
I'll take it.
No, it's not—
Speed Maker, away!
I can't believe Narugino was Strange Juice.
Please, Narugino.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Panty Panic