Why would you come here?
You don't understand anything.
The feeling of rotting alive,
the pain and agony of being burned alive,
the sensation of insects eating
the flesh off your bones...
No one... Not a single person
knows what it's like.
Everyone scoffs at me and calls me a freak.
Do you want people to understand?
Or do you just want to believe
you're the only one suffering?
Is that...
something you're in a position to say?
You're quite blessed, aren't you?
Every day, you're being targeted for
your body, your blood, your soul...
But you had no trouble getting
food, shelter, or education.
The only ones having trouble are the adults
who have to raise a creepy child.
And yet,
you're the one who acts as though
you're the one suffering most.
I lived my life despising and
envying all sorts of things, too.
I thought I could do anything
to escape the misery.
You and I may be alike...
and that's why I need to
beat the hell out of you.
Huh?
What?
You think you're in the right
just because you tried to die?
After you gave the people around
you so much hell for it?
I don't think I'm in the right.
Ashen Eye!
You've become quite strong.
Why are you here?
I see the human child has
served her purpose well.
No...
That's it.
A human heart in motion is so beautiful.
Joy, sadness, distress, anger...
These are the things that move the world.
You and he are both very,
very beautiful to me.
You piss me off.
Elias! Ruth!
Well, well, he's finally arrived.
Ashen Eye!
Kids these days don't know
how to treat their elders.
So you're the ones who scarred
this girl so brutally.
Ariel...
Let's do this, you failure.
Why?
I'm not doing this for you.
We're aligned in our opinions.
A fairy with a mind?
She's going to be trouble.
I don't have time for this.
Ruth, keep an eye on Chise.
Yeah, got it.
Ashen Eye!
You aren't going.
Nettles in the shadow, ring of holly...
Maybe you've suffered more than
me or anyone I've ever met.
But just because it hurts doesn't mean
you can make others suffer with you,
or that you can do anything you want!
So it's only okay if it's you?!
What's the difference between
what you tried to earn
by sacrificing yourself, and what I want?!
Ruth!
It's the same.
So let's end it.
Resound, resound, forest song of the night.
Hear, hear, the howling of the grave keeper.
Sleep magic doesn't work on me.
Not since you're here.
Too bad.
Goodbye.
Got you.
E... lias...
Elias,
I want you to bind us together so that
no matter what happens,
we won't be separated.
All right.
He did it.
Let go!
Why...
It hurts, doesn't it?
It hurts when no one understands.
One, two, where do you bloom?
Under the window where the children sleep,
white flowers on the night of a pale moon...
Three, four, where do you bloom?
On the frame of Mommy's mirror,
a little blue flower blooms...
Let's count, let's count, let's find
and count the flowers...
Count to seven and eight...
In the dream in which the child sleeps.
Mommy will give you a bouquet of flowers.
Mommy will give you a bouquet of flowers...
Good night, Cartaphilus, Joseph.
Chise!
He's right. I wouldn't want
to do this for millennia.
Don't try to talk.
Elias...
Hey, what's going on?
Chise...
It's a promise.
Hello.
I reached a bit of an understanding
with the dragon inside of you.
I'm going to keep you alive, and
the dragon will someday kill you.
We'll be inside of you,
keeping each other in check.
So nothing will happen to you right away.
Oh, but that's how it is for all
ordinary beings, isn't it?
Good for you.
Look, it's time.
Chise...
Go to the child. He's waiting for you.
Now, hurry.
Welcome home, Chise.
I'm home, Elias.
Now, Elias, let's hear your excuse.
Why did you do such a thing to Stella
without even talking to me first?
If you're going to go there, I have
something I want to say, too.
You're always the one who does
things without consulting me.
I already apologized for that!
I just said we'd think things
through together from now on,
and look at what you go and do!
But...
Silky...
Hang on.
I'm not done yet.
I'm not, either.
You, too, Ruth.
I'm off now.
Chise, stop.
Don't put myself in danger.
Back down if I'm about to get hurt.
Talk to someone before I take action.
Yeah.
Off you go.
See you later.
What was that about?
That was the result of our discussion.
So, you were saying?
Let's see...
Stella's back to normal, and the witches
have stopped coming to recruit us.
The two dragons are back with Lindel.
What happened to Cartaphilus?
Who knows?
I don't think he'll be back
for a few decades, at least.
Aren't you going to wake up?
I can't stand that weirdo
getting in my face anymore.
The suffering one has found
a place to rest his head.
How boring.
Chise!
I was waiting for you!
Hello.
We were waiting for you, Robin.
We talked on the phone plenty
of times, but how are you?
Has your wound healed?
My stomach's fine now, but I can't push
myself as much as I could before.
You just admitted that
you were pushing yourself.
Here you go.
As promised.
Thank you.
I can't believe you'd ask
for such a thing, though.
I don't really mean anything by it.
Do you have a fever or something?
No.
Well then, for you...
Here.
What's this?
Take a look later.
See you again.
Take care of yourself!
Happy birthday!
Happy... birth...
You thought it was my birthday, didn't you?
You're wrong!
Today's your birthday party.
Today's your... huh?
You said you've never had a birthday
party before, so I'm hosting one.
Oh, it is true that it's my
birthday today, though.
Let's enjoy it together today.
I'd love to.
Hey, here.
Wow, it's pretty.
Thanks, Chise.
Okay, one for you.
I asked my aunt to make it for you.
Th-Thanks.
Open it.
Okay.
Silver?
I'm sorry, Elias.
I was going to go straight home, but...
Where did you get that?
It's not what you were wearing
when you left this morning.
Um...
Stella gave it to me as a gift.
And the veil?
Angelica-san gave me the veil.
Is this what "beautiful" is?
Um... here.
What is it?
Forget it.
Just give me your left hand.
Your left hand!
Huh? Okay.
That's your right hand.
And take your gloves off.
Okay.
A ring?
I keep this one.
If anything happens to either
of us, it'll let us know.
I thought it might... put you at ease.
I've heard that the left ring
finger is for wedding rings.
It's only been a year, but so much
has changed since you bought me.
I met all kinds of people, and all
kinds of people helped me along.
The world is a lot bigger
than I'd ever thought.
It's not that I was reborn, and
I still resent being in this body.
But now, I can allow myself to think...
that I get to be here because
I didn't jump back then.
You alone didn't bring me
to that conclusion,
but it wouldn't have worked without you.
Nothing would have.
You might have forgotten now...
I...
I do not intend to ever again do
anything that you might dislike.
Even then,
by being involved with you,
I may become monstrous again.
Are you still okay with me?
Stella said...
Words aren't for understanding each other.
They exist for the sake
of talking to each other.
If we butt heads, if we
can't understand each other,
we'll talk it over together.
So that we can find a sweet spot.
Elias...
May I walk next alongside you going forward?
Of course.
You're my bride, after all.
Yes.
Should you quit being my apprentice?
What do you think?
You should continue.
I agree.
I look forward to it,
my... teacher.
Huh?
It's still embarrassing to say.
Cut me some slack.
I'm home.