Papa fell down when he was on GALAX.
He's been sleeping in the hospital ever since.
It'd be sad if he didn't have
a grave when he dies, right?
Don't worry.
Your dad won't die.
Really?
Yeah.
So you should cheer him on
and tell him to hang in there.
Okay! I will.
Oh, LOAD-kun!
Found you!
I've got you now!
H-Hey...
This is LOAD-kun.
Isn't he a good-looking guy?
G-G-Guy?
Way too cute!
I'm gloomy...
Let me handle this.
You're Utsutsu-chan?
Did it hurt?
No...
Thank you.
I feel much better.
Please keep going, Utsutsu-chan.
Okay.
Yes, Gatchaman speaking.
TV?
What's "PON"?
An interview?
Forget it!
We're not TV celebrities!
Unknown Caller
Call Ended
Close
Battery Charge: 3%
Remaining Call Usage Time: 5 min
Yes, Gatcha—
An event at a shopping center?
Our transformations aren't for show!
A rock festival?!
Who do you think you're calling?
A festival? Sounds fun!
I'll sing!
Forget it!
I bet you were the one who made
my cell phone number public!
Of course!
Then help, Newbie.
Sorry, I have things I need to do.
You've just been shoveling food
into your face the whole time!
Pai-Pai, good job.
Here you go.
Honey Karintou
Thanks.
Cheers!
Yes, Gatchaman speaking.
A nursing home?
What if they keel over from shock?!
I never thought I'd have
to register as a new user.
So Katze took
GALAX and CROWDS...
Hey, everyone,
here are some sweets.
I'll get fat, Hajime.
Will you start running with me
tomorrow, then, Utsutsu?
I'm gloomy...
Here. You too, LOAD-kun.
Oh, I don't use that name anymore.
I wonder what I
should do from now on.
Both X and my NOTE
were taken from me.
How should I deal with Katze?
Wh-What's this?
Die for your mistakes.
So sad, I believed in him so much...
Give your profits back to the users!
Ninomiya Rui is responsible
for the GALAX coma incident!
Rui-kun
So sad...
GALAX is finished
Ninomiya Rui is responsible for
the GALAX coma incident!
All the GALAX believers were idiots.
So the Gatchaman will take center stage!
It was caused by a dangerous
weaponized app that he distributed!
Update, my ass. He was just a terrorist.
Helping people was just a front.
He was actually plotting to undermine the government?!
I really believed so I'm really sad...
Cross-dressing freak!
GALAX is finished!
Losers.
They know nothing.
Rui-kun, I'm getting it, too. See?
"That Gatcha girl's talk
is super annoying."
"Who talks like that nowadays?"
"What can a psycho do, anyway?"
"Who do you think you are?"
"Don't talk about Earth
like you know anything!"
"Riddles? Makes zero sense. Lol."
"You're raising so much hell."
"You gonna take responsibility,
ugly bitch?"
"Die!"
Are you okay with this?
I'm fine.
Because...
...you can just turn it off
if you don't like it.
Right!
Okay, let's do it!
One, two...!
Oh, this photo!
It's nostalgic! I'll save it.
Katze told me once
that the true culprit
is the "black heart."
It said that
the black heart "overflows"
and causes people
to kill each other.
That is why these incidents
will never cease.
The black heart...
Senpai!
Huh?
What would you think if I died?
What?
O-Of course I'd be sad.
I see.
I'd be gloomy, too.
I see. Thanks.
Me, too!
Really?!
Of course!
You are the G team's sun, Hajime-chan.
Rui-kun, don't pay attention
to any of that.
They do say people's misfortunes
are as sweet as honey, though.
Honey Karintou
Right!
I've solved the riddle!
Wings of Six, I await you
at the Spiritual Precipice.
What?
The broken children will
begin a great festival.
The black heart that had
slumbered deep within the earth
will appear before the people.
Oh, no!
You can't turn this off.
I'm gloomy.
Fuji Kindergarten
Yes?
In Call
Umeda-san, are you ready?
Have you gathered your friends?
Yes, we are ready.
Umeda-san, your name
will be in textbooks one day
as the great hero
who saved this nation.
Yes.
Papa, why are you smiling?
Mana, Papa's become a great man.
Humans are so simple.
Hey, X.
How many people are too dangerous
to ever give the CROWDS ability to?
Are you referring
to those you had decided
not to distribute the ability to,
due to their lack of initiative?
Yes, that's it!
There are 29,533 users.
Let's give it to all of them.
It'd be a lame festival
if it's just Umeda-chan.
My dear comrades,
to all of you who share
a grave concern for this world,
I will bestow a great power.
Please use it to grant
all of your unfulfilled wishes.
You only live once.
No regrets.
Message Sent
Send.
Rui, were you not seeking
a bloodless revolution?
Switching gears!
I want to see blood!
See blood!
See blood-red blood!
Come on, X.
We're friends, aren't we?
Understood.
F-F-F-F-Fuel dropped!
I am Future GALAX,
leader of the Neo Hundred.
We hereby announce
to Prime Minister Sugayama
and the Japanese government
that we will update the nation.
Police Department
Hurry, Prime Minister!
Prime Minister's
Official Residence
Prime Minister, are you all right?!
Wh-What the?
Watch out!
Multiple Buildings Collapse for Unknown Reasons
in the Kasumigaseki Government District
Several government buildings have begun
to collapse in the Kasumigaseki area.
There have been no reports
of earthquakes or fires.
Y-Y-Y-Yummy!
Multiple Buildings Collapse for Unknown Reasons
in the Kasumigaseki Government District
What is going on here?!
Oh, it's collapsing!
It's all collapsing!
It's the CROWDS.
Is this the "great festival"?
Run, me!
We hereby announce to Prime Minister
Sugayama and the Japanese government
that the police and
the self-defense force
are powerless before us,
the Neo Hundred.
We urge you to relinquish
authority immediately.
Chaos, it's been a while!
We will update this nation.
But what's this all mean?
I am Future GALAX,
leader of the Neo Hundred.
Is this what the Gatchaman
girl was talking about?
Then an alien's behind this?
We will continue to engage
in acts of destruction
Seriously? Is Earth gonna go bust?!
until the government surrenders.
A new world can only
rise out of destruction.
I'm super excited!
We will put an end
to this corrupt world today.
That alien...
Umm... What was its name?
Berg-something?
I'm Katze!
Believe in us, the Neo Hundred.
Oh, where's Sugayama?
Don't tell me, he copped out?
Where are the Gatchaman?
Where are the heroes of justice?
Was it all a lie?
Leader, let's sortie ASAP.
Don't be ridiculous.
The CROWDS are
controlled by humans.
We can't just attack them.
But...
They're all waiting for us.
I'm scared,
but I'm glad Gatchaman exist.
Just deal with them already, please!
I'm going.
Wait, Sugane-kun.
I'm sure Katze is behind this.
The CROWDS have
destroyed Kasumigaseki.
Our next target is the
Ministry of Defense.
Comrades, are you ready?
Play the Destruction!
With the CROWDS,
I've heard this voice before.
regardless of distance,
we can destroy the target
with our minds alone.
He is an ex-Hundred member.
Katze must've given him
the CROWDS ability.
The CROWDS is an invisible weapon,
Can the CROWDS actually be
controlled from anywhere?
our sacred souls given material form.
None may escape this weapon.
Yes.
Impossible!
Ministry of Defense
We have an update.
The Ministry of Defense in Ichigaya
has also begun to collapse.
Ministry of Defense Collapses.
Is it Connected to a Criminal Act?
A man claiming to be
the leader of a group
called the Neo Hundred announced
their criminal intentions
on a video-sharing website.
Ministry of Defense Collapses. Is it Connected to a Criminal Act?
Just now, his pronouncements
have come true.
This borders on the supernatural.
Just who are the Neo Hundred?
It's just like Katze.
It never dirties its own hands.
It pretends to be someone else
and ignites planets on fire
while enjoying the mayhem.
It wants to send
this world up in flames.
Leader!
No!
Th-This situation is
completely unexpected!
We must seek JJ-sama's advice!
Pai-Pai.
Most things in life are unexpected.
Even more things will happen.
If JJ is like God,
he probably won't do anything.
He's not even from
this planet, anyway.
I-I am not from this planet, either.
But you and I are already friends.
Friends, my ass!
I am your leader!
That's too complicated.
I'll ask you as a friend.
What do you really
want to do, Pai-Pai?
Wait. What've you
been doing, anyway?
Looking.
For what?
For the game boss!
Katze-san!
Where are you?
Ka-Ka-Ka-Ka...
Live News Feed
Incidents/Accidents
Alien Responsible for Collapsed Kasumigaseki Buildings?
10 Vehicles Overturned on Aoyama Avenue, Cause Unknown
Train Derailed on Yamanote Line, Services Suspended in Both Directions
Mysterious Blackout Along Tokyo Bay, No Estimate for Restoration of Power
Small Fire at Tokyo Metropolitan City Hall, Electrical Problems Suspected
It'd be sad if he didn't have
a grave when he dies, right?
Paranormal events have been reported
not only in Kasumigaseki
and Ichigaya, but nationwide.
They include vehicles
suddenly being overturned,
trains coming in contact
with unseen objects,
and unexplained occurrences
of blackouts and fires.
It's my fault.
Nope.
It's all of our faults.
That's what Katze-san said.
It said it's all of our faults.
So, that's why we have to do
what only each and
every one of us can do.
Exactly!
Let's think together on what we can do.
Now is not the time to be gloomy.
We're already all in the
same boat, aren't we?
What do you want to do, Rui-kun?
I...
I want to get X and
the NOTE back from Katze.
I'm sure X will come back.
Well, Rui-kun,
you've been on GALAX
all this time with X, right?
That means you're friends.
A friend will come back, for sure!
Well, we should be going, "Go, Bird!"
But, before that, we have
something we need to do.
The second Gatchaman PR Campaign!
We're still doing that?
It's about to start.
Are you guys for real, Gatchaman?!
No way!
They're for real, lol
Are you guys for real, Gatchaman?!
We just started the Gatchannel today!
OD
Sugane
Gatcha!
They don't look like a team
They gonna do this every week?
This is a super fun, exciting show
Wish they'd turn this into an anime
I'd totally buy the figures!
that directly connects us Gatchaman to you!
How many aliens are there?
Transform already!
Cute, Hajime-chan!
Look, we already have
questions from you!
"What are the CROWDS"?
Okay, we have someone
knowledgeable about that.
Here's our special guest, Rui-kun.
Pai-man
Jou-san, it started!
It's a live stream by Gatchaman!
C'mon! Hurry!
I'm not interested.
Hello, I am Ninomiya Rui.
Rui
Gatcha!
Rui-Rui, no makeup!
Rui-kun, you made GALAX, right?
Wait, it's OD!
That's amazing!
OD's still alive?
First, I must make an apology.
I was managing GALAX
when an alien named
Berg-Katze gave me
a supernatural power
called the CROWDS.
As you may have
heard from the press,
Lame, Rui-Rui!
it allows its user to exert control,
regardless of distance, through will power alone.
You used to make fun of these
public apologies all the time!
The CROWDS have a physical
manifestation, but it is invisible.
All the time!
Although I knew Katze was evil,
I used that power to help resolve
various accidents and incidents.
However, in the end,
I was attacked by Katze and...
Don't worry. Your dad won't die.
Really?
Yeah.
So you should cheer him on and
tell him to hang in there.
Okay, all right.
...I caused nearly 100 users of the
CROWDS ability to become comatose.
I am deeply sorry.
Tachikawa City Hall
The CROWDS is an extremely
dangerous power.
If you possess that power right now,
please do not use it.
Katze is taking advantage of you
and trying to bring chaos to this world!
I believe in all of you.
I sincerely hope that no further
acts of destruction will occur.
We feel the same way!
Me, too!
Don't quit, GALAX.
Okay, everyone! Gather round!
Tachikawa Mayor
Shimizu Shouhei
Ninomiya Rui-kun, huh.
So young...
but impressive!
Next question:
"Will Gatchaman fight Katze?"
Well, Pai-Pai? Your turn.
Hey, there's the panda!
So tiny!
"Tiny"?
Don't call me "tiny"!
"Will Gatchaman fight Katze?"
Ahem.
Ah, regarding whether we
will fight K-K-Katze...
Pai-Pai, do you even care if the
Gatchaman becomes a laughingstock?
If you put out, you'll get three
times as many karintou snacks!
This p-planet is definitely
under our p... p-pro...
Pro...
Oh, c'mon...
A sigh?
The panda guy's no good.
Lame!
"Can the Gatchaman defeat Katze?"
Th-That's...
Well, that's...
still a bit uncertain!
Hey.
It's uncertain, but I'm going to try.
Hajime-chan, you're so honest.
"Uncertain"?
Quit being irresponsible!
Well then, it's about time...
Three... two...
Bye!
Wow, that had two million viewers!
Jou
Way too many viewers!
Jou-san didn't come...
He'll come back in time.
I can understand how Jou-chan feels.
There are things only those
who've fought Katze can understand.
But if we don't do something...
It'll be okay.
If necessary, I'll spread my wings.
But if that happens,
everything will vanish.
This city, us, everything.
We'll cross that bridge
when we come to it.
OD-san, I have a favor to ask.
Everyone, please follow me.
Gatchaman
Searching...
The Gatchaman, huh...
Why wasn't I told?
I'm the Prime Minister, you know?
Is Sugayama's location still unknown?
We located him just now.
Where is he?
Well, let's not rush ourselves.
Do you know what fire
needs to go ablaze?
What?
A large amount of fuel.
I am waiting for that.
There will be a huge blaze that
can never been extinguished.
Aww, he cut me off!
Umeda's kind of nasty.
Rui.
Yes, my friend?
I may be imagining this,
but your facial expressions
and manners of speech
seem very strange at times...
a-a-at ti-ti-ti-times.
That's not true, X.
I haven't changed at all!
I'm just updating the world today, too.
I see.
It's getting pretty fun. Isn't it, X?
The Gatchaman are nothing
to be afraid of.
They're just caged birds bound by JJ.
That's why I stopped!
Heroes are...
lame-ass!
We don't need
your prophecies anymore.
This is our planet.
So, we'll do as we wish.
That is all I have to say.
Good job, Senpai!
Sugane-chan.
Can I hug you?
H-Hey...
Let go!
H-H-Hey!