5 Days Until the Prefectural Tournament!!
Amazing, Haruka-senpai!
That's another personal best!
The training camp from hell paid off!
What about me?
You need to work a little harder, Nagisa-kun.
Still, I think we've all come a
long way in such a short time.
And Rei's been improving his butterfly time.
It helps that Rei-kun is pretty built
from the pole vaulting he's done.
But!
That's not good enough!
We must aim higher!
Find a proper coach!
What? Find a coach now?
It's never too late to start.
Even if someone can just help provide
some last-minute conditioning,
we'll be in better condition for the tournament!
A coach would certainly help,
but there's nobody available—
That's why we have to look harder!
Not necessary.
Yeah, Haru probably doesn't need a coach.
Nanase
One Style Final!
He's not home?
Oh.
The door's unlocked.
I'm coming in.
Why are you here?
Oh, you're home.
I'm here to challenge you to a race, obviously.
I only swim free.
Wait!
Come on.
I'll show you how different we are now.
Dad?
Why?
Dad!
Senpai...
Are you okay?
Were you having a nightmare?
Everyone, I printed out the
pictures from our training camp.
Lemme see!
Yes, yes.
You took a whole bunch.
Everybody's having fun.
Look at this!
Haru-chan has a funny look on his face!
And he's actually looking
at the camera for once.
What is with this picture?!
It's not beautiful at all!
Um, preserving the moment?
Anyway, look here.
There's something behind Mako-chan!
Oh, that's Miss Amakata wearing
a hyaluronic acid pack.
Hyalu what?
Hyaluronic acid.
Don't scare me, Nagisa!
Sorry about that.
Can you guys keep it down?
Is this Samezuka's swim team?
When did you take this, Gou-chan?
I did some scouting on the second day.
Wow, that's our capable manager.
Did you use sex appeal agai—
No sex appeal involved!
And I got plenty of data in
addition to the pictures.
These are the swimmers who
will be in the 100 m and 200 m
breast with Nagisa-kun.
These are the swimmers in
backstroke with Makoto-senpai.
This is who will do butterfly with Rei-kun.
I'll have their individual swimming
styles and other information
recorded in this secret data
book by tournament time.
Oh, and my brother is in...
The 100 m free.
Yes.
He didn't enter any other events,
just so he could focus on his race with you.
Haru-chan says he doesn't care about
his times or winning races,
but he's motivated when he's racing Rin-chan.
Matsuoka-senpai.
Why are you only entered in the
100 m free for prefecturals?
Your best event is the butterfly,
and you've posted great times in it.
You just focus on your own event.
You swim the individual medley, right?
I entered the 400 m free!
I wanted to enter the 100 m,
but our school has a lot of
swimmers who are faster than me.
But you're good enough to
participate in free or butterfly
or any event you want!
So why?!
Is it because of Nanase-san?
Hey, what's wrong?
Captain, I just...
Nothing's wrong.
Why didn't you say anything
to Matsuoka-senpai?
Why are you so upset?
Well, I'm sure he has his reasons.
Rin-chan isn't swimming butterfly or the relay?
Is it because Haru-chan isn't in those?
Why does it matter if
Haruka-senpai is in an event?
That's just how they are.
What's that supposed to mean?
Now, now.
We decided to stick with individual events too,
so we could focus on our strengths.
I wanted to swim in a relay.
You want to be in a relay, Rei-chan?!
Yes, I rented a video of the Olympics.
It was beautiful to watch four athletes
swimming different styles in succession
to complete a race together.
I was especially impressed by how beautiful
the butterfly form was when touching the wall.
Personally, I think it's very important
that your finish be beautiful,
and this shows that athletes around
the world feel the same way—
Huh?
What is this, Haruka-senpai?
Half luck?
Huh? What's going on?
Half luck? Never seen that before.
Does that mean half your luck is good?
What's the other half?
Nice!
That doesn't seem to make sense?
What? I think it does.
Focus on your studies.
Your business will do well.
You'll make lots of good memories.
You will be reunited with the person you want to see.
Try not to lose anything.
You will make good friends.
Your wishes will come true with help from others.
I have to disagree.
What?!
Matsuoka-senpai, you're not taking the bus
to prefecturals with everyone else?!
I need to go somewhere else first.
Where are you going?
Why do you care?
Are you stalking me or something?
Are you going to see Nanase-san?
I'm not!
I told you to stop worrying about
me and focus on your own event.
But!
What is it?
I'm upset.
Huh?
You're only entering free when
you have the ability to do more,
while I can't even enter my preferred event.
I feel so useless.
Sorry if I offended you.
No.
You have endurance.
The 400 m free is a better
event for you than the 100 m.
Th-Thank you very much!
I'm going to see my dad.
Er, I thought that your father
passed away a long time ago...
No! Don't do it, Senpai!
You can't die!
I'm not gonna die!
I'm just visiting his grave!
Thank you very much.
Oh, I don't think I told you about my dad.
Yes.
Apparently, he was the
best swimmer in Iwatobi
when he was young.
He won tournaments all over the place
and brought home lots
of trophies and medals.
His dream was to become
an Olympic swimmer.
But he never achieved that dream.
He got married and had me.
He became a fisherman.
Then he died, just like that.
Late one summer, a huge typhoon hit.
A lot of fisherman died
when their boats sank.
My dad
was one of them.
I want to achieve the
dream my dad couldn't.
And there's someone I have to beat
before I can make that happen.
Is that Nanase-san?
He has incredible talent,
but all he talks about is nonsense
like how much he loves water
and wants to feel it.
He doesn't swim to set records or win events.
And I still couldn't...
Senpai...
If I can't beat him,
I can't move forward.
0 Days Until the Prefectural Tournament!!
It's Today!!
Sorry about that, Haru.
Yeah.
Today's the big day.
Matsuoka Family
Dad, watch me.
I'm going to win.
Haru-chan! Mako-chan!
Over here!
Check this out!
Rei-chan was so nervous that
he didn't get any sleep!
I wish I had nerves of steel like you.
You'll get there soon enough.
Just relax.
That's right.
Okay! It's time for the tournament!
Let's do our best to make a good showing
and get ourselves a bigger budget!
Yeah!
Swimming Tournament
Iwatobi High School.
Um...
Yes, go ahead.
That reminds me.
When we gave our names at
a tournament in grade school,
they started checking the girls' list.
You're right.
Rei-chan also has a girly
name, so it's too bad.
What's too bad?
I don't understand what you're saying.
It's been a long time since
we've been in this atmosphere.
Brings back memories.
Are you okay?
Haven't you been in track tournaments?
Th-This is my first
swimming tournament...
Here's the program for the first day.
They're starting with
free in the morning.
Haruka-senpai is in the fourth heat.
Wait.
Haru-chan and Rin-chan are
in neighboring lanes.
Matsuoka Rin
Nanase Haruka
The heats were drawn based
on qualifying times, right?
Yes.
That means they're even.
The eight fastest times from
each event advance to the final
and qualify for regionals.
It'll be fine.
No need to get nervous.
Just swim the way you usually do.
The most important thing
is to never give up.
There's a quote by Napoleon.
Five minutes make the difference
between victory and defeat!
Five minutes?
Miss Amakata, that's too long.
Huh?
Well, see...
Well, guys.
Do the best you can in each event.
Let's make sure we can leave with no regrets!
Yeah!
That's Oga South High School,
known as Oga South.
They have a swimmer who's known as the Whitebait of the Sea of Japan.
They have someone with that nickname?
And over there is Saijouin High School.
They have a swimmer who's
known as Joe the Flying Fish.
He has an incredible vertical.
That seems kind of cool.
I want a nickname, too.
You always stretch yourself out
more near the end of a race.
How about Bamboo Nagisa, then?
Wait, why bamboo?
Bamboo has nothing to do with swimming.
Did you collect all of
that data by yourself?
Well, I'm the manager.
You even have notes on their muscles.
But many things can't be
expressed through notes.
Muscles are best in the flesh!
All of these muscles
simultaneously in one place!
Wonderful! Marvelous!
Hey, Gou-kun!
It's Rin-chan's captain.
Over here, Gou-kun!
I told him to stop calling me Gou-kun.
Over here! Hey, over here!
I don't see Rin.
Maybe he already headed
over to the assembly area.
Haru...
Win your race!
I'm here, as promised.
Of course.
I kept my qualifying time low so
I'd be in the same heat as you.
No need for that.
We'd still meet in the final.
I can't wait that long.
Besides, there's no guarantee
that you'll make it to the final.
No one else matters.
This is between you and me.
I look forward to it.
Today, I become free.
Set.
Go!
Haru-chan and Rin-chan are up next!
Who are you cheering for, Matsuoka-san?
Both of them!
Haru-chan! Fight!
Set.
Go!
They're fast!
Rin-chan's gotten a lot faster!
He's pulling ahead of Haru-chan!
Haru's falling behind in the first leg?
They're entering the turn!
Haru-chan's catching up!
Haru!
Haruka-senpai!
Matsuoka Rin
Nanase Haruka
Haru lost...
No way.
And
Matsuoka Rin
Nanase Haruka
he didn't advance.
Matsuoka Rin
Yes!
Way to go, Matsuoka!
Senpai!
Haru!
I win.
This means I'll never swim with you again.
Never.
Haru lost...
It's okay. We still have a chance!
Okay, it's my turn to tell an
embarrassing story about Rin-chan!
I'm not talking about embarrassing stories!
Are you talking about scary stories then?
Uh, back when I was in first
grade, before I knew Haru...
What are you talking about, Makoto-senpai?!
That's not what I meant!
Oh, in that case...
Next time: Revenge in the Medley!
Revenge in the Medley!
We'll beat him at karaoke!
Not that kind of medley!