You refused... Why?
Huh?
The offer to erase the information
that's going around online.
Aren't you scared?
Having...
all sorts of things said about you?
They're all people I don't know.
If I don't like it,
I just have to do this!
More importantly,
we had a lot of fun
today, Utsutsu-chan!
What?
Let's play hide-and-seek
together again!
X.
Yes, how may I be of service?
Are there those among
the current Hundred
who appear to have lost initiative?
Among current members,
none exhibit a significant drop in initiative.
There are sporadic comments
along the lines of being "made"
to do Hundred activities,
but they appear to be joking in tone.
And what are their numbers?
Numbers 41, 63, and 80.
Please remove them.
I do not want any cause
for concern to remain for our work to come.
Understood.
Numbers 41, 63, and 80
have been removed.
Summon the remaining Hundred.
Tonight, we will eliminate Katze.
Understood.
I'm dreamy...
Oh, Utsutsu.
I have a favor to ask.
What?
Can you go borrow a pair
of scissors from Hajime-chan?
Oh, welcome back, Rui-Rui!
Were you out working away
on your GALAXter project again?
I really think you should stop
piddling around with little things,
and just go out and take over the world.
After all, I went through
the trouble of giving you power.
Right? So much trouble.
What's with that knife?
Oh, that's the first time
you're asking any questions.
Until now, you were too scared
to ask me what I do when I go off.
That makes me happy!
What made you change your mind?
D-I-Y
means Do-It-Yourself!
Come in.
Utsutsu-chan!
Scissors, please.
Oh, sure!
Which one do you want?
Maybe these would be good for you.
I'm here for OD, so...
D-san might like these, then?
Those, then.
Here you go!
What's the matter?
O-Origami.
C-Can we—
Oh!
Huh?
That's a frog, right?
You were trying to make a frog!
Yeah.
It's more fun to have a lot of frogs!
O-Okay.
But frogs are green, right?
There are... red ones, too.
Oh, let's make them
in different colors, then.
You're really good with them.
The only reason this motley crew
hangs together by a thread
is you, I have to say.
I'm a poor leader.
I made another memory again.
When it only brings pain.
Yahoo!
You even brought them here?
Do you finally intend to get rid of me?
Sparkle!
That's right.
I must defeat you, after all!
What is that?!
Could that be...
It was really tall.
Long, tangled hair and
a diamond-shaped tail.
Who is it?
What?!
Go, Bird!
Where'd it go?
What's going on?
Are they trying to defeat that alien?
Hey, you!
Riding a monster like that...
For all your quibbles,
you're relying on that power, aren't ya?
Who are you?!
Oops, you got me.
In the end, you're just like me!
You!
You love violence!
You put on a cool show
with the whole revolution talk,
but in the end, you just wanted power.
Right, Rui-Rui?
Rui-Rui!
Stop!
It disguised itself as a passerby.
No doubt about it:
it's the one!
Wh-Where are you?!
See?
It hurts if you get hit.
Oh, bingo!
C'mon, Rui-Rui. Rui-Rui.
How's it feel?
How's it feel?!
Help...
Here, here, here.
Crap. If we don't do something...
Leader, do you copy?
Requesting permission to attack. Now!
Attack?
What's going on, Sugane?!
The one Jou-san fought—
that alien is causing mayhem
right in front of me!
That alien must be
the bad Gatchaman, right?!
It transformed?
Let's go, Pai-Pai!
Pai-Pai, Pai-Pai, Pai-Pai.
Pai-Pai, come on!
Shut up!
Stay quiet, Newbie!
Wait for JJ-sama's...
JJ-sama's orders!
But people are dying!
Lives will be lost, again!
I can't just stand by and watch!
Jou-san!
It's really the one?
Yes!
Leave it to me.
You watch for an opening
and get them out of there.
But...
I told you, didn't I?
That the next time I see it,
I will definitely beat the crap out of it.
Jou-san...
Amnesia Effect!
Go, Bird!
You're not getting away this time.
Here comes a Gatcha!
Don't go, Rui-Rui!
Sugane, hurry!
Don't go!
Roger!
Come back!
Quiet, monster!
Flame Feather!
Flame Feather...
Hey.
Hey!
Hey, are you guys still
doing the same old thing?
Like, "Gotta save Earth"
and "I've gotta do it"?
Do you really think you can?
Hey, are you stupid?
See, you're stupid!
Damn bastard!
Are you okay?!
You're...
Tell me... What is that thing?
JJ-sama!
It has finally transformed!
It intends to destroy
this planet! Destroy Earth!
JJ-sama, why did not you
give us a prophecy?
Do you mean to abandon this planet?!
JJ-sama, please respond!
JJ-sama!
That's...
Jou-san.
Yeah.
Jou-san's fighting.
It'll be okay, then!
Of course it won't be okay!
Don't be ridiculous!
Pai-Pai, if you're this scared,
that bad Gatchaman
must be really, really strong.
That's right.
Even all of us together
can't take it down.
So, we're going to give up?
I don't know!
I don't know what to do anymore...
Yeah.
It's scary to decide, isn't it?
But we have to decide something.
If we make a decision,
things might change.
One day,
it suddenly appeared
and drew a NOTE out of me.
Since then, I've been
able to summon the CROWDS.
"CROWDS"?
Are they the things
that were near you?
Yeah.
They are the human consciousness
made real. A tremendous power.
A tremendous power?
A power to make my ideals
turn into reality.
I provided GALAXters
I'd personally selected
with an app that
summons the CROWDS.
With them, we've solved
many incidents and accidents.
I saw them, too.
At the tunnel when
the accident happened.
It was thanks to CROWDS
that lives were saved.
But deep inside,
I was always conflicted.
Because it's not my own power.
It's a power that the alien,
Berg-Katze, had given me.
I was aware of its evil nature.
But I thought I could
take advantage of it.
No, I had to take advantage of it,
in order to update the world...
Hey, hang in there!
I'm okay.
How pathetic.
I told you we don't need heroes,
and just look at me now.
I'm no different.
I suspected you,
even though I'd seen
you save so many lives
with my own eyes...
It's pathetic.
But it's okay.
Please believe in us Gatchaman.
Jou-san will defeat it,
without a doubt.
I want to believe.
But you still do not know
its true terror...
Bastard!
Burning Hammer!
Burning Hold!
Damn it.
Jou-san!
Jou-san's...
Don't cry.
You're a man, aren't you?
Jou-san!
Utsutsu-chan!
You can't.
Why?
Please, Hajime-chan.
Listen to me.
But it'll get both Jou-san and
Senpai if we don't do something.
I'll go.
I want to help.
I can't abandon them.
Utsutsu, you've become
a wonderful person.
All right.
I'll go.
You all stay here.
Wait, OD!
OD, do not spread your wings.
That is an order.
Let's go.
All right!
That's more like it!
Pai-Pai, you're too foolish.
Amnesia Effect!
Go, Bird!
Awesome!
Get in!
Okay!
I'm going to gun it.
You couldn't transform, could you?
Coward!
Quit sneaking around
and show yourself!
Okay!
Oh my! You're so manly!
Where are you?!
Here.
Maybe I'm at my limit.
I can't possibly win.
It's impossible.
I acted tough until now,
but in the end,
I'm just a civil servant.
I wanted to make it big,
but I knew my limitations
from the beginning, really.
Oh, well.
I guess I'll just keep
trailing on in life.
Not like there's a whole
lot I can do, anyway.
I should just give up on my dreams
and resign myself to being a nobody.
Stop.
Heh, "world peace"?
I'm so naive!
Stop!
I want to die, really.
Not that I can tell anyone.
I'll defeat it!
Defeat it...
Defeat?
How can I defeat it...
I... I'm sorry!
Pai-Pai...
Gatchaman, finished!
Oh?
Just a human!
How cute when asleep!
Let's get right to it...
You perv!
What?
Hang in there...
Utsutsu-chan...
Um, hello!
I'm Hajime!
A Gatchaman!
Can you tell us your name?
I'm Katze!
Berg-Katze!
Katze-san, okay!
Nice to meet you!
Um... Why won't you
show yourself to us?
Huh? What? You can't see me?
I'm here, though!
I see.
I get it now.
Um, I have a question.
What is it?
What did you mean by
"go up in a big red blaze"?
And... oh, two questions.
What'd you mean by
"it's all you guys' fault"?
What do you think, actually?
Um, are you saying something will
happen because of us human beings?
Well, it's already happening.
That's true.
You're not bad.
You actually thought about what I said.
It's been bothering me this whole time.
Because if that's true,
that means things are really bad.
That's right.
You're good,
for a Gatchaman.
Yeah, things are
really bad on Earth!
Here's a quiz!
When does a planet have
the prettiest shine?
Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick...
I know! Around 5AM in the morning!
Buzz... Wrong!
The answer:
when it is destroyed.
Oh, is that it?
Hajime-chan.
What is it?
I like you,
so I'll give you a riddle.
Please do!
What's the sweetest, tastiest
thing every human being loves?
Think about it, okay?
Oh, one last question!
What is it?
Katze-san, are you
having fun right now?
It's super yummy!
Are you full?
Hmm, not even close.
Later!
Hang in there...
Utsutsu-chan.
I don't really know why,
but I'm super sad.
Rui...
Rui.
Where am I?
After you lost consciousness,
the man hid you here.
I see.
Where is the Gatchaman?
He seems to be gravely injured.
I see...
But I'm glad he is alive.
X, what should I do now?
I've lost the Hundred.
I now have no other
means of opposing it.
You must first heal
and protect yourself,
in order to make your
ideal world become a reality.
My ideal world...
I see.
So he got the CROWDS-chan
from Katze-san.
That might be why
JJ said "broken child."
I see.
That Rui guy...
I don't think he's suspicious.
Oh, so that's your sense
now that you've
actually talked to him.
Yeah, that's how I do things.
It is.
Actually, why are you
eating so much sweet stuff?
I'm thinking.
About what?
A riddle!
Well, aren't you happy-go-lucky.
It's pretty.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's pretty.
It's shining bright.