There was this overwhelming emotion
I had while I was barely conscious.
I didn't have any time to
sort through my feelings then.
It hadn't even been a day
since I had met Senpai.
But I...
Senpai...
I...
You can't.
You can't say it.
Please.
Why?
Why can't I say it?
Because...
There's no way I could ever love you.
You're younger than me,
you wear glasses, you're weak,
you wear glasses, you daydream,
and you're a pervert.
You always think people
are talking about you,
or I guess, it's better to
say you have a huge ego.
Stop it...
Stop imagining things!
Dear Sister,
this is your humbled brother writing you.
Your dear brother has gone crazy
and had it all blow up in his face.
I'm sorry for being so pathetic.
I apologize for being alive.
Kaito-kun.
Wake up, Kaito-kun.
If you don't wake up soon,
you're going to be late for school.
You don't even have time to eat...
Huh?
I'm staying
home today.
What's that?
Staying home?
What's wrong, Kaito-kun?
Are you not feeling well?!
Rinon!
There's nothing wrong with his body?
Then why...
Kaito-kun! Kaito-kun!
Please leave me alone.
-Kaito
Kaito-kun...
"I'm staying home today.
Please leave me alone."
Should I really leave him alone?
And why did he say that on paper
instead of just telling me?
Is it some sort of code?!
You're really interesting, you know that?
Did I get something wrong?
He's just skipping school, Ichika.
Skipping school?
Basically, for some reason,
he didn't want to go to school today.
Maybe he doesn't feel like studying,
or he didn't want to run into someone.
Didn't want... to run into someone...
Reason...?
Did something happen last night?
N-Nothing happened, but...
Something happened, didn't it?
Youth is great.
Please leave me alone.
-Kaito
Hey, Mio.
Do you remember what happened yesterday?
Um... I remember us talking about the movie,
toasting, and playing cards...
I don't really remember much after that...
Yeah, me neither...
Next thing I knew I had fallen asleep,
and my head hurt when I woke up...
I wonder what happened.
Oh, hey.
Oh, Tetsuro.
Do you remember what happened yesterday?
No, I don't really know...
Oh, yeah.
I ran into Remon-senpai on my way to school.
She said to give this to you.
Remon-senpai?
What could it be...
What is it?!
A picture?
No, no, no, no.
You can't look!
Why?
I said no!
What? What is this?
What did I do yesterday?
Kanna?
Everyone take your seats.
We'll start our morning homeroom session.
First...
Kirishima-kun isn't feeling well.
We received a call saying he'll be out.
Kai has a cold?
He seemed fine yesterday.
Make sure you all keep an eye on your health.
Anyway, I'll begin taking attendance.
Kaito-kun...
Aikawa-san.
Did he figure out what I really am?
Kaito-kun...
Senpai...
I... I...
I've figured it out.
You're not from this planet.
Th-That's...
This person's an alien! She's dangerous!
Help me, Men In Black!
No, save me!
I don't want to be a guinea pig!
I don't want to be dissected either!
This is terrible...
How should I explain what's
going on to Kaito-kun?
Maybe I should just tell him the truth.
But then, Kaito-kun will...
Senpai's probably...
What?! Kaito-kun told you he likes you?!
Yeah, out of nowhere last night...
And what did you tell him?!
No, of course.
Man, Kai should have known he was
completely out of his element.
I don't think that'd work out.
Pretty reckless of him.
Why do I keep imagining such
bad things happening?
What do you want?!
Let's go home, Mio.
Yeah.
Huh? You're not going over there?
Going where?
To Kai's place, to see how he's doing.
If he's not feeling well,
we'll just be bothering him.
He might be hungry or something.
Takatsuki-senpai is with him.
She'll take care of him.
That's true...
Ichika-senpai seems like the type
of girl who'd tend to his every need.
I'm sure she's leading him step-by-waist.
Kaito-kun, let's clean you up.
Thank you, Senpai!
I'll have to be gentle here.
N-Not there!
I'll do it from behind you...
Face me!
Mio, I just remembered I have
something to do, so I'm going now.
Huh? Kanna...
It's obvious where she's going.
You're okay with that, Tetsuro-kun?
Okay with what?
Are you really okay with that?
What do you mean?
I mean... you...
This is a good chance.
Re-Remon-senpai!
Okay, let's go.
Where are we going?
Isn't it obvious?
An eight millimeter...
Is that yours?
I thought this might happen,
so I prepared it.
We should be able to film
some realistic scenes.
People always end up getting hungry
no matter what they go through.
What's your name again?
Rinon?
You wanna eat something, too?
Probably a package...
Yes?
Kaito-kun...
Ta-Tanigawa...
You've got it all wrong.
I didn't actually say it,
and I never got an answer...
So don't laugh at me!
What are you talking about?
Your face is red.
Are you still not feeling well?
N-No, I'm fine.
I slept a while longer,
and I'm feeling better now.
I'm fine.
Really?
Sorry.
I shouldn't lie, huh?
I just kind of skipped school today.
Some stuff came up.
That's good.
Huh?
I'm glad you're well.
Sorry for making you worry.
You don't have to apologize.
I feel better now.
You came to check in on me, right?
Thanks.
We don't have to stand here, come in.
I see how it is.
You told me you liked me yesterday
and now, you already brought
another girl into your room.
Kaito-kun, you're such a playboy.
You take anything you can, don't you?
We can't talk here!
Huh? Why?
Uh...
How about we go somewhere?
What's wrong?
I want to go out!
R-Right...
Okay, I guess.
I'm gonna get dressed, so hang on a second.
Okay.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Where are we going?
How 'bout Karuizawa?
Haven't been there in a while.
We'll scope out some places to film.
Sure.
What? They're leaving?
Kirishima-kun wasn't sick?
This will work to our advantage.
Let's go, Snake.
Who's that?
Maybe I should just go somewhere else
instead of back to the house...
But Onee-chan-san told me to
take care of Kaito-kun...
Kaito-kun and Tanigawa-san...
Why...
They can't be!
Senpai's not an Earthling; she's an alien!
Save me, Men In Black!
Rinon! Can you hear me, Rinon?!
Jump me with the linkage!
Why won't you answer me?!
Episode 3
Senpai Says...
God!
Th-There's a lot of people here.
That's 'cause it's a Saturday in July.
Where are we going to look?
I haven't really thought about it.
I was just gonna walk around.
Then let's just walk around.
It's like they're on a date.
Yeah.
But it's hard to film with
so many people around.
What's that?
Of course I'd have something like this.
Of course?
That's right.
The sparkle of youth lasts but a moment.
You need to put a lot of
work into recording that.
Really?
Hm? What's up?
Uh... I...
I'm kind of thirsty,
so I'm going to buy some juice.
I'll go with you.
Remon-senpai, you want some?
Please.
Hm...
Where did they go?
Thank you.
Here you go.
Sorry for having you come with me.
It's fine. I was thirsty, too.
Yeah...
That's really good.
I should have gotten one in large.
Why did Kirishima-kun not come to school?
Well, that's obvious.
Takatsuki-senpai?
Well, something happened,
since it pushed him into staying home.
But this'll be a chance for Kanna.
It'll come back to bite you.
Huh?
If you mess with someone else's love life.
Mess with?
I'm trying to help them out.
You're messing with them.
You're going to end up biting yourself.
It'll... probably hurt.
Thanks for worrying about me.
But you're thinking about it too much.
Kanna's just a friend I've
had since I was little.
Nothing more.
This view here is pretty good.
Did you find a place that looks good?
Guess so.
That's good.
Thanks, Tanigawa.
For what?
You didn't ask why I skipped school.
I am curious.
I'm curious, but...
If you don't want to tell me, that's fine.
Yeah.
It has to do with Senpai.
It's not like anything
really happened, though...
Nothing really happened, after all.
You have to think about
a lot of things when you end up living with
someone else, especially when it's a girl.
Takatsuki-senpai is really pretty.
She's got a nice body, too.
But she's older than me,
and a foreigner.
There are some things that just don't fit.
I started thinking about that...
You're pretty nice.
It's not that.
It's not...
What am I even talking about?
Ka—
What is it?
Huh? Where's Remon-senpai?
What are you doing?
What...
Remon-senpai?
How careless of me.
I was so focused on trying to bring
out the beauty of the
scene, I forgot to hide.
What... are you... filming?!
A girl in the height of her
youth, going through puberty,
clumsily attempting to confess her lov—
Don't talk nonsense!
You are filming without permission!
That's a crime, you know?!
What was up with that picture
this morning, anyway?!
You snuck a picture of me in that pose...
What pose?
D-Don't worry about it!
Ah! She ran away!
Wait, Senpai!
Senpai!
What was that about?
Where did she go?
Isn't that...
Huh?
We were looking for you.
Oh, thanks.
The ice melted...
Totally your fault.
Kanna.
Why are you two here, too?!
W-We...
Remon-senpai told us to help her out, and...
You wanted to come.
No, Remon-senpai...
You've got it all wrong, Kanna. We...
You were watching me this whole time...
God! You guys suck!
That voice was...
Where did Tanigawa go?
Oh, sor—
S-Senpai?
Kaito-kun?
Why are you...
I... uh...
I wanted to talk to you.
And, uh...
Kaito-kun?
Huh?
W-Wait!
I don't wanna!
Why are you running away?!
Why are you chasing after me?!
I have a reason!
I have a reason, too!
Where did Kai go?
Maybe he went home...
Unfortunately for you, Tanigawa-san.
What do you mean by that?
What are you laughing at?! God!
Why did you chase me so far?
What reason do you have?
What you tried to say to me yesterday...
It was about me, right?
Y-Yeah...
Please don't say anything...
If people find out... there'll be trouble.
It'll be bad.
Bad?
It would, wouldn't it?
Well, it depends, but I guess it could.
See? I told you!
Then I wouldn't be able to
stay at your house anymore...
And that place I...
You wouldn't really have to leave...
It might get a little awkward, though...
Sorry, I didn't think I'd end
up making you so uncomfortable.
Just keep this locked up inside of you.
Don't tell anyone.
Huh?
I wouldn't tell anyone!
Really?
I mean, it's embarrassing, isn't it?
Embarrassing?
Of course it is.
It's that embarrassing?
I was rejected!
By who?
Huh?
Question.
What did you think I was going to say?
The... secret I can't tell anyone.
You have something like that?
Question.
What were you going to say yesterday?
I can't say it.
Why?
What's the secret you can't tell anyone?
That's not fair.
Answer my quest—
If you tell me, I'll tell you.
Do you honestly not know?
Really?
I...
Oh yeah, I didn't eat anything today.
We didn't bring up what
happened yesterday again,
and just made small talk instead.
We talked about our hobbies,
and our favorite foods.
I realized that we're not acquainted
enough to talk about more than that.
But somehow, it lightened the mood.
Don't just start filming me.
It's fine.
I'm going to be filming you a lot, anyway.
That's true, but...
Okay, please look this way.
Sheesh...
I have a question,
not regarding what happened yesterday.
What is it?
Who did you get rejected by?
Uh...
Who was it?
I was lying.
I wasn't rejected by anyone.
Really?
Really.
Then is there someone you like?
I...
I know! It's Tanigawa-san, isn't it?
You were with her today—
Nope.
Then, Kitahara-san?
Then...
Is it me?
Just... kidding?
Huh?
Huh?!
Episode 4
Senpai was Amazing.
Remon-senpai, Guy A told Girl B he likes her!
Female A told Male B?
This'll be a problem for Girl C!
I don't know who we're
talking about anymore...