I'm Gouda Takeo, a first-year in high school.
It's summer.
The skies are blue.
The sun is huge.
The trees and bugs are all doing great.
Oh.
Look, Takeo-kun.
Dandelions...
Yamato...
They're clovers.
Takeo-kun, you look like a prince.
I love you.
My Mountain
Yamato,
I'll stay with you today, no matter what happens.
Oh, I told you it's all good.
It was a great birthday.
I have no regrets.
But that makes me happy.
Yamato and I are having a picnic,
as a do-over of her birthday.
ha ha ha
Yamato, looks like your backpack's too heavy.
Here, let me carry it.
Thanks.
What's inside?
Uh, like bento boxes and a water bottle and stuff.
This is all from bento boxes?
Well, there are snacks, hand towels,
a picnic blanket,
and trash bags.
So much... It must've been tough to carry.
I wonder if I made too much.
I got ahead of myself.
I wonder if you can finish everything, Takeo-kun.
Oh, great!
Yamato...
That pin looks great on you.
2km to Summit
Turn right here, right?
Yeah.
I have to say, it's a really nice day.
Sorry, Yamato!
Are you tired?
Do you want to take a small break?
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
I'm totally fine.
I'm stronger than I look.
Sorry I'm slow, though.
Isn't this more of a hike than a picnic?
Didn't ask Sunakawa this time
I might have made a mistake.
Oh, sorry.
I was having so much fun, I started
humming without realizing it.
I'm so embarrassed!
Yamato...
I love you!
We're here.
This feels great!
I bet bentos taste great
at the top of a mountain!
Yeah.
It gets hot when you walk...
Oh!
The pin you gave me!
No!
Yamato...
Yamato's bentos!
The crown of flowers!
Takeo-kun, are you okay?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I saved the bentos, too.
But I don't think we can get
back up there by ourselves.
Where are we?
We have to get help.
No Signal
Takeo-kun, we don't have a signal...
What?
Missing After Going on a Picnic
Meanwhile, Yamato's Friends
Hey, where's Rinko today?
She's on a picnic with Takeo-kun.
Oh, a picnic?
That sounds like them.
It's nice to have a boyfriend.
How long have they been dating? Two months?
Sunakawa-kun was hot,
but I bet he's not an option.
We could barely talk to him.
Yeah.
Rinko's boyfriend isn't bad, either.
He's, like, not hot, but...
Manly
Manly, right?
Oh, right. Manly.
Not hot, but...
Seems Rinko thinks he's hotter
than Sunakawa-kun, though.
Yeah.
Yeah, totally.
Meanwhile, at the Gouda household
Honey, how are you feeling?
Hmm? I'm fine.
I see.
Honey, where'd Takeo run off to?
Now that you mention it, I haven't seen him.
Hey, you're in the way.
Isn't he with Makoto-kun?
I'm sure he'll come home soon.
I see.
Meanwhile, Sunakawa
Book 1...
Book 2...
There aren't any signs of anyone
having passed through here.
Takeo-kun, I'm sorry.
It's my fault...
Don't worry.
We'll get through this.
Wait here.
I'll try looking around from above.
Huh? Above?
Yep.
Be careful, Takeo-kun!
If I'd grabbed on to a tree or something,
we wouldn't have fallen.
But no use crying over spilled milk.
Right now, what I should do
is to get Yamato home safe and sound.
Takeo-kun...
It's okay, Yamato.
I'll get you home.
Huh?
I could hear cars in the distance.
There's a road over there.
Huh?
You're amazing, Takeo-kun!
But it's far away.
Reaching the city might take till tomorrow.
Huh?
Then... We'd have to spend the
whole night by ourselves...
Right.
The whole night by ourselves
She must be worried.
Don't worry.
Let me handle this.
First, we have to head south.
That's south?
Just follow me, Yamato.
You don't have to rush.
Let's just make progress while the sun's still up.
Okay.
Are you okay?
What?
We might get separated.
If you want, you can hang on to my shirt.
Okay.
Takeo-kun, do you want to eat the bentos?
Oh, thanks, Yamato!
Eat as much as you want.
All right!
Digging in.
Delicious.
Really?
I'm glad.
I'm not that good at normal cooking.
Food tastes great outdoors.
Yeah, sure does.
Thanks for the food.
Oh, was that enough?
Let's leave half for the night.
All right!
Let's keep going until night falls.
O-Okay.
Night...
Yamato must be worried.
I want to put her at ease.
We can't really see where we're going anymore...
We'll have to camp here for the night.
Huh?
Sleep here, Yamato.
Camp...
Takeo-kun and me, just the two of us...
Don't worry.
I'll be right by your side.
Yamato...
Mosquito.
I won't let them bite Yamato!
Mosquito
Hand
Night
Yamato, is your cell still not getting a signal?
Huh?
Oh, yeah.
No Signal
It still says no signal.
I see.
Everyone must be worried.
I'm sorry.
And if you set your screen to that,
you'll find a boyfriend.
For real?
Who could this be?
Hello?
Oh, Rinko's mom!
Hello? Good evening.
Yes...
What?
Rinko hasn't come home?!
Huh?
Oh, you want to know if she's with us?
Not Back From a Date
Not Back From a Date = Overnight Stay
Sh-She is!
Rinko's with me...
We have other friends with us, too.
The Lies Borne of Friendship
Huh?
You want to talk to her now?
Um, but she's taking a bath.
Yes...
Please don't worry.
Yes.
Right.
Yes, we're all going to stay over.
Yes.
Okay, good night.
Hey...
Calling Rinko!
Calling now!
Telling her we gave her an alibi...
You're being redirected to voicemail.
What?
I can't get through to her cell!
What's going on?!
I'll text her.
Where'd they go?
Maybe Sunakawa-kun'd know.
Anyone have his number?
We have no choice.
Kurihara
Nanako-chan?
What is it?
I appreciate your calling me
during the weekend.
I've got nothing going on tomorrow—
Hey, do you know where Rinko and her
boyfriend went after their picnic?
Huh? A picnic?
What's going on?
Nothing really.
Later.
Meanwhile, at the Goudas
Honey, how are you feeling—
I'm fine.
Takeo's still not back...
Don't worry.
He'll be back eventually.
I see.
Oh, dinner.
I'll make him eat it for breakfast.
I'll put plastic wrap on it.
Meanwhile, Sunakawa
Book 3...
Thanks for the food.
At night, it's pitch dark in the mountains.
That's true.
T-Takeo-kun, um...
Can we hold hands?
Sure!
She must be worried...
Is something coming at us?!
What was that, Takeo-kun?
A bear?
Don't worry, it was just a boar.
Huh? A boa—
Don't worry.
I'm right here.
T-Takeo-kun...
Yamato sounds worried.
Don't worry.
I'll fight off anything, even a bear.
I'll protect you.
Oh.
Huh?
The Moon's out...
Oh, you're right.
If it's this bright,
Yamato won't be as worried anymore.
Thanks, Moon.
You must be tired from walking all day.
Let's lie down.
Huh?
There.
We're lying next to each other!
Yamato...
Huh?
Look at the sky.
The stars are beautiful.
Wow.
You're right.
You can see a lot because it's really dark.
Yeah.
It's like being at the planetarium.
I'm a happy man.
Are you all right?
Huh?
Are you worried?
I'm fine.
You always ask if I'm all right,
but I am.
Okay.
Yeah.
That's good to hear.
Besides, I...
I wouldn't mind if we had to stay out
here for the rest of our lives.
I'd still be happy.
T-Takeo-kun?
I'm seeing Takeo-kun asleep!
Sorry, Takeo-kun.
You're all worn out because of me.
And here I am with my head in the clouds.
I like you a lot, Takeo-kun.
I love you.
Good night.
Scratch Scratch Scratch
Yamato!
Is she okay?!
I'm seeing her asleep...
Good morning, Takeo-kun.
I love her.
Oh.
Takeo-kun...
Look at all the critters around you.
Huh?
I can see why.
When you're around Takeo-kun, you feel safer.
You do?
Yeah.
Right?
I see.
That's good to hear.
The road!
Yay!
Are you hurt, Yamato?
No, I'm fine.
Oh, I'm itchy.
What?!
I couldn't protect her from everything!
Oh, you've got a lot of bites!
I've always been popular with mosquitoes.
Oh, I see.
Well, I guess I managed to attract one,
so I saved you from one bite, at least.
Yay.
I'm glad.
Yamato...
I love you.
Oh, right.
I should call home.
New Message from Nanako
Huh?
I have a text from Nanako.
Rinko!
To: Yamato Rinko
Subject: Rinko~~!!!!
I smoothed things over with your fam.
Make sure you come over tomorrow
and tell us everything.
We'll all be here waiting.
Guess I'll go to Nanako's place.
Okay, tell her hi for me.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Since we've spent so much time together,
leaving you feels kind of lonely.
See you, Takeo-kun.
Yamato, I feel the same way.
Rinko?
Incoming Call
Kurihara
Damn.
Hello?
Oh, I couldn't get what you told me
yesterday out of my mind.
Did something happen between
Takeo and Rinko-chan?
Well, you could say that...
Oh, here's Rinko!
What? Tell me!
We even pulled an all-nighter waiting for her!
So, how was it?
Huh?
Well... I thought I'd die.
Fun Last Night
Oh, my god! Perv!
Huh? What?
Is it that sensitive?
Don't worry, I'm—
So, details.
Yeah, I was so nervous,
I thought my heart would burst...
It was my first time, too.
We were outside the whole time.
What? Outside?
But Takeo-kun made me feel safe.
A boar showed up, too,
but I slept just fine.
What?
Wait, you're all muddy, Rinko.
Did something happen for real?
Incoming Call
Kurihara
We kind of got lost in the mountains.
Huh?
Gouda!!
I'm back!
Mom, how are you feeling?
Welcome back.
I'm fine.
Where were you?
The mountains.
Oh, okay. Mountains, huh.
Were you worried?
Not really.
Good, I'm glad to hear that.
Received Message
Yamato Rinko
Subject: Glad We're OK
I'm glad we got back safely.
You had to work really hard.
I'm sorry my head was in the clouds.
I was excited and nervous that I got
to spend a lot of time with you,
but I had a lot of fun.
Thank you, Takeo-kun.
Suna!
...was still sleeping.
Teach me about emoticons.
What?
I can't express my feelings for Yamato in words.
Huh... What kind of feelings would they be?
Like...
Bam!
Whomp!
Whoosh!
Dazzle!
Oh, okay.
Wham, shazam, kabloom, and fwoosh!
Blam!
Takeo, I don't think emoticons will help you there.
Wham!
Whoosh!
Dazzle!
Kabloom!
Dun dun dun!
Received Message
From: Takeo-kun
To: Yamato Rinko
Subject: RE: Glad We're OK
Me, too.
I love you so much, Yamato.
My Ocean
Next time: My Ocean.