All right, homeroom's over!
Okay, guys, give it your all today!
Okay!
Hey, but that was fast. How long has it
been since we became second-years?
We're already so used to it
now, aren't we?
But I'm so glad that we all
got to be in the same class.
And we have Ms. Kyoko again.
Right. Especially for you.
The day they announced what class we'd be in,
this one was so happy she was in tears.
Ruri!
You really are a sweetheart, Onodera!
Isn't it great that we even
have the same seats?
What's so great about that?
Really, Ruri!
Oh, I get it!
Because you're sitting near me, Ruri!
I knew it, you couldn't bear
to be separated from me–
Could you like, shut up for a second?
If only they'd assigned you
alone to another class,
we'd have nothing to complain about.
Seishiro, as usual, you're being perverse.
I wish that Kirisaki had been
assigned to another class, too.
Why don't you go?
The way I see it,
there are even more hot ladies
in this class, so I'm satisfied!
Why, you...
June 3, On Duty: Raku Ichijo, Ruri Miyamoto
Hey, who's on duty today?
There are some handouts leftover!
Who was it today?
Totally forgot about it.
Yeah.
Anyway, isn't there anything you can
do about that cohort of yours?
He's altogether too lacking in scruples.
He's been like that as long as
I can remember, so...
It must be hard on you, too.
Well, although whoever that moron's
crushing on should be pitied as well.
Wait...
Do you know who it is?
Who that guy has a crush on?
What are you talking about?
"Support"
Hey, it isn't fair for you to know
who I like and not vice-versa.
Hey, so who is it? This girl that you like?
All right, time for a quiz!
Who is the girl that I like?
Well, how should I know?
Wait. Could it be...?
You said you got two
Valentine's chocolates.
Could it be one of them?
Bingo! Bingo! Right on the money!
For real? So I nailed it just like that?
Yeah, but which is the right answer?
Well, I'd hate to give either one up.
One is a pure, cool beauty,
while the other is a perky, active
beauty with dyed blond hair, so...
Then is it Tanaka from Class D,
the girl you sometimes talk to?
Bingo! Bingo! Right on the money!
Tanaka-cchi's a fine gal, too.
So broad-minded and all...
Jeez. You're not even gonna
give me a straight answer.
No, no, I'm dead serious, you know.
It's just that my love and respect
for women is far too overpowering!
As a male high school student,
that's something to be proud of!
You keep getting clobbered because
you go around spewing stuff like that.
Is there some reason
why you can't tell me?
No, it's not like that, really.
But just like you have your
own way of conducting romance,
I, too, have my own way. That's all.
I think you'll be fine carrying on
like you always have.
I mean, it's so entertaining
for those of us observing.
Hey, you're making fun
of me, aren't you?
And besides, in my case,
my target is an unattainable
flower, way beyond my reach.
Whoops! Was that too big a hint?
Well, never mind about me!
Good luck to you in your endeavors!
Hey, wait! Hey, we're
not done talking yet!
Hello, Seishiro!
Would you be so kind as to
give me an American-style hug?
Seriously. Is he like that year-round?
Hey, Tsugumi.
What's up?
Unattainable flower, huh?
Wh-What is it?
Don't stare at me like that!
Listen, has anyone ever said
you were like a flower?
What kind of drivel
is that, all of a sudden?
Listen, what would you do
if you fell in love with someone?
Hey... Hey, hold up!
What the hell are you talking about?!
For example, if he were
someone unattainable...
Someone you could never hope would
love you back, what would you do?
Hey, my bad!
Come to think of it, you haven't
experienced first love yet, right?
Sorry to ask such an awkward question.
I'd probably hide it...
I'd never tell a soul how I felt,
and never tell him either...
and I would go on hiding it until
the day that romance ended.
W-Well, but I have no experience
in any of that, so I have no idea!
Needless to say!
Hmm, is that right?
But that sounded like the opinion of
a grownup with tons of experience.
You girls really are incredible.
I think I underestimated you.
Did you?
Well, not that it makes me
happy to hear praise from you!
But Tsugumi, if you really wanted to,
I think you could get
any guy that you wanted.
What do you know about it, huh?!
What? Why?
So it's not Tsugumi, huh?
Still, just remembering it
makes my blood boil!
He always, always has that
contemptuous attitude.
Thoughtless jerks like him
annoy me more than anything.
Come to think of it,
there's something he's never
even told his best friend, Ichijo...
Hey, there's someone I'm in love with!
I wonder why he would tell me?
Staff Room
Here you go! Thanks for waiting!
I've come to deliver
the materials you requested!
Thanks, Maiko.
Hey, sorry to make you help me out.
No, no, since it's a request
from the one and only Kyoko!
But in return, may I ask you to add
five points to that English test?
I'm counting on you.
I don't recall ever entering
such a secret contract with you.
I think I'll give you
these leftover cookies.
I thank you for your generosity!
What else did you
want me to fetch for you?
Oh, no, I can take care of...
Maiko, why don't I give you a heads-up?
Yes?
See... I'm getting
married next month.
I'm quitting to get married.
I'll be leaving after this month.
Whoa! If that isn't
the most splendid news!
Congratulations, Kyoko!
Awww, hey, you're
embarrassing me! Thanks!
Really, this makes me happy!
Our very own Kyoko, somehow snagging
a husband just before she hits thirty!
I certainly can't help
breathing a sigh of relief...
Shut up, you idiot! Lay off about that!
Please invite me to
your wedding, all right?
Because I want to catch your bouquet!
You'd better not mess with grownups.
All right, be safe on your way home.
Right...
You know what? You're the only
mature one in the bunch.
Don't forget to enjoy your youth!
Uh... today I have an important
announcement to make.
I'm getting married, so I'll be
quitting after this month.
Hey, so you have a boyfriend, Kyoko!
This month? But it's almost up already!
Hey, when are you getting married?
What's your husband like?
Wow! Ms. Kyoko's getting married!
That was a huge
announcement, for sure.
So wonderful! But I think
we're going to miss her...
Are we all gonna get
married, too, someday?
I don't know, but you're
probably set anyway, right?
You could probably make
a great home with Onodera.
Why are you just taking
something like that for granted?
Seriously, this is totally unfair, after all!
Why don't you just give it up?
Who you're crushing on?
I'll tell you, if you can guess, Raku.
All right, is it Ms. Kyoko?
You guys were tight, and you'll
miss her when she's gone, won't you?
Bingo, bingo! Right on the money!
Kyoko's a babe, and everybody loves her,
and we're all gonna miss her!
That's unusual.
You just lied, didn't you?
What are you talking about, Raku?
It only happens once
in a blue moon, but I can tell.
Since way back when... whenever
something happened to you...
Not that I can always tell, but...
Just once in a while, there are
times when I can tell...
"Hey, this guy is lying
right now," you know?
When we were in sixth grade,
and your mom was in the hospital,
you always had the same
look on your face.
So terrifying...
These childhood friends...
Seriously?
Seriously. I'm dead serious.
Since when?
Right after we started high school.
It was like love at first sight.
I had no idea...
You aren't going to
tell her how you feel?
Well, of course I'm not.
She's getting married, you know?
It would only put her on the spot
if I confessed to her now.
Making sure I have no regrets...
that would just be
self-serving, nothing more.
I know, but...
It's all right, Raku.
I mean, this is a great
memory in itself, right?
I've decided to take this unrequited love,
and quietly put it away in a corner of my
heart as a bittersweet page of my youth.
It's unfortunate, but I'm fine with that.
I see.
He has a point. It wouldn't do
any good to confess now, right?
Wouldn't do... any good, right?
Is that really true?
If I were Shu,
and one day I had to say goodbye to someone
I loved without even telling her how I felt...
Wouldn't I have any regrets?
If I...
If I were never going to
see Onodera again,
if it were me, I'd want to
tell her how I felt... I think...
I know.
Let's say Onodera was getting
married to someone else–
Although just imagining that is like
inflicting horrible damage on my soul...
But...
Yeah, I see it.
If Onodera was really in love with
that person, and happy with him,
I wouldn't want to get in her way.
Confess my love...
True, I don't think I'd do it. But...
What's this? How unusual.
For you to consult me about something.
Sorry, all of a sudden.
Remember how I asked you yesterday,
"What if you fell in love
with someone unattainable?"
What? That topic again?
So anyway,
If that person were to suddenly
say he was getting married,
what would you do then?
Do you think you'd take one last
chance to tell him how you felt?
Married?
I was wondering about this yesterday,
too, but who are you talking about?
Don't tell me Young
Mistress is getting married?!
With somebody other than you?!
No, no, no!
This is just an example, okay?
So? What would you do?
What would I do?
I don't think I'd tell him
about my feelings.
Since he'd be getting married,
it would only cause him trouble.
So you do feel that way, huh?
But... Would you really
be okay with that?
Could you really live with that?
Most likely...
It's not a matter of being
able to live with it or not.
I believe it can't be helped.
If there's nothing else you can do,
then there's nothing else you can do.
How can you sit there and be so
realistic when you have no experience?
You amaze me.
Huh? No... I'm not really!
I'm just telling you
what I think I would do.
But...
just as I thought...
That's how you see it.
Are you really getting
married, Ms. Kyoko?
Lucky you, getting married!
Would it really be wrong to tell her
at a time like this how he feels?
This is just so out of the blue!
I'm so envious!
Hey, Ms. Kyoko,
what kind of person is he?
Is he hot?
He's just an ordinary guy.
Well, when I'm with him,
I guess it sets my mind at ease.
Whaaat? He's ordinary?
That's so boring!
Come on, can't you swoon a little?
Hey, let's throw Kyoko a farewell party!
Good idea! Let's do it!
Let's make it one to remember!
But...
I...
It's tomorrow, huh?
Ms. Kyoko's last day.
Yeah, it is.
You know how you're always
rooting for my romance to work out?
Well, although a lot of things you do
can't really be called supportive.
Now, now...
So now I'm gonna support you, too.
If you're gonna send Ms. Kyoko off
without saying anything to her,
then I'll support your decision
not to say anything.
That's about all I can do.
So after Ms. Kyoko's gone, at least
let me buy you dinner, just once.
Hey, thanks, Raku.
The next day...
Ms. Kyoko's last day at our school.
Come back here, Raku Ichijo!
Tsugumi?
I'm only gonna say this
once! Listen up!
Yesterday, you asked me, right?
If I ever fell in love with someone,
and he was going to
marry someone else,
would I tell him how I felt or not...
And if I decided not to tell him,
could I live with that?
Tsugumi...
Why you would ask me such a thing, what it is
that's eating away at you, I have no clue.
I have no clue, but...
Yesterday, I believe my answer was
misleading, so I'm going to correct myself.
Because as someone you've
consulted, I want to be responsible.
I told you, didn't I?
That it wasn't a matter of
being able to live with it or not?
However...
I believe it's just that you have
no choice but to live with it,
and it doesn't mean
you want to live with it.
You probably wouldn't
be able to live with it.
I don't know much about these things,
but this emotion called love...
That must be how it works.
W-Well, not that I have
any clue about such emotions!
Since I've never fallen in love
with anyone yet...
Thanks, Tsugumi.
Huh? Was that Darling?
What were you two talking about?
Just... about a theoretical romance.
Shu...
I...
On second thought, I...
Goodbye!
Bye, guys!
Yo, Raku! What's going on?
Pretty unusual. Are you ditching, too?
You look like you're hurting.
Do I?
Yeah.
I do, huh?
Shu... I'm gonna say something just
a little bit uncalled for now, okay?
I might be just as clueless
as you always say I am.
I have no idea what other people are
feeling unless they tell me.
I think you're doing
the right thing, okay?
I think it's the considerate,
mature call to make.
But still.
I also think that you should do
what it is that you really want to do.
I'm going to support you.
If you're not gonna do anything,
I'll support you for not doing anything.
And if necessary...
I'll also give you a push.
What would you be
giving me a push for, Raku?
I've just had my heart broken
in spectacular fashion.
What can I do when
the romance is long over?
It's all right.
I don't have a single regret.
Well, that lie...
I don't think it even
has to be me to spot it.
You know what? You're the only
mature one in the bunch.
Don't forget to enjoy your youth!
Raku...
Could you give my back
one hell of a push?
She's at the taxi stand
in front of the crosswalk!
Go!
I...
...don't know if that was
the right thing to do.
But...
Seriously, that Four Eyes...
Where did he go, ditching his duties?
Hey, Maiko! This is your job...
Was that... Maiko?
Thank you!
Right!
Teacher!
Maiko?
Hey, you are enjoying your youth.
You're gonna make
an awesome man someday.
Take care, Maiko!
Did I meddle too much?
No.
Hey, Raku...
You promised me.
Treat me to some octopus balls!
Did I do the right thing, I wonder?
Hey, thanks, Raku.
I got it out of my system.
Even though it wasn't my style, I guess
it's not half bad, this kind of thing.
You think so?
So? What are you gonna do, Raku?
About what?
Don't tell me you're not gonna
do a thing about Onodera
after you just made me
confess my feelings?
No... that's actually, uh...
I know where you're coming from,
but it's really complicated, see?
I was only kidding. I think it's all good!
For you to go at your own pace.
But no regrets, okay?
If you're ever on the verge of
making a choice that you'll regret,
then I'll be the one to kick your butt!
Right...
Shu, you really are amazing.
Since I think if you told me
to confess to Onodera,
I'd have a really hard time...
Ichijo?
Where were you today?
You vanished all of a sudden,
and I was so worried!
My bad, something came up...
But...
Hey, listen, Onodera.
Sorry to spring this on you
all of a sudden...
Want to go home with me today?
B-But why? Is something wrong?
Why?
No... I just kind of feel like it, I guess...
Sure, fine.
Someday, I will, too...