It's been a long time.
Londark!
What are you doing here, Londark?
Don't make that scary face.
There's no need for us to fight now...
As long as you do not interfere.
Do you know what you're doing?
I do.
I'm doing a job and getting paid,
guiding and protecting this iron train.
And what of the result?
Result?
There's nothing about that in my manual.
Inferno Strike!
Of course there isn't.
I never received a manual for this world.
Birthday Song
Birthday Song.
You believe there's a possibility of war
with People of the Land, Shiroe?
I think the Round Table should
consider the possibility.
We're in a world where there's
a possibility of war breaking out.
That's what Shiroe was trying to say then.
How will each individual
who lives in this world confront that possibility?
That was his message.
Londark...
Are you trying to spread war and
chaos throughout the world?
Not at all.
The ones who might be thinking of doing that
are the People of the Land
who gave me this quest!
And you're helping them!
So,
what of it?
Many People of the Land will be lost!
That's what they want.
They fight because they want to.
Frost—
We can stop it before it starts!
I've never heard about a quest like that!
You can't do anything if it isn't a quest, Londark?
Shut up, hypocrite.
I wasn't... I wasn't invited to this world.
I wasn't invited to this world.
I'm useless.
Did you pick from a dialogue box that said,
"Will you go to another world? Y/N"?
I didn't!
I was forced to come here, and nobody asked me.
You were invited, right?
That's why you're so relaxed!
No!
None of us were invited.
This world tried to do something
to me that I didn't want,
regardless of my feelings.
So I'm going to do what I want to it.
Am I wrong,
swashbuckler?
Nyanta /Swashbuckler, Lv. 92
What's wrong?
Are we done already?
What Londark says is true.
He was brought here with no say-so,
and he can't go back, even if he wants to.
Adventurers are both victims and outsiders.
It's natural for them to feel
anger at this unreasonable world.
Status: Combat
Stroganoff /Adventurer
Lycopin /Adventurer
Smash /Adventurer
It's possible to eliminate Londark
and the other adventurers
with this problem by force.
But...
But what will that solve?
Turbulence!
Hey...
If there's anything else I can do, tell me.
Are you saying I should just let
this world screw with me?!
Londark... That's true for everyone.
It's true for all children.
People... At least, all children
are born into a world that seems
unreasonable and crazy to them.
Shut up!
No one is asked at birth if they
agree to come into the world.
Everyone is born that way.
Nyanta /Swashbuckler, Lv. 92
In this world... In our old world... In any world!
Is that all you can do?
You can lecture me, but in the end,
you can't get rid of me.
There is no death here...
So kill me if you can.
End me, please!
Swash—
Is this what you wanted, Londark?
Isn't it wonderful being an adventurer?
You can kill as much as you want,
and die as much as you want.
Why?
Why did you kill him?
I just shut him up for a while.
Like he said, death isn't the end.
It's like moving into the next room, right?
To an adventurer, that's what death is.
No, it's not!
What makes you say that?
Oh, excuse me.
I am General of the Punitive
Expedition, Mizufa Trudy.
Mizufa Trudy
Race/ Human
Warlord, Lv. 68
Plant Hwyaden
I'm the one in charge on the ground.
Are you the one who hired Londark?
Is that how the People of the Land do things?
You're still talking about that nonsense?
People of the Land? Adventurers?
It doesn't matter.
Everyone who is born into this world
uses the cards they have to kill each other!
The strong use their strength as their weapon.
The weak use their weakness as their weapon!
She's strong!
She's so strong, it's hard to believe
she's a Person of the Land!
You can't die, but you're going to talk
to me about conquest and ruling?
Why do you want war?
I'm going to burn my life down
with the alcohol called "war."
Dance, undead!
"Undead"?
It's the perfect name for you
people who can't die, right?
Shut up.
Viper's Rush!
Amazing...
Wonderful!
Almost enough to make me fall in love with you.
But your blade lacks the desire to kill!
Is that what you're proud of?
Your desire to kill?
Early Thrust!
Kazuhiko
Race/ Human
Assassin, Lv. 97
Plant Hwyaden
Kazuhiko...
Astral Hypno.
What is this?
I was just planning to interfere a little.
Dariella /Chronicler
I thought it would be easy.
No, I actually managed to fit in, didn't I?
Just the slightest sign that I cared for
them, and they all trusted me...
Only Shiro is special.
They aren't.
They're only members of the same guild.
That's what I thought.
But...
You wouldn't look weird without that smile.
Why do you say that?
Why?
Because that way, you wouldn't
look like you were lying.
You'd look better that way.
That little child had a blade hidden in his heart.
Yes.
Shiro's teachings are that boy's blade.
Shiro really is special.
Lady Nureha!
Lady Nureha, this is a war zone.
Would you please leave?
Why is this happening to this town?
Mizufa's orders?
Yes.
I see.
I agreed to Mizufa's orders because
I thought they didn't matter.
I came here because I was asked to.
But in this town...
Annihilate as many of the wyverns and
nightshade servants as you can.
Is that all right?
It is the order of the Western Councilor.
Yes, ma'am.
Shiro, I'm going to give them a little help.
It wasn't for long, but they treated me
as a fellow traveling companion...
Will you notice?
Will you think me a bother?
Or will you think I did well?
This is just a whim of mine, not a gift to them.
So hurry.
I can't wait to hear your voice...
It's been a while, Chief.
Since the Tea Party, maybe?
Move, Kazuhiko.
I need to correct something.
No.
I can't do that.
Why are you involved in this?
It's something I have to do.
Kazuhiko is trying to change Plant
Hwyaden for the better from inside.
That's what Shiroe said.
But he's lost his own goodness now.
That's how he looks to me.
You're so slow!
Operation Red Night has already begun!
That's why you adventurers
can't be this world's heroes!
Now sleep!
You won't die, anyway!
Mizufa...
You're strong.
Yeah, you're very strong.
But it's no good.
Your kindness is going to get you killed.
Your desire to save the People of the
Land is going to get them killed!
Now, what will you do?
Mizufa, it's over.
Don't be stupid...
You're just an observer!
It's an order from Nureha.
Just now, the highest-ranking order
has been given to Plant Hwyaden.
We're withdrawing.
The mission is canceled.
Kazuhiko, what is Plant Hwyaden thinking?
What are you—
Enough talk!
This is still better.
The Chief won't have to kill
any People of the Land.
Is it because you used to be my friend, Kazuhiko?
Do you think you're showing me
a fragment of friendship?
Orb of Lava!
What's wrong?
Those kids...
There's nothing I can do.
Little brothers and sisters!
Your sister isn't going to abandon you!
The first friends I made in this world are angry
at this place that only creates sadness.
A fallen country's abandoned princess,
once unable to make friends with anyone,
is crying within me!
You, whose contract was once
broken, walk with me!
Sword Princess Al Quenje!
Wow.
I can't do anything, but I'll sing.
I'm watching.
I'll tell you I'm watching you all.
To tell you that...
Songs are small things.
There isn't much they can do.
No matter how much you sing that
you want to change the world,
no matter how great an artist you are,
music alone can't bring peace to the world.
But... But I'll sing.
I know you.
I know how you feel.
Songs are prayers that are actually heard.
I understand how you feel.
When I sing, I feel the same way.
Don't give in.
Hang in there.
That's what everyone was trying to tell me.
I can't say that I'll become an artist.
But I can promise I'll love music my whole life!
Rudy longed to be an adventurer.
It didn't matter whether he could be or not.
He just wanted to fight what he saw as unreasonable.
I didn't need to worry about whether I had talent.
Rudy brought me close.
He gave me my songs.
Isuzu!
Miss Serara!
It's all right.
I searched all the buildings west
of here with Wolfie's nose.
All the People of the Land have evacuated.
Get back, mister!
Party Chat
Tohya
Minori
Isuzu
Rundel Haus Code
Serara
Roe 2
Tohya...
Shut up!
You're still going to get in my way?
This battle belongs to the Odyssey Knights!
He's still fighting.
Yeah, Tohya hasn't lost yet, either!
He's near the river.
He's close!
Don't mess up until I get there, Tohya!
I, Rundel Haus Code,
will help you!
I won't step down!
I'm not going to give up on you guys!
What does a kid like you know?
If you don't stop,
I'll rip you apart with my Onslaught!
Then do it!
But I'm not leaving!
Tohya!
This is the place where we die.
Don't block our path to hell!
Tohya...
Give me a break!
The place where you die?
A path to hell?
Miss Isuzu?
Rudy...
I want to fill this world with the
sound of a forty-third song!
I want to play the song I made for
the first time in this world!
Because...
This world...
This world I've walked through with my friends...
It isn't...
the path to hell!
The sea wind, the asphalt...
Once we're over the hill,
we can see the next town.
Our journey is just beginning.
Plucking the strings on my little lute,
I'll open up the window
and begin again today.
Even if you can't hear this song,
even if you're locked inside this tiny world,
it's okay
because I'm here.
I'll overwrite the yesterday
that hurt your heart.
I won't forget the shining rainbow I spread,
and my hopes will become musical notes.
I won't forget the shining promise I made with you.
Even my cowardly lute is different today.
The journey is over.
What were they able to do?
Were they able to save anyone?
Minori and the others still feel glum.
Roe 2 entrusts them with a letter for Shiroe.
Meanwhile, a new threat approaches Akihabara.
The Skylarks Take Flight
Next time: The Skylarks Take Flight.
I have friends to run with me.