Legend of the Big Fish
This is my fault. This is my fault.
What should I do? What should I do?
Ayumi-chan!
You can't be serious.
Captain!
Ayumi-chan!
Boss!
Captain?
Ayumi-chan, you're all right.
Huh? Misaki-san?
I'm so relieved.
All right!
Captain!
Oh, Yuki. You came back.
You protected this.
Yeah, but everything else burned.
Misaki-san, I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry we made you go alone.
It's okay.
As long as I'm alive, everything's okay!
Let's go!
You're not all right at all!
It may be broken.
What?
I tripped protecting the tackle.
But this is nothing.
The boat can't go anywhere without me.
I will drive the boat.
Captain, leave the rest to us.
Are you sure, Natsuki?
Even Yuki's fished for tuna before.
Yuki's not the same guy who
couldn't walk on deck.
Guys...
Don't worry. You saw the scroll.
The goddess fished the
dragon out of the water,
working together with her companions.
You are the heroes who
will create a new legend.
Seishunmaru is yours to use.
But Natsuki, you're the leader.
You know that sea better than anyone.
Lead everyone and fish up that
alien or whatever it is!
Yes.
Tamotsu-san, drive the
captain to a hospital.
Yeah.
Natsuki, this is a whitebait bowl.
Don't leave any whitebait.
Thanks.
Come back alive.
Of course I will.
I couldn't die without seeing
your whitebait shop.
Take care of Sakura...
and Mariko-san.
Natsuki...
Once you make it back safely,
let's all go fishing together again.
Yeah.
I can't go.
I came to fish him up.
Once we catch him, I have to go home.
Really?
Yeah. I won't come back to Earth.
This is my last fishing trip.
My good bye fishing trip.
I might not get to see any of you again.
Don't say that.
It's too sad.
But...
You can say good bye after
your last fishing trip.
Captain...
That's right. You're everyone's friend.
At least let us throw
you a good bye party.
Misaki.
It's up to you guys.
Yes.
Leave it to us.
If this is his last trip,
we'd better catch him.
Thanks, everyone.
Haru, it's okay.
We can do it.
Have faith in us.
Okay.
Stop them!
Yes, sir!
Stop!
Quiet!
Yamada, what is the meaning of this?
We are on our way to fish up JFX.
You're still going on
about that nonsense?
Our Duck fleet was destroyed
before it could even get close.
There is no way you can
subdue JFX's power!
Is there another way?
All four reinforcement ships
are under JFX's control.
We do not know when he
will fire more missiles.
Lives will be lost this time.
As the Duck agent given
responsibility of this island,
I simply wish to execute my mission.
In order to do that, I must fish up JFX.
You expect me to believe such nonsense?
You have simply been brainwashed by JF1!
I have not been brainwashed!
We need Haru's help to
resist JFX's power!
This is what I have concluded after
observing him for half a year.
This is ridiculous.
Yamada, if you truly are a Duck
agent, you must understand.
Duck Rule 11:
Duck agents who sympathize with aliens
will be stripped of
their title immediately!
Do not do anything foolish
for your own sake.
Take JF1 away!
Yes, sir!
No!
Let him go.
Let Haru go!
Yamada, as of this moment,
I strip you of your Duck membership.
I don't care.
Are you insane?
I am sane.
Even if you take my
position away from me,
I will still go with them.
I will fish up JFX.
Get Yamada!
Excuse me.
Yamada!
Seishunmaru, set sail!
Yeah!
Enoshima
Island
Emergency
Shelter
A single boat has just
left Enoshima harbor.
What could this be?
Is it an autonomous choice?
What is that boat doing?
Or is it under the control of
the unidentified creature?
What are they thinking
at a time like this?
Look! We just got sight
of the passengers!
Onii-chan!
Isn't that Ayumi-chan's boat?
They seem to be some young men...
and a man wearing a turban.
Yeah, it is.
Tapioca, you saved us. Thank you.
Koko...
I'll do my best.
Natsuki, do you really want
Yuki to fish for him?
Yuki's ready for it.
We only have one rod.
The goddess is Haru, and...
There!
Yuki's the only one who
could be his companion.
Haru, you're not thinking
anything weird again, are you?
If we can't catch him, I'll
go. I'll definitely go.
What if you fail?
It doesn't matter, Yuki.
Whether we catch him or
not, I have to leave.
Haru!
I won't let you go home!
Never!
Yuki...
Is something wrong?
No, nothing.
Natsuki, how are we going to catch him?
What do you mean, how?
Not even I've fished for aliens before.
But Natsuki, you said
an angler has to get in the habit
of always thinking about
how to catch fish.
So he's ready for anything,
no matter what comes his way.
Yeah, but only if he's really a fish.
Haru, he's a fish, right?
Yeah. You guys all saw it.
That huge hole in the
middle of the bait ball.
He's under there.
Then we'll start by getting this
in that hole and finding him.
A countdown, huh?
It's worth trying.
You're right.
Haru, do you know where he is?
Yes.
Ni-ni-ni-ni-ni-ni-ni-ni-ni!
There he is!
Over there! To the left!
Okay!
Yuki, you just have to do it.
Yeah. I'll catch him.
I want to smile when we say good bye.
It's up to you. I'll
give you instructions.
Dry!
Dad!
Sakura!
Tamotsu-san.
The typhoon is approaching.
For the sake of safety, we
must move farther away.
Gather up your belongings.
Hey, wait!
I'm not going anywhere.
My son's risking his life fishing.
I can't just leave him.
He's fishing?
Why is he fishing at a time like this?
I ask for your understanding.
With the coming typhoon, the
monster's strength is increasing.
If the military ships fire another
missile that strikes the island,
Enoshima will become a sea of fire.
I'm still staying.
I cannot allow that!
It is our responsibility
to protect Enoshima!
They do not wish for you to
put yourselves in danger.
They want to protect Enoshima.
That is their only wish.
Who?
Who is he talking about?
Fine. Let's go.
Lifting missile.
Lift up.
There he is!
No!
If we get any closer,
he'll take over our minds!
Akira!
Okay! Stopping!
It's him!
The dragon...
Yuki, he's close enough! Can you do it?
No problem!
Let's go!
Cast now!
Eno...
shima...
Bowl!
Again!
Against the wind! Cast upwind!
Got it!
Enoshima bowl!
All right.
You can do it.
Yay!
Count down from the top!
One...
Nothing.
Two...
Three...
Nothing yet.
Four...
Yes, yes, yes!
Did I hit something?
Cast!
Enoshima bowl!
One, two, three...
Bowl!
...three, four!
Damn it, why?
Bishu!
Why? I feel something,
but why won't he bite?
Think. Think!
What's wrong, Yuki?
What is it, Tapioca?
Yuki.
If you won't do it, I will.
I'll catch him.
I'll definitely catch him!
Hey...
You're going to sleep?
Natsuki, no.
He's thinking about something important.
He's one of Haru's kind.
If he's like Haru...
It's so cute.
I like this one.
Nice hair, Yuki!
Yuki?
That's it!
What happened?
Thanks.
Sure.
What are you doing?
You said I should match my lure
to whatever the fish are
eating at that time.
Yeah, but why red?
Because he's one of Haru's kind.
I love red! Yuki's hair is red!
I see.
You always put red things in your mouth.
He might like red too,
so I'm going to lure him out with this.
I see. Good idea.
On the boat, Seishunmaru, that
left Enoshima harbor
during this dangerous time,
are local students from Higashi High School...
This is becoming ridiculous.
Look!
...second year classmates,
including Duck member Akira.
What we're doing is crazy.
Prepare yourselves!
The world's eyes are on us now!
Hey, Yuki.
The world's eyes on us...
Don't be scared, Yuki.
We're just fishing.
I mean, who cares
if this is the focus of the world?
You're right.
It's a difficult position.
Do you think you can do it?
I'll get in it one try.
Do it.
Yuki, it's an underthrow.
I know.
I'll do it.
I'll get it in one try.
Let's go!
Enoshima bowl!
No good!
It's too far! It's
going to hit the ship!
All right!
One...
Amazing!
Two...
Three...
Got him!
He's strong!
Akira!
Don't worry! I'm watching!
This is an emergency
broadcast from Enoshima.
The unidentified boat that left
Enoshima harbor has just...
Look.
They got it.
They got a bite.
That's it, fish him out!
Fish him out!
Onii-chan...
Can they really catch JFX?
Yamada...
Yamada.
There is no time.
Enoshima will soon be in
the area of the typhoon.
That's your time limit.
When that time comes,
we will strike the vessels
with anti-ship missiles.
No!
Our comrades are on those ships!
I know, but it's to prevent
additional damage.
If they fire more missiles,
not only Enoshima, but
people will be harmed.
But they are still our comrades!
We will fish up JFX without
producing any human casualties!
Yamada...
Yamada. Yamada!
Yamada, where are you?
You can do it! You're almost there!
He's close!
It's no good! He's too close!
Hurry, Yuki! Haru is...
Enoshima has just entered
the area of the typhoon.
With this development...
Prepare to launch.
What are you doing?
What are your orders?
Yamada, can you hear me? Yamada!
Yamada, answer me!
Duck!
No!
The lure!
The waves are too high!
At this rate, the boat will sink!
What is that?
I can't...
I can't do it any more...
Haru, no!
Haru, what are you doing?
It's okay.
I won't bother you any more.
I will lure him...
Don't do it, Haru.
I'll lure him far away.
Don't do it, Haru!
I can't. I'm at my limit.
Everyone's in danger.
Natsumatsuri, natsumatsuri.
Hai yoisho!
Haino, haino, haino...
What's going on?
Otoko nara...
Haru, don't!
I'll catch him!
I'll catch him, so you won't go...
Good bye, Yuki.
Haru!
Continued in #12