Summer Vacation (Part Two)
Cherry Blossom
Jelly
Green Tea
Rice Cake
Polka-Dot
Jelly
Azuki bean
ice cream inside
You drew so many.
Cat Confection
Goldfish Jelly
(soda flavor)
Starry Sky
Gelatin
Japanese White-Eye
Confection
They're so beautiful and look delicious.
I know, right?
The striped jelly is cute, isn't it?
And the jelly balls
look like drops of water, right?
CRESCENT MOON
Grandpa said we could
do it again next year.
Actually, I'd like to do it for the summer festival
and New Year's holiday as well.
But I've got this mountain of homework.
HEAPING
All these ideas for sweets
are popping up in my head,
but I have a ton of homework and mandatory
school days during summer vacation!
This is actually a lot.
Yeah.
We're in the third-year,
but since a lot of things happened in class,
homeroom really fell behind.
So...
Rei, how old were you when you first
wanted to become a professional shogi player?
Well...
I think I was in fourth grade.
No.
That's not right.
That's not quite right.
At some point, I realized
this was the only path left for me.
Or rather...
This was the only thing I knew how to do.
Oh, that's right.
Hina, you love your Grandpa's shop,
so you want to help out there, right?
Yeah.
There are lots of things I want to do right now
and they're right in front of me,
but I can't touch them,
which makes me feel sad.
Or maybe it's just that I want a distraction.
From the mountain of homework,
tests, entrance exams...
People say to choose a high school, but I can't
even picture myself as a high school student.
I don't even know
if things will go well for me there.
Joining another group of people
I don't know is...
I guess I can't really explain it.
Hina, if you'd like, and if you're free
this Saturday...
Flowers, it's flowers!
Kiriyama!
It's a nice clear day, isn't it?
Hoh Hoh Hoh
Thank you very much for inviting us today.
DEEP BOW
Hello, Teacher.
Welcome.
YIKES
When I let my guard down,
the obvious misunderstanding happened!
It's okay. Please enjoy yourselves.
The theme is
"Gravity and the Energy of Water."
This is the culmination of the Shogi Science Club's
summer research project, Flume Noodles!
Wow! This is the first time I've seen one!
Look, Momo!
This is flume noodles!
I love slippery food!
MUHAAA
Actually, part of the bamboo thicket
in my yard had to be cut away
to make room for an addition to my house,
so I thought I better take advantage
and make use of it.
HA
Hey!
HEAP
I boiled the noodles!
Here's the first batch.
Oh, Mr. Hayashida, let me introduce you.
Hello. Thank you for letting us visit.
BOW...
I'm Hinata Kawamoto.
Um, and this is my little sister, Momo.
Ah, yes, hello!
GASP
I see!
- Hey Hina, I want to eat now!
- Okay.
This is the girl Kiriyama was worried about!
Sh-She really is cute!
Kiriyama!
AWW
We're going to get things flowing!
Make sure you eat your fill!
Right, Kiriyama?
Hey, Kiriyama!
JAB JAB
She's such a cute girl
that even a straight-laced guy like Kiriyama
would plunge into the atmosphere of love!
JAB JAB
I understand!
Oh my, it's so bittersweet!
What will I do with him? Sheesh!
GRIND GRIND
Mr. Hayashida, um, that hurts.
Sorry I'm late!
Cooking the tempura took a long time!
It's so hot.
DISHEVELED
SWEAT-
SOAKED
Oh, are you the teacher?
Thank you for always taking good care of Rei.
And thank you for inviting us here today.
DEEP
BOW
Oh wow, tempura?
Everyone will be so pleased.
Thank you so much.
And how beautiful!
Please, come this way!
The situation has naturally become
more complicated again!
Wait, um, Mr. Hayashida?
FROZEN
Your face looks like it's made of red clay!
There!
It looks delicious!
Oh, Mr. Hayashida. What's wrong?
Your face is the color of oxidized iron.
Maybe you have heatstroke?
All right, here we go!
Is everybody ready?
SERIOUS
Then we'll start with the kids!
DAZED
Ease up on the water!
Lower the bamboo chute too!
The child's eyes can't capture
the noodles properly!
Her eyes are swimming!
It's a struggle, eh, miss?
Instead of aiming for it,
the trick is to wait for it.
I see!
Yummy!
The tempura is yummy too!
This is fun! Yay!
Sense of
Accomplishment
YES
Okay! It's now time for the long-awaited...
BA-BAAAM
starving-man time!
SERIOUS
Here we go!
GRAB
Here.
WHOOSH
That's fast!
WHIZ
- Wait!
- I can't see it!
ZOOM
I got a pink one! I got a pink one!
PINK
Yes! Woo!
- I did it!
- For pink, you get chicken tempura.
Chicken tempura.
Green! I got a green one!
Bzzt!
Green is nothing.
What?
Please go to the end of the line.
A pink one!
I'll go get my chicken tempura!
Um, excuse me!
SWISH
NOTHING
Nothing's flowing down here!
I got another pink!
Hey, hey, let me eat too!
I'm the one who boiled all these noodles!
- Delicious!
- The chicken tempura is great!
Damn it!
Hey, let me get at least one. Just one is fine!
Let one come to me!
Mr. Hayashida, you haven't gotten anything.
Rei looks like he's having fun!
Yeah. A lot of fun.
This is nice. I didn't know
there were fun high schools like this.
Yes! Chicken tempura!
Yeah.
- I've got it, Hina.
- Maybe...
- Why don't you try to get into this school?
- I should try to get into this school.
Oh, I got one!
Are you sure it's not a green one?
Summer Vacation (Part Two)
New Year
SUMIYOSHI SHRINE
Early January of the following year.
Question 30
Using the below figure, find ∠x.
However, BA=BC,
ℓ, m are parallel.
Entrance exams are coming up.
STRETCH
HMMMM
TSUME-SHOGI
H-Hey... Um, Rei.
About this figure...
SLIDE
Is this...
Let's see here.
Oh, for this, you should draw
an additional line.
A-Around where should I draw it?
First try drawing it
in the loneliest-looking spot.
COZY
That's right. I decided my first choice
would be Komahashi Private High School,
where Rei goes.
He's been helping me study like this.
"I want to go to Hashi High."
The first time I said that to Rei...
What? Hashi High? Really, Hina?
WHAAAT
For some reason, he was extremely happy.
U-Um, I don't know if I'll get in yet.
Um, I haven't even
been going to a cram school.
The next day,
Rei came over with a "study plan."
FIX
SERIOUS
We have plenty of time.
If we start preparing now,
you'll definitely be all right!
Since then, he's been supervising my studies
several times a week after having dinner here.
I-I think I'm starting to get the hang of it.
Yeah, I think I've got it.
Right? You can only get a feel for math
by solving problems over and over.
You'll be fine if you stay calm
and solve them one at a time.
Right. I'll do my best!
Rei is a patient teacher, which makes this
easy to understand, and I'm really grateful.
ZZZ
PING
I-Is this a late-night snack I'm sensing?
PEEK
Hello. Do we have anyone here
who would like to be pampered?
GASP
Wait, could that be...
RATTLE
Yes! Yes, I want to be pampered!
Pampered?
Hup!
STEAMING
Ta-daaa!
Here you are.
SIMMER
STEAMING
Fried tofu and tempura together as toppings.
SWEET
Th-This is the Kawamoto family's
legendary "Pampered Udon"!
Melting tempura that's been
deep-fried to fluffiness...
next to sweet fried tofu
permeated with sizzling broth!
Something delicious
right next to something delicious!
MMM...
HEARTRENDING...
It makes me too happy!
Pampered Udon...
D-Delicious!
So, which do you want with the udon,
fried tofu or tempura?
I can't choose!
And so, to erase her daughter's troubles,
she came up with
the cockamamie idea of using "both."
She called it...
HEE
Pampered Udon!
Mom often made it for me as a late-night snack
when I was studying for entrance exams.
Eating that always made me really happy.
And I wanted to make it for you when it was
your turn to study for exams, Hina.
Thanks. This makes me happy.
It's so delicious!
Well, I guess you have a little longer to go.
I left the heat on for the bath,
so turn it off when you're done.
Okay, thank you. Goodnight!
When I first thought I wanted to go
to the same private high school as Rei,
it was only the feeling of "I want to go."
I didn't know if it was okay to be selfish.
When we set up a stand in the summer,
it made me think.
BLACK PEARL
TAPIOCA
RICE
FLOUR
CRESCENT MOON
Within these small sweets
that cost 250 yen apiece,
how much time, labor, and money
has gone in to them?
Starting at dawn, Grandpa stands in front of
the stove on days he cooks bean jam.
How much money is left for Grandpa
from one of those sweets?
And if I went to a private high school,
how many sweets
would Grandpa have to make?
Go to Komahashi High School.
B-But...
You girls worked really hard
with the stand this summer.
From calculating the cost to production
to sales to the end, you did a great job.
But you're worried about something.
You're thinking how much income is left
for Grandpa after making these sweets, right?
"Kids don't need to think about that stuff."
That's not how I feel.
Money is precious. That's very important.
And I'm impressed you realized that.
But Hina.
CLANG
You better not underestimate this Grandpa!
GRIN
There are people waiting for my sweets.
CRESCENT MOON
And I still have plenty of will left
to tussle with that bean jam!
You want to go because
that school would be fun.
That one reason is okay by me!
Whether or not you're enjoying your life
is what matters the most to me.
Grandpa.
But, hey, there's another thing.
Your sister and I looked into a few things.
Apparently Komahashi High School,
where the kid goes, is really tough to get into.
AUGH
Are you going to be able to get in?
Ahh, g-good question.
SHAKE
I'll do my best. I'll work hard.
I'll study hard and get into that school!
Um, Rei, I've got a question about this one.
Rei.
TSUME-SHOGI
When Rei is solving tsume-shogi problems,
he gets quiet and absorbed.
The mood was infectious,
enabling me to have incredible concentration.
It was unusually silent,
so I opened the curtain.
Outside the window...
was this year's first snow.
New Year
Next Episode Preview
Episode 43
Five more days
until the entrance exam.
Call me if you want me
to do anything.
I'll be right next to you.
Shikoku. That's so far away.
What the hell am I doing?
Mom, Grandma...
Please watch over Hina.
ILLUSTRATION:
NAO IWAMOTO
The best late-night snack
for entrance exam students is...
Udon, right?
It digests quickly
and is easy on the stomach.