You're right.
Now do you believe me?
There's no mistake.
VR-1's trajectory has changed.
This is my fault.
No! It isn't...
Yes, it is.
It's because I hacked the AFSPC
servers that the Qmay Group...
Buddies
Iridatsu, is it all true?
About you leaving your body,
and having come from the future?
Meika...
I'm all right.
I don't doubt what you said.
But...
Can you give me some time?
I need to come up with a strategy.
Punch Line
We will hereby begin the briefing
for Operation Peacemaker.
Currently, there are plenty of ICBMs
and SLBMs around the world
ICBM: Intercontinental Ballistic Missile
SLBM: Submarine-launched Ballistic Missile
on standby for immediate launch.
Approximately 3,600 of them are
armed with nuclear warheads.
We'll fire all of them at Asteroid VR-1.
Launch all 2,350!
The operation begins tomorrow at 2200 hours.
At that time, I will hijack several
military servers around the world,
and launch one missile after another.
I'll finish launching the last one at 2340 hours.
Ten minutes later, the launched
missiles will gather at one location
and destroy VR-1 in its approach.
Colonel! Why don't we launch
the missiles right now?
Operation Peacemaker
Operation Schedule
Ballistic missiles can't surpass
the first cosmic velocity,
or 7.9 kilometers per second.
In other words, they can't
escape Earth's gravity.
Therefore, in order to obliterate VR-1,
we need to allow the target
to come within firing range.
It's like shooting down a bullet
after it's come within three
centimeters of your nose.
But that's...
Don't worry. We have a chance.
But only if there are no interferences.
Nations with
nuclear armament
Total nuclear missiles
across Earth
Operation Begins                                                   Operation Ends
Police forces attack!
"Police forces attack"?
A huge number of police forces
will most likely arrive during the operation
once they get wind of the hacking.
And that, Iridatsu, is where you come in:
the hundred minutes between the
beginning and end of the operation.
You must protect Korai House at any cost.
Can you do it?
Leave it to me.
It'll be easy, as long as you, Sir,
would do me the honor of
showing me your panties!
Say what?
Well, see,
I have to be Uberfied before
the beginning of the operation.
For that, Colonel, your panties...
Why did you kick me?!
Last time, you said it's okay
because we're both girls!
Your soul is a guy's, isn't it?
In any case, that concludes the briefing.
I have one last favor I want to ask of you.
A favor?
It's New Old Year's Eve! Meikaemon
All right, let's start!
"It's Old Year's Eve! Meikaemon"
is now in session.
Yay!
Huh? Meika, we're out of fireworks.
Relax.
I've kept one for a special occasion.
A special occasion?
A bottle rocket!
I don't see one anywhere.
Over there.
Somewhere that way.
Whatever, let's just go check it out!
Wait up!
That's all you wanted?
I'm completely satisfied.
Now I can die happy.
Hey, don't even say stuff like that.
I'm kidding.
We should get going, too.
Okay, here goes.
Wh-What is this?
Just what it looks like: a combat robot.
Kaku-Maker
I call it the Kaku-Maker!
Uh, where's the bottle rocket?
There!
See it up there?
Anyway, Narugino, get on.
Isn't this...
No way, no way! I can't pilot this thing!
You can't, huh?
Oh, well, that's okay, then.
We'll do it another way.
Another way?
What, you can control it remotely?
For simple motions like this, yeah.
Okay, I'm launching the fireworks now.
Are you ready?
Here we go!
Three, two, one!
For a successful operation!
Wait a second!
Operation?
She's talking about Operation Peacemaker.
Ito...
Meika, you should probably make
the walls at Korai House thicker.
You were eavesdropping on us?
So there you have it.
We know everything.
About you leaving your body,
and about the previous histories.
Please, let us help, too!
No.
I appreciate your offer, but I can't
let you join the operation.
Especially not you, Narugino.
Why not?!
I'm a hero of justice—
Your hero duty is over!
I can't let you fight anymore!
Narugino, remember how I ran tests on you?
It'll only take one more time...
If you Uberfy one more time, you'll...
Are you serious?
I see.
All right.
But that just means I can't Uberfy, right?
Narugino...
Well, Meika's been training me all this time.
Even without Uberfying, I can still...
No!
Knowing you, you'll just snap and lose yoursel—
What have we been doing for eight years, then?!
Professor Tenga talked about the
moment we'd save the world!
Isn't that moment now?!
Isn't that what we met and
spent time together for?
Isn't it?!
All right.
But on one condition.
If I see that you're about to Uberfy,
we're aborting the operation.
You know what that means, right?
Well, then,
It's settled.
Wait, wait!
I never said I'd let you two join in!
Besides, how would you even
make yourselves useful?!
I might not be useful,
but I still... I still...
I still want to be with you!
With all of you.
We are friends, after all.
Fine, then.
Maybe this is fate.
Grandpa told me that
I'd eventually form a secret squad
that would save the world.
The team's called...
Pretty Cutie Moon.
Wrong!
I never said you could change it!
The team's called Justice Punch.
The "Punch" comes from "panch,"
meaning "five" in Hindi.
In other words...
All right, Narugino, it's up to you now.
Huh?
I'm just staff.
You're the leader of Justice Punch.
Uh, gosh, I don't know what to say...
Just say what you're thinking.
I love you all.
I love Korai House, too.
So I want to be with you all forever.
Next year, the year after, and after that!
All right, let's do this!
We're going to protect Korai House tomorrow!
Yeah!
For all the world's people!
For a supremely happy and peaceful future!
Yeah!
Secret Squad Justice Punch!
Here we...
Go!
Episode 11
Secret Squad Justice Punch!
Are you really going to go through with this?
Yeah.
I've experienced this New Year's
Eve billions of times now,
but this is the first time I've
been through such a history.
That's why it's worth doing.
Laying down new tracks will mean something.
In that case,
I won't say any more.
Until we meet again someday, somewhere.
Farewell.
All right, let's do this!
Come at me with all you've got!
Are you the captain?
What if I am?
Tell your headquarters to please
stay out of this for another hour.
No can do.
Why not?!
If you have doubts about the asteroid...
I don't doubt it.
I know the asteroid's coming.
No way...
You get it now, don't you?
Miya Ken here.
Pumpkin Chair, do you read me?
Loud and clear.
I can hear you.
I shut down the southern attack force.
I know.
I heard your conversation.
The police force is teeming with
Qmay Group men, isn't it?
Talking won't convince them.
Strange Juice, how's the northern front?
Sorry...
I'm a little busy right now.
Wh-What the hell?!
Are you okay?
Not to worry.
They're packing up and going home.
See? I told you.
I don't have to Uberfy to fight.
Don't give me that!
It's because of the Ashido-maker that I made.
Rabura, Ito, how's the rooftop?
All clear toward the west.
Likewise toward the east.
It'll be a piece of cake if this keeps up.
Yeah, I think we can hold out.
Hikiotani
Man, that was kind of anticlimactic.
W-Wait!
What is that?
You're kidding me...
Is it the Self-Defense Force?
No, it isn't...
That's...
This is the U.S. Army.
You have been completely surrounded.
Drop your weapons and surrender.
If you do not surrender within 10 minutes,
we will be forced to destroy you.
Seriously?
Why the U.S. military, of all people?
It's because Mikatan was being all
American, with that "here we go" stuff.
What?! I don't think that
has anything to do with it!
I can make a white flag out
of any white cloth, right?
I'm pretty sure I'm wearing white today.
No, Rabura! Don't take
matters into your own hands!
Why?
Do you seriously want
to take on the military?
It's all right.
I have countermeasures in place.
Have you reached an answer?
Guri-chan.
Guriko!
Wait, Miya Ken! Don't abandon your post!
That's right...
Rabura, you take it from here!
Hang on!
Where are you going?!
You're both here now.
Well then, let's hear your answer.
Even if we become Ws,
you still intend to destroy
humanity, don't you?!
To destroy the old humanity
is also a W's duty.
Doesn't that mean everyone
at Korai House will die?
We're not like them.
Why don't you let go of them already?
We won't become Ws!
We're going to protect humanity—
the people of Korai House!
The U.S. military is about to
begin its all-out assault.
The riot police will attack simultaneously.
Add to that these Ws here.
Can you hold them all off by yourselves?
I'll be going ahead to Korai House.
I can't let the asteroid's
descent be interrupted.
Wait, Guriko!
What are you doing, Ito?
This is the same UI as the game
I'm always playing, isn't it?
Yeah, it is, but...
I can do it, then.
Do what?!
Please, Meika.
No!
This isn't a game!
You can't respawn.
If you get hit, you're dead!
I know!
I know that.
But I want to be useful, too.
I want to protect Korai House, too.
I will protect it!
What the hell?!
Fire!
Very well.
I, Torahachiro, will take you on!
Run!
That idiot.
Colonel!
A skirmish has been reported to have started.
Ignore it.
More importantly,
have you found the bear cub yet?
Chiyoko, are you all right?
This is bad...
We have to hurry and go after Guriko.
This scent...
Cinnamon?
Hurry! Now's your chance!
You're...
You can't be...
Yeah, I'm the other you.
The disembodied soul of Iridatsu Yuta.
Huh?!
I don't have time to explain.
Never mind me, just go after Guriko!
I have about six more minutes
to possess this body.
Fine.
I'll take care of you all in six minutes!
Commencing countdown. We have
30 seconds.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Fire!