Vapor pressure stabilized.
It should work this time.
Right! Open the valve!
At last.
At last, we've done it!
Now the Kingdom can finally crush the Commonwealth!
Long live the Kingdom of Albion!
Now we just have to work on mass production.
You'll see what you get for stealing our country!
What's our target?
A C-ball.
The Kingdom has successfully
miniaturized the Cavorite control unit.
I would like your team to take the prototype from them.
So the main players in this shadow war
are the spies and the scientists.
The Kingdom possesses
refining technology that we lack.
If they combine it with the miniature control unit,
they would make large-scale gravity weapons a reality.
If not handled carefully, this could change history.
Isn't this a bit much for a team with amateurs?
Our more experienced spies could...
This is something only your team can do.
Because of Princess?
She is your team's strong point.
You will use her position to infiltrate
the ceremony at the Cavorite mine.
Honestly, the way you work that princess...
Another thing, Dorothy...
This is for your ears only.
Beatrice, switch.
Checkmate.
Your turn, Beatrice.
You won't shake me this time.
You keep saying that,
and yet you have lost ten times in a row.
You've been losing right along with me, Miss Chise.
I have been victorious once.
It doesn't count as winning
when you cut down a police officer.
Fear not. I used the back of my sword.
And that makes it better?
Indeed it does.
Say, I've been thinking.
You don't suppose our team could use a name, do you?
That's a wonderful idea!
They do say names and natures often agree.
We don't need a team name.
We don't want to make up any information
that could turn up as evidence.
That's an ironclad spy rule.
Is that why you tell nothing but lies?
If I'm a liar, then there's no point
in questioning me, is there?
We're all girls, so I think we should have a cute name.
Something pink, or a flower.
What about the name of that unusual bird
we saw the other day?
I think it was a penguin?
Just a moment.
I'll do an onomancy reading for that name.
This is the Security Service!
Open the door!
Welcome back, Dorothy.
You could be a little scared, Partner.
Did you get to see L?
Yes, and he gave us the most annoying target.
And you?
We were thinking of team names.
We were practicing tailing.
Ooh, team names, is it?
All right, I'll be Scotch, Ange will be Calvados,
Princess will be Champagne...
Chise, let's see...
They're all the names of liquors, aren't they?
Don't be a part of this, Dorothy.
They need to learn basic tailing techni-
Oh no!
How do I count the strokes
of the letters in your alphabet?
It's like a mechanical fortress.
Cavorite is the heart and soul of Albion's Air Fleet.
Naturally, the mines will be heavily guarded.
Excuse me.
Are you here for the ceremony?
Hello, there.
Princess!
I brought some friends from school with me.
Is that all right?
I beg your pardon.
Any friends of yours are welcome.
The power of a nation's princess.
If they tried to body check her, heads would roll.
So I'm a key, then?
Yes, a magic one.
The ceremony starts in 30 minutes.
With guests arriving and preparations underway,
this will be their busiest time.
In other words, the time when security is the most lax.
And we'll use that time to get the prototype
from the underground laboratory!
You all know the plan, right?
Dorothy, Beatrice, and I will infiltrate the facility.
Welcome, Princess.
Her Majesty the Queen is here.
If you'd be so kind...
Of course.
Princess, we'll be a-waitin' right over there.
I'm leaving Chise here to protect you.
She's our most reliable fighter.
One guard.
What do we do?
Looks like I'm up.
Um, just wh-what are you...?
Huh?
Another dead end?
You can take the stairs to the right.
Then go straight ahead to the ceremony hall.
Thanks f'r the directions!
I think I drank too much.
Could you get me something to drink?
I-if water will suffice.
Oh, you're so kind!
Wh..what are you-?
You have such a cute face, Mr. Guard Man.
Do... do you really... think so?
What the...?
Hey!
Is that you, Jake?
There's been a methane explosion!
So that's where the dust is coming from!
I'll take over here!
You go get some masks!
They're in Storeroom Three.
Three? That's all the way on the other side!
Give me a break!
I'm already beat from helping with the move!
Miss Ange, all clear.
We'd better hurry.
We have about 20 minutes until they get back.
Miss Ange, I've been thinking.
What?
What do you think about Team Wildcat?
They're so swift and fearless.
But they look adorable!
Would you... change your voice back?
It's unsettling.
How do you do, Grandmother?
We've not seen you since
the ceremony at the music academy.
How is school?
I've made some good friends.
That's good to hear.
Friends can be life-long treasures.
Yes, Grandmother.
What do you think of the princess?
She is not what I imagined.
She's royalty, but she speaks to us as equals.
She even tells jokes.
But none of them are very funny.
She's full of curiosity, and always giving Ange trouble.
Chise.
I trust they don't suspect you?
They removed me from the infiltration team.
We are here to find out whether we can trust
the Kingdom or the Commonwealth.
We must choose which to ally ourselves with.
Yes, Sir.
I understand.
Your Majesty, I believe it's time.
For what?
To discuss marriage.
Mine?
We told you, it's too soon.
Such matters can wait until after she has graduated.
I beg your pardon, Majesty,
but strengthening our relationship with Moscow
will lead to the stabilization of all of Europe.
And to that end you would have Us
sacrifice Our own granddaughter?
Binding our countries through marriage
will squelch the possibility of a world war.
From here on, I go alone.
If I'm not back in ten minutes, you go back to the others.
All right.
Please be careful.
Oh?
Welcome back.
Did you leave Ange and Beatrice?
Yeah, well, you know...
Will they be all right?
You're worried?
Yes, of course.
This is for your ears only.
This mission will deal a damaging blow to the Kingdom.
If Princess is a double agent, she's sure to take action.
You mean...?
We haven't abandoned the possibility
that Princess is our enemy.
Is something the matter?
Oh, no. I was just wondering
what would make a good team name.
Miss Ange has been gone a long time.
No...
Was there a leak?
No, even if there was...
This is some big equipment.
This definitely would have been the research facility.
Give me a break!
I'm already beat from helping with the move!
They moved it?
Up there?
This is...
Miss Dorothy!
Beatrice? Where's Ange?
She told me to leave without her
if she didn't come back in ten minutes.
Really. She must be having some trouble, then.
I hope she's all right.
Come with me.
Let's go, Princess.
What's the matter?
There's no time.
I'll explain on the way.
What's going on?
Apparently they moved the entire laboratory.
Was there an information leak?
I don't know.
But I found the loading dock they used.
It leads to the Thames.
So they escaped by boat?
The drawbridge only opened up ten minutes ago.
They can't have gotten far.
If we take the shortest route,
we should catch up to them at Greenwich.
Got it!
Our research was finally on the right track.
Why should we have to move NOW?
In answer to your question, I'd like you to look at this.
What does that book have to do with anything?
You'll see.
A camera?
There is a Commonwealth spy in our midst.
We will now conduct a VERY thorough investigation.
Left at the next corner.
Right at the next intersection.
Right at the next stairway.
You got it!
Stairway? But we're in an automobile!
Don't bite your tongue.
How do you feel about Team Meikyo Shisui?
("Mirror-smooth Water")
What does it mean?
Next, through that narrow passage
up ahead and turn left!
Nobody fall out!
Be quiet.
There it is.
We made it!
I thought maybe Princess
had leaked the information, but...
It's quite the large boat, isn't it?
At that size, it could be carrying an entire platoon.
I will go with you.
No. You stay here, Chise.
Dorothy and I will go alone.
You would leave me behind again?
Miss Chise...?
I'm a stronger asset than Dorothy!
I know.
Then why...
You came to us under the graces of Lord Horikawa.
We can't ask you to put yourself in danger.
Your concern is unnecessary!
I said I would go!
Your Highness?
I'm going, too.
No, you can't!
I've been trained.
Besides, if I go, you won't have to leave a guard with me.
Wait a minute, Princess.
This isn't some party we're talking about.
It's too dangerous for an amateur.
I'd like to know why you're so eager to take the risk.
Come now, I've been in danger all along.
If word gets out that I'm a spy, it's over for me.
I'm standing on a precipice... a bridge much narrower
and more fragile than this one.
That's no reason to put yourself in MORE danger!
It's the same either way.
If you all fail, that will lead them directly to my secret.
And in that case,
I must put my life on the line to make this plan succeed.
If Princess is a double agent,
it shouldn't matter if her secret gets out-
she would have a safety net.
There would be no reason to take such a big risk.
All right, Princess.
We're on this boat together, then.
Yes!
What was that?
Did you kill him?
He wasn't strong enough to merit killing.
What do we do now?
We split into two groups.
Princess and I will go aft.
Right. We'll take the bow, then.
Charlotte.
Are you angry?
Of course I am, after that stunt...
I was worried sick.
I'm sorry.
Meanie. You like to see me squirm.
Can you blame me, Charlotte?
You act like I'm the only important one.
Because...
When we were children, you talked to me like normal.
If I did that now, people would know we're old friends.
But we're ALL friends.
All right, then, why don't we say
we met and realized we're kindred spirits?
Then we wouldn't have to hide our friendship.
No.
I would lose control of myself.
I think it's good to let your hair down on occasion.
Like you used to.
I hate who I used to be.
But it's the old you
that I love so much.
You've finally shown your true colors.
What?!
The Cavorite research team, I presume?
We'd like you to come with us.
You're...
You can't be...
We are spies.
We haven't settled on a name yet.
Not only did we get the prototype,
but we have the researchers in custody.
The results were even better than we hoped.
Now Princess is clear of all suspicion.
No.
This world isn't black and white.
Only black and grey.
And the princess is grey.
Keep a constant watch on her.
All right, then.
As part of the food series, let's be Team Carrot!
These are getting worse and worse.
I don't especially like carrots.
Your Highness! You mustn't be picky!
I know. What about Team White Pigeon?
Pigeon?
Not bad.
It's pretty and cute. I like it!
They do call spies "pigeons."
Really?
After the Flood, Noah sent a dove...
a pigeon... to scout for land.
Then that settles it.
What do you think, Miss Dorothy?
I like it. Team White Pigeon.
I especially like that it's not grey.
I knew you'd like it!