And now an update on the vicious
assault that occurred yesterday
in front of Toyosu station.
The suspect continues
to deny involvement,
saying she has no recollection
of the incident.
Suspects of the two assaults occurring
near Tachikawa earlier this month
Hey, Pai-Pai, all this...
is by the bad Gatchaman, right?
have also denied involvement,
citing similar reasons.
We don't know that.
Criminal psychologists
have speculated that
Stop calling me Pai-Pai.
the series of incidents
may have been triggered
That's what it meant by
"It's all your fault."
by people's everyday stresses
that subconsciously erupted...
Okay. Question!
If this bad Gatchaman does
even worse stuff,
what are we going to do?
Well, um...
Of course, we'd all
deal with it together!
Really?
Wouldn't Pai-Pai just run away
when the time comes?
O-Of course not!
I'm your leader!
We Gatchaman have a duty
to protect this planet!
Anyway, stop calling me Pai-Pai!
Question!
Have Gatchaman ever fought together?
That has...
No!
Question!
You sure like questions.
Why do Gatchaman sneak around?
Shouldn't we act more like
the police or the self-defense force?
What?
Well...
Maybe you have a point...
We can't.
Why?
Because... those are the rules.
What?! Who made those rules?
What do they mean, Senpai?
What? Well...
If I could act more openly...
Sugane!
Uh, yes?
Newbie!
I'm Hajime!
Listen, you two!
We Gatchaman have special powers
normal humans do not have.
We must never let those powers
fall into their hands!
We're not sneaking around.
We're solving problems
without causing the human race
unnecessary concern or worry.
Then why is the bad Gatchaman
doing as it pleases?
Because it is bad!
Because there are those who use
the power for ill, we must strive,
all the more, to be careful about
how we use our own abilities!
But what if there's an emergency
that won't let us do that?
What if the world goes
up in a big, red blaze?
Then the human race
will be super worried.
I don't get it.
That'd make people say
GALAX is doing more.
That's going too far.
Oh, Hajime-chan.
Hi, D-san!
Aw, your hair's different. Way too cute!
Don't put us Gatchaman
on the same level as GALAX!
Oh, Hajime-chan.
Aw, your hair's different. Way too cute!
Hi, D-san! HeeHee. Oh.
Can you tell me where Utsutsu-chan's room is?
Oh? You got a smart phone.
Okay. Come with me.
You're using GALAX!
No! This is research!
Senpai, come join
the collage community!
No way I'd join that!
Oh, a message from JJ.
When a large box has
vanished into darkness,
the broken child
will finally reveal itself to us.
The white bird shall bear witness.
The broken child?
It's it!
It will finally appear...
before... us...
Leader!
The white bird... Huh...
Rui, what is the matter?
You have not moved for two hours.
X, I'll tell you what
I'm really thinking.
You're the only one I can trust, X.
Thank you.
That is probably what
I should say in response.
You're interesting, X.
You're just like a person.
Rui, your decision appears
to have caused some confusion.
Is it true that LOAD runs GALAX?
Apparently.
He sure looks suspicious, doesn't he?
Isn't it run by X?
You mean that goth-lolita four-eyes
is the one who picked us?
What's this...
So creepy.
"SDWORC"?
I mean, he's totally
ordering us around.
Please read it backwards.
CROWDS, huh...
It is a community created today
by a subset of the Hundred.
I closed it down immediately,
but there will be trouble
if this becomes widespread.
My decision is final, no matter what.
The use of CROWDS is forbidden
for the time being.
Shall I force them
to withdraw from the Hundred?
Who is their representative?
Number 26.
I remember.
He's always wanted to use CROWDS.
Call him up.
Understood.
I will relay your opinion to Number 26.
No, I will speak with him directly.
Understood.
Morning, Number 26.
I have a name: Umeda.
Morning, Umeda-san.
This is LOAD, right?
Yes.
What's your real name?
I'm sorry, but my policy is not to say.
Why?
Because I believe GALAX
doesn't need a solitary leader.
No, it's because you want to be able
to abandon everything and be
irresponsible when the time comes.
It does not matter
what you think of it.
It appears you are dissatisfied with me.
You must know why.
The use of CROWDS
is forbidden for the time being.
Explain why.
It has developed minor
functionality issues.
You're a bad liar.
What do you mean?
You want to get all the
credit, don't you?
Credit?
Don't play dumb.
If used, CROWDS can
easily change the world.
For example?
For example, we can just
kill incompetent politicians.
Execute vile criminals.
Crush corporations
that are repeat offenders.
Would that change the world?
Isn't that what CROWDS is for?
Will the world change,
just by saving people's lives?
This is the real deal.
But now you want
to keep CROWDS for yourself,
to give yourself credit.
What is this "credit" you speak of?
What is it that you want?
Don't put on airs, LOAD.
Let's get real.
We, the Hundred, have endangered
ourselves many times
over for this world.
Isn't it about time that
our efforts are rewarded?
The world is full of praise
for what we've done.
It's about time we revealed ourselves.
Everyone can become heroes.
And that's "credit"?
You want praise?
Reputation?
Not just me. Everyone thinks the same.
Is that true?
I am interested in becoming
neither a hero nor a leader.
A world that lionizes heroes
and leaders is still primitive.
Until individuals who are neither
change their way of thinking
and rise to action,
the world can never be updated.
Like I said, ditch the idealism!
Our way of thinking
had changed way before!
This is a revolution, right?
The world will never change if
revolutionaries just sneak around!
Everyone's raring to go!
Let us use CROWDS already!
Umeda-san, are you having
any fun right now?
Huh?
Do you feel any joy
in being one of the Hundred?
I have no clue what you're getting at.
I do feel joy.
It's a joy that comes
from deep within.
It's not based on external factors like
money, reputation, status, or reward.
It stems from connecting with
people possessing a similar purpose,
giving a helping hand to those in need,
then working together to right wrongs.
It is a joy that comes from
within, innate to mankind.
The circle of community will
spread, eventually creating
a world where everyone will help
each other without compensation.
It will be a world
without heroes and leaders,
where everyone is equal,
working side by side,
slowly changing the world without
holding their own
deeds in high esteem.
That is the revolution GALAX aims for.
As if anyone would be satisfied
by a scam like that.
A scam?
Yeah, that's right.
LOAD, you don't have the backbone.
You think we'll be satisfied
with wishy-washy logic like that?
But I believed you.
Your cheer, optimism,
willingness to help others...
Your selfless actions both within
GALAX and without in the real world.
I felt I could give you special powers
without them being misused.
I believed you would use
them to update the world.
Get credit?
Become heroes?
I didn't create GALAX
for such insignificant things!
C'mon, gimme a break.
Please remember, Umeda-san.
Remember when you first
reached out and helped a stranger.
Everything will be all right.
The world will soon change.
We will change
the prevailing sentiment that
money and reputation are everything.
Everyone will soon realize
the true joy... the true connection.
They will realize that those
are things people really desire!
Umeda-san!
Let's change the world together!
I get it.
Thank you.
I'm glad you understand.
Don't get me wrong.
I really get it that you're
the one who's a useless leader.
Papa?
Mana.
What's the matter, Papa?
It's nothing.
Let's go, yeah?
Okay.
X, please withdraw him
and his friends immediately.
Understood.
The world is regressing...
It appears I have made a mistake
in my selection of partners.
But you have me!
Hey, Rui-Rui.
Why won't you use my power?
Tell me plz!
Watch where you're going!
He's a total asshole.
Rui-san, want me to get him?
Shut up! Be quiet!
Okay, here's a comment from General X.
Rui, a magnitude 8.5 earthquake
has just occurred in the Kantou region.
Tens of thousands
of casualties are expected from
a massive tsunami
and collapsed buildings.
The power of CROWDS is needed.
Stop it!
Stop!
The power of CROWDS is needed.
Oh, it's not shaking?
It's got to be shaking.
The world's shaking up a storm.
Shaking!
GALAX Collage Offline
Meeting in Fukushima
How about this ribbon?
How's that?
Huh?
There's no communications network?
Now that you mention it, no.
But the police and the self-defense force
are right across from each other, right?
The fire station and
the city hall are nearby, too.
What would you do if anything
happened to Tachikawa?
I can't believe what she's talking
about with people like them.
"The broken child will reveal itself."
What's that supposed to mean?
What else?
It's talking about the crazy Gatchaman.
Wow! Jou-san, you're so good!
You've got good taste!
You're a cool customer, too.
Isn't he?
He's great!
Jou-san, we didn't
come here to have fun.
I know.
"The white bird shall bear witness."
Don't take your eyes off that girl.
What's this stick?
I-It's nothing!
Wait! A sword, maybe?
You've got no taste!
Wait! Please stop!
Jou-san!
That's totally weird.
Everyone's connected on GALAX,
but not in the real world?
That's true.
Well, we've gone out
a couple of times for drinks.
Well, why don't we exchange
numbers while we're at it?
Isn't this great? It's the F-15.
This tail wing part was
super hard to get right.
It's not about whether it's hard to do.
We're going to teach children,
so we should choose
something more positive—
You're acting all feminine,
but you totally shoot guns
when you have to, right?
Must be nice being a cop
to do as you please.
There you go again,
bringing up work at the drop of a hat.
I feel sorry for your husband!
What's my husband got to do with it?
I mean, it's better than being single.
What'd you say?!
What?
Now, now. It'll be fine.
When it counts, we come together.
Okay, Tachikawa team!
Be nice to each other!
Let's all go out for drinks again!
That sounds like a great idea.
Oh, here it comes!
Into the tunnel we go!
"When a large box..."
"Has vanished into darkness"!
Good god!
Hey, the tunnel's collapsed!
Are you okay!?
Hey!
Requesting immediate assistance!
The location is, um...
Joufuku Expressway,
before Kamishiro Pass.
One of the tunnel's
ceiling panels has collapsed.
More than twenty vehicles and
approximately sixty people
are trapped in the debris.
Their rescue is a priority,
but there is a risk of fire.
Please move with caution.
Please evacuate children and the
elderly from the accident site first.
Please take advantage
of your skills as a nurse.
Your skills are needed right now.
All right!
Okay!
Are you all right?
Can you walk?
Excuse me! Please carry him to safety.
There are not enough people on-site.
CROWDS is needed.
What is the matter, Rui?
We're not using CROWDS anymore.
That's what I decided, right?
However, if we do not hurry,
many lives will be lost.
Without intervention,
dozens of casualties are projected.
I know!
I know that...
CROWDS is not that alien's power.
I can't stand it anymore.
We can't let young'uns die.
At this rate, there will be a secondary disaster.
CROWDS is your power, Rui.
Save as many people as possible!
Is there a reason?
I can't go! Please help.
Someone, help!
Please, I need guys here to help!
Please!
Thank you.
Utsutsu-chan!
Okay, go!
Where are the firefighters?
They'll be here in twenty minutes.
A self-defense force
helicopter is on its way.
Let's hurry!
If the remaining ceiling panels
collapse, we're done for!
If a fire starts...
Then we'll just have to run.
We're going to abandon them?!
We're hurrying,
so we don't have to do that.
Calm down, both of you.
How many cars are left?
There are five more trapped
upwards from where you are.
Still so many...
Will you help us?
Of course. I'm a cop.
Okay, let's go!
Look out!
What?
What's that?
Amnesia...
The Effect is already active.
What's that?
By whom?
What's going on?
It can't be... Is that the one?
"The broken child"!
Let's go. There can be no casualties.
Play the Game...
First, speak to passengers
to see if they are conscious,
and check if their airways
are obstructed or not.
If they need CPR, bring them here.
Don't worry.
We will save all of them without fail.
It'll be okay.
I hope everyone makes it...
Looks like things are
going to be okay here.
Wow!
Who are they?
We have to do our part, too!
Newbie.
I'm Hajime.
Don't use your Gatchaman powers.
Boo.
You either, Utsutsu.
Get out of the tunnel!
Hurry!
Hey, Newbie!
Gatcha—
What are you thinking?!
Senpai, aren't there times
when you find yourself taking
action without even thinking about it?
What are you talking about?
Hey!
The time is now!
That's what heroes do!
Amnesia Effect!
Wait!
Go, Bird!
Are you okay!?
It can't be...