Is the data accurate?
Yes... Although I don't know why.
Ever since then, MESS has stopped
all harmful activity
toward human society.
Ohhh... Is this a reaction, too?
Don't tell me! You love origami, too?
All the absorbed humans have
been safely returned, as well.
No way!
That's way too awesome!
Case closed!
We can't let down our guard just yet!
They just stopped doing anything;
they haven't stopped
making an appearance.
C'mon, can't you just
be happy, Pai-Pai?
Don't call me Pai-Pai!
Oh, do you prefer Pai-san, after all?
You're messing with me.
So you're saying that no one's
been abducted since then?
Yes. No one since.
Huh? What?
Not "What?"!
What'd you do to it back there?
I just thought I'd make it cute.
Hey, doesn't it seem like it's
communicating with Hajime-chan?
Oh, it's MESSY-chan.
Why are you introducing it to us?!
I mean, don't even name it!
There's no way anyone can
communicate with a MESS...
Wh-What?
Its shape-changing might have
something to do with this.
Oh, we collaborated with our scissors.
Oh, that must be it!
Change the body's shape
to exchange information, maybe?
Maybe that's how
they communicate.
That's way too far-fetched!
But, it's strange.
Why did all the MESS act
as one, at the same time?
Maybe they can share information.
What?
So, just like with this NOTE,
information might be
transmitted instantaneously.
They might be a life
form with a hive mind.
That's kind of sexy!
How?!
Forget it!
My orders were to exterminate!
But when we try
to catch it, it vanishes.
That's impossible!
Aww, so cute!
Maybe MESS-chan never had any animosity
toward us in the first place,
and just didn't realize
we were around.
Impossible!
Ouch...
They've clearly been doing
harm until recently!
"Oh, no! I've stepped on an ant!"
Kind of like that?
Even a philanthropist like me might
do that while I'm walking about.
You don't mean...
From their perspective,
we're like ants?
Ants might be giving
us a lot of credit.
Might be more like rocks.
Way too sad!
I'm dreamy...
Th-Then, what we've been
doing until now is...
A waste, right?
That's being way too harsh!
But it's spot-on!
Well, it's true that
we did save people...
Well, compared to our
Gatchaman predecessors,
we're pathetic enough.
Aw, now my shoulders are tense.
Please keep it together, Leader.
Oh, are you interested?
I'll give this to you, then.
Here!
I'm dreamy...
That's a troublesome neighbor
you've got there.
We have a baby,
so, of course, the baby will cry.
But the neighbor says
we're being too loud
and playing music with
the volume cranked way up...
They might both be unwanted noise,
but for entirely different reasons.
Things have escalated recently.
Even at night, the neighbor
honks the car horn.
It's enough to make
my baby seize up.
Maybe you should
lodge a complaint.
You mean, take legal action?
But I have no experience
in that sort of thing...
Why don't you ask X?
You're right. I will.
What may I help you with?
May I?
Civil lawsuits aren't
too much trouble.
What?
If you'd like,
Someone's having
neighbor issues.
Please help!
Join            Close
I can give you counsel.
Are you a lawyer?
Yes. First, tell me what's
happening, in detail.
It's not heroes who'll
update the world.
It's us.
Seriously?
You're a GALAXter, too, Marippu?
That sounds like trash (garakuta).
Hey!
Fine, fine.
You're asking me if I'm
a GALAX user, right?
Of course, I am.
It comes in handy, doesn't it?
GALAX is good stuff.
The info you can get
from the X app is pretty useful.
Hey, isn't that scary?
There's got to be flame
wars and stuff, right?
It's all fine.
They're good at managing it.
They match users up in a good way.
Just give it a try.
Let's update the world together!
What's that?
I'm back.
Welcome back, Rui.
Were you able to secure
a sufficient caloric intake?
Yes.
Update.
A balanced diet is very important.
Good health is essential
for realizing your ambitions.
Very nice, X.
You've become good
at managing GALAX, too.
Thank you, Milord Rui.
Hm?
There has been a noticeable
decline in job seekers,
given the lack of economic recovery
and effective policies
for the foreseeable feature.
In actuality, job seekers appear
to be relying, not on agencies,
but on GALAX.
Basically, it's a problem of matching
job seekers with employers.
If they can contact each
other directly online,
why would they need a middle man?
Our active users are
continuing to increase today.
That means the number of people
who resent us will also increase.
The more powerful the enemy,
the more enjoyable
the game, perhaps?
Missing Persons Simultaneously Found Across the Nation
Well, I'm the one who's shocked.
When I came to, I was standing
on my usual way home,
but I was told it's been
more than six months.
Not just this man,
but others who had gone missing
are being found across the country.
They all have no memory
of the lost time.
What, what?
Were they abducted by aliens?
No way.
Prime Minister Resigning
This just in.
Prime Minister Kamoshida, who had
been urged to take responsibility
for his cabinet members'
multiple scandals,
indicated his intent to resign today.
We'll be reporting live from
the prime minister's residence...
Aww... and this one'd started off
with high approval ratings, too.
Congratulations, Rui.
Stage clear, isn't it?
He wasn't really a boss character...
The world's so complicated now
that even excellent leaders
might not be enough
to turn things around.
Then, who is the true enemy...
Who is it? One of the Hundred?
An incoming call from Number 26.
Him...
It's probably to ask for
usage permission, I'm sure.
Shall I handle him?
Sorry, yeah.
What a waste, Rui-Rui.
Are you being stingy with
that valuable power of yours?
I did give them power.
the hundred capable GALAXters I chose.
But we'll update the world
without relying on that power.
No matter what!
You're going to take
that thing along to school?
It's fine.
We're the only ones who can see it.
Well, sure, but...
That was close!
I wonder if something's happening.
Either way, he shouldn't have
driven so fast on this road!
But he may have been
driving a sick person.
Oh, maybe his wife
went into sudden labor?
Why do you bother
thinking about things like that?
When you think about it that way,
don't you feel like they had a valid reason?
Don't you feel less angry?
Well, sure...
It's more fun this way.
So, "The current of the
flowing river does not cease"
might be a phrase even
you guys have heard.
Kamono Choumei was a court
poet in his younger years...
Milk?
There has been a worrisome leak.
Last night, there was a power outage
at a factory in Tokorozawa,
and milk was left at room
temperature for several hours.
Class is finished!
According to the source,
even though disposal
was recommended,
the supervisor would not allow it.
Instead, the batch was
shipped out after undergoing
a simple disinfection procedure.
Is that bad?
Yes.
There were factors indicating
a potential emergency situation,
so I illegally obtained data
on the batch's management
and component analysis,
and ran an analysis.
So you did some cracking?
Well, I guess it couldn't be helped.
So, are they guilty?
Thanks for the food!
Yep, looking good.
Yummy!
Milk?
Wait a minute.
Thanks for the food.
It's from X.
The milk's not safe!
Huh? What?
What's wrong with it?
It's urgent, Senpai!
C'mon! Help us out!
We got to the kiosk lady okay.
Next, a school-wide announcement
and then hit the vending machines.
Yeah! Split up and unplug them!
Wait a minute.
Did you get permission
from the teachers?
There's no time for that!
Have you heard about the milk?
Please tell the others!
I feel dreamy...
Seriously?
It's an anti-tampering device.
Oh, no announcement yet?
They won't let us in.
The broadcast room is only
accessible from the teachers' lounge.
So, we need to tell everyone!
Isn't it a ruse?
We can't just take stuff
from the internet at face value.
But there are lots of people
who've been helped by GALAX.
Yeah, X tells us everything, too.
You'd better not be using it to cheat.
Oh, c'mon! That's not why we're here!
Um...
I'm using GALAX, too,
and I think it can be trusted...
Maybe we can,
at least, urge caution...
Anyway, we should
consult the principal.
Consult?
That'll be too late.
Where's the key
to the vending machines?
That's also in the teachers' lounge.
They say we need permission...
I'll send a decoy.
Let's use this opportunity.
Oh, it's kind of like a game.
A decoy?
You, of course, Senpai.
Use your sword and mess around.
Huh, what?!
You can use an umbrella
or whatever, too.
Get the attention
of people who are getting
in the way at the teachers' lounge
and in front of the broadcast room.
That's impossible!
Besides, what about
my reputation at school?
Senpai, you're a Gatchaman, right?
N-Not so loud!
The school's in a crisis.
But that's no excuse to skulk
around and go out of control!
Heroes should face
problems head-on.
Listen, Senpai.
It's like that car
earlier this morning.
That car wasn't
out of control for no reason.
Well, you don't know
if there really was a reason.
That's just your speculation.
But now, we definitely have a reason.
You're a hero, right, Senpai?
We have to protect everyone!
Where's the key?
O-Over there.
The key to the vending machines
is probably there, too.
Don't drink the milk!
Okay!
Next!
Are you still using the key?
They're in front of the
inner courtyard now.
Oh, they're done.
This one's the last of them!
What now? Should we go get it?
Oh, Senpai!
Can you slash right here?
Slash?
Slash!
Fine!
Here goes!
I slashed it!
Congratulations!
The world has been updated.
Mission complete.
Yay, updated!
Nationwide, 68% percent of schools
and 74% of businesses
averted any casualties.
Flaw in Quality Control at Dairy Company
Victims who made purchases
from individual stores
and wholesale distributors
number in the double digits.
That's more than I thought.
Is that an indication
of just how many
people still don't trust
information from GALAX?
It is true that people
of a certain age range
or in certain professions
exhibit markedly lower confidence.
However, many who
acknowledged the information
were still unable to take
appropriate action.
Oh, I see.
They're afraid of being held
responsible in the aftermath,
so they cannot easily take action
based on outside information.
It's what people call the adverse
effects of a vertical society.
That's probably what we're
actually up against.
Running GALAX has made
my enemies clearer than ever to me.
They're the ones who refuse
to see people as individuals.
The ones who cannot see the joy
in helping others if there is no
reward or reputation to be gained.
Either way,
anyone who's not... fun, I guess?
Oh, that was great, Senpai.
You looked kind of cute
being scolded by the teachers.
Is that your attempt
to make me feel better?
Oh, you wanted me to do that?
What are you doing?
But, well...
This kind of... the internet's
got a lot going for it, maybe.
You think so?
Its influence is huge.
That's not true.
Huh?
If your battery runs out,
or if you don't have a signal, that's it.
You can't just blindly
follow the internet.
Okay, then.
Hey, stop it, Al-chan.
Stop. It tickles.
It's dinner time!
Come help.
Okay.
Wait a second, okay?
Oh?
Oh...
Is that from Hajime-chan?
She just pushed it on me.
That girl's way too fun!
Why don't you become friends?
Here.
All right, beans are
on the menu today.
I'm dreamy...
Can you circle around
and get closer?
I want the setting sun
in the background.
Multiple rescue requests
have appeared on the timeline.
A news channel helicopter has crashed
into a ropeway's support pillar.
The pillars bent, stranding
the two gondolas on either side.
You brought that to school?
Isn't Toyosaki,
the gym teacher, annoying?
That doesn't mean you should—
Well, it's not like I'm going
to do anything to him with it.
What?
Now!
You!
Stop resisting!
Don't move!
What?
Where is he? Where'd he go?
Look around!
Hey, there he is!
N-No!
Stop resisting!
It wasn't me!
L-Let go of me!
Let go!
Gatcha...
Who are you?
Was that your doing?
Yummy...
Go...
Number 58 of the Hundred
is on the dispatched rescue team.
They are in operation,
but due to numerous obstacles
that cannot be overcome,
he is requesting usage permission.
There are several GALAXters among
the passengers exchanging information,
but the situation seems pretty dire.
I see...
If we don't use it now, when else?
The rescue team alone would
just end in a fail game.
I simulated all possible avenues
for a successful rescue
given the current available
human resources,
but all results were negative.
I guess we'll have to use...
the Crowds.
Ready!
Play the Game...