My first time switching schools...
Dad decided to open a
studio in the countryside,
so we left Tokyo,
and I changed schools.
I wonder if I'll be okay
in my new place.
Episode 12
"Fireworks
(Once Again)"
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Thank you.
No worries.
Bye.
Wait.
Hinode-hama Port Station
Over here.
It's the harbor!
I'm Touko Fukami.
I'm Kakeru Okikura.
Thanks again for before.
The fireworks.
You're here for the fireworks, right?
Not too many are around yet,
but there'll be more people.
I moved here.
There's a fireworks festival today?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah?
There's a beach and a pier
to the right of that harbor.
That's the stage for the fireworks.
Ah.
Café Kazemichi
Kakeru's late.
I bet he's snowed in
and stuck in his tent.
He's still living in his tent? In this snow?
I doubt it.
If Sacchan says no, then no.
Say what?
Hey.
Here's your hot orange.
I'm Touko Fukami.
Nice to meet you.
So, are you going to introduce yourselves?
Oh, right.
I'm Hiro Shirosaki.
My name's Yanagi Takayama.
I'm Yukinari Imi.
What's with that? Yuki was
just staring at Fukami-san.
Yukinari falls in love with everyone.
Dude.
It'll be my job to show her
around Hinode-hama today.
Too bad, Yuki.
I'm Sachi Nagamiya.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
My father is opening a studio here.
A studio?
Yeah, he makes art glass
and vases and things.
That's so cool.
I think it's a lot more hot and
tedious than you might think.
You're here for the fireworks, right?
The fireworks here are pretty awesome.
Well...
Apparently, she didn't know
about the fireworks today.
Oh, yeah?
We all get together every
year to watch the fireworks
from a place called Hinode-hama Shrine.
It's been a long time now.
All the way from elementary school?
I think it's been like that
ever since we set up
a weird new rule when we were younger
that we always had to
be in groups of three.
It's something that ends up happening
without anyone really talking about it.
You should come with us.
It'll be twice as fun.
May I?
Of course. Right, Yuki?
Of course.
It's settled, then.
Okay.
Are you not used to the snow?
Yeah, I grew up where there's no snow.
Try to keep your center of gravity
straight above your body,
and walk in small steps.
Thanks.
You can see all of Hinode-hama from
the deck on the fourth floor here.
Want to go up?
I can't wait for the fireworks.
You don't really hear about
fireworks in the winter, do you?
Yeah. I wonder what fireworks
are like in the snow.
You probably wouldn't be able
to see them anywhere else.
Everyone else is looking forward
to going with you, too, Touko.
You're calling me by my first name.
Touko, are you going to Hinode-hama
High School for your third year?
Yeah, I hope to.
Must be tough transferring
in your third year.
I'm want to go to art school, so it's probably
more about practice than studying.
Oh, yeah?
Are you taking over for your father?
I haven't decided yet.
I've never been outside this
town, so I don't really know.
What's it like being in a new town?
It's exciting.
I want to see the city more
before the fireworks start.
I'll show you around some more.
Thanks.
But I'll try walking by myself.
Yeah? Good idea.
It's not a big town, and everyone's nice.
I heard there's a new girl.
I won't ask you to knock anymore,
but when you're coming up to a boy's room,
can you at least put out a
vibe that you're approaching?
Why?
"Why?" Because it's dangerous.
So how was she?
She's passable.
Nothing can beat the tragic
glasses girl, huh?
Go away, if you have nothing to say.
Fine, fine.
Tee hee!
Dammit!
Don't overdo it just
because you seem okay.
Roger. It'd be a shame if I got injured.
Hurry up. It's cold.
Twelve more seconds.
Fine, fine.
Your routine is important to you. I get it.
That girl...
Fukami-san?
Yeah?
She's cute, don't you think?
So cold.
What's keeping him? He should be
on his shorter route today.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Are you going to the fireworks
with everyone, like always?
Yeah, I plan to.
What about you two?
We'll be watching from the rooftop as usual.
We've invited the Fukami-san family, too.
Fukami-san?
They have daughters in high
school and middle school.
Didn't I mention?
They're opening a glassware studio nearby.
Isn't it nice?
It turns out they're in my fan club, too.
I have plans to meet up with the older
girl at Hinode-hama Shrine later.
What?
It just kinda happened.
It's going to be really crowded.
It's her first time in Hinode-hama, right?
Do you think you can find her?
Oh, yeah, I guess I should go pick her up.
Oh, looks like they're already here.
She called me on her cell
phone before we got here,
and she said she wanted
to look around the city.
I see.
Do you need Touko's cell phone number?
Yes, please.
Onee-chan moves fast.
I know, in a blink of an eye.
I wonder who she got that from.
She seems to have a fever.
Anyway, come in.
Thank you.
Sacchan, are you okay?
Do you think you can make it?
Sorry.
Damn, I don't have my phone, either.
Wow.
It's so pretty.
I'll be at the neighborhood association.
Okay. Don't be too late.
Okay.
Sorry, please take care of Sachi for me.
I will. Leave it to me.
Yuki, that idiot. It's already starting!
Hey.
Hey, don't take off on your own!
What? You're late.
Hey!
Yeah?
What is it?
No, I—
What? Is something wrong?
What, they don't remember me?
But we just met.
Are they acting?
Is this a prank?
Are they serious?
They seriously don't recognize me?
It's nothing, thanks.
Is there anything we can—
No, it's fine, really.
Weird girl.
Yeah.
Hina, I bet you wanted
to go with Kakeru-kun.
Nope, I don't like crowds.
Oh, yeah?
I wonder if Onee-chan's making the most of it.
Tamaya!
You know some pretty old cheers, Hina-chan.
It's pretty awesome this year, too.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I finally found you.
Hurry!
Wait up!
I thought I'd lost you.
You can see me?
Never mind.
I was worried. You wouldn't
pick up your phone either.
It's turned off.
Is everyone else here yet?
Over there.
But it's weird.
It's like they can't see me.
The fireworks are starting already.
It kinda hurts.
Do you want to watch from here?
Aren't they waiting at the shrine?
It'll be nice for a change.
Doesn't look like we'll be able
to make it to the shrine.
Sorry.
It's okay. We'll make do
by ourselves this year.
Variety is the, uh, what was it—
Spice of life?
Yeah, that's it.
Another spice of life.
It's so pretty.
Can I see, too, Sachi?
I'm next.
You're so obvious.
About what?
Fine, fine, you're next.
I don't think that counts as
an indirect kiss, though.
Indirect what?
Here.
Is this the world of my
fragments of the future?
Seems like it.
So you're the Kakeru-kun that I imagined?
Yeah,
and I'm different
again from my earlier self.
You could say I'm a projection of
myself from your reality.
So you are Kakeru-kun
from my imaginary world.
That would be correct.
So what about Yana-chan and
the others, over there?
They're not real either,
in a different sense.
They're not real?
They might have had some reasons
that they couldn't get together here.
Are you real?
Yeah, I'm definitely real.
And my loneliness earlier?
During the fireworks show,
I can't be seen by the Yana-chan and Sacchan
and Hiro-kun and Yuki-kun of this world.
Because I don't have an unforgettable place
where I spent time with them.
Right, Kakeru-kun?
Nothing.
It's nothing.
I like the name "Touko."
I'll hear it later.
Keep your promise.
It changed?
It's my fault.
Final Episode
"Shooting Star"
Don't go.