So that happened, huh?
To think that that's how I'd reunite with Kazuhiko.
It seems a lot of different feelings were
colliding in and around this town.
What are Minori and the others doing?
They're safe, I suppose, but...
In the end, I couldn't make him understand.
I couldn't save the town.
I wasn't really useful...
I...
The Skylarks Take Flight
The Skylarks Take Flight.
This will take us to Ikoma, right?
Yeah.
Then you're leaving?
I do have someplace I'm trying to reach.
But I don't know where I'll ultimately end up.
Oh, right.
I'd like you to give this to...
your brother, I suppose.
To Shiroe?
Yeah.
Um...
No, all right.
Okay, off I go.
It's such nice weather, you know.
A little too nice...
Thank you.
Would you call me "big sister" one more time?
Goodbye, big sister!
I love the sound of that!
Sis...
Sister Roe 2...
Goodbye, big sister.
Let's meet again someday, big sister.
Yeah.
Let us meet again, my little brothers and sisters!
She's gone.
I'll be on my way, as well.
I wish I could stay, but...
Someone's come to meet me
at Sanaru, just up the road.
It was fun meeting you all.
I hope we can meet again somewhere, someday.
Yes.
We feel the same way.
Was it really all right to let her go like that?
What do you mean?
Miss Dariella.
Oh...
It's fine.
Okay.
You know, Dariella...
Her nails were all chewed up.
Like she'd bitten them because she was suffering.
Is that so?
You were always watching her, weren't you?
And I'm sure it's because you are
who you are that you were able
to notice her pain.
Do you ever bite your nails, Tohya?
Hmm... No, now that I think of it.
Not since I came here.
I'm glad to hear it.
What, Rudy?
If you want to say something, say it.
Well, Tohya, if something's bothering you,
just come talk to me, Rundel Haus Code.
Talk to you? About what?
About romance.
No, if I were going to ask someone
about that, it wouldn't be you!
What?!
Welcome back, Lady Nureha.
We were worried.
Can we just leave them like this?
Maybe we could stay a little longer
and help with the cleanup.
No, we have the wyvern skins,
and we can get the rest in Akihabara.
We've accomplished our goal,
so we shouldn't stay here too long.
But just leaving doesn't feel right...
Don't worry.
This is an important stop on the Red Road.
It'll be back up in no time.
Well, now that you mention it,
the people don't seem that upset.
They're used to this stuff.
For better or worse...
But I don't think having more people can hurt.
If we can help a little...
No, it's really okay.
Help will come from the neighboring towns.
And, well...
Sometimes, it's better to not
have any outsiders around...
Are you trying to be nice, Rudy?
Like, we should leave the People of the
Land's problems to them or something?
Anyway, there's no need to worry!
They'll be just fine on their own.
Well, if you say so.
Yeah.
Don't you think it was fate
that brought us together?
What? Does he think he's hitting on us?
Isn't he creepy?
Would you please become my beautiful bride?
What burger should we have today?
Or should we have rice balls?
Is that what we're doing for lunch again?
That's right.
We also need to decide where we'll
get delivery from for dinner.
Well, there's nothing wrong with eating out,
but since Nyanta left, are we really
getting enough nutrition?
If my skin gets ruined,
fans all over the galaxy will go crazy
and cause another Big Bang!
If you have time to talk nonsense,
why don't you make something yourself?
That's right.
Akatsuki and I both gave it a try.
A try.
An idol isn't allowed to make anything but sweets!
What the heck?
Hey, are you okay?
What's wrong?
Are you sick?
It's nothing.
Jeez, he must've been jealous of the obvious
romance between me and Naotsugu.
I've been thinking...
Haven't there been a lot more
people like that around?
Yeah, you're right.
It reminds me of when we
first came to this world.
At first, there was so much confusion,
and then everyone just sat around,
unable to do anything.
Wait a second, it's only a coincidence.
Look, there are happy people like that, too!
You're overthinking it. Really!
You may look like you only think about panties,
but you're actually really delicate,
aren't you, Naotsugu?
What?
Hey, are you going to ignore that?
She just said pan—
Ow...
What's with them?
I'm overthinking it, huh?
I hope so.
But if the same sense of apathy
is overcoming Akihabara...
It might be worse than last time.
Eat Grass
This world tried to do something to me that
I didn't want, regardless of my feelings.
So I'm going to do what I want to it.
So Londark was talking like that...
There are more and more adventurers
who can't adapt to this world
and are getting angry.
But there are people who
can't adapt to this society.
Are we just going to abandon them?
And adventurers like that are working with
People of the Land who want to start wars.
Sometimes, adventurers even
encourage them to do so.
A war, huh?
I didn't think it would happen.
Not between adventurers, at least.
But if the People of the Land
get involved, things change.
War has always been a part of their lives.
Unlike us, who were born in peaceful Japan.
And once one starts, will we be able
to continue to stay out of it?
Oh, damn it!
If this were a quest, there'd be no problem.
Even if it were a fight, I can handle monsters.
But...
If a war starts between
People of the Land and adventurers,
or among adventurers themselves,
what can the current Round Table do?
It hurts not having Crusty here.
I hope something comes of what I asked of Isaac...
Hey!
Make them run faster!
They're pathetic, giving up so easily.
It can't be helped.
People of the Land don't have that much stamina.
The villain gave me the most boring jo—
H-Hey...
Work harder!
Isaac?
Sir Isaac!
Sir Isaac...
But why was Sara kidnapped?
Hatred, I guess. The unjustified kind.
Hatred?
That Camus guy is no good.
Supposedly, he's a People of the Land merchant.
But he keeps hitting on every girl he sees.
My, he hasn't hit on me.
Anyway, he came after us, too.
Would you please become my beautiful bride?
He was creepy, so we ran away.
But I guess another girl from
our guild rejected him before,
and he's holding a grudge.
There he is!
Isn't Sara acting weird?
She looks more like she's been
seduced than kidnapped.
No way.
Either way, he's no good!
Kurinon...
Bastard! What have you done to Sara?!
Would you please become my beautiful...
Heck, no!
Camus /Traveling Merchant
Sara /Maid
Kurinon /Priest, Lv. 91
Genius of Marriage
Camaysar /Genius, Lv. 83
Rank /Party
The genius...
...of marriage?
Gotcha.
Sara!
It's okay, she's just knocked out.
Fate must have brought us together.
You want to get hit again, huh?!
Would you please become my beautiful bride?
I will...
No way! Not Kurinon!
Be careful!
It looks like he's using some kind of strange skill!
Souji!
Sou!
I suppose these weirdos
are showing up now because the
defensive barrier is gone.
I won't let you deceive these girls!
Would you please become my beautiful bride?
How dare you say that to Sou?!
Oh, my! You're into that sort of thing?
There's a lot to carry!
In times like these, I wish we had a magic bag...
Well, this is all stuff to make a magic bag.
I think you did great, Tohya.
When you were talking with that knight...
Is it that important
whether you can die or not?
Have you ever died?
Did you ever die in the old world?
You told him exactly how you felt.
But I couldn't make him understand.
That isn't true!
Even if he doesn't understand yet,
he won't forget it!
I think there's meaning in the fact
that you were able to say it.
Everyone's so amazing.
Minori, Tohya, Isuzu...
Even Rudy, maybe.
Everyone seems like they're
really doing the right thing.
So are you, Serara.
No...
On this journey, I realized that
I have a long way to go...
I'm glad I understood that, I think.
We're going to have to walk home...
You okay, Miss Isuzu?
There...
I'm fine.
It isn't as far as I thought.
Shall we ask the people around here if
they need any of the stuff we don't?
It might be better than throwing it away...
It's strange.
I thought they would protect us.
But they were useless.
Some heroes...
In the end, they're just adventurers.
They don't care about us.
No, Isuzu!
They aren't talking about you!
Yeah.
They're talking about those knights, aren't they?
But...
I understand why you wanted to get
us out of here as soon as possible.
I think a lot of people's lives were saved
because the knights were here.
But there are some people who feel betrayed
because they got their hopes up.
Yeah, we're also adventurers.
We might be blamed for that.
I'm sorry.
It's not something you need to apologize for.
And I'm really glad we came here.
All the things that were bothering
me seem so small now.
So I wanted to do something for this town.
I wanted to leave something for them.
You gave them a forty-three..
A new song that never existed in this world.
That song... It's hope! Hope!
Thank you, Rudy.
But if it doesn't remain here, then...
Our journey's over, isn't it?
Yeah.
Is something wrong?
A song?
You're right! That song!
Those kids...
It's still here.
You made a new song.
And now, that song will become
a new hope for those kids.
They're singing Isuzu's song over there, too!
This is as far as we were able to come, but...
Yes, but this song...
It'll go farther west.
It will spread out around the whole world!
And it'll give everyone the
most important thing: hope.
A griffon?
Meow.
Nyanta!
Chief!
It'd been so long since we'd seen Akihabara.
And the city and everyone's smiles
seemed so bright, so hopeful.
I felt my whole body relaxing.
All the tension just disappeared...
Cheers!
Yes... We've always been protected
here, by these people.
I remembered that again.
Afterward, everyone else and I fell asleep,
though we don't remember when.
But I remember Roe 2 appeared in my dreams.
Even in my dream, she was a mystery.
Unknown monsters, the Geniuses,
sneak into Akihabara to cause chaos.
Who are they?
The letter from Roe 2 holds
the key to that mystery.
There is still something in this world that
Shiroe and the others know nothing of.
The People of the Land, the adventurers, and...
Next time: Stranger.
Stranger
I have friends to run with me.