It is the turn of the 20th century.
The Kingdom of Albion's new royal air force,
commonly known as the Air Fleet,
has created a dramatic shift
in the balance of global power.
With its monopoly on Cavorite,
and the Air Fleet at its command,
the Kingdom of Albion became
the greatest world power since the Roman Empire.
However,
revolution split the kingdom into East and West,
with the London Wall separating the Kingdom of Albion
from the Commonwealth of Albion.
Ten years later, London became the front line
of a secret war fought between the nations' spies.
Wh-who are you?
Just a passing extraterrestrial.
What?
I am from the Black Lizard Planet.
If you're going to joke, do it somewhere else!
I'm not joking.
I'm just lying.
There he is!
Is that... Cavorite?
Impossible... at that size...
Um...
Incoming. One vehicle!
Okay, we're out of here.
They were ready for us.
Who are you people?
We're under orders to keep you safe
until you find asylum in the West.
Then... you're with the Commonwealth?
Hm? Didn't you tell him, Ange?
I did.
I told him we're from the Black Lizard Planet.
You mean we're spies!
Are you spies always doing this kind of thing?
Well, sometimes.
Refrigeration complete.
We'll use it when we get out of here.
Understood.
Welcome back.
Thanks.
Now then...
We've shaken them off. Ready to go back?
Back?
Back where?
To the perfect place to hide you.
So I found an envelope in my bag.
An envelope?
Yup. I was so afraid my cover was blown,
but then I saw the flower on it.
Flower?
New orders, right?
You workaholic! Try to enjoy being a student.
So? Who was it from?
Lord Rupert's second son.
It said to meet him behind the gymnasium after school.
A challenge to a duel?
It was a love letter!
Um.
Where are we?
At school.
A very formal and prestigious academy.
Members of the royal family go here.
Why did we come here?
"Why"?
Because we're students here.
Welcome back, everyone.
Oh, are you the defector?
Pleased to meet you. I am-
I know!
Everyone in the Kingdom knows...
You can't mean... you're a spy, too?
Princess?
Yes, I am a spy.
Our Principal Team has secured asylum seeker E.
They are currently hiding him at
Queen's Mayfaire Academy.
What a waste.
The Princess should be used for more important things.
What about the Wall Team?
This is the shift schedule.
Tell both teams.
They'll cross the Wall next Thursday.
Good morning!
Is our school that fascinating?
Oh, sorry. I shouldn't let anyone see me, should I?
If you know that, then be careful.
An omelet?
It's the only thing I can make.
That's okay, I like them. Thank you.
Mm, delicious!
We're coordinating a date for your crossing.
You'll be staying here until it's decided.
Why...
Why would a girl like you be a spy?
When I was born, the word "spy"
was written on my forehead.
Are all the lies because you're a spy, too?
The truth wouldn't be very interesting.
What's that?
A chamber pot.
What?!
That?
Oh.
Another lie?
Tell me if there's anything else you need.
I'll get you anything I can.
Even a person?
Can you get me a person?
He wants his little sister?
It's not like getting opera tickets.
You can't just say,
"I'd like to add one more to the party."
Do you think he will threaten not to defect without her?
He already did.
That's that, then!
Defectors to the West, party of two!
You make it sound so easy.
What do we do, Ange?
What do you suppose they're talking about?
Their escorts for the soiree?
Oooh!
Drug Eric and carry him over the Wall alone.
Aww, but...
Good idea. We shouldn't take the risk.
Are you sure we couldn't let them
defect together anyway?
I mean, it would be so sad to tear them apart.
Princess, I understand how you feel, but-
I'll gather intel.
I'll find the sister and figure out
whether she wants to defect.
And I'll get more info on Eric.
Come on, Ange...
We still have four days until Thursday.
Oh, good!
Thank you, Ange!
So Eric's little sister is in the hospital up ahead?
Yes. And we had to shake off some pursuers last night,
so there might be an ambush, too.
Brother?
Why didn't you come yesterday?
Hello. You must be Miss Amy.
Who are you?
I came to deliver some flowers from Eric Anderson.
Flowers?
Oh, yes!
See? They're very pretty!
Is he a relative of yours?
What do you really want?
I know you're lying!
Those aren't from my brother!
Cavorite poisoning?
Who are you?!
How dare you use my brother's name to trick me!
My brother is all I have left!
Get out of my sight! Get out!
Apparently Miss Amy was in a Cavorite accident.
And it's going to take rather a lot of money
to pay for an operation.
Why don't you go on back without me?
What are you going to do?
Go back to the Black Lizard Planet?
I'm getting insurance. Just in case.
An insurance office?
Yes, Miss.
I can never tell how much of what she says is true.
I don't think she knows, either.
What?
But some lies become truth in the telling.
I don't believe this.
Now I have to forge documents for two people.
There's no helping it.
Dorothy! What are you writing?
An essay of apology. Do you girls want to help?
We'll pass.
See you at the match next week.
That was a bold move.
It's best not to sneak around with these things.
I see Ange isn't the only one with a knack for lying.
Spies are all liars.
You're lying to me now, Chise.
As are you.
So what do you say we try
being honest with each other?
The idea has its charm.
But if we stopped lying,
we wouldn't be able to stay friends.
Is that really friendship?
Even parents and children lie to each other.
Ange?
Your sister's operation. Is that why you're defecting?
So you saw her.
You met Amy.
She said she didn't want any flowers
and chased us out.
Since the accident, it's like she's a different person.
Until then, she was a nice girl, always smiling.
But now... You'll need money for the operation.
Ten years' salary.
There's no way I can afford it.
But then, a man I'd never met paid me a visit.
He said that if I defected to the Commonwealth
with my research, he would give me the money.
The timing is just too perfect, isn't it?
Tell me, Ange.
Was my sister really in an accident?
If I weren't a scientist, would my sister
have been spared this suffering?
Spies are told only what they need to know,
so I can't deny that possibility.
Spies aren't champions of justice, after all.
So NOW you're being honest.
Even if it was a lie,
I wish you'd tell me it was an accident.
So... would you like to go outside?
The stars are so beautiful here.
Yes.
Do you hate me?
Why?
I betrayed my research team for money.
You care about your family.
I understand.
I had a family, too.
"Had"?
I watched as my parents were murdered.
During the London Revolution.
That's...
Don't worry. I was only seven, but I didn't go hungry.
Because the Intelligence Agency took me in.
Ange...
No.
Never mind.
Oh.
Don't let it bother you.
It was back on the Black Lizard Planet.
Of course.
Eric.
We'll be taking you over the Wall next Thursday.
Good night.
The man being kept at Mayfaire
has revealed his true colors.
Switch to Plan B.
Wait, Ange!
Where are we going at this hour?
There's been a change of plans.
We're leaving now.
We can't! It's too sudden!
What about Amy?
There's nothing to worry about.
Hurry and get in.
Team 2 to HQ.
No changes yet.
Understood. Carry on.
Do you think we'll spot them?
I've told Eric to refuse to defect
unless his sister goes with him.
Damn. Those blasted ninja.
Kill the underlings if you want to,
but leave one of them alive.
The Duke of Normandy's orders
are to get their escape route.
Did they go to get Amy?
No.
She's not coming.
You tricked me?
That makes two of us.
The one you really went to for help with
Amy's treatment was the Duke of Normandy.
Your defection was all an act
to lure us out of hiding.
This is Headquarters.
The target has vanished!
They're asking for reinforcements.
What?!
Give me that!
What happened?
Uh, well, we took our eyes
off of them for a second, and...
You fools!
Leave someone to keep watch and go find them!
Don't shoot!
You serve Kimble.
I have business with your employer.
I request an audience.
What the hell is going on here?
We received a report from A,
and made a change of plans.
We have mounted an attack
against Normandy's ambush.
I guess that's the end of the Duke's hounds.
It always bothered me. Why didn't you say from
the start that you would only defect with your sister?
But then I saw Amy, and it made sense.
She had the feet of a ballet dancer.
Feet don't get like that without a lot of practice.
I remembered that when I met you,
you dropped your bag.
and I saw an acceptance letter
from the Royal Ballet fall out.
That's when I connected the dots.
You weren't going to make your sister defect.
You! Go look outside!
You!
How did you get in here?
Public Security Minister Kimble, I presume?
Our boss has some questions for you.
We're all done here.
Understood.
Nice work, everyone.
Well, we'd better head back, too.
This is our last stop.
That gun's not loaded.
You're not cut out for spy work.
Now I can't defect OR go back to my laboratory.
And your sister will never be cured.
On the Black Lizard Planet,
we get someone's signature before we kill them.
I'd expect as much from someone
who watched her family's murder.
That was just another lie to get you off your guard.
Then was it a lie that your omelets tasted so good?
A lie, yes.
I bought them.
And that the stars were so beautiful?
Probably a lie.
Are you going to kill me?
No.
It says they found Eric's body in the Thames.
Why did it take an entire week?
Because if you die immediately after signing up,
the insurance company won't pay.
You're very well-informed, Your Highness.
You're so kind, Ange.
No.
I'm not kind.
Liar.