There should be another assault!
Don't let your guard down!
Izuru!
What's wrong? Izuru, are you all right?
This is Red 5. I just... I just...
What the heck did you just do?!
What happened?
I just saw something disturbing.
What?!
What's that?
Like what? Was it a ghostie?
Right! I need to give pursuit.
What gives? Why isn't it moving?
What's going on, Izuru?
What did you see?
During battle, I-
Red 5, you are prohibited
from further communication.
You must not tell anyone about
what you just witnessed.
Upon your return, come
report to me immediately.
Yes, Ma'am.
Izuru, what happened?!
Respond, Izuru!
It's working?
What's wrong with him now?
Maybe he got an owie?
His unit may have taken some
damage, but Izuru is fine.
Hey, look!
All of the enemy vessels are
pulling out of the battle zone?
Does that mean we won?
Yay!
We won! We won!
But why? They had victory
in their grasp...
That was a piece of cake! Yay!
"Disclosure"
The entire enemy fleet is retreating!
We will begin accepting
injured onto our ship!
What should we do?
Commence a running fight?
If we could, I would have
issued the orders already!
The tactical heavy laser system
has been damaged beyond repair!
I am unable to reach the
squad that was guarding it.
The convoy vessel, Stout,
is requesting help.
Likewise, the convoy vessel,
Shiloh, is also requesting help.
We're also receiving distress signals
from ships in the first and second
lines of defense that are unable to move.
Earth's GDF Headquarters
are still on the line.
They would like a
detailed damage report.
Purple 2 has boarded!
Both the unit and pilot are unharmed.
Welcome back, Miss. You did wonderful.
Kei!
Are you okay? Kei!
Hang in there!
I-I'm sorry...
Calm down, Kei. The battle is over now.
We're glad to see you made
it back safe and sound.
Team Rabbits fought valiantly out there.
We're all very proud of you.
Now leave the rest to us
and try to take it easy.
Where is Red 5?
Has Izuru made it back yet?
I don't know.
I haven't heard one way or the other.
Did something happen to Red 5?
Doberman and Rabbits are the
only squads that didn't
suffer any casualties.
For them to survive that battle
royal essentially unscathed,
their units must be something else!
No kiddin'!
We're the ones who assembled these
puppies and kept them up an' running!
There's no way the
Wulgaru could touch 'em!
Right. We owe it all to you.
Thank you for-
Ow!
That's not what you should
be saying, you lame pilot!
Wha-?!
Was that the best you could do?!
Watching you pissed me off!
Well, excuse me!
Man, you suck!
Next time you're gonna get shot
down and die if you keep this up!
If that doesn't sit well
if you, train harder to-
Hey! Watch what you say!
But it's all true!
Let go of me, Papa! Let go, dammit!
I'm sorry about that
foul mouth of hers.
There's no reason to hold me back!
She must have inherited it from my wife.
Just you wait, you...!
You...! You little...!
Believe it or not, she
was worried about you.
Please don't hold it against her.
I'll get you, dammit!
It-it's fine. After all, she's right...
You lame pilot!
They sure did a number on you!
But in a way, you were lucky.
If it had gone any deeper, that would
have been the end of you, Icchan.
Icchan?
It doesn't look like your transmission
cables or drives got damaged.
Are you sure that it suddenly
stopped responding to your orders?
Yes. When I tried to pursue an
enemy unit, it wouldn't budge.
Which means it must have
been the JURIA-SYSTEM.
That's the only explanation
I can come up with.
So the AHSMB tried to defend itself?
Looks like it's gonna take a while
for you to tame this bunking bronco.
That means I still haven't
mastered my unit, doesn't it?
You got into a dogfight
with the enemy, right?
What was he like?
Could you see his face?
Or what he looked like?
Well, uh...
Okay, okay, stop! That's
enough chit-chat.
Isn't the captain waiting?
You'd better run.
R-right!
Anyway, please take good
care of my unit for me.
And then the enemy showed himself to me.
I was surprised to see
that he looked human.
He looked just like that
lady I met at the pool.
At the pool?
Right.
We aren't supposed to
remember our pasts,
but for some odd reason,
I remembered her.
And then-
That's enough.
You may not mention this
to anyone henceforth, not even
the members of Team Rabbits.
I've always found it strange!
Who was that lady?
Why is she the only person I remember?
Instructor, do you know what she-
I am no longer your instructor.
I'm your captain.
I will issue further orders later.
You may leave.
But-
You are dismissed!
I need to report to the commander...
"This duel was amusing."
"Let us fight again,
primitive creature!"
In other words, he has identified
Red 5 as his target?
Most likely.
I never expected this to happen...
Now that it has come to this,
I believe it is necessary to enlighten
Team Rabbits of the situation,
at least to a certain degree.
It is quite likely that the
Wulgaru will go after them.
We must psychologically prepare
them for what is to come,
although I consider
doing so most cruel...
Are you worried about that young man?
That is a given.
He may have forgotten about
me, but I still remember him.
If only I could see that
he is indeed well...
You may go near the
exam room if you like.
Of course, you will not be permitted
to speak with him directly.
Why do you always hang out in my room?!
Go sleep in your own rooms!
I'm too excited to sleep!
When I'm by myself, I keep
thinking about that battle.
Besides, we can see all of the
returning ally ships from this room.
We were beaten like dogs, didn't we?
What?! But didn't we win?
The Wulgaru ran away!
I don't know why, but it's true
that the enemy pulled back.
Regardless, Earth suffered
far heavier losses.
Forty percent...
...of our forces were
literally annihilated.
Hey, something smells really good!
I lit an aroma candle.
I heard they can have
soothing properties.
Yeah?
I wonder what's keeping Izuru...
I bet quarantine is taking a while.
After all, they said his
cockpit got torn wide open.
Can't sleep?
"Lame pilot."
That's what I got called...
by a member of my pit crew.
If I had done a better
job issuing orders,
the battle may have gone better.
If someone else had been the leader...
If it had been him...
Just maybe, more lives...
You're overthinking things!
I doubt anyone could have done better.
There is no way I could have handled it.
Um, I'm not really sure how to put it,
but I felt like I could
rely on you back there!
Those words held a drop of salvation...
He really is taking forever.
He's in the exam room,
right? I'll check on him!
They probably won't let you in!
I'll check anyway!
Izuru!
Thank goodness!
Where have you been? What happened?
Is something the matter?
Hey, say something!
K-Kei!
S-sorry.
Why...?
Wait!
Izuru!
Why? What is she doing here?
Please wait! Who are you?
Let's go back. Please hurry!
What's going on?
Izuru, not gonna eat that?
Huh? Nah, I'm not hungry.
Then I'll take it!
The food is the only thing
that's leveled up since
we've moved to this base!
Hey, what's going on?
Huh? In regard to? It's so good!
That's what I'd like to know!
You two've been acting
strange since last night.
What the heck happened?
They're all dead? That's horrible.
I bet it'll take a while
to regroup our forces.
Looks like we'll be
abandoning Ceres Base.
Apparently the higher-ups have
absolutely no idea what to do next.
What is going to happen to us?
The big wigs are already pointing
their fingers at each other.
It won't be long before this base
is overridden with injured soldiers.
If they strike again now...
We wouldn't last a minute.
What's wrong? You look so glum!
It's the lunch lady!
What are you doing here?
Did you come after me?
Dang, that's awe-
I got reassigned shortly after you left.
They said that this base
was a bit understaffed.
I know it's been crazy
since you arrived,
but don't let one lost battle
get you down in the dumps!
You're the heroes who
saved Earth, you know.
We're heroes?
We are?
That's what the news keeps calling you.
Yesterday's battle was a
huge victory for Earth!
It says that Team Rabbits
is a group of young heroes
who magnificently repelled
the flood of enemy ships!
Really? So we were a big help after all!
This is just a repeat of last time!
They need to throw out some
heroes whenever we lose.
Like I said, don't look so glum!
Come on, Asagi! You ought to eat more.
Want me to bring you seconds?
No, my stomach is starting
to hurt again...
May we join you?
Uh, sure. Feel free.
Aren't you the operators...?
I am Communications Manager
Siegfried von Westernach.
I'm Guiliano Visconti.
Hey, where is my milk?
Oh, sorry!
R-right! Just one moment please.
I can't handle second tier studs!
Excuse me for being third tier!
Sorry for interrupting your meal.
We always talk over the monitor,
so we were hoping to
speak with you in person.
Okay! I love octopus and squid,
especially their pickled innards!
How long do you expect it to
take to reorganize the fleet?
I couldn't say.
As it stands now, we don't even know
the exact scale of our losses.
But not all of the news is bad!
We learned that your AHSMB
units are able to fight
on par with the enemy.
I imagine we'll build upon your
AHSMB team and regroup around that.
But if you flip it around,
the AHSMB units were the only
thing doing any damage, right?
Now, now.
They should already be working on
increasing AHSMB unit production.
Although even we aren't
privy to the details.
Tamaki, this is important!
Are you paying attention?
I-I can't pick one at
the drop of a hat!
I can't, I can't, I can't! I just can't!
You've got your hands full, don't you?
Huh?
How about I treat everyone to dessert?
Please order anything you like!
Then I'll take a space-sized
Star Rose Parfait!
FRUIT PARFAIT: LIMITED TIME ONLY
STAR ROSE PARFAIT: SPACE SIZE
That was fast...
Everyone from Team Rabbits!
I've got a message
from Captain Suzukaze!
For all of us?
Eh?! But I was just
about to have dessert!
She needs you pronto!
Team Rabbits is to meet in
Operating Room No. 7 immediately.
That's all!
At ease!
As you are aware, the GDF suffered
heavy losses in the Battle of Ceres.
Henceforth, I imagine the AHSMB
teams, starting with Team Rabbits,
will be sent on an increasing
number of missions.
In preparation for the upcoming battles,
I have decided to divulge certain
information with you in advance.
However, everything said here is of
the utmost confidential of nature.
If you tell anyone...
We'll meet the firing squad?!
I'll start with this video.
Wasn't I supposed to keep this a secret?
We'll go over it in a bit.
What the heck? We're fighting humans?
He's saying something to Izuru...!
He isn't human.
He may resemble us, but he is
a completely different species.
He looks damn nasty!
Really? I think he's cool.
He's the enemy! The enemy!
Do you like anyone that looks cool?
I wouldn't say that...
But you might be right!
Is this what you were referring to?
It's not just his appearance.
His fighter moves a lot
like our AHSMB units.
Exactly! Our AHSMBs
utilize their technology.
Once, two pieces of information were
leaked through a certain route.
The first was that the Wulgaru
were preparing to invade Earth.
The second was the basic technology
behind the AHSMB units.
That was the intel.
The AHSMBs that Team Rabbits currently
pilot were developed using
that leaked technology.
So we've been piloting Wulgaru fighters?
Their basic plans may hail
from Wulgaru origins,
but we are the ones who adapted
them for human pilots.
The JURIA-SYSTEM was also developed
by a member of the MJP.
Excuse me...
How did that leaked information
get to Earth to begin with?
How did we find out
that the Wulgaru were
after Earth and learn
how the AHSMB work?
A Wulgaru defector delivered
the information to Earth.
A defector...?
I will let her explain
the situation in detail.
It's you...!
So we meet again.
"The Hunter and the Hunted"