Bubaigawara Station
Where is Mashima-senpai going?
Cram school?  Part-time job?
Is he meeting with someone?
I want to know everything...
Cultural Center
Shiranami
Karuta
Society
Practice
Room
More karuta...
Chihaya Furu
Verse 2
As My
Love
First
Came
Oh?
We never see you here on weekdays.
Yes, I guess.
Then you'll be playing...
Uh, can I play Tsuboguchi-san?
It's fraud!
Total fraud!
Public schools are supposed to be co-ed,
but they added classes aimed at boys
and now it's almost a boys' school!
Tsuboguchi-kun got a job
as a high school teacher,
but there are only eight
girls in his grade.
I should have stayed in
school another year...
You don't want to stay
in school too long.
That's the one area where
you can beat Master Suo.
Bastard!
Please be my opponent
for the first round.
What are they doing?
You have 15 minutes to
memorize the positioning
of the 50 cards on the field.
Are they really memorizing
the positions?!
No, no way!
There aren't any pictures, just words!
Plus, the cards on the other
side are upside-down!
Let's begin.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms.
As my love first came to realization,
How do they move so fast?!
Right, she said something
about unique syllables.
Wait, we have to memorize the
poems and their unique syllables?
The night breaks to day,
and day turns to night,
I don't get it.
Why is someone like him...
playing karuta?
He's good.
He's making a totally one-sided attack.
And he's aggressive about sending cards.
I'm moving a card.
I have to memorize the positions again!
I'm moving another card.
I want to be stronger!
A house left...
I want to make every second count!
What's the matter?
Are you watching them play?
Perhaps you're interested in joining.
No, um...
We don't want to distract the
players, so let's talk over there.
No, th-that's not it!
W-Wait!
Wh-What's so fun about karuta?
Huh?
That's something you can't
know until you've tried it.
Obviously
And you still won't
understand after you play.
I've been playing for 45 years
and I still don't understand.
Huh?
I've never been able to figure it out.
That's why I keep playing.
No way.
Chihaya, help me clear the table.
Okay!
Say, what are you working on over there?
Look.
Isn't it nice?
Huh?  Oh...
I'm home!
Oh, Sis is back!
Hey, look at this!
Isn't it nice?
That's awful.
Chihaya-chan?
You're early.
What are you doing?
Oh, you always come early to
clean up the room, right?
I thought I should help out.
Sorry about not noticing sooner.
It's okay, Chihaya-chan!
I only clean when I notice it's needed.
Well, I just realized that I've only
done quick, easy cleanups...
It's okay.  It's okay.
Use dry paper towels
to wipe tatami mats!
Or a rag that's been wrung dry!
Never underestimate the
damage water can do!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
If you want to help clean,
I'll teach you the basics!
Okay.
We're out of time.
The first-years are arriving!
Yes, ma'am!
Take care of your own
responsibilities, first!
I'm going!
New T-Shirts
Victory or Bust           Mizusawa Power
National Number One       World Number One
Shock!
We lost so many!
Is it because I got carried away and took
all 100 cards during the Genpei match?
Everyone wants to use this
one week trial period
to check out the other clubs.
Yep, yep.
It's so hard...
I want them to know
how fun karuta is,
but it's so hard...
Hanano-san?  What's wrong?
What?  Are you thinking
about the karuta club?
Oh.  Nah.
Of course not.
Mashima-senpai won't be there today.
I'm moving on to another target.
Tajima-kun in class 2 is pretty cool.
So you weren't that serious
about Mashima-senpai?
We were just going with the flow.
He's cute, but...
I didn't think karuta would be so intense.
I don't want to work that hard.
Yeah, no kidding.
We've only been friends a few days,
and we're already out of
things to talk about.
Is this what high school will
be like if I don't join a club?
Scary...
I need to find a new boyfriend fast.
I can't waste time worrying about
finding the hottest guy in school.
So the flower has wilted...
Huh?  What?
No, it's nothing.
From: Kazuki
Subject: (none)
Yo!  How you doing?
Wanna meet up if you're free?
What's wrong with this guy?!
He's the one who dumped me,
and now he's asking me out
without a single apology?!
I understand your true nature now!
I've never been able to figure it out.
I would rather choose the
girl I devote myself to.
I want to understand...
Shock!
What?  There was only one left?
This is the last new member, um...
I'm Tsukuba from class 1-10.
Right, Tsukuba-kun.
He was the only one left,
so I brought him here.
I-It's not your fault.
This is what happens when you take
Mashima out of the equation.
Sorry, guys...
I'm sure it would have been the
same if any of us taught them.
I'm sorry...
We were going to make our
school a karuta powerhouse...
It's okay.  None of us were
dreaming that big.
This is why I didn't want
to let Chihaya teach them.
I feel so bad for the cards.
They don't get to make more friends.
Um, nobody was in the classroom...
Are we in here today?
Thank you for coming, Hanano-san!
Thank you!
This is terrific!
Terrific!
Well, you first-years are probably
still learning the ropes,
but would you be up for a casual match?
Sounds like a good idea.
Hanano-san.
Your nails are a little long.
I have clippers here.
Huh?
I'm not gonna clip my nails.
I work hard to keep them nice.
But you could injure your
opponent if you hit their hand.
It's okay.
I won't be trying that hard.
W-Well, they won't be moving
that fast, at first.
Just give it a shot for now.
Yeah.
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter...
Here comes spring, now the flower blooms.
Oh, no!
Hold on!
I think I might have panda eyes!
Yikes!
Come with me, Hanano-san!
Ka-Kana-chan?!
Are the girls going to be okay?
Just let them be.
It's never a good idea
for guys to butt in.
They can be scary.
U-Uh...  Tsukuba-kun, is it?
Sorry about all these hiccups.
Have you learned the cards yet?
Uh...  I only know twenty or so.
Oh, really?
You can take your time.
Still...
I'm good.
What's wrong with you, Hanano-san?!
What do you mean?
I'm making sure I look good.
A woman must always move with grace.
I can see that—
Why shouldn't I make myself pretty?
Hanano-san—
I need to look nice if I want a boyfriend.
It's vulgar and foolish to spend
all your time thinking about love!
What?
Isn't Hundred Poets just
a bunch of love poems?
Humans have always spent
a lot of time on love.
I'm not too interested in karuta,
but I'm willing to work hard for love.
Just so you know, I'm
after Mashima-senpai!
Th-This won't work...
She's seriously crazy about love.
Crazy
about
karuta
Hanano-san, you haven't
finished changing yet?
We're supposed to start practice soon.
Sorry.
You don't need makeup when
you're only in high school—
Please, this is just a little mascara.
It's part of my identity now.
She'd fix her mascara
even in a fire
She'd fix her mascara even in a fire...
These are the Hokkaido cards
I mentioned yesterday.
These are cards?
Oh, I was in Hokkaido through middle school.
They're real wood...
This is known as "Second Verse Karuta."
Oh, I've heard of that before.
It's where the reader skips
straight to the second verse.
Huh?  Really?
That's right.
So I've only memorized
the second verses.
Second Verse Karuta is usually
played in the form of
three-on-three team matches.
When I was in Hokkaido, I played all
the time with my three brothers.
My team was undefeated
in local tournaments.
I heard that everyone on the mainland
plays First Verse Karuta,
so I wanted to become
good at that, too.
Like a Master, I think?
That's how good I'll be.
These first-years are a pain.
I-I understand.
You might have been good
at Second Verse Karuta,
but the rules for competitive
karuta are completely different.
I'll give you a thorough
lecture, so take some notes.
Komano-senpai, what's
your rank or grade?
I'm a first grade in Class C.
No thanks then.
Wh-What about Mashima-senpai?
Huh?  I'm in Class B.
Then I want Mashima-senpai to teach me.
Oh, me too!
Forget it.
Let's start practicing.
The first-years can play each other.
But he's experienced, so all the more
reason to start with the basics...
Ayase!
You're not being realistic!
We can't afford to waste
too much energy when
the prelims are coming up!
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter...
I'm going to work really, really hard,
so I get good fast.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms.
I hope this doesn't take long,
since I get to be with
Mashima-senpai on the way home.
The same problems keep cropping up...
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms.
The mood is terrible.
Why is Ayase...
...so focused on the first-years?
The storm will soon carry
me to the afterlife,
Um.  Um.
Which one was that?
so I wish...
Huh?  Tsukuba-kun's left-handed?
None are left who know me
Takasogo pines...
Wait! He's using both hands!
And he's using his left hand to guard!
Yes!
The next one will be mine, too!
Let's go!
He's slamming the floor to
intimidate his opponent.
Forbidden
What should I do?
Second Verse Karuta is
completely different...
I know that my heart is all aflutter
and by no fault of mine
His hand moved straight to the card...
He has strong fingers...
...are wet with dew
So the flower has wilted during the long
spring rains, just as my beauty has faded
I know this one!
Sumire-chan.
Huh?
Trim your nails.
What?
Why?
Did you see how strong
Tsukuba-kun's fingers are?
If you hit him, you'll tear off your nail.
Tear it off?!
Please, I'm not going to
try that hard at karuta—
You will.
You were happy about taking
your first card, right?
You'll start moving faster and
faster to take cards, Sumire-chan.
O-Okay, how about your right hand?
Just trim your right hand.
Wait!
Stop this!
I already said that I joined this
club to be with Mashima-senpai,
not to play karuta!
Oh...
Oh gosh...
I've had enough!
Wait!
Sumire-chan!
Ayase!
Forget it.
She's made it clear that she
doesn't want to play karuta.
Just ignore her.
Ever since I collapsed and had to forfeit
last year during the national championship,
I've spent every day wondering
what would have happened
if we had one more member.
We finally have new members...
Two of them stayed.
I can't ignore them!
Chihaya-chan...
Chihaya-chan!
I-I'll go get her!
Ayase...
You need to calm down.
You can launch yourself
like a catapult.
Did you see how strong
Tsukuba-kun's fingers are?
Ayase-senpai complimented me.
Tsukuba-kun.
I'm in Class A, and I have
the most experience.
Is it okay if I teach you?
Eh...
Only
likes
attractive
people
Don't groan!
You should thank me!
Eh...
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much...
Let's start with the basics, then.
You're only allowed to use one
hand in competitive karuta.
It's against the rules
to use both hands.
Are you right-handed?
I'll show you the proper
right-handed form, so copy me.
Answer me!
Y-Yes, sir!
Move your right leg back.
Bend over a little.
Your head's crossing the line.
Back up.
None of us blamed Ayase
for what happened at the
tournament last year,
because we all knew that she
was the one who hurt the most.
You want to become as good as you were
at Second Verse Karuta, right?!
I want to become a good player.
Okay, I'll make you good!
We finally have new members...
Two of them stayed.
I can't ignore them!
Hanano-san!
Hanano-san, let's go back.
It's okay, so come with me.
No!
I'm so embarrassed.
He knows now...
Mashima-senpai knows how I feel now.
You're probably laughing at me!
You think love is foolish!
If you're here to mock me, go away!
Yesterday, when you said
that Hundred Poets was
a bunch of love poems,
I had to admit you were right.
We share the same feelings
that they did in the past.
However, Hundred Poets
is an anthology of poetry.
Their poems are still known
a thousand years later,
because they expressed their
feelings and techniques
in adherence to the 31 syllables rule.
The feelings expressed are
dependent on the rules!
Do you really think that
the president knows your
true feelings after hearing
that little outburst?
But...
It's okay!
It's okay, so let's go back.
Come with me.
You make it sound so easy...
Hanano-san.
Can you teach me how to put on mascara?
Since I only have three eyelashes...
Also...
I think crying in embarrassment
is a sign of a beautiful soul.
Hey, she's back.
Is everything okay?
We still have some time left.
Up for a match?
Um... Is it okay if...
I do some studying instead
of playing a match?
I haven't memorized
all of the poems yet!
The feelings expressed are
dependent on the rules.