He said he found a master he could serve.
That's why he was leaving the village.
He was my only friend.
He was strong.
He had the strength I tried
so desperately to achieve.
But...
There goes another.
Come on.
This is all ninja are.
We're used as tools before
we're eventually thrown away.
If that's the case...
I will kill so I can live.
I won't expect anything from anyone.
The Heart of the Dragon
You're awake, Saizo?
I just made you some medicine.
Drink this.
What's wrong, Saizo?
I'm done with this.
I've had enough.
What did you say? Are you crazy?
This isn't worth it.
Besides, I've got no obligation
to finish the job.
Then fight to the death with me!
It seems I overestimated you.
Once you accept a job,
whether your mission ends
in success or failure,
your last and most important task
becomes reporting the result.
Is it really so hard for you to admit you
lost Isanami and screwed up the job?
Hey, watch your mouth, old man.
If you want to run, run.
I will make the report.
Nice weather we're having.
I wish I could lie around and stare
at the sky on days like these.
You're always doing that anyway.
How are Saizo and the others doing?
Why haven't they sent word?
Perhaps they haven't reported anything
because there's nothing to report.
Ana, good timing.
Let me rest my head on your thighs.
No, I hate bending my legs.
But that's an order!
Master!
Akeha.
A message? Good work.
What is it?
Are they asking for more money?
Yukimura-sama...
Or have they found...
Looks like that flamboyant little
adventurer has shown himself.
What? What's wrong?
Sasuke, Anastasia.
Let nothing stop you from
rescuing our comrades!
Yes, sir.
Well...
Did you not like the taste?
You haven't told me your name yet.
What's your name?
Didn't anyone teach you to look a
man in the eye when he talks to you?
There.
Now, what's your name?
Isanami.
All right, Isanami,
if there's anything you want, just ask.
I'll give you anything you want.
Oh, but I can't return you to Ueda.
Ueda.
Her hairpin...
Unbelievable.
Let's go, Kojuro.
Sir?
What?
No... Why?
Saizo!
I can't go home...
I've only heard she's
a visitor from Izumo.
What is that hairpin?
It's a treasure.
A treasure called the Kushimitama.
What exactly is this Kushimitama?
Long ago, humans received four powers
to control the land in place of the gods.
That's one of the four.
The Kushimitama has the power
to keep balance in the world.
So you...
Tokugawa's spreading his influence
through the kingdoms, but he won't act.
That's why...
I will use the power of
the gods against them,
and turn this world upside down.
The power of control...
Once it is in my hands,
I can call storms and
bend them to my will.
Wait!
If you do such a thing now,
you may start a war which
will tear the land in two.
A war?
Sounds good to me.
All I want is to cause massive unrest
that will turn our world upside down!
I will become a god,
and rewrite this country's
history from the beginning!
I will go once the moon is hidden.
I'll try to buy you some time.
What are you criminals talking about?
You will not escape!
Iga Ice Technique.
Zekkai!
I will leave them to you.
Roger.
You will not pass.
Now, let's have some fun.
If the treasure is in her hairpin,
is not the girl unnecessary?
True, but where's the fun in that?
Since she's been entrusted
with the Kushimitama,
there must be some
way for us to use her.
Don't you think so?
Won't others come after the treasure?
Not many would be able to get in there.
Isanami.
Sasuke?
Are you all right?
Yeah.
I will save you.
Where are Saizo and Kakei-san?
On their way home.
We received a message.
Sasuke, I...
I'm not going back to Ueda.
It's best if I don't return.
Tell everyone.
That's right.
This is for the best.
Everything that's happened at
Izumo and Ueda has all been my fault.
It's my...
You captured a Sanada ninja?
Ichimaru, Niko.
Oh?
She's a Nanman.
She's quite strong.
Outrageous.
Truly, outrageously large.
Is this your type, Niko?
I prefer the priestess.
No one asked you.
All right, let's give these a feel...
What do you think you're doing?
What are you doing? That's not fair.
Fine! We'll settle this with
rock paper scissors. Come on!
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
Isanami won't go back?
What does she think I'm
distracting them for?
I'm first!
Damn it.
Let's have some fun, lady!
Iga Ice Technique!
Sohyoga!
Wait! I've got something to do first!
Do what?
Oh, right.
There's something I have to do.
Why?
I won't go back to Ueda.
I cannot force her.
She doesn't wish to go.
But I must follow Yukimura-sama's orders.
I have failed.
I can't count on Sasuke for anything.
Ana.
Men are too easy.
Let's go.
You're covered in wounds.
You did this for me.
I won't go back!
Everyone's worried about you.
I...
If I go back, I'll just cause
everyone more trouble.
Isanami.
Do you think you're the pitiful
protagonist of some sad little story?
You don't want to see anyone get hurt,
so you cover your eyes and ears.
Pitying yourself and avoiding pain...
...by closing your eyes is
the easiest way to live.
But I won't let you do that.
You're a brave warrior.
Do you want be someone who
needs protection forever?
Fight!
What will running solve?
Fight? I'm not even strong.
Whatever you might think,
Yukimura-sama accepted you.
He chose you to be one of his warriors.
Are you going to run from that, too?
But there's nothing I can do.
Physical strength isn't everything!
The courage to move
forward is strength, too.
I...
It's all right.
You have great strength...
...in here.
You are a brave warrior.
I'm a warrior...
Ana, Isanami.
Can you stand?
Yeah.
She's right. This is about me.
If I don't want to cry, I have to stand.
Sasuke, sorry about what I said earlier.
Thank you for coming to rescue me.
Isanami.
None of us fear getting hurt.
Not me, not Saizo, not Yukimura-sama.
I won't be afraid either.
I'm a brave warrior.
Let's fight together.
All of us.
They are back.
Looks like you took quite a beating.
Yukimura-sama,
I wish I could report what
happened immediately...
It's fine. Just rest for now.
We'll talk later.
Saizo! Kakei-san!
We've taken care of business.
Don't worry.
Isanami, I'm glad you're all right.
Same to you, Kakei-san.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
Saizo, are you okay? I...
Old man, I'm gonna take a bath.
Saizo...
You're the one who's been following Saizo?
That's right.
Saizo works for me now.
I can't let you fight him.
I see.
If you get in my way, I'll kill you.
Quickly.
That's no fun.
What isn't?
An attack should always
be carried out slowly...
Patiently...
You're not bringing
your prey to the edge,
but rather your own pleasure.
You build it up...
...and release it.
Doesn't that feel much better?
You're amazing, old man!
You can stay here until then.
You won't be bored.
Saizo, have your wounds healed?
If you need anything, let me know.
I want to help you.
I know you've always
protected me until now,
but I've gotten stronger—
Shut up.
Saizo...
I believe in you.
You're smothering me.
What do you want?
What are you doing, you bastard?!
What are you doing?
I am disappointed. You are a coward.
Look who's talking.
You really think you're
strong enough to say that?
No.
I work hard, but you give up.
You cannot protect her.
Protect her?
I hate trying to act like a hero.
Hate? No, you cannot do it.
You cannot accept your weakness.
Enough.
When I am weak, I hone my skills.
This is important.
But you do not admit it.
You cannot admit it.
That is why you cannot do it.
Enough!
You do not understand.
What don't I understand, you monkey?
Ouch...
Damn it...
You will rise numerous times.
We need you.
You can become stronger
for someone else.
For someone else...
I've never heard you
speak so much before.
Y-Yukimura-sama!
So, what are you going to do?
Are you going to rise
up from where you are,
or will you turn away and
live as a toothless dog?
Who do you think I am?!
Cut the shit!
You heard him, Isanami.
Huh?
Sai...
Saizo!
Bastard...
Saizo.
Welcome back!
Yeah.
All right.
Where are you going?
I know what you're thinking.
Then you know how I feel!
He's an admirable man to steal
the treasure back from me.
It's him. It must be him!
He's the only one who can
go toe to toe with me!
I'll have to pay you a visit...
Sanada Yukimura!
Let's hear your report.
There was something
carved into the rock,
but it was too dark to see very clearly.
And we only saw it.
We couldn't read it, and we don't
remember what it looked like.
I could not understand it at all.
That's not a problem. Rokuro.
Yes, sir.
Why's he so close?
Just wait.
What?
Your eye...
Hush.
He's got tons of letters inside his eye.
What are you doing, Saizo?
How should I know?
Let's see.
What is it?
What'd it say, Yukimura-sama?
Old man?
"You cannot pass. Good work."
What?
You've gotta be kidding.
That's what it said.
You've done your job,
now get out of here.
Very well.
Let's go, everyone.
Fine.
Hey, what did that guy do to you?
You talk too much.
What did you say?
You wouldn't have made it back here
if I hadn't caught that snake for you.
What? Saizo, you ate a snake?
What an ironic fate.
Sir.
Don't say it, Rokuro.
I've already taken this on.
I'm not throwing it out.
You and I are the only ones who know.
Don't let anyone touch
that right eye of yours.
Yes, sir.
However, if this is true,
it's far too dangerous.
I know.
Isanami came to my lands,
along with Saizo.
Then there's us...
Whether I'm following or fighting fate,
I'm placing my faith in Saizo.
Hey, Koga monkey!
You'll pay for what you did today.
Where are you going, Master?
Ueda.
Are you going to see Sanada Yukimura?
He managed to steal the treasure from me.
I want to see his face!
You must not go.
Now is an important time for you.
You cannot afford to waste
time on such minor lords.
What's this?
It seems the ladies are
gossiping about me again.
You're blissfully ignorant, aren't you?
The next episode of Brave 10
is "Much Ado About Nothing."
Much Ado About Nothing
Bring it on!