Join forces?
Don't worry, everyone. Everything's fine.
We'll hear you out.
That's right.
We should cooperate together
so we can achieve our goals.
You all want to escape.
I want to become Mom of this House.
I want to drag Isabella down
from her position as Mom,
and seize that position for myself.
Mom's position?
Just to clarify, those are my true intentions.
I also want to break free from this situation.
Do you know about
the management system here?
Girls who fulfill certain conditions
and live until 12 years old
are presented with two paths
when they're about to be shipped.
To continue and die,
or aim to become a Mom.
What are the conditions?
Scores above a certain number
and the Mom's recommendation.
If you can meet these two requirements,
you can survive without escaping.
- If you're a girl.
- A girl...
But I don't recommend it.
Your body will never be able to leave this area.
What is that?
There's a chip inside.
If an adult steps one foot outside of the farm,
an electrical current will be sent through this
and their heart will stop.
At the same time,
if something else makes their heart stop,
then it acts as a transmitter
that notifies the higher-ups.
So we couldn't kill the adults after all.
I can only live inside the farms.
That's why I want to live
the best possible life here.
As a Mom.
Even if it's fake, it's a life for humans.
But to get that, Isabella is in the way.
If you all escape, she will be blamed.
I won't get in your way.
Escape. That will become a benefit for me.
You're not going to ship us out?
I won't.
Let's cooperate!
Let's work together.
Wait.
Let me verify one thing with Sister.
What is it?
What's your guarantee
that you won't betray us?
You won't trust me?
Just answer!
It's Ray.
If Ray tells this to Mom, you can crush me.
But if I tell Mom that Ray's been a double agent,
I can crush him.
That's why neither of us will betray the other.
We can't.
That's fine, right?
Okay.
Then we have a deal.
I'll also share any other information
that only I know about.
It's proof of my friendship.
Why don't you come to my room tonight?
She wants to live the best possible life, huh?
She was even one of us, too.
She doesn't care at all about
the lives of us children!
But she said she won't ship us out.
It's not that she won't. She can't.
If she really wanted us to escape, she just needs
to assist us quietly when the time is right.
She's showing us her cards only because
she wants to gain our trust.
Why does she want our trust?
She wants evidence that shows our rebellion.
In other words, she's in a position
where the higher-ups
won't trust her without reliable evidence.
Unlike Mom, she doesn't have
the authority to ship us out.
Evidence...
Hey, what if she finds
the rope we hid in the tree?
It's fine. We can say various excuses
to explain the rope.
Like we were going to use it to play with. But—
We're doomed if she finds the equipment
that breaks the tracking devices.
That's reliable evidence
that we can't make excuses for.
Don't worry.
I won't make that kind of mistake.
Besides, it's not finished yet.
If we have her believe that we don't know where
the tracking devices are, or how to break it,
there shouldn't be an issue.
I'm sure Sister would believe us
if we play the cards correctly.
Are you really going to go?
You're dealing with that Sister Krone!
It sounds nice that she'll tell us
anything we want to know, but...
Rather, why do we have to
join forces with her?
Does it give us an advantage?
If we use her well,
we might obtain some information.
And that's one less person getting in our way.
Then we can focus on investigation.
It'll be okay.
We have to use every opportunity we can.
Ray, can I talk to you?
I want to discuss the steps
for the investigation.
Sure.
I have a favor to ask you two.
What do you want to know?
Go ahead. Ask me anything.
Really, anything?
Yes. Whether it be about the farm
or about the headquarters...
Then...
Show us that thing.
The tool that receives the signal
from our tracking devices.
Sure. Here.
See? Doesn't it look simple?
It only shows the current location
but can't specify who it is.
So you knew about the tracking devices?
Yes. Mom showed us once.
But I don't know where it is
or how to break it.
Sister, do you know?
Yes. They're located in your ear.
The left ear. Around here.
I don't know how to break them.
But if it breaks, it sends out a signal.
To that thing, and also to headquarters.
You'd have to take it out. Or cut it off.
But there are no decent blades in the House.
There's a scalpel. For medical use.
Once we're outside, there's no medicine.
When we escape, I don't want
to take risks with blood loss or infections.
The infirmary is equipped
with medicine and tools.
Anesthesia, too.
Well, I think there's enough for five kids.
I'll also teach you how to use them,
and I'll lend you the key to get to it.
That's settled. Okay, what else?
Sister, how old are you right now?
Were you livestock ever since you were born?
How rude to ask a grown woman her age...
Is what I'd like to say.
I'm 26. Born and raised at Grace Field.
Just not here at Plant Three.
Plant Three?
By the way, Isabella is 31.
That's what I saw in the records.
And the outside? You've seen it, right?
I haven't.
Oh, did you think I would say yes,
even if it was a lie?
I haven't.
But there are humans outside.
Your food is made
by the higher-ups and us adults.
But there are humans from the outside
who bring your clothes and other supplies.
I saw them at the headquarters once.
Those humans have equal standing with them.
There are humans outside
who haven't been eaten.
You need to get mixed in with them.
Then you don't know how long
the demons have been around?
Demons? Oh, you're talking about them.
Or do you know how
the world came to be this way?
I don't know that.
Where is this House located?
I don't know.
What about the security of this area?
I know about that. There isn't much of it.
They rely on the tracking devices,
so they don't have many guards posted.
I'm sure they don't even patrol.
Thank you.
You're done?
Yes. Good night.
So you already knew the location
of the tracking devices and how to break them?
I'm impressed.
I see. I understand a lot now.
It's not just words that provide information.
Humans give away a lot of information
just by standing there.
Attitude. Gaze. Blinking.
Sweat. Gestures. Pupils. Pulse.
All of these are hints
to find out what you're really thinking.
And yet for you two, even though I said
the tracking device was in your ear,
you didn't touch them to check.
The arrangements to get them out were made,
but you didn't look happy at all.
So, why did you ask about
the tracking devices when it wasn't necessary?
Is there something you want to hide from me?
Are you keeping a secret?
That's fine.
Do you know about Him?
You don't know, right? Do you want to know?
I'll tell you the next time you come here.
Come back anytime.
Let's talk much more than we did today.
Mom.
I see.
There's really nothing shown at first.
So your last reward is a camera, huh?
I was interested
in the phenomenon of photographs.
I've only seen
photographs and cameras in books.
If I were to get greedy,
I would have wanted to develop them myself.
Amazing.
It really looks like
you cut out a moment in time.
Regarding that matter,
is it okay if it's after lunch?
Yes, that's fine.
Well, then.
I think it's about time.
Let's go over the plan.
When we start free time after lunch,
I'll distract Mom.
Norman and Emma will climb the wall
to inspect the vicinity.
Don and Gilda, stay outside where you can see
the south window on the house's second floor.
Just in case I fail to distract Mom,
I'll signal you.
Let Emma and Norman know
to cancel the inspection immediately.
We have six days until the escape, but at least
until January, we have two and a half months
until it's time for me to be shipped out.
So if something happens,
immediately cancel the inspection.
Everything needs to be done secretly.
We need to pretend to be controllable.
Don!
Play with us!
Gilda, you too!
All right! Ready for some tag?
Ray, can we talk?
Sister found out
that we can break the tracking devices?
So I want to move up the escape day.
When can you break the tracking devices?
What was that?
With this, I have all the necessary parts.
I can break them anytime now.
You weirdos.
Shut up!
This is really a double-edged sword.
Will we break the tracking devices
and escape first?
Or will Sister find this evidence first
and turn us in before that?
Don't worry. I've taken care of it.
Say, I wonder why
they pretended not to know?
They knew the location
and how to break the tracking devices.
How did they find out in the first place?
Rather, how will they break it?
Will they use a special tool?
Could they have made such a thing?
Then would that happen to be
the reliable evidence I need?
Is that why they were scared and lied?
If so, then it's time for a search.
Can you put out the plates?
- I'm so hungry.
- Thanks!
Now's my chance!
What are you doing?
I'm cleaning the floors.
- Did you get the forks?
- Can you help me here, too?
Okay.
Found it.
It's true. This really is the truth.
I got it unexpectedly!
Isabella's second weakness!
So how should I go about this?
If I show this note and appeal to Grandma,
I wonder if I can oust Isabella
and obtain the Mom's position?
Then I can ship out the brats
unconditionally, too.
But how... how does Ray know about this?
Even Isabella shouldn't know about this
in the first place.
It's from the headquarters. You should open it.
It's unfortunate, but that's how it is.
Goodbye.