It's not here either.
We may not be able to find it.
Calm down.
I know just what to do.
Yes, this is New Compton waste disposal.
Hello.
I accidentally put something
really important in the garbage,
and it just got picked up.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Goodbye.
W-Wait!
Is there something else?
I told you, it's really important!
When your garbage is picked up,
you lose all rights to it.
Goodbye.
Wait, I said...
Um, uh... I know!
It's important evidence.
I'm Cecil Epps, with the
San-Teresa Metropolitan Police.
I'm a deputy coroner.
Um... if this evidence is lost,
th-the investigation will...
Um... something really bad will happen to it!
So cooperate with the police investigation!
Please, grant me mercy!
Grant me salvation!
O'Neill, I came here to ask you something!
Look at this. It's the tip you gave me.
I need to know more about the guy
you said is working with the smuggler...
The patient is in pain. Stop it.
It's just a hangover.
Hey! Look at this!
Is this the guy who you saw with the smuggler?
If I tell you, will I be able to go to heaven?
In first class?
Yeah. With all the expensive wine
and cognac you can drink!
I never want to drink another drop of alcohol!
Answer me, you hungover asshole!
Detective!
He's hyperventilating!
Mr. O'Neill!
Calm down, Mr. O'Neill! Everything will be fine!
Shit.
He's gone.
Kenny, do you know the girl O'Neill
went on a date with a few days ago?
She may have seen the smuggler.
That would be the SM queen you just saw.
The one in the kitchen.
She had her head stuck in the fridge, right?
Did she?
My name is Cecil Epps.
Well, it looks real to me.
Not that I've never seen one.
So, what's your address, Miss Epps?
172 Caster Street.
Hunter Waste Management handles that area, so...
It's truck number 3. Right over there.
In front of the WCT.
WCT?
The waste disposal terminal.
Everything we collect is dumped in there.
Oh, no!
Wait! Stop! Stop!
Stop it! Stop it!
What?
Oh, jeez!
Tilarna?
Chief, it's me. Matoba.
About Hellmandes with the CBP...
I just got another call from the man.
So you did get in a fight with him.
Just now?
Something about you not picking up the phone,
and whether or not you were at home.
Hey, are you listening, Matoba?
Which means...
Sorry, Chief! I'll call you back!
Cecil?
I'm sorry, Kei...
We need to talk about Tilarna...
What happened?
So Tilarna and Kuroi switched bodies?
Okay. Magic, huh? I believe it.
So right now it's Tilarna,
or rather Kuroi, who's at my house?
--That's dangerous.
--Dangerous?
I need to hurry. Cecil, I'll call you back.
Wait, Kei!
Kuroi's body, here at the dump, is...
I tried to stop her, but...
Don't worry about that.
It's Tilarna, right? So I'm sure she's fine.
Bye.
I found it. There's the cat!
Tilarna!
Smell it. The smell of latena.
Don't use your nose. Use your heart.
There it is!
It's over...
Damn it...
Give me the damn crossbow!
My life is on the line here!
This is...
Thank you, God!
Thank you, God! Thank you, God!
You can't get out of this
by pretending you're crazy--
Don't touch me.
What?
You saw, didn't you?
Saw what?
I don't know what's going on here,
but you're in for a world of pain!
--D-Don't hurt me!
--Shut up!
--I just wanted to make some money...
--I don't care!
Mercy!
No mercy!
Please don't...
You're going to die like a bug,
with no dignity at all...
Curses of Beyadah upon you!
Hey, don't kill him!
That's you, right, Tilarna?
You're back?
Kei?
My life... my life...
What a mess.
Clean this up.
That weird crossbow only activated
because you were careless, right?
Shut up!
What's wrong with you?
This morning I was trying
my best to get your help,
and you left without figuring out a thing!
How was I supposed to know
you'd swapped bodies with Kuroi?
B-But...
Having you all over me dressed like that
first thing in the morning was freaking me out.
I wanted to get out of there.
It was freaking you out?
Huh?
No, nothing...
So what happened to the crossbow?
It was destroyed.
That's why I was able to go back, I think.
There's no way to know now, though.
I guess that's just how it goes.
I need to get better control of myself.
And thanks to you,
I didn't even get to kill that man.
If you did, it would be mur--
Wait...
Did he do something to you?
No! He definitely did not! Not a chance!
He just saw me!
Saw you?
I-It's very important...
What a pain.
What's a pain?
Aren't you mad?
He saw my butt...
No... Anyway, you should be madder!
Why would I?
Shut up! Get a little mad, you rakebye!
Wait a second.
I think I forgot something.
Don't try and change the subject--
Where are Kuroi and Cecil?
I'm sorry, Tilarna...
I couldn't help you!
Tilarna!
Tilarna, I'm sorry!
I couldn't help you!
I don't know what to say to you!
Fifteen years ago, a hyperspace gate
appeared in the middle of the Pacific.
Beyond the gate lay a strange world
filled with fairies and monsters.
Kariaena Island. The city of San-Teresa.
This city is Earth's "front door."
Over two million citizens
from both worlds live here.
A mixture of different races and
diverse cultures, haves and have-nots...
The world's newest "city of dreams."
But in the shadows of all this
chaos lurked countless crimes.
Drugs. Prostitution.
Weapons smuggling.
The San-Teresa Metropolitan Police maintained
a special unit to deal with these crimes.
I think you overcooked it.
Matoba, are you insulting
the Zimmer family recipe?
You're just burning it.
Put it on a tray, lower the heat,
and close the grill.
You need to get that hot air flowing over it.
The meat looked so good, too.
Shut up!
Whenever you talk about food
or cars, you get all obsessed...
You sound like a food snob!
I'm not a snob!
Every snob says that!
And anyway, this is my home.
This food is under my jurisdiction!
Now quit bitching, go to the kitchen,
and get me a beer!
I'm the one who brought the meat
you're ruining, and it was expensive!
Kei, you want to join us?
The water feels great!
Later.
That's a shame.
Ignore him.
He's pretending to be too cool for it.
What's wrong? What's wrong? What's wrong?
Come on, tell your daddy!
Who took the towel off?
Me. Was that a problem?
I was using it as a cover.
You need to make it dark,
or the clams won't spit out the salt.
They spit out the sand already, right?
But not the salt.
Who cares? It's not a big deal.
It is a big deal!
These clams are filled with salt water.
You need them to spit it out
or you can't eat them.
At least... don't put much salt in.
Or actually, don't put any in.
You always get really annoying
about cooking, Kei.
You really seem like a food snob.
I don't want my son to end up like you.
I'm not a snob.
All snobs say that.
San-Teresa City. San-Teresa City...
The mayoral election?
It's a farce. There's nobody worth voting for.
This Kahns guy is the best of the bunch.
Nathan Kahns.
He was mayor of Seattle for two terms.
City councilman here for two years.
He looks like a guy who no girl
wants to date even though he's rich.
Maybe,
but he's had a lot of mayoral experience
and knows what he's talking about.
And he's a lot better than the other two.
My wife and I are voting for this Kahns guy.
Mozeleemay is running too, huh?
Yeah.
I still can't believe that
guy's running for mayor.
There's also the far-right candidate Tourte,
who says the aliens should go back into space.
What?
Breaking news!
--Mayoral candidate Kahns has just been shot!
--Kahns was shot?
Look over there!
They just loaded him into an ambulance.
He's not responding to anything
his team says to him...
Oh, God... I can't believe this is happening.
Oh, God! Oh, God!
The meat's done, Matoba.
Now where's that beer?
What's wrong?
The news is saying...
We're having an emergency briefing.
A candidate for mayor was shot.
The shooter is John Ennaji.
A male Semanian.
32 in Earth years.
Single, works at a convenience store.
No criminal record except
for a few speeding tickets.
Everybody who knows him
says they can't believe it.
No underworld connections, either.
There's no role for the
Special Vice Squad here, but...
Is there a problem?
I read your report. About Rick Fury.
Zelada?
We never found his body.
It wouldn't surprise me at all
if he was still alive.
So is this what you're saying, Chief?
The shooter who killed Kahns
was controlled with magic?
Don't just come out and say it.
We're just covering all the bases. Got it?
I want you and Exedilica to head to
the coroner's office and see what you find, now.
Now? Dressed like this?
Yeah. Now.
I thought it might have been
another controlled corpse, too.
I didn't expect Inspector Zimmer
would pick up on it, though.
He surprises you with
how smart he is sometimes.
I just wanted to go home.
You don't want to catch the guy
who was behind Kahns' death?
I don't want to waste a valuable
weekend avenging a politician.
Kei...
I was kidding.
I've found myself impressed
by Earth's democracy.
I think a system that reflects the people's
wishes in any way at all is a wonderful thing.
And this shooting is a declaration
of war against that system.
That's a nice speech. Or it would be
if you weren't wearing a swimsuit.
Stop staring.
That's why I didn't want to do this.
I don't understand... Are they mocking us?
Forget it.
You in there, Cecil? I'm coming in.
Kei? Wait!
Who are you?
We'll be quick.
Man, it sure is hot today.
The chief was right.
He was dead, and someone manipulated
his body into doing the murder.
Zelada?
I can't be sure.
But this form of magic is particularly rare.
What do we do now?
We tell Chief Zimmer first.
Damn alien.
Hold up.
What did you just say?
Nothing.
Don't lie to me.
What did you just say when you saw her?
I don't know...
I heard it.
You called her a "damn alien."
You insulted my partner.
What made you think that was a good idea?
Officer Sanders...
Sanders, Sanders, Officer Sanders...
You want to tell me why you said that?
I'm sorry.
I asked you a question.
Um, please...
Kei, that's enough.
Officer Sanders, I told you
to answer my question.
Now, do it!
Please!
Please forgive me...
My family is conservative.
We were voting for Kahns...
And, um... after what happened today...
The killer was... from the other world...
So you think she killed Kahns, then.
No.
Then she killed your family, then.
Christ. Do you have a reason
to insult her, then?
Who the hell do you think you are?
Do you act like this towards the citizens, too?
Kei.
That's enough. Let's go.
But...
It's fine. Let's go.
That was embarrassing.
I wish you wouldn't do that.
Sorry.
But thank you.
I didn't do it because I wanted a thank you.
He just made me mad.
I thought you'd say that.
You call people "aliens" all the time, anyway.
When I do, it's...
It's like a joke.
It's like when a gangster calls his
girlfriend a bitch trying to look cool.
But if somebody else calls her a bitch,
he gets mad. It's like that.
I'm not your woman.
Of course not. It was an example. Sheesh.
Just forget it.
Okay, I'll let you off the hook for now.
Thank me later, doreany.
Quiet, alien.
I see.
It's probably Zelada.
Inspector Zimmer, you were right.
That's a shame.
I was hoping I wasn't.
Why?
Because now I get to go to every
department involved and tell them,
"Watch out for wizards."
That's rough.
A Semanian shot an Earth mayoral candidate.
This is going to be a pain.
How?
Ethnic strife.
Just like you saw earlier.
You know what I mean, right?
Even if Zelada, a Semanian, is behind it,
we need to figure out the truth
as fast as possible.
But how do we find the guy?
It's not like you can catch
a wizard on a security camera.
How about we go back to
the basics of investigating?
What do you mean by basics?
Motive.
Who gains by Kahns' death?
"Next time"
Next time on COP CRAFT.