This guy's the real deal.
I've never seen the Queen lose before.
He's 4-0 lifetime against the Queen.
He's no dark horse.
He's a true thoroughbred.
Wh-What do we do?
How are we going to get
out of that promise?
Well?
I want you to let me attend
a university in Tokyo.
I know!
Let's tell him that he has
to win two years in a row!
There's something I haven't told you.
Arata knows about this...
Grandpa took out an education
life insurance policy for Arata.
I was left
out again?
Huh?  What's that?
B-But aren't you going to
miss having him around?
Plus, housing in Tokyo can be
ridiculously expensive...
I don't look forward to being
alone in the house with you...
What?
But...
Who's going to stop him?
He's doing what he loves
and shining at it, all on his own.
Incredible.
I'll win the individual
tournament tomorrow
and go to Tokyo.
He even beat the Queen.
He's really going to...
Huh?
Aren't you supposed to
high-five when you win?
Huh?
You also won your match, right, Taichi?
Congrats!
Chihaya?
Congratulations on your victory.
O-Oh, thanks.
How...
How are you always smiling?
How are you so calm
when you play karuta,
even when you're up against someone
as strong as Shinobu-chan?
How do you do it?
I'm always so intense when I play.
Sorry.
Impassionate...
How does he play karuta that way?
I—
It's time.
We need all the champions to
assemble on the first floor.
Please start moving.
Sorry, I'll catch you later.
I'm working hard.
I've worked very hard.
But...
Something isn't right.
What is it?
What's wrong?
I don't know what the problem is,
but something's wrong.
Ayase.
Chihaya Furu
Verse 25
I can
look up
and see
the snowy
cap of
Mt. Fuji
Class A Champion
Wataya Arata (2nd Year)
Class B Champion
Mashima Taichi (2nd Year)
Class C Champion
Komano Tsutomu (2nd Year)
plus 1 other
Class D Champion
Tsukuba Akihiro (1st Year)
plus 3 others
Amazing!
Everyone did a wonderful job!
I figured Ayase's goal of winning
every class was crazy...
Mizusawa's really good.
They won Classes B, C, and D.
Should've expected it after they
won the team tournament.
But...
Win every class
It was supposed to go like this!
I couldn't do it.
Everyone else did their best.
I'll carry your stuff.
Everyone have everything?
Let's get going then.
Ayase-san.
Coach Sakurazawa...
Would you like video of the Class A final?
You have video?!
Yes, please!
Okay...
This is my e-mail address.
O-Okay.
Give me your contact information.
Chihaya!  We're leaving!
Thank you very much!
Curses!
Even I don't have her e-mail address!
Goodbye!
It's dangerous to give Eromu
that kind of information
Has anyone else noticed?
Only two players went through the entire
high school tournament without a loss.
Wataya Arata from Fukui
and Mashima Taichi from Mizusawa.
Surgical Hospital
What is this?
The same reaction?
I can't tell what's wrong, so you'll
need to visit a bigger hospital.
What?!
First General Hospital
What is this?
Not again?
I think we need an MRI.
What?!
Don't move.
E-Enchondromatosis?!
Wh-What does that scary name mean?!
A-Are you okay, Ayase?
Are your bones going to
turn to mush or something?
They ran some tests,
and luckily it's only the third
bone in my right index finger
where the bone is softening.
Only here
This is a really rare disorder,
and most people go through their entire
lives without knowing they have it.
So...
What are you going to do, Chihaya?
I-I'm thinking about having an operation.
An operation?!
Most people can just ignore it,
but it's recommended that athletes
and people who use their hands a lot
have an operation to put some
firm material inside the bone.
It calls for full anesthesia and
I'll be hospitalized for a week.
Full anesthesia and hospital time?!
Isn't it just your finger?!
You can't leave the same day?
I'm scared...
B-But I want to be able to play
karuta without having to worry.
Even injured...
...she only cares about karuta.
Well, at least it's summer vacation.
I need to get going.  You'll be okay?
Take good care of my laptop.
Uh-huh.
We'll come back tomorrow
before your operation.
Final Match
Wataya vs. Wakamiya
Young folks have high tech
ways to kill time now.
Isn't that Hundred Poets
karuta, Toko-san?
Why does she look like that?
It's just karuta...
Ayase Chitose
Second Photo Collection
Oh, the Millennium is
taken from Chitose.
Chitose --> 1000 Years --> Millennium
Arata-kun, are you a fan of her?
I prefer girls with bigger boobs.
Like, big enough to close you in between them.
Ayase Chihaya
Yes, hello?
Oh, you answered.
What's that?
You actually answer your phone, Arata.
My sister always ignores me.
Oh...
What's up?
She's not really a flower kind of person.
Flowers are a must when
visiting someone in the hospital!
If I were in her shoes, I would
want flowers as a present!
Wouldn't food also work?
She'd probably like chocolate more.
Or ice cream!
I say we go with a book.
This is the perfect opportunity
for her to do some reading.
Honestly, just buy whatever you want.
Yes!  Ice cream time!
Wait!  Ice cream is a bad idea!
Excuse me.
Huh?
Do you want any flowers?
Can I get some flowers that
are a cheerful color?
She's probably feeling down.
Simply put, I want to
get better at karuta!
That's simple, all right.
That's all I can think about.
I've been working really
hard for a long time.
We aren't even playing,
and you're already fired up.
It hurts...
The cicadas are loud.
I feel like we're in different countries.
Even though we can talk over the phone,
he's so far away.
You know, whether it's an official
match or a practice match,
I always go back to that
room when I'm playing.
That room?
When did you have the
most fun playing karuta?
Where I was never scared,
no matter who came in...
Where I was always happy, having fun,
and wishing it'd never end...
Back when you and I played karuta
in that old apartment...
Back in that old
apartment...
Wow, this place is falling apart.
L-Let's play!
If you become the best player in Japan,
you'll be the best in the world.
The time we spent playing there
is making Arata stronger?
This hospital is huge.
Whew, it's so cool inside.
Sorry, Chihaya-chan.
We ran late.
It's too hot outside today.
The chocolate's melting.
I don't understand.
I don't understand these feelings...
But...
For the rest of my life,
I'll always love karuta,
the red that is the Tatsuta River
and I'll always love Arata.
The operation was a success,
so you just have the
pain to worry about.
We'll keep an eye on it and,
if everything looks okay,
you'll be discharged
in a week as planned.
What are you doing?!
Nervous
No practice swings until the cast is off.
Is this going to leave a scar?
Yikes...
Stop that, Chitose.
And your summer vacation is ruined...
We're going home.
Okay.
Try to finish your homework.
Oh, this is a present.
Doing homework?
Oh, yes.
That's very responsible of you.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Year 2 Classical Literature
Special Assignment
Compose 20 poems
Chihaya-chan...
It's not difficult to compose poetry.
You just have to translate
your feelings into meter.
But...
You must be able to read poetry
before you can compose poetry!
Compose
Read
I believe that amateurs can only
understand 50% of verbal poems.
When written out in modern
language, it goes down to 30%.
If the poem is written in classical language,
only 10% of the meaning is understood!
You must accept that
you don't understand
V-Verbal?  Cl-Classical?
what you think you understand!
I recommend you start
by reading these books!
N-Not happening...
I managed to compose five poems
in a rush before July ended.
I want to play karuta.
I always go back to that
room when I'm playing.
If you become the best player in Japan,
you'll be the best in the world.
Ever since meeting Arata,
my life has been all about karuta.
Always striving to become stronger
and stronger
so I can be able
to receive his passion.
Nurse Station
Reception
Please return these to the
receptionist when you leave.
Understood.
Visitor 32
Visitor 33
Here you are, Prez.
Chihaya-chan.
You're working hard.
Is that your summer homework?
Uh-huh.
Is it okay for you to be moving around?
You can hold off on the twenty poems.
In the sweltering summer sunlight,
I feast upon a whirlwind of ice cream.
Since I could not stop
thinking of Shinobu-chan,
I wonder if she is
practicing right now.
Yeah...
Were you actually trying?
Your grade will drop for every
one of these you turn in.
What?  Really?
Pardon?
Inside a room isolated
from the summer heat,
I feel bliss
upon hearing your words.
Inside a room isolated
from the summer heat,
I feel bliss upon hearing your words.
How's your finger?
It's fine.
I don't remember a thing
after I was knocked out,
but I needed four stitches.
Will I ever turn the
corner and find you?
I can only wait for
a dream or a miracle.
Will I ever turn the corner and find you?
I can only wait for a dream or a miracle.
She's doing better than I expected.
It looks like the operation
was a success, too.
She should recover in time
for the fall tournament.
What is it, Oe-san?
You have to try harder, Prez!
You don't have to invite me along
when you visit her in the hospital.
You can't expect Chihaya-chan
to be clueless for the rest of her life!
I know.
Ayase-san!  No practice swings!
Absolutely not!
Sorry.
Honestly...
Goodbye, Coach.
Be careful on your way home.
Coach, it's getting dark,
so I'll walk you home.
No, thanks.
If I'm around you too much, I'm
afraid I'll have dreams about you.
I'd want that!
And why are you here when
you've already left the club?
Yes, hello?
Coach Sakurazawa?
Oh, Ayase-san?
Thank you very much for sending
the DVD of the high school final!
Was it useful?
Yes, I've been watching it every day.
I'm so glad I got to see what happened
at the start of the match.
Both players were incredible.
I saw Arata—
I saw Wataya-kun play for the
first time, thanks to you.
I see.
What were your thoughts on
that match, Coach Sakurazawa?
Well...
Wataya-kun had a very
balanced play style.
There's nothing special
about his game sense,
but he was consistent and caught
every partial syllable.
I would guess he's a right
brain memorizer,
but he also uses his left brain, so
fatigue isn't as much of a factor.
The Queen is also special.
I'd love to know how she
connects to the cards.
She appears to be apologizing
when she moves cards.
Her connection to the cards is very deep.
Plus, she isn't afraid of committing faults.
Her playing style reflects her
trust in her own karuta.
Oh, sorry about that.
I got carried away.
No, that was very educational!
It helps a lot!
Good.
Ayase-san, would you be interested in
participating in a Fujisaki
two-day karuta camp?
Along with the president and
other players from Mizusawa.
I'll come!
I just had an operation on my
right hand, but I'll come!
Operation?
H-Here we are...
Let's go.
I wish the other players
could have joined us.
I guess it can't be helped that the Suihoku
society has its camp at the same time.
Sumire-chan and Tsukuba-kun
are also busy...
Prez, I'll deal with the first-years.
It has to be the two of you
going to Shizuoka alone!
Anyway, are you sure
about this, Chihaya?
You were told not to do any
physical activity for a month.
Yeah,
but I've never gone such a long
time without playing karuta.
It's hard when I can't
think of anything else.
Forward.
We can only move forward.
Yes.
Huh?  Tokyo?
I'm hoping to get a karuta scholarship.
After winning the high
school championship,
I have permission from my parents.
Wait, Arata-kun!
Don't quit!
What am I supposed to do without you?!
I'm not quitting right away.
Don't leave me!
I'm not quitting yet!