FOUR YEARS AGO
PORT OF STIMMER,
LEIDENSCHAFTLICH
Captain Diethard Bougainvillea.
Your brother is here to see you.
Hey, Gil!
How have you been?
You look depressed, as usual.
You look just like Father.
You haven't changed either.
Father would not approve
of your hair for sure.
I bet he would have cut it off
with a saber.
I wouldn't let him.
You've always been like that.
I'm glad he died.
Sorry.
Stop making that face.
I brought you something nice today
to celebrate your promotion.
Got it? Only use it as a weapon.
Don't get attached.
Open it.
Hey. Get up.
I found her in the northeastern war zone.
Her name is...
Violet Evergarden.
She's going to start working today
as an Auto Memory Doll apprentice.
Please train her on everything.
Okay.
She didn't have any facial expressions,
just like a doll.
Just like the dolls...
that were named after this industry.
Um, first off...
How much do you know about
what Auto Memory Dolls do?
They write letters
at the request of others.
Lt. Colonel Hodgins... I mean,
the president told me so.
That's right!
I can't say that I completely understand,
but I think I can perform my duties.
It's not that easy! "Duties?!"
What are you talking about?!
Iris, that's enough. Get back to work.
All right.
That reminds me, I haven't introduced
the other Dolls to you yet.
"Doll" refers to...
I understand it's an abbreviation
for Auto Memory Doll.
-I figured it out the other day.
-That's right.
The girl just now... Her name is Iris.
She's a new hire who just
completed her training course.
And that's Erica.
She and I have both been working
as Dolls for a while.
This company is still pretty young,
so, we're all like rookies here.
I don't think so.
Violet, do you know
how to use a typewriter?
I've never used one before.
Then why don't you start off
by practicing typing?
It's not that easy to become a Doll.
Iris, can we borrow your manual?
Okay.
Uh, have a seat.
Yes ma'am.
You should remove your gloves.
Okay.
Are you okay?
It's not a problem.
Then why don't you try it out a bit?
Set the paper like this.
Turn the knob and feed it in.
Place your pointer fingers on the
F and J keys, and try typing something.
Okay.
That's right. Just like that.
Just memorize where your fingers
should go for the different letters.
Try typing what it says in this manual.
Oh, wait. Violet.
Violet! Stop!
Can you type a little more...
quietly?
Thank you.
It's 1.2 Liber. So, that's 10 Corse.
-Thank you.
-It's finally time for lunch!
Nerine, Lilian.
Let's have lunch together.
I've bought fried noodles for you.
No, thanks.
And don't come to the reception
looking so sweaty like that.
What's up with them?
When you see a man
who's been toiling away,
can't you at least say,
"Thanks for your hard work"?
And what do they mean, "Don't come"?
-Women these days are so calculating.
-And their perfume stinks.
They're just trying to
snag rich guys at reception.
Don't worry about it.
Who cares. No more working girls for me.
-Hey, you guys. Fried noodles.
-I don't want any.
And stop calling me "Hey, you."
I'll have some fried noodles.
I'm stuck just writing
addresses again today.
The two reservations
we have this afternoon
both asked for Cattleya.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I came all the way to Leiden
to become a Doll,
but all I do is write addresses
and inquiries about missing people
from the war every day.
That's all I do.
Right.
By the way, I heard that new girl
used to be in the army.
Even though she's still a child?
And....
They don't have to make her a Doll.
She's cold and inconsiderate.
She's not right for this job.
I want to write letters
that are more exciting!
Like a letter for a famous person.
Or a secret love letter for an actress.
But those jobs always go to Cattleya.
How is Violet?
I invited her to lunch,
but she said she didn't need to recharge.
She's just been practicing typing
the entire time.
I see.
Sorry for all the trouble.
Hey, then treat me to dinner, Claudia.
Don't call me by my first name!
Just because you wanted a girl.
I can't believe it.
Calling out a girl's name in bed.
That was terrible.
Stop! Please! I'm sorry!
I can't take you anytime soon.
I'm not getting paid this month.
I'm done writing the addresses.
Thanks for your hard work.
I'll bring these
to the delivery department.
Thanks.
Violet, thanks for your hard work.
That's enough for today.
Let me see.
You've improved a lot! Amazing.
This weapon is what's amazing.
Weapon. You're right.
It's a weapon for working girls like us
to go out into society and fight.
I'll have you sit next to a real Doll
tomorrow and shadow her.
I'm going out for a delivery service now.
If someone requests it,
we go to their house
or workplace to write for them.
Can I take this with me, too?
The typewriter? Where?
To my room. For training,
and for...
Address? Gilbert's?
Yes. I want to tell him that I've started
a writing job and begun training.
I want to report my current status.
I'm sure the major is still busy...
and can't see me yet, right?
Yeah.
Okay. I'll send this for you.
How's training going?
It's going well.
There's no problem.
Like you already know,
it's hard making ends meet every day.
"As you already know,
living expenses are tight."
You made a mistake.
Tell him I'll pay back
two chlor every month.
-"Every month."
-If you pay back two chlor every month,
it will take you 120 years
to pay back everything.
Sir, will you be able to
survive until then?
Normally, she's really good.
But sometimes she gets really mad.
"I'm sorry for hurting
your precious child."
Maybe I didn't discipline her well.
"Our teachings were insufficient."
What did I...?
What did I do wrong?!
-Um...
-Crying gets in the way of our work.
-Please stop crying immediately.
-Wait!
Hey! What do you mean by this letter?
"I'm sorry for my selfish request..."
-What do you mean, "selfish?"
-Sorry.
"I apologize for the delay?!"
This makes it seem like it's all my fault!
Who do you think you are?!
She's Erica.
I didn't ask her name!
Anyways, I don't like this letter.
I'm not paying for this!
Refusing to pay because
you didn't like it is illegal.
What don't you like about it?
Out of my way!
Please be specific.
Please give us some guidance.
And provide brief input.
We've received complaints
from a few customers.
Was there a problem?
No, well...
Are you okay?
-There is nothing wrong with my health.
-No, I mean about working as a Doll.
I'm training diligently.
Uh, I see.
Um... We don't have
any more reservations today.
We're going to work diligently together
to make the membership list for the
Chamber of Commerce after this.
Type the company and the address.
-And the type of industry.
-Yes, ma'am.
Hey. Why do you want to do this job?
I...
Oh, is everyone gone?
Welcome. Do you want to request a letter?
-Why else would I be here?
-My apologies.
If you request it,
we'll write any type of document for you.
Auto Memory Doll Service.
Where is the Doll
named Cattleya Baudelaire?
She's on a business trip.
Oh, I came here because I heard
you can never go wrong with her.
Oh, well.
Someone asked me out.
A man who started an automobile company.
He said every household
is going to own a car in the future.
Oh.
But, you know...
I'm not such a simple woman.
I don't want him to think I'm easy.
Uh, in other words...
Well, he's not that great of a catch.
I don't have any feelings for him.
If he showed me he's serious,
and if he really loves me...
Please write an elegant
and romantic letter.
Get started.
Uh...
Oh. Are you the one
who's going to write it?
Yes, ma'am.
What's up with that letter?
Ma'am, please calm down.
Iris. Bring some tea.
Yes.
-I wrote it just as you requested.
-What are you talking about?!
He got angry and sent
the letter back to me!
Read it! Read what you wrote!
"I read your letter.
However, I do not have feelings
for you now.
Furthermore, your seriousness
and love are insufficient.
I am a complex and serious woman.
Please reconsider again
with gifts and funds."
What's wrong with this letter?
I apologize.
The expressions used were too straight.
I...
wanted to date him.
But if I accepted his request too soon,
he would think that I'm too easy!
Women want men to chase them,
right?!
I... loved him!
What would you like?
Water or hot water
is enough for rehydrating.
Two cups of flower tea.
Thank you.
It might have been too soon
to give you such a hard job.
-I'm incapable of understanding.
-Huh?
I wrote the letter incorporating
her requests as much as I could.
Words can have different interpretations.
What one says isn't the whole truth.
It's a human weakness.
They test others to confirm
their own existence.
It's a contradiction.
I'm going to apologize to him in person.
Major.
Major!
Major Gilbert!
Here we go.
Hey!
What's wrong? Are you alone?
You look sad. Are you eating well?
I've replenished my nutrients.
Then did you make a mistake at work?
Come back to the delivery department.
Doing deliveries is no good.
Forget about working as a Doll.
Isn't it better to find another job?
I should look for a job, too.
Hodgins said
he's not getting paid this month.
Seems like our company isn't doing well.
Can I ask you a question?
Am I suited to become an Auto Memory Doll?
I was also...
I'm not asking about you.
You're not suited for it.
Why do you want to do this job
in the first place?
I want to know what "I love you" means.
Is that all?
That's all.
I understand that those words
express a particular emotion.
Why did the major say
those words to me?
I want to know why.
I still want to continue with this job,
even if I'm not suited for it.
There's a towel in the locker room.
In any case,
I think working as a Doll
is too hard for Violet.
This company is still new,
but we get so many requests for Cattleya.
But if we get a bad reputation
because of this...
Just when things are about to take off.
-It's better to have Violet quit.
-No, give her a little more time.
Um...
Erica!
And Violet, too.
What's the matter?
I don't...
I don't think we should make her quit!
She... Violet...
is very accurate and fast when she types,
and she can do tasks like making
membership lists and writing addresses.
Once she learns more...
I think she'll be able to write letters.
Please.
Don't make her quit.
It's a contradiction.
You said I'm not suited for this duty.
I'm the one who isn't suited
to being an Auto Memory Doll.
That's why I got so serious
about defending her.
The machine that was a prototype
for the typewriter
was originally invented by Dr. Orland,
the authority on letterpress printing.
His wife, Mollie, was a novelist,
but she became blind
and couldn't write anymore.
He created the typewriter for her.
The doctor called it the Auto Memory Doll.
That term now refers to the
industry of writing for others.
Meeting her made me remember
my dream, which I had almost forgotten.
My feelings, which were buried away.
Just like how my heart was moved
by the novels written by Orland's wife.
-I'm going to close up shop. Are you okay?
-Uh, yes.
Someday...
I want to write beautiful letters
that can move peoples' hearts, too.
I'm done!
How is this?
Nice. Violet, stand up.
Yes.
It looks good on you.
I was right after all.
Oh, and don't forget this.
Sorry for being late.
Open it.
Opening.
This is it.
This is the brooch the major gave me!
It was on the black market.
Someone must have stolen it
from your belongings.
Oh, yeah! Violet,
do you want to attend
a Doll training course?
They have short-term courses, too.
Iris attended one, too.
The teacher is really strict.
I think it'll be good for you.
You bought that back.
That's why you didn't get paid this month?
Thank you for the drink.
Hey, who is the major she talks about?
Gilbert.
He's a friend
from my Military Academy days.
He's from the Bougainvillea family.
Oh! That margrave...
No. Even though he's from a rich family,
he was a man with spirit.
"Was"?
He's not...
NOT COMING BACK
coming back anymore.
Subtitle translation by
Hoday Stearns