What is this?
How are we going to clean this up?
Achoo!
The Unfaithful Dog
Yesterday...
Thank you for welcoming me,
my human toilets!
Kage!
It's been forever!
Hey, it's Ririchiyo's fiancé.
No, it isn't!
You came back soon this time!
Where did you go?
Hokkaido (M)
I was in Hokkaido!
And I brought gifts.
You get a dog collar!
And you, a candle!
You get a whip!
Why do I always get a whip?
Shikoku (S)
I went to Shikoku, too!
Handcuffs!
Manacles!
You get a whip!
Why do I always get a whip?
I'm sorry.
But Miketsukami and I
have an engagement,
so if you'll excuse us.
Let's go.
Yes.
Rejoice!
For I have bought you a gift as well, sow.
I'm fairly certain that last time,
I told you I'd freeze you
if you ever came near me.
More ice fetish play, I see?
I like it.
She's dangerous...
Roromiya!
Karuta!
What do you think you're doing?
This!
It's a party!
Enjoy it, my human toilets!
Knock it off!
This is my welcome back party!
It will be a dazzling orgy!
Kage, you're wonderful!
Debau-che-ry!
Ry!
I told you to stay away from me!
Five Hours Later
Are you okay?
Miss Ririchiyo, here is some water.
Is it already that late?
Then I shall take my leave, you pigs!
It's already over?
Staying up late ruins your
looks and your health.
It's positively sadistic!
Here he goes again.
Fiancée of mine!
I shall soon depart again.
How about it?
Would you like to come with me?
Did you really expect me to agree?
You needn't rush your answer.
I also have an important matter
to discuss with you.
An important matter?
Tomorrow is Saturday.
Let us have a long chat tomorrow,
my fiancée.
Karuta! Karuta!
Karuta!
Shee you later, Wahanuki.
Thanks to that man, it's gotten quite late.
Let's reschedule our appointment for
tomorrow, after I get home.
Certainly.
Please take care.
Ha, yeah, thanks.
I guess I'll ask you to take me
home afterward, as well.
I didn't see her in the lounge.
I wonder if Roromiya just stayed with him.
I went to her room this morning,
but she wasn't there.
I thought that maybe she'd just
left early for school.
He told me he had something important
to discuss with me last time he came, also.
What could it be?
And as the Assyrian Empire flourished...
Am I not Soushi's old master and your fiancé?
That's right. Miketsukami already knows
that he's my fiancé.
And yet,
he's never brought it up.
Does that mean he isn't
interested in me that way?
I can't believe
you got engaged to that guy...
It's something our parents decided.
But weren't you writing to each other?
Not really...
It wasn't like there was anything
I wanted to say to him.
I wrote to him
every day...
I would run home from school,
as if I were escaping.
But then, I couldn't stand
to be at home, either.
So I stood in front of the mailbox...
As if I were praying.
That little letter contained words
and sentences meant just for me.
That alone made me happy.
But...
Bye!
Let's grab something to eat.
But I'd forgotten about the letters.
After all, that man...
My fiancée, we met most recently
but last night!
I have come to fetch you in person!
Wh-Why you?
I shall treat you to Chinese food, my fiancée!
That's not the...
Roromiya?
Karuta!
Are you all right?
Peking duck!
That's the first thing out of your mouth?!
Let me out!
This is kidnapping!
Let's go!
Peking duck!
This isn't funny anymore!
I was waiting for Miketsukami—
He isn't coming.
I told him not to bother since
I'm taking my fiancée for dinner.
Our coffee appointment...
How dare you?!
Fiancée? Please!
I have no intention of upholding
that agreement!
Why are you so angry?
He and I are not so different.
Yeah, right!
Don't play dumb!
I told you before.
He's a sadist, just like I am.
Stop fitting people into your little world.
I'm sure I've told you that before!
It isn't merely my world.
Everything can be divided by
masochism or sadism.
As I'm sure I've said.
By the way...
That mother's a sadist.
Her kid's a sadist, too.
That salaryman is a masochist.
That dog is a total masochist.
This chauffeur is a masochist...
Stop it!
Ouch.
I hit my head on the glass.
That kind of hurts...
This glass is entirely sadistic!
But we aren't getting anywhere.
I suppose it's this traffic.
And that means this road
is a bit of a sadist, too!
Chinese Restaurant
This table doesn't rotate too well.
Rather sadistic, I'd say...
But that's just a facade.
It's a masochist that yearns to be dominated!
Kage seems to be enjoying himself.
I'm not enjoying myself.
I want to go home.
All right!
I shall spin you, and spin you,
and spin you some more!
Aquarium
The Southern Rockhopper Penguin.
At first, he appears to be the
cute masochistic type.
In reality, however, he is
an uncontrollable sadist!
I want to go home.
Karuta's gone!
Sardines.
Flounder.
Tuna.
They look delicious...
Tea Time
This cocoa's sweet. Masochist!
I want to go home.
Ginger ale is spicy. Sadist!
The Movies
The movie theater is dark. Masochist!
Oh, it's coming right at us.
It's 3D! Sadistic!
I want to go home.
Shopping
This mannequin's a cool beauty. Sadist!
But this one's a masochist.
I want to go home.
Sadist!
Night Sights
The view at night...
Super-sadist.
What?
What, what?
I'm going home by myself,
so return my bag and cell phone!
Is this mutiny?
Is this mutinous super-masochism?!
I like it! I like it...
Home
He dragged me all over town.
It's already 10:30 PM...
I wasn't able to meet Miketsukami.
He always wants to be with me.
Did I make him feel lonely?
Is he mad at me?
Am I reading too much into it?
Anyway, I should at least
write and apologize.
Sending
Message Sent
Is it because I'm waiting too eagerly for it?
Waiting for a Reply
Uneasy
He usually writes back immediately.
10 Minutes Later
This is not unusual...
30 Minutes Later
Uneasy Uneasy Uneasy...
This could happen any day.
50 Minutes Later
Is he angry, after all?
Maybe I should meet him and apologize!
But I can't call on him this late...
He did say that he stays up late.
But then...
I know myself.
Could I really meet him and
properly apologize?
Anyway, maybe he's just busy.
Then again, this hasn't
ever happened before.
Then again...
I ended up leaving my room.
Apology Gift
I'll be fine.
I practiced apologizing nicely.
Now I just have to put my heart
into it, and apologize.
F-First, say, "I'm sorry to
disturb you so late."
Miss Ririchiyo?
He's in normal clothes...
And glasses.
His hair's wet...
He must have been taking a bath.
That's why...
Th-This is awkward!
U-Um, well...
I-I'm sorry to disturb you so late...
I guess I should start with that.
I couldn't keep our appointment today,
which wasn't my intention at all!
That's not what I said in my test run at all!
Why?!
Your uniform...
You're still wearing your school uniform,
so you two were together until now?
Y-Yeah, until just now.
Sorry about that. Happy now?
It seems he hasn't told you.
Told me?
He only sputtered nonsense.
You need not apologize to me for
anything you do with Mr. Kagerou.
Could it be that you actually like him?
Wh-Why?! Of course not!
Then you seem to be quite good
at unintentionally sending men
the wrong signals.
Are you trying to pick a fight with me?
Me?
I am your faithful dog.
Would I bite the hand that feeds me?
Please remember that you
have made a contract with me.
No matter what...
Even if you were to reject me.
You're not yourself today.
I'm leaving!
"Could it be that you actually like him?"
Of course not!
I wanted to go home the whole time.
I...
I wanted to be with Miketsukami...
Huh?
I...
Miketsukami...
This is a good morning.
A bath where you gaze at humanity below.
Now that is exceptional...
I love looking down on people!
I know you do, Mr. Kagerou.
Good morning.
You're naughty. Don't sneak up on me.
You didn't end up talking
about it yesterday, did you?
No.
I didn't want to say anything
with the others there.
It is a petty issue to me,
but I suppose it is something
women care about.
My fiancée will soon be sixteen.
Couples should have no
reservations between them.
Mr. Kagerou...
Would it be possible for you
to avoid mentioning it?
I shall do anything in my power.
For her? Or for yourself?
In any case, your "anything" bores me.
You really would do anything.
You'd do any embarrassing
task with a smile,
without hesitation.
It makes me feel like I am beneath you.
I never liked that.
And now,
you are begging me.
But I refuse!
How is it? Truly being on your
knees for the first time?
I bet you hate it!
What are you saying, sir?
I have been on my knees
many times in your service.
However,
the issue I bring before you
is no petty matter.
So I shall ask you again.
Excellent!
I'll play.
Your strikes suggest that you're serious.
It's nice to get attacked, once in a while.
But now, you should enjoy my treatment!
I couldn't sleep.
I'll buy a drink, and get some
morning sun while I'm here.
Could you not find it within your
great heart to consider this weak and
insignificant servant's request?
Weak and insignificant, you say?
You're a stubborn, shameless super-sadist!
You deceive everyone with
your aura of purity,
but in reality you're a ****!
Admit it, and I shall consider your request.
Very well.
I shall accept it, and bear the dishonor.
I deceive everyone with my aura of purity,
but in reality, I'm a **** pervert—
What are you doing?!
You should do this outside! You're adults!
Good morning, Miss Ririchiyo.
Good morning, my bitch!
Spare me your salutations.
Get away from that man,
and sheathe your sword.
Yes.
So,
what did you do?
Me? The aggressor?
I like it! I like it...
Miketsukami would never hurt
anyone without cause.
I see you trust him.
Even though we're cut from the same cloth...
No, I should say we're guilty
of the same offense.
What are...
You should ask him directly!
That man is good at deceiving others,
but he probably cannot lie to you.
Miketsukami?
I can lie.
It's better that way.
I intended to keep it from you.
However,
I'd rather tell you myself than have
you hear it from another.
Miss Ririchiyo, it is as Mr. Kagerou says.
I have
been deceiving you.
Please forgive me, Miss Ririchiyo.
Miss Ririchiyo,
I have been lying to you.
I deceived and betrayed you.
I thought I could hide it from you.
But... But, Miss Ririchiyo,
all I wish for is your...
Next time, on Inu X Boku Secret Service:
Kagerou.
Kagerou