Mid-terms
Ranking Announcement
What rank am I? What rank am I?
Don't act so giddy.
63 - Raku Ichijo
Damn, only 63rd out of 207?
What's it gonna take
to crack the Top 50, anyway?
Hey! There I am! There I am!
6 - Seishiro Tsugumi
5 - Chitoge Kirisaki
Darn... only No. 5?
Well, not that I really
studied that hard...
I'm next to Young Mistress!
Damn you prodigies!
How'd it go, Ichijo?
Onodera!
How about you?
I was No. 88. Well, I guess
it's the same as usual for me.
I see.
Well, I guess I did so-so myself.
23 - Ruri Miyamoto
22 - Shu Maiko
Hey, look! We're
side by side, huh, Ruri?
I had no idea.
Maiko gets really good grades!
R-Ruri!
He's always like that, you know.
Irritating as it is...
Huh? Come to think of it, I haven't
spotted Tachibana's name yet.
Oh, now that you mention it...
Wonder where she's at?
Knowing her, I bet
she's right near the top.
185 - Marika Tachibana
Wait, what's up with that?!
"Teach Me"
I'm embarrassed to say it,
but studying has never
been my strong suit.
Yeah? Well, who would've thought?
You seem like the type who'd have
no trouble with that kind of thing.
To be honest, I have zero motivation.
You really are being honest there!
For a long time, in order to become
your bride, Master Raku...
all my efforts have
gone into various lessons,
and how to become as attractive
a woman as possible!
I wish you wouldn't just blurt out
stuff that makes us all freeze!
Yeah, but you can't just keep hanging on
with grades like these, can you?
You could end up getting held back.
The teacher said if I got below 40 points
on my next math test, I'd have to re-take it.
I know, Master Raku!
If you don't mind, could you
tutor me at my home after school?
Hey, what are you talking about?
Can't you study by yourself?
I'll thank you not to
underestimate my ineptitude!
I can't possibly improve my grades
without someone's guidance!
What's with the attitude?
Oh, is that so?
In that case, why don't
I tutor you myself?
I'm sure it's more fitting for
someone ranked No. 5 like me!
Oh, surely you jest.
You don't seem like you know the first
thing about teaching others, Kirisaki!
Come now, Master Raku!
You don't mind, do you?
Since my father won't be
coming home tonight,
we should be able to study
to our heart's content till daybreak!
Till daybreak?!
Hey, hey, let's not
get ahead of ourselves, okay?
Look, I don't mind helping you out
with your schoolwork...
But spending the night is
going overboard, don't you think?
Oh, no, regarding that...
Since the math test is tomorrow...
Please help me.
Was it tomorrow?
Yes, it is!
You'd forgotten?
So...
Why is Kirisaki tagging along, too?
All you're doing is having
friends over to study for a test,
so what's wrong with me
being around, I wonder?
There's nothing wrong with it, really.
But if I may be blunt... you're
like a third wheel, should I say?
You don't have to be blunt
about that kind of thing!
Well, I'm glad you're here.
Come on, get ready to study, will you?
We'll help you with whatever
you don't understand.
It's not as if you're going to
be the one to teach me.
Oh, never mind.
All right, I'll start then.
Master Raku!
I don't understand this problem!
Heave-ho!
No more fooling around!
You don't have to glom
onto him to learn, do you?
But I would learn faster
if I was next to him...
Man, thank goodness she's here, too.
So...
Which part don't you get?
Oh, factorization, huh?
Listen up. For this, you go like this...
Ah, I see!
I think I understand it
just a little bit better now.
In other words, if this a is me,
the b is you, Master Raku,
and the x is Kirisaki...
Then all I have to do is
lock out just the x, like this!
Hey, you!
That pisses me off, so
don't memorize it that way!
Modern Japanese
Now, then, Master Raku!
Would you mind showing me
how to do this, next?
Modern Japanese? What about math?
I want to know how this lady feels, waiting for
her husband's return in this chapter...
Well, let's see...
Here, she's... See,
she's not just waiting.
She's about to go off
and see him herself, so...
Oh, my! That is correct, Master Raku!
All right, on to the next problem!
What is the correct
answer you should give
to a courageous girl who's cared for
her beloved for ten years?
Yes or yes?
Study, for God's sake!
Wait... Oh, crap.
How do you solve this problem again?
If the tutor himself doesn't
get it, how helpful is that?
No way around it, then.
Where? Let me see it.
Right. It's this problem.
You can't just use a formula
like you normally would...
Hey, would you stop interfering?
My, my, did you say interfere?
By that do you mean
to interfere your studying?
Or a world where only you two exist?
If the latter, I have every intention of
hindering you as much as I can.
Look, you... are you
at all motivated to study?
If you don't shape up,
you really will repeat a grade!
Well, it's not that I'm not motivated.
I simply can't do what I cannot do.
Well, then, how did you
get into our high school?
Don't tell me you got in
through the backdoor?
A-Are you serious?!
Well, I'm only joking about that,
but the day before the entrance
exam, I pulled an all-nighter.
And thanks to that, I barely passed.
An all-nighter, huh?
Hey, wouldn't you say
that in your case,
it's not a matter of you
not being a good student...
...just that you didn't
bother to study?
I mean, it seems to me that you'd start
getting good grades if you really hit the books.
You really think so?
Give it all you've got!
I'll do what I can to help you.
You don't want to
get held back, do you?
Oh, Master Raku!
In other words, you'll miss me if
you can't get promoted with me, right?
I'm going to do my best!
That makes me so happy!
Well, you're not wrong about that,
but you sure took it in a positive way!
But for some reason, having you tutor me
like this reminds me of those days 10 years ago.
Wait, so you helped her
with her schoolwork?
No... after all, I was
only in kindergarten.
Master Raku taught me so many things.
Games that I could enjoy
even if I was alone.
What was going on at kindergarten...
he'd teach me the songs
and talk about his friends.
It really brings back memories.
Not cool, not cool...
I totally nodded off.
They're both asleep,
for crying out loud!
Well, but I can't really blame them.
I mean, it's the dead of night...
Rakkun...
Rakkun, I adore you...
Seriously, I don't know
what it is that she sees in me.
She's a pretty weird girl,
but she's a good kid.
She's hot and popular with the guys.
I'm sure she could
have anyone she wanted.
Being told "I love you" by someone...
I don't know...
It feels so strange.
Ohhh, Rakkun!
That's your biggest fault!
Oh, but as long as you're
okay with it, Rakkun...
I'll...
Look, you - I know
you're totally awake.
If you have time to mess around
like that, just go to sleep!
I'll work hard! I'll work hard, all right?
Seriously...
This isn't good.
I completely dozed off.
Master Raku is very sweet, after all.
So very warm...
Take Note!!
I really...
...really love you, Rakkun.
I suppose pulling an all-nighter
can only take me so far.
This really looks quite difficult.
But this is the problem
that I did with Master Raku.
So's this one...
and this one!
Oh, my! This is wonderful!
If I add up the answers that I'm sure
I got right, it comes out to 40 exactly!
Now I won't have to re-take the exam.
Oh, man, a 38?
You came so close, huh, Tachibana?
It's too bad, but you're gonna
have to re-take the test, huh?
Well, but considering you got a zero on your
last math test, I'd say you did real good.
Is that right?
Huh?
Looks like she re-wrote this answer here.
And she got it right the first time.
Hey, Master Raku!
Unfortunately, it looks like
I'll have to re-take the exam,
so please tutor me again, will you?
Look, you! At least try to
study on your own a little!
Well, you're asking for the impossible.
Oh, jeez...
Are you all right? Young Mistress...
Studying all night... you're
pushing yourself too hard.
If it takes too great a toll on you...
Don't worry.
It's nothing I can't handle.
It happened during that
Culture Festival as well.
You've been pushing
yourself too hard lately.
You don't have to tell me.
I know that myself.
Rather than as your bodyguard,
I am by your side to watch over you.
Please don't forget that.
You don't have to tell me.
I know that already.
"Master Raku"
So you want me to take care of him?
Yes. So sorry to trouble you.
I'll be away on a trip with
my father for just one day.
Okay. No problem!
I like taking care of animals anyway.
You can count on me!
Thank you so much!
I'll have to thank you
in some way, sometime.
Hey, does this little guy
talk or something?
Oh, yes! He's very smart, you know.
Riiiight?
Riiiight!
Whoa, that's awesome!
To Master Raku
A love note
I've summarized
how to take care of him,
and what to watch out for in this note.
I'm really counting on you!
Gotcha.
So what's his name?
Right...
It's Master Raku!
Um...
What's his name?
It's Master Raku!
Master Raku?
Why would she pick out
a name like that, of all things?
I don't know if she's
needling me or if she's serious.
Hey, Master Raku?
Master Raku?
Crap, you look like a dimwit!
Somehow, this is depressing.
Come to think of it, we don't
have parrots at school
so this'll be my first time
looking after one.
Since you're a parrot,
I'd love to see you talk.
Are you about to say something?
Oh, Master Raku!
That's your biggest flaw!
Really, Master Raku!
So... bold... of... you!
What does she think she's doing?!
Master Raku, you pervert!
Heh, heh, Marika...
Does it feel good there?
Is that my line?!
Seriously, what the hell does
she think she's doing?! That idiot!
It's almost time to feed you.
There you go!
It's your favorite food!
Huh? Why isn't he eating?
You're hungry, aren't you?
That's weird.
Uh, the note says...
"How to Feed Master Raku."
"Master Raku absolutely
will not eat unless you say,
'Here, Master Raku... ahhhhh!'
with all your sincerity."
That girl... what kind of
training is that?!
Here, Master Raku...
Ahhhh!
How did I ever end up like this?
Oh, man...
But hey, never mind the content...
this little guy can speak pretty fluently.
Wonder if he'll learn
to say what I teach him?
Master Raku, you're so cool!
Well, that goes without saying!
You really are amazing, huh?
Wait, did you get what I just said?
Your memorization skills are unbelievable!
That was practically a conversation!
Okay, I'm gonna make you
learn no matter what!
Hey, Master Raku,
try saying "How much wood would a woodchuck
chuck, if a woodchuck could chuck wood?"
I'm talking to you, Master Raku!
Hey! Master Raku!
Young Master... what's
up with that, I wonder?
"How much wood would a woodchuck
chuck, if a woodchuck could chuck wood?"
Naming his pet after himself,
even sticking on a "Master."
Well, I'm sure Young
Master has his reasons.
Hey, Master Raku!
What a bust.
I got so caught up in
teaching him phrases.
And he never did learn
to say any of them.
Huh? Master Raku? Where'd you go?
Oh, crap, I did it!
A pet that I was entrusted with!
I don't believe myself!
Hey! Where are you? Ma—
Master Raku!
Where are you?!
Idiot!
There you are! Thank goodness
you didn't get too far!
Oh... oh!
You mustn't, Master Raku!
You mustn't touch me there!
Oh, what's the problem, Marika? Your
body doesn't seem to be resisting me.
Master Raku, you're so mean!
Oh, crap... I've got to do
something about this right away!
It's not even a matter of
Tachibana never forgiving me...
My reputation around
the neighborhood will be in shreds!
Hey, hold up, Master Raku!
Come back here right now!
Young Master...
You know you can always
come to us with any problem.
This is so sad...
Let's leave him be.
Young Master's in
the throes of adolescence!
Dammit!
He's heading downtown!
This is not good!
Whoa! What the...? You scared me.
What is this?
Did it escape from somewhere?
But really, your face pisses me off
for some reason, you know?
You kind of remind of that moron...
Oh, oh... Master Raku!
What?
You mustn't be so rough with me!
Not that I don't
find that attractive, too.
Come on, Marika, relax...
Is that Chitoge?
Hey, Chitoge!
Glad you're here!
By any chance did
a parrot come flying by?
Was that... your parrot?
Yeah, that's right.
I'm taking care of him
for Tachibana, see.
Did you see which way he...
Make amends by
dying, you dumbass!
Why?
Who cares about your parrot?
Go look for it yourself!
What's your problem, for Pete's sake?
Dammit, I never have any
clue what she's thinking.
Hey, there he is!
Damn him... I swear I'm
gonna catch him this time.
Oh, crap! That's Onodera!
What a sweet parrot!
I wonder where he came from?
Did he escape from
somewhere, I wonder?
Shouldn't we catch him?
Come on, Mr. Parrot!
Here, boy! Here, boy!
You really have a way with
any kind of animal, huh, Sis?
Did you lose your way?
Do you know where your owner is?
Just kidding.
I belong to Master Raku!
Oh, my beloved Marika!
My sweet honey!
Really, I don't believe you, Master Raku!
I am so embarrassed.
Oh, no, was I too late?
Hold up a second, Onodera!
It's not what you think!
Just hear me out and you'll see!
Ichijo!
I-It's fine, all right?
I haven't heard anything, and I haven't
seen anything, so it's all good, okay?
Nooooo!
Marika!
You're the only one that I love!
Come back here, you dumbass bird!
Or I'll end up frying you
and eating you up, dammit!
Damn...
I want to set the record straight,
but if I don't go after him,
it'll mean more grief for me!
I gotta catch him as soon as possible!
Could that be...?
Tsugumi! Glad I ran into you!
Help me out, will you?
See, there's this pet parrot...
You bastard!
You've been with Marika Tachibana...
Have... have you no shame?!
She hit on me first!
Divine punishment!
You're just a bird! You're just a bird!
Dammit, I'm never gonna
get anywhere like this.
I know!
Does it say anything in that note?
If Master Raku escapes,
this is the retrieval process
That's it!
How can I do that?!
What the hell is she gonna
make me yell all over town?!
You come back here, Raku Ichijo!
But unless I catch that bird,
I can't make things right.
Still...
Say this in a loud voice?
What should I do?
You come back here!
My sweet honey, Marika!
I... love... you!
What was that, just now?
Look, it's him.
The Shuei-gumi heir.
It's over.
Oh, you mean...
That's youth for you!
Oh, my! Master Raku?
What are you doing in a place like this?
Oh, Master Raku!
It's so good to see you looking well!
Were you a good parrot
while I was away?
Marika! Marika!
Huh?
You're all here?
Marika... Do you know what
that parrot's been saying?
Oh, you shouldn't take
any of that at face value.
That's so misleading!
Knock it off!
Thank God...
Everything's all cleared up.
All right, if you'll excuse me now.
Master Raku, I'll
thank you another time.
Good day!
For some reason, she left without
making a fuss today, don't you think?
I'm exhausted.
My sweet honey, Marika!
I... love... you!
The operation was
a resounding success!
Now, then, Master Raku, I want you
to learn this phrase next.
And try to really nail it!
My beloved Marika... I...
...love...
I'm getting the chills.
Are you okay?