I'm glad you're here.
This time, you won't get away.
Why is she here? It's still light out.
Wait, if she hadn't been with me,
would she have arrived this early?
You never quit, do you?
I'm telling you, just give up already!
Sorry, but this is something I cannot give up on.
If you do as I say, I won't hurt you.
I have only one demand. Return my insignia.
It's very important to me.
If she were just another magic
user, I wouldn't back down,
but this one's trouble...
What's with you, Old Man Rom?
Admitting defeat before we even fight?!
Young lady, you're an elf, ain't ya?
Not exactly.
I'm only a half-elf.
A half-elf?
And with silver hair... Wait, are you...
It's an accidental resemblance!
Really, it's bothersome to me.
You set me up, didn't you?
Huh? No, I didn't do anything...
After you said you'd return it to its owner,
I thought you were suspicious!
What do you mean? You two aren't working together?
Her nature never changes, no matter how
many times I start over in this world.
Hey! What are you laughing about?!
Come on, isn't that enough? Return her insignia.
And, Sat— you, hurry and get out of here.
Try not to let anyone steal it again.
Why are you suddenly being so nice?
I don't understand at all.
I don't understand you, either!
What's up with you?
Puck! Shield her!
That was a bit closer than I expected.
You saved us!
Nice one, Puck!
Thank goodness it was before five,
while you're still on duty.
Thanks!
A spirit... That is a spirit, yes?
How wonderful.
I have never dissected a spirit's stomach before.
Hey, what do you mean by that?
We can hardly negotiate, if the
item's original owner is here.
So I have changed my plans.
I shall slaughter everyone here.
You failed to see your job through to the end.
You talk a good game, but you do terrible work.
You really are just another slum dweller.
You bitch...
Cut the crap!
Don't get your kicks from picking on a little kid!
You guts-loving sadist!
Felt is doing her best to live strong...
Just because your plan was thrown off,
you think it's over and flip tables?
Are you a little kid?!
You should value life more!
Do you know how much having
your belly cut open hurts?
Well, I do!
What are you talking about?
I'm in the process of letting the justice
and chivalry I never knew I had
denounce all the world's unfairness!
And what I consider "unfair" is you,
this situation, and...
Stay tuned, folks.
There!
All done buying time...
Get her, Puck!
A brilliant display of awkwardness, which I
hope survives through the ages.
I'd better live up to your expectations!
We haven't introduced ourselves, have we?
My name's Puck.
Remember my name
after you die!
Did they get 'er?!
Don't trigger that flag, old man!
One should always be prepared.
Don't underestimate a user of the spiritual arts.
For a girl, you're well accustomed to battle.
My, it's been a while since I was
regarded as a simple girl.
Well, from my perspective, all opponents
are basically babies.
Still, you're so strong, I almost pity you.
I'm deeply touched to be praised by a spirit.
If this turns into a battle of attrition,
we should have a chance.
No, fer a spirit, the real battle is how
long they can stay corporeal.
That's right, it must be almost five...
Oh, and just when we were having
such fun. What a bore.
That's what sucks about being a ladies' man.
The girls just won't let you sleep.
But you know, staying up late is bad for
your skin, so we should wrap this up!
I wasn't just randomly throwing those around.
Does this mean I've been had?
Goodnight!
My, how lovely...
I thought I was going to die.
But you're a girl, so I don't find that
sort of thing very impressive.
Puck, can you keep going?
Sorry, I'm really sleepy...
I underestimated her a bit...
My mana's gone, so I have to disappear.
I'll take care of things here,
so you can rest. Thank you.
If anything happens to you, I'll act
according to my contract.
If it comes to it, call me, even if you
have to squeeze me out of my odo.
You're going away?
Well, that is very unfortunate.
We can't keep just sitting around, watchin', Felt.
Yeah, I know.
If we're going to run, we should get moving now.
About before, well...
I guess you kinda saved me.
But just a little.
Also, don't call me a little kid!
I'm fifteen, you know!
That can't be much younger than you!
I'll be eighteen this year...
No way! You're totally a kid!
You need to live a life that
shows on your face more!
Here I come!
Ah, but isn't it a bit boorish to cut in on a dance?
If you wanna dance, I'll show you the
best dancin' you've ever seen!
Here we go... Round an' round!
Eh? What in the—
You're so strong, I was able to do this.
Not gonna happen!
Old Man Rom!
You bad girl...
You have neither the resolve nor strength to fight.
You should have at least stayed in the
corner, making yourself small...
Damn, we're done for...
There's really nothing I can do.
I guess I'll have to Return by Death and start over.
No, I don't want to feel that pain again.
I don't wanna die...
I guess, as long as I have life,
all I can do is fight with all my might.
Haidara!
Are you okay?
Why did you...
Listen to me, Felt. I'm going to buy us time.
I'll give you an opening somehow.
So when I do, run as fast as you can!
What? You're telling me to tuck my
tail between my legs and run?!
Yes... Stick out your butt,
tuck in your tail, and run.
You're fifteen, and I'm eighteen.
That means you're probably
the youngest one here.
So it's a given we'd pick the method
most likely to keep you alive.
It's a given!
Give me a break. A minute ago,
you were cowering in fear!
That was then. This is now.
I'm not cowering now, so it's fine.
Take this!
Now! Go, Felt!
You think I'll let her go?
Whoa, I'm awesome!
But that hurt the tips of my toes
more than I expected.
You let one get away...
For once, I did feel a tiny bit annoyed.
Don't forget about me.
I've grown quite tired of that game by now.
Do you think you can still keep me amused?
If you've got some hidden true power,
now would be a good time to use it.
I do have a trump card.
But if I use it, I'll be the only one left standing.
No exploding yourself, please...
Don't do anything hasty, okay?
I won't use it.
Not when you're still here,
doing your best.
Just now, I didn't see anything...
Huh?
None of that whole conversation ever happened!
I finally remembered why I'm here, to begin with.
I'll kill you, you shitbag!
I won't let you play your trump card!
I'll blow you away and get
a happy ending!
It looks like you have a bit too much energy.
You black widow!
Well, there's no doubt you'll be
the first caught in my web.
Nice cover!
Ouch, damn it! How do you like this?!
I caught you.
That's enough.
It looks like that was a close call,
but I'm glad I made it in time.
Now...
You're...
Shall we put an end to this?
Someone!
Anyone! Is anyone here?!
Damn it! Please... Please, someone...
Someone help!
Very well.
I'll help.
Reinhard?
That's right, Subaru.
We meet again. Sorry I'm late.
Black hair, black clothes,
and a blade unique to the northern provinces.
There is no mistaking those characteristics.
You are the Bowel Hunter.
What kind of evil nickname is that?
It was derived from her unique killing style.
Her name is known, even in the capital,
as that of a dangerous individual.
Reinhard... Yes, a knight among knights,
born to a line of master swordsmen, correct?
How remarkable, having all my
opponents be so much fun.
There are many things I'd like to ask you.
I strongly suggest you surrender.
You expect a starving predator to
resist such choice, juicy prey?
Subaru, stand back a bit.
If you could stand next to her, I'd appreciate it.
You got it.
That woman is like a monster,
so don't lower your guard...
As luck would have it,
hunting monsters happens to be my specialty.
Old Man Rom is still alive?
He isn't out of the woods yet.
I have to heal him now.
You really want to? He's part of the
gang that stole your insignia.
That's why.
I need him to recover, so he'll repay
the favor by giving me information.
He wouldn't lie to the one who saved his life.
This is as much for my own sake.
I would rather not use violence on a woman.
Just as the rumors say... No,
you are even better.
I'm not sure I'll meet your expectations.
Aren't you going to use that sword at your hip?
I would love to experience its legendary sharpness.
This sword can only be drawn when needed.
The fact that it hasn't left its sheath
means this is not one of those times.
I do believe I've been underestimated.
Well, it's an upsetting judgment for me, as well.
Therefore,
I shall take you on with this instead.
Do you object?
No, it is wonderful. Wonderful!
Do entertain me, please.
If you've lost your weapon,
I strongly suggest you surrender.
She's got a second one, Reinhard!
I'm impressed you knew.
Well, I've personally experienced it...
But I don't have merely two fangs.
Would you mind if we start again?
If I divest you of all your weapons,
will you be satisfied?
If I lose my fangs, I'll use my claws.
If I lose my claws, I'll use my bones.
And if I lose my bones, I'll use my life.
That is how a "Bowel Hunter" fights.
Surely Reinhard won't fail to land
the decisive blow, will he?
Because I'm using my spiritual arts,
he cannot fight at full strength.
What do those have to do with each other?
If Reinhard were truly intent on fighting,
all the mana in the atmosphere
would turn away from me.
I'm almost done healing him.
When I give the signal, let him know.
Now he's all right. Go ahead.
Reinhard! I don't really get it, but do your thing!
What will you show me?
The swordplay of the Astrea family.
The Bowel Hunter, Elsa Granhiert.
Reinhard van Astrea, of the
line of master swordsmen.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hunting monsters is your specialty, my ass!
You're a monster yourself!
Even I'm a bit hurt by a comment
like that, Subaru.
I'm sorry I asked too much of you.
Rest well now.
There isn't a shadow left, let alone a body...
This is all that's left after just a sword swing?
It's over now?
Yeah, somehow or other. Literally.
Why are you staring at me? That's quite rude.
It's just, you still have your arms
and legs, even your head...
Of course I do. Don't say such scary things.
Yeah, you're right. It's obvious, huh?
I still have my arms, too.
And there's no knife in my back
or gaping hole in my gut.
You talk as if you've experienced
those things before.
There was a time when I did.
Oh, yeah, Reinhard... I haven't thanked you yet.
You saved my ass!
Back in the alley, too.
I guess you heard my heart's cries for help, friend!
If I did do that, I'd certainly be proud...
Friend.
She was desperately running around the streets,
and she asked for my help.
That's...
Now, hang on...
If she hadn't brought Reinhard,
we'd have been destroyed.
Just take a look at this face, and spare
me the ice-statue punishment, okay?
I wouldn't do anything so violent!
And what does your face have to do with—
Subaru!
She'll go for the gut!
He got in my way again.
That's enough, Elsa!
Soon enough, I'll disembowel everyone here.
Till then, take good care of your bowels.
Are you all right?
Whether I'm all right doesn't
matter! More importantly,
are you all right? That was far too reckless!
Ow...
Oh, it was no problem.
I sure took the long road, but I
finally reached this point.
My name is Natsuki Subaru!
And I just saved your life from a heinous villain!
Are we OK on that?
"OK"?
It means "Are we clear on that?" So...
OK?
O-OK...
I, your rescuer, saved your life.
And you are the heroine I saved!
So wouldn't that mean you should
repay me in kind? Wouldn't it?
All right, I get it.
Only if it's within my power, of course.
In that case, I have only one request!
Yes, my request is...
Tell me your name.
Emilia.
Huh?
My name is Emilia. Just Emilia.
Thank you, Subaru. For saving me.
All those times I got hurt, all the crying I did,
all the pain I felt, all the fighting
I did with my life at stake...
And my reward was her name and a single smile.
Jeez...
Talk about unequal compensation.
Anyway, Subaru, I'm impressed that you're unhurt.
That thing protected me just in time.
If not for that, I'd be in two pieces right now.
True, if not for this...
Eh?
Uh-oh. I should have seen this coming.
Subaru?
Subaru!
Man...
She's so cute when she's panicking...
A parallel world fantasy...
There. His treatment is complete.
He should be over the hump now.
By the way, Lady Emilia, what is
your relation to Subaru?
A passing acquaintance?
I don't recall ever meeting him before.
I thought our meeting, earlier today, was the first.
But he was looking for you.
He said he had something to give you.
That's why it's so strange...
What shall we do with him?
I would be glad to take him home as a guest.
No, I'll take him home with me.
That way, I can learn what's really going on.
But more importantly, what will become
of that girl and the old man?
Officially, I cannot overlook what they've done.
But...
Unfortunately, I'm off duty today.
You're a bad knight.
Is this old man your family?
Something like that.
Old Man Rom is the only one I have...
I guess he's like my grandpa.
I see. I only have one family member, too.
But he's always asleep at the
most important moments.
When he's awake, I'd never say that aloud.
I thought you'd be a lot harsher to me.
I'm sorry.
You saved my life, and I can't let a debt go unpaid.
I'll return what I stole.
If it's important, keep it hidden,
so no one can steal it again!
It feels funny, having you give me that warning.
Reinhard?
You're hurting me! Let go!
How can this be?
What is your name?
Huh? It's Felt...
And your family name? How old are you?
I don't have anything fancy like a family name!
I'm... about fifteen, I think.
I don't know my birthday.
Look, just let me go!
Lady Emilia, I am afraid I cannot
keep my promise to you.
I shall be taking this girl with me.
May I ask why? If it's for stealing my insignia...
That is, indeed, no small crime.
But compared to the gravity of overlooking
the crime unfolding before me, it's trivial.
I need you to come with me.
I'm sorry, but I cannot allow you to refuse.
Get over yourself! Just because you saved me—
That wasn't very courtly, either.
I was careful not to use too much.
Lady Emilia, I will be calling
upon you soon, most likely.
I hope you understand.
Please take good care of Subaru.
Today may be the last chance we
have to gaze calmly at the moon.
Starting Life from Zero in Another World