I've come from Lieseltania.
My name is Flora.
I'm very pleased to meet you all!
Really, you should've at least
sent me word that you were coming.
But His Majesty promised me
tickets to the Phoenix Festa,
in exchange for not saying
a word to you, no matter what!
True to form, he's just
a bit too fond of mischief.
And it was my big brother
who put you up to wearing that, right?
Yes! He said if I wore this,
you'd know me right away!
Seriously... I don't believe that guy!
But this is what I normally
wear, anyway.
A maid's uniform? But why?
Flora's working
as a maid-in-waiting at the palace.
Well, actually she's still just a trainee.
But I never would've guessed!
Corrupt Ruler
That you've been fighting for the sake
of an orphanage, Riessfeld-senpai.
I-It's really not all that big a deal.
Hey, I know. Tell us, Flora...
Yes?
What was Julis like back home?
What's that all of a sudden?!
No, no, I'd just like to know, that's all.
What was she like?
She's more or less the same
as she is now.
Whenever she was with us,
she was so kind and warm-hearted,
and when she was at the palace,
she was dashing and cool.
So she's the same as she is now!
Now, then...
Please take a look!
These are my memories of the princess!
You have so many!
There was a nun who wanted to preserve
memories as much as possible.
Thanks to her influence, the kids got
into the habit of taking pictures, as well.
Flora, what's this?
Oh, that's me getting my hair washed!
Did you see? Did you see?!
You saw, didn't you?!
N-No, I didn't! I didn't see anything!
Flora, how many times
have I told you to delete that photo?!
But... but... that's one of my
precious memories of you, Princess.
Flora, you really adore Julis, don't you?
Yes! I really look up to Her Highness!
And someday I plan to come here
as a student myself!
And then I'm gonna help everyone
in the orphanage, just like her!
Really? That's impressive!
I told you there's no need
for you to do that.
But! But! I want to do something
to help everybody, too!
You're still just a child. Don't worry
about such things, you should be—
I hear the student council president
at Jie Long is even younger than me!
So why not me, then?
It will be at least two years
before you're old enough to enroll here.
By then, I'll have already
fulfilled all your wishes.
I told you the last time
I saw you, remember?
That I'd save you all, no matter what,
and change that country myself.
And in order to do that,
I'm going to win all of the Festas.
Or do you have so little faith in me?
Of course that's not the case!
Fine, then.
That's our Riessfeld.
Your goals are lofty and epic.
But sadly, you're out of luck.
At the very least, we're going to win
the Phoenix Festa. Right, Kirin?
Uh, right!
I-I'm not going to lose, either!
Because I have a wish I can't give up!
Lady Sasamiya and Lady Toudou...
you're my princess's rivals, I see!
Rivals?!
Wh-What is it?
You have a point, I guess.
I'm home.
Huh? Yabuki's not back yet?
Your older sister... what about her?
It seems like he's seen another person
wielding that same Ogre Lux.
Oh, Mr. Amagiri!
Good evening, Priscilla.
Sorry to call you out of the blue.
Oh, no, that's perfectly fine!
I was thinking
that I needed to thank you,
but since the Phoenix Festa is still
going on, I didn't want to bother you.
But thank you very much
for the other day!
Hey, I haven't done anything
you should thank me for.
You brought my sister
back to me, Mr. Amagiri.
I can never thank you enough for that.
Oh, I know! Would it be all right
if I asked you to dinner again—
All right, enough! Just let me talk!
W-Wait a second!
Yo, Amagiri.
Good evening, Irene.
You wanted to talk to me,
not Priscilla, right?
No, that's not right, either.
It's not me that you really
want to talk to...
It's that bastard Dirk.
Good guess.
No, I'm just repeating
what I heard that damned Dirk say.
He told me that you'd be
calling me sooner or later,
wanting to get in touch with him.
Then could you give him
a message from me?
Tell him that I want to ask him
about Haruka Amagiri,
so I'd like to meet up.
Sure thing. All part of my job, after all.
I owe you one. Thanks.
But you'd better watch your back.
We're not the only ones
he's got at his beck and call.
Rumor has it that Erenshkigal herself
works for him, too.
Erenshkigal?
And also...
He's got Grimalkin
in his clutches as well.
Grimalkin?
That's Rewolf's
intelligence organization.
Those guys are seriously hard core.
Just give them the order,
and they'll do any kind of dirty work
without a second thought.
Gotcha. I'll be vigilant, then.
You do that.
There's no point
unless you still have your life.
By the way, I saw your match today.
Man, you were toiling!
No thanks to you!
Serves you right!
E-Excuse me, Amagiri!
Would you mind waiting for a second?
Hey! Hey, what's the big idea?
You're going to thank him
properly, remember?
You don't have to tell me!
A-Amagiri...
Something wrong?
No... Uh, let's see.
I just thought I should
thank you myself, see?
But don't read too much into it!
Thank me?
You know, for that thing.
The Gravi-Sheath thing.
Not that I want to admit it...
but since you busted it, I'm barely
earning anything, and it's awful...
Well, if it wasn't for you,
the fact is, I'd be a goner.
Oh, is that what you're talking about?
You saved me. Thanks, man.
Now the ball's
in the Tyrant's court, huh?
Sister...
I'm home!
Man, I haven't been home in ages!
Yabuki?
Hey, my bad. Did I wake you?
No, that's okay.
Anyway, long time no see, huh?
Well, the Phoenix Festa
is a profitable time for me, you know.
Oh, hey, by the way,
I saw your match yesterday.
So now you're into
the quarterfinals. Congrats!
DELICIOUS TEA
Though it did feel like a hollow victory.
Oh, well, you still managed
to win, so it's all good!
So who are your next opponents,
the Jie Long twins?
Those two are gonna be a handful.
I mean, their personalities
couldn't be worse.
Thanks.
I've seen their match data,
but it sure seems like they have a knack
for hitting you where it hurts.
Those two really know how to take
advantage of Star Senjutsu, after all.
I bet their opponents just hate
going up against them!
Take advantage of Star Senjutsu?
Oh, that's right, you've never
gone up against Taoists, right?
JIE LONG
Well, the short answer is
that Star Senjutsu takes
the power of a Strega or a Dante
and generalizes it
as a technique, I guess.
It's more common to see Stregas
and Dantes use distinctive powers,
but then they lose stability,
and it's easier to mount a counter-attack.
But Taoists have
no such vulnerabilities.
Is that right? Thanks.
Thank goodness. So you're awake?
Yeah. What's up?
Actually... Flora insists
on inviting you to lunch.
Apparently there's something
she just has to ask you.
Flora?
Needless to say,
as long as you don't mind...
No, that's totally fine with me.
Really? Then if you don't mind,
can you come out to the Business District?
The thing is, it's horribly
crowded along Main Street.
We should probably
meet up somewhere else.
Hey, what's this?
Looking for a place to eat?
Then I'll be happy
to recommend a place.
This is a date, right?
D-Date? Y-You moron!
Don't get the wrong idea! Flora's the one
who has some business with Ayato,
Okay...
and it's not like I want to see him...
See? Here it is.
Hey, listen to me!
Not a lot of tourists,
and the atmosphere and the food
aren't bad. A well-kept secret...
A stylish hidden café in a quiet neighborhood
Rice omelet and parfait are recommended!
I'm impressed
that you knew this place.
What do you think, Julis?
Want to meet up here?
I guess so.
Although it's annoying that it was
Yabuki who recommended it...
All right, then that's settled.
Let's meet up in two hours.
Okay.
Thanks, Yabuki. I owe you one.
Hey, not a problem.
Because after all, having you owe me one
is sure to come in handy sometime.
I'll just have to pray
that it doesn't cost me too much!
That was so delicious!
Oh... Really, now...
Look, there's ketchup
all over your face.
Okay, got it.
Thank you very much!
Well, but the atmosphere
and the food are quite good here.
I hate to admit it,
but Yabuki gave us good information.
Tell that to him yourself.
He'll be thrilled.
I will do no such thing!
I've come to grief many times,
thanks to him!
He's got a long way
to go to offset that!
So... what is it
you wanted to ask me, Flora?
R-Right!
Hold on a second, please!
Let's see...
Thank you for waiting!
Here's your jumbo parfait!
What, do you want one of those, too?
Yes.
Here's your jumbo parfait!
What are you staring at?
It's delicious!
Uh, nothing.
I was just thinking
that you're surprisingly soft on kids.
Well, I can't help it.
Since it's not often that these kids
get the chance to be spoiled.
And besides, at the orphanage
they rarely get to have such sweets.
Once in a while shouldn't hurt, right?
But you know what?
Since you've been sending us money,
it's been a lot easier.
The nuns said so.
You're sending them money?
I-It's no big deal, really. It's my
bonus money for being a Page One.
And it's not like there's anything
I could spend it on here.
Your Highness! Your Highness!
What's up?
Open up and say ah, Your Highness!
I see.
Yes, this is quite tasty.
Yes! I feel like my
tongue's gonna melt!
Oh, that's right!
While I'm at it, let me
offer you some, too, Mr. Amagiri!
You mean I can have some, too?
Of course!
The princess and the nuns always say
that good food tastes
even better when you share it!
Right, Your Highness?
W-Well, th-that's certainly true, but...
B-But you see, that spoon...
I myself just...
Okay, here you go!
Say ah, Mr. Amagiri!
You're right! This really
tastes great, huh?
Yes!
Thank you, Flora.
Uh... Julis, is something wrong?
Huh! It's nothing!
Anyway, Flora, what about those
questions you wanted to ask?
Let's get this done and over with!
Okay!
Seriously... Now we're finally
getting down to business.
Um... What was the first thing?
Oh, here it is!
All right, here's my first question.
Um, how far have you gone in your
relationship with the princess?
Wh-What kind of question is that?!
That question... you didn't
think it up yourself, did you?
Nope!
His Highness told me
to investigate the boy
who might become his
younger brother in the future!
Curse you, Brother!
I'm confiscating this!
You can't do that!
This is a job I was entrusted with!
Please let me see it through to the end!
Denied!
Uh, excuse me...
Sorry to bother you when you're busy.
Could I speak to you for a minute?
Um...
You're Ayato Amagiri, right?
That's me.
Sorry to bother you, but I wonder
if you could come with me?
Pardon me!
I still haven't introduced myself.
I'm the secretary to the student council
president at Rewolf.
My name is Korona Kashimaru!
And, you see...
the president awaits you.
President, did you say?
What does the Tyrant
want with my partner?
Hey, hold up, Julis.
Actually, I'm the one
who asked for this meeting.
What's that?
What are you talking about?
I'll explain later.
Julis and Flora, you wait here, okay?
Wait. I'm coming
with you to this meeting.
We're partners, aren't we?
What? B-But it's just Mr. Amagiri
that the president wishes—
Is there a problem?
That's fine with me.
Bring them over, Korona.
I might as well take this opportunity
to see the Glühen Rose in person.
V-Very well, understood!
Flora, I'm sorry, but there it is. You can
get back to the hotel on your own, right?
Yes! I'll be fine!
This way, please.
Get in.
So you're Murakumo, huh?
You sure look absentminded.
If someone like you is their Rank #1,
Seidoukan's nothing special.
I wonder who it was
that gave the order
to destroy such an absentminded
opponent... Tyrant?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You bastard, you've got a lot of nerve!
The other day, I heard
Irene Urzaiz say it!
- That you... Ayato!
- Julis, it's no use.
Irene only told us
because it was a one-time thing.
We don't have any proof.
But still!
And besides, we have to let it go,
or we'll only make trouble for her.
I see your wits, at least,
are reasonably quick.
Well, that has nothing to do
with what I want to ask you.
That's right.
But before we start talking,
let me warn you.
I'm not obligated
to answer your questions.
Just be sure to keep that in mind.
But... If that's the case,
why are you here?
I don't know...
let's just call it a whim.
A busy student council president
like you is acting on a whim?
No way.
There's something I can
provide you with, too.
Am I right?
That's right.
If you want something,
you have to offer something yourself,
or no deals can be made.
Fine, you pass.
What did you want to ask me?
My sister... Haruka Amagiri.
Everything you know about her.
Unfortunately, it's not as if I know
all that much about her.
I've only ever seen her once.
Where?
The Eclipse Festa.
Do you know about it, Julis?
Well, yes.
It was created by scumbags
dissatisfied with the Festas,
who wanted something
more violent and stimulating.
An illegal battle game with no rules.
No rules...
The matches are decided when one
of the players either loses consciousness...
or else...
loses his or her life.
Apparently it had a fervent following
among some wealthy patrons,
and it thrived.
However, it's been...
That's right, they did away
with the Eclipse Festa years ago.
Because the captain of the Guard
really couldn't stand it.
When I saw Haruka Amagiri,
it was as a contestant of that Festa.
You're saying...
that my sister took part in it?
Yeah.
I remember it well because she was
using the damned Ser=Versta.
And... how did that match end?
Haruka Amagiri lost.
Hey, Ayato.
Are you all right?
Uh, yeah... Sure.
Well, I hear that she didn't actually die.
Not that I know
what became of her afterward.
That's the one and only time
I ever saw Haruka Amagiri.
Is that... right?
All right, now it's my turn
to ask you a question.
Look, you...
what's Madiath Mesa to you?
Madiath Mesa...
You mean the Chairman
of the Festa Steering Committee?
Doesn't look like you're
playing dumb there.
Fine, then.
We're done talking.
Now get out of my sight.
Hold up!
There's just one thing
I can't figure out.
Just how did you find out
where we were?
We only decided to go to that café
only a few hours ago.
I could understand
if we'd made a reservation,
but on such short notice, how...
Idiot.
I'm under no obligation to answer that.
Uh, come to think of it,
when I went to pick up Mr. Amagiri
and Ms. Riessfeld,
there was an adorable
little girl with them.
Really, she looked just like a doll.
I wonder who she was?
What did you say?
She's not listed in the data
you gave me.
But she's still quite small,
and she wasn't wearing
a school emblem,
so I don't think
she's an Asterisk student.
Oh, one more thing!
She even had on a maid's
uniform, that little girl!
Can you believe it? A maid?
It really became her! She was adorable!
Tell me more about her.
Oh, my...
Now then...
T-Time for guard duty!
It's the true heroine's
time to shine!
Episode 15
Breaking the Memory Barrier
Oh, no, of course
I wasn't sleeping!
This is my hour,
so there'll be plenty of...