The culture festival
will finally begin tomorrow.
I once had someone precious
that I wished to protect.
Maids, Ghosts,
and the Stage of Dreams
The culture festival starts
for real tomorrow.
Fujimiya
Everyone's in a mad rush.
Some students are prioritizing their
club projects for the festival, like us,
and others are focusing mainly
on their class projects.
Huh?
Come to think of it,
what was our class going to do?
We decided that in homeroom.
Don't you remember?
Acting
Uh... I haven't had room in my head
for anything but acting...
Yeah, lately you've been working
day and night, as if your life depended on it.
If nothing else, I must admit I'm
impressed by how focused you are.
To the point you haven't noticed that.
Acting
Huh?
Yikes...
Haunted House
Oh, a haunted house?
Isn't this something you
wanted to try, Hina-chan?
Huh? No, I didn't really...
If you're aiming to be a stage actress,
you need to be able to play any role.
But I can't do this!
I'd freeze in front of everyone
and turn into a scarecrow!
That could work, actually.
Yes, it could.
Huh?
Oh, so your class is doing a haunted house?
What's your class doing, Mayu-chan?
Can't you tell?
A maid outfit...
So it is.
Which means...
Which means?
Mayu-chan's dressed like usual...
Does that mean you're
in the going home club?
Will you be working at Hitotose's
coffee shop during the festival, too?
No!
I'm wearing a maid outfit,
so I'm obviously a maid!
We're doing a maid café!
She's so cute.
Mayu-chan's doing what
she always does, I see.
Jeez! Why don't you guys get it?!
Looks like the maid café
part is true, though.
Maid Café
Welcome!
It looks like there are
lots more Mayu-chans.
All of their costumes
were made based on mine.
Oh! We have to hurry, too!
Can't breathe...
Almost got it...
Aki-chan, help me!
Okay.
There! All done!
You look beautiful, Hina-chan!
Yeah.
It looks great!
Not bad, I guess.
Sorry you had to help me
get dressed, Mayu-chan.
I know you're busy with
your class's café, too.
It was nothing.
Besides, I helped with the other
theater club members' outfits.
I wanted to at least help you put yours on.
Thanks!
I truly thank you.
You've done wonderfully with
the heroine's wardrobe.
Now, the rest of you
should get changed, as well.
Okay!
I-I'm Sakuragi Hinako, and I'll be
playing the h-heroine.
I'm Nakajima Yua, and I'm playing the
wealthy young detective who solves the case.
I'm Natsukawa Kuina, and I'm playing
the caretaker of the mansion.
And this is...
Hiiragi Mayuki-san,
who's playing the mansion's maid.
Pleased to meet you.
Huh? Wait! I'm not in the play!
You didn't look out of place
among the cast at all.
Yeah! You should be in it, Mayu-chan!
L-Like I told you, I work behind the scenes!
Darn it...
I hope you'll join us next time, though.
She's so cute.
With the costumes on,
everyone's starting to look
just like their characters.
Yua-chan really looks like a
wealthy young detective, too.
And I'd almost think Kuu-chan
really is a caretaker at a mansion.
And the landlady's in her tracksuit...
Huh? Tracksuit?!
Is something wrong?
U-Um, the landlady is...
Landlady?
Uh, I mean... um...
Chiaki-senpai is still in her tracksuit,
so I was a bit surprised...
What?
I'm working behind the scenes this time.
I won't be in the play.
Y-You won't?
Hina-chan, you didn't know?
N-No...
I mean, you've remained active
in the theater club all this time, right?
Yeah.
But I talked to Sensei
and decided that we should
keep the focus on
the new members this time.
That's right.
The script I wrote for this production
is better suited to fresh, new performers.
Oh...
You've been working on
memorizing the script, haven't you?
How could you not notice
who the other actors were?
J-Just memorizing my own lines
and cues took all of my brain power...
I only just finished memorizing
all my lines last night.
You do have a lot of lines,
being the heroine and all.
W-Well, I get that, but...
Still, it's unbelievable that she didn't
even read the other actors' parts.
It is indeed an unusual approach,
but it's okay for acting styles
to differ from person to person.
Some read the whole script and
calculate how they should act within it,
while others focus on mastering
only their own part.
Hinako-san.
The culprit can be none other than you!
No, I'm not the culprit!
I wasn't here in the
great hall at that hour!
Huh? I just reacted naturally...
Please continue.
Hinako-san is truly special.
Okay.
The fact that her line came to her instantly
I only just arrived here yesterday.
proves that she is one with her role.
To be stuck in the middle of this incident
all of a sudden is truly a shock.
My choice to cast her as the heroine
was clearly not a mistake.
I never thought this vacation that I was
supposed to enjoy would end like this.
Sh-She's not bad...
This morning, I seriously considered
leaving this mansion.
Aki-chan, don't tell her.
I once had someone precious
that I wished to protect.
Is she going to do that
during the play, too?
I never thought an incident
like this would happen...
Someone here is the culprit!
And this handkerchief is
the greatest evidence of that.
It can't be... It can't be!
I can't believe it! It was you?!
Yes.
I had someone precious
that I wished to protect.
Well done.
That's the first time I've made it to the end
without messing up any of my lines!
Yeah, though you came
dangerously close at one point.
You were great, Hina-chan!
Yeah! I can't wait until tomorrow!
Yeah.
Thank you! Thank you, everyone!
I couldn't have done it without all of you!
I made it this far because of you all...
Your hard work paid off, Hina-chan!
Kuu-chan...
You know...
Ah, Yua-chan, great job—
The show isn't over yet!
Oh, yeah.
Look, you two...
Now, we'll rehearse it one more time.
The show is tomorrow.
We have no time for playing around, everyone.
Right!
Fujimiya Festival
Tea Club
Tea Room
Science
Club
Experiments:
- Color-changing
water
- Slime
- Air cannon
- Hydroponics
Display
- Cartesian diver
Dumplings
Wind
Ensemble Club
Concert
Time Schedule:
Class 3-E
Movie
Screening
Performance
Performance: Handbells
Movie: "The Day is Long, Walk on Boy"
Chorus
Year 3 | Chorus
Theater Society | Play: "And Everyone Is Part of the ABC Tragedy Case File!"
Closing Ceremony
S-So this is a culture festival!
You're too impressed.
Hey!
Where are Mayu-chan and the landlady?
Mayu-chan's class is
about to open their maid café.
And Chiaki-senpai said she had
a meeting with Ruriko-sensei.
That's too bad.
I wanted us all to eat these together.
All of that?
Did you just buy everything you could carry?
No!
Oh?
This is my own selection of the
best of culture festival gourmet!
Just look at this grilled chicken skewer!
This is made with free-range chicken meat
provided by a local farm.
The meat's savory flavor
and texture are exquisite.
And the flavor of the tamari soy sauce
in the glaze is delectable!
Th-That looks delicious!
And this yakisoba!
This was delivered directly from a town
that's famous for its B-grade cuisine!
The crispy bean sprouts create
a perfect balance of textures!
And just look at this takoyaki!
It was made by a transfer student
straight from Kansai.
Fluffy on the outside, gooey on the inside...
it's a true masterpiece!
The moment you eat one...
A glorious harmony fills your mouth!
Um...
Oh?
You keep talking about how they taste.
Have you eaten all these already?
Of course!
I spent all morning conquering
every single food stall!
Seaweed
What? A-All of them?
Just what kind of stomach do you have?
Delicious!
Isn't it?
Yeah, this is pretty good.
I'm glad you like it.
It's not a culture festival if you
don't enjoy the food stall cuisine.
I don't think there are many
other students who've taken it this far...
Aside from the stalls,
you also can't miss the cafés
and other shops run by the classes.
Oh, like Mayu-chan's maid café!
Yes.
I've already checked all of those out, too.
Maid Café
Recommended
Pancake and
Omelet Rice Combo
Wow! They have a pancake
and omelet rice combo!
That's the most important item
on their menu.
Let's go eat there next.
I can't wait!
Wait, you two can still eat more?
So delicious!
Y-You're right. This is pretty good, too.
But should we really be spending
all our time doing this?
Our play is in the evening.
It's still a while off.
That's right.
Besides, we practiced until
really late last night.
But I feel a little uneasy...
You're a real worrywart, Hina-chan.
You got all your lines perfect yesterday.
I guess we have no choice, then.
Why don't we run through
just the opening lines?
Greetings, everyone.
Welcome to our mansion.
If you'll pardon me.
And who is this young lady?
Hina-chan?
Hinako?
Huh? Is it my turn?
Personnel
Only
Beyond
This Point
H-How could you forget the first scene?
We practiced that part over and over!
Sorry!
Is something wrong?
Actually, after practice ended yesterday,
I tried to check out
everyone else's parts...
Someone here is the culprit.
Y-You don't mean...
And...
Reading all those lines
made you forget your own?
Maybe...
What?!
Acting
You read something new
and forgot the old stuff?
Everyone Else's Lines
Is your brain a noodle press or what?!
S-Sorry...
Now that you mention it,
there was a food stall with
really good tokoroten noodles...
There they are.
Now everyone is here.
I-I'm gonna be so nervous...
You're getting nervous after all we've done?
You'll be fine.
No, I'm not the culprit...
We just practiced again earlier, didn't we?
All wrong!
Yeah...
You'll have Yua-sama to
back you up on the stage, too,
so all you need to do
is act with confidence.
Yua-chan...
I'll support you as much as I can, too.
Kuu-chan...
Greetings, everyone.
Welcome to our mansion.
If you'll pardon me.
And who is this young lady?
Hello.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Sheesh... I feel like the mother
of a child who's a real handful.
I never thought an incident
like this would happen...
Hinako's acting has gotten much better.
Someone here is the culprit!
And this handkerchief is
the greatest evidence of that.
Oh, no! I was so distracted by Hinako,
I forgot to pick it up!
The handkerchief!
Oh? Where is this handkerchief?
Does anyone have a handkerchief?
It appears the lady has misplaced it.
M-Miss...
This is the handkerchief you're looking for.
Here you go.
Oh, thank you, Miss Maid!
You're quite welcome.
I'll return it after the play, okay?
Is this the handkerchief you lost?
Yes, it is.
Yes, this handkerchief is
the greatest evidence of all!
Thank goodness.
The scent of the perfume on this
handkerchief tells us who the culprit is.
Looks like they managed
to get back on track.
If it came to it,
I was about to ad-lib
running out there to take it to her.
Does anyone recognize this scent?
Uh, no, you'd ruin the play's setting.
Seeing everyone acting on a stage
makes them seem like different people.
The colorful spotlights,
the gorgeous costumes,
the speech patterns
they don't normally use...
They all look like they're having fun,
and they're shining.
And to think that I'm speaking
in front of all these people...
I feel like a different person, too.
In the short time
since I came to this island,
many people have passed away.
But there is still something truly
precious that I wish to protect.
I never knew it'd be so fun
to speak in front of people!
Yes, that something is within my heart.
This concludes all of today's performances.
Thank you for joining us.
It's like what happened earlier
was just a dream...
Hinako...
Oh? Yua-chan?
Um... I'm sorry about before.
I acted so stuck-up toward you,
then I messed up myself.
Don't worry about that.
All's well that ends well!
Come on, let's go
to the after-party together!
Hinako... thanks.
That aside,
you're so cute when
you're being honest with yourself.
Wh-What are you saying?! I'm always cute!
Hinako-san, Yua-san.
Your acting was wonderful.
Ruri-chan!
I'm sorry!
I ruined the script you wrote.
Sometimes accidents are a necessary spice.
That was the kind of wonderful ad-lib
you can only see on a stage.
I was deeply moved.
Thanks!
The truth is, if this
production was successful,
I had planned to formally start up
the theater club again.
Then...
Yes.
The theater club will have
its new start tomorrow.
On that note, Hinako-san...
Would you like to make
your show business debut?
What?!
Let's star on TV together!
That's far too aggressive!
She can't, Sensei.
Kuu-chan?
Hina-chan will be working hard
with Hitotose from now on!
Hitotose?
It's a theater troupe we started
with our apartment's tenants.
I'm the principal.
We haven't put on a
performance yet, though...
I see.
Is there anything I can help with?
You'll help us?
Supporting club members in their
activities is part of an advisor's job.
I-I'll help, too!
It scares me to think of
Hinako as the principal.
Thanks for worrying about us!
I-I never said I was worried!
Hey, guys!
The after-party is starting!
Coming!
Well, shall we go?
Now that our troupe has grown,
let's do our best to make it to Suzuran.
Yeah!
I was so worried when I first came to Tokyo,
but maybe I've gotten just
a little closer to who I want to be.
Come on, let's get moving.
Hina-chan, let's go.
Okay!
The Lost Swimsuit
My choice to cast Hinako-san
as the heroine was not a mistake.
For our next performance,
how about a show in summer,
taking place at the beach,
and starring girls in swimsuits?
Next time, "The Lost Swimsuit."