"Act 9
Serious Bomber"
Oh, our lord's carriage.
Come back safely!
It's Elf. Please look, princess, it's Elf!
Why the heck do you have
to come with me?!
Hmph!
Oh my, princess, it's not fair for
you to have them all to yourself.
Share with us, wouldn't you?
--By the way, princess...
--Huh?
...the Drifters' next target
will probably be Gadolka.
They'll likely to attempt
to free the Dwarves there.
However, their security is very tight
as it is the largest armory in Orte.
I wonder...
We have no idea what
the Drifters are capable of.
If Gadolka falls, the end of
this country will be inevitable.
Are all these weapons also
going to the western front?
Yeah. We were told by headquarters
the naval transport unit was destroyed,
putting us in dire need of weapons and armor.
As a result, they ordered us to
increase the production quota.
So, we need to get the Dwarves
to ramp up production.
That may be, but...
...increasing the workload
any further is just abuse.
They will drop dead one after another.
Quite a few of them have
already been worked to death.
--What the...?!
--What the hell is happening?!
Did the mine collapse?!
The soil taken from the toilet's subfloor,
the sulfur from Boobienu, and charcoal...
It's the perfect combination for...
...black powder.
Wh-What the...?!
The hell is going on?!
The primary effect of gunpowder is...
...not the flames that char the body,
nor the shrapnel that tears through flesh.
We're charging forward. Raise the battle cry!
The enemy is terrified. Get them!
It is the sound and light,
the shock and awe...
...utter terror...
Cannons, fire arrows, and firearms
all have the same effect.
The Shimazu clan controls Tanegashima,
the birthplace of Japan's first firearm.
It's no surprise that Toyo knows
how best to put them to use.
Rush them down!
The enemy! It's an enemy attack!
Is it the Elves?!
Is this a revolt?! Shit!
Damn demihumans!
Wh-What the hell is that?!
Incredible!
Wh-What a terrible concoction...
We had no clue that
he was having us create such
a terrible powder all along.
Mix it carefully, or else
we all may die. Cautiously.
Calm down. It's all right.
You Elves are all incredibly dexterous.
Now, let's rain arrows down upon them.
These explosive arrows aren't bad.
I thought they'd work about
the same as fire arrows,
but in the hands of Yoichi and the Elves,
they became devastating weapons.
However, I wasn't expecting
them to burn this well...
We could have taken so many supplies.
Oh, well, it's too bad. Such a shame.
What the hell is happening?!
Who knows?!
Shout! Shout! Bring them to their knees!
It's going to blow! The
fire is rapidly spreading!
Run! They have us surrounded!
They will kill us all! Run!
Wh-What the...?!
The hell is happening?!
Don't give them the chance to rally!
Destroy them all!
Hey, this looks bad. Let's get out of here!
Eh?!
To the castle town! Charge forward!
Go invade the town!
The ground you step on
is Orte's largest armory,
and this land is protected by us,
the Armored Guards Corps of Orte!
We shall not give in to you rebels.
Heavy armor, heavy swords, heavy spears...
...no arrows, no bow, and no horses...
Withdraw!
Running?
We won't let you!
Olminu... I wonder if she is doing all right.
There should be no problems.
Those guys from the deserted castle
should be able to put Olminu's
powers to full effect.
"Olminu of Stone Coffins."
Her casting of the "Stone Wall Spell" is...
...unmatched.
In fact, she is probably the
most talented one among you...
...especially in the chest area.
Ah, you sound like a dirty old man.
Coming from someone who is
actually 83 years old, that fits.
Wh-What the hell is that?!
Toss them over!
The enemy is falling apart.
Perfect opportunity!
Worth its weight in gold.
Let's go!
Our heavy infantry was destroyed!
Damn it... What the hell?!
The gate! Close the gate!
Close the gate!
It's amazing he used the
"Stone Walls" in that way.
Well done, Toyohisa! As might be
expected... that was a dirty trick.
The spell was supposed to be for defense.
Instead, he used it to annihilate the enemy.
It is as if he were born to
take on the battlefield himself.
Yet, they closed the castle gate.
That could be problematic...
Huh?
Grandpa, are those raspberries good?
They're good.
Why did he even come with us?
How are we supposed to deal with
this stupid southern barbarian?
Hey, kid.
Huh?
Messenger! Messenger!
I need to send a message to Olminu!
Ah... yes, sir.
Grandpa... you...
I want more raspberries! I want more!
There's no more left.
If you don't give me more raspberries,
Carthage will fall.
Here, sir.
Can I just talk into this?
What the hell is this sphere?!
Olminu said it would work.
Come in, Boobies! Come in!
Can you hear me, Boobienu?
Shut up!
Remember my name, you jerk!
I don't give a damn.
You should still have
the charms for the "Stone Walls," right?!
Do as I tell you!
We can make things work with
your charms and Yoichi's archery!
The gate is closing!
That was dangerous...
What the hell just exploded...?
Don't know. I lit the signal fire.
It'll probably take half a day for
reinforcements to arrive, but...
it's almost impossible for them to
besiege the castle with the gate closed.
We will crash them against our walls.
The troops in the areas outside
the walls are falling apart.
Very few soldiers are left!
Damn demihumans!
When reinforcements arrive,
we'll attack those idiots from both sides.
There are stairs on the wall!
Nobu! It's amazing! Nobu!
Sure, the "Stone Walls" are great,
but they cannot be better than this sphere
by any stretch of the imagination.
There is no need of messengers anymore.
Best of all, a message can be
delivered instantly... No more time lag.
For those magicians, did
it never come to mind
that this was such an incredible discovery?
Probably because of the difference
in perspective... They have no clue.
They only consider it a convenient device
to report their daily investigations.
This sphere can also enable troops
who are far apart to cooperate
with one another...
Such an idea never entered their minds.
Splendid! Well done!
Their views on the
"Stone Walls" are no different.
Olminu cast the charms to defend Toyohisa,
but he used them a
launchpad instead, and now...
...as a tool to breach the castle.
In other words, the Drifters are those
who introduce technology as well as
recognize the differences in perspective.
Then what on earth are
these so-called "Ends"?
Why are we here?
What kind of scheme do they have for us?
That's it. That is what you are,
and what you are is the reason you are there.
That difference in view
could change the world.
Stir it up, Drifters.
There is no "way things
should be" in this world.
Keep the world turning, Drifters.
The castle is mine!
Toyo, let's go free the Dwarves.
Huh?
We've been told countless
times since childhood
that the Dwarves are strong warriors.
The Elves certainly despise the Dwarves.
Every night our fathers told us about them,
filled with fear and loathing.
But behind all that lies a jealousy
for the traits that the Elves lack.
Their strength, their perseverance,
their sharp axes...
They are likely to be captives
here in the castle town.
Once, it was inconceivable for the Elves
to fight beside the Dwarves.
But now...!
That's the way things should have been.
Let's get them out of there.
The Dwarves are vulgar, violent,
foul barbarians with scruffy beards.
They drink a lot, eat a lot, smell bad,
and are totally frightening.
Their massive arms can
crush boulders and strike steel.
Their massive legs stomp the ground.
Their massive axes cleave
their enemies in two.
And after all that, they go drinking,
laughing and singing bawdily.
All the other buildings
are the same as this one.
This place really is a concentration camp,
a "workshop" in name only.
Even after we Elves surrendered,
the Dwarves kept fighting.
We were lucky to have
just been made into serfs.
It seems the Dwarves were enslaved in
the mines or in workshops all this time.
We were wondering about the
commotion outside...
Was it your doing?
It's ironic. You of all people
came to save us, huh?
"We" didn't.
We too were saved... by the Drifters.
Whoever, doesn't matter. Free us.
We are through.
Free us. I'm begging you.
Please. Even if you are Elves...
...free us. We can fight as well.
All right.
So, you are Dwarves?
Your beard is incredible.
You're really small. You're
also really thin, huh?
You are... You are one of those "Drifters"?
Don't care about that stuff!
They just call me that.
An army marches on its stomach!
It's time to eat! Time to eat!
Hum? What happened, Boobienu?
What happened?
Have the castle defenders fallen yet?
Come in! Boobienu!
Well... it appears Toyohisa
has freed the Dwarves, but...
...the Dwarves were starving
and severely malnourished,
so Toyo started saying, "It's time to eat."
Wait! Don't tell me... they've begun eating?!
They haven't even taken over the keep yet!
They dug into the food storage,
collected all the food in stock,
including whatever survived the
fire, then dragged it over here,
mixed it all together in the
pots, and started cooking.
They actually started eating
in front of their enemies' eyes?
Ahh! The horses! The horses!
They are butchering draft horses, warhorses,
everything, and starting to cook them!
Stop them!
That jackass... really is an idiot.
Grandpa, I brought more raspberries for you.
Mmm... this is good.
As a reward, I shall present you with Gaul.
--Make rice porridge!
--Huh?
Be sure to use plenty of water in that.
Food doesn't digest well after starvation,
which may lead to death.
"This is Monkey, my lord."
Long ago, that Monkey did a horrible thing.
He said if you stuff yourself
quickly after starvation, you will die.
Eh? Monkey?
We can't allow those Dwarves to die on us.
--Huh?!
--Argh, annoying!
Just tell them to eat slowly!
That's all we can do for now.
"Nostalgic"
Ranmaru! Bring me rice bowl soup also!
No, he isn't here.
I know that.
I was aware of that, you idiot!
Aaaaahhh! I wanna eat rice!
What is rice?
What is rice bowl soup?
The assault stopped?
What's with that smoke?!
What the hell are they doing?!
Hey!
I have freed the Dwarves.
They're eating for now,
but if you haven't run away by the
time they are done, you will all die.
If you run, we won't chase after you.
Drop your weapons and surrender.
Decide quickly!
The Dwarves are focused on eating for now,
but there isn't much time
until they are through.
Once the food runs out, you'll be next.
They will completely devour you
all the way to your livers.
He's good. He is no fool.
Everything he knows, every skill he has,
is honed for the battlefield.
That was the last bite!
Now, will you give up the keep
or will you die?! Decide!
Wh-What should we do?
What else can we do?
What could we do?
They breached the first gate;
we don't have time to wait
for reinforcements to arrive!
I already know that!
Commander, the moment the Dwarves
fill their stomachs, they will come for us.
If those idiots dig through, we will fall.
They'll kill us all!
Drifters! You're not going
to kill us, are you?!
If we give up the keep,
you'll let us go, right?!
It's the warrior's way of battle
not to take the head of a soldier
who lays down his arms!
Hm. They gave up gracefully. Next...
Where is the lord of this castle?
That's me.
I've already surrendered.
You'll let me go now, won't you?
All right. I'll have them
set up a place for you
to commit ritual disembowelment,
so please wait for a little while.
Disembowelment?!
I shall act as your second
and behead you at the end.
Did you just say... disembowelment?!
What the hell?!
You lost the battle, therefore you lords
must know that an honorable
suicide should follow.
It is your responsibility
and honor as a lord!
Th-That's absurd.
Don't be an idiot, you bastard!
Why the hell do I have to
commit dis... disembowelment?!
No way in hell will I spill my own guts!
Alright, then...
You don't have what it takes to end yourself.
You are not fit to be lord.
The only thing of value
you possess is your head.
You don't need to pursue them.
Oh, you knew, huh?
You said you would assist me.
You're a man of your word.
It's just my old habit...
Those were my previous orders.
Nobody can order you to do anything anymore.
This is our battle to fight.
Well, let's get back to the food.
Yoichi, are we going to pursue them?
You don't have to do
that... at least for now.
Let's eat!
We won't be able to get closer.
Dragon cavalry are flying all over with
detection charms hanging from them.
Don't use any of our charms or magic.
They will give us away.
This is a difficult task.
I only took this job because
it's for the Octobrists.
Had it been a normal assignment
for the Adventurer's Guild,
I wouldn't have done it. It's too risky.
Appreciate it, Doug.
Huh?
That is such a convenient telescope.
Is that also a rumored
relic of the Octobrists?
Look!
Bronze Dragon! What the
hell?! It can't be...!
Although he ranks last, he's still
one of the six Great Dragons.
Will he join the Black King's army?!
Did the army stop advancing southward
because he joined the forces?
No, that's probably not the case.
Take a look at the southern
tip of the "Northern Wall."
Perhaps that's the reason.
Wh-What on earth is that?!
Is something wrong with my eyes?
Is that a field? Are those monsters farming?
Monster civilization?!
They've begun primitive agriculture!
What the hell are the Black King
and those idiots doing... over there...
...at the Northern Wall?!
Grand Master was right.
The Black King is different
from the "Ends" we've known.
He doesn't wish the
eradication of this world.
His intention is to become a savior
to the monsters who would
take the place of humans.
"Bedtime Stories"
"Soup for Hundreds"
"Cheaply Wasted"
"Act 10
Baba Yetu"