Shoot!
Huh?
Rei?
It's raining hard.
H-Help!
Rei!
Shocking No Breathing!
Haru-chan?
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
That voice.
Huh?
Makoto?
What's wrong?
Huh? They're gone.
It's still warm.
Did they go to the restroom?
What is it?
Hel—
Rei!
Ma—
Is that...
Haru-chan!
Contact Miss Amakata!
Huh?! Wait!
Hold on, Haru-chan!
It's not safe to go in alone!
Makoto!
I'll get Rei-chan!
Please!
Rei-chan, I'm coming!
No way!
Makoto... Makoto!
Wake up!
Someone...
Is anyone there?!
Nagisa? Rei!
It's beating...
Is he injured?
No...
His breathing is so weak...
Makoto!
Haruka...
Are you okay?
Where are we?
I'm guessing this is Sukishima.
The island facing the tents.
Where's Rei?
You shouldn't be moving around!
Rei!
You need to rest!
But Rei's in trouble!
Nagisa's taking care of it!
You don't need to worry.
Nagisa?
Here, Rei-chan.
Thank you very much.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm very sorry about this.
It's okay.
But it's my fault that everybody's...
That stuff can wait.
Right now, we should go
look for the other guys.
I'm sure that they're fine.
But...
I saw Makoto-senpai coming to help me,
but he didn't seem like his usual self.
Have you calmed down?
Yeah.
You're still scared of the ocean, aren't you?
I thought I'd gotten over it.
But when I saw Rei drowning,
I completely froze.
The memory of that day immediately surfaced.
Sorry I dragged you into this.
It's not your fault.
But...
I was the one who decided to hold a camp.
And I chose to start the swim club.
But that was because I wanted
to swim with you again.
I wanted to swim in a relay with everyone again.
But...
If you're not there...
It's meaningless without you!
I want to swim with you!
Ah, there they are!
Haru-chan! Mako-chan!
Rei! Nagisa!
Fantastic!
You're both okay.
Rei...
Sorry that I couldn't save you.
Don't say that!
I'm the one
who should apologize!
It's okay. I'm just glad you're unharmed.
It's not okay.
Why were you swimming
in the ocean at night?
You were practicing, right?
He wants to catch up to the rest of us.
Yes...
Besides, Rei-chan wasn't the
only one at fault.
Mako-chan, you shouldn't have
tried to save him by yourself!
And you just dove into the water
without thinking, Haru-chan!
So did you.
Well, at least everyone's okay.
Anyway, isn't it kinda cold?
Yeah...
I wonder if we can find shelter
from the rain somewhere.
Oh.
Sukishima Rest House
Rest howse? What's a rest howse?
It's a rest house.
Let's go inside.
Wait, we're really going inside?
Makoto.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Hey...
Stop talking like a couple
about to enter a haunted house.
Did you see that shadow?
Oh, sorry.
I-It's okay.
I'll take a look inside,
so wait here.
I'll come with you.
It'll be fine since we're all together.
Wow, it's so dark.
I have a feeling something's
going to pop out.
Whoa!
What?!
A flashlight.
Don't scare us!
Nothing here.
Looks like this was a kitchen.
Oh, then there might be food.
I'm starving.
How can you be thinking about
food in this situation?
Aww...
That wasn't a compliment.
Okay, let's look around!
I'll check the cabinet over here.
Haru-chan and Mako-chan
can check under the sink.
Rei-chan gets to check the
dubious-looking fridge.
Wait! Why do I get stuck
with the worst job?!
Because Rei is for refriger-"rei"-tor!
That's a bit of a stretch!
I-I refuse!
I have a feeling something is going
to ooze out if I open the door!
Stop it.
Then we'll use rock, paper, scissors
to decide who checks the fridge.
Do we really have to open it?
It's the most likely place to have food.
There's no power though.
The fridge is our only hope right now!
Okay, rock, paper,
scissors!
See? It's still Rei-chan!
Fight!
Whew...
It's empty? That's too bad.
Okay, everyone!
Put these on!
Sukishima
Rest House
Why are we wearing these?
I couldn't find anything else.
Don't complain.
We're dry now, so it's not necessary.
And once again...
Pineapple mackerel...
Looks like we lucked out.
Uh, can't you at least eat them separately?
This water hasn't expired yet,
so we can boil it and drink it.
Pineapple mackerel and hot water...
You should be grateful that
we found anything edible.
True, I just have to use my imagination.
This isn't water. It's rich consommé soup.
The ultimate soup, glistening gold.
Doesn't that just make you feel worse?
This is the problem with people
who have no imagination.
At least it warmed us up.
Yeah.
It's still raining.
I guess we'll have to stay
here until morning.
What do we do next?
Sleep.
What?!
But we're stranded on a deserted island!
Aren't we supposed to harpoon fish
and search for edible mushrooms?
We're not on a TV show.
Still, it's hard to go to sleep in this situation.
I know.
That's what we can do!
Who's it gonna be? Who's it gonna be?
Haruka
Nagisa
Rei
It's Rei-chan!
Uh, my name's on three of the faces.
Because you're Rei-chan.
What's that supposed to mean?
Okay, Rei-chan!
Tell us an embarrassing story.
Why does it have to be an embarrassing story?
Go ahead!
This happened when I was in fifth grade.
I was on a school field trip...
Huh? It's not here.
Hey!
Someone left this in the bath!
Whose is it?
Gross.
Oh, it was your underwear.
Don't rub it in.
Rei, uh...
Don't worry.
If you leave your underwear in the
locker room, I'll grab it for you.
I won't!
Haruka
Nagisa
Rei
Haruka
Oh, Haru-chan's up next.
Tell us about a romantic encounter you've had.
Or in short, a love story!
Love story?
Go ahead.
My turn?
Haruka-senpai's been in love before?
Er, I have no idea.
When I was in grade school,
my parents took me
to climb a mountain nearby.
That was where I had my fateful encounter.
I couldn't look away.
That intensely beautiful,
positively vibrant,
sparkling and pristine
waterfall.
Waterfall?
That doesn't count as a love story, Haru-chan.
Okay! I'm up next!
I've got a performance for you.
What are you doing?
You can't tell?
That was a rockhopper penguin imitation.
It was?
I couldn't tell.
Wh-What?!
Why couldn't you tell?!
Just look at this!
Ah, Mako-chan!
You finally smiled.
Huh?
That's good.
You seemed a little subdued.
Sorry for making you worry.
Uh...
I've been wondering...
When you tried to save me,
you were acting strangely.
We're not gonna discuss it.
But...
Just drop it!
Thanks, Haru.
It's okay.
This is something I want to tell them.
I suddenly felt scared.
Scared?
Scared of what?
I'm scared of the ocean.
When I was little, I would often visit this
small fishing harbor in the next town.
There was this old fisherman
who was really nice
and would sometimes play with me.
During the summer, there was
a festival near the harbor.
I wanted to scoop goldfish, but I
had already used up my allowance.
Instead, I just watched the goldfish swim.
But then, the old fisherman showed
up with some goldfish for me.
I was really happy!
But later that summer,
there was a big typhoon,
and the old fisherman's boat sank.
Many of the people on board drowned.
The boat sank about three
kilometers away from the harbor.
We swim three kilometers every day.
I wasn't so much sad
as I was scared.
I fed the goldfish and changed
the water in the bowl,
but they still died.
Ever since, I've been scared of the ocean.
It feels like there's something
unknown hiding in the water.
That's enough, Makoto.
But you still tried to save me.
Hey, can I ask you something?
If you're scared of the ocean,
why did you participate
in this training camp?
Because I wanted to swim.
Because
I wanted to swim with you guys.
When the four of us swim together,
I feel like we can go anywhere.
The rain stopped.
Wow! It's gorgeous!
The sky is nice and clear.
That's the Summer Triangle.
There's Vega from the constellation Lyra.
Deneb from the constellation Cygnus.
Altair from the constellation Aquila.
Is that a squid constellation?
Where's the mackerel constellation?
Neither of those exist.
Is that the rockhopper penguin constellation?
No such thing.
What? That's no fun.
Let's pretend there is one.
Look at this.
It's not that far away.
If we wave, Miss Amakata
or Gou-san might spot us.
They're probably still asleep.
Hopefully, they notice we're missing
when they wake up and send a boat.
I'll swim over and let them know.
Huh?
Don't be stupid!
He's right!
But the ocean is so calm right now.
Plus...
Everybody's here with me.
I'll come with you then!
I'm coming as well.
Okay, let's see who can get there first.
A race, huh?
Fine with me.
Hurry up, Haru-chan!
Let's go, Haru!
I'm pooped...
We're almost there.
Hang in there, Rei.
What are they doing?
You're falling behind, Nagisa-kun!
I'm falling asleep...
Nagisa! Wake up!
Oh, dear...
What are you guys doing?
Hung out to dry overnight?
Okay, okay.
Time to start practice!
Um...
Are you listening?
Wake up!
5 Days Until the Prefectural Tournament!!
I wanted to hear more embarrassing stories.
I have an embarrassing story about Rin.
Really? Let's hear it.
Back in grade school, Rin accidentally
called the coach Mom.
0 Days Until the Prefectural Tournament!!
It's Today!!
Don't tell them!
Haru, you're the one who said,
"I'm home!" when you arrived
at our swimming school!
Never happened!
It totally happened!
Next time: One Style Final.
One Style Final!
Will Haru-chan win or Rin-chan win?!