The Second Plate
Episode 12
Not a day goes by in Paris without someone
mentioning the name of
Mr. Shinomiya Kojiro, the chef of SHINO'S,
and now he's opening his first
restaurant in Japan in Tokyo.
Gourmands have mounting expectations
for Mr. Shinomiya's dishes,
as he is called the Magician of Legumes...
Huh?
I barely get any sleep
getting ready for the opening.
That's exactly why Chef Dojima
suggested sending over a student
to serve as your opening staff.
It'd be mutually beneficial.
Shinomiya Kojiro
Chef, French Restaurant SHINO'S
I'm sure you would be happy to cooperate,
given that the request is coming from me,
a sad hired chef at Totsuki.
So he said.
Like I said before,
don't hold that against me!
What would you know about any of this?!
You're a hired chef for the Totsuki Group!
I won't accept anyone less
than one of the Autumn Election finalists.
'Sup!
Thanks for having me, Shinomiya-senpai.
The Magician Once More
I wasn't expecting you,
of all people, Yukihira.
Yeah, I was surprised, too!
I didn't think I'd end up in your restaurant.
I'll be in Shinomiya Kojiro's kitchen...
Not to mention, I need to make a visible
mark if I'm gonna pass the Stagiaire.
It won't be easy, but I'll do it.
First, you'll be wrapping up
construction and interior work.
Huh? That's the stage they're still at?
Hurry up and work!
Do you want to get fired?!
Got it!
Chef Shinomiya!
Gao Wei
Service Manager,
SHINO'S Flagship Restaurant
We have to create the menu
at the same time, too.
Lucie Hugo
Chief Blucher,
SHINO'S Flagship Restaurant
That's right!
We should ask contractors!
Considering our remaining budget,
we'll do what we can on our own.
I was very selective about things
like the interior and the dishware.
But Chef Shinomiya, you could
get any budget you want.
You have the Pluspol Award.
All the sponsors who backed
my flagship restaurant
You're thinking about opening a new restaurant at a time like this?
Don't go, Shinomiya!
Come back in 6 months... No, a month!
have opposed my opening this restaurant.
I can't ask them for money.
Yeesh! You're too proud!
The pre-open is tomorrow!
Oh, sorry.
We're staff from SHINO'S,
the flagship restaurant.
We're here to support the Tokyo restaurant
until things settle down after it opens!
Right!
Nice to meet you!
He's the head chef of
SHINO'S Tokyo, Abel Blondin.
Abel Blondin
Head Chef, SHINO'S Tokyo
(Ex Sous Chef, SHINO'S)
He was the sous chef in the main restaurant,
so he's Chef Shinomiya's right-hand man.
Nice to meet you.
Sure, hi.
Well, good luck.
Hey, cut the chatter!
Yukihira, come over here!
Got it!
Opening a restaurant's tough, huh?
Well, I'm lucky I get to train
at your restaurant, Senpai.
Shut up and just carry the cabinet!
What's with him?
He's acting so familiar with Chef Shinomiya!
He has no idea how long it took me
to get friendly with Chef Shinomiya!
And when he finally picked me to be
the head chef of the Tokyo restaurant,
it was the best moment of my life!
Yeah, yeah.
It's only the millionth time
you're telling us this.
But Chef Shinomiya's gotten
pretty mellow, hasn't he?
Did the change happen
after he went to Japan in spring?
Could be.
He was some kind of judge, right?
I think he became a bit nicer
when he got back.
He'll teach you with patience
if you ask him about cooking, too.
Yeah, right?
He might complain while doing it, but still!
Maybe he actually likes teaching
and looking after people.
Focus on the work at hand.
By the way, Shinomiya-senpai,
what made you decide
to open a new restaurant?
And why in Japan?
I read in Totsuki Sports that it's rare
to open a new restaurant
when you're trying to get
three Michelin stars.
And what did you mean earlier?
Huh?
About being lucky that
you can train at my restaurant?
It would've been easier to pass the Stagiaire
if you'd been assigned
to a small local restaurant.
I need to come up with a specialty.
I can't stay the way I am now.
I have to take one step forward
and shine a new light on my cooking.
Break time!
I'm exhausted.
We can finally see the light
at the end of the tunnel, though.
What should we do for lunch?
I'll make something—
I'll do it.
What?
Chef Shinomiya will cook for us?
What's going on here?
Set the table, will you?
We'll get to eat
Chef Shinomiya's staff lunch!
Mincing chicken!
Carefully sauteeing mushrooms,
hen-of-the-woods, and shimeji with butter...
Then pour in an appareil made from
eggs, soy milk, and white miso
into a mold lined with pie crust dough.
Wow, it looks delicious!
What is this dish called?
It's a quiche.
It's originally a regional dish
from Lorraine,
and a typical lunch menu item,
even in Paris.
Not that you'd know, since you're
not familiar with France.
Oh, I see!
It's perfect for a staff lunch, too.
Thanks for the food!
I'll savor it.
The magic of legumes...
What is this crunchiness?!
Burdock root, right?
Bur-what?
It's no wonder you don't know.
The ingredient tends to be
avoided in the West.
The crunchy texture of
thinly-shaved burdock root
combines with the melty cheese!
It pairs well with the juicy chicken
and the black pepper, too!
How'd he achieve such deep flavors
without even using bouillon?
He extracted the sweetness and
bitterness from the skin of the burdock root
in perfect balance, to provide an edge to the
mellow flavors of the chicken and cheese.
Combining Japanese ingredients
in this way into a regional French dish!
This dish is good enough to serve
at the main SHINO'S restaurant!
No wonder you're the Magician of Legumes!
Magician of Legumes
Damn, I've still got a long way to go.
All right, let's open up some wine!
What?!
Aren't we barely within budget?
This is my cooking.
It'll go to waste
if we don't pair it with wine.
Got it!
Idiot, bring better wine!
Okay, sorry!
After making something this good,
he still thinks it's not good enough?
Yukihira.
You will get closer to your own specialty
over the course of this week.
That is, if you can keep up with
the work I require until the end.
Are you prepared, Monsieur Yukihira?
Yep!
The Next Day: Day 1 of the Pre-Open
It suits you better than I thought it would.
What do you mean, better than you thought?
The chef's uniform.
And here I thought
I'd get a laugh out of you.
Oh, well.
It's almost time for the pre-open.
Don't fall behind.
Yep!
By the way, what's the difference between
the pre-open and the actual open?
Let's see.
Basically, it's a practice run
before the official open.
You invite mostly people you know,
and check how well the staff are working
together while serving guests food.
Huh!
I see.
Also, it's partly to test
the new menu of SHINO'S Tokyo.
We'll be changing dishes every day
while checking how the guests respond.
On the final day of the pre-open,
we'll even do a competition between
the staff members for new menu items.
A competition!
Yukihira!
You're done with your assigned tasks?
Oh, yeah.
I peeled everything,
and made lobster bouillon.
Oh, I've also already marinated octopus
and daikon root for half a day.
Good! Yukihira,
you'll be my assistant for now.
Once you get used to the work,
you might also become Abel-san's assistant.
Okay, I'll try my best!
In the pre-open, three courses
will be available for order.
Depending on the course,
a different main dish is served,
or more amuses-bouches are served.
Well, either way, it's easy when you know
every dish that needs to be prepared.
Shinomiya-san, it's been too long!
Welcome.
Thank you for coming.
The first customer has arrived.
I should get in position—
What's with this sudden tension?
Please watch over me, O Lord.
The customer has been seated.
Let's go.
Oui, Chef!
So fast! Yet so quiet!
I can only hear the sound of knives,
and the simmering of the soup.
Don't make any unnecessary noise.
Next time that happens,
I'll be kicking you out.
I see.
It's so you don't miss
any minute change in sound.
Table 1's amuse-bouche is ready.
Oui!
It's different from any other
kitchen I've experienced!
So delicious!
It's just as good as its reputation!
He's indeed a magician!
The hors d'oeuvres are ready.
Oui!
For Table 2 next.
Four guests for Table 3.
Orders for Table 4.
Yukihira, don't fall behind.
Quietly strain that fumet de poisson.
Hurry.
Got it!
The workload is huge.
Even single prep work task has double the
number of steps there'd be for a diner dish.
In addition, even while
we're making appetizers,
we also have to start preparing the
time-consuming main dishes at the same time.
Yukihira, langoustine!
Er, langoustines are... Norway lobsters!
Here you go!
Also, prepare a mirepoix ready to go
by around the time Table 3 finishes eating.
Mirepoix...
Diced aromatic vegetables!
Shit. I'm deciding so slowly.
But I can manage to keep up, just barely.
Table 3 just got their appetizer,
so I need to start with
prepping the fish for Table 1.
Yukihira!
Where's the mirepoix?!
Table 3's already finished!
Crap!
Sorry, it's not ready yet!
In a course menu,
it's an ironclad rule to serve the next dish
only after everyone at the table
has finished their current dish.
You have to match the pace of the guests
and adjust when you'll serve the next dish!
There are multiple tables,
and they all arrived at different times.
If you rush to prep for one table,
a different table will sneak up on you!
Yukihira, start prepping
the mirepoix right away.
Lucie, delay Table 3's order!
Prepare Table 1's fish first!
Oui!
Wei, Table 3's meat dish
will be delayed five minutes.
Go explain to the customers.
Oui!
Abel, clean up after Yukihira's mistake.
Oui, Chef.
I'll assist Table 1's order.
Step aside.
Got it.
Instead of helping Abel-san,
I held him up instead.
Until now, if I've fallen behind,
I've just had to worry about
catching up on my own.
But here, if I fall behind,
I'll affect everyone involved
in preparing the course menu!
I'll say this.
I haven't accepted you as one of the team.
Abel!
What, you disagree?
We don't need anyone who'll
slow down the kitchen's workflow.
I'm the head chef of SHINO'S Tokyo.
I have a responsibility to manage the work.
Now you know.
In the end, you're just part of the Stagiaire.
Don't get arrogant and think you've
made your way into the team.
Now that you get it, know your place—
Sorry, I'll be right back!
The pre-open lasts five days.
I can't leave like this!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
I'm going to become a core member
by the last day!
Hey, where are the ingredients?!
Hurry up!
Sorry!
No, you've failed.
What?!
You failed.
Fail!
You can use the staff shower
anytime you want.
Keep Out
The kitchen staff usually arrive around noon,
so take care of personal matters until then.
Don't oversleep, no matter what.
Got it.
Based on how you worked today,
it'd be better if you didn't stay, really.
My success in Japan depends on the pre-open.
You may not feel the pressure,
being a student and all.
Am I wrong?
I plan to bring in more
customers starting tomorrow.
The workload will increase
two or three-fold.
Unless you change, you won't
be here by the last day.
Chef Shinomiya!
You're not going to give him any advice?
I don't have the time to hold his hand.
Besides...
No, never mind.
Yukihira, don't fall behind.
Quietly strain that fumet de poisson.
No, no!
This recette requires
the ingredients to be julienned!
Redo!
If you do it again, I'll kick you out.
Is it delicious, or disgusting?
Tell me!
Enjoy!
Hayama Akira
Yukihira Soma
Kurokiba Ryo
43rd Autumn Election Main Tournament
Winner
Hayama Akira
My own...
...unique...
...cooking.
There are three possible ways to cut the
potatoes that are served with this recette:
pont neuf, allumette, and paille.
The thickness and the length
of each type differ.
As for how to cut fish,
there's médaillon, darne,
tronçon, and escalope.
I have to differentiate between them
based on the ingredients and the dish.
Day 2 of the Pre-Open
Good morning, Abel-san!
Good morning, Lucie.
Good morning!
Yukihira?
You're here early.
Hi!
Um, so I had questions about how to cut
ingredients, the ones I messed up yesterday.
May I ask you for your time?
We have to clean and prep ingredients.
You've got some nerve asking
after holding us back yesterday, huh?
The restaurant can't waste any more on you—
Abel-san!
The cleaning and peeling...
everything's done.
Lucie.
Answer Yukihira's questions.
S-Sure!
What do you want to know, Yukihira?
Oh, about the different cutting techniques...
I get that médaillon and darne
basically look like this,
He did all this work by himself?
but do tronçon and escalope
basically look like this and that?
Did he even get any sleep?
Oh, well tronçon is like this. Get it?
No good!
Redo!
Sorry, right away!
You have 20 seconds.
Got it!
Yukihira, ingredients!
Sorry, I'll get right to it
after I'm done with this!
Day 3 of the Pre-Open
Isn't that kind of like an hors d'oeuvre?
Okay, I'll make it an entree.
Too slow! Faster next time!
Got it!
Day 4 of the Pre-Open
Again?
This is three days in a row.
Yeah, I'm really sorry
to bother you like this.
So, today I have about fifty questions!
I can help.
Um, it's about this.
Oh, you did it just like I taught you.
There are about three things
I want to improve.
What about?
Yukihira...
First off...
How can he stay so indifferent
No, no, no!
So my way is fine, then.
after being berated day after day?
You can figure out the rest on your own.
He should be painfully
aware of how useless he is.
Got it!
Why isn't he dejected?
Yes, tomorrow is the last day
of our pre-open event.
All right!
Yukihira—
The fish for Table 8, right?
The prep work's all done.
Merci!
Finished with prepping the scorpionfish!
Please check!
Finished with deglazing the suc!
Finished with making champignon tourné!
Finishing with mincing shallots!
Please check!
It's fine! Good work!
Yukihira, Table 6's next!
Got it!
I don't have even a second
to feel sorry for myself.
Because I'm having way too much fun
mastering new techniques!
He's absorbing it all!
With incredible force and speed!
Table 4's quickly working
through their course!
Can we hurry up their soup?
Damn!
I'm not done with the prep work.
Abel, can you handle it?
Sorry!
I can't right now.
I'm busy here, too!
The prep work's done.
Yukihira.
You've memorized the recette, haven't you?
Finish the dish.
Got it!
Well, that was the best food
I've ever tasted!
I'm glad I could check it out
during the pre-open.
I'd like to bring a few friends next time.
Once it opens, we won't be
able to make a reservation.
Good work, everyone!
The pre-open ends tomorrow.
Don't slack on the last day, Yukihira.
Of course not!
Good job, Yukihira!
Thanks!
Abel, do you object to
keeping Yukihira around?
No.
Well, I suppose he gets
passing marks right now.
I was really worried for a while.
You didn't give him any advice.
There's no point if he can't
figure it out on his own.
Besides...
Shinomiya-senpai, I'm sorry to bother you,
but I have one more thing.
Yes, Monsieur Yukihira?
Do you have another complaint?
Does that Totsuki rule apply to alumni, too?
What are you talking about?
Shokugeki.
If I beat you in a Shokugeki,
will you rescind Tadokoro's expulsion?
You challenged me, of all people.
You wouldn't fail at something
like the Stagiaire.
I lost.
Damn it!
Shinomiya-senpai!
Sorry, do you have a minute?
What, Yukihira?
Do you have a complaint?
No.
Since it looks like I'm allowed to stay
until the last day, I have a request.
What is it?
The competition.
There'll be a new menu item competition
after the restaurant closes tomorrow, right?
I want to submit a dish, too.
What?!
The competition?
But you've had your hands full assisting us!
Yukihira!
No, I always planned on
participating in the competition.
I want to make everything I've envisioned
until now into a reality as soon as I can.
Will it be anything decent?
Yes.
Come to think of it, it'll be the first time
I'll have tasted an original recette of yours.
Yep!
Very well.
But I won't guarantee that your
hard-won confidence will survive this.
I swear I'll make him speechless...
...with a dish only I can make.
With my specialty!
Food
Wars
The Second Plate
Final Episode: Pomp and Circumstance
Final episode, "Pomp and Circumstance."