Is it true, Lizardia?
Yes, High Priestess.
It's underground in the Holy Misurugi Empire.
The Aura signal certainly came from there.
You have done well.
The time has come.
Children of Aura, we will hereby recapture
the almighty mother Aura from Embryo's hands.
Lizardia, open the Singularity as scheduled.
As you wish.
This battle is for the fate of this world.
May Aura and Earth have victory!
Victory!
Resonant Battlefront
The DRAGON world...
I don't intend to treat you like prisoners.
...in turn, to learn about you.
That is Salamandinay-sama's wish.
What's she trying to pull? Jeez.
Oh, I forgot.
That's awful! You're the one that wrapped me up!
I didn't want to risk sleeping
with a frustrated animal.
I told you, that was a misunderstanding!
What are you looking at?
Huh? Nothing.
Good morning.
Huh?
Ah, morning intercourse, I see.
Please, continue.
More, please.
Dear, be sure to chew properly.
Okay, Mom-san.
Vivian.
Morning-san!
Salamandinay-sama.
Did you sleep well last night?
I ended up staying up all night talking with Mii.
I'm so tired!
That's good to know.
Now, sit down.
Let us have breakfast, as well.
Huh? Okay.
Please, eat up.
Th-Thank you.
Is it to your liking?
It's really good.
I've been eating emergency rations for so long...
How can eat this stuff so casually?
What if it's poisoned or something?
S-Sorry...
I wonder if Vivian's okay...
Huh?
Appeasing the enemy to gain information.
It's the oldest trick in the book.
No way.
I'm not convinced that's even her real mom.
They don't look like strangers, though...
Eat up before it gets cold.
I know.
Going back home?
I wanted to show her the house she was born in.
I want to see it!
Okay, I'll be back in a bit.
They're really getting along, huh?
Ange?
I don't like it.
Any of it.
So?
Yes?
I've had enough of this farce.
What's your goal?
What do you plan to do with us?
They say you can't fight on an empty stomach.
Have you had enough to eat?
Huh? Yes.
Then let us go.
What is this?
An ancient arena.
It is said that many a warrior
gathered here to compare their might.
Wait, is this facility five hundred years old?
It's perfectly preserved...
The princess restored it herself.
Huh?
Salamandinay-sama uses her great
intellect to study the old world.
She has restored many artifacts for modern use.
Even our Ryushinki was—
That's confidential, remember?
Sorry.
So, what are we doing here?
Will you fight?
Alongside us.
Huh?
Our goal is to recapture Aura and take back
the balance and stability that we had lost.
The prime evil that stole Aura, killed our people,
and made you fight is Embryo.
Defeat him, and our fighting will end.
We get Aura, and you get freedom.
Our goals may differ,
but our enemy is the same.
We can cooperate.
Oh, that's what this is!
You just want to use me, too.
As a soldier.
All that talk about wanting us to learn,
wanting to get to know us...
All of those niceties were calculated.
That is correct.
You are a valuable asset.
To hell with that.
I'm done—
Done being used by someone, right?
I thought you would say so,
which is why I brought you here.
Let us have a competition, Ange.
A competition?
Yes, for your future.
If I win, you will become my property.
Why do you get to decide?
But if you win, I will release the two of you.
Go where you wish, do what you will.
It will be up to you.
Ange...
"Slavery or freedom.
Seize it with your own hands."
Is that right?
Fine. Let's do it.
Great.
All I have to do is hit that ball back into the box?
That is correct.
Let us begin.
Service, Salamandinay-sama.
Me, property?
Who does she think I am?
That lizard bitch!
I'll show her!
Fifteen-love, Salamandinay-sama.
Oh, dear. Was that too fast?
I'll go easy on you, then.
No thanks!
Fifteen-all.
Salamandinay-sama, right hand, green.
Ange, left hand, red.
This is more than I expected, Ange.
What?
I was looking forward to this, somewhat...
Until now, there has been no
one who could fight on my level.
Salamandinay-sama, left hand, red.
So I am really enjoying this.
Damn you!
You're using your tail! Isn't that cheating?
Don't!
Hey!
Biting my tail is cheating!
You don't have to cry about it.
I know, but...
The princess is laughing.
I don't think I've ever seen her like that.
I am impressed, Ange.
You have impressive skill.
You're not bad either,
Salamanday.
It's Salamandinay.
I'd never had such a match in Iaria, either.
Iaria?
It's a sport in my world.
Then let us play your Iaria next time.
We can't.
Why not?
Because Normas aren't allowed to play.
Norma... a non-human incapable of using mana.
How twisted...
For the haves to discriminate
against the have-nots.
No matter how much we suffer,
we study with Aura, and think and exist
within bonds of caring for one another.
Do you not feel anything about
a world as twisted as yours?
I know that as a princess,
you were once in a position to lead others.
Is it not your duty as a leader
to right the world's wrongs?
How convenient of you.
I'm not a princess anymore.
Leadership, duty, that's none of my business.
Besides, some people are content
with that twisted world. So who cares?
In the end, it's you people
who want to change the world.
Embryo and Aura have nothing to do with me.
Then what will you do now?
Huh?
Knowing the truth, do you still intend to do nothing?
You have some interesting friends.
Right?
And then when I fell asleep,
Salia started reading a secret book
from inside my drawer.
What the?
Salamandinay-sama!
It's the Iaria stadium.
What the?
This way!
The house!
Enryugou!
Kaname, notify the high priestess.
Naga, take those two somewhere safe.
Yes.
Ange, we will continue our competition later.
Once we notify the high priestess,
we should go, too.
I know.
You two come this way.
Huh?
Wh-What are you doing?
I'm going to help Vivian.
Wait, we aren't done repairing that machine yet!
This place is dangerous.
Escape to the temple!
Salamandinay-sama!
Hurry!
Help!
Mii!
Ow.
Were you all right, Mii?
Mom-san!
Dammit, dammit!
What am I supposed to do?
Retreat, Salamandinay.
High priestess...
The Ryushinki is pivotal in
the fight to recover Aura.
Voice communication
We cannot risk it.
But...
The people of Vivel are headed that way.
Let them take care of the rest.
That won't be enough.
Retreat.
I cannot abandon these people!
This is an order.
Why are you just standing there, Salamandrill?
Ange!
What is that?
It's Embryo.
Embryo can control time and space.
Me, my dad, my friends...
They all died, buried in rock!
Like that!
Vivian...
Why did you do that? It was dangerous.
I have training! I'd have been fine.
It's a mother's duty to protect her child.
Mom-san...
Vivian!
What do we do, Salamando?
So long as we don't know what's causing it,
there is nothing we can do.
I know! We have that thing.
Huh?
The thing that wrecked Arzenal.
What if we used it to clear that tornado?
It will not work.
Why not?
The Spacetime Convergence Cannon
will destroy not just the city,
but the entire temple.
So cut the power by about 30%.
It cannot be adjusted so easily!
You're not very accommodating, damn it.
Hurry up and go, Mii.
I won't go.
I won't go without you.
Mii...
I know.
It doesn't need to be 30% less powerful...
Huh?
I just have to cancel it out after you fire it!
Like last time.
A counter-blast? That wouldn't be—
Whatever it is, we don't have a choice, do we?
But—
Aren't you a princess, Salamanman?
Stop the crisis and save your people.
That's the duty of a ruler.
I understand. We will do it!
Spacetime Convergence Cannon
Ange!
You're falling, Ange!
I can see that!
Hurry up and recover!
Not now of all times!
You're the weapon that
destroyed the world, aren't you?
Get a grip, Villkiss!
Mom!
Mii!
Looks like we managed somehow.
Thanks to you, my people are safe.
You have my gratitude, Ange.
I just helped a friend.
I didn't think that song could help us.
Huh?
The song you sang is the song
Embryo sang to destroy this world.
Where did you learn that song?
My mother taught it to me.
She said it would show me the right path,
no matter what happens.
That is the same as us.
The Song of the Stars...
Aura taught us that song, too.
How foolish it was
for me to try and own you.
I am humbled in my immaturity.
Protected the people and stopped a crisis...
That is how a leader must be.
I would like to become your friend, too.
To learn with you, and walk with you...
But "Salamandenden" is so long...
Huh?
I'll just call you "Salako."
Then I will call you Anko (red bean paste).
No, you won't.
Anko isn't any shorter!
But it sounds tasty.
No! It's so sweet and blubbery.
We're rivals giving each other names,
and you're calling me Anko?!
I see.
The Black Angel of Destruction
Maybe Kinako (soy flour)?
Are you trying to pick a fight?!