So for this problem—
What? I still don't get it.
Akagi, why did you decide to go out with me?
Ryoko-chan, you're calling me Ma-kun,
not Akagi. Remember?
Authority
Are we seriously doing that?
I'm not answering your question
unless you call me Ma-kun.
Ma-kun.
I couldn't hear you.
Say it up close.
Ma-kun.
Seriously, we were talking
about something important!
You knew I was going to do that.
What did you even see in me anyway?!
I wonder.
Dammit, we were in the middle
of something serious!
You knew I was going to do that.
What do I like about you?
Your face, I guess.
What?
So my personality doesn't matter, does it?!
You have a cute face, though.
You don't care about
what's on the inside at all?
Well, you're cute.
Again, not the point.
You're cute, Ryoko-chan.
Dammit, shut up!
Then what if you found someone cuter than me?
Would you go for her?
It's possible.
Die!
Don't get upset.
You've got plenty of things going for you.
Like your boobs—
Face, boobs... That's all you care about!
You don't care about who I am, do you?!
I never said that, did I?
I think I do care about what's on the inside.
What's so good about me, then?
Nothing.
Nothing?
Not at all?
Nope.
You said it yourself.
You're short-tempered and crass.
Well, sorry.
Guess I'm not...
And you're a pain in the ass
when you sulk like that.
Then why don't we break up already?!
There you go again.
Sure, you've got a lot of problems, but...
Shut up!
I don't want to hear it!
But I still like you.
Y-You just like my boobs or some shit, right?
I like your personality, too.
Your short temper, your crassness...
I'm obsessed with you.
If you're happy, you can show it, you know.
Shut up, jeez!
It's true, though.
You're so cute,
you make me want to bully you.
Then tell me you like me again.
You don't want me to tell you I love you?
Fine, tell me you love me.
"Tell me, please."
Tell me, please.
Call me Ma-kun.
Just hurry up and say it.
Ryoko, I love you.
Things got good with my boyfriend
the other day.
But we ended up not doing anything.
Even dramas get special effects these days.
Neither of us has been able
to make a move since then.
It's like we've been avoiding that kind of stuff.
I wonder why.
X-File
I wonder if he's embarrassed
that he got cockblocked.
It didn't bother me, though.
I wouldn't mind him
being a bit more aggressive.
Then again, I'd feel weird
about bringing it up.
So have you seen it, Kana?
Huh?
What were we talking about again?
The drama.
We said we'd get our comedy ideas from dramas
because "bang" was getting old, remember?
Oh... Yeah...
So let's try me as the detective
and you as the suspect.
Wait, I've never seen that show.
It's fine.
I'll just go with the flow.
Just follow my lead.
Honestly, I don't care about
comedy ideas right now.
FBI! Hands behind your head!
W-Wait.
Close your eyes.
Don't resist arrest.
Fool! You've let your guard down!
D-Despicable.
You too, mister.
Wait, we've broken character.
Oh, yeah.
Did he try to kiss me just now?
Glance.
Don't tell me he's gonna do it via skit.
No, no, no, you can't be serious.
All right, I'll be an alien next!
You can't be serious!
And you're the FBI agent this time.
U-Uh, all right, I'll try.
A-Assuming...
Assuming he was trying to kiss me,
this set up can only mean...
You can't be serious! Are you for real?!
Stay back!
Stay back, or I'll shoot!
Seriously?!
Something like that.
Er... I don't know.
This bit doesn't have a punch line.
We need to come up with something.
Hey...
Let's just go home.
Yeah.
The End
I heard you like movies,
so if you're up for it...
I-I don't mind, but...
Okay, see you tomorrow at the theater!
Yamane-dono!
How did the exam go?
We Don't Need Girls
Motoyama-kun!
What? Nothing.
Let me guess, you were
thinking about tomorrow.
Tomorrow?!
Dunno what you're talking about...
We have plans to see
a movie tomorrow, remember?
I've been so excited about it,
I couldn't focus on the test.
Was that tomorrow?
Don't tell me you've forgotten.
We're supposed to watch Magic Shin-chan.
I never miss a movie in that series.
C-Can we do that the day after tomorrow?
I actually have—
It better not be a jezebel.
Jezebel
No.
That was a joke.
You? With a woman?
O-Of course not.
Such vile pigs deserve not to bask
in the youth of we whom they deem gross!
I-I know, right?!
I hate girls, too.
I was invited by a guy friend, actually.
Oh, you have friends besides me?
M-My friend from middle school.
He texted that we should catch up—
Oh, is that the case?
Then I, Motoyama Tomomichi, shall yield
to your previous engagement.
We are nothing if not repulsive.
Thus, the bonds of our friendships
are our greatest treasure.
Do kindly introduce me
to your friend someday.
Motoyama-kun!
I shall watch the movie by myself.
You're such a good man, Motoyama-kun.
And yet, I...
And yet I lie just to spend time with a girl.
Okay, see you tomorrow at the theater!
I'm worthless. I don't need a woman!
Sorry, Motoyama-kun, I'm lying!
Wh-What?!
I don't have another friend.
My phonebook is only your number
and my parents', and in fact—
Yamane-dono!
Well done, confiding in me a shameful truth.
I have never had the pleasure
of having a soulmate.
Motoyama-kun!
Do what you must do tomorrow, Yamane-dono.
I shall not pry further,
if you are inclined to hide it so.
It's fine.
We're friends, I'll tell you.
Although, it's just that a girl I know
asked me to watch a movie with her.
We actually had lunch together before,
but we didn't really hit it off, so I don't
know why she's inviting me again.
You lied to keep a woman hidden from me?
S-Sorry, Motoyama-kun!
But I can't go with you tomorrow—
I implore you to choose her!
It warrants no mention
that I despise women.
I would like nothing more
than to render blind
those eyes with which they gaze upon me
as though I am foul.
Nevertheless!
Just how could I possibly find fault
in so pure a maiden
that she would call upon
as repugnant a man as Yamane-dono?
I... I...
I am overjoyed!
Motoyama-kun!
Have the two of you
entered into a relationship?
No way.
It's nothing like that!
We're really just friends.
I mean, even that's presumptuous of me.
I don't even know
what she's thinking, really.
I see, that is a platonic relationship.
Would you like to come with us?
I'm sure she's going to bring her friends.
If you don't mind hanging out with girls.
Any friend of yours
is perfectly acceptable to me.
The End
A lot of people come to me for dating advice.
But I've never been in a relationship.
Why do people ask me?
I wish I—
Oh, what?
Who are you?!
Sorry, but I don't care
to talk to girls from above.
What's with this guy?
Why was he in the tree?
Dating Master
Come out, little kitten.
Were you helping a kitten stuck in the tree?
Nah, I just felt like climbing the tree.
So, what's on your mind?
So you were listening?
Nah.
You just had the same troubled look
on your face as that kitty.
What's up with this guy,
calling me a cute little kitty?
You don't think I'm a dating master, do you?
What?
N-Not really.
Bingo.
Dating master?
Do you think you're cool or something?
Of course I don't.
There's nothing cool about a man
who's made more girls cry than smile.
Oh dear, I'd better stop
calling myself the dating master,
or the dating gods will smite me.
Oh dear.
He's so cool!
What is this feeling?
I'm falling...
You can tell me anything.
If I'm good enough for you.
Are you my prince?
Oui.
Then will you—
I can't do that, my kitten.
I'm everyone's prince.
Fall for me, and you'll get burnt.
I don't care!
That's just my afterimage.
Give it up, my kitten.
No one can hold me down.
Fine!
Come on, help me like you helped that kitty!
Meow!
Help me, meow!
Silly kitten.
Whoosh!
Y-You're bleeding!
I'm all right.
It's the spaghetti I had for lunch.
I'm sorry.
It's all because I was being stupid.
Being stupid?
What are you talking about?
It's a prince's job to save
a kitten in distress.
I love you!
Farewell, my kitten.
Don't put yourself in danger anymore.
Wait...
Wait, what's your name?
Katori Shin'ichi.
Toodles.
Katori-senpai!
Next time: It's All the Fever's Fault.
It's All the Fever's Fault