This is bad... Very bad...
Subaru? What's wrong?
Ah, I see. This is where they suck you in.
No... Run! Hurry!
Miso Natto
Nah, not natto.
Wait there...
That'll be 363 yen.
Oh, a grooved-edge ten.
I'm...
going to...
save you...
I guess anyone's eyes would be tired after
holing up in their room, gaming all day.
What's going on?
This stuff obviously isn't fake.
Which means...
So does this mean...
I've been summoned into a parallel world?!
I guess I can assume this is a fantasy world
with the typical medieval-style culture.
A realm where demihumans are commonplace,
and probably stuff like wars
and adventures, as well.
And here, I'm...
Hey!
Watch out!
This is it! It's my turn!
This must be the event where
I produce my first magic!
Look out!
Way to go!
Well done!
I guess I'm not quite ready to use magic...
I can't read this.
Hey, boy.
Those are some weird clothes.
Are you traveling?
What are these?
Those are appas.
They understand me, though.
The question is...
Huh? What kind of money is that?
You can't use that stuff in Lugunica.
That means you're flat broke, huh?
Get outta here!
Don't interfere with my business!
There's no other way...
I'll just have to go around
gathering information first.
This place is for demihumans only.
Ow! I can't... see...
Is this how it's supposed to be?
Wasn't I summoned into a parallel world?!
Where'd my protagonist status go?!
Damn it.
[Phone Menu]
(1)Contacts
(2)Group Search
(3)Abbreviations
(4)New Contacts
[Contacts]
City Hall
Dad
Mom
Pizza
My cell phone still works...
Out of Range
But what's the point in having it?!
And my starting gear is way too wimpy!
You need a more substantial welfare program
to satisfy pressure-free
generation kids like me!
I don't even have Excalibur or anything!
And besides, if I was summoned,
where's the cute girl who summoned me?
Did she summon me only
to leave me here alone?
Hey, is she finally here?!
The cute girl who summoned... me...
What are you babbling about?
If you don't wanna get hurt,
cough up whatever you've got!
Crap, it's a compulsory event...
Move it, move it!
You guys!
Out of my way!
Here we go!
Is that the cute girl who summoned me?!
Summoned? I dunno what you're
talkin' about, but I'm busy!
Sorry! Live strong!
Wait, what? What?!
Hey, that didn't make you decide to be less
hostile toward me, by any chance, did it?
Actually, it rained on our
parade and made things worse.
Yeah, of course...
Just calm down, Natsuki Subaru.
Since ancient times, it's the rule that anyone
summoned into a parallel world
will display supernatural powers!
I'll mow these guys down and make
them fuel for my shining future!
You lumps of EXP!
That's the first time I ever hit someone!
I didn't expect it to hurt me that much...
But this world is set up
so that I'll be strong!
My adrenaline is surging! I've got this!
I'm sorry! It was all my fault!
Forgive me! Spare me!
Play games with us, will you?! Die, scum!
And don't think it'll be painless!
That's enough.
Who the hell are you?!
Stop now, and I'll let this slide.
So just graciously return what you stole.
What we stole?
Now, please. It's important to me.
I'll give up on the other stuff,
but I can't let you have that.
Be good and hand it over, please.
You didn't come to save this kid?
What strange clothes he has...
If you asked me whether I had any
connection to him, I'd have to say no.
Then you've got no business with us!
If someone stole from you,
it was that brat who just ran by!
Yeah! That way! She ran that way!
Hmm... They don't seem to be lying...
I need to go after her!
But regardless of that...
I can't overlook what's going on here.
Magic?
Mess with us, will you?!
I don't care if you can
use magic! I'll kill you!
You think you can win when
it's two against one?! Huh?!
You're right. Two against one may be unfair.
Two against two should make it fair, then.
You're a user of the spiritual arts?
Correct. Back off now and
I won't come after you.
Decide quick. I'm in a hurry.
You bitch! Next time I see
you, I won't go easy on you!
Do anything to her, and I'll
haunt you and your kin forever.
Not that you'll have any kin if I do that.
You saved me. Thanks.
Don't move.
See? You averted your eyes because
you have a guilty conscience!
Looks like my judgment was spot-on.
Are you sure?
I think it was just an
instinctive male reaction.
I didn't sense any malice at all.
You be quiet, Puck.
You know who stole my insignia
from me, don't you?
Uh, sorry, but I don't
have the slightest idea.
Huh? Wait, it can't be!
Did I really just come around the long way?
You should probably hurry after her, miss.
I could... help...
Aww, you shouldn't have tried to get up.
What should we do?
It's none of our business.
He won't die. We'll just leave him.
Really?
Yes, really.
You say that, but I bet
you'll still help him.
I will not!
Yeah, right.
Absolutely not! I am not going to save him!
She's even super cute when she's mad.
That's a parallel world fantasy for you...
Is my head on someone's lap?
You're awake?
I didn't know cute girls were this hairy...
Wait, that can't be right!
It's just a thoughtful arrangement we made
so you could at least feel
happy until you woke up.
First of all, don't talk in that high voice!
No sane guy confuses a cat
for the main heroine!
Aww, making myself bigger was
worth it to see you so happy.
I'm not happy!
I'm sorry about this.
You stayed with me the whole
time I was unconscious...
Don't get the wrong idea.
I had to stay because there
are things I want to ask you.
Healing your wounds and making Puck
your pillow until you woke up
were for my own benefit.
So I need you to repay me in kind.
For such a normal favor, you're making
it sound like I really owe you big.
No such thing.
You have some idea who
stole my insignia, right?
Insignia?
You mean one of those badge things
that shows your affiliation?
It has a jewel in the center,
and it's about this big.
Sorry, but no matter how many
times you ask me, I have no idea.
I see. No helping that, then.
But you've given me the information
that you know nothing,
and you gave me my answer,
in return for healing you.
Huh?
Well, I'm in a hurry, so I'm going now.
Your wounds should be better now,
but next time, don't do dangerous things,
like wandering into deserted alleys alone.
I'm not concerned. I'm just warning you.
If that happens to you again,
saving you won't be of any benefit to me,
so don't expect me to help.
Sorry about her. She's so insincere.
Don't think badly of her.
Insincere?
I think this goes beyond that.
She was in such a hurry to find
what was stolen from her,
yet she stopped to help me.
And she even came up with that lame excuse
for a favor so I wouldn't feel like I owed her,
even though I'm a total stranger.
Anyone who lives like that...
is gonna end up wasting their whole life!
Hey! Wait up!
What? Just so you know, I can only spend
just a little more time with you.
I sense you're being a tiny bit lenient...
Forget that. You lost
something important, right?
Let me help you.
But you said you don't know anything...
But I remember her face, at least!
If I see her again, I'll know!
You're very strange...
Just so you know, I can't
do anything to thank you.
I don't need you to.
I want to thank you.
That's why I want to help.
I didn't do anything deserving of thanks.
I told you, I've already received
compensation for healing your wounds.
Then...
I'm going to help you for my own sake, too.
My objective is... Let's see...
Yeah! One good deed per day!
I don't sense any malice. I think
you can just accept his offer.
The more shields between yourself and
ruffians, the better, after all.
That's what you want me around for?!
I mean it, though.
I can't do anything to thank you.
No problem. Just leave it to me!
I talked big, but isn't this town too
huge to find one little thing in?
It's the capital of Lugunica.
You didn't even know that, um...
That's right. We haven't
asked your name yet.
Should we all introduce ourselves?
Oh, yeah, you're right.
I'll introduce myself first, then.
My name is Natsuki Subaru.
Not only am I clueless,
I'm also broke beyond compare!
Nice to meet ya!
When that's all you say,
you really do sound hopeless.
And I'm Puck! Nice to meet you!
It's very unusual to see someone who
can touch a spirit so casually.
Where are you from?
Well, following the usual pattern,
a small island nation to the east.
Lugunica is the easternmost
nation on our continental map.
There's no nation east of here.
No way, really?
There's nothing east of here?
You have no idea where you
are, you have no money,
you can't read, and you have
no one who can help you.
You might be in an even more
precarious position than me, um...
Subaru... was it?
Yes, that's my name.
But when I look at you this way,
you look pretty well-built.
I do work out every day.
For a shut-in who's gotta guard
his house, that much is a given.
I'm not sure I understand
what a "shut-in" is,
but that means you're from a
respectable family, right?
H-Hey—
Your fingers, too. They're very pretty.
They're evidence that you don't
live like a peasant at all.
And your muscles don't look like
the kind you gain by working.
Uh, anyway, I know your cat's name now,
but I haven't heard yours yet.
My name?
Yeah.
I'm...
Satella.
I have no family name.
You can just call me Satella.
I see... Satella...
That's a nice name.
You have terrible taste.
Okay, time to get back to asking around!
Hey, Subaru...
Do you get the feeling that child is lost?
Uh, but what about our questioning?
That's important too, but if she's
lost, we have to do something.
I'm in no place to talk after you saved me,
but do you understand the position we're in?
But...
She's crying! Is she not, Subaru?
If you can't do this with me, that's fine.
Thanks for all your help, Subaru.
I'll handle it on my own from here,
after I help that little girl.
I'm sorry I'm not who you were looking for.
So, what's the matter?
Aren't your mom and dad with you?
Um, uh... Don't cry...
I won't do anything to you, okay?
What I have here is one
grooved-edge ten-yen coin.
I will now clutch it tightly in my hand.
Tight, tight, tight... like that!
And now... Imagine that!
And this... is where the coin was hiding.
You can have this.
It's rare, so take good care of it.
Thank you!
I see. You got separated from your mom, huh?
Hey, it'll be fine.
Just leave it to me and
this young lady here.
We'll find them for you in no time.
When we do this,
people who don't know us probably think
we're a married couple and child, huh?
How embarrassing.
At best, I can't see you as anything
more than her older brother.
What makes you think I'm that
much younger than you?!
Oh! Mommy!
Mommy!
Looks like she found her.
Yeah. I'm glad.
So...
I think we took a pretty long way around,
but what benefit will you insist
that you got out of this?
That's easy. Now we can continue our
search with our minds at ease, right?
Anyway, why did you help me?
You were against the idea.
I could say I just wanted
to show off my magic trick,
but that would be a lie.
I told you, finding your insignia will
be my one good deed for the day!
Then, since you helped the little girl,
isn't your one good deed over?
That comeback was way too logical!
Come on, it doesn't hurt to do more
than one nice thing in a day, right?
I just got tomorrow's out of the way.
My plan is to get a week's worth
of good deeds taken care of early!
Subaru, you're the type that basically
wastes your whole life, aren't you?
You're the last one I
want saying that to me.
You're not a bad boy, though.
Why are you treating me like
I'm younger than you again?
I doubt there's that much
difference between us.
I don't think making guesses
on that will help you.
I'm a half-elf.
Now I get it.
No wonder I thought you were so cute!
Elves are always beautiful, right?
What?
"What"? Well, I mean... I'm a half-elf...
Yeah, I heard you.
What'd you do that for?
I just had to do something about
this unbearable tingle I feel!
I can't accept being hit
for a reason like that.
Though I'll forgive you
because it was squishy.
I didn't hit you out of anger or anything.
The opposite, in fact.
Subaru, you're such a dunderhead!
Dunderhead? Who says that
in this day and age?
And why are you insulting me?
Hmph! Whatever!
More importantly, we have
to get back to the search.
Hey, hang on!
Running around without
a plan never ends well.
There's a basic rule of searches.
A basic rule of searches?
Yep. You revisit the crime
scene a hundred times.
Where was your insignia stolen?
So you see, it seems the crime
happened right around here,
so I came back to this fruit stand after
valiantly telling her to leave it all to me.
What? I thought I had a customer,
but it's just the broke kid?
Do you really want to take that attitude?
Haven't you noticed I'm
not who I was before?
What?
Just look who I brought with me!
I brought someone who just
might become a regular!
Um, Subaru...
You seem to have some
weird expectations of me,
but I don't have any money, either.
Huh?! Seriously?
So what did you want to say to me now
that I've got two broke customers, boy?
We're actually looking for someone,
and we hoped we could ask
you some questions...
That was a sarcastic way of telling you I
don't have time for losers with no money!
Get outta here!
Mister!
Thanks for your help earlier.
What brings you back here?
It's my husband's shop,
so we were just stopping by.
Husband?
Hey, there's my girl.
Wait, you know these broke losers?
She got lost, and they found her.
Here, lady.
Please accept it.
She wants to thank you in her own way.
Thank you.
Sorry about that.
You helped my daughter,
and I want to thank you.
You can ask for anything.
There, you see?
That came back around
and worked in our favor!
The air, the atmosphere, and most likely,
the attitudes of the people
living here are awful.
Are you sure she's here?
It might be that Felt girl.
You said a nimble little blond girl, right?
She's well-known in the slums.
Dunno where she lives, though.
Maybe someone will tell us if we ask.
No one would sell out one of their own,
so I don't think that would work.
Maybe we should come back later.
Whether you stay or leave,
you should decide quickly.
I'm almost out of time.
You're what? Out of time?
I have a cute appearance, but I am a spirit.
It take a lot of mana just
to appear in physical form.
So at night, I return to
the crystal I was summoned from
and prepare for the
emergence of the sun.
On average, my ideal staying time
is from about nine to five.
Nine to five? You sound
like a civil servant.
Employment terms for spirits are
more severe than I thought...
We'll be fine without Puck.
We have to move forward.
Yeah. But, sorry... I'm at my limit...
It's almost like he's dying
when he disappears...
Sorry to work you so hard, Puck.
We'll handle things from
here, so get some rest.
Don't do anything reckless.
If it comes down to it,
use the odo to summon me again.
Okay, take care of the rest, Subaru.
Hey, I haven't been alone with a
girl since I was in grade school!
Don't get any weird ideas.
I can use magic.
I won't!
The bigger issue is how
we should find Felt now.
I'll ask the lesser spirits.
Lesser spirits?
Lesser spirits are beings that
haven't become spirits yet.
They grow over time, and when they
gain strength and self-awareness,
they become full spirits, like Puck.