Tsuritama Episode 3
I don't regret my decision to fish,
but I don't get this at all.
Lonely Casting
You're doing it wrong.
I knew you guys weren't
ready for the ocean yet.
Listen, you can't just throw your lure
out randomly when you cast.
You have to aim precisely for the fish.
I'm not letting you fish in the ocean
until you can cast into this bucket.
Seriously?
Yuki, you can do it!
Fine. Just watch.
I'll get it in.
Use this practice lure.
I like this one.
Don't be ridiculous!
Okay.
Listen, I'm only going to say this once.
First, place the line
on your index finger
and lift the bail.
The line's the string?
Is this the bail?
Put your other hand on
the end of the grip.
Swing the rod straight back...
and let go of the line
when you swing forward.
When you're starting out,
count to three as you do it.
One, two, three.
Seriously?
You're amazing, Prince!
Count out loud when you do it.
Think of something to say for
each of the three beats when you cast.
What? I have to talk out here?
I can't do that.
Yuki! Haru! Prince!
Doesn't this guy have any shame?
Fishing! Fishing! Fishing!
Eno-shima bowl.
Enoshima bowl?
Here you are.
No way.
Eno-shima bowl.
There's no way!
You guys go with that.
No!
Do it! Shout it!
Eno-shima bowl!
Huh? It's not even close.
You're letting go too early.
That's why it's going up so high.
Enoshima bowl!
That's too late.
What? Around here, then?
I told you, that's too early.
I don't get this!
Why? Why?
Why is Haru scared of him?
Excuse me.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'll leave.
What's your name?
I am Akira.
That is Tapioca.
Tapioca? You're so cute.
Here's your whitebait
bowl and Enoshima bowl.
Thank you for the food.
Exquisite!
Eno-shima bowl!
Good, just like that.
But I'm still so far from the bucket.
Now you just have to learn feathering.
Feathering?
Use your finger as a break,
so you don't let out too much line.
After you cast, put your
finger on the spool
of the reel while the lure is in the air.
Watch.
If you press down too hard,
the line will stop
and the lure will fall, so be careful.
Casting is hard.
It's not supposed to be easy.
I thought I'd at least get it in once.
Cast until you can't cast any more.
Look at the time.
See you guys tomorrow.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Onii-chan, is it ready yet?
Sorry, I know it's late.
I'm starving.
Hey, Sakura, your brother's a busy guy.
Come here. I'll give you a
special toss in the air.
I'm not a baby. I'll help.
Get some plates.
Okay.
Natsuki, I heard you've been
fishing around here lately.
Here, Onii-chan.
Onii-chan's teaching
his friends to fish.
Really?
Take me with you the next time you go.
We'll catch a big one together!
I want to fish, too.
We used to go together all the
time, saying "Enoshima bowl!"
Yuki, you can get the Enoshima bowl in.
Thank you, Haru.
You're welcome.
Oh, Yuki.
Haru, listen.
What is it?
Starting tomorrow, I won't be here.
I'm going to the hospital
for a little while.
Again?
The hospital?
When I told them I wasn't
feeling well yesterday,
they decided to give me a check up.
The hospital makes such
a big deal of things.
Haru, I'll be fine.
I'm just going to get fixed,
and then I'll come back.
Okay, got it.
You should've told me!
You always wait until the last minute!
I'm sorry. I didn't want you to worry.
It's fine. I'm used to it.
This time you'll have Haru,
so you won't be lonely.
Yuki?
He'll be fine.
Sorry, we're done for the day.
What? Again?
That sucks.
I have successfully infiltrated
target JF1's school.
I believe he and his
alleged younger sister,
JF2, are impersonating humans.
What is JF1 doing in Enoshima?
He fishes every day.
He fishes? Is he just a tourist alien?
Last month one of them came
to Nagoya to play pachinko.
They possess a dangerous power.
They can control humans using water.
Control? What does that mean, exactly?
He made his classmate perform
the Enoshima dance.
Fine. Take care of the rest.
we've got our hands full with the
Bermuda syndrome investigation.
Yamada, enjoy your high school
life a little longer.
Farewell.
Duck.
How dare they treat me like a fool?
I don't have time to sit around here.
Water feels great.
Koko, the Indian guy is scary.
His eyes are scary.
And that white bird...
That's called a duck.
It must be some kind of weapon.
If we lock eyes with it, it'll kill us.
What? I think I already did.
Nii-chan, you should
get out of that house.
Why?
You'll be in trouble if they find you.
Besides, Yuki still hasn't
caught a single fish.
We should pick someone else.
Nii-chan? Do you understand?
Are you taking care
of the flowers again?
I won't be seeing them for a while,
so I wanted to see their faces.
Keito, can I ask you something?
What?
All these flowers will die, won't they?
Yes.
Then why do you take
such good care of them?
Because they'll die.
I don't understand.
They'll all die eventually,
so I want them to bloom beautifully
and healthily while they're alive.
I see. They're beautiful.
Haru, look after Yuki.
Okay, I'll do it.
Thank you, Haru.
That's wrong.
I haven't done anything for you.
You don't just thank people
when they've done something for you.
Really?
You thank someone because you're happy.
Haru, you became Yuki's friend.
You eat together, go to school together,
and fish together.
Yuki didn't have anyone like
that before, so I am happy.
That's why I'm thanking you.
You thank someone because you're happy?
That's right. I know Yuki is happy, too.
He just doesn't know how to express it.
But he'll be fine as
long as he's with you.
I'm sure he'll show you
his happiness some day.
Think of these as me and
keep them with you.
Those are Keito?
Yes. If something happens,
look at these flowers.
If something happens?
When you think you're bothering Yuki,
when you think you'll
have a fight with Yuki,
when you're not happy,
when you want to wish for something...
That's a lot of things.
What will happen if I look at them?
They will make you happy.
Water them every day.
That way, they'll live for a while.
Will they die without water?
Yes.
Just like me.
I should get going.
Okay!
Enoshima bowl!
Don't give up.
It's okay. Yuki won't give up.
You're right. If he gives up,
his friends will be sad.
Yuki, it's okay.
Everyone dies someday.
So...
What's wrong with him?
Grandma's in the hospital.
I see.
Get up, Yuki!
We'll be late!
Come on.
Hey, Haru, where's your place?
Huh?
Where do you guys live?
Did you get it in the bucket?
You're pathetic.
I can't let you fish if you can't do it.
There's still a lot to
learn after casting.
Sorry, but I don't have
time for that right now.
This is the perfect time to cast.
Yuki, let's do some Enoshima bowl.
If you get the Enoshima bowl in,
Keito will be happy.
You're an alien, aren't you?
Yep, I'm an alien.
Then you wouldn't know how I feel.
There's no way you could know!
May Yuki smile.
May Yuki be happy.
May Yuki get the Enoshima bowl in.
May Keito get better.
This is Keito.
They'll all die eventually,
so I want them to bloom
beautifully and healthily
while they're alive.
That's what Keito said.
Nii-chan, you're going to break
it off with Yuki, right?
I don't want to leave him.
Yuki don't feel the same way.
You shouldn't bother your friends.
You should give up on Yuki.
I want them to bloom beautifully
and healthily while they're alive.
Don't give up on Enoshima bowl.
This is the perfect time to cast.
Give up.
Enoshima bowl!
Why don't you give up already?
There's no point in casting into that.
Nii-chan, let's go.
No, Yuki's thinking!
Leave him. You don't
know how Yuki feels.
I do know.
Yuki thinks about important
things when he's by himself.
That's what Keito said.
Enoshima bowl!
Yuki.
Nii-chan!
Yuki... Yuki...
Enoshima bowl!
Enoshima bowl.
It's because my finger slipped just now.
Enoshima bowl!
All right.
I did it.
You did it! You did it, Yuki!
Natsuki.
Thanks.
I did it. Thanks.
I didn't do anything.
Natsuki, you're wrong.
You taught Yuki the Enoshima bowl.
That's why Yuki's happy.
You became Yuki's friend.
You thank someone because you're happy.
Yuki.
You haven't seen anything yet.
Enoshima bowl!
We casted over and over that day.
Enoshima bowl! Enoshima bowl!
Tapioca, I don't like...
such stifling relationships.
From this world where
nothing goes as planned...
to a distant and dark future
where I can't see anything.
The ocean was still far away.
He was still sleeping in the depths.
Continued in #4