Episode 8   Umaru and Christmas and New Year's
Onii-chan! It's snowing!
I thought it seemed cold. It's snowing, huh?
It's all white outside!
Do you think it'll stick?
I was going to go to the supermarket today,
but I probably shouldn't go out in that.
All right! Then since I'm the
expert on being a shut-in,
I'll plan the ideal day off for you!
Now, sit.
You're just going to play games, right?
There's something I was
planning to bring out today.
Bring out? What?
The kotatsu.
Umaruun
Now, then.
What do we need to do first, Onii-chan?
She only gets motivated at times like this.
First...
Clean up the mess you've made.
What?
One, two. One, two.
Don't just move it all to one corner!
Jeez... What would happen
to her if I weren't here?
I'll get serious next year.
Disembodied Head
Mogu Mogu
Hey!
It's done!
Yep, it's done.
Don't dive in!
It's such a confined space,
yet why does it feel like heaven?
Now that we've got the kotatsu out,
I've gotta bring over some stuff!
You sure are busy...
This is my paradise!
I should have bought some mandarins.
Let's go get some tomorrow.
Okay, Umaru?
She already fell asleep?
They say it's easy to catch a cold if
you let your upper body get cold...
Hey, Umaru, wake up. You'll catch a cold.
I guess I'll wake her up in an hour.
Clementines
Wake up! Wake up!
You're in the way! Go sleep in your own room!
Just one more hour...
Zuzashaan
December 24th
Merry Christmas!
Christmas... It is the celebration of winter!
I'm sure people will go out
at night to see the the lights.
However, I will not be
leaving the house at all!
Today, we will have a lazy little
party, while eating cake.
Now, then...
I wonder when Onii-chan will be home.
Overtime on Christmas...
You can't be serious!
What the hell is wrong with this company?!
I know how you feel,
but don't say it out loud.
Hey, Taihei. Let's quit this stupid company!
It's not that much, so just tough it out.
How is this "not that much"?! How?!
This sucks. I want to go back
to how things used to be.
When we were young and free...
Hey, don't just run away from reality.
More importantly, what are
you looking at during work?
Oh, that...
It's a Santa outfit.
Wanna wear one with me, Taihei?
It's not going to come the same
day you order it, you idiot.
True...
Have you finished your checks?
Ch-Chief Kanau...
I-I was just taking a little break...
You can quit at any time, A-f-ro.
I'm sorry about this, Taihei.
I know it's Christmas and all...
N-No, it's fine...
Your proposal the other day was spectacular.
The higher-ups that didn't pass it are shit.
Thank you very much...
Say, do you have any plans today?
Um... I can't see the screen.
Kirie-chan hasn't tweeted anything today...
And Ebina-chan went to visit her parents.
I wonder if she's out with her family.
I-I wonder who that is.
Onii-chan would have a key.
Onii-chan! And Kirie-chan!
What's going on?
I just ran into Kirie-chan over there.
You guys didn't have plans together?
Huh?
I-I bought a present for you, Master.
Octopus
Santa
Wh-Why are you dressed as Santa, Onii-san?
Well, I went and bought
one with my coworker,
and he said I might as well just wear it home.
Merry Christmas, Umaru-chan!
Akita is covered in snow!
Oh, Master! You're a reindeer today!
Oh, you're right.
Yep!
Honba
Heya, Kirie! Santa's home!
Huh?
New Year's Eve Across the Country
The year is coming to an end.
What was the most memorable
part of the year for you?
What about you, Taihei?
Well, a lot happened...
For me, it was...
Dressing up as Santa and waiting
for my sister to come home.
Isn't that really recent?
Oh, yeah. And...
She beat the crap out
of me when she got home.
For me, that steak was really yummy.
I wanna eat it again!
Sure, sometime soon.
I wanna eat ramen, too.
When Ebina-chan comes home, let's go again.
Who's Ebina-chan?
She's my friend.
She's back in Akita right now.
I see... Akita, huh?
Ayup.
Come to think of it, the first time
Ebina-chan came over was this year, too.
A lot happened this year, huh?
Master!
Oh, yeah. I became friends with
Kirie-chan this year, too.
Maybe I should have invited her over today.
My little sister's so violent.
Though, I'm sure she's
just being shy around me.
Huh...
It's not yet time to ring the
New Year's bell, but take a look.
There are already this many people in line.
Shuba
Shubaan
I got to ring it first!
Hey, give me back my mic!
I-I hung out with Sylphyn-san a lot, too...
First Shrine Visits
Around the Country
This is live footage from around the country.
Everyone's lining up,
even though it's so cold.
Man, that's way too many people for
the first shrine visit of the year.
Should we all go later?
What are you talking about, Onii-chan?
We have to count down in the kotatsu.
Gaki no Chikai is okay, right?
Umaru, are you going to stay
up until the countdown?
Of course! I'm so pumped,
like I was going to see the first sunrise!
Well, then. I guess it's time to get started.
Are we going to do something, Onii-chan?
Could it be... the samba?
What kind of way is that
to start a new year?
Yakitori
Yakitori!
Edamame
Edamame!
Kakinotane
Kakinotane!
Nothing says ringing in
the New Year like drinking!
Bomber, I appreciate you
preparing all of this,
but I wasn't going to drink
this year, since Umaru is here.
Bringles
Bringles!
Sweet
Breads
Fluffy Steamed Egg Bun
Soft Melon Bun
Coarse Anko Bun
Sweet breads!
Lacto Ice
Hyper Cup
Chocolate
Ice Cream
Ice cream!
And...
Nothing says ringing in
the New Year like cola!
Those are all colas?!
Hey, this cola's all red.
And there's a clear one, too?!
I picked them out specifically
for New Year's.
Umaru Ranking
1:               Cola
2:   Melon Soda
3:  Lemon Soda
4:     Plain Soda
5:     Ginger Ale
The best pairing with snacks is, of course, cola.
Points
Though, the sweetness of melon soda
brings out the saltiness in the
snacks, making it the runner-up.
She started explaining!
Onii-chan has given his blessing!
Let's party!
Yay! Party time!
Wait, I didn't say anything yet!
Your beer snacks are like actual food, Bomber.
Beer snacks aren't just snack foods, you know.
Yum! I've never had yakitori and
potato chips together before!
The meat and potato chips
are melting in my mouth...
Eat the green onions, too.
Eating ice cream after kakinotane is delicious!
Not to mention, it's chocolate flavor.
And the textures are different, so it's great!
So good!
Come on, eat up! Eat up! Wow, this is good.
This is great! Let's have another!
And then I told the section chief...
Is she asleep?
Yep, she's asleep.
You sure we shouldn't wake
her up for the countdown?
Let's let her sleep.
Happy New Year
The best thing about New Year's
is that I can openly laze around.
I want to go to a world
where New Year's just loops.
Oh, Onii-chan.
Umaru.
Yes, sir?
Happy New Year
Do you remember what you promised me?
Promised?
It was in the latter half of November.
That's a long time ago.
Latter Half of
November
Umaru! The room's a mess!
There's not much time left in this year,
so I'll do it all at once next year.
Don't do it all at once! Do it now!
Don't worry, Onii-chan! I'll
get serious starting next year!
You remember that, right?
Yeah, I did say that, but...
New Year January
New Year February
New Year March
The "next year" when I was gonna
get serious has actually come!
I remember it as clear as day.
You wouldn't lie to me, would you?
I-I did indeed say that...
Psst Psst
However, I would like you to
recall that I never specified
an actual date or place, Onii-chan.
That's enough!
I guess I don't have a choice...
Okay, I'll clean up.
Oh, you can clean when we get back.
Huh? Are we going somewhere?
Let's go for the year's first shrine visit.
Tago Shrine
Piping Hot
Buttered Potatoes
There're so many people.
Yeah.
Yay!
Really? A peace sign?
Umaru, did you want to
come in a kimono, too?
No. Not at all.
I see...
Oh! Fortune slips!
Let's see who has better luck!
Of course you take interest when
there's a gambling aspect...
Luck: Good Luck to Come
What'd you get, Onii-chan?
Slightly good luck.
Is that better than "good luck to come"?
I have no idea.
Here. For an offering.
Hey!
What did you wish for, Onii-chan?
It's more likely to come
true if you don't say it.
Really?
Apparently.
Then I won't tell you, either.
Okay.
New
Year's
The new year lazily begins.
I wonder what this year will be like.
Oh, Onii-chan.
I'm counting on you again this year!
Yeah, same.
Wait, what are you counting on me for?
Oh, you know. Like cleaning.
Oh, and dinner tonight! I want meat!
You're not going to get any more
serious this year, are you?
I did indeed say I was going to get serious.
Pssst Pssst
However, I never specified a date or...
That's enough of that!
December 24th
Good evening, Chief.
Good evening.
Oh, good evening.
She's as hot as ever.
Kanau-san's still here, even
though it's Christmas Eve?
I'd say she cares more about
work than Christmas.
System Support Section
This sucks. I want to go back
to how things used to be.
When we were young and free...
Hey, don't just run away from reality.
More importantly, what are
you looking at during work?
Oh, that...
It's a Santa suit.
Wanna wear one with me, Taihei?
It's not going to come the same
day you order it, you idiot.
True...
Have you finished your checks?
Ch-Chief Kanau...
I-I was just taking a little break...
You can quit at any time, A-f-ro.
Say, do you have any plans today?
Um... I can't see the screen.
W-Well, you know...
It seems like it's Christmas
today for the rest of the world.
I'd feel bad making you work overtime
if you actually have plans.
O-Oh. No, I don't really have plans.
What? Really?!
Yes. I just plan on going home, as usual.
I-I see...
Then... Um... So you're free,
even though it's Christmas Eve.
And you're also here because
you have nothing else to do, right?
Hey, Bomber!
Well, think about it. We're the
only ones here, so who cares?
No one cares, but you piss me off.
What was that for, Kanau?!
Oh, I'm terribly sorry. My hand slipped.
Th-Then, Kanau...
Why don't the three of
us go out like old times?
Huh?
No, I'll pass.
I'm going to have dinner
with my family tonight.
You two should also go home and
spend tonight with your families.
Lucky break! She said we could go home!
It's pretty rare for Kanau
to stop by our section.
Is it? I don't think so.
Anyway, are you renting anything?
I'm thinking about renting
something for my sister.
I'm sure she's home by herself.
What?
U-Uh, well...
What? Is it so rare for a lone woman
to rent a DVD on Christmas Eve?
No... Your card...
Hey, I know.
They might have Santa outfits
at Village Ganvuard.
Th-Thank you very much...
Just how much do you want
to wear a Santa outfit?
So cold!
FROM: Doma Taihei
Attachment
Merry Christmas.
Touch-up                                                 Resize
Rotate                                                      Trimming
Next Time
Episode 9              Umaru and Valentine's
Why do you have an afro, Bomber?
What? My philosophy?
Yes! Let us say my afro reflects my burning soul.
So what if some hot lady said she hated afros?
Farewell, my afro!
Talk about a lukewarm soul...