There are people among
the Shirakiin family
who aren't fully human.
They inherited blood mixed with
that of supernatural creatures.
But our family isn't the
only one like this.
And for some reason,
each of these families is rich.
As this blood ran thickest
in me, the throwback,
it's no surprise that
the family raised me as their lucky charm.
I've never even had the chance
to just be my parents' daughter.
However,
only once, they hit me.
When I said that I was
jealous of my sister
because she was not a throwback,
my father asked me,
"Do you not understand?
Can you even imagine the
degree to which
she is constantly compared to you?
Can you not see how
sad her position is?"
It was crystal clear that the emotion
flowing from my father's eyes was
for my sister alone.
The Real Contract
Miss Ririchiyo in a schoolgirl uniform...
It's out of this world!
School starts again today.
Good morning.
That's right. You'll be a freshman
in high school now, won't you?
I hope you make lots of friends.
May I slip one finger into your
knee sock and feel your thigh?
No.
Miss Ririchiyo.
So this is where you were.
Good morning.
G-Good morning...
I thank you for your courteous
message last night.
It deeply touched me.
Sending
I certainly have
my flaws, but I
look forward to
working together.
I was just practicing sending
messages from my phone.
I shall read it every night
before I go to sleep.
Give me that!
I'll erase it!
Impossible.
What do you mean, impossible?
I have already backed it up to
my computer and SD card,
as well as via external
message recovery service.
And I have printed and laminated
the note, and placed it in a safe.
Who does that?
Forget about it.
Did you buy a dress?
A dress?
For tomorrow's social get-together.
Yes.
It's taken care of.
I brought one from home.
My school caters to the upper echelon.
Not only do we hold a welcoming ceremony,
but we also have a social get-together.
You're enrolled as the top student,
and will be giving a speech as
the new student representative.
I'm so proud of you.
I need a picture of you in that dress!
You two sound like parents!
Social get-together, huh?
Yeah, I remember that...
So, you're in high school, young master?
You wouldn't think that at all
from his appearance, right?
He looks like he's either a
construction worker...
Yo!
...or some kind of debt collector.
Lady, I know you're in there.
It's because you look
so mature, young master.
Thanks for sticking up for me.
I wonder who we'll get for homeroom.
It'd be nice to be in the same class again.
I'll need to take care not to be
unpleasant toward my classmates.
That's Ririchiyo Shirakiin, huh?
I can't believe someone like her enrolled
at the head of the class.
Well, her family's loaded.
They probably used their
influence to pull some strings.
So, you're jealous.
I'm used to this, so please continue.
If this is what will soothe your injured pride.
However, I am quite busy, so you'll
have to carry on without me.
Bye.
I already told someone off...
You're going to school here, too?
We're in the same class...
Oh, I see.
Anyway, we merely live
in the same building.
Don't act like we're friends...
Let's go.
Wait...
It ended earlier than I expected.
He said he'd come and pick me up,
but I suppose there's still a lot of time.
I don't want to be a nuisance.
Hello?
Huh? Yeah.
Who is it?
Yeah.
Really?
And then?
Oh, yeah...
I guess this is when one
uses a cell phone.
I thank you for your courteous
message last night.
It deeply touched me.
Huh?
Hmm.
What are you doing?
Oh, Ririchiyo.
Ririchiyo!
It could prove a bit difficult
to get in at the moment.
Difficult to get in?
The current mood over there
seems quite serious.
And isn't she pretty?
And aren't her boobs big?
Miss Ririchiyo...
You're saying she isn't your girlfriend?
Correct.
Some time ago, she confessed her
feelings for me, and I rejected her.
She said she'd give up on me if I kissed her.
You ladies' man!
But is it normal to kiss someone
for a reason like that?
Of course!
It comes with no responsibility or burden.
Your idea of "normal" is disgusting.
I'm not saying I do that.
I'm saying it's how normal,
healthy boys act.
After all, they are male.
Miss Ririchiyo...
I'm going to my room.
Ririchiyo?
Miss Ririchiyo?
You can be nice to someone,
with no real feeling behind it?
It's completely empty.
You really don't think you
treated her dishonestly?
I truly am sorry...
Then you agree?
I am sorry.
Are you?
Miss Ririchiyo!
If you tell me not to,
then I'll never do that again.
That's what I mean by being dishonest!
I had no idea you were so filthy!
You are absolutely right.
I am not someone who should
be in a position to serve you.
It appears that, since I met you,
I've been so happy, I forgot that fact.
Perhaps I cannot live up
to your expectations.
Then this means our contract is void.
If that is what you wish.
Very well.
Then thank you for all your help.
Why did I say those things?
I had no idea you were so filthy!
Why did I, when it's none of my business?
Perhaps it was...
because I saw myself in her place.
The me that everyone always
gave fake smiles to,
with no real emotion.
He sees the true me, and is kind to me,
from the bottom of his heart...
And yet,
he could do something like that,
without any emotion.
And that scared me.
All I could do was hit him
with my distrust for others.
Good morning, Ririchiyo.
Today's the party!
What do you want?
Good morning.
Ririchiyo, what happened?
You look more pale and sickly than usual!
How I love those fragile-looking girls!
Okay, let's get you ready!
Why don't I do your hair?
What are you talking about?
I can do it myself.
Then put on a bra!
Huh?
You think a bra is just something
to wear over your breasts?
Depending on its use,
it can adjust your cup size!
Can a girl incapable of correctly utilizing
a bra possibly wear a dress?
That's a massive stretch...
I was so looking forward to helping you...
Always eager to help, aren't you?
Fine, if that's what you want...
I would love to!
That was fast.
This is the first time
she and I have been alone together.
I hope I don't say anything rude to her.
It would be a shame, after she was
nice enough to come here for me.
You don't need to be so nervous.
I just want to be friends with you.
She's a nice person.
Ah!
Your ears are so small... I love that...
And she's a pervert.
Are those bags under your eyes
because of Miketsukami?
What are you talking about?
It's not like he means anything to me.
Then, would you like to contract with me?
I just can't get motivated about
protecting such a big, black, dirty boy.
Shredder
Don't you kind of want to shred him?
Sorinozuka, run!
Thanks for the offer,
but I never intended to
hire an agent anyway.
Still, you did enter into a
contract with Miketsukami.
I hope you two can make up soon.
Ta-dah!
Karuta!
She's so full of life...
Miss Yukinokouji.
Oh, I wasn't expecting you.
I thought I would look
after Miss Ririchiyo
until her next agent arrives.
Where is she?
She seems restless.
She keeps wandering around.
Ah, there she is.
Miss Shirakiin!
I trust you've thought about
your speech as a representative?
Of course I have.
I wrote it on the day you mentioned it.
Anything else?
I-I see... Well...
Good luck, then.
It's true.
I just can't be around people.
How could I hurt someone
I appreciate so much...
...when I never even thanked him properly?
Hey, look at that.
Think she's nervous?
Merely being good at tests isn't enough.
She just isn't cut out for this.
You can see this is her real nature.
It's the truth.
Her big mouth is all an act.
Yes.
How sad...
She's at this glamorous party,
but she's all alone.
Yes.
Naturally. She's a total bitch...
The only people hanging around her are
after her family's fame and money.
Wh-What was that for?
Pardon me.
It's just that
you've angered me.
What the hell are you talking about?
You think you can do something
like that and get away with it?!
I'll kneel down and beg for
your forgiveness if you like.
But I request that you
take back what you said.
Miss Ririchiyo may not always be
the most socially adept of people.
But she is honest, conscientious, and loyal.
She is also very, very delicate.
What do you even know about her?
Fine, I take it back!
But I want you on your knees!
Right now! On your knees—
That won't be necessary.
He is my Secret Service agent,
so I take full responsibility.
Miss Ririchiyo...
I hope we're even now.
We will now have a speech from the
representative of our first-year students.
If she would kindly make her way
to the stage at this time.
Miss Ririchiyo!
I wanted emotion.
I have grown up in exclusive surroundings.
I know that what I ask for is a luxury.
But still...
Please wait!
Miss Ririchiyo!
Do you not understand?
Still, Father,
there has never been anyone who'd
say something like that for me.
I am the blood throwback
of the Shirakiin House,
and that is all I have ever been
to those around me.
I expected to live my life
not understood by anyone,
not noticed by anyone,
all alone.
Please wait!
Do you really intend to go
on stage like that?
I do.
I have no time to change and
nothing to change into.
This is all my fault...
How can I make it up to you?
I understand.
You are someone who does not,
by nature, put on appearances.
Miketsukami,
thank you.
There is someone, even for me.
Someone who wants to understand me.
There is someone...
They're going to find something
for you to change into.
Sorry about that.
About that...
And about yesterday.
I-I'm sorry...
Wh-What are you doing?
What will that accomplish?
True, it accomplishes nothing.
However,
I simply had to do it.
You really are
a total idiot.
This time, I am going to ask you.
Would you be my Secret Service agent?
Are you certain I am worthy?
Yeah.
This time, you really won't be
able to break your word.
Yeah.
This time, we really won't be separated...
Cross your heart, and hope to die?
Stick a needle in my eye.
I'll take the needle.
Huh?
So please don't kill me.
Then take care.
Was that a message from Karuta?
What did she say?
She said her school has started.
What are you doing anyway?
Whatever. I know I'm no good, but—
There it is!
Don't interrupt me!
What else did she say?
She told me there's someone
new living at the house.
Really?
Hope it's someone fun...
Who gives a crap?
Arrhythmia...
Arrhythmia is an irregularity of the pulse.
Ririchiyo, are you reading?
With your glasses, you're just
about the cutest thing!
You're reading, too.
What are you...
Wh-Why is there so little
cloth covering up...
Why are you striking that
kind of pose there?
The area around the tummy
just drives me crazy.
Next time, on Inu X Boku Secret Service:
Ayakashi Kan Walk Rally.
Ririchiyo, I'll make your heart
pound even more!
Ayakashi Kan
Walk Rally
Please permit me to accompany you again next time.