Our Tackle
Yesterday, on Enoshima, an island shaken by panic
caused by extraterrestrials,
a boy claiming to be
an alien wildly fired a
water gun at island residents.
I'm an alien!
This island is mine!
Residents of Enoshima have been
instructed to evacuate...
Haru...
What were you thinking then?
Alien investigation organization
Duck is pursuing the boy.
Dry!
Hot! Hot!
Dry! Dry! Dry!
Haino, haino, haino...
Rescue!
Hot! Hot!
While gradually gathering force,
Enoshima
Island
Emergency
Shelter
a typhoon is approaching
the Japanese islands.
We fear the storm may
reach in several hours.
Whoa, that storm is really coming?
My boat's exposed to the elements.
I didn't close the shop's shutters.
Have some safe water.
Here you are.
Dad, when can we go home?
Just wait a little longer.
WANTED
Contact DUCK
if you see this face!!
A message to all Duck units.
This afternoon, all of Shonan will
be in the area of the storm.
We will find JFX before this happens
and conduct a direct missile assault.
Should the typhoon reach land,
the influence of JFX,
who controls humans
using water, will increase dramatically.
Keep your waterproof
suits well maintained!
Duck!
This isn't good.
If the naval crew fall under his
control, we'll be in serious trouble.
And that's not all.
If nuclear and scientific plant
operators fall under his control...
The world will end.
You still haven't found JF1?
We are searching the island,
but we have received
no word of his capture.
Yamada may be with him.
He may have been
brainwashed, so be careful.
I can't take it any more!
I'm going fishing!
This isn't the time?
No! I have to catch JFX myself!
I know it's dangerous
to do it without Haru,
but I don't have time for that.
Get everyone to help me?
No, I cannot involve civilians.
They're my friends? They'll help me?
Friends, huh?
Where to?
Um, Enoshima.
Kid, haven't you seen the news?
We can't go to Enoshima.
Excuse me, I need to go to Enoshima.
I can't go to Enoshima...
Please. I have to go!
Give me a break!
Please, please!
Hey, careful!
We have just confirmed all
water lines have been stopped.
Good work.
Yamada!
Yoga.
I don't want any.
I took out the whitebait.
Akira!
So, you're a member of Duck.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
Natsuki, would you like to go fishing?
Huh? What are you going on about?
An alien organism who controls
humans using water is in Enoshima.
Haru came here to catch him.
What are you talking about?
You lost me.
We have to fish him out of the water!
What are you saying?
Have you gone crazy?
You have to fish out the dragon!
You must not anger him any more!
If you don't do something,
it will be too late.
Yes, yes, I know, old man.
There are some sweets over there,
so why don't you have some?
Let go! Don't treat me like a fool!
Let go of me! Geez.
Excuse me, but it's me. Namaste.
You're that guy from before!
That's the Enoshima dance.
That's right.
It started when the
dragon made them do it.
The same thing happened hundreds
of years ago on Enoshima.
How did they calm the dragon's rage?
By fishing.
Look at this.
Hey, listen.
You must have a reason for going
to Enoshima at a time like this.
It's my friend.
I see. Your friend, huh?
You'd better go see him, then.
Don't die, everyone.
You have to bloom
beautifully and healthily.
I'll protect you.
Stop the car!
Huh?
Sir, we're still in Totsuka.
I'm sorry. This is all I have.
I'll go as far as I can take you.
You can't buy friends with money,
and they'll last you your whole life.
I see.
You're saying we have to
fish this unknown whatever
out of the sea?
That is correct.
Huh.
That's ridiculous!
Indian, is he big?
Most likely.
I'm excited!
But we're dealing with an alien.
Huh?
That's right, and he can control
people with water, right?
Who's gonna dry us if we
start dancing on the boat?
Haru can probably protect us.
Let's find him and go fishing.
Okay. You can use my boat.
Wait!
But, Natsuki, if something
happened to you, I...
Dad.
Dad?
I haven't heard that in a while.
Dad, it's okay.
I'm the fishing prince.
That's great.
We're the only ones who
can protect Enoshima.
Yeah.
Sakura,
I'm going out for a bit.
Where are you going?
Don't worry. I'll be back soon.
Mariko-san, please look after Sakura.
Don't do anything reckless.
Onii-chan.
Here.
Mom will protect you.
Thanks.
So, Akira, how are we
going to get out of here?
Leave that to me.
Everyone, how is your acting experience?
What?
Owww!
Is something wrong?
Can't you see? She's
about to give birth!
But they told us not to use the trains.
We received permission.
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
I think it's coming!
I hope she has a healthy baby.
Yeah.
Sorry. I guess this is
the end of the line.
Don't worry about it.
I'll figure something out.
Thank you very much!
Run, kid!
I guess the legend was true after all.
This thing's a lure.
You have to use that lure.
Could this be...
That's at our shrine.
I wanted to bring it,
but the dragon had a firm grip on it.
I will get it later.
Thanks, now we just need a rod.
Leave that to me.
I'll bring the best one
we have at the store.
The rod's an Ocean Bluefin Tuna.
The reel's a Stella SW 20000PG.
I'll go. It's near the
sea, so it's dangerous.
It's fine. I have to close
the shutters, anyway.
I'll take care of it
when I prepare my boat.
Misaki-san and Erika, go with
Dad to the shopping district
and collect food supplies.
Okay.
Sure, leave it to us.
So, who's gonna fish the guy?
We've got plenty of fishermen here.
It can't be just anyone.
The goddess fished up the
dragon with her companion.
Her companion?
He won't answer his phone.
Damn it, what is he doing?
Yuki will come. He's a man of the sea.
I'll go set up the boat.
Take care, everyone.
I'll wait for Yuki here.
So, how are we getting into Enoshima?
Duck's bound to be guarding the area.
We will have to force our way in.
Stop!
A car carrying Yamada
just entered Enoshima.
We did it, Tapioca.
This is gonna be a big storm.
Yuki...
I'm drying out.
I don't think I can last any longer.
This is how everything should be.
I'm almost there.
Wait for me, Haru!
Natsuki.
I've been waiting for you.
What'll we do?
Leave it to me.
I might not look it,
but I'm a 17 year veteran.
Otoko nara kosoyo, manatsu no umi ni...
If you're a man, the midsummer ocean...
Dry!
Hot, hot, hot!
Otoko nara kosoyo, manatsu no umi ni...
This is a new symptom. Be careful!
Careful, it'll spread! Run!
I have to try, even if I'm sad.
I have to try.
I have to go.
But I...
I don't think I can.
Haru.
Why did you come back?
I told you to leave!
Yuki, I hate...
Don't go running off like that.
You didn't say good bye. You promised!
You promised Grandma...
But it's dangerous for you to stay here, Yuki.
Is that why you helped everyone escape?
Because I love everyone.
Haru, tell me everything.
Why did you come to Earth?
I came to Enoshima with
Koko to fish up one of
our kind from the ocean.
One of your kind?
The baitball we saw from Akira's boat.
One of our kind was underneath it.
He's one of us,
but he causes trouble for humans,
so we came to fish him out.
But we can't fish,
so we thought we could
get a human to do it.
Is that why you chose me?
Yeah.
That's what you meant
by saving the world.
But he's strong. He controlled me.
I didn't think we could catch him,
so Koko and I decided
to lure him far away.
Lure him away?
What does that mean?
Koko and I are fish, so we baited him...
Hold on!
You're a fish?
He's a fish, too,
so if we went in the sea
and lured him far away,
I thought we could save
everyone from harm...
But I couldn't protect Koko.
What happened to Koko?
She fell under his control and
became part of his horde.
She may not be able to come back.
You're the only one who escaped?
That's why I sent everyone
away from Enoshima,
so I could lure him away this time.
Can you do that by yourself?
I don't know.
But if I don't hurry,
he might control me again soon.
When that happens, my hair will
stand straight up, and then...
I won't be myself anymore.
No one will be able to lure him away.
Then no one will be able
to save the Earth.
But what are you going to
do if you end up like Koko?
I know, but...
You'd be running into death!
But it's the only way.
I can't catch him myself.
You always do whatever you want.
Since the day I met you,
you said, "Let's fish together."
You forced me to fish,
and we fished every day.
Now, after learning from
Natsuki and the captain,
I love fishing.
Do you know what I was
thinking while I was
running here to Enoshima?
I thought I'd like to fish.
I want to fish with you,
Natsuki, and Akira.
But you disappeared
without saying anything,
saying you can't fish,
that you'd do something yourself,
doing whatever you want!
Sorry, but I didn't know what to do.
I'll fish!
Then everyone will be saved, right?
Give me a chance.
But...
We promised we'd fish together.
Yuki.
I'll try it.
I can't let you face danger alone.
Thank you.
Thank you, Yuki.
Don't be so secretive.
Water!
I ran out of water,
so I might be done for.
Seriously?
Someone's got to have some.
Let's hurry and meet
up with everyone else.
It's okay.
What?
Something's coming out.
Haru...
That should do it.
Natsuki?
You're the only companions for me.
Haru, are you okay?
Yeah, but there's something
else I have to tell you first.
What is it?
Even if I manage to catch him,
I have to go home to my planet.
Is that right?
The heroes are here!
Yuki, Haru, we've been waiting for you!
You guys!
Why? Even though I did something bad?
There's no way you're a bad kid, Haru.
Everyone wanted to see you.
Here!
Thank you! I wanted
to see everyone, too!
I'm rejuvenated.
Are you all going...
Yes. We're about to catch the
biggest fish of our lives.
There's no time. Let's go.
What about a boat?
The captain will get us one.
Ayumi-chan went to get a rod, too.
You still haven't established
JFX's position?
JFX found! JFX found!
Prepare to attack!
Acquiring target information!
Ready to fire!
Don't worry.
As long as we protect ourselves from
the water, JFX poses no threat to us.
In an instant,
this Duck fleet will be...
Captain?
Haino, haino, haino.
Yoisho, yoishona.
Haino, haino, haino...
Ayumi-chan, how are things
going over there?
I just reached the Hemingway.
I'll get the rod.
Head over here as soon as you can.
Thank you. You really are
dependable, Ayumi-chan.
Yes!
Hey, look...
You can't be serious.
We could only watch
without saying a word...
Duck fleet.
Respond, respond!
Kokoroiki, kokoroiki.
as our Hemingway burned.
This is his fault.
What should I do? What should I do?
We were completely stunned.
Continued in #11