Miss Nureha...
Um, where are you going?
Will you take an escort?
You really saved us.
I thought it was just boars, but then
we were attacked by ogres.
No need to thank us.
We are adventurers.
Of course we save people in trouble.
I'm just glad you're safe.
Of course, we were saved by that lady, though.
I really can't take the sun...
Odyssey Knights
Odyssey Knights.
How are you feeling, Roe 2?
Sorry, can you close the curtains?
I can't take the sun.
Of course.
Water?
Thanks.
Not at all.
What is it?
Nothing... Is that the Celestial Robe?
Yeah. I'm impressed you know it.
My teacher wears the same thing.
Is he a caster, too?
Yes.
He's an enchanter.
This robe's pretty high-end gear.
It has wear-resistance and
is good for normal use.
It's perfect for long journeys.
You sound just like Shiroe.
Um... My teacher's name is Shiroe.
You sort of remind me of him.
So, you're a shrine priestess, and your
subclass is apprentice, huh?
Yes.
Oh, right...
I'll heal you.
No, no need.
But...
My subclass is vampire.
Oh, that's right...
Vampires are damaged by healing spells.
Yeah.
I'm still tired.
Um, what will you do now?
Where did you come from, Roe 2?
Where are you going?
Where did I come from, and where am I going?
A very philosophical question.
No, that's not what I meant!
I know.
Minori...
What's up?
Well, you see, during the last battle...
Croissant and Danish weren't hurt, but...
It's broken.
Oh, right.
Items have wear bars, too...
If we repair it, can we call them again?
You'd need the woodworking skill.
We were talking about pushing
the carriage to the next town.
It'd be really bad if more monsters appeared.
So Tohya says we should escort
the People of the Land.
Understood.
Why don't you get on the carriage, Rudy?
A sorcerer has more strength than a bard.
No.
I wouldn't want to make a lady do my job.
This is a big problem, though...
Monsters that normally live at higher altitudes
are coming down to the foothills.
Yeah, they're all displacing each
other's habitats, I'm sure.
Really?
There's a mountain area called
Boxurt to the west, right?
It has a pretty lake.
There are nobles that rule it,
but supposedly, monsters are
showing up there, also.
Boxurt?
We're going through it, right?
Yeah.
Oh, you don't need to worry.
The Odyssey Knights are over there now.
Yeah, that's right.
They're our heroes.
They risk their lives to protect
us from the monsters.
Heroes?
Maybe they're like D.D.D. or the Black Knights.
Yeah.
Odyssey... That's...
They're a nostalgia faction,
Flavor Horizon
Szechuan-style mapo tofu with a sinful flavor
a group that wants to go home,
sometimes called "Odyssey."
Their goal is to go back to the real world.
But sometimes they go too far
and cause trouble.
But he didn't say they were knights.
They may be someone different.
Yuyurugi Village
Japan Server
Odawara
Safe Zone/ No Monsters
No PvP
Skill Use Restricted
Entry Restrictions/ None
Exit Restrictions/ None
You saved me!
If I'd kept walking under the sun,
I wouldn't have lasted.
No, thank you.
We helped each other out.
Here's the food!
The People of the Land are paying for it.
They want to thank us.
Soy Sauce
I want soy sauce!
Worcestershire Sauce
I'll take Worcestershire sauce.
Me, too.
Mayo
Mayo is the best!
It's the cheap, everyday food
that's the best in this world.
Some adventurer, somewhere,
came up with this egg bowl, right?
This one's soy sauce, and
that's Worcestershire sauce.
She's using both?
The issue of Worcestershire versus
soy sauce is a complicated one.
Okay!
This thick, black one is Worcestershire sauce,
and the thick, black one is soy sauce, right?
Got it!
The mayo is good, too.
By the way, where were you
before you came here, Roe 2?
I came here from Oou.
I left about three months ago.
Oou?
That's where Shiroe went on his expedition.
Before that, I was someplace even farther away.
I used castling to get there.
Castling?
Well...
It's a special spell that lets you
change places with a servant.
Roe 2 is a summoner, after all.
Lately, Eins's guild, Honesty, has been
using it to investigate the fairy rings.
You know all kinds of things, Minori!
It's just something Shiroe told me...
Which means you switched
places with your servant?
I don't know if "servant" or "brother" is best.
I know... We'll go with "brother."
I switched places with my brother.
Your brother?
I'm heading toward Ikoma for now.
I can't get rid of this vampire
subclass without going there.
You can't take any quests to overwrite it, right?
Yeah.
I just have to drop it.
Jeez, how did I end up with this subclass?
I really want to ask the person in charge.
It just changes your appearance!
I mean, it's a little helpful on the moon,
but I wish they'd think about what
happens when you're on Earth!
Anyway, I can't go on being a vampire!
The moon?
Ikoma's near Minami, right?
What are we gonna do now, anyway?
It looks like we can't repair our
summon flute in this town.
It'll be hard to go on without horses.
Couldn't you just call some horses?
You can call horses, Sis Roe 2?
"Sis"?!
Ahem.
W-Would you call me "Sister"?
Sister.
Once more...
You, too!
Sister Roe 2...
That's it!
Sister!
I love it... "Sister"!
When someone calls me that,
it feels like they're relying on me.
I want to be someone who's
treated like a big sister!
I want to be loved for being a big sister!
Okay, I'll accompany you on your
journey, and give you horses.
I'll summon you a whole stack of horses,
better than anyone's ever seen!
As payment, you'll let me act like a big sister.
Got it, guys?
O-Okay.
I can't take the sun...
The water is so nice.
They say adventurers don't need baths, but...
Our wounds heal fast, and we
have self-cleaning functions,
but it just doesn't feel right without baths, huh?
Oh, yeah.
I heard that Boxurt place
we're going to is a big pain.
Rudy was saying so.
Really?
Well, it's all part of the adventure.
Hey!
What's going on with you and Rudy?
Going on?
He's my puppy, and I go on walks with him.
No way!
You two totally seem like a couple.
Then, what about you and Nyanta, Serara?
Nyanta's teaching you all kinds of things, right?
It's the stuff you'll need to
know to get married, right?
Serara, I've got a Marriage Ring that took
thirty raids and lots of delicious food.
You're married to me now.
No! It isn't like that!
Hey!
I'm sorry!
Jeez, Serara...
If you act like that, Nyanta will get mad
at you when you bathe together.
Bathe together?!
Isn't the water nice, Serara?
So...
How are things going with
you and Shiroe, Minori?
H-How are they going?
There's nothing going on with him, really.
It seems you have a lot of rivals for Shiroe...
Really?
I mean, he's the guy who founded the Round Table.
Both Marielle and Henrietta are
pretty, and friendly with him.
And then there's the Tea Party's leader, too, right?
And also, Akatsuki!
If you want to get close to my lord,
you must defeat me first!
Come to think of it, isn't Roe 2
wonderful, as well?
No, no... Sister Roe 2.
Wh-When did you get here?
Since I'm the big sister, I have physical
advantages over you guys.
Of course, my boobs, too!
Get a grip, girls.
Breasts are just for show!
Was that too much for my little sisters?
Marie?
You look glum.
What's going on?
I was wondering what to do for the spring event.
The typical answer would be flower-viewing.
Flower-viewing, huh?
Yeah, you're right.
That's a good idea.
Everyone can enjoy it.
And that might make everyone friends again.
Marie...
Is there really no way for people
to be friendly and have fun together?
And so, it hasn't been a major problem so far.
Got it.
Keep at it.
Understood.
But I think you should look at the encounter
frequency in a bit more detail.
You're right.
Thanks.
Shiroe
Log Horizon (Guild Master)
Akatsuki?
How do things look there?
Yeah.
Right now, nothing major is going on here.
What about the old chief, my lord?
Things seem okay.
You keep at it, too, okay?
Yeah.
Leave it to me.
You tired, Shiroe?
It's too early for sighing.
There are many problems to discuss, villain.
Yeah.
A major gap is quickly developing here in Akihabara.
Those who can develop new
technology or go hunting
in the fields are getting richer and richer,
and those who can't are spending the small
amount of money they make just to live.
That again?
So, what are you trying to say
is the cause of this gap?
People learning the Teachings and the
development of new items by crafters.
Why are the Teachings a problem?
Anyone can get one if they work hard.
That isn't the issue.
The large guilds are using their manpower
to expand their businesses.
We should work to prevent anyone
from establishing a monopoly.
That's quite the accusation.
Honesty's no different, in terms of scale.
We don't do that.
And we haven't gained any Teachings.
The Teachings that each guild has
learned should be made public.
The same with crafting recipes—
Hey!
That's going too far.
That's right.
Since the Apocalypse, making items has
been a process of trial and error...
The ramen, soup, figures, the custom carriages.
Each of those represents a huge time
investment by a craftsman.
The Teachings can only be used by the person
who gained them, so even if we make
them public, there's no point.
I see.
Then why don't we confiscate any bank accounts
above 80,000 gold,
and redistribute it to adventurers
with the fewest assets?
That would help the income gap.
That's insane.
The money, the Teachings, the recipes...
They all belong to the people who
worked hard to get them.
If we take them, it'd be a huge deal.
You know that, don't you?
But there are people who
can't adapt to this society.
Are we just going to abandon them?
That's why we've been holding all these events,
to try and make it easier for people
to participate, I thought...
That arrogance just keeps them further away.
Hey.
I w-wasn't trying to be like that.
I just...
If we give these people money and recipes,
will they start working hard and happily?
Well...
But we cannot just leave them.
If you force people to publicize
their crafting recipes,
that would hurt the engineers' motivation.
Whenever you're making a recipe,
it's a lot of hard work before it's done.
If only Crusty were here at a time like this...
Don't be ridiculous.
I understand your proposal.
And I think some kind of action is necessary.
But the Round Table has a finite budget.
We aren't getting money from
the nobles like Minami.
Let's all see what we can come up with.
But if it becomes too late...
There's no point in doing this anymore.
If we make a huge decision
like that just among ourselves,
it could destroy Akihabara.
Boxurt Mountains
Boxurt
Field/ Monsters Present
PVP Permitted
Skill Use Permitted
Entry Restrictions/ None
Exit Restrictions/ None
Thanks to Sis Roe 2's horses,
we made it into the Boxurt Mountains,
but this path is a mess!
Um, in the old world, this was Hakone.
Hakone was originally a volcano.
Should I go on ahead?
Visibility is low, and if there are any
obstacles in our way, it'll be dangerous.
Yeah.
Sulfur, huh?
Wait.
I'll go, too.
I'll summon you some servants.
After all, I'm your big sister.
Servants?
Wh-What the?!
I'll pass...
Then take Wolfie!
Thanks, both of you.
Let's get going, then.
The sulfur really stinks...
I told you Boxurt wasn't going to be easy.
But the fog's thicker than when
I last came through here.
Looks like trouble.
We've still got quite a few...
You guys in trouble?
Are you adventurers?
Want to buy some swords?
We have some from levels 10 to 15.
They're real treasures, made in Akihabara!
No, our levels are higher than that.
Anyway, what's going on?
One of our carriages broke.
Then push the broken one into the ravine,
and pile all you can into the second.
I don't want to throw away our cargo.
Would you guys buy them all?
That'd be great.
You two together could afford them, right?
That's crazy.
I'd love to help, but...
Forgive them, travelers.
Since their axle broke, they've spent
a whole day and night here.
Dariella/ Chronicler
I know they're rude, but please forgive them.
Oh, um...
I'm Dariella. I'm a traveling writer.
A Person of the Land.
Hello, lady.
I'm Rundel Haus Code.
He's Tohya.
We're adventurers from Akihabara.
Oh, my. From Akihabara?
Would you be willing to carry some of
these boxes to the fortress ahead?
It would really help the merchants
if adventurers were to aid them.
It's amazing how strong you are,
with those thin arms!
Um, Igarashi?
It's Isuzu.
Um, this box is filled with goat slimes...
Some weird guy in Akihabara made us take them.
They ate really fast and passed right out!
They spent a whole night on
a mountain with monsters.
Of course they're exhausted.
Are you one of the merchants' wives?
No, I was just riding back to
Minami on their carriage.
Minami is the same direction as Ikoma, huh?
Yes.
Everyone, how about some after-meal tea?
We have snacks, too.
Snacks!
These are Nyanta's special cookies!
How are they?
They're sweet.
They're very good.
Where are you all going?
The Redstone Mountains.
I'm heading to Ikoma, but I'm
going that far with them.
Because I'm their big sister!
Big sister...
You all certainly are young.
Our goal is just beyond the pass.
Yes.
But Shiroe said there might be wyverns here...
Wyverns are flying monsters, right?
Their range is spreading.
As are those of the ogres and other monsters.
What's that sound?
Something doesn't feel right, somehow...
It's coming closer!
A raid team?
They're with
Plant Hwyaden.
From Minami!
Shunichi
Race/ Elf
Guardian, Lv. 90
Plant Hwyaden
He's level 90.
So are the others.
They don't look like PKs.
They're probably the Odyssey Knights.
The ones protecting the People of the Land?
Yes.
What's that thing they're carrying?
It's the Mobile Temple of Boreas.
The Mobile Temple of Boreas
The Mobile Temple?
I only heard about it on my travels,
but the Odyssey Knights are taking
them all across the land.
It immediately revives any adventurer
who loses their life in its vicinity.
With that temple, they can revive
anywhere and at any time.
An instant Cathedral.
So the Minami adventurers invented that?
But they look so lifeless.
It's like a funeral procession.
It lets you revive anywhere.
And I don't know if it's a side effect of that,
but I'm told it disturbs the voices
of adventurers' hearts.
The voices of their hearts?
Even so, that temple is something
important to you adventurers, right?
On their journey, they stop at the town of Safil.
There, Isuzu performs a concert.
Her melodies entrance the People of the Land.
Isuzu is happy and exhausted
when Rudy shares with her
the secrets of this world's music and the
People of the Land's dream.
Next time: When the Concert Ends.
When the Concert Ends
I have friends to run with me.