Taichi.
Huh?  What?
Stay focused.
If Arata comes to watch us,
I want to show off my team,
and how strong we are.
Watch us play, Arata.
This is the second round
of the group stage...
We're up against Yamaguchi
Mioka High School.
Mioka...
Yamaguchi Mioka?!
Yamaguchi Mioka is the
public school with the most students
accepted to Tokyo University!
The star of public high schools...
They're all wearing glasses.
Desktomu-kun times five...
Huh?
He started placing the cards from
the left after shuffling them?
They all used that method?!
So there's no pattern
to their placement?!
They're that confident in
their memorization skills?
Wait, that's not what we
should be worrying about...
The three guys over there
won the All Japan High
School Quiz Championship!
Why are they playing karuta?
Why do we keep getting matched
against weird opponents?
The five of you have to get us there!
We absolutely have to win!
It doesn't matter how
distinguished their school is.
It doesn't matter if
they're quiz champions.
We've spent so much time
on competitive karuta!
We can do this, guys!
Hey, Captain!
Chihaya Furu
Verse 10
Rain
takes
longer
to dry
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
You may be barred from playing
in the tournament tomorrow.
No unauthorized personnel allowed
What do we do?
There's never been an incident
with substituting before.
I could ask a friend of
mine who coaches baseball.
Wait, baseball is tough on violations.
We should look towards a
sport that isn't as harsh.
Letting this slide won't teach
our students anything.
Committee
Member
Masuoka
Masato
(Grade 6)
If his purpose here is to participate
in the individual tournament,
it is our duty as educators to
punish him by taking that away.
B-But, you must realize...
They're close acquaintances
So they can't say anything
Wataya Arata-kun is special.
Because he's the grandson
of an Eternal Master?
No, that's not why.
He's a truly marvelous karuta player.
Hello
I dare say that Master Suo can
only be defeated if Wataya-kun
continues to mature.
Sunglasses
aren't
allowed?
I can't deny that Master Suo is strong.
Why not?
But his strange behavior
makes it difficult to use
him as a role model for children.
I truly believe that it is our duty
to nurture Wataya-kun's growth!
So much pressure on Arata-kun!
So much hate for Master Suo.
I don't
know if I'll
graduate
this year.
He's right...
Master Suo is the biggest headache
the karuta world has ever seen.
Honestly, I want to see him
lose as soon as possible,
I don't know when
I will graduate.
but that doesn't make this right...
Excuse me!
It wasn't Arata's fault!
I asked him to sit down with us!
He helped make this tournament
memorable for us!
We weren't trying to cheat
our way to victory!
We just wanted to be able to play a match!
Shoji!
Please let Arata play in
the individual tournament!
Shoji!
I beg you!  I beg you!
Is that so?
In that case...
They can't do that!
I have to accept my punishment.
Arata...
But...
I'm focused on winning the
individual tournament.
I'm not interested in team tournaments.
Thank you...
Thank you, Arata.
You should have started a team.
I was just jealous.
Jealous that Taichi and Chihaya
had their own team.
Next time, we'll meet in a match.
Arata
Sorry...
I'm sorry...
Yamaguchi Mioka High School Karuta Advisor
Oikawa Tomonari (38)
Excuse me...
Are you the coach for Yamaguchi
Mioka High School?
I'm Miyauchi, the advisor for Mizusawa.
Oh, hello.
I'm very surprised.
Your members are all third-years.
They chose to participate in
this tournament when they're
probably busy studying
for college exams?
Yes, karuta is very useful in
studying for college exams.
Oh, is that so?
It lets students train their concentration
and memorization through a game.
A convenient tool.
I'm not too interested in winning,
but it's funny how we're
beating schools that spend
all their time practicing
competitive karuta.
My, that's terrifying.
Beat the crap out of them.
Spends all
her time
practicing
karuta
Especially you, Ayase-san!
My life means nothing...
The storm will soon carry...
What now?
My style is big on attacking
the opponent's side,
but I've never seen cards placed
evenly in the middle like this!
This makes it easier for me to make mistakes!
I need to memorize!
I'm moving my cards.
Huh?!
He...
He moved all of them!
so I wish for a memory
of you to take with me
Stay calm!
If I focus, I can memorize
their positions!
None are left...
A dead card!
I moved because he did!
Chihaya, be careful.
I was thinking that they were
a bunch of intellectuals who
were giving karuta a try,
but they understand karuta.
They're good.
She typically places "None are"
towards the upper left.
Yamaguchi Mioka High School
Quiz Society President
and Karuta Club Vice-President
Nakayama Manabu (Third-year)
Specializes in astronomy
Such mistakes can arise when you stick
to certain placements.
Nicknamed Poseidon
Karuta is very fascinating.
My first encounter was a year ago.
When Sasaki from the karuta club
came to see me for advice.
You want us to practice with you?
You can draw parallels between
buzzer pressing and karuta,
so it might help.
It all began when I watched the DVD
with the Master and Queen matches.
This is...
Exactly like buzzing in
early and the lag effect!
Buzzing in early is when:
Question: The Winter Triangle
is formed by Procyon, Si—
At that point,
you can guess the rest is "Sirius, and what?"
Betelgeuse!
It's exactly like unique syllables
in competitive karuta.
The lag effect is when:
As this trip takes me away...
Humans aren't machines.
If I buzz in after hearing "The Winter
Triangle is formed by Procyon,"
the moderator will still say
part of the next word.
The Winter Triangle
is formed by Procy—
—on, Si—
Oops
If I can catch that extra syllable,
I have what they call
"game sense" in karuta.
He knew which card to go for after "As"?
No way...
I'm moving my cards.
What?!
I have to memorize
their positions again!
I don't have any game
sense to speak of.
I just have decision-making skills!
Gust of wind...
I'm losing my sense.
I'm moving my cards.
Huh?!
Nakayama...
I'm his teacher, and I'd have
to describe his intelligence
and memory as freakish.
hence the name fall leaves
You have to press the button
before you can answer.
Inspiration...
You have to trust in that
moment of inspiration
and attack!
Above all, he has guts.
For you, I head out to the
fields to pick spring greens
A multi-syllable card! Got it!
I'm relieved that I was
able to keep my own card?
This is how I play karuta?
Really?
May the time we spend...
How many cards did I hit?!
I took a card from the opponent's
side, but I was just forcing it!
What was that?
Scary...
Wasn't that the Queen?
So she really did lose weight.
Shinobu-chan's back to the weight
she was at when we played.
Have I grown at all?
What are you doing, Shinobu-chan?
You're soaked.
What happened to the Birdman rally?
Uh, what?  Again?
Shinobu-chan, I won't be able to
play in the individual tournament.
I broke one of the rules.
Good luck tomorrow.
Mr. Masuoka.
If Wataya Arata isn't playing, I forfeit.
What?!
What are you talking
about, Wakamiya-san?!
The Queen can't drop
out of the tournament!
Yeah, you shouldn't joke around...
I don't know what you did,
but stop acting cool
and lower your head!
Beg them to let you play!
I'm also asking you to let him play.
Wh-Why are you doing
this, Shinobu-chan?
I didn't get to watch the
Birdman rally, and now...
Can you not disappoint me any further?
Do you not want to play against me?
What will Shinobu-chan and
Arata see when they watch me?
I'm no longer the high
school first-year me...
No longer the sixth grade me...
Omi Learning Center
We finally made it!
I'm completely drenched!
What do I do now?
I can't go watch the match
by the main office.
Everyone else is running around,
but that person with glasses
is taking it easy...
I really appreciate it!
Thanks.
Hanano-san?
You actually thought to bring an umbrella?
The forecast said the chance of rain was low.
Well, the JMA and the websites
I checked said it would be sunny,
but the Japan Weather Association
said that there was
a chance for showers.
O-Oh...
How was the Akashi Girls' match?
Here are the notes I took.
How do you think our match went?
There are a lot of people
so it's not easy to get in.
First Akashi Girls' all look ordinary
Girl in front (with long hair)
Pink checkered handbag (Ponita)
white hand towel
pink macaroon phone strap
I was too far away to see the cards,
Girl with glasses
(ordinary, sharp-tongued, popular)
black handbag with a charm attached
white plain towel... cell
but I wouldn't have understood
what was going on anyway.
Thanks, Hanano-san!
Even the color
of their socks...
This is more than enough information.
I was so relieved
when you didn't suddenly tell me
to play in a match this time!
That was a big shock at the Tokyo regional!
Just to be clear, I'm not interested in
playing in the national championship!
I'm fine with scouting other teams!
Unlike everyone else, I don't have
the fighting spirit to be a player!
I'll try to consolidate these notes,
so grab some lunch when
you have a chance.
O-Okay...
I thought that everyone else in our
club was itching to play in matches,
but Komano-senpai might be different.
Makes sense to me.
The world of karuta is too competitive
and intense. Who wants that?
This is turning out to be a good match.
Nakayama, your drive to challenge
yourself has always impressed me.
To think that you would
work so hard at karuta
for the sake of doing well
in the quiz championship.
That's probably what the
coach is thinking...
However, in reality...
I work hard at the quiz championship
for the sake of karuta.
Huh?  Really?
I love this atmosphere.
He's a freak...
The tension before a card is read.
So silent, you can hear people breathe.
Wow, she has crazy lung capacity.
Chihaya, you can win
if you just breathe.
Excuse me...
I can feel it rushing in.
I can see it.
She's kinda pretty.
Star-wise, she's a Vega.
Orihime...
I don't mind it when she
looks down on me.
Sorry about that.
Oops, I'm wasting my brainpower
on unnecessary thoughts!
How's everyone else doing?
In the back
We're losing the other three
except the one in the back?!
I'm moving my cards.
What?  Again?
Doesn't really matter.
I don't know why he doesn't get it.
Our Suihoku society teaches
defensive karuta.
The opponent can change his placement
around as much as he wants.
My goal is to prevent him from taking
any of the 25 cards on my side.
By making that my priority,
I'm somehow able to take the
opponent's cards, as well.
...wet with dew
As friends and strangers come
and go from the capital,
A dead card.
A poem by the blind monk Semimaru.
Check...
There are six poems by
monks on the field...
My fear is not of being forgotten,
Got it!
This poem was written by Ukon about
her attachment to a man who left her.
There are four poems
by women on the field.
I'm moving my cards.
This girl is impressive.
I keep shuffling my cards around
and it doesn't faze her.
If he's randomly placing his cards,
then I won't bother remembering
them by position.
I'll admit that it's impressive.
Their style has no fixed card placement
and frequently moves the cards around.
But in karuta, you're only
allowed to move your arm.
Against opponents who aren't
great at memorization,
his swing is fast enough.
But I'm good at memorization.
I can understand.
Their emphasis is on
memorization and accuracy.
That's how I play karuta.
You need mental and physical
strength to play karuta!
I only memorize about half the cards.
Nishida was trying to teach me that
your body is important too!
It takes both mind and body...
I can't let her get into a groove.
I'm moving my cards.
And heart...
Again?!  How many times is that?!
Wow!  Can he really memorize them?!
Kill!  Kill!
That's impossible for me.
I could never do that.
Yes, that's me...
Can memorize
Can't memorize
I belong to the group that
can't memorize too well!
Once I realized that,
I felt a lot better.
While I sigh and lament...
Stay calm.
When the misty bridge...
I'm moving my cards.
This is the first time I've faced
someone who keeps moving his cards.
Stay calm.
If I stick it out long enough...
There, they're almost all
one-syllable cards now.
I'm moving my cards.
He's moving them back now,
...that this love has
also sullied my name
and he moved them to a strange spot.
It's go time.
Note that though...
She moved the instant the reader spoke.
She moved faster than sound!
...I shall return to you
When I must hide...
I don't even get a chance to move.
I trust my inspiration and attack.
My inspiration travels
through my brain...
But in her case...
It goes straight from
her ear to her finger!
She's no Orihime.
She's as sharp as...
...Bellatrix of the constellation Orion!
The Amazon Star!
Yamaguchi Mioka High School
Nakayama Manabu X
Hayashi Sosuke X
Toyota Hiroichi O
Sasaki Makoto X
Tokoro Daisuke O
Chihaya, don't fall asleep
while standing up!
Mizusawa High School
Ayase Chihaya O
Mashima Taichi O
Oe Kana X
Nishida Yusei O
Tsukuba Akihiro X
Wake up, Chihaya!
You were so close, Kana-chan!
You lost by two cards!
I was close, too!
Come on, Chihaya!
You lost by 12 cards!
You all did well.
It hurts to lose in the group stage,
but this experience will
help in the future.
I'm sure it'll help in
the Quiz Championship!
It won't help...
It doesn't have to help!
This loss was a loss in karuta...
I'll avenge it by playing karuta!
You guys are so smart
and so dumb.
Good work, everyone!
Congratulations on advancing
to the playoffs!
I brought some homemade cookies!
I won't have any
How did the other schools do?
Was it rough moving around
in the rain, Komano?
It was no problem!
Oh, speaking of which, the
Queen was completely drenched.
Oh, I saw that!
It was
scary!!
She walked in dripping wet,
then she helped this person
in a Fukui T-shirt and begged
them to let him play in
the individual tournament.
Because she wanted to play him.
So the Queen has a rival.
It's Arata.
Arata and Shinobu-chan...
Because she wants to play him...
Sumire-chan, can you tell me what—
We don't have time for that right now!
Taichi.
Let's come up with the
order for our next match.
Stop it.
Queen and Arata.
Those words will distract Chihaya.
I need her to focus
on the team match.
So Arata is...
here.
Uh...
I believe that Komano-senpai should
be a starting member for the playoffs.
What's that?
You're tired, so you
want to switch out?!
Bingo!
So you must not want
to play that badly.
You're wrong!
Komano-senpai will know better how
to use all the data he's collected!
That's right.
Either Tsukuba-kun or I can drop out.
What do you think, Desktomu-kun?
Yes...  I'd say...
Wait.
I think we should use the
same members we've been
using for the next match.
Huh?
I think we should go without Desktomu-kun.