The raid boss is in there, isn't it?
So it seems.
Calling Fortress
Safe Zone B
Japan Server
Shibuya
Dungeon/ No Monsters
No PvP
Skill Use Restricted
Entry Restrictions/ None
Exit Restrictions/ None
You stay here, old man.
We'll have plenty of work for you later.
Sure.
I'll be waiting.
Only fifteen minutes and
thirty seconds until moonrise!
Begin the operation.
So you're here, adventurers?
Engage!
All groups, formation B!
Take these, Shiro!
Shield Other Stance!
Reactive Heal!
Purification Barrier!
Shiro!
My lord!
Mana Channeling!
These empathions...
The Pioneers
The Pioneers.
The eternal moths steal MP.
Tetra        Naotsugu        Marielle        Kushiyatama
So we'll use Mana Channeling
to absorb all MP from party 1
and redistribute it evenly.
Shiroe        Akatsuki        Tetra        Naotsugu        Marielle
The extra MP that our bodies
emit during the process
will draw them out.
There they go.
Look at all of them!
Their individual levels aren't an issue, but...
Their numbers and locations are the problems.
Shiroe's group will draw all of the
enemies from around the area.
Using an enchanter as a tank?
That's crazy!
The enemies are all lined up.
Let's tear them apart!
Round Windmill!
You're getting into this, Shouryuu.
It's the only way I can keep up
with Naotsugu!
Maestro Echo!
Lightning Nebula!
Freezing Liner!
Summon Servant: Phoenix!
All right!
That's most of the ones in front, Shiro!
You have paper-thin armor, Shiro.
You shouldn't be doing this.
I've done kiting before.
I'll manage.
We can't do it like Demikas,
but let's finish this!
More enemies from 4 o'clock!
Six moon rabbits!
Can you do it, shrimp?
Don't call me shrimp, Stupid-tsugu!
Shield Swing!
Axel Fang!
A combination technique?
W-Wow.
We will protect my lord.
Stop it!
I wanna do that, too!
Akatsuki's gotten even better, hasn't she?
Yeah!
Shiro's serious about this now.
Then I have only one job!
Ikkigake!
This is the big show.
Go, Souji!
The raid boss has started moving.
Shiroe,
party 2's assault team has
engaged the enemy leader!
Finally time for the boss, huh?
Head straight to the roof!
Soujirou!
Shiro, good work back there.
We warmed him up for you, Shiroe.
Whoa, is that him?
That's...
His name is Taliktan,
Genius of Summoning
Taliktan /Genius, Lv. 86
Rank /Raid
the genius of summoning.
His level is 86.
He's raid rank.
His level isn't that high...
But our levels are all over the place,
and we've never worked together before.
Soujirou        Henrietta        Korou
And that AoE attack he just
used on Soujirou's group...
Nazuna        Nyanta        Soujirou
Groups 2 through 4, get to the rear
and heal the assault group.
Anchor Howl!
So that's a Genius...
There are nine minutes and
forty-seven seconds left!
Gaia Wind Healing!
All will fall asleep.
Why?
Why are you doing this?
All will fall asleep!
We can't talk about this?
Fall asleep, adventurers!
He's just like Camaysar.
There's no way to talk to them...
We're talking past each other.
Shiro, I can't keep this up!
What do we do, Shiro?!
Everyone attack.
All will fall asleep.
All will fall asleep! Fall asleep!
N-No...
Why?
All parties, hurry and get set up!
The moon isn't up, but they're back.
If you don't fall asleep, their dust will
hit you with another status effect,
so be careful!
Shut up, Demi!
You need to...
Finish this fast, Shiroe!
Those damned Odyssey Knights!
The jerks are making our lives harder.
All will fall asleep.
All will fall asleep!
Shiro!
Look!
If we let this continue,
the antenna will shatter before
we can do anything about it!
Party 1, raise your DPS and maintain aggro.
Get him away from the antenna
and down into the hall below!
Parties 2 through 4, deal with the adds,
and then meet up with us!
By "hall," does he mean that thing?
We're really high up.
Aggro Exchange!
Now!
Party 1, move to the hall!
Look! Look!
It's a flying idol!
We've lowered his HP by forty percent.
But his dodge rate has suddenly shot up.
Sleep, and your safety will be assured.
Waves will return to waves,
and particles to particles.
Give me your souls,
and I promise you safety and return.
The sleep of the eternal moths?
What do you people know?
Those who agree to the contract
and hand over their souls
are to allow access and
choose to stand by in sleep!
That light is bad!
Insta-kill AoE!
Split up!
Nyanta!
What is this?
We were far away from that!
Party 1     Party 2     Party 3      Party 4
This is the attack that hit us.
It can't be dodged, and it selects targets randomly?
Fall asleep and choose, adventurers!
Crap!
You saved me!
That's my job!
Are you okay?
Marie!
Thank you.
Boot-Up Heal everyone!
Roger!
Tetra...
Leave it to me!
We can still do this!
You can do this, so do it!
Aurora Heal!
Front ranks for parties 1 and 2,
increase DPS to the limit!
Nazuna's group, put a barrier
on each of them in order!
You got it!
Roger!
What are you going to do?
Everyone else, keep your HP up
and attack in waves!
Sleep... Sleep!
Genius of Summoning
Taliktan /Genius, Lv. 86
Rank /Raid
He's down to about thirty percent of his HP!
Sleep, and I promise you safety and return.
That AoE is coming back.
If we get attacked now...
We survived it with Boot-Up Heals and barriers?
You knew who it would attack?
I figured it out the second time.
It's a penetration attack on
the threat table's top five.
So it targets those who generated the
most aggro during its cool down?
In this crazy battle,
he kept track of every skill the raid
used and the damage they did?
Even though we've never fought together before?
Parties 3 and 4, draw the tentacles' attention.
Parties 1 and 2, attack the main body.
And our MP isn't as low as I thought.
Wolfie, go!
This is
the Full-Power Controlled Combat of the
Tea Party's legendary mana controller...
Full-Control Encounter!
Leave this to me, Shiro!
We know what we need to do.
So finish this, Shiroe!
Minori!
You're in charge of parties 3 and 4!
Right!
I was arrogant.
What's wrong?
Everyone flattered me and said
I was a strategist and the
training squad's leader, but...
I have a long way to go.
I'm all fired up now!
Lamination Syntax!
Frost Spear!
Sleep...
Stand by within the peace.
The beach where my lord and I
walked wasn't like that.
Our memories weren't stolen.
We offered them up and made them
into the power to rise again.
We shattered the fragments of the past
and turned them into the power to rise!
You are models with no power.
Anchor Howl!
We're greedy.
We want to take everything we can.
Singularity.
I have my friends and a place to strive for.
Infinity Force!
All right!
We have people waiting for us!
Thorn Bind Hostage!
Merciless Strike!
Assassinate!
Looks like he ended it.
Way to go, villain in glasses.
I see.
Got it.
Yeah, we're finished here.
The Calling Fortress, huh?
It sounds like a fun place to try and raid.
You...
Darling, why are you crying?
I-I'm not crying!
I'm drooling!
My eyes are drooling!
There, there.
Jeez, get a room, you two.
My blushing pinkie has a hangnail...
Day 1
Tetra's Recital!
Is it because they defeated the raid boss?
Things seem different.
I guess we saved both the antenna
and the world, huh?
Yes.
A fine example of "two birds with one stone."
Still, I can't believe there's
communications equipment here.
It's probably because we defeated Taliktan.
The weird parts are still a game.
That's my line.
Don't get mad.
You're such a kid.
Well?
I understand...
Okay, there we go!
Are we connected?
With the moon?
He...o... An...ybod... hear ...e?
Is it Princess Kaguya?
Ni hao?
Bonjour?
Hello? Can you hear me?
Aloha?
Guten tag!
Hello?
That voice...
Is that you, Shiro?
Don't tell me...
I knew it!
Yoo-hoo, Shiro!
Kanami?
K-Kanami?
It can't be—
Shiroe's ex-girlfriend!
It's been so long!
How have you been?
Don't "It's been so long" me!
I heard you're doing something
interesting in Akihabara.
Um, what was it?
Round robin?
The Round Table.
How did you know about that?
And wait, did you come back to the game?
And wait, where are you?
She's not on the moon, is she?
She might be...
This is the China server.
Okay, that's the last one.
Everyone's okay, right?
Hey, Kanami!
We're done!
I'm on a journey, and I found this TV station.
It looked interesting, so I fiddled with
some stuff, and it connected.
Because it looked interesting?
Oh, right... Shiro!
My daughter's three now.
Daughter?
She has a daughter?
I know.
I'm sorry I never got to congratulate you.
Did I tell you?
No.
But I heard.
So I'll say it now.
Congratulations.
Thanks!
You have a kid?! Seriously?
And she's so cute!
She moves around so much.
She'll run up to you and then cling to your leg!
I see.
Then you need to go home
to our old world, right?
Huh? Why?
Hey, Shiro!
I want to show this world to my daughter.
It's so big and so pretty and so wonderful.
And her mom has lots of friends here.
I want to send her on an adventure where
she'll meet people all over the world.
She loves high places.
So I want to let her ride a griffon.
I want to show her the great forests
and the seas and the deserts.
I want to teach her that the
world is a beautiful place!
Yeah...
That's true.
You're right.
It's not that I'd never considered the possibility.
I'd just given up on it as impossible.
Instead of going home
or staying here,
there's a third option.
Connect the two worlds
and make it so you can travel between them.
Is that possible?
It's worth trying, I think.
But didn't you say the adventurers
might cause a war here?
That doesn't mean going home
is necessarily the best option.
That's just what I'd expect.
That's my lord.
Then go get it done, Shiro!
Is that a quest?
Yes, that's right!
A quest!
No.
What? Shiro!
Kanami, I made a guild.
It's called Log Horizon.
I have lots of friends.
So we'll accept that quest.
We'll be the first in the world to see that.
But since we're old friends,
if you hurry, there may be time
for me to show it to you.
Shiro...
There's an answer that doesn't
involve giving up on this world
or the old one.
Find it. Promise.
Log Horizon accepts your quest.
That's my bus guide!
Bus guide?
Oh, right...
Crusty's here, too.
Crusty's there?
M-My lord?
What?!
What do you mean?
My lord... My lord...
Crusty's there?
Yeah! And he said—
I didn't do anything...
Hey! Shiro! Hello?
You'll break it! You'll break it!
I see Shiroe is as interesting
as ever.
Interesting?
So, who will be the one that comes to get me?
Misa or Rieze?
Kanami's friends are all so unique.
Jeez...
After all this, that monster still isn't here.
Now I'll have to find him and give
him a talking to, no matter what!
You want me to tell the Westelande nobles
to restore normal relations with Eastal?
Those Genius things caused the moths, right?
This is no time for infighting.
Does that mean
you're telling me to work with
Shiroe and the Round Table?
Depending on the circumstances.
With that traitor?
No way.
I'm not letting him go home, either!
I'm ordering you, as well.
Stop the war with Eastal.
Huh?
Ordering?
You're ordering me?
You're a filthy woman. A rat.
You're just a puppet.
And you're ordering me?!
You...
I'll remind you what happens
when you get smart with me!
Enough.
I was the one to make the promise.
You will not be the one to deal with Shiro.
The Round Table will contact us.
The villain in glasses is probably thinking
about how to negotiate with us right now.
Let's wait and look forward to seeing what he does.
Okay, Indicus?
I'm not like Kanami and Leonardo.
I'm a mere supporting player, like Kazuhiko.
But that doesn't mean
I have the option of giving up
on the last performance.
I need to get stronger,
so I can see the clear blue sky
that comes after the storm...
Ruin Islands Jacksea
Japan Server
Field /Monsters Present
PvP Permitted
Skill Use Permitted
Entry Restrictions /None
Exit Restrictions /None
Did that help Shiroe a little, I wonder?
Little siblings, your big sister did her best!
I'm hungry...
Come to think of it, so am I.
We haven't eaten anything since yesterday!
I miss mayonnaise.
When you're tired, you need red bean buns.
Or we could have gelatin sometimes.
Let's eat breakfast as soon as we get back, then.
I'll give it all I've got and make you my best meal.
Then we're having curry! Right, Chief?
My lord? My lord?
What is it, Akatsuki?
Good work, for now.
You, too, Akatsuki.
Let's eat!
Hey, where's the old man?
Still fixing the communications equipment.
And we're stuck looking after Regan?
I want to take a bath.
Well, it's fine.
While we're here, let's practice a little.
The old man's gone! He ran!
There's still more mabo!
No, my lord needs more curry.
No, I'm full...
It looks good.
May I join you?
The End