What happened to me?
Is this...
I, um...
Sh-Shiina, I—
I know.
A person must first experience
pain to be able to pilot Nyapollon.
What?
I will defeat all of the Nyangoro aliens.
I don't know how to respond
to that kind of confession...
So, this is goodbye.
Hey! Shiina, h-hold up!
Wait!
You're being a wimp, kouhai-kun!
What?
Take your rejection like a man,
for the sake of Earth's future!
What's going on here?
#13 One Step Before Winter
What was with that dream?
What? Are you still dreaming?
Jin-san? What are you, psychic?
I get that a lot, but I'm afraid not.
I thought you might still be buzzing
from the Nyapollon experience.
Oh, that...
Look at this.
Culture Festival Multiplayer Game:
Please participate in the following survey about "Milky Way Cat Nyapollon."
Nyapollon's survey.
This is the majority of them.
Looks like everyone enjoyed the show.
Really?
Good job, Sorata.
It was because everyone else
did such a great job...
It didn't matter who was in my position.
The end result would
have been the same.
That's very modest of you.
It's a level-headed analysis.
But...
I do feel a little more confident now.
Are you going to reapply to the
"Let's Make a Game!" contest?
Yes! I submitted my
application right after that.
I'm waiting for the results.
Akasaka told me to look over the notes
from the Nyapollon review meeting...
so that I wouldn't make
the same mistakes again...
and I wrote a pitch based on that.
So, how confident are you feeling?
Pretty confident.
Wow, that's great.
Your entry has been submitted.
Thank you.
Speaking of Ryunosuke...
That was pretty bold of Rita-san.
She's been texting me
constantly since that moment,
so I finally gave her Akasaka's number.
Maid-chan must have been mad.
Completely outraged.
It'd be nice if those two could
get it together properly.
Yeah.
What are you two doing together?
Mashiro asked me if I knew
where Kanda-kun was...
I figured you might be
up here, so I brought her.
Huh? What's wrong?
Do you need something?
I don't need anything.
What?
You came looking for me because
you needed something, right?
No.
I don't understand...
Aoyama, what's going on?
Don't ask me.
I found everyone!
Hey, Jin!
What am I going to do, kouhai-kun?
My once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity has presented itself!
I don't understand what
you're talking—
Why are you pouncing me
this early in the day?
I couldn't wait until tonight.
I feel like I'm in danger,
so I'll be staying out tonight.
Here, Jin, I made you lunch.
Oh, thanks.
Wasn't Jin-san just eating bread?
I Love You
Well? Did it win your stomach over?
I haven't eaten any yet.
Mashiron, what's wrong?
Did you see something you want to eat?
No.
What did Shiina come up here to do?
Who knows?
Are you mad about something?
Not at all.
I'll make it even more gorgeous next time!
You don't understand Mashiro, do you?
Look forward to tomorrow's lunch, Jin! Jin!
What? Do you?
I do, but I'm not telling.
It's not like you to say something like that.
I'm not that nice.
Aoyama, you are kinda mean
to me sometimes, aren't you?
I don't know what you're talking about!
Huh? What?
I'm depressed. Christmas is next month.
Really?
What? Are you saying
you have plans, Yayoi?
I'm throwing a party for the Softball Club.
You're such a kid.
Do you have plans, Mayu?
What about you, Nanami?
Who, me?
What about Kanda?
What will you do about him?
"Do"? What do you—
Don't you know that people suspect...
Kanda-kun and Shiina-san are dating?
You've got to get your act together!
That's right. It's not fair to Miyahara, either.
But I turned him down...
Wait! How do you know about that?!
It's obvious just by looking at Miyahara-kun.
Isn't it?
In any case, you've got
to make your intentions clear!
Okay...
To: Jin
Um, Mitaka-senpai?
Hey, Aoyama-san.
Is that a love letter?
Yes, something like that...
Wedding Registration
Mitaka Jin
Kamiigusa Misaki
C-Congratulations on getting hitched.
That's not funny, Aoyama-san.
I'm not surprised
Kamiigusa-senpai sent you that.
Oh, yeah...
I've got something I've
been meaning to give you.
What?
Happy White Christmas
If you'd like, why don't you
go see this with someone?
Tickets to a play! Are you sure?
Asami-san invited me,
but she can't make it now.
It'd be wrong of me to invite someone
else, so you can have them.
Thank you.
Oh, I almost forgot:
The performance is on Christmas Eve.
Huh?
You've got to use the tools at your disposal.
Happy White Christmas
Dec. 24, 7:00 PM
Shiina,
what were you going to
do if I had taken off...
my underwear while I was changing?
I would have knocked.
It'd be too late by then!
So, what do you want?
Are you going to say you
don't need anything again?
No, I do.
Are you hungry?
Promise you won't get angry.
If you're telling me that,
you must be about to
say something crazy.
It's incredibly normal.
Then, don't lead off with
a weird statement like that!
I want to make a lunch.
What?
Hold on, Shiina. A lunch?
You idiot, don't grab my arm!
Heed my words, Shiina.
Great potential lies within all humans.
However, there are some
things people cannot do.
People cannot grow wings.
These are things you have to accept!
There! That should do it!
Jin-san, why are you
putting an apron on her?!
How do I look, Sorata?
Take it off.
I never dreamed you'd be so forward.
That's not what I meant!
Shiina and cooking seriously don't mix!
I'm ready to cook.
It looks to me like you're
ready to make me cook!
I've got to go meet Rumi-san.
Have fun, you two.
What? Jin-san...
Sorata... I... cook.
Why are you talking like that?
I mean, are you serious?
Don't you need to work on your manuscript?
You must be behind schedule
because of the culture festival...
It's okay.
I'll work on my manuscript later.
You'll do it later?
You...
What?
Uh, nothing...
Sorata?
O-Okay, I get it.
You want me to teach you, right?
Please.
Sheesh...
Your main dish will be fried mackerel.
We'll also make fried eggs and a salad.
Let's start with the eggs.
I'll start with the eggs.
You don't have to repeat what I say.
Crack the egg by hitting it
against a bowl like this,
and then, break it in
half with both hands.
Try it.
Break it in half.
I feel like a parent...
who's just sent their kid out on
an errand for the first time.
Sorata, where's the knife?
No. Only after you've
leveled up your cooking skills.
I can break eggs.
That's all you can do.
I like knives.
Just how much do you like them?
So much that I can't sleep at night.
Okay, I hear ya. Let's use a knife.
That's how you hold it
when attacking someone!
This way feels more natural.
Don't point it at me!
What exactly are you planning to cook?!
Do you want to be cooked?
Forget this!
You can't cook!
No more knives!
I cannot allow that.
Then, hold it normally!
Fold the fingers of your free
hand when you use a knife.
Like a cat.
Exactly.
Whatever you do, don't cut yourself.
What? The end—
Did I win your stomach over?
If that's all it takes to win my stomach,
I'd be the guy who was won
over by a cucumber farmer.
Cooking's so deep.
What could you possibly have understood...
just by cutting off the end of a cucumber?!
I'll cut some more, then.
Fold your fingers.
Like a cat...
What?
You klutz, let me see that!
Wait right here!
Sensei! Shii—
There, that should do it.
Ow! What was that for?!
Revenge, of course!
Um, I'm s-sorry.
What are you apologizing for? It's creepy.
Will you be able to finish your manuscript?
Isn't the deadline tomorrow?
I have the cover left to do.
You should contact your editor.
Give up on cooking.
I shouldn't cook?
What?
Sorata, don't you want me to cook?
You don't need to injure yourself
any more than you did today.
That's not it.
What's not it?
I...
I don't understand.
What do you mean by that?
Enough talk.
I'm calling Ayano.
Huh? Hey...
What's her problem?
Up until recently...
Up until recently, it seemed like
she lived solely to draw manga...
Hello?
I want you for my
Christmas present, Onii-chan.
Who do you want to speak to?
What?! Oh, I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
Do you want something, Yuko?
Onii-chan?! I just had a
supernatural experience!
I called the number in my contacts list,
but it connected me to someone—
And that's what you call a
"supernatural experience."
I'll be going now.
Um, do you have a minute?
I like brown foods.
I-I see...
Will her manuscript be all right?
From the looks of it,
she'll finish up today.
The cut on her finger doesn't
seem to be causing any problems.
I see.
I want you to give me
your honest opinion.
How do you feel about
Shiina-san now?
What?
I mean, has she gotten prettier or cuter,
or do you get the urge to hold her?
Wh-What are you trying to get me to say?
Putting that aside...
You're putting it aside?!
Don't you think Shiina-san has
changed a little lately?
When I first met her,
she had the face of an artist.
A strange feeling washed
over me while talking to her.
She was looking at me
with those lucid eyes,
but not really seeing me...
She seemed otherworldly.
I got the same feeling the
first time I met her.
It's different now?
Now...
I want to make a lunch.
I'll work on my manuscript later.
I don't understand.
When I look at Shiina now,
something feels off.
There's something uncomfortable...
Or unpleasant... No, that's not it, either.
It just... well, it irritates me.
That's a valuable opinion.
Before, it seemed like the
only thing she thought about...
was manga, and nothing else mattered.
But then she suddenly
says she wants to cook...
It doesn't make sense.
It feels like...
the current Shiina isn't
the real Shiina...
I actually think her current
behavior is normal.
What?
Normal for a girl, I mean.
But I'm conflicted.
It's important for a girl who's
spent her whole life studying art...
to have normal high school experiences...
and learn what it means to be normal.
But if that causes her to lose her
unique outlook on the world...
I've been thinking about things
an editor shouldn't worry about.
Her talents and experiences
won't falter on her now.
I kinda understand what you're saying...
Before, or now...
Kanda-kun, which is the Shiina-san you like?
Huh? What...
What are you talking about?
But in this case, if you choose either
answer, it means you like her...
I...
I feel more at ease around...
the old Shiina than the new one.
Kanda Sorata-sama
Sorata?
What are you doing?
Cooking.
What about your manuscript?
I finished it.
Yeah, but what are you doing?
Cooking.
You hurt yourself doing that!
What if you hurt yourself
again and it doesn't heal...
within a day or two next time?
I'll be careful.
Don't be ridiculous!
Focus on your manga!
I finished my manuscript...
You used to work harder!
You focused on raising the
quality as much as you could!
People who have been allowed
to draw shouldn't slack off!
In that case...
In that case, get out from inside of me!
What does that mean?
I don't know!
I don't know what this feeling is...
What are you...
Tell me.
Tell me, Sorata.
End-of-Year Party Announcement
I know it's a little early, but...
the publisher's having an end-of-year party.
I forgot to give it to Shiina-san,
so could you give it to her?
I missed the right timing...
Kouhai-kun, I need your
advice about something!
Why are you Santa in a miniskirt?
Only a few more nights until Christmas!
It's still more than a month away.
Don't sweat the details.
Come to my room!
Want a lift?
I know better.
He might already have
plans for Christmas Eve.
I mean, it's hard to invite him
when we're not even dating...
Sakura Hall
What are you doing?
Misaki-senpai wanted my
advice about something.
Oh, I know. Come in
with me, Aoyama.
How can I make my feelings reach Jin?
You aren't dressed like
someone who's worried.
I'm sending out such passionate signals,
but Jin's too dense to notice!
So, these passionate feelings
you're trying to send him...
You know I wrote "I love
you" on his lunch, right?
I even put a marriage registration
form in his shoe locker.
M-Marriage registration?!
Yeah.
And when I took him
around the back of the school
and confessed my feelings,
all he said was: "It's cold.
Let's go back inside."
And when I confessed my
feelings behind the gym,
all he said was: "I'm tired.
Let's go home."
He's completely ignoring you.
Yeah.
I've done everything I can,
but he thinks it's all a joke!
That's why I've decided to
resort to my final option.
Your final option?
On Christmas Eve, I want you to
leave me alone with Jin.
What?!
Please help me.
She had her answer before she
even asked for my advice.
I should...
Huh?
Uh...
Aoyama?
Can we go... to your room?
Why don't you come in?
I-I'm fine here.
Oh, okay.
What's up?
Uh, here!
What is it?
I have two tickets to a play.
I was wondering if you'd go with me.
A play?
Yeah. It's actually on Christmas Eve...
Sure.
What? I-It's on the 24th.
Are you sure you want
to make plans with me?
I'm sure everyone else
has plans, so why not?
Then, it's a promise.
Okay.
Promise!
If you really don't trust me,
we can pinky swear it.
Let's do that!
I was only kidding.
Let's do it!
It's a promise.
Yeah, a promise.
Why am I anxious on Christmas Eve?
#14 The Windows and Lights of Christmas Eve
This'll be my first time spending
Christmas with a girl!
This is a big step up!
I guess I should recite some
sutras to calm down...