This is how you do swings!
I don't think so...
That dream made me nostalgic.
Yeah...
Suna looked cool,
even on a swing.
I'm going home.
What, you don't need to hold back.
Yamato may have made enough for you, too.
It's okay.
I have something I need to do.
Oh...
Yeah, later.
Something, huh?
My Friend
Takeo-kun!
Oh, where's Sunakawa-kun?
He said he had something to do.
Oh, I see.
I only asked because you guys are always together.
Are we?
Yeah!
I think we'll have some leftovers,
so give them to him later, okay?
Oh, I remember these!
They're "cake the kele," right?
Almost!
They're cake salé.
I made some star-shaped ones, too!
They're delicious.
They bring back happy memories.
Hey, Takeo-kun...
When's your birthday?
January 1st.
Huh?
That's amazing!
It's right in the middle of winter break,
Yeah!
Thanks!
Takeo!
Happy New Year!
Happy Birthday!
but my friends always came all the way
to our door to wish me "happy birthday."
January 1st, huh?
I'll have to start making preparations!
New Year's Day, so there's mochi...
Mochi Cream Puffs   Mochi Waffles   Mochi Donuts
There are mochi sweets, aren't there?
I wonder which ones would be good...
When is your birthday, Yamato?
Huh?
Um, June 15th.
I see.
June 15th...
That's real soon!
Y-Yeah, it is, actually.
OMG, I really said it
Sorry.
I guess I made it sound like
I want you to celebrate it.
Of course I do!
Let's celebrate!
What do you want?
I don't need anything.
I don't!
I really don't need anything...
On that day, can I...
Can I have you stay with me the whole day?
Yamato,
thank you for being born into this world.
People are born into this world.
Suna!
Birthday!
Happy birthday.
Wait, yours is on January 1st.
You have great memory.
Well, given the date...
I remember your birthday, too.
It's September 13th, right?
I remember, every year
in elementary school, I was invited
to your birthday party.
Thanks.
So, whose birthday is it?
Yamato's!
Oh, Yamato-san.
When?
June 15th.
The 15th...
Okay.
You have something on the 15th?
No, nothing really.
Really?
What're you going to do for her birthday?
Are you planning something?
Suna...
Yamato said she doesn't want anything.
She just
wants me to spend time with her...
She said that's all she wants.
Oh, okay.
But I want to take her to a
lot of places and celebrate!
You would.
Brainstorm with me!
Okay.
Suna!
Thank You
Yeah, yeah.
Welcome back.
People are born into this world.
Take, you're going to become
a big brother in January.
Hey, can you push that for me?
How old are you, Mom?
Forty, but I'm told my physical age is twenty-two.
So young...
Don't carry anything heavy!
This is fine!
I'll hold it!
I said I'm fine!
When I had you,
I had to carry another pregnant lady
to the delivery room,
when she went into labor first.
But I was fine then, too.
Press that
I don't really get it,
but that's amazing.
I see...
So I'm going to...
I'm going to have a little brother or sister!
People are born into this world.
Get out already
Wow, you're going to become
a big brother, Takeo-kun?
Wow!
Congratulations!
Do you know whether it's a boy or a girl?
She doesn't know yet.
And your mom is...
Forty.
Cool!
Takeo-kun as a big brother...
I'm sure you'll be great!
I bet you'd be a great father, too!
I think you'll be a great mother, too.
*blush*
I should get going.
Already?
Yeah, I have something
I need to take care of.
What's wrong?
I'm wondering if Suna's been
acting a bit strange lately.
Huh?
But he seems like his usual self.
I can't read Suna.
He almost never talks about himself.
Oh, could it be that...
Maybe he's lonely.
He's been hanging out with you all this time,
but now he spends less time
with you. He might be lonely.
You know, Sunakawa-kun adores you.
Takeo-kun, we don't have to spend
my birthday by ourselves.
Let's invite Sunakawa-kun, too!
Is that okay with you?
Sure.
Yamato...
Thanks!
I love her!
Suna!
Why don't you come and celebrate Yamato's
birthday with us on the 15th?
Huh?
Why?
Yamato thought you might feel lonely.
No, not at all.
Stare
Is that right?
Yeah.
Besides, I have something on the 15th.
I see.
So it isn't that he's feeling lonely.
Why did that even come up, anyway?
Well, I thought you've been acting
a little different lately.
I just wondered if something was going on.
Oh, yeah?
Even if there is something going on,
if he doesn't want to talk about it,
I'm not going to force him to.
I'll wait till he chooses to tell me.
Too close.
So, about this schedule you put together
for Yamato-san's birthday...
Yeah?
This schedule is packed like a day
in the life of a US president.
What? Tell me more!
6 AM: Watch sunrise at Enoshima
7 AM: Beach walk ~ gather seashells, etc.
8 AM: Movie ~look up what's in cinemas
10 AM: Amusement park
12 PM: Lunch ~somewhere good
1 PM: Zoo
2 PM: Hiking
3 PM: Tea in a café
4 PM: Park
5 PM: Back to Enoshima to watch sunset
6 PM: Walk her home
For starters, the 6 AM thing has to go.
This plan assumes sunshine,
but what will you do if it rains?
Oh, right.
There's also no time for breaks and for
getting from point A to point B.
Probably, no one except you could
handle this kind of schedule.
I see.
Guess I need to start over.
What are some places you can go,
even when it's raining?
How about that place we went after the school
festival when we were in junior high?
It was some indoor place where you could
bowl and do karaoke and stuff.
Oh, nice.
I'll go for that!
When we went, you...
What?
You couldn't fit your fingers into the bowling ball,
Hilarious...
so you just grabbed them to throw them...
I guess that happened.
I'd never seen anything like it.
Every time it was your turn,
the whole bowling alley was staring.
Toward the end, you'd attracted a small crowd.
I'm surprised you remember.
It was like you were playing softball
Who could forget?
6 AM: Bowling
7 AM
8 AM
They aren't open at 6 AM.
They open at 10.
Okay, 10 it is!
Now, what to do for lunch...
10 AM: Bowling
12 PM: Lunch
Beef bowl?
Ramen?
Isn't it better to pick a place
with a good dessert selection?
Yamato-san likes baking,
so she probably likes seeing and eating sweets.
Right!
It's her birthday,
so I'd like to let her eat something amazing.
How about this place?
It appears they take reservations,
and their menu looks pretty extensive.
That's it, Suna!
I'm making a reservation!
Is there anything else we can do?
What's left?
Aquariums,
planetariums,
the movies...
You had that one down, too.
That's about it, no?
A planetarium, huh?
In elementary school, we went to one.
When we went,
you got stuck in a hole they were trying to repair.
You managed to get out on your own,
but they thought you were
some underground monster.
You have a really good memory.
You're smart.
All right!
A planetarium, it is!
Yamato likes stars,
so this'll make her happy!
This is going to be good!
You're really into it, huh?
Yeah! It'll be great!
I never knew it was so fun to celebrate
the birthday of someone you care about.
That's good.
I'm happy for you.
Yeah, thanks!
They're all places I've been to with you.
Well, given that we've been friends for ten years...
He's right... We've been
friends a really long time.
What about her birthday present, by the way?
Do you have one?
I'd totally forgotten about that!
Of course you need presents for birthdays!
Normally, yeah.
Do you have money?
Nope!
Well, with how often you eat Korean BBQ...
Want me to lend you some?
How can I use someone else's money
to celebrate Yamato's birthday?
Maybe a part-time job, then?
That's it, Suna!
Anything goes, as long as
it has good hourly pay and
is OK hiring short-term,
high school students!!
I'll get a part-time job!
Let's take a look.
It's morning!
Zing!
10 AM: Meet in front of station
12 PM: Lunch
2 PM: Park if sunny, café if rain
3 PM:
He's done all the research.
Thanks, Suna!
I'm one lucky guy!
I'll make sure my day with Yamato is the best.
Morning
Afternoon
I'll go on ahead.
Are you heading somewhere again?
I have to stop by somewhere,
so I'll just go home after that and crash.
Okay.
Thanks!
Suna!
Are you okay?
Okay about what?
Something... I dunno.
Yeah, I'm okay.
Okay.
If he's fine, it's all good...
I see. So Sunakawa-kun
wasn't lonely, after all.
That's good
Let's celebrate your birthday just the two of us.
That's good        It sure is
Okay.
Oh, it's just one more week!
Is it okay that I feel so happy?
I'm happy, too.
So happy...
Oh!
I have to go to a job interview.
Huh? A job?
I hope you look forward to your birthday!
Huh?
But I really don't need anything.
I'm happy enough spending time with you.
I'm not lying, it's the truth!
I know!
Let me do this!
It's fun!
Yamato...
As of June 8th
Gouda Takeo
Thank you.
I'm one lucky guy.
I'd like for this to be short-term.
Well, you're a rare find,
so we'd love to have you longer.
Thanks!
Thanks! I'll do my best!
I'll do my best!
That's the spirit.
Suna!
I have a job!
Congrats.
Where?
Here!
Bro Café
Machos
Manager: Susie Honeyama
Will you be okay?
The menu's short, so I should
be able to memorize it!
That isn't what I mean, dude.
Well, whatever...
Come with Yamato next time!
You told Yamato-san that you're getting a job?
I thought you were keeping everything a surprise.
What is it?
No, it's fine. It's nothing.
Okay.
Can you help me choose her present?
Oh, sure.
I just remembered what you
used to pick as gifts.
What did I give you?
Bugs... And rocks.
How about this, Takeo?
What's that? A bowl?
Café au lait bowl and tea spoon
Last time, Yamato-san was talking about how
cute a café au lait bowl was, remember?
So cute!
We don't have any at home!
I'd like one to drink café au lait from!
That's right!
So this is a café au lait bowl.
I see
In your hand, it looks more like a teacup.
Suna's very observant of others.
He always keeps an eye out for me, too.
Suna, how about that for Yamato?
Wouldn't that look cute on her?
I'd like to get this for her.
Sure, why not?
I'd hate for it to sell out before I get paid.
I'll see if they can put it on hold for you.
Of course!
They said it's fine.
All right, I have to go.
Okay, thanks!
Bro Café
Machos
I hope you're looking forward to this, Yamato.
Welcome!
Wow, you're perfect!
Are you new?
Thanks!
Protein teas, right up!
Hey, which gym do you go to?
You have wonderful delts.
I'm one lucky guy...
I just have 'em naturally!
I'm home!
How are you doing, Mom?
I'm fine.
Welcome back
You ask the same questions as your dad.
I do?
I'm fine,
but I saw Makoto-kun at the hospital.
What?
I heard his father's been hospitalized.
You didn't know?
Oh, right.
He isn't the type to tell him...
Sunakawa
What's wrong?
Why don't you come in?
Where's your family?
Oh, Mom's gone overseas with Sis.
I can't reach them on their cells.
You're all by yourself?
Where's your dad?
Did your mom say something?
He collapsed the other day,
so he's kind of in the hospital.
That's not "kind of"!
He's going to need surgery.
But I've asked my uncle to come with me.
When is the surgery?
June 15th.
Um, June 15th...
Suna, people are born into this world.
And people are taken from this world.
What a coincidence, huh?
I'll come with you to the surgery, too!
What about Yamato-san's birthday?
I won't go!
I'll stay with you!
I'll explain what's going on to Yamato,
and she'll understand.
Don't tell Yamato-san about my dad.
She'll take it too seriously.
Yamato will understand!
Listen, Takeo...
I don't want to get in the way of my friend
spending his first girlfriend's birthday
with her.
Weren't you looking forward to it?
You aren't getting in the way of anything!
Takeo!
Why won't you get it?
Even if you scrap the birthday plan you've been
looking forward to, and come to the surgery,
it won't make me feel any better.
My dad's situation isn't anything new.
I've been kind of prepared for it.
So I'll be all right.
Suna's father
is a kind person who never
left much of an impression.
They aren't letting anyone see him.
He's always had heart problems.
He collapsed once before...
Maybe when you were in elementary school?
Back then, they weren't sure he'd make it.
So Mom never said anything to me,
even though she knew.
She's a real grown-up.
There are things I don't know about Suna,
even though I've known him more than ten years.
Even though I know his birthday
and what kind of underwear he wears,
there's still a lot I don't know.
A lot... But Suna...
There is a lot I do know, too.
Bro Café
Suna!
What's with that getup?
Are you headed to the hospital?
Oh, yeah.
Suna, I'm going to respect your wishes.
So you don't need to worry about me!
That does make me feel a bit better.
Suna, don't worry.
It's going to be okay.
Don't worry.
I'm home!
How are you feeling, Mom?
I'm fine.
Received Messages
From: Yamato Rinko
Subject: I'm hyped!
Takeo-kun, thank you for planning tomorrow!
I'm so excited, I can't sleep!
I'm too worked up!  Too happy!
Thanks, Takeo-kun!
I'm one lucky girl!
Compose Message
See you tomorrow, in front of the station, at 10 AM
Suna, I'm...
I'm going to spend a good birthday with Yamato!
I'm going to give it everything I've got.
My Friend and I
Next time: My Friend and I.