Hey! We need more over here.
Right away!
Where's that bonbori?
It's coming!
Thanks.
Ohana, are you done over there?
Um... yes.
Man, it's such a shame when you're getting so many reservations.
Yeah...
Oh! What are you going to write on your wishing plaque?
I haven't really thought about it.
What? You should get on that.
I heard it really works.
Makes dreams and ambitions come true.
Dreams...
Me?
I want to study abroad.
I want to learn about the hotel situation overseas.
And...
A goddess takes everyone's wishes to the sky
as thanks for lighting her up with bonbori...
When I came to Yunosagi, I felt like I wanted to shine.
Then the days flew by, and I came to like my work and Kissuiso.
But what's my dream...?
What's the matter?
Uh... pardon?
Almost forgot, Ohana!
Here!
With this many people, we have a lot to prepare for dinner,
so we don't want to overwork ourselves serving breakfast.
Yeah.
With that in mind, we'll have to make the breakfast a buffet.
What?
Something wrong?
Well... We have people saying
they like how they can take their time in their own—
Just live with it, okay?
We don't have enough staff in the kitchen.
Minko.
Cleaning after the guests check out will also be tough.
The girls also have school.
We'll stop assigning rooms, and I'll also help.
You took more reservations?
Madam Manager!
Didn't I tell you to stop?
Well, the other inns are doing
fine and they have more guests than we do.
You think you can run an inn if you
all overwork yourselves together?
I'm not saying we'll lower the quality of our service!
We're just finding new ways to make ends meet.
Food is still food in a buffet.
We'll still cook the way we used to.
The service won't go down either!
With no one in charge of one room, I'll oversee everything.
Fine. Do what you want.
Madam Manager!
However,
you will do as we've always done for the Bonbori Festival.
We're not backing down.
No.
The Kissuiso I Love
Hey.
Um... I brought some wishing plaques.
Here. You... write your wish and...
Maybe later.
Sorry.
Guys...
I'm sorry, Ohana.
We're too busy for that.
Nako!
Thanks, I'll have one.
I feel like it's not quite right.
I want the Kissuiso to stay open as much as everyone else does.
Minchi...
Stop.
Stop siding with the Madam Manager.
It's not like I'm on her side!
Maybe you don't care.
You have a place to go back to.
A place to go back to?
I don't have a home!
This is my home!
I don't care about the Bonbori Festival!
This is where my dream is.
You...
You made me happy when I thought you felt the same.
Minchi!
You're all good people.
All of you here are good people.
Nakochi...
What's with the luggage?
I thought I'd also sleep here for a while.
Can I?
Sure, I don't mind, but are you sure you're okay on the floor?
I can't get here in the morning
and everyone's working hard, so I also...
Working hard...
Yeah, maybe, but...
They're not festing it up... I don't think.
Huh?
Nothing.
Hey, if you're going to sleep there, sleep in my—
Nako, get to sleep.
Minichi.
Work starts at 4 tomorrow.
4?!
It's already past midnight.
Okay.
Nakochi's sleeping over, but we can't even talk.
Everything feels too tight...
I... don't really like it.
What are you doing?
You don't have time to be taking a walk.
You're helping too, right?
I'll give everyone a word in about you.
You'll just feel left out siding with the Madam Manager.
But it's not that I'm siding with anyone. I...
You don't want to restore the Kissuiso?
Just listen!
This isn't like you.
You usually butt in on everyone's business
and make the whole place fun.
I don't...
Yet you're...
Kissuiso didn't change. You did.
First, bring the guests to the main hall and identify their names.
Don't forget to call, too. Okay?
Okay!
O-Okay!
That's done.
Take this please.
Okay. Whoa.
Nako. More rice porridge.
Okay.
Wow, this dish is top notch.
You don't usually get this kind of food in a buffet.
Yeah.
The food's top notch and made with seasonal ingredients,
and people still love the food, but...
Yes?
Say, is breakfast only served as buffet now?
Yes, that's how it is.
I see.
I liked how we could relax at this inn.
Well, this is fun too.
Actually, can you leave some room in-between?
Okay.
Maybe a little more to the left.
What are these?
I'm making an art gallery of some local artists.
This will get us guests and profit.
Just you watch.
Kissuiso is going to change.
Ohana, you also- Huh?
Kissuiso is going to change...
But I wanted to show Ko
the Bonbori Festival and the Kissuiso I love...
I see... a friend?
I'm sorry.
We can't take any more reservations, right?
If this room will suffice.
This room?
You want to show him the Kissuiso, right?
Then he can stay here as a friend.
Madam Manager!
Is your health okay? Are you okay?
What?
Well... I've never seen you so nice.
He's an important friend, no?
Yes.
Thank you very much!
Tsurugi!
Hello, Minko?
I'm sorry, Tohru—
I got a glimpse of the princess sleeping.
Who's Tohru?
Um...
Hey, Minchi—
Don't talk to me.
You know what that is?
She's sulking.
Because you're siding with the Madam Manager.
Tsurugi likes you, Ohana.
That's hard to believe.
How's the soup stock?
Checking right now.
Minko, wash the vegetables!
Okay!
When you're done with that, get the duck ready.
I can still be a cook whereever I go. Tohru's right about that.
But... I want to stay here
because Tohru's here...
Mr. Ren's here...
Everyone's... here!
Balut!
There's no way we're serving something that eerie.
I'm sorry—
Hey, Mr. Ren!
What's wrong?
You tell me!
The bowls aren't out, and the guests are complaining.
It's not like I'm having an easy time having to change the soup.
Are you saying it's my fault?!
Hey Mr. Ren...
Oh, no! What's going on with you two?
Why don't you waitresses get the
bowls out or something before you make excuses?
We don't have time to be arguing!
Say that again?
This is the kitchen's problem! Not blame us!
We need to work together.
Your heart's like tofu!
I'm just sensitive! Okay?
With that face?!
I'm a pure, innocent, sensitive...
Shut up!
Don't you want to protect the inn?
It's a crucial time for us right now.
Please don't fight here!
Please...
Have a great trip.
Thanks.
Dear, say bye.
Bye-bye!
Something doesn't feel right.
I like the Kissuiso.
It makes me happy
when everyone's doing their best to make the guests happy.
But... it's not the same anymore.
Everyone's too focused on the Madam Manager.
Ohana, you know her real intentions, don't you?
Tell me!
I want to know!
She's the very person who founded the Kissuiso I love!
Nakochi...
Stuck with her dream, huh...
Yeah.
She just doesn't know.
Because she's a runner.
Some people can't have their own dream,
but they can follow someone else's dream
and make it their own.
Yunosagi Springs
Tomorrow's the real deal.
Yeah...
Did you already come up with a wish?
Oh, not yet.
And what happened to the Kissuiso's wishing plaques?
I gave them to you, right?
Well... they seem to be busy.
What?
Ohana, they're taking advantage of you.
That's not it.
Very well!
I will go get them for you!
Hey! Wait up, Yuina!
I will not!
Good evening!
Hey, Yuina!
Tomoe?!
During the festivals, we get people from all over.
Are you from Tokyo, Miss?
What makes you think so?
Well, you have that city grace.
Do I really?
That hurts!
Stop, Beanman! That really hurts!
How is it?
It's sprained.
How will we get by like this?
We'll ask the union for help.
Oh, that's not possible.
We also asked for help,
but no one can help since it's before the festival.
You're kidding...
The Madam Manager said that
we have to do everything the way we used to
for the Bonbori Festival.
That was part of the promise.
That's just impossible!
We'll have to beg her.
We can get by if we use the new way.
I'll do it!
No! You need to stay put!
I can't stay put!
I'm not going to lose to the Madam Manager!
You're going to lose... to the Madam Manager?
Was work a battle?
What are you...
It's just wrong!
Is it more important to win than
make the guests feel comfortable?
If we lose, the Kissuiso will close!
But—
Do you really understand that?!
Please just stop!
Nako...
I love the Kissuiso.
I really do!
But this isn't the Kissuiso.
Please bring back the Kissuiso I love!
Please!
I... finally found a place I could be me.
"I love the Kissuiso."
Everyone there felt the same way.
Yet somehow, their feelings slipped past each other.
Kissuiso... 'Tis a castle...
in a long lost dream.
Excuse me?
Oh, I was just speaking your thoughts.
I'll do it in your place.
Madam Manager!
I'll work as a waitress.
I should be able to fill in for Tomoe to an extent.
B-But...
Hey!
Mom?!
I came again!
Why?
I needed a change of scenery.
Staying for 2 nights. One adult.
Sis, we're full right now, and we don't have time for you.
Don't worry! I'll sleep in Ohana's room.
If you let me stay, I'll help out too.
You were yelling in that argument.
And why is no one at the front desk when you should be busy?
Mom, are you really going to help out?
No, you aren't!
Enishi?
This is our fight.
If you or the Madam Manager help—
What?!
Don't run on your emotions!
Don't you want to save the Kissuiso?
Takky...
Enishing...
And... it's the day of the festival.
Mom, can I have that?
Thank you for coming.
Yes, immediately.
Takky, the Moon Room needs—
You're busy?
Ask my sister?
But...
Young Master, the Moon Room?
What do they need?
The yukata's too small. They want size L.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Young Master.
I'm a waitress today.
You need to give the orders.
Madam Manager...
You have the wrong person.
I'm not the Madam Manager.
Okay, I'm counting on you, Sui.
Minko, how's the vinegar dish?
Just needs the final toppings.
Grill dish is done.
Okay.
Can I get the Wave Room next?
O-Okay.
Nako, I can take care of it.
But...
I can still clean with a sprained ankle.
Can you take care of the banquet hall?
Very well.
Good. Good. Good.
And stop.
You're all good.
I need to check the Crane Room next...
Madam Manager?
Madam Manager!
Don't worry, I'm fine.
I just felt a little dizzy.
Maybe you should rest a little—
In an inn business, the guests come first.
We worry about ourselves last.
But I enjoyed that kind of work.
Madam Manager...
Now, go back to your own job.
Okay.
I'm done over here.
Can you get the stuffing in?
Okay.
Is the Wisteria Room ready?
Right there.
Keep it up.
Mr. Ren, the tempura's ready!
I'm taking it to their room.
It felt so weird.
It's usually just us working here,
but Mom and the Madam Manager were helping.
Have a nice trip.
Okay, the Happiness Room?
I finally realized...
my dream.
Granny! Granny!
I'm exhausted!
Everyone's done with dinner.
Good work, everyone.
Thanks to all of you, we got through.
For now, let's—
Good, you've rested.
We don't have time to slack off.
Let's go, everyone.
Go where?
To the Bonbori Festival. Where else?
I love you! I love, love, love you!
If it's possible, I'd like to...
I really found it.
Dear...
Finale: To Bloom One Day