Morning.
Chiaki!
Why'd you ignore my text yesterday?!
Sorry, wasn't feeling it.
I mean, every day,
you're like, "What'cha doin'?"
Shut up!
Chiaki and I have been
dating for nearly a year.
We still haven't even kissed yet.
Point-Blank Relationship
What? You still haven't kissed, Kana?
W-Well, it's only been a year.
It's too early.
Isn't that a bit late?
Hasn't Chiaki-kun said anything?
Not really, he's like...
Man, that was a huge dump.
You poop tanker!
So what if I poop?! Everyone poops!
You're so immature!
Come to think of it,
it feels more like
we're siblings than dating.
Hey, Chiaki, we get along well, right?
Bang!
Augh! I've been shot!
Yeah, we're definitely in sync, at least.
Perfectly.
Hey, are you satisfied with this?
Our relationship, I mean.
You're not?
It's not that I'm not, but can't
we be closer? Skinship-wise?
Oh...
Ready to rumble?
N-No!
I meant relationship-type stuff!
You could have said so.
You're awful.
I was just a toy to you, wasn't I?
I'm not trying to be funny, here.
What about, like, kissing and stuff?
That's way too embarrassing.
We aren't even dating.
It's embarrassing for me, too,
but we're in a rel—
What?
Do you really want to waste
your time with me?
Don't you have a crush or something?
We are dating, right?
Huh?
Who is?
We are.
Wait a second, since when are we dating?!
I confessed to you last spring, remember?
Coming home from school?
H-Hey, I like you, Chiaki-kun.
I like you more, stupid.
Sorry, I thought that was a comedy bit.
I knew something wasn't right.
You wouldn't even try to hold hands.
But you were always, like, my best friend,
so maybe you were embarrassed.
I was okay with that, though,
since you were always right there.
Well, I guess we've always been close
but never touching.
What? Why are you crying?
Because, because...
I've been texting you nonstop
and smacking you like we're that close.
I'm so low.
Then let's hook up properly.
What, is this another bit?
No!
I've thought about being your boyfriend, too.
But I couldn't tell how you felt,
so I kept quiet.
I like you.
Let's date for real!
Really?
Really.
I'll text you like crazy.
Yeah, text me.
Can I smack you again?
Sure, smack me.
Okay.
So let's keep doing comedy bits, okay?
Hell no!
I confessed to my crush.
I'll Kill Senpai
And got rejected.
This sucks.
I'm going home to sleep.
Huh? Going home, Matsuura?
What about club?
Are you skipping? Hiuh?
Sabotage? Huh?
Skipping? Huh?
Katori-senpai, I'm not feeling well today.
Oh, really?
You had a sad look on your face.
I was sure you were heartbroken.
Huh?
I nailed it?
Sorry, should I not have asked?
No, I don't care.
But you worked up the courage, right?
That's awesome, don't you think?
Senpai...
You have an absolutely dazzling
look on your face right now.
Are you messing with me?
You are, aren't you?
Not at all.
I'm trying to cheer you up.
Are you angry?
I don't need you to cheer me up.
You're crying in here, though.
Sorry, my hand slipped.
Hit me all you want.
Huh?
But, it's really yourself
you want to hit, is it not?
You are messing with me.
Not at all.
Besides, you feel better
after hitting me, don't you?
Senpai was doing that on purpose?
Not that I feel grateful at all.
Let me know if you need anything.
No, I'm good.
Why do you even care so much?
I'm your senpai. You're my kouhai.
Understand?
Good, now you can make it to club.
Oh. Yeah...
Senpai's annoying, but he's
a nice guy at heart.
But he's annoying.
Excellent.
It gets lonely without our local idol.
So annoying.
Huh? What's up?
Let's go.
Nothing's up.
Don't look at me.
Sorry.
You haven't fallen for me, have you?
Sorry I'm such a hottie.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Yeah?
Am I badass? Huh?
My crush called me out.
Would you like to go for lunch sometime?
What? With me? Why?!
I want to thank you
for helping me the other day.
Am I imposing?
N-No, not really.
Thank goodness!
Okay, I'll see you on Sunday.
Why is such a cute girl
asking out an uggo like me?
Love Is Derpy
Did I get here too early?
I've secretly been in love
with this girl on my bus.
I never had the courage to talk to her.
But one day...
A groper!
M-Morning!
Wh-Where a coinkydink, Kurihara-san!
H-How's up?
I mean, wh-what's life?
I thought I totally creeped her out.
I never thought she'd want to thank me.
Wait, is she actually coming?
Isn't there no way she'd invite me?
That's it, it was all in my mind!
Yup, case closed.
Thanks for waiting.
Heungh!
Heungh?
What the heck is this?!
She's so cute!
Um, please stop staring at me.
N-No, I'm not staring at all!
I don't think you're cute or anything!
No! I did! I do think
you're cute, but your outfit!
That's it, your outfit's cute!
I mean, not just your outfit, but...
Yamane-san, was it?
What should we have?
It's on me.
Huh?!
What am I supposed to do, here?
I shouldn't go too pricey, but...
Maybe somewhere cheap, quick, and tasty?
Th-Then how about soba?
That sounds good!
There's a standing soba stall right there.
Soba     Udon
Come in.
May I choose?
S-Sure.
You don't have to hold back.
O-Okay.
Should we order fountain drinks?
I-It's fine, I'll go home
right after we're done.
Oh, of course.
No, it's not that I want to go home!
I'd love to be with you forever!
Wait, that was creepy, right?
D-Don't worry, I'll go home right away!
I'd actually noticed you
on the bus every morning.
What?
You give your seat up
for seniors all the time.
I-I have to do good when I can,
because, y'know, I'm a weirdo.
But when you helped me out...
Sorry to remind you about that awfulness!
I'm such a failure!
She invited me out, and I'm ruining it.
You're so funny, Yamane-san.
Oh, my face, right? I get that a lot.
Your face is great, too.
M-M-Maybe for the Heian Period,
but this is the 21st century.
Is she kidding?
Or maybe I just look like a dorky mascot.
Um...
Why?
Why the serious face?
Impossible!
Seriously?!
Are you serious?
No, no way this could happen to me!
She's deceiving you!
Don't get your hopes up
I've been getting ignored by girls for years.
Really?!
No way no way no way
Why?
Don't get your hopes up!
What if she's serious?
Why?
There's no way!
I'm not prepared for this
Really?
If it's okay with you...
You'll regret getting your hopes up!
Badger Badger Mushroom
Why does she look so serious?
Nothing to see here
Don't get your hopes up!
But what if she's serious?!
No, that's impossible!
Would you...
Wait, I'm not prepared!
Go out with me?!
Yes!
Fountain drink, please.
The person on cleanup duty went home.
This sucks.
Takano?
Sugawara-kun.
Sugawara-kun is in my class.
Cleanup Duty
Sometimes, we chat a little these days.
Cleaning up by yourself?
I'll help you.
But...
It's too much for one person.
I'll get a broom.
He's a good person.
Huh?
Cleanup duty, Suga-yan?
Practice is about to start.
Y-Yeah, I'll be right there!
Sure.
I don't want to keep you
from club practice, Sugawara-kun.
It's fine.
I just want to help.
Why is he so eager to help?
Maybe he's a clean freak?
Do you help with cleaning often?
No, not really, but, like, since you're...
Since I'm what?
Is it something he doesn't want to say?
Am I doing a crappy job of cleaning?
Sorry, I'll shut up and get to work.
Huh? Sure.
Did she figure out how I feel?
J-Just so you know,
I didn't mean that in a weird way!
Sorry if I made you uncomfortable.
No, sorry I didn't notice, either.
What should I do?
What? Do? About what?
Don't mind me.
You're helping me because
you noticed me, right?
I was actually interested in you.
I knew it.
Sorry, I never learned about this stuff.
I've never learned, either.
Like, what do you want to do, Takano?
I want to get better at it.
Better? Huh?
Like, so that I can clean up better.
I think you're pretty enough as you are.
Really?
What should I do, then?
Well, I wanted to tell you...
No, maybe I'm rushing things.
Take your time.
I'll be waiting.
Wait, am I going too slow?
Sorry, I was taking too long.
That's not true.
Sorry, I'm really hasty.
I'm just glad you know how I feel now.
I'll ask you how you feel next time—
Thanks.
I'll learn to clean quicker.
Huh?
It isn't a topic that's easy to bring up.
You sure are a good person.
Wait, what are we talking about?
About cleaning, right?
Huh?
Yeah, that's it!
Cleaning, right?!
Next episode: Romantic Comedy.
Romantic Comedy