Phil?
I'm playing hide-and-seek
with Naila and Eugene.
I see.
So...
What we need to investigate now is...
Outside.
We know most of what we need to
about the House.
The training is going well.
The tracking devices can be broken.
We just need...
...to get intel on the outside,
and if we can outmaneuver the adults here,
we can definitely clear the wall.
Next is checking out an escape route.
So this escape has three steps.
One, get over the wall and escape.
Two, get away from this farm safely.
Three, establish a way to survive outside
and become self-reliant.
Currently, we have hope
of accomplishing the first step.
Next is the second step.
We need to focus on the outside.
Evade the pursuers
and get away from the farm safely.
We need to examine and prepare for that.
First, we need information
about the area around the farm.
Oh, when I climbed up the tree,
I saw a forest beyond the wall.
Those are the things
we need to properly check.
We should look into it as soon as tomorrow.
Okay.
Hey, can I talk about another thing
having to do with when we get outside?
I have someone I want to introduce.
Sorry, Mom. I'm in a rush!
Mom, look!
I did it.
Amazing, right?
The person I want to introduce is...
this person.
Mr. William Minerva?
Yep.
Who's he?
I don't know. What I do know is that
he's the previous owner of that book.
But he could be someone who's on our side.
What do you mean?
This person has been conveying
a certain message through books.
And not just one book.
Through many of them!
This symbol is...
A bookplate.
A label that indicates the book's owner
before it came here.
And what's that certain message?
Look carefully.
They all look like the same owl.
No.
This circle...
Morse code!
Correct.
Run.
Doubt.
Danger.
Truth.
But with just this...
What about these?
Harvest.
Monster.
Farm.
This is a message from the outside to us,
hidden from the demons and the adults.
I think we can at least trust that.
Trust that?
Unlike her, I'm more suspicious.
This man named Minerva could be an ally to us.
But we don't know if he's dead or alive.
We shouldn't get our hopes up too much.
Why are you always like that?
William Minerva. This man is outside
and knows our farm exists.
And though indirectly, he's trying to help us.
Yes!
There was an ally on the outside.
And he might still be there.
If that's true, then there could be
a society of humans outside.
Exactly!
These kinds of messages
can only be found in Minerva's books.
I don't know when
these labels were attached,
but I at least know this one
was attached after the year 2015.
I see.
Is there anything else we could know?
Like something in common between
the contents or the type of books?
Not much.
The genres are varied.
The publishers and the years were—
But what about that thing?
Uh, which one was it?
I didn't understand the Morse code
on these two books.
For the content,
one is a typical adventure novel,
and a mythology book
that I didn't really understand.
There's no Morse code on this.
And the other one is...
Promise.
Promise?
Why is this here?
So it was true, what they said.
Mom was lying.
No one was sent to foster families.
But why...
Because if they were,
there's no way this would be here.
It would have been delivered to Conny.
It's not just Little Bunny.
They were all snatched away from them
by Mom when they left,
and they were all taken away by bad people.
Stop it.
I think these have a meaning.
Like how one book doesn't have the Morse code,
and there were others with ripped pages.
And the message of "promise."
So you think these two books are special?
Yeah. I feel like...
these will become some kind of
an important guide for us.
What's your reasoning?
My hunch!
Don't give me that look!
Who is Mom communicating with?
The base Ray was talking about?
Are they the bad people?
That's right, he said he had Mom under control,
but we're doomed if Sister finds out.
What did he mean by doomed?
If they find out, is Mom or Sister
going to do something to us?
What if Mom is much more dangerous,
and Conny and our siblings are already...
Stop it. Norman said he doesn't know
what happened to Conny.
No. They're just hiding it from us.
They probably have a reason and can't tell us.
I can't believe them like that.
Because they don't believe in us.
But I think it's worth looking into.
Mr. Minerva and the mystery of his books.
We're not just running away.
Let's find a way for us to survive in this world.
Yeah. Let's run away.
Let's live.
No matter what the world is like.
Hold on, Phil. I'll be there in a moment.
But I'm surprised.
It's expected from Ray
who reads books all the time, but...
For Emma to notice those bookplates...
I wasn't the one who noticed them.
Phil found them and told me.
Phil?
Yeah. He was reading a children’s book
and it was one of Mr. Minerva's.
It was a book that had Morse code in the story.
Can you get the plates?
Thanks.
Where are Don and Gilda?
They're not here either.
They can't be...
Mom!
Oh. What’s wrong, Eugene?
I found this on the floor.
Thank you.
I'm hungry.
Don. Gilda.
Thank goodness, I thought you'd...
Where were you?
So?
We went in to Mom's secret room.
How?
Don stole the key.
From Mom?
And, did Mom...
I don't think she noticed. We already
returned the key, too. So probably...
You did something really stupid.
What would you do if the room was equipped
with either a camera, a bug, or an alarm?
If Mom or Sister found out,
you two... no, all of us would be—
Tell us what would happen.
Would we get killed?
We found Conny's Little Bunny
in the secret room.
So much for your "I don't know"
and "let's go save them".
We can't even go save them, right?
Because Conny...
Conny and everyone else is...
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry!
So they're really...
I told you, Gilda.
They were lying after all.
What are you hiding? Tell us the whole truth.
Demons? A farm?
No. Just to be eaten...
And you're a spy? This whole time?
It was for our sake.
Then Ray, you knew what was going
to happen to Conny that day?
Emma and Norman, you both tried to trick us
and take us out into a world full of enemies?
You're kidding me!
Hey, Don!
Don.
Are we that much of a burden?
Are we that weak and useless to you
that you feel the need to protect us?
That time, when you asked us to help you,
I thought you were relying on us.
Was that a lie?
We're not as smart as you three.
We're not, but still...
...aren't we family?
Aren't we siblings?
I just want you to have a little faith in us!
Sorry, I'm acting a little weird right now.
I'm going to go cool off.
Don.
I was wrong.
That's not it.
I'm just taking it out on them.
I'm not frustrated because
they treated us like weaklings.
I made them lie.
I couldn't do anything
for Conny and the others.
I'm ignorant and powerless.
It's frustrating because I really am a weakling.
It's so frustrating!
I want to become stronger.
Yeah.
Don! Gilda!
Emma.
Sorry. I didn't understand.
I was prepared to be resented, but I didn't
have enough resolve to believe in you!
I'm also...
Sorry.
No, well, I'm also sorry
that I suddenly punched you.
Are you okay? You're not, huh?
I'll be okay.
I'm sorry, too, about acting on our own.
Yeah. Of course Ray would get mad.
So we're really...
Come on, Ray.
Geez, fine.
Even if the worst happens,
I'll take care of it somehow.
I'm also sorry for the other things I did.
I apologize.
Don. Gilda. There's no more lying,
so let me ask again.
If we mess up, we die.
The outside is, at worst, a world full of demons.
Even so, will you run away with us?
Of course we will!
I feel better now that we told them the truth.
Yeah.
One week until we carry out our plan.
The preparations are going well, too.
We just have to figure out
how to escape with everyone.
Hey, Norman, about that...
I tried to figure out on my own
how to escape with everyone.
Do you think it's reckless?
It is.
But with this plan,
we can catch Mom off guard.
Realistically, this is the only way
to escape with everyone.
Yeah.
Should we tell Ray?
No.
Do you think Ray
would really have everyone escape?
Of course he would.
Ray's been moving all this time
while thinking about us.
Always, for the both of us.
Both of us?
Oh. Don't worry.
I'll bring it up to Ray sometime soon.
Okay.
"All this to make sure
you two don't get killed."
I see. You're amazing, Ray.
I stole them, just like you wanted.
Detergent and herbicide.
What are you going to use these for?
They'll come in handy for our investigation.
By investigation, you mean we'll go past the fence
to climb the wall and look outside, right?
What about the tracking devices?
We just have to make sure
they don't check them.
We'll have both Mom and Sister
looking somewhere else,
and create a situation where they
won't look at their trackers.
But how?
I'll have Ray stall Mom.
I'm having him give her false information.
So you had a fight with that Norman?
We had a difference of opinion.
So what did you want to tell me?
Norman is trying to kill you.
If he wants to escape with everyone,
that's something he would think of.
And?
He's collecting items.
A hammer, detergent, herbicide,
or anything else that he thinks he can use.
Including that rope that's too short?
Yeah. I tried to stop him, you know.
I told him it's too risky and wrong.
And that's how you got that bruise.
Murder by poison.
Chemicals can be troublesome.
Yeah. You'd better not ship them out early.
I want them to live to the end,
until 12 years old.
In this House, without any discomforts.
So let's replace the chemicals
with something else.
Put fake stuff in the containers.
Do you know where it is?
- Yeah.
- Then let's deal with this tomorrow.
Is that all you have to report?
Yeah. Do you have something else
that's bothering you?
Not at all.
Oh, right.
I'm letting you know a little early.
I received a notification from the top
at yesterday's scheduled check-in.
The next shipment has been set.
There will be no regular shipment
for next month.
Then the next one will be in January.
My 12th birthday.
So the next shipment will finally be me, huh?
But even if we leave Ray to deal with Mom,
what about Sister?
Yeah, if she finds out,
we'll be shipped out immediately, right?
Don't worry, I have an idea.
Do you need something?
I saw it.
I was watching the whole thing!
Talking in the dining hall last night,
all of you!
The ones who know the secret
about this House
is Norman, Emma, Ray, Gilda, and Don.
The five of you.
So...
would you like to join forces?