Santa Claus is my Sweetheart
Weird.
What?
Youngest.
Usually she just hangs out, looking
bored and reading her books,
but today she looks...excited.
Yeah?
She must have gotten her hands on some
kind of incredible super book!
Pipe down.
I can't believe how detailed this is.
It was kind of expensive, but
it was worth every yen.
The official Gachi Rangers Guidebook!
He saw.
Crap, I was so close!
You wanna see?
O-Of course I do!
You...like them?
Yeah, man!
I'd give up FOOD if I had to
choose between the two!
I like them too.
Oh, I know.
N-No way...
There's actually another Gachi fan here...
I'm so happy...I wanna talk about them.
I dunno what's gotten into
Youngest-san but I like it!
So hey, lemme take a look-
What's your favorite part?
Huh?
You know, specifically?
"Part?" Dude...
The boobs, THE BOOBS!
I knew it, he only watches to ogle
Gachi Pink and the female boss!
All boys are like that!
Never mind.
Wh-Wha-
What else is there but boobs and butts?!
Don't insult me!
The scenes, the adventure, the different
ways they merge together,
the way you can FEEL the energy!
Every moment is a priceless work of art!
Porn...is art?
I've been such a fool...
Well I'm glad you understand now.
I do, I swear I do, so can I...
What's your favorite kind of move?
Move?
Mine's definitely the type where
they end it in one shot, POW!
Like the Gachi Lariat or the Gachi Sobat!
In...one...shot?
Like a sex move?
Don't you have one?
I do! I practice all the time!
Oh...I see...
Well, you can try it on me.
I-I can?!
Just don't hurt me.
My first time...playing Gachi Rangers!
Finally, I get to test the secret moves
I've practiced and practiced!
All right, here I come!
I'm putting my full power behind this one!
What're you doing?
It's time for class.
Oh yes, sensei's a fan too.
Ah...of course he is.
Why don't you try it on him?
Then you won't have to hold back.
But-
What's wrong?
You can't do it?
Super move!
Lightspeed One-Handed Panty Snatch!
The first time I get to do
this and it's on a DUDE...
Damn it all!
Mitsudomoe!
Yabecchi's Room
Now for the first edition
of "Yabecchi's Room!"
Our first guest is the eldest of the
Marui triplets, Marui Mitsuba-san!
Today's guest - Marui Mitsuba-san
What interesting topics will
we talk about today?
Hey, what's with this overlay?
"-san"? Forget that!
I demand you put "-sama"!!
And another thing, what's the idea of calling
me over and only having Oolong tea?
You dumb virgin!
V...
Get me something to go with this,
like cake! Or cream puffs!
Look at all that, why didn't you have this
out in the first place, you dunce!
Om nom nom
Umm...
Umm, Mitsuba-chan...
Om nom nom!
Om nom nom
Mitsuba-chan, we're supposed-
Why did we do this?! I quit!
Good idea.
What was the point of all this?!
Yabecchi's Room - Fin
Mitsudomoe.
December 24th
Goodnight!
It's FIVE.
Santa comes tonight!
Sixth grade and she still believes
in Santa...I mean really.
There's your Santa.
Your fever's not going down...
What a time to be sick...
You can't look!
To Santa
Here's my letter!
Futaba wants Santa to come...
That's right...
I got something nice for you, Hitoha...
That...that bag...
What is it? A Christmas present?
It's all...up to you...
Gulp.
She's huge.
Now that I think about it, I only have
to put the present on the bed...
Why did I change?
Boobie Pillow
Boobies...boobies...
Who's there?!
Oh no, I set off her boobie-sense!
Santa? Is that you, Santa?
Are you the real Santa?
I thought you'd feel different...
You're...a boy.
Are you really Santa?
I can't see.
Well are you?
Lemme see your face!
Are you handsome? Really handsome?
Lemme see, lemme see!
What is she doing?
Ah well...
Let me see! It's no big deal!
Freeze!
That's a fake! I'm the real Santa!
What're you doing, Micchan?
I said I'm the real-
Where'd you get the costume?
Hey, wait!
Don't bother him, Santa's very busy!
I just wanna see his face!
Hey!
Give it up!
Santa...
I understand...you hide your
face because it's so ugly...
Ugly-
But you're Santa, Santa!
I love you!
Good enough.
Don't look at me!
New Years
I-Is this...
This year's new pattern?
Yup! I had to look all day for those!
How adorable!
My Chinese zodiac collection
is finally complete!
Awesome!
Who cares?
It's an incredible feat!
Incredible!
Now let's get these...
Hey!
I wanna see how they feel-
I haven't even worn them yet!
And how are you gonna feel them if
you put them on over your shorts?
Fine, I'll take off my shorts first!
That's even worse!
Let go!
Just a little, just a little!
So peaceful...
It's not gonna hurt anything!
I said no!
My panties...
I'm disowning you, you...mirror-mochi!
Mirror-mochi?
An insult with an unknown meaning...
I never should've shown her.
There they are! Way up there!
Freeze!
I should've expected this
from panty-freak Satou!
What'd you do, pick up the
scent of new underwear?
Are you nuts?! I'm trying
to get my kite out of there!
Huh? Oh...
What's going on, Satou?
Check it out, panties!
Yahoo!
God's answered my prayers
for the new year!
Hold it, hold it!
Hmm? Wait, are they YOURS?
Uh...they're not, but...
Then what do you care?
Well, umm...
Wait, I'll get them!
I feel like climbing a tree!
Very well. You go get them.
I'm surprised you let her go.
If I'm gonna see panties,
I'd rather they be on a girl.
Man...
Almost got it...
Gotcha!
Bah, I don't want these.
Who wants to keep that silly kids stuff?
Shut up!
So they are hers.
Panties!
My panties!
This year, I want something
GOOD to happen to me.
Mitsudomoe.
Pheasant, Monkey, Dog
Momotaro
Depending on how you arrange Micchan's
panties, they can be the Chinese zodiac,
Momotaro, or Saiyuki!
Pig, Monkey, Kappa
Saiyuki
A kappa...she's even got
mythical creatures.
Who cares? And stop stretching them out!
Do you have the tsuchinoko?
Of course not, that's lame.
I see.
Snake, Dragon
Whoooooah...
Mitsudomoeeee.
@#*$!%@(&^#!?!
&@*%(@@$!@!!
Third School Period, A Sunday
Shin-chan, Chiba!
What're you doing by the pool
in this freezing weather?
Looks like we got a pain in
the butt on our hands.
Futaba, where're you-?
She changed that fast?!
Whee!
Wait-!
It's frozen solid.
We're not doing a polar bear swim meet?
We're skating, stupid.
Nowadays all the skating rinks are too
crowded for us to skate properly.
This is our secret spot.
This is fun enough for me!
Skating? How childish.
Don't tell the rest of the class,
this is our secret spot!
Oooooh, what should I do?
You squeal and I'll tell everyone you
still wear kindergartener panties!
I'll kill you you bastard!
And how do you even know that?!
Everyone's already seen
them a million times...
I've always thought that it was your fault
for continuing to wear them
after everyone found out.
Exactly! Well put, Youngest-san.
All right, I'm gonna show you
two clowns who's boss!
Oh yeah?
How did I get involved?
The game is ice bowling.
If I win, you have to worship
me and call me...
"Mitsuba-sama" for the rest
of your miserable lives!
That's the same thing you always say.
Never in a million years...fine, if I win
you have to show me your pant-
Wait, we've already seen her panties...what
should we bet?
And that's the same thing YOU always say.
I know, show me your boo-
No point in demanding something
that doesn't exist.
That is correct.
All right, 500 yen.
How inane.
What're we using for a bowling ball?
This!
Ka-pow!
Holy crap!
Futaba you moron, you left two!
This is nuts.
Whee!
Twirly twirly!
Four and a half spins, nice.
Your turn.
After you.
M-Me?!
Come on Shin-chan, kick me!
Come on come on!
Go!
Sorry...
That sucked!
I can't! I actually have a conscience!
How could you possibly feel
any sympathy for FUTABA?
You little...
That didn't count!
Boot her good, Satou!
Forget it, I'm not calling her Mitsuba-sama
for the rest of my life!
Shin-chan!
I'll be fine, kick me as hard as you can!
Go! Get her, Satou!
Kick me, come on!
Whatsamatter, can't do it?
What's wrong with you, Satou?!
Kick me, kick me hard Shin-chan!
Of course, you're the panty-pervert Satou,
you won't touch a REAL girl!
Damn it!
You know Satou's Kamo Elementary's
ace striker, right?
Uh oh, I forgot to reset the pins!
Wh...Wheeeeee!
F-Futaba!
Why did you have to be an ace striker!
You idiot! You murderer!
What'd you say?!
Wheeee, this is great!
She's alive.
The Next Day
Shin-chan, you gotta nail me
in the butt again sometime!
It felt great!
I-
I think I'm sick...
Oh no, Micchan!
Quick, take your panties off!
Wh-Why? What're you holding?!
Episode 10
We're gonna be *******
Just stay still...
N-N-Noooooooooo!