In a pig's ass!
I was wrong about you, traitor!
Richie, wait!
Listen to me!
Don't touch me! I don't
want to listen to you!
I don't need you anymore.
What should I do?
I forget what I was like before I met you
The wind caresses my cheek
♪Lullaby of Birdland♪
Kick my heels going down the slope
As my worthless shadow grows
It's like an endless summer vacation
Feels like sneakin' into the swimming pool
Hey, let's swim with our clothes on, jump in!!
A shocking seductive spiral
This beat that pierces my heart is strange
(It flares up, then vanishes)
Every miserable day is swell,
dress it up
A high-speed swing surrounds us
(What's this dance called? I can't stop)
Don't you go, it's twined around my ears
and won't leave me ever again
This melody...
...is like love
My feet feel heavy.
It's just like the first
time I climbed this slope...
Kaoru-san...
Would you like to have this onigiri?
Why? I'm fine.
I'm already stuffed.
Just eating half a thing of bread
isn't enough to give you energy.
Then I'll have just one...
This is good. What's in it?
Let's see... Clams boiled in soy sauce...
I shouldn't have said
that! I'm such an idiot!
Me and my big mouth!
Say, Ri-chan, I can't help but notice
that you're on really good
terms with Nishimi-san lately!
Tell me the truth, are you two going steady?
N-No!
Look at her, she's blushing!
You don't have to hide it from us!
We're in your corner!
But we're not...
U-Um...
Honestly... we're not dating.
Mukae-san and I... are just friends.
So... please don't get the wrong idea.
Crap. What did I butt in for...?
This is a surprise...
Nishimi-san, you hardly ever talk and
I had you pegged as unapproachable.
For a second there, I could've sworn you
were going to blow your stack at us.
M-Me too...
Hey, tell us something. What's the
trick to getting good scores on tests?
Yeah, I wanted to ask the same thing.
Oh, I don't...
Oh, we've put him on the spot...
Huh? What do you know? I
don't feel sick at all...
Hey, Richie...
Don't ignore me! Would you just
listen to me, you blockhead?!
Wow, what a pad, Yamaoka-kun!
And set apart from your house...
This is where we're gonna
practice every day from now on!
Huh? Kawabuchi-kun, you look kind of glum.
Don't tell me you're having second thoughts?
Don't be stupid. Once I decide I'm
gonna do somethin', I see it through.
That's the way to be.
We better hurry up an' decide what songs
we're gonna do. What's it gonna be?
Well, I wanna get the Spiders in there.
And the Ventures, of course. And then...
Hey, what about the Beatles?! What's
with all the different genres?
I think the girls will dig
it more if we play a variety.
That isn't what you said before!
Ryunosuke...
We just got a roll cake. Why don't
you share it with your friends?
Mama! Don't bug us!
We'd love to have some roll cake, Ma'am.
Let's discuss this over a
snack, okay, Ryunosuke-kun?
Kawabuchi-kun, aren't you coming?
Nah. I'm gonna stay here an'
practice a little by myself.
Oh...
Pops...
What are you doin' wearin' a
tie on a hot day like today?
Oh... I'm in mourning.
For who?
John Coltrane.
C-Coltrane died?!
You didn't know? Well, I
guess it's only natural
that a rock and roller
wouldn't get word of it...
Please don't bust my chops about that, Pops.
That aside, have a look in the shop.
There's a beauty girl in there
I've seen around before.
Y-Yurika-san...?
Oh my. I haven't seen you
in a while, Sentaro-kun...
I heard that you're going to be in
a rock band for the school festival.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yurika-san... Chet Baker...
If you're interested, wanna hear it?
Sentaro-kun... I...
Please... don't say anythin'.
I can't...
Because... I...
W-Who's down there?!
Oh, sorry. Didn't mean to interrupt, Sen-boy.
Brother... Jun...?
Don't pay no attention to me.
Go on with what you were doing.
Dammit! I forgot to tell him about Junichi!
Yurika-san!
Hey, Sen-boy. Your woman forgot something.
Sen!
That packed quite a wallop...
What are you lookin' at me like that for?
You're not satisfied with one punch?
Wait, Sen. Junichi has had
kind of a breakdown...
Brother Jun...?
What's wrong?
Tell me, what happened? Sentaro...
Sentaro, wait!
Okay, everyone...
I'd like to decide on the members
of the committee for the festival.
I'm open to volunteers or nominations...
Okay! Then I nominate
Nishimi-san and Mukae-san!
I'm sure those two would take
responsibility and do a good job!
I think that's a good idea, too!
No objections here!
East High School Festival
Talent Show Sign-Up Reception
Oh, the brass band...
Could you write down the
representatives' names and program?
Um, could I have an application form?
Here you are.
You're good to go!
I'm sorry, Kaoru-san.
The new term's just begun and you've
been saddled with this busy job.
Actually... since I was always
transferring from school to school,
I never had the chance to take
on a responsibility like this.
It's more fun than I thought.
Kaoru-san, have you talked
to Sentaro recently?
No.
Then... you wouldn't know about it.
The other day at the shop,
Sentaro punched Brother Jun.
I didn't see it myself, and I
don't know what it was about...
...but I heard Yurika-san
was at the shop that day.
Could you two bring the completed
applications to the student council office?
Sure. I'll do it.
Kaoru-san, stay here at the reception desk.
Okay.
Oh, Ri'ko, good timing.
You're on the committee, right?
Do me a favor an' copy this info
onto the application, would ya?
Forget it! The reception desk
is in the materials room.
Go over there and fill out the form yourself.
I can't accept a scrap of paper.
Fill out a form.
Did he really hit Brother Jun?
Is he taking it all on himself
and suffering in silence?
Hey...
That band name... In katakana
it should be spelled
with a "Ji", not a "Za", for "The Olympus".
"Za" is fine.
No, it's not.
No, that isn't what I want to say!
Se...
Excuse me! Is there still time to sign up?
Yes.
Whew! Good!
"Za" Olympus
The Olympus
Somewhere in my heart, there was
still a little hurt and regret...
As the festival drew closer, I became
busier with my committee duties,
and before I knew it, the distance
between me and him had grown.
I even looked back fondly
on that silly conversation.
but they seemed so long ago.
18th School Festival
And at last, the day of
the festival arrived...
The Olympus is next!
I'm gonna go to the front!
I can't wait!
Are you ready, ladies?
1-2-3-4!
Look at him with that smile on his face
Which of the girls now is he gonna chase
Kaoru-san...
After this festival is over, you two
will be back jamming at my place, right?
Um... You're not going to watch from inside?
Things are... awkward between
me and Sentaro-kun right now.
It's my fault... I gave in to loneliness...
and betrayed him in the worst way.
What the...?
You're on the committee, right? Follow me!
What happened?
There's suddenly no sound
coming from the amps!
No good...
The main electrical system isn't down.
Sorry, but could you help look
for the cause? We'll split up.
Boy, what a bummer, huh?
Hey, second-year!
You can't do anythin' without
electricity, so quit actin' big!
I bet you just wanted to show off
your fancy shmancy electric guitars!
Rub your money in our faces!
Why don't you get off the stage?!
Th-That's not what...
Sorry to burst your bubble,
but him an' I are poor and
the instruments are borrowed.
He may be a flashy guy,
but he's got a real goal,
so I'll ask you upperclassmen
to stop interruptin' just
to amuse yourselves.
Kawabuchi-kun... You're actually a nice guy.
I'm seeing you in a new light.
"Actually", huh? I'm always nice!
Ow! Y-Yes, of course, of course!
B-But I really am surprised. I never
thought you would join the band...
Yeah. I was gonna refuse at first.
But I changed my mind after Matsuoka told me
he wanted to become a star so he could
support his parents and brothers.
I know how it feels to desperately
wanna be useful to your family.
U-Um... Kawabuchi-kun, would you
consider staying with the band?
Nah. This was a one-shot deal for me.
Jazz is more up my alley.
Besides... I'm keeping my
important partner waiting.
They can't fix it, huh?
Guess I'll go...
No, don't leave!
Wait! Wait!
Please!
Don't panic. I'll keep them
occupied for a little while.
You be ready to go on as
soon as the problem's fixed.
What's he doing all of a sudden?
He's wearing an armband, so
he must be on the committee...
This song...
Can we get it all back?
Hey, what's goin' on?!
Kawabuchi-kun...
But... it sounds totally
different than it did then...
It's like two princes arguing
good-naturedly as they come back home...
Richie!
What the heck?!
They're running away?!
Cool...
My body feels light...
It's as if I've been born again...
I feel... like I've got wings on my feet...
I waited for you on that slope
For our after school promise
There was a 'goodbye' blurred far away
I was so weak, so awkward, and so fragile back then
But you gave me a small pair of wings
In the twilight hour of the sky,
I'm searching for a gleam of light
If only I could have said that I love you…
The note that I wrote in the corner of my textbook
has never been delivered to this day