A battle was held in
Biscotti territory
to welcome the Hero.
Naturally, Sink was Biscotti's Hero,
Nanami was Galette's,
and a new Hero was born
for Pastillage in Rebecca,
making things even more
lively than ever.
We're also preparing
for the next battle
by resting and practicing, but...
The meetings between the
three countries leaders was
concluded successfully,
and the people from
Pastillage and Galette
are all returning to their
respective countries.
Bye then!
See you at the next battle.
Yeah!
Rebecca-dono and Couverte-sama
have gone to Pastillage.
You guys don't have to make
a big deal out of this.
You'll be seeing each other
again before you know it!
But there are so many things
I want to talk to her about.
Yeah. We just became friends.
Right?
As for Sink and Eclair, and then Noir...
they will join up with me
for our summer training
camp near Fuugetsu Lodge!
Hey!
Biscotti Summer Camp!
Everyone's going to be at
the next war, too. Right?
Yes. All three countries will be
coming together for one big event.
Galette, Biscotti, and Pastillage.
It'll be a huge gathering with songs
and events for the general populace!
Wow, that sounds amazing,
like so much fun!
That's right!
The citizens will have a blast,
the country will make a profit,
and the fighters will have a battlefield!
It's not an easy operation,
but it's totally worth it!
I see.
Can I help, too?
You sure can!
I think I'll have my hero,
Rebecca, go against
Millihi-nee by singing on-stage.
That was a joke.
You can see Pastillage, now.
Esnart is a city of refinement and art,
erected right on the border of Biscotti.
There's our castle, Eschenbach!
Wow, it's fantastic! Beautiful!
Hero!
Yes, hello guys!
Nanami-sama!
You're very popular, Nanami-chan.
She is a Hero, after all.
It would be bad for us
if she wasn't popular.
Leo-sama looks happy, too, now
that she has a dependable partner.
Milady, will you take your lunch soon?
Oh, is it that time already?
Thank you for this meal.
Yes.
I can't help but feel sorry
for Yuki-chan and the Hero
for having to set up an
outdoor training camp
in this kind of heat.
Children love to play out in nature.
That's true.
Dear me!
What is this ringing I keep hearing?
That was a present from the Hero.
In their home world, such a
thing is called a "wind chime".
Time's up.
Too bad.
I guess it's a draw.
Wow, you're really good, Yuki.
I couldn't get a single attack in.
Actually, you're a lot stronger
than you were before.
You think those two are still at it?
Yeah, probably.
Wow, this is incredible.
Looks like they clashed hard again.
Eclair... are you losing?
No, I'd say I'm ahead.
I won't stop until I'm ahead.
Fine then, we can say I lost.
Let's just end this already!
Finally... victory.
Your dislike for losing and your
perseverance are peerless.
It's the spirit of Galette.
Eclair, are you all right?
This is why I don't like fighting her.
Well, it looks like everyone's
worked up a fine sweat,
so let's go change and then
move on to the water exercises!
Okay!
First one in!
That was quick.
Guys always change quickly.
Let's change, too.
Playing in the river,
playing in the river...
It's supposed to be training.
We'll be practicing swimming
and lifeguarding skills.
We're all pretty tired
from our training before,
so we can just enjoy a little
rest before we resume.
If you say so, Yuki.
Noir, is something wrong?
I won't lose to you.
One of these days...
Stop fooling around and get changed!
You either, Eclair!
You might be leading now,
but don't get too full of yourself!
Don't touch them!
Don't squeeze them either!
You've gotten bigger.
Knock... it... off!
Oh, no!
Noir, are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm sorry, Sink.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine... I'm...
Just stay right there, Sink.
I'm going to get my bathing suit on.
P-Please do...
I'll do that!
All right, let's try that again.
Everybody's ready!
For the next 15 minutes,
you are free to rest
and do what you like.
After that, we'll move on
to lifeguard training.
Okay!
Sink, I'm sorry about before.
Oh, I'm sorry, too.
By the way, how come you're here alone?
Well, I'm the only one in Genoise
who didn't take their vacation,
but I actually wanted to learn
a bunch of things about
monsters and cursed swords
from Yuki and Lady d'Arquien.
Monsters?
In Galette, they don't have a team
of counter-monster specialists
like our Onmitsu Squad.
So Leo-sama and Gau-sama
both suggested that I
try to put one together.
Her ladyship and I have
been asked to cooperate.
I see.
It would be terrible if another
monster like that appeared again.
Oh, but if you're going to do that,
what about Genoise?
I'll continue that side
as well, of course.
I'm Genoise's center, and
Gau-sama's personal guard.
I see. That's good.
For Gaul, of course,
but also because I want
to play with you guys
and fight against you, too.
Thanks, Sink.
Jau and Vert will be happy about that.
Oh yeah, would you like a drink?
I'll get some.
Yes, thank you.
Hero, I'm telling you this
just as a precaution:
you shouldn't get so close to
girls from another country.
Huh? Is something wrong?
Not really wrong,
it's just that you're
too relaxed around girls your age,
and your sense of space is all weird...
I'm not really sure how to put it...
If you have time to pet a
girl from another country,
pet me instead, you insensitive Hero.
Something like that?
Noir, you stupid cat!
Bright Power Release!
Whoa, Eclair. A new skill!
A blade made from bright
power, the Bright Ice Blade!
Don't you think that having
someone really be unconscious
will be beneficial for the
lifeguard exercises?
Great suggestion.
It's so nice of you to
want to be unconscious.
Noir, you, too?!
Cool!
Bright Power Gear, Seven Tails!
In a physical battle, you
have the upper hand,
but when it comes to controlling
bright power or emblem arts...
I'm better!
Bright Ice Blade!
Light Fang Vortex!
Seven Tails: Squeeze!
Um, I guess we should
start the lifeguard exercises.
Then, let's rescue the
unconscious people first.
I really wonder why these
two always clash so hard.
They're the same age,
both personal bodyguards,
both best friends with Rico...
they have a lot in common.
Well, they're simply great rivals.
Rivals, huh?
I suppose your rival
here is Prince Gaul.
Yeah...
I want to play with Gaul, too.
I guess he's playing with
Nanami-dono right about now?
Yeah, you might not think so,
but Gaul's actually quite shy with girls.
Gaul! Hey, Gaul!
Gah, you're so persistent!
So why won't you let me pet you?!
You're asking why?!
I won't let people just
touch me in public!
Besides, I'm actually not that
comfortable with having people touch me.
But you're so close with
Genoise and Leo-sama.
My sister is my sister,
and those three stooges
are basically family.
Aww. Well, I'm not into forcibly
touching those who don't like it...
All right, I won't touch you,
so will you come down?
Well, it's not like I really
hate it that much,
but you and I are prince and hero.
Let's try to stick to proper
decorum and moderation.
Gaul, you're so serious.
All right, but is it okay
if we become friends
as long as we observe that
moderation and decorum?
That sounds great.
Let's do this, cool as we are.
Roger that.
Oh, Nanami, Gaul.
Leo-sama!
Sister.
I'm going to have a bit
of time after this.
Nanami, could you come to my quarters?
I have a favor to ask.
Sure!
Mmmm, Nanami, your
technique is quite good!
How about this?
Oh, that's good, that's good!
Violet, is it okay that
our ruler is like this?
Yes, as long as Leo-sama
is happy, it's okay.
What do you think, Rebecca?
This is Pastillage's Crystal
Magic research mecca!
This is the main hall of the
Esnart Crystal Magic Research Institute!
Everybody, it's me, Couverte!
Did you watch Hero Rebecca's
success on the broadcast?
Did you watch me, too?
I want Rebecca to really fall
in love with Pastillage and us
until the next war!
I want you all to love
our Hero Rebecca, too!
Will you love Rebecca as
the Hero of Pastillage?!
Thank you!
I will do my best as your
Hero for all of Pastillage!
Tomorrow morning, we're going
to wrap up our training.
In the afternoon, her ladyship
will give us sword lessons.
Sounds like a full course.
We should go to bed soon,
so that we can start training
while it's still cool.
Yeah.
So, good night, everybody.
Wait, we're not doing a
"say who you're in love with"
contest before bed?
No, go to bed!
Oh, for me that's her ladyship,
the princess, Rico, and...
No, stop it!
I don't think that's how you do it...
Go to bed, I'm tired!
Eclair...
You woke up, too?
I woke up because Yuki was choking me.
She has that hugging habit...
Happened to me a lot when we were little.
Can I sit next to you?
You were sleeping next to me.
It's so quiet.
You think so?
The sound of the water and the insects...
there's plenty of noise.
Well, it's been really lively
ever since I got back here,
so this is quiet enough.
Everybody's just happy that you're back.
Whenever a letter arrived from you,
Rico nearly flipped out.
The princess was always waiting
for you to come back, too.
And you?
I'm not...
I'm happy to see you again.
I mean the reason that my
summoning was possible again
is because you
accepted my wristband
and have worn it ever since.
It's not like I'm the only one
who accepted an item of promise.
I haven't had a chance
since I got back to say it properly:
I'm glad I got to see you again...
and I hope that we can
work together as a team
again this summer.
I remembered!
Hero, come here for a second!
Here?
You've pet me before.
I just remembered that
I didn't pet you back then.
Um...
I am obligated to return the favor.
Let me pet you.
Roger that.
Uh, so what's going on here?
Uh,
Eclair and Sink were talking
and exchanging friendly cuddles,
and Sink ended up on her lap.
Because of their exhaustion from the
afternoon, they passed out like that.
I see.
Eclair...
This is not what it
looks like! Not at all!
It's not what you think!
Don't worry, we know.
It's totally fine that you
guys get along. Really.
No! It's not like that at all!
It's okay, we understand.
Eclair, you're annoying.
And then...
We have just returned!
Thank you for having us.
Show me the results
of your training camp
once you've rested a bit.
Okay!
The training camp at the river
ended without any problems.
So this is it.
You just copy the skill I spent
blood, sweat, and tears to learn?!
No,
your skill is also based on Lady
d'Arquien's Lupine God Void Fang, right?
Since the school's the same,
it's natural that they look alike!
But, still!
Really, you two, excellent work.
I think I can soon entrust you with
our monster sealing techniques.
Thank you!
And of course, you, as well, Noir.
Thus, this fun and hot summer
moment came to a close.
Idiot, idiot, idiot!
Why didn't you wake up?!
Maybe it was just comfortable.
Galette Sword Style Record!
Eclair, you should hold back a little.
Tune in again, next time.