Victory
Ten.
Nine.
Korai House
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Fire!
Deploy the defense shield!
Take this!
Where is she?
Where the hell is she?
Thirty minutes until the operation's over.
Make it happen, you guys...
Punch Line
Hey, you!
What do you think you're
doing to our Korai House?!
Shit, where is she?
Where are you even looking?
There she is!
Squeeze of Death: Takompressor!
That takes care of the Ws, but...
Damn, I guess this is it.
Huh? Is it over?
So you're here, Teraoka?
Still, I'm not giving up.
Never!
Meika!
I guess that just about does it.
Meika, did you see me take them out?
Hey, Meika.
Can't you hear me?
Meika?
Meika!
Meika! Meika!
Never would've thought she was a robot.
That explains her superhuman hacking skills.
Guriko! You...
I destroyed the robot.
Now there's nothing left to
stop the asteroid from falling.
Give it up and become a W.
Guriko!
Colonel, our troops have been wiped out.
Pine!
M-Meika...
Tell me what to do, like always.
No...
This can't be happening...
Narugino,
you were born to become a hero.
That's your destiny.
You can't get away from it.
It's okay, Ito-chan.
I'm a hero.
So I'll never give up.
Stop, you two!
Chiyoko!
Pine!
Sorry, Chiyoko.
I don't want you getting in my way.
Meika...
Guriko...
What happened to you?
You and Chiyoko would never understand...
The despair I've felt...
The loneliness of having to give up
everything, and just accept it!
I won't let the sadness repeat itself...
And to that end, I have to kill them all!
I've finally found you!
What are you doing?!
Now, hand over that cub!
Are you...
Chiyoko...
No, don't!
I don't know how you know about me,
but I'm sending you to Hell.
You're the one going to Hell!
Wh-What is this?!
The sacred sake of God!
Auxiliary Power Activated
Ito, I need you to do something.
Meika?
We don't have time.
Listen to me.
There's one more...
Just one more to launch.
So help sit me up there.
Guri-chan, you...
Rin, Pyou, Tou, Sha, Kai, Chin, Retsu, Zai, Zen!
There.
Guri-chan, you...
Evil spirits, begone!
You idiot!
To all members of Justice Punch...
The mission was a success.
I repeat:
To all members of Justice Punch,
the mission was a success!
Chiyoko!
You idiot, what have you done?!
Chiyoko...
Hey, Pine, when summer comes,
let's go catch stag beetles.
Giant stag beetles, the really big ones.
And we'll play tag in the fields,
and slide down the hill on cardboard sleds.
We'll make crowns out of Dutch clovers
and pick watermelons in the fields.
Okay? Let's do it again, all three of us.
Yeah, let's do it.
Promise me.
I promise.
Hey!
Chiyoko!
Please, wake up...
Open your eyes!
This isn't the future I wanted!
There's no point in saving
the world if you aren't in it!
Looks like she isn't gone yet.
You!
You're still such a simpleton.
What?!
We can't do what happened at the dam
unless all three of us are Uberfied.
Hey, why were you fighting earlier?
Guri-chan said she was going
to give you some weird thing.
Some weird thing?
A wedding ring?
W-Wedding?!
N-No, no! What are you talking about?
All I said was that it's a promise ring.
Huh? Three?
Yeah.
I made three.
Chiyoko,
Pine,
and me.
Okay, let's make a promise.
The three of us will always
be friends, no matter what.
Of course I promise!
Yeah, me too.
Well, we should head back
before the sun goes down.
Yeah!
Well, we should go back, too.
Back to the bodies we used to have.
Sorry, Guriko, but I can't do that.
I can't forgive you.
So...
You're going to live.
Live, and atone for your sins.
Wait! No!
Pine!
Chiyoko.
I'm giving this body back to you.
No!
You can't!
I promised.
I promised, didn't I?
That I'd protect you.
But...
You can't, Pine!
Please,
don't!
49 Days Later...
Three, four...
General liberal!
Deflation spiral!
Natural mineral!
Come on!
Now, come, Yuta's spirit!
There's something I have to say first.
Narugino!
Can't you do something about that outfit?
But I'm...
a girl.
I know, but...
So, the Yuta that's in Rabura's body now is the
Yuta that was disembodied
this whole time, right?
Yeah.
It's the me that had my body stolen
by the future me at the river
on December 21st last year.
You're so confusing.
But are you really leaving now?
Yeah.
It's going to get lonely.
There are things I have to do.
I have to go back 25 years
and possess 5-year-old Rabura.
And you're going to fax Meika's
schematics and instructions
for the future to the Reizoukou.
And then what?
And then I'm going to go back
to December 21st of last year
and do the same thing.
I'm going to the riverside to
possess my unconscious body.
You don't have to think too deeply about it.
You guys just go on making a bright future.
Meanwhile, I'm finally...
Going to make a supremely
peaceful and happy future, right?
Hey, that's my line!
Well, I'd better get going.
Good luck!
I got this!
It's been 49 days since the other Yuta died.
We have to mourn him well.
Did you all bring your offerings?
Of course.
Rest in peace.
What was that noise?
It came from Ito's room.
Wh-What the hell is this?
It's a chinchilla, a kind of Persian cat.
That's not what I meant!
My friend in technical school
really wanted me to take him in.
What's his name?
I haven't decided yet.
Then, in that case,
how about Chiranosuke?
Isn't that cute?
I love salmon
Hey, Muhi, what are you doing?!
No!
Darn it!
Stop! Chiranosuke!
Punch Line
Hey, what's wrong?
Wake up! Come on!
To a supremely happy
and peaceful future