This is all there is of Eleven?
There'd be no point in having
lots of ordinary people join battle.
Besides, it's not as if we asked to join Eleven.
It was probably God's will
or something like that
that gave us superhuman powers.
To fight against Machines,
and survive.
Hey, traitor! Give me a shot!
Shut up!
Idiot.
It's not that complicated.
Kill them before they kill you.
Some wastes you can't
even throw out.
This is all your fault, Karen.
Me? Why?
You destroy the machines so
excessively, and then sell them to me.
That probably pissed them off.
I'm out of this, you tomboy!
Right... if Karen's the cause,
let's hand her over to the machines.
Give me a break.
Humans have to be rational. Right? Rational.
I forgot to tell you one thing.
Their annihilation target is Sector 17.
That's my place!
Dammit, I'll beat the crap out of them!
That's exactly what we were talking about.
Shoot them all, Karen!
Everyone has a natural right to defend
his life, liberty and possessions.
Those natural rights are being taken away.
We aren't garbage.
John Locke's social theory?
Sorry, "all I did was be born,
and God gives us all these rights."
I thought I overheard such nonsense
by a fairy tale writer, so...
And so, have all of you
made a contract with God?
Not that it matters to me.
Then what are you doing here?
Ah, that's harsh.
I guess you could say it's a sense of duty.
I know what they have up their sleeve.
They intend to completely annihilate Sector 17.
A dimensional oscillation bomb.
They'll send it to the bottom.
SEEK lost control of Jay.
He is going down the pipeline
with that bomb.
You could keep wrecking the minions,
but it's all over
once this thing blows.
Keep talking about God's will or whatever,
but Eleven's talents will be gone, too.
Hey you!
Isn't it your job to
figur something out?
I'm just a messenger.
Then do something, messenger!
I think I'll be going, now.
To where?
Where? The pipeline, of course.
Hey, you can't deal with
it all alone.
Thanks for the food.
Please take care of the rest.
Hey, isn't anyone going to stop her?
She'll be dead!
Thanks for your concern,
but this wound here tells me to go.
I'll take you down along
with the rest of Sector 17, Karen.
You obsolete garbage!
Am I garbage because I'm old?
Is everything old garbage?
You're all garbage!
Go, Karen! We'll stop them here!
You're not going anywhere.
Eat this!
Dude, isn't this a rare item?
Stop, I'm a negotiator!
don't come any closer!
Psych.
I can't simply stand by
and watch my men die.
The advance team is having trouble in Sector 17.
We can't send any more backup.
No matter! Move them forward!
What will you do, Karen?
Incoming object detected.
It's Karen!
I'll take you out myself.
Come on, Jay!
Don't underestimate me!
I hope your repairs are good, junk shop!
Next!
Launch tripods.
Time for the hunt.
You want to kill me, don't you, Jay?
Give me your best shot!
Oh shit!
Direct hit on Karen. Her bike is destroyed.
Wait a second...
High-energy object approaching at high speed!
Karen!
That bitch!
You!
Karen!
I'm the one you're after.
Then this attack is quite cowardly.
Don't flatter yourself.
I'll annihilate all humans! With this!
Come on, shoot me!
Just kill me.
Self-sacrifice, huh? That's
what makes humans weak.
Look, it's Sector 17.
Go down with everyone, Karen!
The detonator.
No.
Seek, you --
If you think humans are garbage,
and you're trying to become like humans,
then you're garbage, too.
Machines are not garbage!
Great Genie!!!
I was born from you, SEEK!
Yet, you...
You're not getting away.
What?
Evolution is a process of selection.
For humans and for machines.