Hey, bro!
Yes, sir.
Over here!
It's huge!
Mahi-mahi, mahi-mahi!
It's been three weeks
since I started working.
Work is growing on me,
but even more fun than working,
is fishing after work.
Enoshima bowl!
Look at that. It's a bait ball.
Bait ball?
A school of small fish at the surface.
There are bigger fish
underneath trying to eat them.
What's there?
Probably tuna.
I should've brought my tuna rod.
You can fish for tuna?
Well, yeah.
It's not easy, though.
Tuna, huh?
Horrified Splash
Yuki, you're quite tan.
Well, I've been running
around on a boat all day.
Haru, not so much.
Huh? I'm tan, too.
It's because you're
always skipping work.
That's not fair, Yuki,
pretending you're the only good one!
What, you got a problem
with that? Huh?
Listen up, Yuki.
I have something to tell you.
I should be able to leave the
hospital by the end of the week.
Really?
Hooray!
Yuki, let's celebrate!
It's all right.
Celebrate!
You don't need to do anything special.
Golden Cat Cup
Tuna
I see.
That's great.
Yuki and I are going to
celebrate Keito's return.
Celebrate, huh?
Are you going to give her a present?
Yeah, I was thinking fish.
Fish?
I want to catch something
myself for her to eat.
Good idea.
What do you want
to catch? I'll help you.
Tuna.
Seriously?!
Tuna's great!
Grandma loves tuna,
and I'd like to try catching
one at least once.
Tuna fishing, huh?
He's carefree, isn't he?
In Enoshima
Yamada, we read your report.
It's a strange incident.
When I asked the local
police about it...
they said the surfers...
didn't seem to be lying.
We have already received
information regarding the incident.
Of course, this incident deals
with neither aircraft nor sea vessels.
When they came to their
senses, time had passed...
and they had moved to
a different location.
I believe it may have something
to do with Bermuda Syndrome.
Yamada, we did not instruct you
to investigate this incident.
I know, but...
Continue your assignment.
Duck!
Enoshima...
Kamikakushi.
Kamikakushi?
You might want to ask
Grandpa about that.
Grandpa?
My grandfather.
He's the head priest of this shrine.
He's also the town mayor.
What is it?
Nothing, you just look quite different.
Really? Do I look good?
It's a little strange.
You're one to talk.
Is that him?
Yeah, that's Grandpa.
Grandpa!
Akira-kun wants to ask you
about the Kamikakushi.
Akira-kun, be careful.
The trick is not to interrupt him.
Bye-bye, Tapioca!
There's an old legend of this island...
about a dragon who would spirit
people away, and the
goddess who subdued him.
A dragon and a goddess?
You think it's a load
of bull, don't you?
Not at all. But, this dragon...
What does it represent?
The dragon's a dragon.
But dragons are creatures of fantasy.
I don't think so.
The dragon was real.
He really did spirit people away.
It just happens to be peaceful now.
But lately, I've been
getting a strange feeling.
I hope it's just my imagination.
By the way, you.
Yes?
I bet you like fish with whiskers.
Like catfish!
Amazing!
I hate jokes... so much.
Catfish.
We're fishing for tuna today.
What is this?
It's a fishing belt.
It'll support your rod.
Tuna are big.
Without one of these,
they'll take your rod.
Really?
We'll use these lures. Pencil bait.
Pencil, pencil!
That's right.
Because of its simple, pencil-like shape,
just reeling it won't
create enough action.
Wave your rod down like this to
make it sink into the ocean.
Make it seem like bait by
letting it swim a little,
before pulling it up to the surface.
That's what you call jerking.
Do this repeatedly to
lure the tuna to you.
If you do it right,
the tuna will go for it
when you bring it to the surface.
Give it a try.
Enoshima bowl!
The most important part of tuna
fishing is accurate casting.
What are you doing?
Tuna are cautious, so you
cannot approach them easily.
To avoid missing your only chance,
you must cast accurately.
Indian!
That's not the only important
part of catching big fish.
You need good teamwork between
the guy fishing and the
guy steering the boat.
Teamwork!
Even if you hook one,
tuna swim fast and pull hard.
If the guy driving the boat sucks,
you'll lose him in a second.
Catching tuna seems hard.
It's okay. You'll catch one.
The real problem is location.
Location?
Casting and teamwork are both important,
but we have to find where they are first.
Wave the rod down and let it sink.
Make it seem like bait by
letting it swim a little,
before pulling it up to the surface.
Do this repeatedly to lure the tuna.
Hey, bro. There's a ton
of birds over there.
Can we go there?
Oh, Akemi?
Akemi?
It's written as "bright sea"
and pronounced Akemi.
It's an artificial fish reef.
Fish reef?
A man-made object placed in the
ocean to encourage fish to live and mate.
I don't get it.
It's a place where lots of fish gather.
Sir, we can't go over there.
They don't allow fishing.
Why would they prohibit fishing
in a place with lots of fish?
How suspicious.
Could it be a secret
fishing spot for locals?
There isn't actually a fishing ban.
But the locals won't go anyway.
Why not?
Hey, you guys.
Don't just stand around talking.
Okay.
I don't know the details, but apparently,
a fishing boat disappeared
over there a long time ago.
You guys have been working
hard this past month.
You've all gotten stronger.
Thanks for all your help.
No, thank you.
Thanks, Captain.
Thank you!
Okay, bring it in!
He does this every year.
I want to jump in, but...
What's wrong? Don't be shy.
He won't let us go until
we do this. Come on.
Ready, and...
Come on!
All right!
Good.
Your movements are
becoming more natural.
The captain's the
cool supporting character
who gives the fishermen a hand.
Listen closely to the guys fishing,
watch their movements carefully,
and move the boat into the
easiest position for them to fish.
You'll slowly approach bait balls,
and sometimes move to cut the tuna off.
Once they hook one, you close the gap.
I see.
I have one more question.
What is it?
You can ask me anything about boats.
Are there tuna at Akemi?
Who knows?
No one's been out there recently.
Because a boat disappeared?
Why do you ask?
You said you wanted me to
teach you how to drive a boat.
I'm just curious.
Hey, it's time to head back.
But the sun won't set for a while.
I know how you feel,
but the currents are shifting,
and I've got something to do after this.
Well, I can have someone
else take you out,
but don't go to Akemi.
Under no circumstances.
Got it?
Okay.
Thank you.
Thanks.
This sucks. None of the boats are free.
We won't be able to catch
tuna from the shore.
Would you like to take my boat?
What boat?
Enoshima bowl.
Damn it, let me fish!
I know. This is an investigation.
We've cast tons of times...
Maybe we're not in the right place.
But I've heard of people
catching tuna around here.
Should we check it out?
But the captain said...
I know, but the tuna
are definitely there.
Then we have to go.
Don't you want to catch one, Yuki?
I definitely want to catch one.
Look!
That's amazing.
I've never been to such a great spot.
There's tuna.
Really?
Akira, slowly approach the bait ball!
I know!
It's okay.
I'll catch one.
I want to catch one myself.
Look at the distance.
Are you sure you can do it?
I'll try.
Don't miss. You only have one chance.
What's wrong with you? Aim better.
Don't panic.
Think of casting into the bucket!
It's Enoshima bowl, Yuki.
Calm down.
Enoshima bowl!
Go!
Um, what am I supposed to do?
Yuki, jerking.
Oh, yeah!
Wave the rod down and let it sink.
Make it seem like bait by
letting it swim a little
before pulling it up to the surface.
Got one!
How far is he going to run?
Wait for him to stop.
Don't let your guard down.
Won't I run out of line?!
It's okay.
Just like that.
Now! Reel it in!
It's so... strong.
Close the gap, Akira!
Damn it.
So close.
Hey, I'm stopping the boat!
So, so close.
That sucks, Yuki.
What do you want to do, Yuki?
What are you doing?
Yuki can't do it. Let me do it.
Wait. Give him one more chance.
It'll be the same, no matter
how many times he does it.
You idiot, have some faith!
If Yuki doesn't catch it, it's pointless!
Yuki, Grandma's waiting.
Good evening.
Sakura-chan.
Natsuki should be back soon.
Boss.
Sakura, wait here like a good girl.
Got one!
Try to keep your cool, Akira!
Akira!
Answer me!
I can hear you! You calm down!
You can do it, Yuki!
The tuna quieted down.
Now's my chance.
Reel it in!
That's it!
Yuki!
You'd better get it this time.
It's huge!
Bring it closer!
Got him!
You can do it!
Hooray!
You did it, Yuki.
Thanks.
You caused so much trouble.
Keito will be so happy.
Thanks, Akira.
What are you talking about?
You're the one who caught it.
No.
Everyone helped.
They disappeared!
Whoa, it's pitch black!
Natsuki! Akira!
Hey!
He's not moving anymore.
What is this?
Akemi disappeared.
Akemi's gone.
That's odd.
They must have lost track
of time while fishing.
Heihachi-san.
This isn't good.
The sea god's in a sour mood today.
It's because of those unscrupulous
kids who headed into Akemi to fish.
You don't mean...
Them!
I found Akemi.
How did it get so far away?
Teleportation?
No. We have less fuel,
so it must be memory loss.
Or perhaps memory manipulation.
Manipulation?
It's a bait ball!
I've never seen one so huge!
There's no way that's real!
It's him!
This is where we meet
after a hundred years!
Sorry, guys.
Let's go up, everyone!
Haru, let's go.
Haru.
Fish, human, alien. Fish, human,
alien. Fish, human, alien.
Fish!
You've finally shown your true form.
What is your goal?
Damn it.
Humans are so interesting!
Yeah, Ayumi?
Yeah, they weren't at the Koshigoe Dock.
The guys at the yacht harbor
hadn't seen them either.
Yeah, please do. Search near Akemi.
Natsuki!
Seishunmaru here.
What a scary face!
Open your mouth and smile.
Huh?
Where am I?
Huh? Enoshima?
Nii-chan, I told you it was dangerous.
Hey, are you okay?!
Captain.
Captain!
I'm the one who said we should go.
No, I said I wanted to fish for tuna.
I'm sorry.
Idiots.
You're idiots.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
Natsuki!
Do you know the trouble we went through?
Do you have any idea...
how worried I was?
I'm so glad! I'm so glad...
I'm so happy, Tamocchan.
The next day...
Welcome home!
Grandma came home.
Keito!
I'm home.
I was sad to see summer end.
It was the first time I felt that way.
That outfit is cute!
Thanks a bunch.
A bunch.
Huge success!
I didn't see Haru truly smile
for a while after that day.
I didn't find out why
until a little later.
Hey, something's wrong.
Is Yoshizo-san still fishing?
No, they're dancing.
What?
That's the Enoshima dance.
Continued in #7