At 18:00 Space Standard Time,
a GDF Special Forces unit
set up transmission satellites
to replace the ones destroyed by the
United Pan-Galactic Empire,
also known as Wulgaru.
However, the unit was
rushed by a Wulgaru squad.
Although they tried to counter the attack,
they were nonetheless overpowered
and the replacement transmission
satellites were destroyed.
Consequentially, we are currently unable
to send transmissions to Undina.
Several years have passed
since the invading
"Surprise Attack"
Wulgaru army suddenly appeared in our solar system,
but we still do not know the
motive behind their invasion
and acts of destruction.
The news keeps going on about us.
So Wulgaru are actually called
the Half Fried Rice Tofu Empire...
That wasn't even close...
Are you too stupid to
even have common sense?
I can go through life
without common sense!
What type of retort was that?
They keep showing the
clip where I botched it.
Check out my Asagi Special.
Knock it off! Not before my checkup.
Man, even our cutting-edge
units look pathetic...
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Nah, you didn't make us wait any!
I'd like the boys to proceed to
Examination Room 1
and the girls to proceed to the
Measurements Room.
Okay!
I've gained! I knew I gained weight!
Let's try that again...
It will turn out the same each time.
It just says I've gained because of
the sudden bursts of gravity!
I don't wanna drink that...
You can choose from a
selection of flavors.
It comes in yogurt,
vanilla and chocolate.
I'll let you decide!
Sheesh! That crazy stunt is
giving us a run for our money.
Could you make the five
units activate quicker?
Forget it!
Just getting them all operational
is near-enough miraculous.
That isn't good enough!
I can't do what I can't do.
And could you make the linkage
a simpler auto function?
I'll think about it.
None of them have mastered
the JURIA-SYSTEM yet,
so it's our job to help
them however we can.
Please take your job more seriously,
Head Mechanic.
There is a difference between
"serious" and "frantic," Rin-Rin.
You've gotta relax some.
Otherwise you're going to break.
A Special Forces unit set up
new transmission satellites.
When rushed by a Wulgaru squad,
they tried to counter the attack.
However, they were-
Not again!
You've got it lucky!
They only show the part
where you managed to fire a shot.
Just like a hero to steal the glory.
Thank you!
That wasn't a compliment!
Huh? But you just said...
You're all done.
Detailed reports will
be ready in a few days,
but from what I saw today,
everyone seems to be doing fine.
Thank you very much.
Isn't that great news?
Totally!
Have you finished your exams?
Uh, yes.
Then move over to the briefing room.
Huh?
We will explain your next mission there.
Everyone, get running!
How are they?
From what I saw, I'm worried about
psychological fatigue.
I believe they could use some down time
instead of another mission.
Aren't those children more developed
than normal humans in some areas?
Toshikazu Asagi is able to process
vast amounts of data.
Kei Kugimiya has highly developed
auditory perception.
Tamaki Irie has an abnormally
high G-tolerance.
Ataru Suruga has outstanding
memory in select areas.
Izuru Hitachi has an excellent
capacity to concentrate.
But it looks like these strengths
are hard on their bodies.
Why did you choose those five?
I'm sure there were more
evenly balanced students.
All five of them showed
top-class survival instincts.
That made them ideal
pilots for AHSMB units,
which were installed with the JURIA-SYSTEM.
I see...
Also, about Izuru Hitachi...
He may require a reexamination.
Why is that?
I cannot pinpoint the problem,
hence the reexamination.
I see.
Jeez, what are they going
to make us do next?
This is depressing.
At ease.
Sir.
GDF Headquarters is calling you to arms.
They found an enemy supply route.
Your next mission will be to launch
a surprise attack on their supply ships.
We're attacking them?
That is why it's called
a surprise attack!
The mission commences in
36 hours. That is all.
Sir, could you go over
the mission in more detail...?
I will right before you set out.
Uh, were we the ones
assigned to this mission?
That was a pointless question.
Yesterday's mission ended in failure
and we still aren't accustomed
to piloting the AHSMBs.
Your opinion has been dismissed.
They'll brutalize me if I fail again...
I thought we'd finally become heroes,
but we're still losers...
Will we be the Failure Five forever?
Team Rabbits!
You have been authorized
to take a day and a half off.
The ship is ready for takeoff
as soon as you are ready.
Time off?
Right!
You get to go on a vacation,
albeit a short one.
Meet Your Special Someone in this
Charming and Relaxing Vacation Spot
PARADISE RESORT
Awesome!
Isn't this is a super expensive resort?
Resort! Vacation! Romance!
Time off before a mission?
So we won't die with any regrets?
Guys, you should be happy about this!
Resort. Vacation! ROMANCE!
Enough with that lame cheer.
We're only getting a day and a half off.
After that, we have to hit the enemy
with a sneak attack.
Even so...!
Resort! Vacation! Romance! Yay!
Whoo boy! Look at all the babes!
And all the dudes!
...unit set transmission satellites to replace
the ones destroyed by the Wulgaru.
However, the unit was
rushed by a Wulgaru squad
and the replacement transmission
satellites were destroyed.
Uh, aren't you getting hungry?
Why don't we grab a bite to eat?
I don't want your commiseration!
They're open all hours of the day, huh?
Just what I'd expect from a resort!
No matter what we eat,
the army's footing the bill, right?
I'm getting curry!
A big bowl of rice
with salted fish guts!
They won't have that.
Those are the kids they're
showing on the news.
Yeah. I'm just like, "Are
they gifted or not?"
What are they doing here?
Did they finish a mission?
It's not like this is
anything new, y'know?
When you get down to it,
we're the Failure Five.
We may have high specs, but we're still
failures for some odd reason.
We heard that crap all the time
at school, remember?
Everyone at school saying that
isn't the same as the whole galaxy saying it!
I'm going to the cottage.
Same.
Damn, they're such party poops!
They should enjoy the resort since we're here!
Seriously.
Thank you for waiting.
Here is your white rice
and pickled fish guts.
Who ordered the curry?
Man, the party's starting to heat up!
I'm totally getting pumped!
I'm going.
Wait! If you're gonna hit the town...
No, I'm going to train.
Train?
After a hero fails, 80% of the time
he goes on a training spree!
Welcome back.
Where's Asagi?
Sleeping.
Where are Suruga and Tamaki?
They said that they were going
to enjoy their vacation.
Kei?
Yes?
You've got some cream here...
Cake!
It'll be ready soon. Want some?
Well?
It's sweet, I guess...
It wouldn't be a cake
if it wasn't sweet.
It's super sweet.
Got a problem with my recipe?!
Uh, no!
I wonder what we're doing
in a place like this.
Until just recently, we were students.
I figured we'd be put on
the battlefield eventually,
but this was so sudden...
They keep sending us
on one mission after the next.
They even ordered us to take leave...
But we can't choose anything else
for ourselves, can we?
We were born to fight.
All of our memories were erased
before we entered the academy...
If they order us to go, we have
no choice but to fight.
Sometimes it's too much to bear.
Just what am I?
I can't even make decisions for myself.
Izuru, doesn't it bother you?
It doesn't matter.
Even if I don't have a past,
even if my future is nasty,
it doesn't matter to a hero.
What?
When I first entered the academy,
I spent all of my time reading
the manga in the dorm.
Those manga were brimming
with cool heroes.
I thought it would be awesome
if I could be like them.
I think that if we can
accomplish something,
it will prove that we were born for a reason
precisely because we started with nothing.
We may be the Failure Five,
but let's work to become heroes together!
Heroes, huh?
Would you like another slice of cake?
Gimme just a sec!
Could you tell me what you think?
I just know you'll appreci-
No!
Ladies, you've got such nice bodies!
If I compared you to guns,
I'd say you're as wonderful as the
Beretta Cx4 Storm designed
by Master Giugiaro.
It has an elegant bodyline with curves
reminiscent of a violin!
At any rate, practicality has nothing to do
with the pursuit of a beautiful body!
Why'd we all come to the pool?
Of course, guns overflowing with
beautiful functionality rock!
Because this is a resort?
But your dazzlingly beautiful bodylines
make you like
Say...
Hell no.
thoroughbreds amongst pack horses,
diamonds amongst glass beads
and silver chips amongst lead balls!
At last! Resort! Vacation! Romance!
He has a girlfriend...
She must be his sister!
Who are you?!
Hey!
Let us be off.
But I still haven't told him how I feel!
Hey, can he swim?
Don't invite us to the friggin' pool
if you can't swim.
I-I'm sorry.
Hey, so, do you know that girl?
Who was she?
No, I don't...
And you tried to ask her out?
I could never do that!
You did not say that.
But... I've seen her somewhere...
How was your vacation?
Go get changed and meet
back here in one hour.
A man from GDF Headquarters will be
supervising this mission;
you will meet him then.
This is GDF's Vice Chief
of Staff, Captain Komine.
Attention!
At ease.
The Vice Chief of Staff will personally
command this upcoming mission.
That is an indication of just how
important this operation is.
Thus far, the GDF has
only fought in defense.
But with the completion
of these new AHSMB
units and you as their highly-trained pilots,
we are finally able to take an aggressive
stance and initiate an attack.
This mission is crucial for stopping
the Wulgaru invasion. Therefore-
Sir, I apologize for
interrupting your speech,
but could you please introduce me?
This is my adjutant, Lt. Amane.
Explain the upcoming mission.
We discovered a set Wulgaru
route from beta 25 to 27
on Jupiter's third
quadrant orbital grid.
We believe there is a high probability
that it is a supply route.
This is where we will strike!
It is currently amidst a particularly
strong solar storm.
Soon the area will be bathed
in extremely powerful CME
Note: CME is the acronym
for "Coronal Mass Ejection"
and high-energy charged particles.
As a result, many electronics,
including radar, should be
rendered temporarily inoperable.
Wait for the enemy to go blind
and then crush them when
they fall into disarray!
You will wait for the solar flare
to pass behind a planetoid
that has a powerful shield in place.
It will take 24 seconds at full speed
to reach the enemy's anticipated location
from behind the shielded planetoid.
We expect the enemy's systems
to recover in 40 seconds.
You have 16 seconds to destroy
everything and pull back.
This operation requires
clockwork precision.
As such, I shall be issuing
the orders from start to finish.
You are still inexperienced soldiers
fresh from the academy.
You may possess latent abilities,
but you are painfully lacking in experience.
You must not perform pathetically
like in your prior operation.
Have I made myself clear?
We have dedicated a large portion
of our budget to you, not
just the AHSMB units!
If you fail to perform accordingly,
it defeats the point in ever creating you!
Sir, it is about time they
prepared for takeoff.
The AHSMBs' maintenance is complete.
You may see them if you like.
I could show you the way.
You are to go to your cockpits.
How dare he say,
"It defeats the point in creating you"?!
It's not like he's our
creator or anything!
Grr! He totally pissed me off!
"Perform pathetically
like last time," huh?
That's what got you upset?
Well, this time we're
going after supply ships.
And we should have the upper hand
since it's a surprise attack.
I don't want you to trying
to make me feel better!
In any event, we have
to fight under some
old fart who resembles
a squashed cream puff.
Yep! Let's do our best!
That's not how most people
would typically respond.
Pay attention to the conversation.
Stupy-dupy poopy.
Quit randomly trying to console people.
Gordinion is ready for takeoff.
Roger.
Commander Simon, what will you be doing?
I will remain on standby here.
Understood. That would make things
less strenuous on me as well.
I will be careful with how I inform
the Vice Chief of Staff.
Where is Simon?
He is on standby at Headquarters.
Well, it was merely his
job to nurse the MJP.
It is our job to properly utilize them.
Takeoff in T minus 30 seconds.
Heavy armor?
Are we getting fully outfitted 'cause
the Vice Chief of Staff is in command?
The grill ads are gone!
Probably because this
isn't getting aired.
That or we've lost our sponsors.
Already?
May I not goof up this time!
I've confirmed that the Pits are
in position for blast off.
All vessels are prepared for blast off.
All ships: Blast off!
Thank you.
I hear they went to a resort.
When do you think we'll get to go?
Wulgaru ships spotted at Point D7.
All units, get into battle formation!
I'm putting them on the screen.
A supply fleet? Really?
What are those?
They don't appear to be supply ships.
Then what are they?
I believe this is an armed
reconnaissance squadron.
Wasn't this a supply route?!
That was merely speculation.
You are the one who determined
it to be a supply route.
We should avoid contact.
Are you saying to pull back
without achieving anything?!
Doesn't the JURIA-SYSTEM demonstrate
its prowess best in situations like this?!
Commence Operation Night Blow!
Commence the operation!
Mission: Start!
I had the units fully
outfitted just to be safe
as we were unsure what type of
enemy vessels they may encounter.
That's a given!
Attack!
Orders to attack?
My AHSMB is terrified!
You mean you are!
No!
Don't run from a fight! Attack!
I'll cover you!
They're quick!
They're fast! This squadron
is using cutting-edge units!
Incoming attack from the front right!
They're quick to dodge.
Here's the next attack!
And they're good at defense.
They can't win! Issue a retreat.
I can't do that!
We are clearly at a disadvantage!
If you're going to state your opinion,
give information to back it!
How are they at a disadvantage?!
Can't you see that for yourself?
I can't hit 'em!
How are we supposed to fight them?!
Rose 3!
S-sir!
What are you doing?! Charge!
Didn't you hear me?
Charge at full speed!
Uh, okay!
Wait, Tamaki!
Rose 3, activate shields!
Tamaki?!
My shields...!
Tamaki!
"Loss"