The sports festival is coming up soon.
Sports Festival
Please be sure to have your guardian look
over the information we just handed out.
Sports Festival Notice
Saikawa, what's a sports festival?
Wow, didn't you have them
in your country, Kanna-san?
A sports festival is a very fun event!
There's running,
Running?
ball-tossing,
Ball-tossing?
tug-o-war,
Tug-o-war?
and lots of other events where
the whole class works together!
Oh!
Mothers and fathers come watch, too.
You can eat lunch with them, as well.
Oh!
You're great at sports, so I'm sure
you'll be a heroine of the day.
Then your mother will praise you!
Oh!
Work that day. Can't.
Kobayashi. Take the day off.
I can't do that.
Kanna, Miss Kobayashi's in the
middle of her death march
and on the verge of facing Hades.
Give it up.
No!
Also, what is a sports festival?
You train with everyone to
defeat strong opponents.
No, I don't think that's quite right.
Kobayashi, come!
Defeat Hades!
Don't be selfish.
At least I'll be sure to come for you.
No.
Why does it have to be Miss Kobayashi?
Saikawa said mothers and
fathers come with us.
Lady Tohru, you're like a big sister.
Kobayashi's like a mother.
A mother? I'm not that old... Wait.
Some of my old classmates
do have children already...
Miss Kobayashi, hang in there!
Well, at any rate, I can't.
Sorry, but you'll have to
make do with Tohru.
Make do?
Forget it!
Ah, Kanna!
Is it that important whether
a parent shows up or not?
For one thing, I'm not exactly
Kanna-chan's mother anyway.
But Kanna does tend to
view you as her mother.
I'm not that great though.
I never had both my parents
come to a sports festival.
They were busy with work.
I understood they were
supporting our family, too.
Kanna's parents basically
gave her free rein.
They felt a dragon would grow
up strong on its own.
They probably told her to live strong
since she bears the name Kanna Kamui.
But Kanna's pulled many different pranks
to try and get her parents' attention.
To the point she was
banished to this world...
So I think that's why she
wants you to spoil her.
Even if you say that...
Hmm...
Good morning, Kanna-san.
What's wrong?
Kobayashi won't come to the sports festival.
Wow, really?
But there's more to the
sports festival than that!
It's still fun working together
with everyone to be victorious!
Victorious...
Your "working together"
sounds fishy, Saikawa-san.
Shut up! You got a problem with that?!
No, no problem. I just don't believe you.
That is basically having a problem with it!
Sports festival?
Yeah.
That date overlaps directly
with our delivery date.
Well, I'm wondering if there's really
any need to go in the first place.
You don't want to?
Well, I think it would be nice if I could go.
Hmm? What?
It's my first time seeing you
worry about something like this.
Really?
Oh, I guess so.
Well, I think it's more a question
of do you want to go, rather than can you.
If I want to go, huh?
Lalala, I'm a cute maid!
I'm home.
Oh, welcome home.
Kanna, are you still in a bad mood?
Would you give—
Lady Tohru, perception blocking.
Huh?
Place it on me.
Oh.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
I'll get your dinner ready.
Yeah.
Kobayashi.
Hmm?
It's all right if you don't
come to the sports festival.
Huh?
It'll still be fun working together
with everyone in my class.
So, good luck with your work, Kobayashi.
Oh, sure.
Good night.
It seems that Kanna went to your work
today and was secretly observing you.
Hmm...
I've felt this feeling before.
Oh, right.
It's the same guilt I felt then...
Tohru.
Yes?
Starting tomorrow,
I'll be getting home even later.
You mean...?
All right!
Boys Relay
Girls Relay
Thirty-five!
Thirty-six!
Thirty-seven!
Thirty-eight!
Thirty-nine!
For—
Shoot!
So close!
Okay. That's enough for today.
You're all able to jump a lot now, huh?
That's incredible.
Let's keep it up and work hard toward
winning the sports festival!
Yes!
Kanna-san, let's do our best!
Okay.
You're working hard.
Yeah.
Planning to go to the sports festival?
Mhmm.
Decided you want to go?
No.
Decided I ought to go.
Want some help with your work?
Huh?
Oh, uh...
Yeah, could you?
Okay, next night drinking is on you.
Sure, sure.
Sports Festival!!
I'll be coming tomorrow.
Really?
Yeah, really.
You beat Hades?
Yeah, I did.
Kobayashi, I love you!
Whoa.
My goodness.
Kanna's still such a child.
What do they expect me to do?!
What do I do?!
I could go for both!
No, that would go over
my daily limit! I can't!
But, still!
Chestnut Cream This Season Only!          Sweet Potato This Season Only!
Umm, ma'am, if you could please...
I-I know!
I'll make my choice now!
Episode 9
Sports Festival! (There's No Twist Or Anything)
43rd Oborozuka Elementary Sports Festival
The 43rd Oborozuka Elementary
Sports Festival will now begin!
43rd Oborozuka Elementary Sports Festival
First on the program is our opening parade.
First Grade
Second Grade
Third Grade
Oh, there's Kanna.
Where, where?
She's looking our way. Hey!
Yeah, she would be curious.
Riko!
Little Miss!
Do your best!
Shouta!
Oh, Miss Lucoa's here, too.
I'm rooting for you!
Do your best!
The pledge:
We athletes hereby pledge to honor
the spirit of good sportsmanship
and compete fair and square with
everyone until the very end!
Now, fifth on our program is the
three-legged race by the third graders.
Kanna, do your best!
In moderation!
Riko! Fight on!
Do your best!
Ready!
O-Okay, let's tie our legs together.
Done.
Th-Thanks, Kanna-san.
Now we hold each other's shoulders.
Yeah.
Okay, next pair.
Come on, Saikawa. It's our turn.
I-I'm sorry, Kanna-san.
I was just too happy.
It's all right, Saikawa.
Let's do our best next time.
Jeez, Riko, what are you doing?
Third Grade
Class 1                      Class 2
Class 3                      Class 4
Fifth Grade
Class 1
Class 3
Seventh on our program is the
fifth graders' treasure hunt.
Huh? Me?
World Class
Yes, okay.
Shouta-kun, your older sister's incredible!
Y-Yeah.
We'll now be taking a break for lunch.
Students and parents,
please enjoy your lunch together.
Be careful of heat stroke and
be sure to drink plenty of water.
Oh, it looks good!
It's normal.
I'm not who I used to be anymore.
Thanks for the food!
Lady Tohru, this is good.
Thank you.
Miss Kobayashi, here, ah.
Tohru, what kind of meat is this?
Tch.
Knew it.
Ah.
But this lunch really is good.
Thank you, Kanna.
Eat plenty, and give it your best today.
Yeah.
We'll turn things around after this.
What do they expect me to do?
What do I do?
How am I supposed to choose just one
from over ten different combinations?
I could go for all the variations!
No, then I wouldn't last.
But, still!
Pear | Grape | Pumpkin | Sweet Potato | Chestnut
20% off! Double Scoops!
This Season Only!
There's the pumpkin and sweet potato.
Umm, ma'am, if you could please...
Wait, chestnut's hard to pass up.
Still, the surprising pairing of grape
and pear would be good, wouldn't it?
No, wait. Chestnut...
Now we'll be starting this
afternoon's segment.
15th in our program, the
third graders' jump rope.
Now to begin.
Ready, set!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven...
Good luck!
That's it!
Riko, fight on!
eight, nine, ten, eleven...
Do your best, Little Miss!
Twenty-two, twenty-three...
twenty-four, twenty-five, twenty-six,
twenty-seven, twenty-eight...
Ah!
Classes 1 and 4 tripped on their ropes!
Forty-two, forty-three...
Ah!
Class 3's tripped on their rope!
forty-four, forty-five, forty-six,
forty-seven, forty-eight...
Class 2's amazing, they're still going!
Fifty-five, fifty-six, fifty-seven,
fifty-eight, fifty-nine...
Keep at it!
sixty, sixty-one...
Keep it up!
Done!
Class 3-2 wins!
They even jumped 60 times!
Miss Kobayashi, we won!
Yeah, that was impressive.
19th on our program,
the fifth grade boys' cavalry battle.
Shouta, do your best!
Fight on!
Begin!
Do it!
Go, Shouta!
Now!
Get them!
Finished!
Class 3 with an overwhelming
victory in the cavalry battle!
Shouta-kun, your older
sister's really incredible!
Y-Yeah.
20th in our program,
the third graders' tug-o-war!
Class 1 and 2, ready!
Begin!
Kanna-chan!
Fight on!
Don't lose!
Little Miss!
That's enough! Class 2 wins!
Saikawa, we did it. We won.
Hooray!
Yeah, you did well out there.
Keep this pace up!
Kanna's class is in second place now.
Yeah, they'll be in first
after this next one.
Oh, it's starting.
32nd in the program,
the third graders' relay!
Kanna-san, let's take first place and win!
This will be the last event
for the third graders.
Everyone, please give them
more support than ever!
First female runners, take your positions.
Ready!
Iida-san, do you best!
Iida, fight on!
All the classes have started off.
Right now Class 1 holds the lead. Behind
them are Class 2, Class 4, and Class 3.
The baton's passed to the second runner.
Class 1 still remains in the lead.
Makishima, keep it up!
Saikawa, do your best!
Of course.
I'll pass you the baton from first place!
Class 1 and 2 are neck and neck!
Everyone, give it your best!
Here I go!
Wow, Class 2's really fast!
They've passed Class 1!
Ah! Class 2's dropped the baton!
Class 1 is currently running in the lead.
Behind them are Class 4,
Class 3, and Class 2!
I'm sorry!
Leave it to me.
Their anchor's taking off!
Class 2's really fast!
She's passing the others one after another!
Kanna-san.
Just one more!
Do your best!
Go!
Goal!
Class 2 wins!
We did it!
Kanna-chan!
That was incredible, Kanna-chan!
You were so cool!
K-Kanna-san.
Umm, I'm sorry. I messed up...
We won because you closed
the gap as much as you did.
Thanks, Saikawa.
Kanna-san!
Class 2
Entrance    43rd Oborozuka Elementary
Nice work out there, Kanna-chan.
Thanks, Kobayashi.
You worked hard out there.
Yeah. We won because everyone
in our class worked hard.
But you must feel unsatisfied,
not being able to go all out.
Congratulations
Gold
That's fine. It's better
being with everyone else.
Kobayashi.
Hmm?
Thank you for coming today.
You're welcome.
Thank you for lunch too, Lady Tohru.
It was hardly anything at all.
Participating in a sports
festival as a guardian, huh?
My life's really changed.
When did I change this much?
Still, it would be nice to let
loose a little bit more today.
Congratulations
Gold
Right?
How about it, Kanna? It's been a while.
You're on.
Let me in, too!
Great! Shall all three of us, then?
Mhmm.
Is that all right, Miss Kobayashi?
Well, as long as you do it somewhere
where you won't bother anyone.
Lady Tohru, where should we do it?
Let's use the same place we did last time.
Good grief.
I'm itching to go!
Which should I choose?
Which should I...?
Which?
Melon Flavor     Kids' Toothpaste    Grape Flavor
Strawberry Flavor
Why must the products of man trouble me so?
Humans are frightening!
Next Episode
I'm the maid Josie,
servant of the Saikawa family.
I'm Shouta's familiar, Lucoa.
Familiar?
Yeah.
It seems we both have rather unique hobbies.
Episode 10
Troupe Dragon, On Stage! (They Had A Troupe Name, Huh)