Shichimiya.
You can't do things like this.
You just can't!
I have no experience
when it comes to romance...
...and I have always been dense
when it comes to things like that.
Shichimiya.
As dense as I am, seeing her tears
were enough to make me realize.
I realized what Shichimiya
had been attempting to make war with.
Why she asked me those questions,
and why she made me say those things.
The water mage's
attack has intensified.
Rescue requested.
And why she wept.
What are you doing?
New discovery. I would like to
commence exploration.
Forget it. You haven't brought your umbrella.
Kuzuha said...
What does Kuzuha have to do with anything?
Just duck under here.
You're freezing.
Dark beings always maintain
a low body temperature.
I'm coming in.
I made you some rice gruel. Try to eat some.
EPISODE XI BLUE MOON RAGNAROK
Can you sit up?
The real world is becoming distorted!
Is it due to the weakened state
of Wicked Lord Shingan?!
Hey, you okay?
You still have a fever.
I want you to stay in bed for another day.
I cannot afford to.
Listen, you have a cold.
Remember how you tried to go out yesterday...
...and ended up in a sorry heap
just past the door?
Ugh, the world is banishing me.
I am fine now. A night's sleep
has fully restored me.
No way. You are grounded until you're all better.
Where are you trying to go anyway?
That I cannot answer. I have said so before.
I put the question to you as Dark Flame Master!
Where do you go?
It's not like I'll do anything
with that information, you know.
I just don't like you going off somewhere...
...in secret from me.
Forgive me.
But soon, all will be revealed.
Master!
How could you perish this way
and leave me alone?!
It's d-d-death!
She is not dead!
She'll be better soon, right?
If I were so inclined...
...I could use the power of Wicked Lord
Shingan to recover. However...
Gasp! Do you mean that to recover...
...I must feed you the black dragon
flower that only grows...
...at the summit of the great dark wall
in the Wicked Lord's World?!
Please don't provide her with a scenario.
Stay back or you'll catch her cold.
Master! I'll be waiting for you!
I swear this to you!
Thank you both, but we can't have you
catching her cold.
That's true.
See you around, Chimera.
Take care of that cold. I'm sure you have stacks
of homework to do.
You spoke what must remain unspoken.
What do you mean?!
Tell them the cat ate your homework.
I want to know about Sophia.
Huh?
I made several attempts to contact her
through her electro-protocol code...
...but she has yet to make an appearance.
O-oh, really? I wonder what's wrong?
She said she was really busy.
He's so transparent.
From the moment Shichimiya
said she was going to make war...
...I thought it might come down to this.
You're saying you realized?
It was easy to tell.
All that girl ever looked at was you.
Actually, it was Toka who told us about it.
So? What are you gonna do about it?
Do about it?
You can't just leave her like that.
That girl is in love with you.
How am I supposed to know what to do?
I never even had a girlfriend before now.
MYSTERY JEWEL 298 YEN
Don't get defiant with me.
I'm just being honest. What should I do?
Pardon?
Aren't women supposed to know
about this sort of thing?
H-how am I supposed to know?
Chicken.
I'm not chickening out.
Then stay out of it.
You're always such a busybody,
like that time with Rikka.
I help you guys out when you need it!
I never asked for your help.
Do what you want. See if I care!
Kumin-senpai, let's go.
What?
Ow!
What the hell?!
It's nothing!
Don't knock people over for nothing!
It's nothing, but it's also something!
Who do you think you are? Dekomori?!
What?
Shichimiya!
Hero!
What is she doing?
Whoa, hey!
I have returned!
What do you think you're doing?
You could have died!
Ripples and magical energy were vital...
...to conquer the inner me!
I get it!
Please don't accept that.
Thanks to that, I've conquered it for good!
I am 100% victorious! From now on...
...I am magical devil girl
"Spin-off Revision Plus Alpha!"
It sounds like a game that's being
gradually ruined by sequels.
That's why you can permanently delete
what happened earlier! Let it disappear!
Shichimiya, will that do it?
Yup! That'll do it!
That's a relief.
Oh! Angel detected!
Togashi.
What?
Did you take what she just said seriously...?
...thinking, "That's good.
She looks like she's coping fine"?
You mean she isn't?
What the...?!
Why would she be fine?! She's acting tough!
How am I supposed to see that?
Just look at her!
I've hung out with her enough
to know how she works!
Then what do you expect from me?!
Well...
Do you know how they say
that love is like a dream?
With a dream, you eventually wake up from it.
It's hard to force yourself to wake up.
Kumin-senpai.
Where are you going?
Who cares? You're not my keeper.
What's with her?
Morisummer loves you.
What?
She loves Rikka, and Dekomori...
...you, and Shichimiya so much...
She loves chunibyo.
I'm a bit jealous of you guys.
I wish I could have chunibyo too.
You do?
Then I could feel the same way as all of you.
But I doubt that's how you get chunibyo.
The fact that you admire it means that
you have a good case of chunibyo.
You think so?
Aren't you Wicked Lord Shingan
the Second, Kumin-senpai?
YOU'VE GOT MAIL
Morisummer!
Sophia, you appear to have lost your way.
What brings you here?
Did you regain your memory?!
Wanna eat some medicinal plants?
I do not!
I expressly came wearing this uniform,
hoping it would make it easier to communicate.
It's a tight fit.
Huh?
Ahem. Sophia.
I have words for you.
The words of the magician Morisummer.
Morisummer once fought someone
who stole her identity...
...and punished this person.
That is when she made a realization.
She realized how one might face and fight
one's other inner self face-to-face.
One's other inner self?
Yes. You must look outwards to know thyself.
Just as I found myself
when I fought my imposter...
I am certain that you, too,
have an opponent to face.
Find that opponent.
Morisummer.
Then your path will open before you.
Thank you.
What a total pain. Message received?
Morisummer! Thank you.
I'll give you a supply of magical energy!
You're too close! Stop that.
It's you!
Hey, Mjolnir Hammer! Come over here!
Was Dark Flame Master not enough for you?!
Do you dare mess with
Fake Mori Summer as well?!
Unforgivable!
How do you feel?
Kuzuha, is the moon out?
It's a lovely full moon.
It's going to be a blue moon tonight.
A blue moon.
Shichimiya is in love with me, but I love Rikka.
Forget it. It's too complex. What should I do?
Shichimiya.
Hero. Or rather Dark Flame Master!
Wanna see my magic?
Shichimiya.
I've been looking everywhere...
...but you are the only suitable
opponent for me to fight, Hero.
This is the only way to settle the score.
Which means...
This is war!
But you're...
Here I come! Devil Lord, recognized!
Big Brother. Oh, Satone?
Uh, yeah.
Big Brother, Rikka is gone!
What?
I only looked away for a moment.
Why that...
What do we do?
Shichimiya.
There's a blue moon out tonight.
Yeah.
I think she probably realized
that there's a blue moon out tonight.
Blue moon?
You really don't remember?
This is it!
Dark Flame Dragon?
Hero, you're the one who said that
the Dark Flame Dragon...
...sleeping within you would come back to life.
You said you wanted it brought back to life.
To whom I am bound by the absolute contract,
unchanged from long ago and for all eternity.
Even if I should travel through
time and dimensions...
...past the reaches of the parallel world...
...our contract shall continue to be binding...
...and by its absolute power,
you will appear before me.
At this very moment, in this world of chaos...
A world I was born into by mistake...
...I am now attempting to use
its powers of containment...
...and memory falsification,
to rob myself of my true memories.
I fear that in the not too distant future,
I will pass into nothingness.
I hereby entrust thee...
...with the Dark Flame Dragon
that dwells within me.
With the power of its form,
which can plunge this world into shadow.
With the power to consume
this fallacious world...
...to revolutionize and remold it.
Three keys are needed to revive
the Dark Flame Dragon.
Skuld.
Belldandy.
And Urd.
You, to whom I am bound by
the absolute contract.
If you indeed hold the power
to share my destiny...
...surely you can assemble
these three keys effortlessly.
You, to whom I am bound for eternity.
I will enter a period of slumber...
...to await that appointed time.
I want you to endow me with power...
...on a future night of the blue moon.
Is this where it's hidden?
I only half-remember it,
but it has to be around here.
I have to dig here.
What's this?
The Wicked Lord Shingan left this here.
I think these are markers to
show this has already been searched.
No way.
You mean...?
I also searched for them.
I just couldn't find Urd.
The key you sent into the past.
The only way to send a key into the past
is to utilize the parallel world.
According to your memo,
the entrance to the parallel world...
...is in the shadow cast by the 14th pylon.
But I didn't know which pylon
to start counting from.
So, she went through each and every one?
Forgive me. But soon, all will be revealed.
All this time, she's been doing it for that?
Do you know where it is?
Yeah, but just vaguely!
I remember this street!
This way!
Rikka.
No matter how serious you were about chunibyo.
No matter how serious you were about love...
...you always put me first.
Rikka! Rikka! Rikka!
Hero.
Rikka!
Yuta.
What are you doing?!
Yuta, is this it?
Urd?
You idiot!
You went out looking for this
while you're sick with a cold?!
Do you want to make it worse?!
But it said the one you are bound to...
...by the absolute, eternal contract
could bring it back to life.
That's no reason.
I am bound to you for eternity.
I have to find it.
I have to find it, and prove it!
Yuta?
What're you doing? You don't have to do all that!
But I'm supposed to be bound to you...
...but I didn't have a single key.
But Sophia did, so I had to...
I can't breathe.
Yuta?
Yuta, are you bound to me?
Yes, we are bound together
by the absolute contract.
I broke a bone in my
second summer of middle school.
So, I went and buried it inside the cast.
I'm amazed at all the effort
I went through back then.
Here.
That's incredible!
Nobody could tell where it is from that clue.
It was so hard to bury it in metal
that I gave up halfway.
I guess things really do stay
untouched after so many years.
It's just a rock.
That is the enchanted stone that
will summon the Dark Flame Dragon.
Sorta.
The blue moon.
I researched back then to find out
there'd be a blue moon tonight.
Rikka. Or rather...
...please do this, Wicked Lord Shingan!
You, to whom I am bound for eternity!
Be destroyed, real.
Blow up, synapses.
Vanishment...
...This World!
Incredible.
Hero!
Or rather, Ghelzonianses! This is war!
Let me do combat with the
Dark Flame Dragon at full power!
What?
I finally realized which opponent I must fight.
My true enemy I must fight...
...is the Dark Flame Dragon
I loved, pursued, and gave up with you!
That is the enemy with whom I must fight!
That is the opponent with whom
I must settle my score!
Shichimiya. I understand.
I am Ghelzonianses!
I am the one who will destroy
the entire world and give it new form!
Magical devil girl!
You wish to retain your magic for eternity!
Observe the power of my Dark Flame Dragon...
...with your own two eyes!
I couldn't ask for more!
The Dark Flame Dragon never actually existed.
So it could never actually be seen.
However...
Wh-what is that?!
Rikka's cold came back with a vengeance
and knocked her down.
Yuta, I am going back in time to July 20th.
Impossible!
With a catastrophic amount
of homework still looming...
...summer vacation came to an end.
What? Really?
I've got too much homework.
You'll miss Yumeha growing up.
I'm gonna transform!
I was unable to go visit them
in Jakarta as I was told to.
And then...
How are you handling your homework?
No problem is too great
for the born-again Sophia!
Shichimiya concluded her battle
with the Dark Flame Dragon...
...and successfully
evolved into a new Shichimiya.
So, what exactly has changed about you?
I never change.
I am a magical devil girl, for all eternity.
In order to stay unchanged,
I needed a powerful life-changing battle...
...to destroy the stress I had built up
in the name of staying unchanged.
What's that supposed to mean? Wait...
Is that the natural logic of the world?
That's it. It's the natural logic of the world.
Going out to look for angels again?
Yeah. Say, Hero?
Bye-bye.
TO BE CONTINUED