Thank you very much!
What?
Porky was crushed?!
Lost by 13 cards
If I speak, it shouldn't be
to ask if she's okay.
It should be to announce
a win for Mizusawa!
may the wind bring clouds
to extend their stay.
In the sleepy...
Chihaya-chan, are you...
...trying to use both
of their strengths?
Chihaya Furu
Verse 6
To
set the
Tatsuta
River
ablaze
In the sleepy spring sunlight,
What?
"In order to restore" hasn't been read yet
"In the sleepy" isn't a
one-syllable card yet.
In the
sleepy
In order
to restore
So why?
Was it because she was
camping that card?
I think she moved before
I even heard "In" spoken.
That's impossible!
No human is capable of that.
She just happened to guess right!
Focus, Amakasu!
She's not guessing cards!
Ayase Chihaya can hear.
She can hear!
I don't know what it is in
my voice that she can hear,
but there's a difference between
the "In" in "In the" and the "In" in "In order."
I want to know what
it is I'm telling her.
My voice isn't
telling her anything...
a whirlwind of flower petals descends.
She's taking control of my voice...
Nothing can be worse...
Again?
"No more" is still in play,
but she moved on "No."
There are other players who
can move fast or react fast,
but that's not what she's doing here...
Huh?
Nine months have passed...
Stop taking cards with your speed.
It must have been hard, Chihaya-chan,
but you've made incredible progress.
You concentrated on your
accuracy the first half,
and now you're taking risks to
take cards with your speed.
You're giving yourself more weapons!
There are 28 one-syllable cards for him.
You have 20!
This is what I wanted...
What I could never explain...
The sound that comes
before a sound forms...
I'm finally able to say I can hear it, too!
when I cannot bear growing any
weaker than I already have.
A mountain stream...
when people and grass grow scarce
Crap!  A fault!
Damn!
This is bad.
A fault this late in the match...
I'm in trouble!
Amakasu!  Say something!
Don't let your opponent focus!
Say that she's encroaching
on the playing field
or that there's a hair
sticking out of her nose!
Now I know how it
feels to be a reader!
I don't want to interfere!
as helpless autumn leaves are
caught against the flow.
While autumn leaves...
Not when she's this focused!
His five-card lead is
gone, just like that.
Damn, why do I have to
play such a tough match?
This is all Retro's fault!
Retro's losing his own match!
Our ace against their ace.
Our number two against
their number two.
Isn't that how we should win?!
Hokuo Academy is the
strongest school in Tokyo!
That's what I want to show everyone!
Sudo-san is gone.
I'm the Hokuo ace now.
In every other sport I tried,
I was told that I could
never be a starter,
but in my last summer here,
the members voted for me to lead them.
Said world grants no change, I pray,
"Said world grants no change"
is a five-syllable card.
Chihaya-chan covered the
"Said world grants no escape" card
on her side before attacking
the opponent's side.
My body may be small,
but I can still cover my
own cards against a girl.
I don't need a big lead.
One card is all it takes.
I'll still win in the end...
by playing karuta the Hokuo way.
Amakasu-kun is working hard.
I want him to be able to relax...
Why haven't Takuma and Kameda won yet?
I can tell my teammates
are trying their best.
I can see that my
opponent is worn down.
Why can't I pull ahead?  What's wrong?
He was a weak amateur last year!
I need to finish this match quickly!
I lost to Takuma-kun
by 15 cards, last year.
when the fisherman who casts
his nets can seem dear.
All he remembers is
that he crushed me.
He's not taking me seriously,
so he's placed all his
cards to the lower right.
Impassionate gods...
Yes!
All four of them got it!
W-Wait!
"Impassioned vows" is still in play,
so I was able to cover in time!
I touched the card first.
I moved around your hand
to tap it from the side.
It's easier to bypass a right-handed
cover with your left hand.
Was that his goal?!
Of course, Takuma-kun has played
karuta much longer than I have.
However, in the year
since I lost to him,
I've had more fun playing
karuta than he has.
I just know it!
are joined at river's end.
Two cards left...
May the time spent in our one night together
Kana-chan has one card left.
Mashima, Ayase, and Desktomu-kun
have two cards left.
Crazy...
I've never seen a match where
four games were all this close.
All four may possibly come down to luck-of-the-draw.
The finals are incredible.
All four games are down
to three cards total.
It's possible that we could see...
Crap!
Crap!  Crap!  Crap!
Mashima!  Ayase!  Desktomu-kun!  Kana-chan!
Pay attention!
If all four of you are put in
luck-of-the-draw situations
without realizing it, we'll lose!
We're guaranteed to lose!
bring a life of everlasting love.
I know that my heart...
N-No way!
Huh?!  What?!
They moved so fast that I
couldn't tell what happened.
Ayase-senpai, Mashima-senpai, and
Komano-senpai won their cards.
I've never seen this happen before...
Four simultaneous luck-of-the-draws!
Uh, I'm moving "The hazed early" left.
Is he doing this because
I'm left-handed?
I'm moving "The fall paddy" left.
Oh, sorry.  I think I'll move it back.
No, that's not what
they're trying to do!
Ayase!  Please!
Look around you!
Thinking about which card to send
Don't look at the cards!
Look around you!
Wait until Kana-chan has received hers!
Don't send your card yet!
but from the crystal white snow of Yoshino
I'm sending "The hazed early."
They got us.
Hokuo...
...successfully split their cards.
In a luck-of-the-draw, the rule
is to protect your own card.
Whoever's card is read, wins.
It's a 50-50 contest.
But in this situation...
Hokuo is good.
You can tell they're
used to team matches.
They were able to split their cards.
Splitting your cards
is a strategy employed towards
the end of a team match.
In a 5 vs. 5 team match, you
only need three wins to win.
In other words, the team
that already has one win
only needs two wins out
of the luck-of-the-draw.
So to ensure victory, they made sure
that they have two of each
of the remaining cards.
After "I know that my heart" was read,
Amakasu vs. Ayase
Takuma vs. Komano
Kinashi vs. Mashima                                      Kameda vs. Oe
they casually told their
teammates what their card was.
Uh, I'm moving "The hazed early" left.
I'm moving "The fall paddy" left.
Oh, sorry.  I think I'll move it back.
They waited until they saw
which card Chihaya-chan sent,
but from the crystal white snow of Yoshino
I'm sending "The hazed early."
before setting everything up
by sending the final card.
The hazed early                                            The hazed early
dawn light                                                      dawn light
The fall paddy                                                 The fall paddy
Now their cards are split.
As a team, they have two of each card,
so regardless of which card is read,
as long as they protect their
own cards, they'll win.
It's a strategy that's
borderline against the rules.
Oh, I should ask Tashiro-kun
to provide a ruling.
Mizusawa should have tried
for a 3 to 1 split.
The hazed early dawn light comes not from the moon
Then, it would have come down to luck.
They would have had a
50% chance of winning.
Hokuo wins
The fall paddy shacks have rough thatching
Mizusawa wins
Now, they can only win if
they take an opponent's card.
Crap...
It's basically impossible
for us to win now!
Only looking at her own cards      Can't see the cards that are further away
We were unprepared...
I never thought this might happen.
Our lack of experience in
team matches is showing!
This is the worst time for Hokuo's
karuta experience to pay off!
Huh?
The hazed early
dawn light
The fall paddy
The hazed early
dawn light
The fall paddy
Does this mean...
...it's really hard for
us to score three wins?
No way!  What do we do?  What do we do?
What am I doing...
I told our first-year
that I'd make him strong,
then I alone lost early on....
I'm pathetic!
They're all fighting!
Giving their all!
This is all my fault!
Practicing swings that reach my side?
Is Ayase planning to attack
her opponent's side?!
Mashima-senpai...
"The hazed early dawn light" and
"The fall paddy" are on the field.
The empty cards that
haven't been read are
"Long," "Impassioned Vows," "Like the,"
"The hazed field," "The fall wind"...
We can't move on "The hazed" or "The fall."
It all comes down to
the third syllable!
If "The hazed early" is read,
Chihaya will take the opponent's card!
If "The fall paddy" is read,
I'll take the opponent's card!
We're not giving up!
Mizusawa will take three wins!
We'll be the champions!
Long last we meet...
Like the sound of someone
knocking on my door,
They're really trying to
take the opponent's cards?
Mizusawa is serious about attacking...
This isn't a typical luck-of-the-draw.
Unlike Mizusawa, none of us need
to attack the opponent's side.
We just have to focus on
protecting our own cards.
It's impossible to penetrate
that kind of defense!
Mashima must know that!
I'm taking it!
He has to!
...blown by the autumn wind.
The fall wind parts the wispy clouds
A fault...
One win for Mizusawa!
That wasn't just a simple
mistake by Retro-kun.
Eyebrows' focus and
unwavering persistence
pushed Retro-kun into that error.
Luck-of-the-draw isn't about luck.
Luck doesn't decide a match!
Each school has one win.
It's an even match now.
What the hell, Retro?!
First, you lied about
your retrot cards.
Now, you made a mistake that
ruined our perfect split!
What if we lose?!
How are you going to make up for this?!
I'll sock him.
The two remaining teams get
to go to Nationals, right?
We don't need to try that hard, then.
I'll sock him.
I'll win...
I'll win and sock Retro hard!
The Hokuo ace is also
practicing offensive swings.
He's going to attack.
Amakasu-kun...
Cover my card on "The."
If the next syllable is "fall," I attack.
If it's "The hazed field," I cover,
and if it's "The hazed
early," I clamp down.
There's no such thing
as a throw-away match!
We're Hokuo!
Hokuo wins!
Amakasu...
Be careful, Amakasu!
There are people...
to reveal moonlight, clear and bright.
capable of clearing their
minds in this situation.
The hazed early dawn light
comes not from the moon
Who got it?!  Who got the card?!
I can't tell!  They moved too fast!
Who got it?!
Who moved faster?!
It's mine!  I moved faster!
No.
I touched it first!
Ref!
No.
It was
at the same time.
Huh?
In that case, it goes to
the side the card was on.
Amakasu-kun wins.
Thank you very much.
Hokuo Academy wins the Tokyo regional
over Mizusawa High School 3-2!
Thank you very much.
Wow, that was an incredible final.
That was exciting.
That was a once-in-a-decade
kind of match.
Amakasu.
Is Hokuo the strongest team in Tokyo?
No.
On the last card, I only moved
because I felt Ayase move.
If it had been "The hazed field,"
I would have committed a fault.
I couldn't hear a thing.
After that match, I can't say that
Hokuo is the strongest team.
Lame.
If you can't be the
strongest team in Tokyo,
show me that you're the
strongest team in Japan.
Sudo-san...
I'll be coming to watch on your budget.
Shouldn't we wake up Ayase?
Yes, the closing ceremony's
about to begin.
E-Everyone!  I'm sorry!
It's all because I screwed up!
Because I lost first!
Chihaya...
Th-That was fun!
That was the most fun we've had!
Five matches is really difficult.
Huh?  Where's Tsukuba?
He said he was going somewhere
with his brothers.
They're really close.
Guys!  We start practicing
for Nationals tomorrow!
Chihaya!
Let everyone rest for a day.
What?!
Huh?  Aren't you going
this way, Hanano-san?
Sorry, I have something to do.
What?!  You want to join
the Shiranami society!
All four of you?!
Really?!
Yes, please accept us.
What's a karuta society?
Can we become strong?
I'm gonna become a Master.
Oh, we meet again.
Will you be number five?
Bye!
We start practicing for
Nationals in two days!
Oh, it's Arata!
An e-mail from Arata!
Did you have fun at the
high school regional final?
Why are you crying?
It was really fun.
Arata.
That match was the most
fun I've ever had,
and it was the most
difficult loss I've ever had.