The meteor shower.
What are you talking about?
We haven't seen it once
since the saucer came.
Even if we could,
it's still half a month away.
No.
Togawa-san's been waiting for me.
Since that day seven years ago.
Please everyone,
let's enter the Hokubi Festival.
What She Believes
Later, Mizusaka.
Yeah, see you.
Hey, are you seriously
entering the Hokubi Festival?
Don't you have to get
ready to study abroad?
Yeah.
But she's kind of a friend.
Shione, do you have plans later?
Why do you ask?
Well...
I want to discuss something with you.
Is that good?
Hokubi Festival Participation Form
It's fine.
Really?
It's not a big deal.
Leave the rest to me!
Got funding!
That was too fast.
Also, I wrote Shione's name
down as a participant.
Wait, what's this about?
The Hokubi Festival, of course.
Hey...
Let's do it, the five of us.
Is this what you wanted to discuss?
No?
Third years are supposed
to join independently.
Wait.
Hey.
Now that we're all here, let's go.
I said—
Sorry, Togawa.
She's always been like this, remember?
So where are we going?
Shopping.
What are those for?
I think they go on your fridge.
I got dragged out here suddenly.
What do you expect me to do?
I know, it must be a pain.
It's your sister's fault.
Not Yuzuki.
It was Komiya's idea.
Nonoka?
What does she want?
How would I know?
You'd know, wouldn't you?
Why?
You used to be really close.
Did you get in a fight?
Does it matter?
I used to be like that, too.
It tends to be something really
stupid that sets it off.
How would you know?
I don't even know what we're making.
How would I know what to look for?
Oh, Komiya did all this
research by herself, too.
Let's make a planetarium!
A planetarium.
That's that.
Prep Room 3
We're just starting.
What?
I'm tired...
It's getting late.
Let's start working tomorrow.
Agreed.
Togawa-san, thanks for coming.
Shione, if you don't mind, see you—
See you tomorrow.
Welcome home!
Noel, I'm home.
Shorty?
Noel, you were waiting?!
We're back, Noel.
Oh, right.
Here.
You should come if you can.
Hokubi Festival?
No fair, Koharu.
Mine's a special golden ticket.
Mine, too.
You can give it to friends and family.
Nonoka!
I missed my chance to give her one.
So many!
But I can't go.
Why not?
I'm the saucer.
Things get bad when I'm
far from the saucer.
Things get bad?
Nonoka, did you watch the
meteor shower with Shione?
No.
But
I think we'll be able to.
Really?
Can Shione smile with you guys, too?
Thanks to your message.
Oh, yeah. The fridge is full today.
I'll make you anything you want.
Really? How about a rice omelet?
Of course.
I'm going to draw on
it with the ketchup.
Prep Room 3
There.
It's kind of shoddy looking.
You don't get it, Souta.
This prototype may not look like much,
but it took a lot of effort
and spare time to make.
First, the light bulb.
Is this really going to work?
We put a plastic sheet over this light
bulb. It has the Kiriyako City sky on it.
It should, I think.
Let's try it.
It has to be darker.
Couldn't we use that
thing you made, Togawa?
Yep, this should work.
I helped, so I'm looking, too.
Come on, Yuzuki, everyone else helped, too.
Right, Shione?
I didn't really.
If it works, let's all take turns.
Like I said, I—
Hey, hurry up.
Okay.
I'm turning on the switch.
Huh?
What's wrong?
It's not bright enough.
I think it just needs more power.
No, that probably wouldn't be...
Give it to me.
No, Yuzuki!
Just give it to me!
Hey, are they okay?
Max power!
Hey!
Water! Firetruck!
Right!
No, cut the power first!
I'm saved.
I'm back!
Koharu, wait!
Sorry.
I was the one that messed up.
No worries.
So do you always have these with you?
I was hoping to eat
with you guys today.
It's good!
Let's eat together.
Come over here.
This brings back memories, though.
The observatory.
Yeah, Nonoka said we
should call the saucer.
Remember we all got prepared,
like we did today?
We talked about how we should do it,
and we tried all sorts of things.
It was pretty stupid in retrospect.
It was so fun.
And a saucer actually came.
Did we really call that saucer?
Togawa-san?
Togawa-san!
I'm leaving.
Your friends?
Yeah.
But we're in different schools,
so we can only meet here.
Yuzuki and Souta are twins,
but they're really different.
But they're really close.
Koharu's really, really nice.
And Shione.
Shione's friends with Mom, too.
We're going to watch the stars together.
The stars?
Yeah.
We promised to watch
the meteor shower.
Together.
Meteor shower?
Are you staying here, Noel?
Why do you ask?
If Shione comes,
can you tell her something?
I won't be able to meet her,
but I'll be back.
I'll come back right away.
So...
Tell her when I do, let's watch
the meteor shower together.
Okay.
Leave it to me.
Thanks.
I was supposed to tell her myself.
I don't want to say bye.
Nonoka, does it hurt somewhere?
How can you make it better?
I know!
I'll teach you, too.
Mom's song.
Keep Out
Nonoka?
Nonoka!
Who are you?
Are you Shione?
Yeah.
How do you know that song?
Where's Nonoka?
Nonoka went far away.
What do you mean?
But Nonoka told me
that she's coming back right away,
so she wants to watch the
meteor shower with you.
Really?
I'm glad.
Hokubi
Festival
Have this.
Thank you.
What?
But I can't go.
Why not?
Because I'm the saucer.
Things get bad when I'm
far from the saucer.
Can you get in without this?
Aren't you going to watch the
meteor shower with Nonoka?
Is it because of me?
Is it because I didn't
explain it to you properly?
No, you did fine.
Then why?
Can't you smile together?
I told you.
It's because Nonoka's a liar.
Nonoka's not a liar.
I always believed her.
Nonoka's coming now, right?
We're going to watch the meteor
shower together, right?
What did you come back
for after all this time?
I always believed her, too.
Then...
Shione.
I'm scared.
I'm afraid of my trust being betrayed.
Nonoka came back, like she promised.
So don't be scared.
I know.
It's my fault for not being
able to trust her completely.
It's because I changed.
No.
That's not true.
You all haven't changed.
Nonoka kept her promise, so now
it's my turn to grant your wish.
Noel?
Shione, let's watch the
meteor shower together.
We'll get a good view this year.
Hey, Shione.
Let me on.
Now's a good time,
so tell me the truth.
What?
What else?
Do you like her or not?
I'm talking about Nonoka.
Togawa-san.
You made this?
I got a lot of help from everyone.
It's not quite a meteor shower,
but I couldn't keep my promise, so...
You're right.
It's not the same as back then.
I knew that, so why did I wait?
So stupid.
Togawa-san!
I mean, Shione.
What did you come back for,
after all this time?
I'd like to say it's to
keep my promise to you,
but I'd really forgotten about
this town until I met Noel.
Not just you.
Even Yuzuki and Koharu and Souta.
I've been trying not to
remember those times.
If it weren't for Noel, I probably
wouldn't have even thought about it.
I'm so awful.
But I want to watch a
meteor shower with you.
That feeling's always been here.
It hasn't changed.
And this, too.
You're my precious, precious friend.
I'm sorry, Nonoka.
I'm the one that's awful.
I couldn't trust my beloved friend.
Even though you came back.
And about Noel.
I want to watch the meteor
shower with you this year.
I want to be friends with you again.
That's not right.
My name is Togawa Shione.
Please be my friend.
Okay.
A planetarium in place
of a meteor shower, huh?
We'll get a good view this year.
I'm the saucer.
Noel.
Is Shione coming today?
Yeah, she said she'll help.
That's good.
Yes?
Shione.
Come in.
You were the same Nonoka
that I knew before.
But
we can't be together anymore.
Next episode of Celestial Method:
"The Meaning of Goodbye."
Enjoy.
The Meaning of Goodbye