Akatsuki
Race/ Human
Assassin, Lv. 92
Log Horizon
An elemental blizzard attack...
And the Royal Guard's armor
is boosting all of his stats!
When you actually see it up close,
it really seems like cheating.
I'll ask again. Have you ever been in a raid?
Nope.
Me, neither.
I don't feel like facing the new year
on the cold Cathedral floor.
Right.
This is our first battle!
Yeah.
Target sighted.
Moving toward Old Ogawa Town, on Chuo Street.
Group C has made contact.
One healer present.
Group D is to rendezvous immediately.
All other groups are to remain on standby.
Group C is Akatsuki, right?
Yeah.
So far, it's gone according to plan.
Her detection abilities are crazy.
It's finally time!
Will you be okay, Kyouko?
I'm the athletic type, after all.
Let's go all-out!
All-out!
Akihabara Raid
Akihabara Raid.
Know your enemy.
Know exactly what he can and cannot do.
And face yourself.
Face your own weakness!
Death Stinger!
She hit him! That's a poison DoT!
I've always been ashamed of my small size.
But...
Your blood will be as dew on my blade, adventurer!
The gifts everyone gave me are supporting me.
Akatsuki!
I'm fine.
I'll end you!
Orion Delay Blow!
Get to the next area now!
Thanks!
Thank you!
You're running away, girl?
A raid in Akihabara?
When this was a game, I never
could've imagined that.
Viper's Trash!
Bloody Piercing!
Why aren't the other Royal Guards
coming to arrest Nelreth?
The system is set up so that
only we can be arrested.
Which is what makes it possible for
us to fight him in town, but...
You're still running, girl?
We'll slow him down a little here.
Get to the next area!
We're with you.
So don't worry, and smack him hard.
Got it!
Thanks!
For every adventurer within fifty meters,
Rugrius gets a boost to his stats.
That's why we've put a curfew in effect.
The only people in town are the twenty-four
members of the full raid.
We've formed them into small groups,
and put them as far apart as possible.
And Akatsuki is leading the
murderer through the city,
so that he passes through each area.
Contact
Kiting, in other words.
Each group will simultaneously heal
their allies and attack the enemy.
I can see why you're the training squad head
for the Yamato server's largest
combat guild, D.D.D.!
This plan is going to work!
Yes. Or it would, if this were a game.
But this isn't a game anymore.
Not every raid is designed so that it's possible to win.
The enemy has that katana, as well as
Royal Guard armor, and he can teleport.
He's entered the next area!
I'll rip you apart, adventurers.
Wait, Nelreth...
First, that girl.
And it gives him the knowledge and
experience of a Royal Guard.
There's no guarantee he will act the way we expect.
Rieze-san...
I'm sorry.
Is it okay if I complain for a bit?
I just realized
how terrifying it is
to involve someone else and not be able
to take responsibility for them...
That princess has faced this terror
since she was born, hasn't she?
I respect that.
That's true for everyone at the Round Table.
And you, too, right?
For now, it is.
For now, focus on your job.
Yeah.
Group D is to heal, and then
meet up with Group C again.
Group F is to change course.
Stand by at road D!
You're sure about this?
Yes.
This city will be defenseless
against external attacks.
It may not be able to stop internal fighting,
and the zone will become lawless.
Yes.
This failure is not only the
Kunie Clan's responsibility,
but that of all the People of the Land.
We need to do what we can
to apologize to the adventurers.
This time, that means shutting off the magic supply.
You may end up causing them greater trouble.
Don't worry.
As I've said before, the Round
Table has agreed to this.
As fellow citizens of Akihabara,
we'll do whatever it takes to
help you put a stop to this.
Very well.
Regardless of the cause of this,
it's true that the Kunie Clan has
failed to keep the city safe.
We've left a blotch on our several-century-long history
of operating the magic circle and protecting the city.
Then...
As you say,
we need to find something we can do and do it.
We need to take a step forward,
instead of rejecting you.
I'm sorry for testing you earlier.
And I'd like you to know I am in
your debt for this, Lenessia.
Of course, I'd prefer to pay
that debt to someone else.
Let us go, then.
What is this?
Come this way.
Yes.
Team J, get out of there.
I'll tell you where to rendezvous
after healing in a moment.
Team D will continue to its designated position.
Engage in approximately thirty seconds!
Are you okay, Marielle?
Just fine!
I could keep this up all night!
Why?
Sutu Inaw, why did you betray me?
Shut up!
Get back!
I'm not Rugrius!
Right!
No, this girl betrayed me!
Me, a proud hero!
Summon Servant: Golem!
Use him as a shield!
Thanks!
Heartbeat Healing!
Go!
It's warm.
Akatsuki
Race/ Human
Assassin, Lv. 92
Log Horizon
Status Effects
Phys Atk Up, Phys Def Up,
Dodge Up, Cold Res Up,
Regen
Thank you.
She's cute.
Combat Skill Summon: Lance Diesel!
You can do it!
Thanks!
Ten meters to the next area!
Just one more step...
Just one more step, and I think I can figure it out!
No!
Support can't get there in time!
I'm weak.
This katana wants your blood.
Faster...
Faster! Faster!
Faster!
What is this?
Akatsuki is multiplying...
What was that?
I wanted to go fast so badly,
I activated Hide Shadow.
I should only be able to use it when
moving around, but I did it anyway?
You learned a new skill
Teaching
Shadow Lurk
This is my Teaching...
A Teaching that belongs only to me.
Looks like she finally learned one.
Awesome, Akatsuki!
You can't learn the Teachings from someone else.
It's a state you reach after endlessly
facing yourself and training.
Akatsuki, good job!
How stupid.
You just forget what you knew from the game,
and use your abilities to their fullest.
That's all it was.
How stupid.
I sought power outside of myself.
Just like you.
But...
I'm different now.
I'm fine with being weak.
Embart Nelreth...
Rather than face yourself,
you sought cursed power,
and that power controlled you.
Which means your overwhelming strength
is much more fragile than my weakness!
Okay.
You got him!
What's this?
C-Can't get it out...
Like this? Huh?
Like this?!
Race/ Human
Assassin, Lv. 92
Akatsuki's HP is down to five percent!
And she's unarmed...
Marielle's almost out of MP, too.
She can't even heal properly!
Sorry... This is all I can do.
Really, I'm sorry.
Marielle, get out of here.
Team D, get there now!
We're on our way!
Run away and leave me here, Akatsuki!
Don't give up.
Status/ In Combat
Zone/ Akihabara
Skill Use Permitted
Tatara Amenoma
Lv. 90
Amenoma
Come to me.
Crawl to me if you have to.
Run!
Route change.
Team C is moving down Chuo Street,
toward Kandamyojin Street.
All teams, update your area positions.
Sutu Inaw, I'm right here.
Don't run anymore.
No... That isn't right.
You're the adventurer girl.
He isn't making any sense.
Get back, Marielle!
What's this?
The Screaming Sword Haganemushi?
No.
I reforged it into the "Haganemushi Tatara."
I've matched it to your size.
But...
I'm giving it to you.
Use my katana to defeat that thing.
The twenty-seventh maiden has arrived.
Defeating him won't end this.
I need to destroy Byakumaru.
Originally, Haganemushi had the effect
of lowering the condition of an
enemy weapon it touches.
I need to end this quickly
for everyone's sake!
Again?
No!
Senpuu Izuna!
Don't build up too much aggro.
I know!
Party Chat
Isami, how's the enemy's HP looking?
Um...
The bar is acting weird,
but it's around twenty percent.
I don't know the absolute value...
Understood.
Team C will swap Marielle and Nazuna.
Move.
Roger.
If the enemy's a raid boss, its attack
pattern should be changing soon.
Be careful.
Roger.
Team K is ready to move, as well.
Follow backup plan 6!
Got it!
That was quick. He broke through already?
Engage!
Thorn Bind Hostage!
Rapid Shot!
Now then, if you're Shiroe's friend,
you're my friend.
I'll have to help you.
What's wrong?
You're crying.
So this is a raid...
It's amazing, huh? Yeah.
While I'm at it, I'll show you my Teaching, too.
Divine Step!
What's this?
Walls of Purification are damage-blocking spells.
You're using them as steps in the air?
Is that how you saved me back there?
Yep.
It's just a different way to use them.
Stupid, huh?
You're right.
It looks more likely that he's about to die than
that he's about to change attack patterns.
You're done running around.
Three...
Two...
One...
Now!
Y-You're just outside the fifty-meter area...
Do it!
Freezing Liner!
I won't let you shed another drop
of my companions' blood!
Take this instead!
We did it!
You can't teleport.
We cut off your magic supply.
That armor is just a hunk of metal.
Girl...
Curse you!
Curse you, adventurer!
Haganemushi Tatara
Effect/ Haganemushi Tatara
Steals stamina from an enemy's weapon
and armor when used in physical attacks.
The flavor text has been rewritten...
"Haganemushi Tatara."
"Reforged by Tatara, the blacksmith of Amenoma,
for the personal use of a quiet, unsocial wielder.
That this earnest girl may go forward
without bending or breaking,
repelling evil curses and this world's tragedies,
so that man may support blade,
and blade support man."
It's over, isn't it?
Yes. His remaining HP didn't matter.
We were only after that cursed katana.
It was a wonderful plan.
Okay!
Good work. I'm impressed.
You should be.
Girls really are strong, aren't they, Shiro?
Okay, we have New Year's soba here!
Lots of desserts, too!
Oh, wow! This is amazing!
I've never been to a pajama party before.
Me, neither.
Oh, no!
If I eat it all, I'll get fat!
But I'll eat it today anyway.
It's like a red vs. white party!
I know you'll all be on the red
team, so should I be white?
The curfew in Akihabara's been lifted,
and everyone's having a party outside.
Now Minori and the others will
be able to come back.
By the way, um...
I don't think you need to worry.
Seeing everyone in their pajamas
just knocked all her screws loose.
Right...
Akatsuki, thank you.
I should thank you, Lenessia.
My lord, protecting someone means
giving them a place to belong.
Giving them a place where they can be happy.
I finally understand.
That's why you were working so hard.
I miss you.
Shiroe
Lv.92
Log Horizon
Akatsuki?
Hello?
M-My lord?
What is it?
Weren't we supposed to not use telepathy?
That's true, but...
It's rare for you to break your own rules...
Is that how people think of me?
Yep!
You're a stiff blockhead!
It went well, didn't it, Akatsuki?
Congratulations.
My lord...
We still have some work to do here.
But we won't give up, either.
We're about to give it another retry.
On Christmas Eve night, Shiroe and the others died.
The rules have changed.
This world isn't a game anymore.
Their time is over.
They've been rejected.
Shiroe loses his physical body and
wanders a town of memories.
On a moonlit beach, he encounters Akatsuki.
Next time: The Changing Battlefield.
The Changing Battlefield
Rise up once more.