What's that?
A tatami?
Isn't that Ayase Chihaya?
Ayase?
You know?
The one who was putting up
that karuta club poster.
Oh, "Beauty in vain."
Isn't that Mashima from
Class 1 with her?
Mashima, as in the one who had
the top score in our grade on the last test?
Huh? A karuta club?
When they're both so famous...
All in vain...
Club in vain...
Chihaya, we're attracting
too much attention.
Hey, where's Oe-san?
She was here a moment ago...
Is she skipping practice again?
The captain will have a fit.
So spring ends and summer comes
now white robes hang to
dry on Mount Amanokagu
Oe-san! Where did you go?
Oe-san!
The upperclassmen are throwing a fit!
I-I'm sorry!
Chihaya Furu
Verse 6
Now
Bloom
Inside
the
Ninefold
Palace
This is it.
Huh?
We finally made it!
This is our clubroom?
Yeah.
I kept begging the Empress and
she finally gave it to us.
It's a storage room.
There's dust everywhere.
Don't complain!
It's quiet.
Perfect for playing karuta!
Okay, back we go!
We need three more!
What? This is enough...
How can you say that,
after the nice man agreed
to share these with us?!
Once we have five members,
we'll be recognized as an official club,
and they'll even assign us a teacher!
Can we even find three more people?
We can!
We absolutely can!
Now look, Chihaya.
Hmm?
Do we really need more members?
I was pretty surprised.
I never knew that was how you felt.
If I can be the best in
the world at something,
I think it's worth a shot.
Your goal is to become the Queen, right?
Huh?
Y-Yeah...
You're not serious about
this at all, are you?!
You were just following Arata's lead!
Anyway!
We have to carry three
more tatami mats over!
Then we practice!
Right. Yeah, yeah.
What's Oe-san like?
Archery Club
No idea. She's always
reading old books by herself.
She was born in the wrong era.
I'm sorry,
but I can't do it!
Why must I run in a hakama?
That would be so embarrassing!
And I'll never be able to
hit a target with an arrow!
I just want to wear
traditional clothes!
Let's start a competitive karuta club!
Please come see Ayase Chihaya in class 1-2!!
Ayase Chihaya-san in class 1-2...
The lovely girl who
turns heads everywhere
is looking for people who know
the poems of the Hundred Poets.
Oh, dear. You took
another card off me.
You're still very strong, Lady Chihaya.
I should have knocked
on this door instead!
I thought that Ms. Miyauchi was
using the old student council room.
Oh, no...
What if they already
have too many members?
when people and grass grow scarce
Rain takes...
leaving a hovering mist
above the trees and grass
Huh?!
You're too good at
first-syllable cards.
Huh? Huh?
The storm blasts...
Wait... What...
I wish I could show...
What is this?
My fear is not of...
Don't tell me that...
...this is karuta?!
Thank you very much!
I won!
But you're actually pretty good.
You took a bunch of cards
in the first half.
I think I've figured out
why you always start slow.
Huh?
You rely on the advantage
of your ears so much
that you haven't learned how
to memorize card positions.
You still can't memorize
where the cards are.
That's not true.
Today was just a fluke.
I have no trouble in the first
half at the Shiranami Society.
You've only been practicing at
the Shiranami Society, right?
People who train together tend to use the
same positioning techniques, so it's easier.
Against me, you kept
touching the wrong cards.
So in other words,
you're an idiot.
Yet you lost to that idiot!
Idiot!
You even talk like an idiot, idiot.
Oh?
Huh?
Welcome!
Wait!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Why are you running away?!
Are you here because you're
interested in karuta?!
Do you like karuta?!
Y-Yes, I guess...
As you already know,
the Ogura Hundred Poets lived
during the Kamakura period.
Fujiwara no Teika
compiled them by taking one poem
each from 100 of the best poets,
in chronological order from
Emperor Tenji to the Retired Emperor Juntoku
to decorate the sliding doors
at the Ogura mountain villa,
the summer home of the general
and poet Utsunomiya Yoritsuna.
I love the backstory.
Many of the selected poems
were ornamental in nature,
because they were meant
to be used as decoration.
His judgment was wonderful!
Seventy-nine male poets!
Twenty-one female poets!
I paid particular attention
to the poems by the women!
You can feel the seasons
and modesty in a way
that can't be found in modern poetry!
The beauty in each word
is just as fresh as it
was a thousand years ago!
I still haven't found the words
to express the rush of
emotion they bring me!
R-Right!
So!
Do you like competitive karuta?
Do you wear hakama?
Hakama?
I've never worn one before.
You haven't either, Taichi?
Huh? Yeah...
Most people don't wear them.
Why?!
Only members of the imperial
court dabble in poetry!
I wouldn't expect you
to wear junihitoe,
but you should at least wear a hakama!
The kendo club and
archery club require hakama!
Wh—
Why don't we wear them?
Because they're expensive?
It's a lot of effort to wear one.
My family has owned a traditional
clothing shop for many generations.
I love kimono.
I want everyone to understand
how wonderful they are,
but we can only sell cheap yukatas...
Our business is so bad that
we can't even afford a model
for next year's catalog!
If I won't be able to wear a hakama,
I might as well stay
in the archery club.
I apologize for interrupting you.
Her love of karuta is
completely different.
We don't even pay any attention
to the poems anymore.
You probably don't know the
meaning of most of them.
She isn't cut out to play
competitive karuta.
She's so adorable.
Hey, look.
There she is!
Wow, you read really hard books.
A-Ayase-san!
I asked one of the girls
in the archery club.
Your name is Oe Kanade, right?
So you're Kana.
You like karuta, right?
Let's play karuta together.
Yamamori Masao
Higashiyama Culture and Modern Japan
My love for karuta is fundamentally
different from yours.
I'm not interested in a
sport with no emotion.
But Kana-chan, I'm also...
If you'll excuse me...
Huh?
Kana-chan?
The first collection of laws,
the Omi code, was created at
the order of Emperor Tenji.
In 670, there was a national
census released as the Kogo...
Kana-chan!
Hey, why don't you come watch us play?
I have archery practice.
Wait, Kana-chan!
Taichi...
There's no point in pestering
someone who doesn't want to join.
But she loves karuta so much...
Like I said yesterday,
she's not cut out for it.
Oe Traditional Clothing
Kanade, I'm going to a
neighborhood meeting,
so watch the store for me.
Okay!
Explanation for Ogura Hundred Poets
Would the mountain cherry
blossoms return my affection,
for there is no one else out here
Ayase-san.
It's beautiful.
I'm starting to understand
why you like kimono.
Is this about the karuta club again?
Hmm?
Well, you seem to like karuta.
As I said earlier,
my love is fundamentally
different from yours.
But I also have a poem I really love.
Impassionate gods have never seen
the red that is the Tatsuta River
I even know what it means.
It's talking about how the
Tatsuta River is so beautiful
when it's completely red.
I read it in a book.
It must look something like this.
Classic poetry becomes fascinating when
you know the history behind each poem.
Huh?
I believe that this poem
is about passionate love.
Huh? Love?
It's not about scenery?!
That would be the universal
interpretation,
but did you know that
Nijo no Kisaki was in love
with Ariwara no Narihira
before she married the emperor?
This is a very
famous
story.
N-No...
This poem was displayed on a
folding screen in the palace.
Some accounts say that Nijo no Kisaki
was the one who requested the poem.
I like how Narihira concealed his
passion for her in a scenic rendering
since he wasn't able
to forget about her.
"Impassionate" is a decorative word
for gods that implies great force.
The red river can be interpreted
as an autumn scene or a suicide,
but I believe that the crimson leaves
represent a love that never faded.
the red that is the Tatsuta River
When you look at it that way,
the card with its black letters
becomes deep red,
don't you think?
Incredible...
Huh?
Incredible!
Incredible! Incredible! Incredible!
Teach me more, Kana-chan!
Huh?
Starting from The Autumn Paddy!
All one hundred poems?
Uh-huh!
This poem is supposed to have
been written by Emperor Tenji.
Huh? It wasn't?
Yes, it's believed that this was
edited from an anonymous poem
in the Collection of
Ten Thousand Leaves.
Oh...
Fujiwara no Teika, the person
who compiled the Hundred Poets,
would have known that...
The autumn paddy shacks
have rough thatching
as my sleeves are wet with dew
A "paddy shack" is a small
cabin for farmers.
When the farmers rest under the
rough roof of sedge and straw,
they wake up to discover that
their sleeves are wet with dew.
So Fujiwara no Teika may
have started with this poem
to convey the idea of an ideal emperor
who understood the hard
work of the farmers.
Oh...
Next one!
So spring ends please!
In the past, when people
unpacked their winter clothes,
they would hang their
summer clothes out to dry.
The green mountains
and white clothes...
There is only a brief pause
between the verses...
As the slightest breeze will make
the slender bamboo shake...
Mugwort was used for moxibustion.
Oh! Hence the burning feelings part!
When I must hide
mugwort = moxibustion
I never knew...
The false rooster's crow
is an expression from
I never knew!
the Records of the Grand Historian.
Here, shadow actually means light. So the moonlight is...
There is a rich and colorful world behind each card!
Here, the autumn scenery
is green instead of red,
which means these are evergreens...
I never knew!
I had no idea!
Yamamori Masao
Higashiyama Culture and Modern Japan
She's always reading
old books by herself.
A classical literature geek?
She was born in the wrong age.
Explanation for Ogura Hundred Poets
Teach me, Kana-chan!
Teach me more!
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
Like the sound of someone
knocking on my door...
The night was young...
Though I prayed
Before, I only recognized
the cards by sound...
but you can also recognize
them by their meaning!
Look!
Every card is a different color!
I win!
Oh, man...
You're on a roll today.
Have you been doing
drills or something?
Kana-chan.
The person who taught me karuta
said that I should become
friends with the cards.
You're already friends with
all one hundred cards.
You can become strong.
O-On one condition...
Okay! Relax and smile!
P-Promise?
Promise that you'll
join the karuta club?
No changing your mind!
And during matches,
we all have to wear hakama.
Wh-What if we don't have one?
We can rent them.
Wait, stop!
But why were you trying
so hard to recruit me?
You don't need other
people to play karuta.
Well, I guess we can practice.
We can start with how
to place the cards...
First, can we do
something about this room?
Huh?
A house left to the weeds...
As I said the other day,
only members of the imperial
court dabble in poetry.
This dusty room is not
appropriate for-
Okay, let's!
Can't we just keep the
tatami mats clean?
Okay, let's go borrow
the cleaning stuff.
Yes!
Come on!
Hurry up, Taichi!
Yeah, yeah...
I want to play karuta
with Arata again.
I want him to know
that karuta is fun...
That it's fun when you're with friends.
Then we'll start with
how to place the cards.
Yes!
Our new friend, Kana-chan
taught me something new.
Chihaya furu is a poem
about deep red love!