Ragna-mail connector, purge.
Deploy pressure barriers.
Dragonium reactor, engage.
Connect D-brane resonator.
Begin feeding all power.
The preparations are complete.
But...
Ange isn't here.
Why did you let her go?
Jealousy?
Why do you need Ange?
I've promised you my loyalty, Embryo-sama.
I fought for you.
Yet it's Ange again?
Are you done with me?
It's strong, intelligent women
that will create my new world.
That's why I chose you.
I chose Ange for the same reason.
I have no use for foolish women.
Ange will surely come here...
If only to kill me.
Salia, if you were truly
intelligent and strong,
you would know what to do.
I'll capture Ange and make her submit.
I'm hoping you do, my Salia.
Replace the damaged plating on the laser.
Prioritize resupplying on Rosalie's machine.
Do a damage check on Hilda's machine.
Yes, ma'am.
Marika.
Marika!
Merge the two Earths?
The Ragna-mails are the regulators,
and Aura is the energy source.
Embryo is going to merge the
two Earths, space-time and all.
He'll make a new Earth.
She can't take anymore.
She needs to rest.
If the two Earths were to merge,
everything would be destroyed.
We must hurry.
Commander, the People of Aura
wish for an alliance with the Norma.
An alliance?
It'll be difficult to penetrate Embryo's
defenses with our Ryushinki alone.
I imagine your situation is much the same.
It's true that we can't do anything
against their Ragna-mails alone.
Fine.
We can form an alliance.
But only once Ange is back.
Oh? Ange isn't back?
Dear, oh dear, where has my wife gone?
Officer?
No, that's...
Embryo.
Embryo, you say?
Vulcan!
Have you lost it?!
She's only being manipulated.
What?
Chasing after a woman who left you?
That's pathetic, Sir Tuner.
The princess of the DRAGONs?
There's no rush.
Ange and I will be seeing you soon enough...
To have your head.
Oh?
Officer!
Commander.
It seems Embryo is desperate to find Ange.
Can you avoid his notice and rescue her?
Make no mistake, Ange will return.
H-How do you know that?
Because she's my friend.
Dear, oh dear. What a barbaric woman.
Embryo-san.
What is it, Ersha?
The preschool children...
Please, bring them back to life again.
I can't do that.
The new world is for my new humanity.
We can't bring those girls there.
But...
I will have you be a mother to the
new humanity of my new world.
You understand, don't you, Ersha?
No.
No!
Those children!
Those children are my everything!
I don't care what happens to me.
Please!
I thought you were a more intelligent woman.
Do not trouble me further.
I'm busy.
Are we really going to wait for Ange?
The world's in peril.
What are we going to do?
I'm thinking about it.
You're only thinking about Ange.
What can we do without Ange and the Villkiss?
Chris took us down by herself.
I'm going with the DRAGONs.
I'll do anything, if it means killing Chris.
We have to do it.
For Marika.
Rosalie...
How?
How did it end up this way?
Tell me, Hilda.
I'm too stupid to understand.
I thought I'd always be friends with Chris.
I heard it was Chris that
felled the Villkiss.
What?
She shot down the Villkiss
and murdered a new recruit.
Embryo's men are exemplary.
The soldiers and the commander alike.
What are you trying to say?
Well, if we'd been nicer to Salia,
she might have never become an enemy.
It was all a lie.
A peaceful world, a fair life...
I'm sorry, everyone.
Just as it was that day...
When I went home, you were always there.
When I got home, Momoka, you were...
Yet...
I'll avenge you, Alektra!
"Ange will surely come here."
"I'm hoping you do, my Salia," he says.
You liar.
But Ange, if you're gone,
and if he understands that I'm stronger,
Embryo-sama will accept me.
He'll accept my value.
If I can achieve that much,
I don't need anything else.
The DRAGONs' voices interfere
with Mana and drive humans mad.
That's why only the Norma could fight them,
because they have no Mana.
I was never told about that!
This world is full of lies.
But Normas, who could destroy Mana,
would expose all those lies.
That's why they were oppressed and isolated.
The humans were programmed
to instinctively despise the Norma.
If that's true, then we're all just puppets!
What just happened?
I don't know, the Light of Mana—
Help...
Hold on, I'm calling for help.
What's going on?!
Why can't I use my Mana?
So it begins.
The destruction and
recreation of the world...
And in what manner are
we to greet this new world?
We must escape quickly, or we'll
be caught in the space-time merger.
Who said you'd be going?
The new world will be
made by intelligent women.
You failures will take responsibility
for plunging this world into chaos.
Embryo-sama.
Are you abandoning us?
What's happening?
Huh?
Anyone?
I'm the First Princess...
No, I'm Queen Emperor Sylvia I!
Come help me immediately!
Ersha.
Why do you look like that?
It's nothing.
We're moving out soon.
Where are you going?
I don't know anymore.
Those children were all I had.
That's why he manipulated me.
I'm an empty, shallow whore
with nothing left to live for.
Hey, are you okay with this?
With having to kill your friends?
Hilda-chan and Rosalie-chan?
Friends?
Them?
I hope I do!
I see.
Water...
Morgan-san died.
I'm alone now.
Trying to fight Embryo was futile.
As was trying to destroy the world.
No matter what, I'm alone.
I'll go crazy from the loneliness.
People aren't meant to live alone.
Tusk...
A girl washed up today,
along with the Villkiss.
She's pretty violent,
and she doesn't listen to
what anyone has to say,
but Ange is light.
She's light, shining in
from the outside world.
Dad, Mom, I finally found her.
"Protect her. That's my duty..."
"Mine alone."
He always protected me.
Yet...
Come back to me, Tusk.
Come here, Momoka.
Don't leave me alone.
Momoka. Tusk.
You need to live on.
Pathetic.
I can't even die by myself.
It's pretty.
You're even prettier.
Idiot.
Why did you...
Because I'm your knight.
Were you really okay with that?
With losing everything for your duty?
What kind of world were you hoping for?
I'm just hoping we'll
get to enjoy peace someday.
I'll be back for you.
What's the point if you're not here anymore?
I love you.
If I knew this would happen,
I would've let him go all the way.
Really?
Thank goodness you're okay.
Why?
I told you, Ange's knight is invincible.
Tusk?
Yeah.
Tusk is dead.
You're one of Embryo's illusions!
I'm not.
You aren't injured from the explosion.
You don't have your gunshot wounds.
I'm alive.
I don't believe it.
Tusk is dead!
What?!
I won't believe it.
Sorry.
Ange, what are you—
I'm going to make sure.
Find out? What?
Don't talk. Please.
Can you hear me? Ersha here.
A white bra?!
No, it's a white flag.
Ersha here.
I surrender.
It's pretty.
Yeah.
A lot more than last time.
I was trying to kill myself.
Huh?
People aren't meant to live alone.
You read my journal.
You can't do anything when you're alone, huh?
You can't insult each other.
You can't hold each other.
You really weren't brought
back to life, were you?
I'm alive. I am.
Are you satisfied?
I have no more regrets.
That's not good.
We're just getting started.
It's strange.
Everything looks like it's brand new.
That pervert stalker asked me...
...to destroy the world and make a new one.
But I like this world.
No matter how incomplete and foolish it is,
I like this world.
I'm the same.
No matter what.
Because you're my knight?
Because I love you.
We have to protect this world.
We have to live...
With the lives Momoka protected for us.
I've been waiting for you!
Today's menu is smoked river fish,
berry and mushroom potage,
brawn with crimson glory vine sauce.
I highly recommend this potage.
It was left to stew for about twelve hours.
Twelve hours...
Wh-Why's Momoka...
It's all thanks to this frying pan.
You sure are my top maid.
Yes, Angelise-sama.
Oh, Princess.
I can't use Mana anymore.
What is that?
Embryo's beginning the destruction
and recreation of the world.
What's this?
It's Mom's machine.
Let's go, Ange.
First, we have to retrieve the Villkiss.
I don't think that'll be necessary.
Come, Villkiss.
Let's go.
Next Episode
I'm back, Ange!
You changed into flameproof clothing
at the exact instant the explosion happened?!
That's such a convenient plot twist!
Whatever, I'm a convenient person!
The Warped World
You really were a ninja.