Hey, are we there yet?
It's just a little farther, Ben-chan.
This guy's nice and quiet
when he's hung over.
Unbelievable.
You're eager, aren't you?
Yukimura-sama, I am glad
you are all right.
Yes. Thanks for looking
after the castle, Sasuke.
I'm home, Sasuke.
W-Welcome back.
Who is that?
He's called Benmaru-kun.
Yukimura-sama hired him.
We've got a new old guy, too.
Don't call me an old guy.
Who is she?
That's Veronica.
Sasuke, where's Anastasia?
Ana is patrolling the grounds.
She will be back tonight.
I see.
I guess we'll have to wait
until tomorrow to meet.
Meet?
Why do we have to do that?
I finally gathered all of you.
One brave warrior for
each of my ten fingers.
The True Face of Ice
My bed!
Welcome home.
Ana!
How was Kyoto? Did you have fun?
Yeah. We ran into some trouble, though.
Oh.
What?
I didn't get to buy you any gifts. Sorry.
That's too bad.
I'm sorry.
I won't forgive you.
What?
Unless you tell me all about your trip.
And I shared a fish with Veronica.
What? Who's that?
Veronica's like a cat,
except she's not a cat.
She's huge.
Yukimura-sama decided to bring
the pirate and Ben-chan.
I think he'll introduce
them to you tomorrow.
Our group's gotten quite big.
You're right. We're like a big family.
I wonder if this is what you'd call a home.
It feels so cozy being with everyone.
Right, Ana?
Yeah.
I'm not looking for male company tonight.
If you knew I was here,
you should've said so.
Are you going to sleep with me tonight?
I'll kill you.
Then what do you want?
What's this business...
...about having one warrior
for each of your ten fingers?
I'm sick of you blowing us off.
Let's talk man to man.
They're my brave and powerful warriors.
I already know that.
Besides, that's just a front.
Why have you gathered us?
With ten men, I can rule the world.
Like hell you can, you idiot!
Would you prefer to do the job yourself?
What are you drawing?
This.
It's just a yin-yang.
There's nothing unusual about it.
But what are these circles around it?
This symbol represents the ten primordial
elements that make up the universe.
It's in the Sanada family book of secrets.
Earth, metal, thunder, fire, wind,
ice, water, grass, light, and dark.
He who controls the power of these
elements will change the world.
That's what you all are.
Seikai of the Earth,
who causes the ground to quake.
Juzo of Metal,
who fights with a metal gun.
Jinpachi of Thunder,
who summons lightning.
Benmaru of Fire,
who knows about explosives.
Kamanosuke of the Wind,
who controls the wind.
Sasuke of the Grass,
whose playground is the forest.
Finally, there's Anastasia of Ice,
and Rokuro of the Water,
who recalls everything just as
the water's surface reflects all.
Your reactions are
quicker than I thought.
What do you think you're doing, Ana?
Surely there is a more
appropriate time for pranks.
Pranks?
I want you, Unno Rokuro.
The Ten Elements.
I guess they do fit.
What am I, then? Darkness?
No, you're this.
You are the Light, Saizo.
That's impossible! That doesn't fit me!
What, then? That would
mean Darkness is...
It's Isanami.
Hold on! That makes even less sense!
You've seen it, too. Isanami's power.
That's the power of her hairpin!
Let me see that secret book of whatever!
It's gone. I burned it.
What?
A lot of men would like to
get their hands on the book.
I had Rokuro memorize its contents.
Rokuro-san, huh?
Y-You mean my right eye?
I'll be taking that.
Why are you doing this?
I told you.
I want that eye of yours
that remembers everything.
You can't move now. Just hand it over.
I won't hurt you.
I will not let you take it.
I'd rather destroy it
than let you steal it.
You bastard.
Rokuro.
What are you?
What am I? A ninja.
Annoying creature!
If you get in my way, I'll kill you.
Her intent to kill is real.
What is all this racket?!
Lord Rokuro?
You! Wait!
Get Rokuro.
This is...
Lord Rokuro, wake up!
What? What's going on?
Who was that lady?
Benmaru, get Yukimura-sama. Quickly!
Got it!
Ana?
Ana, stop.
Iga Ice Technique.
Hyoso!
You can't escape now.
I'll freeze you to your core.
You hesitated, didn't you?
You're a fool.
A naïve little boy like you
can't truly understand a ninja.
I liked you, too. How unfortunate.
You already noticed?
What's going on, Ana?!
Who knows?
What are you doing?
What's wrong? Are you fighting?
There's no such thing as a cozy place.
Huh?
This is...
The kunai was poisoned.
Rokuro!
Go boil some water.
Bring me an antidote, too.
Yes, sir!
Friends? Family?
What you call home is a lie.
This world is simply kill or be killed.
Sasuke!
Iga Ice Technique.
Kesshojin!
My lord.
Just rest.
I am sorry.
Don't be sorry.
You must not let anyone
touch your right eye.
Yes, sir.
You kept your promise to me.
I cannot say I kept it since I lost my eye.
You're too serious.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Why don't you explain yourself, Ana?
Are you so stupid you need me
to explain it to you, Saizo?
You're a spy, aren't you?
You finally noticed?
I'm not one of Sanada's ninjas.
I serve another master.
You can only be so much
of a coward, Saizo.
Oh, I'm sorry. Did I upset you?
Yeah, I'm pissed...
At how clouded my eyes were.
You were just doing your job. That's all.
And now I...
...will do mine, as well.
If you withdraw now, you won't have to.
I don't know what you're after,
but I won't let you get away with
any information about Sanada.
You won't leave this place alive.
That's quite the line!
He's fast.
He doesn't hesitate like Sasuke.
At this rate...
Ninpo Hayabusa Otoshi!
Iga Ice Technique.
Ninpo Kirigakure Style.
Saihyozan!
Zekkai!
There's nothing scary about your ice
if I break it before it hardens.
I haven't known you since
we were kids for nothing.
Is that so?
Now, let's hear you talk.
That blood lust...
Even I can't go in there.
What's wrong with them?
Start with your master's name.
It won't work.
We're close enough to it now.
You couldn't follow through, Saizo!
The river?!
Shit!
Sasuke, are you all right?
Ana is an enemy.
I faltered.
I failed as a ninja.
I do not deserve to serve
you, Yukimura-sama.
What are you talking about?
You protected Rokuro just fine.
You don't have time to
feel sorry for yourself.
We have to figure out who
Anastasia is working for.
Yes, sir.
You hesitated, didn't you? You're a fool.
Ana...
She escaped?
Yeah.
She must've been fighting for her life.
How's Rokuro-san?
I removed the poison.
However, his right eye has been ruined.
I see.
Does that yin-yang...
...have anything to do with
why Ana attacked Rokuro?
You're right.
I'll have to tell you.
I'd like to hear that story.
Looks like something
happened while I was out.
Why don't you fill me in?
We're not playing around.
Hold on, Saizo.
As a newcomer, Jinpachi might
be able to see the big picture.
Big picture?
Why you're the Light and
Isanami is the Darkness.
Let's hear it.
The other eight members of my...
...ten brave warriors each have
an associated element.
You're Lightning, the pervert's Wind,
the monkey's Grass, Kakei-san's Metal,
Seikai's Earth, and the kid's Fire.
What are the others?
Ice and Water.
That makes sense.
But what do you need all ten of us for?
The ten elements balance the universe
by neutralizing each other's effects.
And that balance is now
on the verge of collapse.
You brought us together to suppress
the big power in the middle, right?
The girl... Isanami, right?
What's her power of Darkness?
What you call home is a lie.
Who's there?
I thought I'd come check on your wounds.
Also, I thought you might be hungry.
Let's have some manju together.
I want some, too.
My wounds aren't serious.
Sorry, I let my guard down.
Don't cry. Don't be sad, Isanami.
Sorry. I won't cry.
Don't you remember what
the priest used to say?
Your sorrow will summon the darkness.
She was abandoned under the
torii of Izumo Shrine.
The priest who raised her soon realized...
...that there was something
strange about her.
When she cried, a priestess disappeared,
as though swallowed by darkness.
They searched the shrine grounds,
and found darkness seeping out
from under the stones by the torii.
The priest was horrified.
According to legend, underneath there
was the Slope to the Underworld.
Are you really all right, Isanami?
I'm fine.
You two should rest as well.
I'm going to sleep.
Will you be okay by yourself?
I can stay with you.
I'll be fine.
Thanks, Ben-chan. See you tomorrow.
Ana, why?
Why?
Saizo.
Saizo...
When the girl cried, the earth screamed.
She was calling the darkness.
There is only person who can call
the darkness from the Underworld.
Izanami no Mikoto.
Drawing on the negative
human emotions for strength,
she is the goddess of
death who threatened...
...to kill a thousand men in a day.
That's Isanami?
You can't be serious.
The Kushimitama keeps this
power of destruction contained.
In other words, Isanami does
not protect the Kushimitama.
The Kushimitama protects
our world from Isanami.
Isanami.
Damn it. Everyone's so annoying
I can hardly stand it.
Feeling bad won't make Rokuro-san
any better, and Ana...
You're the pirate's black cat.
What do you want?
What are you doing? Stop licking me!
I'm not depressed like the stupid monkey!
Get off of me!
Don't bite me!
Cut it out, Veronica!
You'll get a stomachache.
Is that all you have to say?
The next episode of Brave 10
is "The Start of Tragedy."
The Start of Tragedy
Bring it on!