We're almost done with this area.
We missed two platoons or so.
Watch for them.
Roger.
Message from Naotsugu.
The enemy might be approaching.
I'll report once I have visual.
Tohya!
Lure them out! Got it!
But how far can Miss Minori
see in this darkness?
She's using magic eye drops
that Naotsugu lent her.
She should be able to see
like a cat for a full day.
So far, it's all gone according to plan.
It has to go well.
I forced everyone into agreeing with me.
A night attack?
What are you talking about?
You said you were just getting
them to evacuate!
Those kids can't protect the city alone...
No, they didn't say they could.
That's why they're attacking.
What?
The goblins aren't protecting anything.
If we worry about protecting
something, we can't beat them.
So we attack them.
That's the plan.
But...
And when they're attacked, they'll get spooked.
They aren't well-trained,
so that'll slow them down.
And their attacks will be more sporadic
and more easily defended.
Honestly, it isn't a bad strategy.
Yeah, that's it.
We'll be with them. Don't worry.
It's going to be a long night.
Yeah.
But we aren't alone, are we?
As long as they have something
to protect, anyone would...
Marie tells me they're going
to be defending Choushu.
Naotsugu and his group are
preparing a surprise attack.
What? We haven't even finished
discussing things here.
If you were actually there, seeing it,
you naturally wouldn't want to just ignore it.
The three of us hold all power over decisions in
this matter, which includes sending troops.
We must quickly come to a consensus
before the next full conference.
A plot?
You're saying the goblin attack
is an adventurer plot?
If the adventurers had acted to weaken them
from the start, this wouldn't have happened.
Though I think calling it a plot
is a rather drastic leap...
Baron Krendit,
right now, it's important that no
one withhold their thoughts.
Isn't that why we've held this
conference without them?
To be honest, I don't expect
Choushu to last for long.
Most likely, their next target will be
Tsukuba, Lord Kiliva's territory.
Or possibly...
Maihama?
A Lazy, Cowardly Princess
A Lazy, Cowardly Princess.
What?
Are they still having their little secret meeting?
It's probably about something they
really don't want us to hear.
They haven't settled on a course of action,
and they have to consider their pride.
They'd prefer not to owe
the adventurers anything.
The first group they're likely to turn to is...
Yes, the guardians they've held in
high esteem since ancient times...
The Izumo Knights.
But...
Then, as we thought...
Yes, none of us has any idea why,
but the Knights of Izumo are gone.
Our recon teams report
that several of the fortresses
they once used are empty.
And they found no corpses or signs of combat.
It's as if they've been spirited away.
But in any case, the fact is that they're gone.
Th-Then our only hope is for all the lords
to unite and attack the goblins...
Strategically speaking,
surrounding them is the most feasible plan.
We force them to lay siege to
a well-defended stronghold city,
and when they're tired, we surround them
with a large, combined army, and attack.
Oh, my...
That sounds like you're telling us
to sacrifice one of the cities.
You aren't...
going to tell me to sacrifice Tsukuba since
it's the one they're likely to target, are you?
No, no one's saying that.
Of course not!
I won't let Tsukuba be sacrificed!
Calm down, Lord Kiliva.
Let's take a break.
They're approaching!
Two platoons.
Ten or so...
Tohya's succeeded in luring them out.
Okay...
Start the countdown!
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one...
Zero!
Willow Spirits!
I've rooted them!
Okay!
Here I go.
Icicle Blade!
Thank you, Rudy!
Save your big spells and
attack small-scale for now.
I'll back you up for thirty seconds.
Got it.
Second wave at two o'clock.
Flare Arrow!
Maestro Echo!
Wonderful, Miss Isuzu.
Not now!
Seconds Left
Once your cool down finishes, attack again!
Leave it to me.
If they aren't able to rely on the Izumo Knights...
That would make us their only other option.
As long as we're here, in this world,
we won't be able to avoid fighting in its wars.
But it wouldn't be a good idea for either side
to hand over its soldiers easily.
We'll need to do this properly, you're saying?
Yes, and for that, I'd like us to
agree on something in advance.
Another of your plans?
Way to go, villain in glasses.
It's nothing that special.
I think we three should decide
our roles in advance.
Our roles, huh?
The goblin attack...
I've never seen Father look so serious.
How intense will the fighting be?
It'll have to be Tsukuba.
It's well defended,
and should last a long time.
But who will tell Lord Kiliva?
He'll lose more than a few
fields and outlying villages.
In the worst case, most of the population.
I'm sure everyone is thinking
in the back of their minds
that asking the adventurers
would be the right move.
Yes... If they die, they return to life.
But that would mean owing them a large debt.
Which is why we avoid showing
them our vulnerability,
while getting information from
them by any means necessary.
And they cannot learn that the Izumo
Knights are gone, no matter what.
Ultimately, we know nothing about them.
We need them to be our shield,
even if it means lying to them.
They've finally called us?
I hear the West Wind Brigade has arrived, too.
Yes, they just contacted me.
It's huge.
They'll have to wait until the conference ends...
Well, if it isn't...
Um—
Is something wrong?
I'd imagined you'd be asleep in
your soft bed at this hour.
It's true that you may
see me as nothing but a lazy, cowardly girl.
But I am also a member of the duke's family.
There are nights when I'm too worried to sleep.
I apologize.
Well?
You seemed to have something you wanted to say.
Didn't you say that freedom requires resolve?
Yes.
I haven't forgotten those words.
That's all I wanted to say.
Yes, we're all right.
I think we've wiped out all
the enemies in this area.
We're resting now.
Proceeding north-northwest, yes?
Yes.
Three kilometers or so.
Roger.
You and Nyanta both be careful.
Mage's Gauntlets?
Yes!
Nyanta identified them for me.
They're an item for magical attackers.
As long as you're above level 25,
you can equip them.
Level 25?
Then they can't be that great...
But they're the first item we
acquired by working together.
Yeah.
We worked together in Lagranda
Forest to get them.
Doesn't that make them an amazing treasure?
Yes, that's right.
But what do we do with them?
We can't all use them.
Um...
Why don't we let Rudy use them?
You said it's an item for
magical attackers, right?
That's right.
Rudy's the only mage in our group.
Um, but something that important...
That isn't like you, Rudy!
Since when are you so modest?
What do you think I am?
B-But...
Well, are you sure?
They look good on you, Rudy.
Let's get going.
We'll head down into the ravine,
keeping watch as we move.
Okay...
I swear by these gauntlets that
I'll defeat even more next time.
Don't get too fired up.
What? Is it bad to be fired up?
No, let's do our best!
And so, for these reasons,
we lords of the Freedom Cities of Eastal feel
that in this emergency situation...
Hey, we aren't getting anywhere.
They're probably waiting for us to say something.
We both want more information about what
the other's thinking, to gain an advantage.
So we'll go with the plan.
I'll talk about agreeing to send troops,
to try and gain information.
If this is how they want to play it,
there's no need to hold back.
If anyone knows the status of the
Izumo Knights, please tell me.
Oh, that's even worse than I expected.
It seems clear that, for some reason,
the Izumo Knights won't be coming.
We cannot bring the Izumo
Knights into a war like this!
I would rather ask the Akihabara Round Table.
With Akihabara in danger, why do you not rise?
You're asking us to send troops?
W-Well...
I'd thought the purpose of this
conference was to hear
each individual lord's thoughts...
Or did you simply hope to hear our opinions?
I-I'd heard the Akihabara knights
were unmatched in combat...
If you're using "knights" to mean a
standing force, ready for battle,
neither Akihabara nor the Round
Table has any such thing.
Then what are you adventurers good for?
What does that mean?
What else?
The adventurers' abilities are
a blessing from the gods!
You have a duty to save the land!
That's news to me...
What nonsense is that?!
You're invincible, immortal.
And despite that, you would
abandon your duty to the land?!
You should be ashamed!
Shut up!
First off, we are not citizens
of the Freedom Cities!
That's why we weren't summoned
to the conference before.
Am I wrong?!
I don't know what plot you've devised,
but we have no obligation
to accede to your demands.
Don't you agree, Baron Krendit?!
Th-That isn't...
We didn't mean... Well...
We are most certainly not plotting
to get Akihabara to send troops.
Then it was Lord Kiliva's individual request
that Akihabara send troops, not the will
of the League of Freedom Cities?
Are you saying that I'm acting
for my own benefit here?!
It is not the will of the entire League.
But it's also true that many of us
within the League feel that way.
Or will the proud, mighty warriors of Akihabara
stand aside while Yamato faces its hour of peril?
We are not pets...
"You guys are immortal, so go
and kill the goblins for us"?
Anyone who believed that, and sent
their comrades to the battlefield
could never gain the people of Akihabara's trust!
Was that too much?
The adventurers risk losing their memories.
Anyone would get mad about that, not just you.
And it's your job to oppose sending troops.
But...
Yeah, that may have been a bit much.
I'm not sure where we go from here...
Lenessia...
What... What am I doing?
You're looking as beautiful as ever.
Like a fairy on a lake, on a moonlit night.
I shouldn't have come here.
I shouldn't have come.
I want to put on my flannel
pajamas and go to bed...
I want to put my face down on
a cold table and lie there.
Are you not slacking off today?
Did I imagine that?
I'm sure I heard it.
No, it doesn't matter...
Of course I want to slack off, but...
Lenessia...
Sir Crusty...
Yes, Princess Lenessia?
I am going to Akihabara.
Accompany me.
To Akihabara? Why?
To raise an army of volunteers.
Impossible... What can a single woman do?
Speaking to a foreign band of
knights without permission?
That far exceeds her authority...
No, the Round Table's representative
is going with her...
That could change things.
I'm sure that's likely to be a lot of work.
Yes.
Then why?
You said that adventurers were free.
I'm just a stupid girl, so I don't
really understand politics.
But I think that when you ask
someone for something,
you should show respect.
As a member of the duke's family,
that's what my father and
grandfather taught me.
That's why
I don't think we should be
hiding things from you.
Including the fact that the
Izumo Knights are missing!
What has she done?
She's told them our secret!
Well, now you've done it.
When I take responsibility, apologize with me.
And, exactly what are you planning?
I see there are things even you don't know.
Nothing.
I don't have any plan at all.
But...
As a member of the Cowen family,
I do not wish to be insulting.
Grandfather...
Continue.
Adventurers are free.
They are more free than we are.
It's true that we may be weaker than they are.
But that doesn't mean that, in our weakness,
we can become aggressive.
We don't have the right to take advantage
of our weakness and use them as tools!
I shall go to Akihabara, and ask
the adventurers directly.
Sir Crusty said that adventurers are free.
So if any of them will agree to help us,
why would we stop them?
I shall find even ten or fifteen
that will agree to help us.
I learned from my grandfather
that showing respect
doesn't mean using fancy words.
I'll go there myself, to stand in the street,
and speak to each adventurer individually!
Princess Lenessia!
It's fine.
She was just very nervous.
Can I leave the rest of this to you?
I couldn't. That would be a waste.
So what will you do?
Will you accept her resolve, or not?
The final decision lies with you.
A bird?
It's scary out here at night.
There are probably all kinds
of enemies still out here.
It's true.
We've only defeated a tiny
percentage of the goblins.
No matter how many we kill, it may not matter.
It's even scarier when the fighting starts.
You can trip on roots and soft ground.
Yeah, you lose your balance easily.
I'm always anxious because I never know
when the enemy will appear.
Maybe it's because you're
on higher alert at night...
Like for the scent of the monsters.
Yeah...
I hate that scent.
But...
It's okay to do our best!
It's okay for us to try and save them!
Yeah, it's just fine!
Yes, of course.
If you'd leave behind people in trouble,
how can you be an adventurer?
That's right...
We don't need to think about anything else.
We'll all protect the people we care about.
That's all there is to it.
And as a shrine priestess,
my job is to keep us all safe.
Why are you laughing, my lord?
I've never seen Crusty looking like that.
He was totally overwhelmed.
That princess impresses me.
I didn't expect her to do that there.
It's about respect, huh?
Respect?
Yes.
Even if the Round Table promised to send troops,
it wouldn't mean Akihabara would act.
Because, as she said, adventurers are free.
If you want them to act, you need
to persuade each one individually.
And she seemed to understand that perfectly.
She said she'd do all she could to
show respect at that meeting.
But in a way, isn't that obvious?
Yes, you're right.
But everyone there was about to ignore it.
Including us.
What's that light?
The city of Akihabara.
It's night...
But the light is so warm...
She may be the one who saves the Freedom
Cities of Eastal from the dead end
in which they've found themselves.
That lazy, cowardly princess...
She finds herself in a town she doesn't know
with things she's never seen,
things she's never heard,
and people she's never met.
She learns how big the world is,
and how tiny she is.
She cries out her resolve and her hope.
And her words drive the adventurers to action.
Expeditionary Force
Next time: Expeditionary Force.
Always look thirty seconds ahead.