Kuu-chan, are you okay?
Why is it so hot every day?
Hmm... because it's summer?
It sure is.
Yeah...
That's right! When it's this hot in summer,
I want to go to the ocean!
Don't you, Hina-chan?
U-Uh... I've never been
to the ocean, so I'm not sure.
My family lived deep in the mountains, so...
Really?
Yeah.
The ocean is great!
Shaved ice, yakisoba, ramen,
watermelon-splitting...
Those all have to do with food.
Oh, morning, Yua-chan.
Morning.
Wh-What?
I know!
Let's all go to the ocean this weekend!
Huh?
O-Oh, all right...
If you insist, I guess I
don't mind going with you.
Then it's settled!
Wait a minute... Isn't the ocean
dangerous because of shark attacks?
This isn't some panic movie. It'll be fine!
Really?
Yeah!
Thank goodness! I can go to
the ocean without worrying, then.
But animals tend to like you, Hina-chan.
Maybe they'll come to you
when you're swimming...
Huh?
Swim, swim... swim, swim, swim...
Kuu-chan, if it comes to it,
leave me behind and run!
I was just kidding.
But if you're scared of the ocean,
can't you just play on the beach?
O-Oh, yeah...
But if I'm going to the ocean,
I would like to swim.
Actually, I don't even have a swimsuit...
Then let's go buy swimsuits after school.
Good idea!
I've been wanting a new one!
A new swimsuit...
Will I be able to pick a swimsuit
that works for me?
I don't know what kind is in right now...
You can just leave that to me!
I'll pick the perfect swimsuit
for you, Hina-chan!
M-Mayu-chan?
Aren't the second-year classrooms upstairs?
I felt I was being called.
The Lost Swimsuit
Wow, this is amazing!
So this is a department store!
This is my first time shopping with friends,
so I'm really excited!
It'll be my first time in the swimsuit
department, so I'm excited, too!
There are so many!
Oh, look!
That one's really cute!
Oh, you're right!
And how about this flowery one?
It's cute, too!
And this chic style is nice, too!
Yeah! I want to try it on!
Hey, you two!
You're going to disturb the other customers.
Don't be so loud.
Yua-chan, look at this one!
Let me see!
Wow, it's nice!
Isn't it?
Mayu-chan, there are so many, I can't decide!
I know, but don't worry.
I'll give all my effort to
helping you choose a swimsuit.
Okay! Thanks!
You can count on me.
Good luck, Hina-chan...
What do you think, Mayu-chan?
Yeah, it's cute.
All right, try this one next.
Okay, I'll try it.
How many more is she going to make me try on?
Ta-da!
How do I look?
It suits you, but I'm surprised
that was your choice.
I thought you'd pick a more revealing one.
Well... I've gained a little weight lately,
so I want to cover my stomach.
I really was planning to buy a bikini, but...
With your proportions,
I think you're perfectly thin now.
Ch-Chiaki-senpai!
You don't need to worry.
Hearing that from you
makes me more confident!
I'm going to try on a bikini right now!
She switches gears fast...
This one's kind of a funny shape.
Is this the first time
you've worn one like that?
Yeah... or to be exact,
I've never worn anything
but school swimsuits.
Really?
Then we were right
to go swimsuit shopping today!
No high schooler wants to go to
the ocean wearing a school swimsuit.
I'm planning to go in my school swimsuit.
Huh? You are?
Yes. The one I used in
elementary school still fits,
so I don't see the need to buy one.
I see... That is an option...
Mayu-chan, I still have my swimsuit
from last year, so I—
No! You have to buy a new one, Aki-chan!
You can't use that one! No, no, no!
O-Okay...
What do you think?
You look so composed and beautiful
in a swimsuit, Miss Landlady!
You have grown-up appeal!
You do like simple styles,
don't you, Aki-chan?
I figure I could wear something
like this at home, too.
Or, like, when I clean the bath.
You use yours on normal days?
Yeah.
I only wear a swimsuit a few times
in a year, so it's wasted otherwise.
I'm not sure if that's
economical or realistic...
Well...
Now that everyone else
is done picking swimsuits,
I should pick one for myself, too...
Let's see...
My, what a cute little girl!
What are you looking for?
W-Well... um...
You look like a doll!
I'm sure any swimsuit would look good on you.
No, really...
Let me see... For you...
How about that one?
What do you think?
I-I'll go get my mom.
I'll be waiting!
I'm... I'm not a child...
All right! If that's how it is,
I'll show off how grown-up
I can look with a sexy swimsuit!
Well, I tried to pick one,
but I don't think this is quite right...
Um, excuse me...
Could I get another...
Um... Th-This is, well...
You can't wear that, Mayu-chan!
You'll catch a chill!
I don't think you're ready
for that kind of swimsuit yet.
Darn it!
Stop treating me like a child!
-Why bananas?
I wonder why you can only have up to 500 yen for your snacks on field trips...
I hear people ask if bananas count as snacks all the time, but why does that come up? Because they're cheap and there's more than one? Does that mean that it counts as a meal since it fills you up?
-I guess it doesn't really matter, but I'm curious...
Thank you very much.
I ended up getting a one-piece.
I hope it won't look too childish.
Mayu-senpai looks worried.
Is this about...?
Mayu-senpai?
Oh, sorry to keep you all waiting.
Um...
Mayu-senpai, are you... um...
worried about how small you are?
Huh? Small?
I'm insecure about that, too.
Yua-chan worries about her height, too?
I don't think you're small enough
that you need to worry.
I'd say you're about average, actually.
Really?
But I'm only an A-cup...
Huh?
Th-That's what she meant?
I can't wait to go to the ocean!
I got a really nice swimsuit, too.
I'm excited to go swimming!
Shark!
I'm gonna eat you, Hina-chan!
Gotcha!
A-Actually, I think I might be
scared of the ocean...
I-I was just kidding, really!
I'm so excited to go to the ocean.
That's right... it's going to be my first time
at the ocean, so just in case...
What is Hina-chan doing?
Not sure...
Swimming practice?
She stopped.
Help!
I guess she's practicing
what to do in case of drowning.
Someone help!
There's a shark!
Help! I'm drowni—
Shark!
H-Help!
S-So this is the ocean!
It's the ocean, Hina-chan!
Ocean! Ocean!
Let's hurry and go swimming!
We need to make sure we stretch first.
Okay!
There! All done stretching!
Hina-chan.
Do you know how to swim?
Yes, though I'm not very good at it.
Are you a good swimmer?
Chiaki-senpai excels at all sports!
Of course she's a good swimmer!
I'm just normal.
But last year...
Didn't you swim in a tournament
as an emergency substitute and win?
Really? Wow!
I'm surprised you know about that.
Oh, I just happened to see a photo of it
outside the swim team's club room...
So, Yua-chan, you can't...
Huh?
N-No! I can swim fine,
but if I get caught in a current,
my feet won't touch the bottom!
So wouldn't that mean you can't swim?
Anyway! Let's just go swim now!
Y-Yeah, let's.
This feels so nice!
That's it, that's it.
You're doing great.
Whee!
Take that!
S-Sorry...
I've got it!
Got—
I'm thirsty.
I'm going to go buy some drinks.
Try not to get lost.
Come on! I'll be fine!
Jeez... Kuu-chan is always
treating me like a child.
I'm the shortest in the group,
but I'm still a year older than she is.
She should rely on me more...
Huh? What is this place?
What do I do? I need to
contact Aki-chan somehow...
But I left my cell phone back there.
Huh?
That little girl is out here alone?
Is she lost?
But she doesn't look like
an ordinary little girl...
Wait... Kuroyanagi-sensei?!
Oh. Greetings.
Um... Sensei, what are you doing here?
I'm filming a drama near here.
I'm waiting for my next scene now,
so I took a walk.
Are you appearing in the drama, too?
N-No!
Oh... I thought you had
entered show business.
I always thought it was a
terrible shame for someone
as sweet and beautiful as you
not to strive for a job in show business.
Oh, I know. Since fate somehow
brought us together here,
why don't you take this opportunity
to enter show business?
No, thank you!
I see.
Too bad. By the way,
are the girls you're usually with
not here today?
Oh... Actually, they are here,
but I've lost sight of them.
Could it be that you're...
lost?
N-No, I'm not!
Then...
We don't need to contact
Chiaki-san, I take it?
I'd rather we did!
Mayu-chan sure is taking a while.
Yeah...
Maybe she got lost.
I'll try calling her.
The line's busy.
What?
For the time being,
which direction did you come from?
Um... I think it was that way...
Then let's go.
O-Okay...
It's no use.
Mayu-chan isn't answering.
Should we have them make
a lost child announcement?
That might embarrass Mayu-senpai so much
that she wouldn't come back.
That's true...
Oh...
Mayu-chan left her phone here.
Wh-What do we do?!
We have no way to contact her!
She really is lost...
I'll go look for her!
Hina-chan?
Hina-chan left her phone...
I think we're about to have a
second lost child on our hands.
Yeah...
Mayu-chan!
Where are you?
I've looked so much,
and still can't find her...
Where in the world did she go?
What? Me? Oh, I couldn't!
Maybe she got scouted by someone in
show business who happened to be here,
and they took her to the
scene of a drama filming?!
As cute as she is, I can believe it...
Excuse me!
Could you take a picture of us?
U-Um...
A-Ah.... I...
They're all coming to her!
Wow!
Oh?
Did they find fish?
But this is the shore...
Hina-chan!
Sensei, look! It's Hina-chan!
Now I can get back to the others!
That's wonderful.
Yeah!
Hina-chan!
Mayu-chan!
I'm so glad to see you!
I was so scared all by myself!
H-Huh?
I can't tell which of them was actually lost.
Mayu-chan and Hina-chan still aren't back.
Yeah...
Everyone!
Hina-chan!
Mayu-senpai's with her, too!
I see...
You ran into Mayu-chan while taking a walk.
Yes.
I'm so glad!
I was worried, since you
left your cell phones here!
I'm surprised you made it back
without losing your way.
Yeah!
The crabs showed me the way.
I like mountain animals, too,
but marine animals are really cute!
Oh, right! Some people talked to me
and I turned into a scarecrow,
but then Mayu-chan happened
to walk by and saved me!
Huh? Mayu-senpai, you weren't lost?
Huh?
It's so cool that you helped
Hina-chan when she was in trouble!
U-Uh...
You're like an older sister
we can all count on!
An older sister?
Th-That's not true at all.
No, no, it is!
You think so?
Of course!
We won't tell anyone that
she really was lost.
Thanks, Ruri-chan!
Thank you so much!
The horizon looks so pretty.
And the sea breeze feels nice.
It was so fun playing with everyone, too.
Hina-chan, how was your
first visit to the ocean?
It was so much fun!
I wish I could live here forever!
Huh?
Are you animals from the mountains?
I-It was just a joke!
It's okay. I love all of you, too.
-New students welcoming party
-Welcoming party at the karaoke place near school
-Dinner near the karaoke place
-Planning to finish at 19:30
-Get RSVPs and make reservations
-Confirm what time everyone plans to go home
-Think about the event
-Come up with next year's club budget
-This month's club report
-Ideas on what we want to show the first-years (by 4/15)
-Party: 12 with student discount = 1080 yen per person
-Dinner: Do we go with a 2 hour all-you-can-eat? Or eat something we all want?
Wh-Where did they come from?
Hey! Let's all take a picture together!
O-Okay!
Aki-chan, hurry!
Yua-chan?
Everyone's asleep.
I'm starting to feel sleepy, too...
I hope we can all come to
the ocean together again next year.
Trying Too Hard
My first visit to the ocean was so much fun!
But I can't just play around all the time.
I have to help Kuu-chan
and Mayu-chan at work,
and I have to study theater, too.
Next time, "Trying Too Hard."