And now to finish it
off with high heat...
Hikari!
Is the food ready yet?
Shut up!
I'll bring it over there in a
second, so just be quiet and wait!
Above the surface: there are
no advisories or warnings in effect.
Hot, hot, hot...
Because of the warm snow that has fallen since yesterday in the seas in the southern part of the Shioshishio Peninsula,
Here, eat.
Smells like morning.
Today's Salinity Level
Change from Yesterday
the high salinity line
is heading south.
The salinity in the Narunami
area around noon is 55 per mill.
Done.
And it will be about 52
per mill around 6PM.
Make sure you clean this up.
Sure thing.
The currents are normal, but plenty
of caution should be exercised when going out.
Isn't it still a bit early?
I have to go call Manaka.
Oh, right, right.
Next is the weather on the surface. The
Shioshishio Peninsula will continue to be sunny.
I see that you two haven't tired of
each other yet and are close as ever.
Shut up!
I don't have a choice.
Because she's...
...a total helpless good-for-nothing.
If I'm not there for her...
It really is pretty
salty this morning...
Mornin'!
Hey, it's Hikari-oniichan.
Good morning.
Good morning, Hikari.
Morning.
Manaka! What are you wearing?!
Uh...
We promised!
We were going to wear
Nami Junior High's uniform today!
Why are you wearing
Hama Junior High's unis?!
B-But making a point of being an
outsider like that might make waves...
You know...
Just because our school closed,
doesn't mean the soul of
Nami Junior High will disappear!
Let's totally show Hama
Junior High a thing or two!
Right?!
That hurts!
Jeez, Hikari...
You're way too excited
this early in the morning.
I-I'll go change after all.
You should have done
that in the first place!
Don't yell at me anymore!
Let's go.
But...
Let's just go!
Shioshishio Entrance
Hii-kun?
Chii-chan?
Kaname?
Hii-kun!
Aren't we going ahead?
After we rest first.
And our clothes need to dry.
So you are worried about Manaka after all.
Damn you, Chisaki!
We're gonna go.
Those guys...
They're trying to fish outside
the permitted areas again.
Seems pretty big.
Manaka?!
I had witnessed it...
The moment when two people have...
their special first meeting...
Episode One:
In Between the Sea and the Land
So...
Namiji Junior High has closed,
Mukaido Manaka   Sakishima Hikari   Isaki Kaname   Hiradaira Chisaki
so it's going to be merging
with our Mihama Junior High.
Well, you can all get along, right?
Now, introduce yourselves, please.
R-Right.
I'm H-Hiradaira Chisaki.
I'm hoping that I get used to
living on the surface quickly.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Isaki Kaname. Nice to meet you.
Doesn't it smell like fish?
Man, sea people are totally lame.
Man, it stinks!
I'm Sakishima Hikari!
All of you surface people smell like pigs.
Nice to meet ya'll, oink!
Hii-kun!
Make sure you give it to
'em good, too, Manaka!
"G-Give it"?
I-I can't do something like that.
I said do it!
Hey, Hikari!
I'm not talking to you again, Hii-kun!
Fine!
The heck was that?
They're having a lover's quarrel?
What are they doing when
they just transferred here?
Girls' Changing Room
See?
You won't really stand
out with a track suit on.
This is your track suit, Chii-chan.
I'm going to be skipping
gym, so go ahead and use it.
Thanks, Chii-chan.
Hikari... feels like he has
to protect you, Manaka.
I know...
I need to tell Hii-kun I'm sorry...
Right?
You haven't done anything wrong, Manaka.
But when Hikari comes
to apologize to you,
please accept his apology, okay?
Okay.
You better pick up the pace!
Put more into it!
He's...
Whoa. He's really fast.
It's like he's swimming on land.
Oh...
It's Hikari.
There's no way I'm gonna
lose to surface people!
No way I'm going to lose...
Ah?!
Oh...
You two! What are you doing?!
Damn it...
Oh, Hikari?
Akari.
What happened? Where's Manaka-chan?
We don't have to be together all the way
to school and back. We're not kids!
Says the kid.
Shut up!
Huh?
I wonder if they did it again?
"Again"?
Go a
Gum letters?!
Well, it's not in a noticeable spot,
so I'm sort of curious about
what they're trying to write.
"Go a"...
Or is it "go away"?
But when you've come this far...
Are they kids you know?
It's not important.
Come on. You should get home soon.
You're in charge of dinner tonight.
Oh, I want a light
salty soup tonight.
Tonight we're having ginger pork!
What?
Hey, Hikari! Get over here!
I heard that Manaka was reeled up!
Whoa!
Now they're even invading
our fishing grounds!
Young Men Coalition
Even the fish I'm raising in the
fields are getting pulled up.
We've already hit hard times
because of salt damage.
Not to mention, they're saying they
won't do the Ofunehiki.
What? The Ofunehiki?
Unbelievable, right?
Long ago, everyone lived in the sea.
Who do they think makes the
fish in the sea for them?
But the people who were fascinated
by the land abandoned the sea.
Casting off the special robe the Sea God
had given us to be able to live in the sea.
Many hardships awaited the
people who went up to the land.
Drought continued, and
people fought over water.
Thinking that the Sea God
must have been angry,
the people offered a girl as a sacrifice,
and sent her out into the sea on a boat...
That was the beginning of the Ofunehiki.
Now, instead of a sacrifice,
they offer rice or sweets.
But apparently we who live in the sea,
are the descendants of the
sacrificed woman and the Sea God.
What are we going to do if the Sea God
is angered by the cessation of the Ofunehiki?
This is why humans suck.
But we're technically humans, too...
Sort of...
Don't compare us to the
ones without Ena.
We're in a totally different
class! Completely different!
I'm going to head home now.
Make sure you tell the Chief Priest
and ask him what we should do now!
We've got to talk to Uroko-sama, too!
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, a half-hearted response
like that isn't reassuring!
Come on now, heir to
the Narunami Shrine!
Sure, sure.
Sea God
What?
I thought you weren't talking to me.
Sacred fire, huh?
And is that stew?
Is that for Uroko-sama?
I'm sorry about today.
Okay!
Yo!
Uroko-sama! It's Manaka.
Hello.
Welcome, Mukai-dono.
U-Um... our sacred fire ran out,
so I came to get more.
Thank you very much.
Here... my grandma likes you very
much, so she put in young bamboo.
Smells wonderful.
Yes.
The young bamboo, carrots, and chicken
have all been cooked separately
so the flavors wouldn't mix...
I meant you...
Huh?
You smell of a female.
What do you think you're doing?!
I'll curse you!
Uroko-sama, what do you mean
by "smell of a female"?
Mating season.
More importantly, how was the surface?
I wonder what's going to
happen with the Ofunehiki.
Who cares?
It's just for show anyway, right?
See ya!
Manaka!
Uroko-sama said something weird!
He always does.
Just ignore him.
But he said he'd curse me...
Uroko-sama is sort of a god...
He's not a god, he's a
scale of the Sea God.
He's just keeping an eye on us to
make sure we don't do anything weird
like the people on the surface did.
But...
Mating season.
Let's head home.
Oh, right.
Yeah...
Huh?
All you need to do is to stay
close and keep following me...
The Ofunehiki doesn't matter...
but then again, we have Uroko-sama...
Whatever is meant to happen will happen.
Should the Chief Priest be saying that?
I don't really want to get
along with the humans on land,
but I'm not as extreme
as the old guys either.
Manaka-chan!
Oh, the three of you
came to pick her up?
Where's Manaka?
Well, she's not coming
out of her room...
Oh, I'll go get her.
What's wrong, Mana—
Don't come in here!
Go away!
Don't... Ow!
Whoa...
So you were cursed by Uroko-sama...
It's awful...
He's so childish...
Whoa.
This noise is gross!
It just totally farted! Farted!
It's not a fart!
I can't let anyone see
this no matter what!
"Anyone"?
You're already showing me.
You're allowed, Hii-kun!
Wrap this. It'll hide it.
Okay.
Your legs are so thin...
Huh?
Oh, nothing...
All right, I'll be collecting
your notebooks next week.
Let's go home.
Where's Hii-kun and Kaname?
The guys had wood shop, so let's
wait in front of the classroom.
Okay.
Hey.
Huh?
Hey, look! It's just like we heard. Look.
Her skin's totally shining.
It's like a saran-wrapped convenience store bento.
H-Hey!
This is the "Ena"?
So you aren't human after all.
Please stop!
Why?
Who cares. Just let us see.
But...
What are you guys doing?
Ow!
Huh?
What? What was that noise?
A fart?
Manaka!
Hikari!
Manaka has...
What?
No, no, no, no!
I can't... breathe...
Manaka!
I thought she may have come back, but...
I-I can't anymore...
my Ena is starting to dry...
You guys head back first.
But...
Hikari!
Come on, Chisaki.
I can't...
keep up...
Chisaki?
Oh...
From the outside, it looks
like you and Hikari are married...
and Manaka's like your daughter.
Huh?
Not to mention,
if Manaka were to disappear,
the one next to Hikari would be you.
Don't say that at a time
like this, even if it's a joke!
Sorry...
Manaka is precious to me...
Must be troublesome...
Yeah. It is troublesome.
Once the... song plays at 5 o'clock,
I need to head home, but...
I need to head... home.
She's from Umimura?
Fill the tub with water and let her soak.
Put in a little salt, too.
Right.
Thank goodness!
I was starting to see these flashes—
D-Don't look! Don't look! Don't look!
Ow!
So I am gross after all...
Huh? That's...
I wonder if it'll eat it.
N-No, stop...
Don't feed it, please!
I thought it was pretty.
Huh?
This fish has scales
I've never seen before.
"Fish"?
And you...
really do have Ena...
You can live in the sea
because you have this, right?
It's radiant and beautiful.
What's wrong?
I-I'm still having a
hard time breathing...
and it's getting worse...
Should I add more salt?
Y-Yes.
Manaka!
Hii-kun!
Hii-kun?!
You bastard! What were
you doing to Manaka?!
Hii-kun! Stop!
Tsumugu-kun saved me!
"Tsumugu-kun"?!
At that moment...
It was like a bolt of
electricity ran through me...
Let's go!
Huh?
H-Hii-kun, w-wait!
Hii-kun... You were
looking for me, right?
I'm sorry I caused you
so much trouble...
Hii-kun?
Oh, they're practicing singing.
When Manaka took off her towel...
I can't let anyone see
this no matter what!
You're allowed, Hii-kun!
So I guess she's not embarrassed...
in front of him...
I hate it when you say
perverted things, Hii-kun!
I think the Village
of the Sea is great.
Manaka... has Hikari.
The guys on land have no business concerning
themselves with the Village of the Sea...
Episode Two: The Chilly Desert