My name is Gouda Takeo.
I may not look like it, but I'm
a first-year in high school.
Soon after I entered high school,
I fell in love with Yamato after
saving her from a groper.
Get off this train at the next station!
Thank you.
I'll get going.
Huh?
You're leaving?!
But Yamato had fallen for Suna.
She's...
kind of nice.
Suna seems to have a thing for her, too.
Now that I think about it,
you're always helping me...
Thank you.
Next time, could it be without Sunakawa-kun?
I... I'd like it to be just the two of us.
She's finally ready to ask for
advice with her relationship.
You can count on me!
My Blue Ogre
Here I am...
Sorry, was I late?
No, you're still five minutes early.
Thank goodness.
I thought I'd kept you waiting.
No...
Huh, is it just my imagination,
or does she look extra-ridiculously cute today?
O-Oh...
Yeah?
Um, I thought it shouldn't always be cake,
so I made cake salé today.
"Cake"?
What's this?
You might take a bite, thinking it's
sweet, but it's actually salty.
So don't take a bite, thinking it's sweet,
because it's actually salty!
She said it twice.
Thanks.
It's great!
It's awesome.
I've never tasted anything like it before!
You always eat a lot of my baking.
That makes me happy.
T-Takeo-kun...
U-Um...
Oh!
I brought tea today, too.
Last time, Sunakawa-kun bought drinks,
and that was really considerate of him.
Yeah! Suna is really considerate!
He doesn't have a girlfriend, either.
And he spoke highly of you.
He wouldn't cheat on a girl, either.
He's smart and good-looking.
He's a good guy.
Yamato...
You can't do much about how people feel, but...
Take it from someone who's known him
since we were three years old.
You have my guarantee!
Suna's a good guy!
Don't worry... I'm a man.
I won't make you uncomfortable
by confessing my feelings to you!
This is how it should be.
They'd make a great couple.
She thanked me.
She lifted the beam with me.
And sometimes,
I get to eat tasty cake like this.
That's enough for me.
In the end, I'm the Red Ogre.
So I can't be like the Blue Ogre, but...
I do want the people I care for to smile.
I want them to be happy.
Yamato, Suna's...
Yamato?
Sorry...
Something got into my eye...
Uh-oh, I guess my contacts shifted...
Sorry, I have to go!
Sorry!
What was that?
Why was she crying?!
Did you do something to Yamato?
Nothing.
"Nothing"?!
Today, you aren't even going
to say, "I'm coming in"?
Then why did Yamato cry when
I told her about you?!
She cried?
It's because she likes you,
you idiot!
Dude, way too close.
Actually, you're the idiot.
What?
It's because Yamato-san likes you.
Don't mess with me! She likes you!
No, it's you.
No, you!
Why?
Because you're cool!
Suna, you're cool!
Thanks, I guess.
Don't worry. You're cool, too.
Yamato-san said you were cool, also.
What?
This is getting really tiresome.
Can I just tell you everything?
When we met Yamato-san in the
park to return her phone,
you vanished into the restroom
at some point, remember?
At that point, she'd told me a lot of things.
Um...
Does he have friends?
A girlfriend, maybe?
Of course he does.
He's so cool!
Nope.
Really?
Really.
No way! Really?
He isn't the type who
could hide that sort of thing.
Then I can like him?
I can't help myself, you know?
He was so cool yesterday!
You can't help but fall for that.
Fall for you?
Dude, are you even listening?
But that time in my room,
she didn't want you to leave!
Really?
Really.
I'll get going.
Huh?
You're leaving?!
Her face totally said she wanted
to spend more time with you!
She probably didn't want me to go
because she'd be too nervous
if she were alone with you.
She's always looking at you!
You're always staring at her.
Of course she can't look you in the eye.
Think back harder...
I'd like for you to develop
a better eye for people.
She likes me?
Yamato likes me?
No way. It can't be true.
You said Yamato's a nice girl, right?
You don't like her?
She is a nice girl.
When I'm with her, she only talks
about how she likes you.
Till now, you've had poor taste in girls.
All the girls you liked talked smack
about you behind your back.
I think Gouda likes you!
Ew, creepy...
His face is huge.
Way too huge.
He's loud and annoying.
But he's always looking at you, Satou.
That's seriously creepy!
You should seriously have better taste in girls.
Really?
Who'd want to date girls that talk
smack about your friends?
So that's why you...
You always turned them down when they
told you how they felt about you.
Suna, you're the manliest of men!
I'm sorry I said you didn't have a pair!
You definitely have a pair!
Yeah, yeah. I do.
But I still can't believe that Yamato likes me.
Well, I guess you might find it hard unless
you hear her say it for yourself.
May I come in?
What's up?
Someone named Yamato-san's here.
Hide!
Where?
Man, you're huge.
You're welcome to make yourself at home.
Thank you.
Hello.
Hi.
I'm sorry I came without any notice.
Why don't you take a seat?
Oh, okay.
Sunakawa-kun, I...
I cried in front of Takeo-kun!
What should I do?
How can I explain it away?
Takeo-kun looked really uncomfortable.
What should I do?
Why did you cry?
Takeo-kun's always suggesting you...
He's always talking about you...
I thought he was turning me down
in a roundabout way,
and that just got tough.
Then what are you going to do?
Give up?
I don't want to.
I'll keep trying!
I don't think I'll meet
anyone else like Takeo-kun.
Well, you may be right there.
I really, really like him!
Okay, say that again.
Say that again, please.
I like him!
Like who?
I like Takeo-kun!
Say it one last time, so the point gets across.
I really like Takeo-kun!
Just to be sure, say it one more time.
I like Takeo-kun!
Got it?
Huh?
Come on, you tell her, too.
What?
Come out.
Eh? Huh?
How?
This is mean!
You manipulated me, Sunakawa-kun?
He couldn't get it through his thick
skull without hearing for himself.
I've liked you from the day we met!
We Are Happy
Thank You,
Sunakawa-kun
Uh...
It's a sign of her gratitude.
Sunakawa-kun, thank you! Thank you!
You're welcome.
Um, I have a friend who's really great.
I have her pic here...
You don't have to try to spread the love.
Stop!
Suna,
I see
don't be so lonely.
I'm not lonely.
Suna...
I like seeing you happy.
This cake looks like it
has a fairy or something
hiding inside...
Suna, you really are like the Blue Ogre!
Where'd that come from?
Remember the kindergarten play?
You were the Blue Ogre,
and I was the Red Ogre.
All the moms cried a river, watching you
act out the two ogres' friendship!
I don't remember any of that.
Well, I do!
You mentioned that before.
What's the story about?
Well...
Once upon a time,
The Red Ogre Who Cried
a kind-hearted Red Ogre lived all by himself
in the mountains.
The Red Ogre wanted to
make friends with people,
but they were afraid of the ogre
and kept their distance.
It made the Red Ogre sad.
But his friend, the Blue Ogre, tells him
that the Blue Ogre will go stir
things up in the village,
and the Red Ogre should come beat him up.
The Blue Ogre thought that'd change the
people's opinion about the Red Ogre,
and make them willing to be friends with him.
The Blue Ogre went to the village,
and went on a rampage, although he
was careful not to hurt anyone.
The Red Ogre pretended to beat the Blue Ogre.
The Blue Ogre pretended
to be defeated and fled.
Henceforth, the villagers
trusted the Red Ogre
and would come over to his place.
Now that he had human friends,
the Red Ogre led a happy life.
But one day, he became worried about the
Blue Ogre, who'd stopped coming by,
and he went to see him.
The Red Ogre crossed entire mountains and
valleys to reach the Blue Ogre's home.
But there,
he found that the Blue
Ogre had left on a journey,
leaving behind a letter to the Red Ogre.
The letter said,
"You finally became friends with humans.
If you're friendly to me,
they'll just come to mistrust you."
The Blue Ogre had left the Red
Ogre without saying anything.
That's so sad.
Right?
Isn't it awesome?
The Blue Ogre's such a great guy!
Yeah.
I don't think I could go that far,
even for a friend.
Right?
The Blue Ogre's way too nice!
Yeah!
He's got way too much integrity!
Suna's awesome!
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
I don't know about that.
Isn't that normal?
I mean, they were friends, right?
Who wouldn't want their friends to be happy?
That's just normal, man.
It's nothing amazing.
Suna's...
Suna!
Suna might have always been
keeping an eye out for me.
Takeo... can't breathe...
Always...
Since long ago.
It's so nice. It's a bromance.
Bromance, huh?
You're right about that.
I got asked a lot why we're even friends,
but I guess it wasn't only because
we were neighbors.
It's great!
This one's another winner!
I'm glad to hear that.
Here, have some tea.
What kind is this?
Um...
They're madelines.
Oh, madelines?
Takeo, Age 5
Let's go to the park!
Okay, I guess.
Yahoo!
Suna, look!
Transfo—
Did you see my mad skills just now?
Achoo!
I wouldn't call those mad skills...
Orya!
Takeo, Age 10
Why is it that...
Why do I always fall into this hole?
Maybe because you aren't jumping over it?
You know, Takeo's always up close and personal.
Sunakawa Ai
(Junior High School Student)
Talk
Volume
Brightness
Step back.
Oh, right.
What, did something funny happen?
No, it's nothing...
Bathroom break!
Okay.
Sometimes, Takeo-kun's so up close and
personal, I don't know what to do.
It makes my heart skip a beat, you know?
Yeah, I don't know what to do, either.
Because it's so friggin' hilarious.
Huh?
What's the matter?
It's nothing.
My Boyfriend
Next time: My Boyfriend.