It's up! Nice!
A feint!
Karasuno                             Johzenji
Futamata!
Again?! I'll stop them again!
This time, not with my face.
Back attack!
A break...
I totally thought you were going to hit that.
You scared the crap out of me!
His own team didn't know
he was going to do that.
But he was able to hit it so calmly.
They're vicious... How creepy.
Johzenji seems to be doing
well after their time out.
Yeah... They're starting to actually look
at their opponents as they're playing.
That's not good.
Haikyu!!
Episode 16: "Next"
I'm not saying you need to play seriously.
You guys may seem stupid,
but you're not, are you?
Huh?
Playing doesn't equal not thinking.
Left! Left!
Nice!
It's up! Get the last one!
When you're not sure they're
actually going to hit,
don't go up to block, and take a step back.
Right on point!
I have no complaints if
you actually stop them.
When you know how to move
and have the skill to actually do it,
that's when you can actually play freely.
I guess the more we improve,
the more we'll see people like that.
Tsukishima, nice serve!
Here he comes! #10!
Hey, listen up a sec.
Johzenji hasn't been able
to stop Hinata's quick yet,
so they'd better get this point.
Nice receive.
Their #10 jumped up! That quick is coming!
Er, huh?
Johzenji's blockers aren't marking #10?
If we can't block it,
it's better to go for the receive.
Whoa! They did it!
They managed to counter by not marking #10!
It went over!
Playing doesn't equal not thinking.
Having the simulation in your
head and reality join together...
...is awesome!
Karasuno                             Johzenji
A two-point difference, huh...
This happened to them with Aoba Johsai, too.
Eh?
Hinata's spike is still pretty light.
I don't want to get blocked,
but being ignored by the blockers
is even more frustrating. Why?!
Kageyama!
Could you give me another one next time?
One more, nice serve!
Got it!
I can see it.
Seriously?
Nice kill!
I guess this means things have changed
since the Seijoh match.
Karasuno                             Johzenji
Hinata! Give 'em one more!
A receive from that close up?
If we can touch it...
...we can control it!
All right!
So their play is to touch the ball
before we can hit it into
a space they can't reach.
I'll win the next one!
Hinata, isn't there a move
you haven't done yet today?
Your new special move.
Karasuno                             Johzenji
Nice receive!
Go, Hinata!
Bring it!
All right!
Karasuno                        Johzenji
Match point!
All right, you guys...
Let's play for real.
Simplicity and Fortitude
Johzenji Parents' Association
Got it!
Another synchronized attack?!
Those guys aren't thinking
about when they mess up,
even for a second.
Just the pleasure they
feel when they succeed.
Be careful! That one isn't like before!
All right!
We did it!
Now they've made it into the quarterfinals.
I expected that ending....
Karasuno                             Johzenji
Are we really done? Damn it...
And I was just getting hyped up!
They still look like they want to play.
They're terrifying...
Thanks.
Eh?
It appears that you really do
understand those guys better than I do.
Because of that, they didn't
completely break down.
I guess I should expect
that from a third-year.
No...
Thank you very much!
So I wasn't imagining it.
Their quick is evolving.
All right. I'm gonna go on ahead.
Don't stay too long.
Johzenji High School
Well, I guess, if anything...
I don't mind you guys getting hyped up,
just don't lose control.
There's no one to whip your
butts into shape anymore.
All right, dismissed.
Don't skip your stretches.
Ah, um...
Don't you guys give Runa-chan a hard time.
She's still a first-year, so
I'll be watching you guys.
Also... About your style where you
always go all-out with playing around...
I actually like that a lot.
Let's go. The next team is here.
Th-Thank you very much!
You did it!
Ye-ah!
E-Eekyay?!
You both doing a jumping
high-five at her is a bit much.
R-Right...
Yay! Yay! Yay!
I'm going to stop you tomorrow.
And I'm going to get through!
Shut up!
I wonder if he was waiting
just to tell Hinata that...
The game on court B's done?
That would mean whoever won
that game is our next opponent.
Wakunan                                   Sensho
You can do it, Takeru!
You can do it, Takeru! Nice kill, Takeru!
Takeru
Yeah!
His family's here to cheer him on?!
That's the team Ukai-san said
we need to look out for before
the Inter-High prelims, too...
In order to fight Date Tech again,
we need to beat them first!
Haikyu!!
Congratulations on completing the first day.
Thank you!
Unlike our other opponents, Wakutani South
has third-years left
on the team, just like us.
They are a well-rounded team.
Their defense and tenacity
are close to Nekoma's.
Don't lose your temper just because
you can't get your attack in.
Especially the hyperactive ones and simpletons.
It'll be fine. We'll follow up on them.
Th-Thank you very much.
Damn it. They're more under control
than I made it sound.
Yeah, leave it to me.
All right. We're going to
make it through tomorrow, too.
Karasuno, fight!
Yeah!
Qualifying Tournament Grouping (Boys)
Winner
Go, go, Takeru!
Go, go, Takeru! Go, go, Wakunan!
There are even more than yesterday.
A younger brother?
Why do you look so jealous?
Come on, concentrate.
Go, go, Takeru!
What's the matter, Ukai-kun?
We're going all out, Sensei.
Huh?
It might just be my gut feeling,
Go, go, Takeru! Go, go, Wakunan!
but this Wakunan team
may be hard for our team to handle.
Karasuno                                       Wakunan
Captains.
Let's play.
There'll be no lowering our guard.
We're honored.
Heyo.
Ah, Shimada-san, hello.
Are you by yourself?
Takinoue has work today.
He said he could probably
come by in the afternoon.
Man, I'm getting hyped!
This really gets you fired up, huh?
Hello.
She reminds me of someone...
Hey! Thanks for always
taking care of Ryunosuke.
I'm his older sister, Saeko.
Tanaka's sister!
They look alike.
Ryu! Ryu-chan!
Ne-san!
Geh.
I came to cheer you on!
Let's play!
Get 'em!
The second day begins...
They'd better survive.
Bring it!
Nice serve!
Got it!
Good! First, break through with a quick!
All right!
Hinata, nice kill!
Wh-What the heck was that?!
A quick? Was that just luck?
All right, we're shutting
them down quickly next.
Yes!
Yeah!
What? Wakunan doesn't seem
very surprised by that quick.
There's no one in Karasuno
that you can call a flightless bird anymore.
They're the most outrageous
team in the prefecture.
We're super lucky to be able to play them.
Looks like they've figured out
how to deal with Hinata...
They don't seem panicked at all.
I'm not sure if they're a bad match
or if they're just a team we
won't do well against.
Yeah.
Unlike the trend up until now,
where Karasuno fights a team that
just keeps throwing attacks at them,
we have a problem handling teams
Their #9's serve is powerful!
Don't let your guard down!
that keep their own pace and
deal with us intelligently.
Right!
Seijoh and Nekoma are exactly that.
I see.
Opponents who aren't
surprised by that quick...
Now, what are they gonna do?
Hinata, looks like
a powerhouse school is
on their guard with you.
They've probably been researching you...
Researching you... Researching you...
A powerhouse school... researching me?
Man, you're totally overshadowing us.
But I am able to triumph
over myself from yesterday.
Hey, if you guys are just watching
Hinata, I'm gonna peck yer eyes out.
Well done, Captain.
He knows exactly how to get them going.
Karasuno                               Wakunan
Kageyama, nice serve!
That felt perfect against my hand.
That's intense!
Nice receive!
Pineapple Head is coming in from behind.
He's so fast!
You can do it, Wakunan!
Whoa! From the furthest back?
Tabi, nice kill!
You can do it, Wakunan!
A delayed attack, huh?
So that's Wakunan's weapon,
their combination...
Though their average height is not very high,
you can definitely see why they're
always a top team in the prefecture.
Yeah, but that's not Wakunan's only weapon.
Eh?
Don't keep reacting to the spiker each time!
Go after the ball!
I-I know that! In my head...
But your body acts on its own...
I know how that feels.
Karasuno                              Wakunan
Nice receive!
It's up! Cover!
Takeru! Get the last!
We're going to stop it! Ready, and...
A wipe...
All right!
They were targeting the edge of my hands.
It would appear that Nakashima-kun's
technique in mid-air battles
is as troublesome as his combination.
Nakashima Takeru...
Shiro! One more, nice serve!
His play style might be the most
similar in the prefecture...
to the former Little Giant.
Takeru-ni, go!
Takeru
All right!
Nakashima again! So good!
This is how the pace is going to be...
They won't get too far ahead of us,
but we won't be able to take the lead.
Does this mean that Nakashima-kun
can see really well, just like Hinata-kun?
I don't know just how much Nakashima can see.
Rather than aiming for
small spaces like Hinata,
I think he uses angles.
I think he changes the angle of his spikes.
He'll hit it against the blocker's hand,
to change up the angle of the rebound.
Tsukishima, it's written all over your face.
Concentrate on that receive!
A strong one's coming!
Well, as a blocker, spikers like that
are just plain annoying.
Shiro, one more! Nice serve!
Right into the center!
I knew it was coming, but it's still so fast!
Karasuno's #10 isn't losing to Wakunan's #1.
All right!
Damn it!
Tanaka-san, nice serve!
You almost had it!
Yeah! Leave it to me!
You're reading them, though.
You'll get the next one for sure!
Half of that is just trying
to get you riled up.
Don't give in.
Oh?
It appears that Wakunan has one
blocker on Hinata for sure,
but won't pursue, apparently.
They put a tall middle blocker on Hinata,
and rather than stop him,
they limit his course and
make it easier to receive.
It's impossible to completely stop Hinata...
They understand that,
but they're still not going to
let Hinata do what he wants.
But...
Our next generation of Little Giants
are going all out in a mid-air battle, but...
Don't forget about our kingly ace, either.
Right.
Looks like I don't need to say anything.
Nice serve!
I knew it. Their middle blocker is on Hinata.
And the other two are dealing
with our other spikers.
However, if you're going to stop our ace...
You need to bring an iron wall.
Damn it...
Asahi-san!
Nice kill!
Right...
All right, we're good.
Everyone's calm. This is
how we're going proceed.
Damn it...
It's okay. Let's get the next one!
Karasuno                                    Wakunan
#3! #3!
All right!
Is Karasuno's attacking from the left more?
That goatee guy is super strong.
What?!
Karasuno               Wakunan
All right!
Hey, they finally have a two-point lead.
It finally feels like the match is moving.
All right! This is our chance!
Let's make sure we take it!
Right!
Damn it!
Hey, Tabi.
Over on the right, in the third row,
there's a super cute girl.
Seriously?
Whoa!
Keep getting the ball to me!
Right, right...
I'm gonna get this next one, no matter what!
Good work, Takeru.
He definitely knows Tabi well.
Fight!
I'm used to surviving in a Jurassic Park
filled with free-willed people.
I'm gonna go play.
What?!
If my house is Jurassic Park,
Yay!
this is just a zoo.
Makoto, where are you going?!
Okay, say "Ah."
Don't underestimate the second
brother who's been through hell.
Aah.
We're Wakunan, known for our tenacity!
This is when we show what we're worth!
Yeah!
Their captain's a pretty
good foundation, as well.
Yeah. If that last game
was a bunch of playing,
this match is going to be about the captains.
#11! #11!
Nice cover!
He got it again!
I'm counting on you!
They're both great at connecting.
Asahi!
Nice, Akiu!
He got it again!
Cover! Cover!
It's hard to even watch.
This is the longest rally of the day.
Whoever gets this is going
to get the momentum of the game.
Don't let your guard down!
We're definitely going to get this one!
Yeah!
Takeru, I'm counting on you!
Three blockers!
Another wipe...
Go!
Get the last one over!
We did it!
All right!
Er...
Huh?
Daichi-san?
That's so cool, having
your family cheer you on.
I would hate it.
Why?
Well, I actually understand
how Tsukishima feels.
Huh?
I'm not sure how to feel about having
the same opinion as Tanaka-san.
Episode 17: "The Battle Without Will Power"
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"The Battle Without Will Power."