Episode 2  Umaru and Ebina-chan
Today was another rough day...
But it's about to get rougher.
Shonen
Jumpu
Welcome home, Onii-chan!
Now make me dinner!
I'm home...
Hm?
That's not true.
No, really. Everyone says
you're amazing, Umaru-chan.
Welcome home,
Onii-chan!
Huh?! What happened to you?
Oh, stop. This is how I always am.
No, usually you're...
Ebina-chan's over, so you know the drill.
Oh, now I get it...
Sorry about that, Ebina-chan!
But it's pretty rare for Umaru to
bring someone over to the house.
G-Good evening... Pardon the intrusion.
Whose room is this? It's so clean!
Ebina-chan and I were having a study session.
Ebina Nana-chan, who also lives in our
apartment building, is Umaru's classmate.
Thanks for being so nice to Umaru.
All of the online order boxes are put away...
Umaru... Did you put them away?
Umaru, who hates doing anything?!
Ebina-chan!
Y-Yes?
Ebina-chan... You can come over anytime.
O-O-O-Okay...
Maybe Umaru can be
self-reliant with her around!
O-Onii-san...
I want my cola...
Th-Thank you for dinner.
You were so kind to let me eat with you.
You can come over anytime.
See you later, Ebina-chan.
Nothing's better than cola after
holding back for so long!
The taste of the devil!
I-Is he going to yell at me?
Drink from a cup.
Also, I bought some Takoyaki Snack today.
What?! Tako-Suna?! Awesome!
Since she cleaned the place today,
I won't say anything.
This might actually motivate her
to do things on her own.
Umaru, I'll get the bath ready, so you
can have the Tako-Suna after that...
Hey, Onii-chan, these are wasabi-flavored!
I can't eat wasabi!
Damn it, Umaru!
What?! I'm the one who's mad here!
Onii-san...
I knew it. Umaru-chan's brother is so nice!
What are you mad about?!
Why shouldn't I be?!
Sunday
I ended up playing online
games all night again.
Hardly anyone's left online now that it's morning,
so I have nothing to do until Asahi's
Sunday morning anime block.
I guess I'll have my morning cola.
What to do...
He looks so happy.
I wonder if it's because he's been
coming home looking like a zombie lately.
It's his first day off in a while,
so he's totally out.
I guess Onii-chan gets tired, too.
But I'm still waking him up!
Onii-chan! It's time for work!
Mornin', Onii-chan!
This little...
Why are you up at this hour?
I pulled an all-nighter.
Now, come have a Pop's showdown with me
until Sunday morning anime time, Onii-chan!
You doofus. I'm going back to bed.
Awaken! Onii-chan fever!
So annoying...
I'm exhausted from work.
Oh, this is his serious,
"too tired to even fight" face.
I guess it can't be helped, then.
Sleep for a while.
Thanks.
She probably wouldn't even consider
why this makes me feel guilty.
Thirty minutes will be enough, right?
Teenage standards for
required sleep time are scary!
Give me a break, would you?
I haven't slept at all yet.
I haven't slept, either!
Then you should sleep, too.
But Sunday morning anime...
All right. Goodnight, Onii-chan.
She took that rather well...
Huh?
What are you doing? You should be on the bed.
My innocent Onii-chan won't be able
to sleep while I have my outside face on.
You have no choice but to
play with me, Onii-chan!
Now, give up, Onii-chan!
I'm sure she was plotting something,
but she just fell asleep.
I see... She's been playing
one-player games lately.
I'll play with you today.
But first, I'm gonna catch
some more Z's, too...
Why are you asleep too, Onii-chan?!
I missed both the morning
and afternoon anime blocks!
Wait, this is my fault?!
Here you go. Please take one!
Here you go.
Aww, how cute.
Huge Rock-Paper-Scissors Contest
The Healing Local Mascot
Necolumbus Big Plushie!
Super Big Size!
A rock-paper-scissors contest for a
super big-sized Necolumbus plushie.
I'm home.
Onii-chan! It's an emergency!
Wha— What? What's wrong?
Now, let's go, Onii-chan.
Umaru, don't tell me the emergency is...
Yep! I'm totally going to get it!
Wh-What's so urgent about this?!
I turned down a weekend shift for this!
Now, now, Onii-chan.
It's important to take time off, too.
I don't even want this thing!
You could have gone by yourself.
Huh? What are you talking about? I...
wanted to hang out with you, Onii-chan.
Huh?
Onii-chan, it's rough on you
working all the time, isn't it?
So if I don't resort to something
like this, you won't take time off.
Yeah...
It's true that I've been so
focused on work lately
that I haven't made time for Umaru.
All right! I guess a day
off is meant for rest.
Yep.
Don't worry, Umaru.
I might not look it, but I'm really
good at rock-paper-scissors.
Thanks, Onii-chan.
We are handing out rock-paper-scissors
contest tickets over here.
Please wait in line.
D-Damn her...
All right, I'm gonna hit the shop
by the south entrance.
You handle the north entrance shop, okay?
What?
Here you go.
Not only did she bring me
to increase her odds of winning,
but she totally just went to another store.
I wanted to hang out with you, Onii-chan.
She tricked me for the possibility
of getting two of those things!
Big Rock-Paper-Scissors Contest
All right, everyone.
The rock-paper-scissors contest is starting!
Only those of you who beat me at
rock-paper-scissors will come up on stage.
All right, here we go.
All right!
What in the world am I doing?
Okay, the rock-paper-scissors contest
has reached the final round.
I made it to the finals...
This young man in the glasses
and this girl will go one-on-one!
Huh? Ebina-chan?
Eh?! Ah... Huh? O-O-Onii-san?!
Y-Yeah...
All right, you two. Here we go!
What?!
Rock, paper...
You're really good at rock-paper-scissors.
Well, I heard that, psychologically,
using either rock or paper gives you
a better chance of winning.
This isn't good... Ebina-chan
might have really wanted this.
I wonder if this'll make things
awkward between her and Umaru...
Ebina-chan, here.
Huh?
You can have it.
I can't take it when my little
sister's friend wanted it.
N-No, it's okay!
You really wanted it, right?
I'm sure this thing would
be happier with you, too.
Thank you very much...
Yoshida Apartments
New Tenants Wanted!
R-Really. Thank you very much!
No problem. See you later.
U-Umaru, how long have you...
Since the shop!
I lost right away, so I went
to the north entrance shop.
O-Oh...
Why did you give it to Ebina-chan?!
That makes no sense!
You four-eyed corporate slave!
Hey, wait...
I-I did it for you!
That wasn't for me at all!
S-Stop it!
Onii-san really is... so nice...
A Few Days Later
Delivery!
In the end, she got the giant
Necolumbus through a net auction...
Welcome, Necolumbus!
at my expense.
Last Fantasy 15
Finally on Sale!
Onii-chan! Buy me Last Fantasy 15!
No. I bought you Wyvern Quest not long ago.
Umaru, we're here to buy groceries today.
I'm not buying you a game.
I know, Onii-chan.
Then why are you giving me that expectant look?
Onii-chan is weak against pressure,
so if I throw a tantrum in public,
he'll buy it for me.
Even if she throws a tantrum in public,
I need to make sure I don't buy it.
All right. This should do it.
Almost time to head to the game shop...
Oh, Ebina-chan.
What?!
Oh, h-hello, Onii-san!
Umaruun
Oh? Ebina-chan.
What a coincidence. Are you shopping, too?
Yeah. I always shop for groceries here.
Oh, I see.
Her "outside face" is so sweet, as always...
I've got it!
Um... Are you sure you
don't mind buying me lunch?
Yeah. It is lunchtime, after all.
Well, if you insist...
Wow... Everything looks so delicious.
She won't be able to beg for the
game in front of Ebina-chan.
You have to learn some restraint.
Curse you, Onii-chan!
Using an underhanded tactic like this...
I can't throw a tantrum in front of Ebina-chan.
Thank you for waiting.
Does this complete your order?
Yes.
Th-This is the first time I've
been to a family restaurant.
Huh? You don't eat out much?
They had some back home in Akita, too, but...
Oh, thank you.
I mostly make food at home.
That's pretty admirable,
considering you live on your own.
Don't you think so, Umaru?
I'll put some ketchup on your
omelet rice, Onii-chan.
Okay...
There.
Game
Nao
Game, game, game...
This serving dish is a bit small, but it's cute.
Oh, that's to put your empty shells in.
Game, game, game...
Game
Why are you ignoring me, Onii-chan?!
Game! Game!
How embarrassing... I really don't
know anything about these things.
This is your first time,
so it's to be expected.
Onii-chan, say "ah."
Go on, Ebina-chan, before it gets cold.
Th-Thank you...
Nuuramu
Argh!
Onii-chan, you jerk! Four-eyes!
Hurry up and buy me the game!
H-Hey...
Buy it!
Let go!
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
Onii-chan! Hurry up and buy it!
Hey, stop!
Game! Game! Game! Game!
Hey, you sure you want to do that?
Ebina-chan's right here...
Game! Game! Game!
Umaruun
Did she see me?
Restaurants in the city
are so gosh darn good!
Oh, I'm sorry. It was so delicious, I just...
That was Akita dialect...
I-I'm saved...
Good for you, Umaru-chan.
Yeah!
In the end,
he was forced
to buy it.
Good morning, Ebina-chan.
Oh, g-good morning.
You two are together again?
You're such good friends.
Umaru, hurry up and eat!
Ebina-chan's already waiting.
1 Year Prior
I'll be fine!
We been to Tokyo lotsa times.
Yeah, but you ain't been there all by yerself.
Visitin' somewhere and livin' there
ain't the same thing.
Yeah, but I cain't go ta
school in Tokyo if'n I'm here.
Seconds!
Ya still want more?
Akita Airport
Yer a careless sort, Nana.
Won't they call ya a country bumpkin?
I'll be fine! Fine!
I been practicin' standard Japanese,
and I bought me some popular
clothes from Eion Mall.
There's nothin' to worry about.
Why are so many people looking at me?
I-It's just my imagination.
I'm only thinking that because I'm nervous.
I just need to act natural.
But If I act too natural,
my dialect will slip out...
Would you like some coffee?
Oh, y-yes.
Here you go.
Th-Thank you very much.
So many people...
B-But I shouldn't look
around so much as I walk.
Huh? Wh-What's goin' on?
Weird... My clothes ain't funny or anything...
My dialect didn't slip out...
I haven't even spoken.
Damn, her boobs are huge!
H-Huh?
Lots of people were staring at me
all the way from Akita to Tokyo.
And yet...
No one will look me in the eyes.
Yoshida Apartments
New Tenants Wanted!
Hello.
He's the first one...
to look me in the eyes...
Um...
O-Oh, I'm sorry.
I-I-I just moved here today...
Oh, I see. I'm Doma from room 201.
Nice to meet you.
Um... I'm Ebina from room 101.
If you need any help with
anything, let me know.
Okay.
Onii-san...
Because Onii-san's been there, I...
Good morning, Ebina-chan.
G-Good morning, Umaru-chan.
Morning. Sorry to keep you waiting.
U-U-Um, good morning...
Uh, right...
We'll be late! Let's go, Ebina-chan!
R-Right...
E-E-Excuse us, O-O-Onii... Onii...
Ebina-chan!
Wait up, Umaru-chan!
Next Time
Episode 3  Umaru and Her Student
Now we have matching Necolumbuses.
Yes. Put together, they look like siblings.
Well, since you got yours first,
I guess yours would be "Onii-chan."
What?! So I was doing those things to Onii-san...
What did you do?!