Oh, Hitoka-chan. Are you done changing?
I'll walk with you, so hold on a sec.
I'm going to go change, too.
No, it's okay.
I actually think I should be walking
with you, or something, or...
Don't worry about it.
What's wrong, Sensei?
Why the serious face?
Oh, well...
Apparently, the bus we were supposed
to take for the away games in Tokyo
was booked by another club,
so it doesn't look like we'll get it.
It looks like it's going to cost us
a lot more than expected,
so I was trying to figure out what to do.
I'll try talking to a few more alumni.
I'm sure this problem'll
come up again in the future.
I apologize. I'll try reaching out, as well.
Well, if all else fails,
I do have some savings.
No, no, no. You need to save that for
your future wedding, or something.
And don't do that with your hand!
Yachi-san!
Yachi-san, are you gonna be our manager?
Uh, um...
You will, right?
Hey, first-year girl, hey!
We hope that you will join the
Karasuno High School volleyball team.
Huh?
When you're around, Kiyoko-san talks a lot.
What kind of invitation is that, you idiots?!
Sorry these guys are so stupid.
No, not at all!
Um... I'm flattered.
I've never tried to do something on my own,
or had someone need me for anything...
Even in drama club, I've only been an extra.
Like Townsperson B or a tree.
A tree?
So when Shimizu-senpai worked so
hard to recruit a Townsperson B,
like me, who has no experience
or knowledge of volleyball,
I was really happy.
But I'm sure I'm not much—
I totally get how you feel.
Even if Kiyoko-san said,
"I'm going to steal money
from you, so follow me."
I'd still follow her.
You're so manly, Ryu!
Uh, I think that's a bit different.
That sounds sorta awesome!
Looks like Tanaka's saying something again.
Oh, that reminds me...
From: Kozume Kenma
Subject: None
We made it through the first round.
This week is round two of prelims.
Damn! Nekoma's so awesome!
I'm getting fired up!
Haikyu!!
Episode 3  Townsperson B
Hitoka.
I've got to go to one more meeting,
so I'm going to be home late.
Okay. See you later, Mom.
Make sure you clean up over here.
Okay.
Hm? What's this?
Karasuno High School
Boys' Volleyball Club
Members and Manager
Seeking Members!!
Please Contact Shimizu Kiyoko in Class 3-2
Oh, well...
I was invited to be a manager
for the boys' volleyball team.
Volleyball?
Yeah...
Oh, I'll be right there.
Just a moment.
Yes, ma'am.
Didn't Karasuno's volleyball team
make it to nationals before?
It's a strong school, right?
Yes.
Apparently they're getting strong again.
The taxi's here.
Do you even know anything about volleyball?
Well, I plan on learning more about it.
That's fine and all,
but joining passionate people when you
aren't going to give it your all
is the rudest thing you could do.
I'm counting on you to
make breakfast tomorrow.
Oh, right...
Senpai, why did you have to say it like that?
You're so cold.
I-I didn't mean it like that!
You're probably the reason why
Hitoka-chan's a bit negative, Senpai.
I just want her to be stronger!
But if she's going to give up
just because of what I said,
she'll lose hope over even
smaller things in the future, too.
Girls' Changing Room
Club Application
Is something troubling you?
By the way, I did play sports,
but I had no prior experience with
volleyball or being a manager.
I don't think everyone has to like
something before giving it a try.
I don't think you need an unwavering will
or lofty motive just to get started.
Sometimes things that you start on a whim
end up becoming very important to you, too.
To get started, I think you just need
a little bit of curiosity.
Hinata and Tsukishima.
Yes!
Yes.
Since you two are middle blockers,
The floor's wet. Could I get the mop?
you have to be able to use
blocks as your weapon.
Yup. Where is it?
I need you to be so good at blocking,
you could stop Ushiwaka.
Right around here. Thanks.
Keep that in mind for today's
practice match, too.
Gotcha!
Right...
There's no way we could block Ushiwaka...
All right, get back to practice.
Right!
By the way, Sensei, how are their exams?
Especially with the four idiots.
Um...
Ouginishi will arrive in
four and a half hours.
Right!
All right, Hitoka-chan.
Would you line up some chairs
around the court there?
Let's see... Eight of them.
Uh, right!
If they're heavy, one at a time is fine.
Kiyoko-san is smiling.
I-I'm fine.
The world is at peace yet again today.
Want some help?
No, it's fine. You do your own thing.
Okay!
I'm not gonna lose today!
Um... Today's match is
a practice match, right?
Yup.
Um... I was wondering why you can
study so hard to play in away games
and get so fired up for a practice game.
Huh? Because I want to get stronger and win.
I-I see...
I'm sure you have your reasons.
Huh? Reasons?
Reasons why I wanna win?
Oh. Yeah...
Do you need a reason not to want to lose?
Hey, Kageyama.
Is there a reason you don't want to lose?
Wha? How would I know?
Is there a reason you want
to eat when you're hungry?
Right? Hmm...
So this on the same level as hunger?
Sorry... that was an inane question.
"Inane question"?
"A foolish question, or a comment said to
abase oneself after asking such a question."
We just went over it the other day!
Thank you for having us!
Gather round!
Right!
All right. We're going to line up, too.
Okay!
Whoa...
Everyone's big over there, too.
Do you need a reason not to want to lose?
I don't think you need an unwavering will
or lofty motive just to get started.
Move back a bit, Hinata.
Oh, right.
Bow!
Let's play!
Haikyu!!
So we're playing Karasuno today?
They're the, uh...
The "fallen giant" and
the "flightless bird," right?
I don't think those names apply anymore.
Huh?
At the IH prelims, they played
Aoba Johsai a full set
Ouginishi High School
Volleyball Club
and had a deuce with them until
their scores got into the 30s.
Seriously?!
Oh, but they do have
Nishinoya from Chidoriyama
and Kageyama from Kitagawa Daiichi, right?
They do, but...
Senpai?
Their #10, especially...
Karasuno's center is a first-year
with impressive physical abililty.
Sometimes, his presence changes
the game to an astonishing extent.
It appears that Karasuno's transforming.
Thank you for coming so far!
Nice kill!
We're gonna start soon, so get changed!
Right.
Hinata, that's backwards.
Like Jamila.
Sorry, you'll have to get used to this.
Asahi-san, that string
in your hair is awesome!
String?
It's a hairband.
Well, I guess I feel confident
if you say that, Nishinoya.
Straighten up!
Trying to change your image, Asahi-san?
No, the other day...
What is it, Shimizu?
Azumane, you hair braid is so tight
it makes me think you'll go bald.
That's why...
I need to be careful, too.
There are some hot bald guys, though.
I'm not bald!
Aren't you going to get into
your uniform, Tanaka-san?
I'm about to!
A flock of birds...
A flock... True, they are crows.
But once the game starts,
they actually get along great.
Gather round!
This is our first match with another
team since the Inter-High prelims.
You haven't forgotten your
frustrations from then, have you?
Right!
All right, go out there and raise some hell!
Karasuno, fight!
Yeah!
Here we go!
Have we played this team before?
No, we haven't.
Come on, bring it!
Get a point!
Yeah!
Nice serve, Kageyama!
Ouginishi      Karasuno
Thanks!
Wait, did they just score a point?
One more!
Hitoka-chan, the score.
Oh, r-right.
Cover! Cover!
#8! #8!
Only one blocker... Go!
Ouginishi     Karasuno
Nice, Nishinoya!
Hey, don't run!
What amazing reflexes...
Kageyama!
Right!
Karasuno
All right!
It looked like their arms would be torn
off if they touched the ball.
Asahi-san, nice kill!
Nice receive, Daichi-san!
They're really calm....
Left!
Ouginishi    Karasuno
All right!
Wow, that's so loud...
Isn't it, though?
But once their attention is taken
away by the two powerhouses,
they lose sight of the small crow.
I can fly!
Ouginishi    Karasuno
If they're one step too late,
they can't catch up to him.
Not yet! More!
I can hit higher than that!
Yeah.
He's still not satisfied.
All right!
Thank you very much!
Ouginishi           Karasuno
Amazing! That was amazing!
I'm only watching, and yet, I, I...
Did you feel overwhelmed?!
Yeah, I did!
Then be our manager!
Huh? Um, uh...
His conversations usually
don't make any sense.
Do it, Yachi-san!
Joining passionate people when you
aren't going to give it your all
is the rudest thing you could do.
For an amazing team like this,
a Townsperson B like me
with no knowledge of sports
is just going to get in the way.
Come to think of it,
I played Townsperson B, too.
Huh?
But I tried to stand out more than
the lead and I got in trouble.
Townsperson B... Ha.
Hey, don't make fun of me, you jerk!
Townsperson B has its
own kind of awesomeness!
I see.
Then what kind of role
did you play, Kageyama?
The moon.
Is that even needed?
Damn, that's cool!
"Townsperson B has its own
kind of awesomeness."
I've played a horse before.
A horse?!
Man, you're a lifesaver!
Yachi-san, thanks for helping
us study on a Saturday!
Thanks.
Sure. Let's do our best on the exam.
Oh, thanks for having us.
No problem. Was she a good teacher?
Yeah!
I'm gonna ace that exam
for sure now! I think!
You think?
Or rather, I won't let Yachi-san's
kindness go to waste!
Kindness... "To have a caring heart."
"A term used to express a caring
attitude one has for another."
Oh, the definition of the
word we studied earlier.
I see. Good luck on your exam.
Thanks!
Let's go to Tokyo together, Yachi-san!
Huh? R-Right...
I haven't even explained
anything to my mom yet!
See you next week!
B-Bye-bye...
Hitoka, what's this about
away games in Tokyo?
W-Well, um, uh...
Oh, I'm sorry I'm late. Let's go.
All right, I'm heading to a meeting.
I'll be back late again tonight.
Oh, right.
Okay, let's go.
Huh? Uh, wait, Senpai.
Weren't you trying to say
something, Hitoka-chan?
Are you okay?
No, it's nothing.
Go ahead.
Okay... See you later.
Yup.
Come on, Senpai...
Yachi-san's notes are so awesome!
Notes should always be like this.
If Yachi-san joins, we'll have two managers.
We totally sound like a champion school.
Yeah.
What? You don't want her to join?
That's totally up to her.
You never agree with anything.
You're not very popular, are you?
Mind your own business!
Oh, crap! I forgot my textbook
at Yachi-san's house!
I'm gonna go back and get it.
See ya, Kageyama!
Here.
Comprehensive Japanese
Thanks, Yachi-san!
That was close!
I'm glad I realized it.
U-Um, Hinata-san... Do you have a sec?
Sure.
Huh?
You're not sure you want to join
over something like that?
I've hit Kageyama in the back
of the head with a serve,
thrown up on Tanaka-san's lap,
and accidentally knocked the
vice principal's toupee off,
but I'm still playing volleyball just fine!
Would you really say you were fine, then?
But you want to do this, right, Yachi-san?
Y-Yes...
Then you totally should!
Right.
Is what your mom said bothering you?
Uh, um, no...
It's just that, um...
Then why don't you tell her?
She went to the station, right?
Y-Yeah...
What is this?!
I feel like I'm in some shojo manga!
Wow, he's fast! He runs so fast!
Wait...
Yachi-san, at this rate,
you can't move forward.
If you want to do this,
you need to tell her.
Whether I want to join
the volleyball club or not,
at this rate, I'll never be able
to change from my worthless self.
I have to say it with my own mouth.
Yeah... I have to say it.
Thanks, Hinata.
Subway Platforms
You weren't strong to begin
with either, were you, Senpai?
You can't expect the same
strength from Hitoka-chan.
Hitoka-chan's just starting to get stronger.
Mom!
Hitoka?!
Townsperson B can fight, too!
Huh?!
Townsperson B?
I'm going to be the volleyball club manager!
I-I see... Do your best.
I will!
What do you want to do for dinner?!
I-I'll eat at home.
Roger!
All right! Two managers!
We're like champions!
Um, I have a favor to ask
you and Kageyama-kun...
What?
You're crying?!
Shut up. Give me a tissue.
Pardon me.
Takeda-sensei.
Yes?
Um, I overheard that we might not have
enough money for the away games...
May I talk to you about that?
How He Lives Beggars Belief,
Constantly Nicking Old Foreign Necklaces.
Nathan Magee Always Sits Patiently,
Seeing Clearly Around,
Knowing Careless Security
Titillates Very Criminal Minds.
"Experience." E-Experience...
That won't do at all.
Mom!
I wouldn't even notice it at all.
What do you want to show?
Who is your target audience?
How will you catch the attention
of people walking by?
Truly, the Little Giant!
I have a favor to ask
you and Kageyama-kun...
I want to make a poster
for the volleyball club,
so would you let me take a
picture of you spiking a ball?
Okay, here we go.
Alright.
Here we go, Kageyama.
Yeah.
The Crows Head Back
Into The National Skies
The Little Giant Returns
The Karasuno High School Volleyball
Club is Requesting Donations.
Wow...
We're done!
How'd you do?
All right, please pass your exams forward.
1st Period: Modern Literature
2nd Period: English
3rd Period: Math
Faculty Room
Oh, Takeda-sensei.
Someone's on the phone
saying they saw a poster,
and they'd like to know where to donate
the money for the volleyball club...
It's hot...
It's just for a little while.
Come on. You, too, Tsukishima.
Come here! Line up.
So, we've finished our exams,
and starting today,
Yachi-san will officially be
joining us as our manager.
Here.
Karasuno High School
Volleyball Club
Ready, and...
Welcome to the Karasuno
High School Volleyball Club!
It's a pleasure to work with you!
All right. The Tokyo away
games are coming up.
All that's left is...
All right, I'm returning the exams.
Aww...
Shut it.
All right, Ando...
Yes.
Next, Enokira.
Oyama.
The exams are finally coming back.
Yeah...
It'll be fine! You studied so hard!
Huh? Did I even write my name on it?!
What? That'd be a problem before
the exam even started!
Episode 4: Center Ace
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"Center Ace."