Aah...
Another peaceful day...
How right you are, Master!
This room is... the picture of peace for me!
'Sup, Kirie?!
I've told you...
stop barging into my room!
And that room... is the picture of HELL for me.
I wish things could stay like this forever!
Huh? Someone's here.
Alex!
As of today... I'LL be your girlfriend, Big Brother!
I bought this on the way over!
It's that adventure game everyone's been talking about:
"My Younger Sister is My Girlfriend (BOOM!)"
Or, "YoungBOOM!" for short.
Hold on, Sensei. Who is this person?
"Sensei"?!
Uh, this is my friend, Kirie.
F-f-friend...?
This is Alex. He works with my brother.
It's a pleasure. Please, call me "Alex."
DAZZLE!
You stood in line for this?
It was a pre-order.
Ooh! Is this girl the main heroine?
YoungBOOM! has a famous voice actress for each
of the younger sister roles, so there is no "main."
However! This character, Hikari, is based on the famous
actor Hikaru Kongo, who's really popular right now.
So, naturally, she's become a favorite character.
They've already started selling merchandise
for this character online.
Ah! We've got some options!
Um... B, maybe?
I... I guess that would be all right.
But only to the school gates.
Otherwise, people will think will that we're classmates.
Her voice is great, isn't it?
Even better than on her last show.
She does a good job
of not sounding too lovey-dovey, huh?
What should I do? I can't keep up
with what they're saying!
Kirie?
Oh, no! I'm the only one who
can't follow the conversation!
I can't have the Master scolding me for it!
Ah! There she is, in the hallway!
Hmm... this is a tough one, isn't it?
Well, I guess we should go with "C."
These types tend to be shy, so I doubt
they'd enjoy being spoken to at school.
"SHY"?!
Look, it's Motoba!
Ah! It is!
Her gaze is as sharp as ever, huh?
Motoba!
I think... "A" would be a good choice.
"A - Talk to her"?
In my experience, that makes your
Favorability Rating go down...
I-in any case, pretending you didn't see her
is out of the question!
So... shall we save the game and try both options?
Um... s-sure.
Hey... c'mon, don't talk to me at school.
Enough's enough. You can't just ignore me!
Ka-poww!
I-I did it!
Motoba!
Thank you for always spending time
with my younger sister.
Motoba... you want to go home together?
Y... y-y... yes!
Did you buy a new game?
It's "Chomp Chomp Watching"!
Oh, I've heard of that.
They're always running commercials for it.
Chomp, chomp! Watching 'em chomp and chomp!
Chomp, chomp! Chomp, chomp!
I've gotta keep up with the new trends,
so I've had my eye on this for a while now!
This game is for kids, so I can finish it by tomorrow!
Be sure to take breaks, though.
I've already gotten the hang of this thing.
This sure does have a lot of side quests...
I'm ho... Huh?!
Umaru, you're still playing that game?
Yeah. I can't find any of the super rare items...
Your eyes look straight-up DEAD!
How long have you been playing that today?
Uh... about 10 hours.
Come to think of it, she had the same look when
she played that social-network game for an entire day...
Once she gets into it, she just can't stop, huh?
Well, she'll probably get tired of it soon.
Woo-hoo! This week's JUMPU is awesome!
Don't play games while you're eating!
And you're using the touch pen to eat!
Go to sleep!
Get up!
Get out already! GET OUT!
It looks like more and more people
are playing this game way too much...
Good morning.
Alex! This isn't good at all! It's already 10:00!
I'm sorry. I just couldn't find any super rare items...
Th-this game is bad news.
I have to do something, and fast!
A way to make someone... quit the game?
Yeah. One of our junior workers is playing it too much,
and it's gotten me worried.
The truth is, this is about Umaru...
I don't really play games,
so I don't know that much about them.
I'm sorry, but I don't play them either.
Huh? Really?
Ah! Still, if there's something I really like...
I'm sure I won't be able to stop myself.
I-I-I'm sorry!
This is no help at all, is it?
That's not true.
Thank you, Ebina.
Umaru!
Umaru! I bought a game too!
Huh? What gives?!
Well, it looks like a lot of fun.
You're ready to hop on the big wave, huh?
Let's play co-op!
Well, let's stop here.
Huh? But we've only been playing for an hour!
When a game's as fun as this,
it's a shame to play too much at once, right?
I like to enjoy it a little at a time. Well, time to make lunch.
When she likes something, she just can't quit.
That's why I'll teach her...
the way to TRULY enjoy something.
This super rare item...
Our collection's complete!
It sure was a long road getting here!
These modern games have gotten pretty tough, huh?
Anyway...
At least now she'll have gotten over
Chomp Chomp Watching.
Everyone out there...!
We have a big announcement!
"Chomp Chomp Watching 2" will be going on sale soon!
And this time, there will be different versions:
Truffle, Foie Gras, and Caviar!
Y-you!
It can't be...
With that horn, there's no doubt about it...
It's the demon.
Taihei the Demon!
That's how Taihei was back in high school.
Stop lying already.
Jeez, what the heck? That was a lie?
Well, it was exaggerated a little but it wasn't a lie, right?
He was a test-taking demon who always got 100s,
so they called him Taihei the Demon.
That's news to me.
They called you that all the time.
Like, even when you met Kanau...
That's enough talk about the past.
I'm gonna get dinner ready.
Is Big Brother mad?
Nah, he's a good guy.
He wouldn't get mad over something like this.
Taihei wouldn't yell or do something half-cocked.
Sure, he'll scold you,
but he doesn't actually get MAD, right?
Yeah...
Get up, Umaru!
Eat your vegetables!
Listen closely, Umaru...
Ah! But he can get super cranky
if you bug him when he's cooking.
True enough.
Say, Tanukichi...
Huh? What's up?
I'd sure like to see Ebina again.
Does she not come over often?
Don't tell me...!
But, why Ebina?
Oh! You wanna hear, Tanukichi?
Ebina is SUPER kind, right?
Yeah...
I started thinking, a girl like that
could make friends with my sister for sure.
Sis always has a scary look on her face,
so I don't think she has many friends.
Ebina doesn't seem like the type
who'd worry about that, right?
You're a good guy, Bomba! Ebina would-
Huh? For real?! Like, what's "good"?
Seriously, what's good?!
I often think to myself, "Self, you ARE a good guy!"
Like, I think the area around my eyes TOTALLY
makes me look like a good guy, right?
You really get me, Tanukichi!
You're in for it now!
They sure are getting worked up...
Metal Nyankosu - Metal Beam!
Bomba takes 105 points damage!
Pew, pew, pew! Bomba is almost out of Life!
Ah! It's raining! I have to bring the laundry in!
Metal Nyankosu merely shakes its head!
I'm going to go get it. So stay out of the kitchen!
Jeez, and these were almost dry!
Let's taste test!
All clear, all clear!
All clear, all clear.
HANDS OFF!
It's... Taihei the Demon!
L-look, we're sorry for barging in here, but you're getting
a bit TOO angry. What's going on, Taihei?
I-I'm sorry.
I put the lid on just in case when I stepped away
from the stove, but I didn't make myself clear...
I was heating up oil.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
But, why oil?
In the 20 years I've known you,
that was the first time I've seen you get mad!
Huh? Twenty years?!
Quit lying. It's been more like 10, right?
Kirie! Let's hang out!
C'mon in!
Master! I hope you're well!
Welcome, Kirie.
Oh, it's Cold and Bristly Girl.
Yeah, she doesn't look too happy...
Wait, "bristly"? Like, thorny?
Well, she only seems to go from cold to painfully rude,
so: Cold and Bristly Girl.
I'd say that's some nice naming, wouldn't you?
I'm not sure I'm following any of this...
Cold and Bristly Girl!
Anyway, the timing couldn't be better.
I brought a present with me today.
Here, Sensei.
It's an Italian cat figurine.
I gave one to your brother as well.
Ah! It's Metal Nyankosu!
Sorry. The truth is...
Whoa! You've had this customized
all nice and cute, haven't you?
Huh? Uh, yeah, that's right.
Please, have this one as well.
But, what is this present for?
It's just my way of thanking you
for all you've done for me.
Here. This is for you, Cold and Bristly Girl.
Huh?! No...!
I don't even want this, but I totally accepted it!
Come to think of it, this is the first time I've gotten
a present from someone who wasn't a family member...
Shukaa!
This is the Damage version of Madam Black Death Devil!
Her Damage powers make her
already-erotic clothing even MORE erotic!
No thank you!
Aah, I'm so glad that this made you happy.
Honestly, I was surprised by your choice
in that game we played before.
I never dreamed someone could
beat me at a girl's game!
This is my all-time favorite figurine.
It's only right that you have it!
That doesn't make me happy at all! And I don't know
how to react when getting a present I don't want!
I never thought you'd get THIS happy!
You sure lucked out, huh, Kirie?
Also, this thing is really well made!
You can only buy it at anime events.
That's it! I'll give it to my Master!
If it's mine, it should be all right to give it away!
I can't have something so LEWD
go anywhere near my Master!
I-I'll be going now!
Huh? Already?
Well, if you're all free, we'll be having a Christmas party!
Yaaay!
Christmas has no place in this house!
Huh? C'mon, give us SOMETHING!
Hey, Kirie! When is your birthday?
Never mind...
I'll go buy you a present!
No, this cake is plenty!
I-I couldn't...
Oh, it's Cold and Bristly Girl.
You sure lucked out, huh, Kirie?
YOU SURE LUCKED OUT, HUH, KIRIE?
Note: German for "Every rose has its thorn."
Keine Rose Ohne Dornen.
Once you crave it, there's no going back.
And right now, your burger combo meal
comes with CRISPY NUGGETS!
I'M LOVING... HAMBURGERS!
Where...
Where do they get off using a commercial like this?!
Now I want a hamburger!
Hamburger...
Wake up, Umaru.
It sure feels like winter now, huh?
Hamburger...
U-um, here's a picture from when
we went to the movies the other day.
Hamburger...
I wish to go somewhere
during our winter vacation, indeed!
Would you like to come to my house?
Is there anywhere you want to go, Umaru?
Hamburger?
Oh, no! I said it without thinking!
Hamburger...
Shwburger!
How right you are! Mention hamburgers,
and of course that means GERMANY!
Speaking of, you mentioned in your class introduction
that you're from Germany, right?
Umaru, how kind of you to remember!
Huh? Uh, well...
Indeed! Let's all go feast on Japanese hamburgers!
I-I've never been here before.
M-me neither.
Oh, really?
This is one place you can NOT go to
unless you're with friends!
Let's proceed!
Welcome!
S-Sylphin! Which should we choose?
I recommend one of the combo meals, indeed!
"Once you crave it, there's no going back."
I'M LOVING HAMBURGERS!
This convenience store burger and fries
go great with cola!
It's hard going out to eat all alone,
so having it at home is best.
What's the matter, Umaru?
D-do you not like it?
I was just thinking, this feels
like a high school girl experience, huh?
Dang, this is good!
So... good!
Huh? What's with all of you?
E-Ebina, are you going to eat all those?
Just one has about 500 calories, you know.
No! I-I'll freeze them!
I was going to freeze them when I got home!
Let's all eat before they get cold.
Yes, you're right.
Indeed, these taste best when they're freshly made!
Dang, this is good!
Sensei! It seems we'll be doing
this next episode preview together.
That's fine and all, but why do you
keep calling me "Sensei"?
It's a sign of respect! But I could call you Wise One,
or Master, or Your Majesty, or Honored Husband -
whatever you like!
Hold on. Those last two seem sort of different...