How does it look, Azalea?
No change in its standby location.
No other signs of enemies.
Okay, let's get started!
All right!
Let's go.
You know the plan, right?
Right!
Stay sharp, Naotsugu.
Leave it to me.
Naotsugu, you're within twenty meters.
Roger.
Castle of Stone!
Okay, now!
Let's go.
Keep those shields up!
Eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen...
The skill Luseat just used,
Hearken to the Mourning Bell of Moonlight,
has a ninety second cool down.
We'll be in position by then.
Time to retry!
Yes, that's the way.
Keep your eyes on me, Luseat.
Twenty-three, twenty-four, twenty-five, twenty-six...
Rear line, get back!
How is the damage?
Twenty-seven, twenty-eight, twenty-nine, thirty...
Mostly dodged.
Put a barrier on Naotsugu.
Sasameyuki will handle the count
for the area of effects.
Thirty-one, thirty-two, thirty-three...
Deal with individual attacks yourselves.
When he's in Black Knight Mode,
everyone except the nine attackers,
remember not to touch him.
He's changed.
He's talking with us more than he used to.
It feels like, after that defeat,
the members have grown closer.
We aren't friends... We're comrades in arms.
You can't be friends with someone you dislike...
Lightning Straight!
But you can't keep hating a comrade in arms.
Retry
Retry.
Viper Slash!
Party 1    Party 2    Party 3    Party 4
Sure, Shiroe is introverted,
moody, and puts up walls.
Naotsugu, switch with Dinkuron.
Roger.
But that's a minor flaw.
We're all game freaks.
We're all the same.
War Cry!
Highland Sky
Race/ Wolf Fang
Swashbuckler, Lv. 94
Silver Sword
Eltendisca
Race/ Elf
Assassin, Lv. 95
Silver Sword
I still don't want to die, but...
We're here because we choose to be.
How many times have we died
since coming to this world?
And each time, we have that horrible dream.
But...
I've never seen the members of
Silver Sword in that dream!
Yeah,
not even once.
Companions I'm never ashamed of...
Is this what having a place to belong means?
It's embarrassing to say this at my age, but...
I guess you could call them "friends."
Ragoumaru!
Right!
I want to win...
It's not because we want to beat the raid boss.
Or because we want glory or treasure.
We just want to win.
What we've done wasn't a waste.
All we want to do is prove that!
Zantetsuken!
William!
It's gone critical!
Hurry!
Shiroe's team will take the lead!
Team one, trail the Shadow
Vanguard and defeat them.
Don't neglect a single one!
Right!
So this is Shiroe's plan.
Last time, Ibrahabra and Taltaulgar
appeared after the gates opened.
Ibrahabra of the Third Garden, Lv. 93
Rank/ Raid
In other words, while they're closed, they're immobile.
As is Luseat.
If we enter the western corridor,
we can fight Ibrahabra alone.
Yeah.
And we've confirmed that the
dungeon's goal lies beyond him, too.
Of course, it's possible that Luseat
will destroy the gate and come after us.
And it looks like it's possible
that if we take too long,
Taltaulgar could also come.
Even if we defeat Ibrahabra,
there may be another raid boss beyond.
Th-There are things we aren't sure of, but...
That doesn't change the fact that there's a chance.
Yeah.
It doesn't matter if it's fifteen
percent or five percent!
If we miss this chance, there may not be another.
Damn it, he's right.
But that was always true.
There is no perfectly safe, secure future.
But after I came to this world, I forgot that.
I believed that since it was a game,
I could do anything, and
everything would go my way.
And I was crushed.
Sometimes, things don't go the way you want.
This world is undeniably real!
I was forced to realize that.
But I still underestimated it,
under the delusion that it was a game.
You made another mess.
Hey, move.
What?!
You're just in the way, with that big body of yours.
You damn little Land girl—
If you're going to do nothing but talk,
just hurry up and kill me.
And if you aren't going to kill me, move.
I can't clean.
O-Okay...
And I lost again.
I lost to Silver Sword,
and my guild disbanded.
And I lost to the raid boss.
And I lost to William, as a game master.
He lost so badly, but no one left him!
Not a single person.
Abyssal Shaft — Great Cave
Japan Server
Beneath Tearstone Mountains
Dungeon/ Monsters Present
PVP Permitted
Skill Use Permitted
Entry Restrictions/ Yes
Full Raids Supported
Exit Restrictions/ None
Shiroe, that's it behind Ibrahabra?
Yes.
At the end of that corridor is this raid zone's goal.
Anchor Howl!
Concentrate your buffs on the main tank!
Boosting fire resistance!
Hit it with all your ice, water, and wind attacks!
Naotsugu, bring Ibrahabra
from the side with the corridor
to the southwest wall!
Right!
Fortress Stance!
Time to test out my new shield and armor!
Fortress Stance increases your defense,
but lowers movement and accuracy.
Out of the way, tank!
I can't lose anymore!
Another Keen Edge?
That damn enchanter.
That's...
An AoE attack!
Get back!
I won't let you!
Huh?
It isn't hot!
Covering...
A skill that allows you to absorb damage
from other party members at close range.
Nice going, Demikas.
So damn hot...
It's true that monks have better
elemental resistance
and higher HP.
If we divide the damage, I can
still fight on the front lines!
That's it!
Head around to the left side,
and whittle down his HP!
We can keep going!
Come after me, dude!
Naotsugu, you're really getting into it!
Leave this thing to me!
Okay!
Everyone, do your best!
You can do it! Do your best!
Aurora Heal!
Nice timing.
Wonderful healing work.
Well done!
Leave it to me.
I'm feeling good now!
Of course! I'm an angel!
What are they talking about?
They sure are carefree.
Naotsugu, are you in love with me?
Definitely not.
You're no fun...
Oh, right. I had something to tell you.
What is it? I'm really busy now.
Actually...
I'm joining Log Horizon!
Why?
So I can play with you!
I got Shiroe's permission, too.
Thanks a lot, Shiro...
Um, isn't that bad?
Front line, retreat!
Federico, stay there and keep up the debuffs.
Everyone else, focus on defense and healing.
Taltaulgar...
Luseat
Taltaulgar
Abyssal Shaft
Ibrahabra
Taltaulgar...
H-He's here!
Don't panic!
Dinkuron!
I've been waiting for you.
I let him take the tank role so I could fight you!
Healers, are you all in formation?
Roger.
Castle of Stone!
Ibrahabra and Taltaulgar.
We were prepared to fight both at once.
So what do you mean when you say we have
a fifteen percent chance of winning?
During the last battle,
we were attacked by two
raid bosses simultaneously.
There's no way you can win that.
That's right.
So what if it were only one?
We probably would have been fine.
Which means...
If we don't let the raid bosses' attack
radii overlap, we can survive?
Yes.
The Great Cave has the minimum
size required for this to work.
It's pretty close, though.
Naotsugu will draw Ibrahabra
to the southwest wall.
And Dinkuron will tie down Taltaulgar
at the northeast corridor's entrance.
The plan requires some very difficult positioning.
We'll need to give both Naotsugu and
Dinkuron two dedicated healers,
and the other healers will need
to switch between the two.
If those two get too close,
their attack radii will overlap,
and if they're too far, the buffs
and heals won't reach them.
The rear-line fighters will need to watch
enemy movements, and constantly
adjust their positions.
We'll be fighting on a tightrope, but...
Sounds more like a thread than a rope.
But we'll win, Shiroe!
Federico, attack power debuff!
Attack radius debuff!
I know!
Tetra, up your healing output!
I can't do any more than this!
I'll support you.
Wow, that's pretty.
Force Step!
I'm shining!
Force Step increases your cool down
speed by twenty percent for one minute.
Sacred Wall
Time Left
Aurora Heal
Healing Light
Reactive Heal
Aurora Heal's normal cool down
is six hundred seconds,
and this cuts it to four hundred, eighty seconds.
This one hundred, twenty seconds
makes a big difference.
And...
Mana Channeling.
Tetra           Naotsugu            Federico
Shiroe             Vuoinen              Demikas
I supply the extra MP required
with Mana Channeling.
Thank you, Shiroe.
Here!
The Sequoia of Life.
One of the druid's summons.
Its shining green leaves heal
the party at set intervals.
Good choice...
That spell can heal ten people's
HP over thirty percent!
Karma Drive!
Ibrahabra of the Third Garden, Lv. 93
Rank/ Raid
Ibrahabra's area-of-effect attack,
Merciless Purgatorial Banquet, hits every
one hundred, eighty seconds.
We'll get through the next one with
Vuoinen's Mercy Rain and Life Burst.
And the next one will be in three
hundred, sixty seconds.
Naotsugu's Castle of Stone
will be ready to use again,
and we'll use that to neutralize it.
And in five hundred, forty seconds,
we'll use Tetra's Aurora Heal to recover.
Ragoumaru
Race/ Wolf Fang
Samurai, Lv. 95
Phys Atk Up, Phys Def Up,
Dodge Up, Accuracy Up
Silver Sword
The Karma Drive I just cast
restores MP whenever a critical
hit lands on Ibrahabra.
Junzou
Race/ Wolf Fang
Samurai, Lv. 95
Phys Atk Up, Phys Def Up,
Dodge Up, Accuracy Up
Silver Sword
If we can keep our damage up,
we'll finish him in seven hundred
seconds at this rate.
Then we can bring our full power
to bear on Taltaulgar, and...
We can win.
We can win if we keep up our DPS!
You hear that, guys?
The villain said so.
Give it all you've got!
No holding back!
Yeah!
N-No!
Not now...
You're kidding me.
This is impossible!
Shadow Vanguard...
The same number appear as people
that attacked Luseat.
I predicted we'd have to deal with
a few that got through, but...
I was sure we defeated all the Shadow
Vanguard when we moved to the cave.
Even if Luseat goes back to black,
there's no one in that zone to damage him...
No, wait.
It's dealing damage to itself?
After a while, it'll revert to Black Knight Mode.
And then...
Each time it goes back to black,
it takes damage from itself and
the new Shadow Vanguard...
How many must there be now?
If they increase exponentially
every two hundred seconds...
Are there thirty-one? Sixty-two?
If it's thirty-one, we can still win.
We can defeat Ibrahabra in six hundred seconds.
Ibrahabra of the Third Garden, Lv. 93
Rank/ Raid
Forwards!
Kiting...
If someone aggros the Shadow Vanguard,
drawing them away...
Charge in and kite them.
Going in!
Wyvern Kick!
Demi?
Taunting Shadow!
He's...
Oh, Demi-Demi...
Follow me, shadow dolls.
Shiro!
What are you...
Shut up, glasses-jackass.
Wyvern Kick!
After all this...
Is he planning to get revenge
on me by ruining the raid?
But wait... This might not be a bad situation.
Mind Bolt.
If I can keep supporting him as if I were
a cannon platform he'd equipped...
Head toward Taltaulgar's corridor.
Shut up!
Why are you telling me what to do?
That motion...
It's Taltaulgar's White Night.
A movement debuff!
I don't care.
Lynx Tumbling!
Shiroe! Hey!
William, defeat the enemy!
Go, Demi-Demi!
We're counting on you, villain!
Mind Shock.
Astral Bind.
For now, the kiting's going fine.
But...
What is he thinking?
I never did understand him.
It's possible he may have been
so confused, he acted extremely.
I understand that.
But...
Even so, I couldn't forgive him.
Stop!
We're too far away.
I can't see the Shadow Vanguard.
Let's wait.
If they go back to the Great Cave, it's over!
What are you thinking?
At this rate...
You damned enchanter,
say my name.
De—
Demikas.
Right.
Demikas, I don't like you.
Me, neither, Shiroe of Log Horizon.
So...
What are—
Shiroe, you die down there.
This isn't where I'm going to die.
Down here?
This is...
The deepest level of the Abyssal Shaft?
The goal we were after?
Welcome.
I don't want to welcome you,
but I suppose I must say that anyway.
Shiroe has reached the deepest
level of the Abyssal Shaft.
A river of gold sleeps there.
Awaiting him is the last raid boss,
Uru of the Ninth Garden...
And Kinjou of the Kunie Clan.
Shiroe's desires and true goals
are finally revealed.
Next time: The Gold of the Kunie.
The Gold of the Kunie
Rise up once more.