As you are aware,
you have final exams starting next month.
Right?
So, I think you know what I'm getting at,
but if you fail any subjects...
Supplementary classes will
be held on weekends.
Sometimes, they may be held
during summer vacation, too.
Participating in club activities
would prove quit difficult.
Hey! There's nowhere to run!
Ennoshita, catch them!
Got it!
Fail... Fail...
What counts as a failing grade?
That's your question?
Kageyama's not breathing!
Since we said we were going
to continue club activities,
we have to at least make decent grades.
You shouldn't fail.
Nope.
M-Maybe if we beg the vice principal...
Why don't you try really hard
and not fail the exam?
Even if we get the vice principal's permission,
if you have to take supplementary classes,
those will take priority.
Coach!
W-Well, this isn't something you're
gonna be able to avoid as a student.
But...
You need willpower!
You need to believe you can do it!
Mind over matter?!
No, that's fine.
Please teach me!
Hinata, I didn't really
want to bring this up,
but do I look like someone
who got good grades?
Hinata, I'm sure you don't have
to worry this much about it.
I've never had a double-digit score
on any of my quizzes.
Will I still be okay?
Huh?
Hey! Stop it with the
bodhisattva faces, you two!
They can do it if they try.
They can do it if they try...
Sensei, pull yourself together!
Ah, the sound of anguish.
Get a hold of yourselves!
We still have time until exams start.
There's no way Karasuno could bring
our best without these four idiots!
Not a chance!
I don't know if I'm flattered or insulted...
We're gonna do this...
We're all gonna go to Tokyo.
Haikyu!!
Episode 2  Direct Sunlight
Listen up, you guys.
The one thing that you're going
to promise me right now...
We're Gonna
Go to the Spring
Tournament!
...is that you will not fall asleep in class.
That's the first priority?
Staying up late through sheer willpower.
Screwing up in your classes and in club.
It's all absolutely unreasonable!
Right...
We're heading out.
R-Right. Good job.
It'll be all right.
I mean, you guys passed your
high school entrance exams.
Suga-san!
If you fall asleep in class,  you'd better
be prepared for the consequences.
Kageyama.
What? No!
You have no right to be picky!
We can't go to the away games if we fail!
It's Nekoma!
There's gonna be plenty of
strong schools from Tokyo!
You're okay with not being able to go?!
You told Ushiwaka that you'd
become the best setter!
I'm actually surprised that
Kageyama's grades are bad.
He seems pretty smart.
Hinata's grades don't surprise me at all, though.
I'm sure all that's in
his head is volleyball.
Tsukishima!
...san.
Help us study...
Please.
What? No.
Just, like, less than an hour each day!
Or tell us how to study...
It wouldn't hurt to do that a couple
minutes before or after club.
Hey, I don't think it's fair that
you're having the shrimp
ask for the both of you.
What do you have to say, big guy?
Kageyama, ask him!
Please teach us.
What?
Please... teach us how to study.
I don't think I quite heard you.
Teach us how to study!
Hey!
Shut the hell up!
You're disturbing the neighbors!
S-Sorry!
Why am I getting yelled at?
Sorry.
No, thanks anyway.
Shimizu-senpai!
I found someone in another
class that's not in a club yet.
Thanks!
Yes, no!
"Yes, no"?
She smiled!
U-Um, doing a manager's job by
yourself must be hard, right?
I'll do whatever I can
as a first-year to help.
We're Going to the Spring Tournament
We third-years are going to be
gone after the next tournament.
Watching all of you grow stronger,
I thought again about what may happen
next year and the year after that.
I have to make sure I do my job properly.
I-I'll help.
Thanks, but you should
focus on studying.
That and practice of course.
Everyone's counting on the ultimate bait.
Right!
All right, let's get the next one over with.
Hinata, what's the first
answer to question 6?
For this, you do this...
Question six: Please insert the correct word
or phrase that goes in the parentheses
to correctly complete the idiom.
This idiom expresses that even ruthless people
can show compassion or even cry at times.
Even ogres can be moved to...
...an iron club?
Ow, my eyes!
Hey, how could you do that to the ogre?
You're thinking of another idiom.
Did you not read explanation?
Oh, shut up.
You probably saw the word "ogre,"
didn't read the rest of the question,
and just wrote the first
thing that came to mind.
You really are a simpleton.
Yeah. You need to calm down.
You're too careless.
Why do you guys have to keep going?!
You're one to talk, Kageyama.
Honestly, you're probably
worse off than Hinata.
You need to memorize English
vocab words on your own.
Japanese people can't understand English!
Then give up on going to Tokyo.
Kageyama.
B quick.
A. C. Timed attack in front of the setter.
Left-back attack.
D. Side-by-side. Semi.
Timed attack behind the setter.
So fast...
How long did it take you to memorize those?
I think... less than a day?
Which is exactly why I'm not going to let you
say you can't memorize those words.
O-Oh, no...
I-I'm not gonna lose to Kageyama!
All right. Let's go to my place
after club on Saturday.
Got it.
I'm not gonna lose to them, either!
And I said you need to calm down...
Nishinoya, let me see
your quiz from yesterday.
Karasuno
Volleyball Club
Snacks!
In general,
you can find the the answers for the
Japanese questions in the passages given.
So, if you just read them carefully...
Question 3: In the passage,
identify the sentence that best reflects
Norio's contradictory feelings.
Live more like a man, Norio!!!
Question 4: Fill in (A) from the passage
with the most appropriate word.
Live more like a man, Norio!
It tells you right here to
find it in the passage!
Don't ignore both the question and Norio!
You're so awesome, Noya-san.
You're good at memorization,
aren't you, Nishinoya?
Leave the memes to me!
Tripod
Headstand
That won't be on the exam!
Ugh, are you guys actually studying?
Are you feeling okay?
What'd you mean by that?!
Heyo, Saeko-nesan!
Hey, Yu!
You're looking cool, as always.
Thanks!
P-Pardon the intrusion...
You're totally fine.
Let's see... Want your big sis
to teach you a thing or two?
Shut up!
You're just as dumb as me,
so there's no point.
Hey, don't you dare
underestimate a college girl.
You only go to your job and practice!
Sh-Shut up! I'm working
hard when no one's looking!
Tanaka's sister is so cool.
Yeah.
Don't come crying to me later!
Practice? What kind?
For taiko.
She's getting a team together.
When it's festival time, she goes all out.
Wow. How cool.
Viva chest wraps!
All right, let's do this.
You're going to Tokyo, aren't you?
Yes, Ennoshita-sensei!
Sender: Hinata Shoyo
Tomorrow!!!
Tokyo's starting their IH
tprelims tomorrow, right?!
tDo your best!
Tokyo's starting their IH
prelims tomorrow, right?!
Do your best!
Yeah, gradually...
You guys are coming
over here, right?
Yeah, gradually...
You guys are coming over here, right?
Ni-chan, let's play jump rope!
Nat-chan, your brother's busy studying.
Aw...
To: Kozume Kenma
Subject: Totally!!!!
We're totally going!!!!
We're gonna win this time, just you wait!!!!
Message Sending
All right! I'm gonna go to Tokyo!
Shoyo, be quiet!
Faculty Room
Goodness, Tanaka from Class 1...
Not only is he not sleeping in class anymore,
he's been asking questions after class.
Same with Nishinoya from Class 3!
Looks they can do it if they try.
Maybe the Tokyo away games
are becoming a reality.
That just leaves Shimizu-san...
I wonder if it's going well.
Hey, do you have a moment?
Karasuno High School
Boys' Volleyball Club
Members and Manager
Seeking Members!!
Please Contact Shimizu Kiyoko in Class 3-2
Trying to find a new manager...
Haikyu!!
Wow... She's so pretty.
Even at the Inter-High prelims,
So, she's a third-year...
She's so pretty.
they were neck-and-neck with Aoba Johsai,
who actually made it to the finals.
The mole by her mouth is sexy, too.
So pretty.
Though we do have quite
a few troublemakers,
Her hair is silky-smooth.
but I'm sure you'll find that they're
a team you want to root for.
Everyone's totally staring at her, too.
So, why don't we try a trial membership?
Huh?! Sure!
Really?! Thank you so much!
Then I'll come by again after school.
So you found a new person!
What's up?
What's going on?
Um, she's joining the club on a
trial basis as the new manager...
I-I'm Yachi Hitoka!
Seriously? That's awesome!
Nice job, Shimizu-senpai!
So cute...
You're a first-year?
I-I'm in Class 1-5, sir!
"Sir"?
Asahi, back up a bit.
Huh?
Hey!
Don't stare like that! It's rude.
Thank goodness.
Now there'll be a manager next year, too.
Yes!
Sh-She hasn't actually joined yet.
I asked her suddenly today,
and before work with the
membership committee,
so she's just dropping in to say hi today.
I-It's a pleasure to meet you!
Same!
Could you not surround her
until she's more comfortable?
S-Sorry for the intrusion.
Shimizu.
So you were looking for a new manager...
Yeah.
I didn't think we got enough response
when we tried to find people in April.
I thought it was important to find
someone to carry on as manager,
especially with Karasuno
getting so much stronger.
Shimizu-san!
Kiyoko-san!
I just came on a whim, but
there were so many big guys!
What am I going to do tomorrow?
I stood next to that pretty
lady for like two minutes...
What if her fans try to kill me?!
What's the matter?
Blonde hair and pierced ears!
To think that he's a fan, too...
I-I'm gonna get killed!
What? Killed...
I'm starving.
Year 1 Class 4
Let's go to Sakanoshita!
We agreed on just before
and after club, right?
Right?
Well, the English teacher,
Yoshida-sensei, was gone, so...
Please come back during business hours.
Year 1 Class 4
Damn it, Tsukishima's so stingy...
Stingyshima!
I have to do something...
Hinata!
You're gonna teach me, Yamaguchi?
Sorry, I suck at English.
Remember that girl who came
yesterday as a manager candidate?
She said she was in Class 5,
so she might be good at studying.
That's right.
Classes 4 and 5 are advanced.
What should I do after school?
Volleyball club, huh?
Yachi-san!
Pardon us.
Huh? What?
They're from the volleyball club?!
What should I do? What do they want?
Did they introduce themselves to me yet?
Their names... What were their names?
To think that I can't remember
names I've heard before...
You can't even remember names?!
Unable to make it in society,
I lose my job...
Forced to wander the streets...
Maybe even sell my organs!
I'm Hinata Shoyo from Class 1!
This is Kageyama.
Hey.
H-Hey.
Yachi-san, do you like studying?
I don't hate it.
Could you teach me this English?
You should ask her, too, Kageyama!
Please teach us.
If we fail any tests next month,
we won't be able to go
to the Tokyo away games,
so we've been having the tall guy with
glasses named Tsukishima help us...
Why can't you do this?
But lately, he's getting irritated
because Kageyama and I are so stupid.
I'm not scared of him.
But it'd be better for
someone to teach us nicely!
I-If I'm good enough...
Really?!
Yeah.
But I wonder if I'll be able to teach in a
nicer way than the tall guy with glasses...
You definitely don't have
to worry about that.
Wow!
I see! Wow!
Oh, it's nothing...
Your notebook's really easy
to look at, Yachi-san.
You're great at drawing, too!
My mom works at a design firm,
so she's always been picky
about things like this.
Oh, if you leave a space here,
it'll be easier to fill in later.
Also, if you limit the number of colors
you use, it won't get confusing.
And...
I'm sorry! I was writing
all over your notebook!
Oh, I see... You're amazing!
I-It's n-nothing... nothing...
So, Hinata-kun...
Just Hinata's fine.
Do you not like studying, Hinata?
I hate it. Sitting for
a long time like this sucks.
So you're trying really hard
so you can go to Tokyo?
Yeah! We're gonna have practice matches
with all the strong schools from Tokyo!
That's amazing.
I've never been that serious
about anything before.
There's this school called
Nekoma High School in Tokyo,
and the setter there is super-smart.
And then like their leader
has a really spikey head...
He's really big and seems like a bad guy.
And there's a guy that's totally awesome
at picking up one recieve
after another like foom.
The libero from Nekoma is awesome.
He's on par with Nishinoya-san.
Setter?
There are a lot of amazing guys!
Spikey head? Libero?
Not just in Tokyo, but in our prefecture...
Are these positions?
There's the Great King from Aoba Johsai,
Ushiwaka, who's known as
the undefeated champion,
and Date Tech has the Iron
Wall who's 190 cm tall!
190 centimeters?!
Um... Hinata, are you a manager, too?
Why?
Oh... I thought only tall
people played volleyball
and the club was full of tall guys.
I may be short, b-but I'm a regular!
Oh, my goodness!
I can't believe I judged someone
by their appearance!
I'm so sorry!
It's okay. I'm used to it.
Even if I'm not big,
I can fly!
Hinata, don't you need to copy this down?
Oh, yeah.
Everyone's so big and they look strong,
but when we're in a match,
I feel like I'm taking those people on.
It's exciting. It's nerve-racking.
That's amazing, taking on people like that.
That makes you a Little Giant, Hinata.
Huh?!
What?!
You know who the Little Giant is?
Huh?
Uh, no. I, uh...
Don't you call Japanese players
that when they're fighting
with much bigger foreign
players in sports?
Oh, right.
Yeah, I'm gonna be the Little Giant.
Hey, Little Giant that's
not gonna make it to Tokyo,
hurry up and copy this.
Year 1 Class 5
Will you help us study again?
Sure. Teaching you guys helps me
remember the material, too.
Thanks! Thank you, Yachi-san!
Oh, no, it's nothing...
See you in club!
What is this?
I feel like I've been left out
in direct sunlight for a while.
Yachi-san!
This afternoon's English quiz...
Some parts you taught me were on there,
and I got a third of them right!
Wahoo!
That's amazing, Hinata-kun!
Hinata's so good at communicating...
Hinata's fine!
That's amazing, Hinata!
They're already buddies.
So you'll be observing today.
One, two, three, four...
You don't have to be nervous.
Five, six, seven, eight...
Wight!
"Wight"?
Oh, but be careful of stray shots...
Right!
Stray shots?
Could it be someone's trying to kill me?
Hey, you okay?
Th-The scary person from yesterday!
He's gonna kill me!
Um... I'm actually the coach...
Oh, my goodness!
I judged someone by their appearance again!
I'm so sorry!
Left!
All right!
Nice, Tanaka!
Don't open up the block space!
Right!
Next!
I'm sorry!
I need to hear you guys!
Left!
Two blocks!
Nice, Hinata!
Sorry!
Are you okay?
Uh, yes.
This is my first time seeing volleyball
outside of PE class so close.
It's pretty amazing.
I think our team's offense is among
the best in the prefecture.
Sorry!
Kiyoko-san's talking!
She's smiling!
Her lips are moving!
So that's what girl talk looks like.
Stop goofing off, damn it!
Come on, next round!
Karasuno was actually strong enough
to go to nationals before.
Right!
Nationals?
But in the last few years,
we've been called "the fallen giant"
and "the flightless bird."
This time, we're going
to stand on the national stage.
That's amazing...
So amazing!
Totally different from me.
Fall in.
So, this is rather sudden,
but Ouginishi High School requested
a practice match tomorrow, and I accepted.
They saw us at the Inter-High
prelims and insisted.
Don't forget the frustration and
bitterness you felt losing to Seijoh.
However,
you don't need to hold onto
the feeling of losing.
Hurry up and wipe that away!
Yeah!
I wonder if Ouginishi is strong.
It doesn't matter who they are.
All right. Let's do this!
Kiyoko-san has sure changed since
that first-year girl showed up!
Yeah! It must have been hard to
talk, surrounded by all us guys!
We need to work on our girl power
from now on, too, Noyacchi!
You got it, Ryu-tan!
If you talk like that,
I'm never speaking to you.
Episode 3: Townsperson B
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"Townsperson B."