So we need your songs to
heal the Star Whale's sickness!
All right.
If that's the situation,
I'll head there now.
Will you be okay, too, Cou-sama?
Of course!
We'll head up into the sky right away!
Okay, thanks!
We'll come get you now.
There's no time, so let's meet in the sky.
Right!
Roger!
Let's meet up with the princesses
and head back to the sky.
I've got a bad feeling somehow.
Song of the Stars
Aria...
I'm sorry... oww.
Sorry.
This will hurt a bit.
I was caught off guard.
I'm sorry I couldn't do more.
Me, too... I couldn't do anything.
They must be pretty good to do
this much to Sharl and the chief.
It looked like a kid.
It had human form, but that wasn't human.
It was a type of demon.
A humanoid demon.
Is there such a thing?
A disciple, yes?
Yes.
Demons who took the form of
humans existed in the distant past.
They were highly intelligent,
wielding power that
was a manifestation of greed and disaster.
That must be the Disciple of Illness.
We must bring back Aria-dono.
No, chief!
We'll follow him
and kick his butt!
We need to save Aria, after all.
Yeah.
This way.
I hear the sound this way.
The presence is getting stronger, too.
Leave.
Leave. Humans... Leave.
It talked?
These things aren't talking.
They're just sharing the Disciple's voice.
You're in Aria's way.
Leave!
Not happening.
We have something we have to do.
Prince!
You're the one I can least forgive!
There are two princes here.
Well, you mean me, right?
If you want to talk, let's talk.
Aria's safe, right?
Don't you say
Aria's name!
Idiot!
I don't have even know
what the heck's going on!
Can we calm down and talk?
I don't get you!
Vert, where is he?
I can hear a sound that
sounds like his main body.
I think I can follow it.
Then leave this to me!
Vert and the others take
Gaul to the main body!
I'll stay here!
I'll help Nanami-san!
Thanks! I'll let you guys handle it!
Transform!
Just you wait, damn it!
Aria.
Verde?
Verde...
it's you, right?
I'll give you back your voice.
I remember.
I remember everything!
Aria!
You've gotten used to this
form now, haven't you?
Yeah.
I'm used to it now.
And you're with Verde again?
Yup!
He's strange for a sky person.
He seems strangely human, somehow.
But isn't he cute?
He's always nice to me.
Right, Verde?
Aria?
Were you watching the surface again?
J-Just a little.
The heroes and the princesses are so cool.
And there's a wonderful prince, isn't there?
Th-That's not all, but...
What do you mean?
I like to think about what I'd do
if I went to the surface.
That's fun, too.
You can have the same form
as a surface person.
Couldn't you go if you wanted?
Even in this form,
I can't get far from water,
just like you guys.
And this year I was chosen
to be the songstress.
I won't go.
For the Priestess and the
Star Whale's sake, as well.
And for everyone's sake.
My life in the village is
so peaceful and quiet,
but it's just a little boring.
My love for the surface is just a dream.
But...
Someday I'd love to
go to the surface...
It can come true.
I'll grant your wish.
Verde... wow!
You can talk now!
I'll make your dream come true.
Let's go to the surface and keep
it a secret from everyone.
You're right.
It would be wonderful
if I could go with you.
If I grant your wish,
will you sing for me?
Of course!
Promise?
Of course.
It's a promise.
I know where the power to
make Aria's dream
come true is.
The reason I was born.
My true form...
I'll make Aria's dream
come true.
Now I can make her dream come true.
The Star Whale that locks Aria away...
The village and priestess
that hold her back...
I can make them all go to sleep.
What's this?
What happened, everyone?
Aria.
Verde... Is that you?
You promised, Aria.
We'd go to the surface in secret.
Verde, it's you, right?
No... this isn't what I wanted.
Aria... you promised,
but you lied?
I didn't lie!
I didn't lie, but...
But this wasn't...
Don't cry.
I'll protect your songs and voice.
Let's go together.
We can go anywhere
you want.
The Star Whale...
You're trying to stop me?
What am I doing here?
I can't remember.
Who's there?
I have to help them!
Aria...
Don't go...
Find me... and stay by me.
This way!
There's a door!
Yeah!
Aria...
Gaul!
You...
Is it you?
My guards are famous for appearing and
disappearing when you least expect it.
They can chase and run faster than anybody.
Y-Y-You...
Don't get in
our way, human!
Just like I thought, you're just a kid.
Don't think you can get by in the world...
Just by being a selfish brat!
Let me go!
Sorry, I can't.
It's our boss's orders.
It's my fault.
I made him like that.
I don't know the reason,
but you can't handle him anymore.
I guess that's a really
troublesome type of demon.
If I go back, he'll do what I say.
But that would mean
we're abandoning you.
Our boss wouldn't let that happen,
nor would any of our friends.
But...
Our biggest goal is to save the Star Whale
and all the Star People, including you.
But I'm also training to be a specialist
in dealing with demons.
Even if he's a Disciple, if he
can be saved, I want to save him.
What we need isn't sacrifice and dedication,
it's information and a plan!
Would you tell us the details?
What happened between you and him?
Aria said she wanted to go to the surface.
I'm going to make that dream come true!
You don't have to do this; we'll take her!
If you promise not to be
bad, we'll take you, too!
I won't believe that!
The people of the surface
refuse to accept us.
Even in the distant past,
they tried to exterminate us,
even though we didn't do anything wrong.
I see.
I won't believe in the star people
or the humans of the surface.
I'll make them all sleep with my power,
and make a peaceful and gentle world.
Wait. Wait a second!
I won't wait!
Once all the humans
in our way are gone,
Aria can go to the surface to play in peace.
She'll let me be the only
one to hear her songs.
So human...
Sleep here.
The Hero Shinku
is here in Hero Mode!
Don't get in
my way!
Seems like
the situation's worse than we imagined.
We'll just have to cut open a path.
Alliance knights and medics!
Hang on!
Right!
Princess, I'm going to up our speed!
Okay! Please do!
Everybody's here!
The songstress from the
surface is here, isn't she?
Everybody, get the dais for
the Star Festival ready!
Right!
I have to go, too.
Pega, this way.
Your wings may be the key to saving everyone.
Show the dragon priestess
Sharl and everyone else
your true form.
I'm sorry princess, to ask you
to sing in all this chaos.
Not at all.
I'll sing anywhere, at any time.
Especially if it can help
keep the Sky Sea safe.
There's nothing that would
make me happier as a singer.
No way!
Princess of Biscotti, Hero Rebecca,
I'm glad you're safe.
Priestess!
Who's that?
It's Pega.
This is his true form.
Let's hurry.
The star festival will be ready soon.
Right!
Stay sharp!
There's still more!
Right!
There's no end to them!
No army is infinite.
Right!
Let's go, Shinku!
Yeah, Gaul!
Divine Rule: Glorious Flying Slash!
This is it.
Not yet.
No, this is the end.
This song...
It's starting...
The princess' song.
Everyone!
Let's sing a song of healing
to the Star Whale, too!
Yeah!
Who is this wonderful person?
Who could it be?
Call me Pegasus Mask.
Huh? Next week's the last episode?
Returning Home