I shouldn't have given birth to you.
Who would you be sold to, you ask?
I thought you weren't interested.
I don't handle pain very well.
I thought I should at least be prepared.
Don't worry.
You're rare.
Sorry, you didn't care whether
you lived or died, did you?
Hey...
Thank you.
Morning, Chise.
G-Good morning.
Who is she?
She's a neighbor that lives
here. Her name is Silky.
She's a fairy who does the cooking and
laundry, cleans and tends to the fire.
Silky prepared that, as well.
You could say she's less of
a servant and more of a landlady.
A little something for my acquaintance.
Apparently, I was purchased
by this mage for an outrageous sum.
As his apprentice, and...
I also hope to make you my bride.
Apprentice or bride...
Which do I take seriously?
You've been asleep for two
days. Do you recall anything?
Two days?
You must have been emotionally exhausted.
His appearance, his mannerisms...
I don't understand him very well yet.
Aren't you going to eat?
But he's going to take care of me, so
he's not a bad person... I don't think.
I hate to bring this up to you
so early in the morning,
but shall we prepare for our honeymoon?
But... he's seems pretty weird.
I thought I'd introduce you to my
acquaintances while we go shopping.
His face is bone, so I can't
read his expressions.
I can't tell when he's serious or kidding.
Wh-What happened to your head?
I would look suspicious wandering
around outside with that head.
I used a little magic.
See?
It feels different to the touch, too.
Do I look good?
Am I handsome?
You look kind of fake.
That's harsh.
I come here often.
You'll find almost all
your equipment here.
Is this place open?
This is just for show.
Angie.
Angelica.
Hey, it's Ainsworth!
Who would have thought you'd
ever come out of your hole?
You're no less of a hermit, Gem's Bee.
I'm running a business.
Chise.
Y-Yes!
I thought I'd have you gather
the things this girl needs.
I made her my apprentice three days ago.
A-Apprentice?!
Yeah.
Wow.
From Japan, huh?
Chise, was it?
Here you go.
Thank you.
She's cute.
You better not have done
anything shady to get her.
The money I bought her with was clean.
There's nothing proper about buying her!
He hasn't done anything
weird to you, has he?
What do you think I am?
Anything weird?
Chise, Chise, you need to
be quicker to deny that.
He washed me after taking off my clothes,
and he proposed to me... Does that count?
Oh?
You perverted mage!
Go take a walk!
He doesn't have a smidge of common sense.
Man, so that Ainsworth
found an apprentice, huh?
Did he really propose?
Um...
Oh, I forgot to introduce myself.
I'm Angelica Burley.
I'm a mage, which are a dying breed.
I'm a magus craft artificer.
Magus craft?
Tools and contraptions that run
on magic instead of electricity.
Processing gems, making knives...
I do it all.
Mom!
A visitor?
Althea.
Look!
Sorry, but we're putting that off.
Stay quiet.
You promised you'd watch my training!
All right, just scram!
Was that your daughter?
Yeah.
Sorry, she's not very well-behaved.
For better or worse, she's got what
it takes to become a mage.
I'd prefer that she'd take up a proper
job, especially in today's world.
Mage?
Has Elias not told you yet?
He hasn't.
There's magic and sorcery in this world.
Do you know the difference between the two?
To put it simply, sorcerers
employ a science called "sorcery."
They have an understanding of reality,
and they use their own power to rewrite
it and change it to their own ends.
Meanwhile, the magic that we mages use
refers to the miracles that are caused
with the help of fairies and spirits,
their powers bending said reality.
Miracles?
Magic sounds easier, doesn't it?
But it's like having someone be your arms
and legs, so it's hard to regulate and control.
Should you try to do more than
what you're capable of...
I made a silly mistake during my training,
so that's what I got.
There's a lot to study
when it comes to magic.
You have to take it seriously,
or this is what happens.
So make sure you study hard.
Can I use magic, too?
Why don't you give it a try?
Hugo!
Hey, robin.
I'm loyal to Angelica,
so I can't promise to be
my kindest to you,
but nice to meet you anyway.
This is Hugo, my familiar.
A vodyanoy water spirit.
He's mischievous, but he's hard-working.
Hugo, give her a hand, would you?
She needs to practice magic.
B-But I...
There's a first time for everyone.
You'll be using that for practice.
Will it to take on a shape of your choosing.
Will it?
Yup.
Think of your favorite flower, for example.
A flower?
Air is hot water.
You, yourself, are pressure.
Therein, the crystal forms.
Picture that in your mind.
What is my favorite flower?
When? Where?
Look, Chise.
It's a flower garden.
How pretty.
How pretty, Chise.
Chise.
Please, Angelica.
Don't go teaching my apprentice things.
Elias...
I-I'm sorry.
The room...
Ainsworth.
What is that young lady?
Magic is a miracle,
but it isn't omnipotent.
She's a Sleigh Beggy.
I see.
Why didn't you tell me?
The less people know, the better.
Don't look so worried.
Hugo!
Why didn't you tell me?
No, well, I mean...
She's a special existence to the fairies.
I-I'm sorry.
I made a mess.
You don't need to apologize.
Listen, it's that bonehead's fault.
That shithead who didn't tell us anything.
Shithead?
If you can't explain things to your
apprentice, you're nothing but a shithead!
Chise, would you do me a favor and get
me the broom and hammer in the back?
Yes!
What's wrong with you, Ains?
I'm charging you extra.
Chise.
Y-Yes?
An ocean alloy knife forged with
the nectar of a crystal moonflower.
An overcoat woven from thunderbird feathers.
What else? Glashtyn hide, a belt...
I think I'll throw in some steelvine
string and a fluorite loupe.
So you like poppies, Chise?
I'm not sure I actually "like" them.
It's just something I remembered.
I saw a flower garden like
that a long time ago.
With my mother.
Are your parents dead?
Or did they abandon you?
You're pretty blunt, aren't you?
However your past or
upbringing may have been,
it makes no difference regarding
the fact that you're here.
You're right.
His plain, dispassionate words
are somehow comforting and kind.
I don't know what my father
is doing, but my mother...
She died.
In front of my eyes.
It was a long time ago.
Hey!
Ainsworth!
Didn't I write back to you saying
I'd be here around now?
Why'd you take off just
as I was getting here?
You're supposed to be a hermit!
I have things to do, too.
Your servants hate me.
They won't even let me in the house.
You didn't have to bother coming.
So you're Chise, his new apprentice, right?
Hello.
My name is Simon.
Simon Cullum.
I'm here today to ask you two to
do a bit of an errand for me.
I waited outside for two whole hours.
Simon is the priest at the village church.
Although, he does sermons both as a priest
and as a pastor, so he sits on the fence.
Call me "studious."
You don't need to be tense, Chise.
Simon is just a coward.
Yes, I am but a pitiful lamb, cowering
in fear of the terrible mage.
Die.
You pull no punches.
They don't get along.
It's still cold outside, even
though it's almost summer.
Elias is especially spiteful.
You could have gone back to
church and come tomorrow, then.
Silky, too.
But that's a pain in the butt, too.
Chise-kun, I think I understand
your situation, now.
It must have been terrible.
You're free to come to my church if
you ever get sick of this bastard.
I'll hear you out.
Stop.
So?
This isn't something we can deal
with, but it should be easy for you.
Three?
That's quite a few.
It's a penalty for your free actions.
You've been silent for decades, and now
you've suddenly taken an apprentice.
I don't have any option but
to report to the brass.
I don't think of myself as
being managed by the church.
I know.
I'd rather not bother with this, either.
We don't want to mess with you mages
who have already lived longer than we know.
How many centuries is it going to take
before your superiors rethink their ways?
If only God or his son would
write us a letter or two.
Is it because I'm here that
you have to bother with this?
It's absolutely not your fault.
We have all kinds of nasty issues.
May I have the usual?
Yeah.
I heal all the people of this village with
the medicine that Ainsworth makes.
Should you learn magic and use it to craft
medicines, they will work miracles.
The medicine of a mage is
effective and gentle to the body.
Study well.
I wouldn't believe he'd think highly
of you, being that he's a priest.
Does he?
Britain is a land of ancient magic.
Mages are an important
part of life here.
Now, Chise,
why don't we go on our honeymoon
while we run our errands?
You weren't kidding about that?
Iceland, a volcanic island
in the Arctic Ocean.
I'm told that the dragons
are on the move lately.
I've been asked to check on them.
Dragons?
Chise!
He's still not very careful, is he?
He couldn't even hold
onto his own apprentice.
Wh-Who are you?
We shall discuss that at our own land.
At the last land of the dragons.
The two are torn apart.
Death and life intertwine
at the ends of the earth.
What does the girl see when the
door to her memories are opened?
Good night, little sorceress.