I see.
You found the candidate who
could become the next queen?
She's close by, is she?
I must go see her.
The Rising of the Shield Hero
Release Van-sama!
Filolial Queen
Stay away!
This place is done for.
We're getting out of here.
Right.
You okay?
Yes, somehow.
I can't believe that rotten noble released
that monster just to take out Naofumi!
Seriously.
Keel-kun...
Raphtalia-chan...
Okay, what now—
How'd it find us?
Shit. We're screwed if
it charges at us now.
You stupid...
Filo-chan?
Filo!
Are you going to fight here?
We're in the center of town, you know!
I know! We'll lure it out of town first!
But...
How?
Hey, Naofumi.
What?
Look at Filo-chan's belly.
Now look at the monster.
Maybe it's really coming after...
Filo?
Yes.
Then she can lure it out of town.
But...
Don't worry.
I'll take these kids and run.
Thanks. Please do.
Raphtalia...
Say, Raphtalia-chan.
You're in the Shield Hero's party,
aren't you?
Yes.
Then you should go.
I'll be fine.
Go on.
Keel-kun...
Rest assured.
I'll go meet up with my people.
Van-sama!
I understand.
Please take care of Keel-kun.
Certainly.
Filo!
Yeah!
Be careful.
I will.
I'm sure we'll meet again.
Let's go!
Yeah!
Roger!
Run away!
That way, Filo!
Gotcha!
It really is coming after Filo-chan.
Yeah.
I'm sorry I gave away that bracelet.
It's yours now. You're free to
do whatever you want with it.
How far are we going?
As far as possible.
We're almost past the forest!
This place will do.
Everyone ready?
I'm all set to fight.
I'll do my best.
Air Strike Shield!
Zweit Aqua Slash!
I can't cut it!
It's slow, but we can't even scratch it!
Master, give me some footing!
Air Strike Shield!
Second Shield!
It's not working!
One more try!
Naofumi-sama!
I'm fine! Keep going!
Got it!
We don't have unlimited stamina.
I'll have to use the Rage Shield.
Don't.
Naofumi, something seems wrong here.
Is this...
magic mist?
It's a high-level magic field.
A magic field?
You mean we're trapped here?
I hear footsteps!
Filolials?!
What the hell?
Damn it!
Detecting transformation jamming
Don't resort to that power.
Who's there?
It can't be!
The Filolial Queen?!
So cool!
Fall back.
Your body reacted badly to the Dragon
Emperor's fragment and grew beyond control.
If you hand over that fragment now,
I shall spare your life.
But begone at once!
Watch out!
As you wish.
Weak.
I'll end this at once.
The Shield Hero, I take it?
Yeah.
I wish to discuss many things with you,
but I know this form isn't suitable.
One moment.
Now, to introduce myself.
I am the queen of all
filolials the world over,
Fitoria.
Fitoria?
You're her?
You've heard of her?
Of course.
Centuries ago, a hero of the time
is said to have raised a filolial.
Her name is legendary.
"Centuries ago"?
So she inherited the name?
No, I have always been Fitoria.
Will I also be as big as her one day?
I couldn't feed you if you grew
that big, so you'd be on your own.
That would take dozens of times
longer than a normal filolial's lifespan,
so don't worry yourself over it.
In other words, she's lived that long?
It's your turn to introduce yourselves,
Shield Hero's party.
Iwatani Naofumi.
Okay.
I'm Raphtalia. Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
My name is Filo.
We've met before, haven't we?
Thank you for your help that time.
No problem. I'm Melty Melromarc.
It's a pleasure to meet you again.
Mel-tan, then.
Mel... tan?
You've met before?
Yes. I ran into her on the way back to
the capital after a diplomatic visit.
So you've made a habit of that, huh?
Anyway, I'm grateful that
you took out that monster.
But what do you want with us?
It's a long story, and this
isn't a great place for a chat.
Let me take you somewhere more suitable.
Wait, before that...
I don't like a Cardinal Hero using
dragon material in his equipment.
It serves as precious fodder
to develop my shield.
And I already sense an ominous
aura in your shield.
Curse powers are certainly immense,
but so are their consequences.
You mustn't use them.
It's not a problem. I have it under control.
Not for long.
Regardless, I need dragon material and
the Rage Shield in order to survive.
Fine. Do as you wish.
That does it.
Are you finished?
Yeah. But the rest of this...
I'll order my family to bring it along.
Thanks.
Get in the carriage.
I'll need you to answer several
questions when we get there.
Portal.
Wh-What just happened?
Did we travel instantly?
Wow.
Ruins, huh?
You can practically feel their history.
What a dump.
I hear it's considered the remains of the
civilization the original heroes defended.
You don't sound very sure.
It existed before I was born. For what
it's worth, I'm watching over it.
Is this a filolial sanctuary?
Yes. I'm not supposed to bring humans here.
Wow...
Then I guess we'll be safe
here for the time being.
I think you should get some rest.
Let's take a break, then.
Yay!
That was one long day.
I wonder if Keel-kun and the
other kids are all right.
They've got Van and those
demi-humans with them.
They should be fine.
You're right.
First, let's eat.
I bet you're all hungry.
Time to dig in!
U-Uh, you know...
I feel too guilty to eat.
Same here.
Isn't it yummy?
It's great.
They're like sisters.
Right? They even eat in
the same sloppy manner.
Um, Naofumi-sama?
God, fine! I'll make you some!
Bring me some huge pots
and a ton of ingredients!
Why'd I even have to feed this KFC farm?
What? You're not getting any seconds.
I know.
It's time to talk.
I want to know how that monster
was released from its seal.
I thought you came to save
us because you knew.
I was there because I was told a new
queen candidate had been found.
A queen candidate? You mean Filo?
Yup.
Can I ask you something?
What?
Why is Filo growing so differently
than other filolials?
That's because...
a hero is raising her.
Tell me. Why was the seal removed?
What?
I'm appalled at you Cardinal Heroes
for squabbling with the Wave nearly here.
Hey, they started it!
I know the Shield Hero has always been
scorned by human supremacist countries.
Then you should understand.
That's why we're trying
to cross the border—
That won't solve a thing.
Talk it out.
As much as humans and demi-humans
might hate each other,
it is unacceptable for
heroes to be fighting.
Don't you Cardinal Heroes
know about the hourglass?
You mean the dragon hourglass?
We do know about it.
Then why aren't you fighting
Waves across the world?
Are you saying the Waves happen
outside of Melromarc, too?
The Four Cardinal Heroes are meant
to be summoned to one country each
and help them fight the Waves.
First I've heard of that.
I'm going wherever I'm asked.
But you four aren't taking
part in any other battles.
Hell, I only found out recently that other
countries had their own hourglasses.
Honestly, I don't care about
what happens to humans.
I fight because the hero
who raised me asked me to.
A hero asked you to?
My job is to protect the world.
She wants to save the world when
she doesn't care about humans?
But I can't protect it all by myself.
I need the heroes.
But you seem far more capable than us.
Maybe I am now.
But eventually,
I won't be able to save a thing.
And that's why you need the heroes?
Exactly.
Is this the place?
Looks like it.
Yeah, it definitely seems like the
Three Heroes Church is hiding something.
I can't believe Naofumi was right.
Is this an archive?
Let's check it out.
Keep your noses out of this!
You're telling me to make
up with those guys?
Heroes are supposed to work together.
That is an absolute necessity
in order to protect the world.
Not happening.
That country, along with those guys,
is trying to get rid of me.
I've heard the gist of
what's been happening.
But heroes mustn't fight among themselves.
You seem rather obsessed with that.
Because it's unacceptable, that's why.
They don't wanna play nice.
It's a lost cause now.
Are you sure?
Absolutely.
I see.
Very well, then.
It was all so long ago that
my memory of it has faded,
but I do still remember
the right thing to do.
If the heroes are fighting each other
instead of the Waves of Catastrophe,
then for the sake of the world,
I must kill the Four Cardinal Heroes.
A Promise Made