Long time no see!
Yes.
Here's a get well gift...
They're beautiful!
And you remembered my favorite flowers!
I'm sorry to call you here so suddenly.
Won't you sit?
I read in the paper that the choir group
took first place in nationals again this year.
It's not called the choir group anymore.
It's the choral group.
You're already in costume?
Is that bad?
It's fine.
I dig his enthusiasm.
Esteemed Western District shoppers!
Are you enjoying your
shopping experience?
Holy, he really went out there.
Do we have to go?
Seriously?
Let go of me, Sawa.
I could run...
I'm a heroine, I'm a heroine, I'm a heroine!
Let's go, team!
Okay.
From the ordinary to the extraordinary.
We've got everything you need!
Welcome the Western Shopping District Heroes!
The WestStoprangers!
Episode 10
Crushing and Burning
I'm going to need everyone's full cooperation, even those who are busy.
For what, exactly?
You're going to get beat.
Beg your pardon?
Beaten to a pulp.
The Germ Squad is here!
We won't let you lay a
finger on the merchandise!
The Western Shopping
District's fruit
is the best in the world!
Its veggies are fresh!
Eat this! Curry Punch!
Why you!
Behold the Power of Curry!
Damn, that hurt.
We'll get you for this, WestStoprangers!
Kitaike-san.
We've protected the Western
Shopping District's peace!
And its tastiness!
To celebrate this victory,
we'll hold a 30 minute
sale, starting now.
Say the code word for 10% off!
And the code word is...
Western Shopping District Heroes!
The WestStoprangers!
WestStoprangers!
Did I hear sale?
That's great!
Please read this flyer
for more information.
Here you go.
Take one.
Thank you.
Fantastic job, guys.
Especially for your first time.
We passed out a lot of flyers, too.
But we can do so much better!
Our tempo and timing were subpar.
Your hero mode is intense...
Hero mode?
Kitaike-san's toast.
He threw his back out.
Oh dear.
In that case...
Who can we get to take his place?
Desperate times...
For all your shopping needs,
visit the Western Shopping District!
Mango Beam!
Curry Punch!
Take this, you pesky WestStoprangers!
Bacteria Wave!
Don't give up, Green!
If you fall now,
who will protect the peace
of the shopping district?
You're right.
I can't let myself be defeated!
Take this!
Beta Carotene Shower!
Damn you, WestStoprangers!
We'll be back again tomorrow,
somewhere in this shopping district!
Mark my words!
We've protected the Western
Shopping District's peace!
Sakai.
We're the Western Shopping District Heroes!
The WestStoprangers!
Oh boy, can you believe it?
They say I make a perfect villain.
I'm sorry to let you down like this.
Not at all.
Thanks to you, today was a huge success.
Hey, is there any way
you guys would consider
extending our agreement?
Huh?
No?
We have the White Festival coming up.
It's not like you
practice every day, right?
But we've barely done anything to get ready.
Like, wouldn't it'd be hard for you to write
your song between shifts?
I guess.
So she needs time to figure the song out...
What do you guys think?
If you want to do it,
it's fine with me.
I can get that song written in no time!
Shiho-san's done a lot for us,
so it'd be rude
to just brush her off.
It's not like you've
finished anything
for the festival, either.
I'm happy to keep going,
but could we maybe have some
time to think it over?
Yes, of course.
Lessons in Composition
If you want to know
more about composition,
you should talk to the vice principal.
The song on that cassette tape
was co-written by her and your mom.
We will now commence singing—
Too awkward, Nao!
Mahiru...
We'll now sing a song
born between Nao and me,
and nurtured by our choir.
Miyamoto-san,
come to the staff room, please.
We need to talk.
What is it?
We'll discuss it there.
Come along.
What's with her?
Who knows.
Maybe it's about the WestStoprangers.
What about 'em?
I saw some girls from the choral
group watching the show.
Why now, though?
We had permission.
When she's set on something,
she'll spin things any
way that suits her.
Really?
We're here!
Why did you all come?
If this is about the choir club,
concerns us, too.
So you're all aware, then,
that after school jobs are strictly forbidden.
But—
I shouldn't have to remind you
to conduct yourselves as students at all times.
We were totally
acting like students!
What am I going to do with you...
Everything we did,
we did with your permission.
Um, we'd like your stamp of approval...
That was...
That was before you explained
what you'd be doing.
I don't believe that makes a difference.
The shopping district's customers liked our act.
We'll be using our pay
for the White Festival.
I fail to see the problem.
You're missing the point.
I'll let it go only
if you quit immediately,
otherwise—
Madam Vice Principal.
Don't you think going back on something
you've already approved
is extremely unprofessional?
Why are you doing this?
Our club fully intends to finish its job.
What she said.
Excuse us.
We sure told her.
Wien?
Don't worry, Wien.
We schooled her good.
Thank you
for telling her you won't
abandon the WestStoprangers.
Stop that, Wien! It's embarrassing.
I'm just so happy.
I figured it'd be all over if
we were ordered to stop.
Thought we'd give in?
Of course not!
Once I got into
the role of Curry Yellow,
it was pretty fun.
I forget what you call this...
I feel abducted.
Oh, you mean indebted.
Long ago, a very poor man named Ted
borrowed his best friend's
only coat, named Deb.
By clothing his friend Ted with Deb the coat,
he coined the term "in-deb-ted."
It's a touching tale of priceless friendship!
Slow down!
I definitely need to share this with Jan.
I know one about
flipping your debts.
Wait!
Stop messing with him, guys.
He takes you seriously.
Huh?
I was thinking something like "ta-ri-ra-rira"!
But that's not what you sang before.
Really?
Yes really,
so which will it be?
Both?
Please, Nao?
Is your name read as Naoko or Naomi?
Your first name, I mean,
Madam Vice President.
Naoko. Why do you ask?
But my mother called you Nao, right?
Recording, now!
We will now commence singing—
Ah, yes, she did.
Your mother and I belonged to
the same club in high school.
The choir club?
That's right. That's what
we called it back then.
Wait, did you ever visit
my mother in the hospital?
Yes.
Your mother wanted to see me,
so I went one time.
I see.
Why do you ask?
No reason.
If you're wondering why I didn't tell you that
she and I were acquaintances,
it's because I must respect
the rules of this school.
Okay.
No matter what happened in the past,
you are currently nothing
more than one of my students.
I will treat you no better
nor worse than any other.
I understand that.
Then what do you want from me?
I'd like to ask you
how my mother went about writing songs.
You two wrote that song together, right?
I'm trying to finish a song of hers...
How should I go about it?
Or maybe...
Nao, say something!
I'm listening.
That's not enough.
Which do you like better?
You should sing, too!
I can't just...
What?
It doesn't come naturally to me,
like it does for you...
What?
You're just overthinking it!
Don't you enjoy singing?
Music is about having fun with sound!
You've gotta have fun!
Because you're not enjoying yourself.
You can't do it if you think you "have" to.
That's work.
A song is something that flows naturally
from the depths of your heart.
In any case, I'd appreciate it if you wouldn't
waste my time with such petty concerns.
I'm sorry. And...
Thank you!
I should go.
Oh, all right.
Get well soon.
Sheet music?
Yes.
I'd like to write a song with my daughter.
Just like you and I did.
Maybe if she's accepted to your school,
and joins the choir club,
she could be with you—
It's the choral group now.
I told you.
Right.
That song, and the original club,
were both essentially your creations.
That's not true.
I'll be going now.
Thank you, Nao.
I'm glad I could see you one last time.
What?
It seems I'm not going to make it.
No way.
Why not?
Some no-name group's
album isn't worth a dime.
B-But this is a special edition
and it's autographed!
I thought we could sell it for our festival fund...
I mean, we can't keep doing this
after school job thing forever.
This is my biggest treasure.
Konatsu, I'm sorry.
I was in a bad mood the other day
and I lashed out at you.
When?
When I said it was
rude to reject Shiho-san.
But you were right.
We'll figure out what to do
about the festival together.
If we quit now,
it'd be like the vice principal won.
We can handle the White
Festival and a job!
No sweat!
That an order?
No, I was more pumping myself up.
I agree!
I'm in, too.
Same. And I'll get the song done.
You sure?
Don't forget to get the script checked.
Okay, okay!
White Festival, here we come!
Great!
Getting a lot of energy from Yellow.
Iwasaki Cleaning
We did it!
Yeah!
Western Shopping District Heroes!
The WestStoprangers!
Join us again at 4:30,
in front of the Japanese sweets shop.
Until we meet again!
That's mine!
Wien!
Evil will not be tolerated!
Wien, just leave it!
A true hero doesn't have
the choice to give up!
What the...
Dearest Jan:
I've been busy lately
protecting the world's peace
as an inheritor of Gamba Red's will.
Thankfully, I have four
trustworthy friends at my side,
There!
and they are warriors imbued
with the same passion for justice.
Like everyone, a defender of justice
has his share of rough times,
but I refuse to get discouraged!
Why you!
You did not just steal a bag back there!
That's a proud symbol of
Yellow's dedication to her fri—
Let go!
Get off of me!
A hero never gives up!
Because we...
...keep the Earth turning.
We can do it! With beads of
sweat gleaming in the light,
we reach for the future in front of us!
We're scared, but that's
why we'll never give up!
We don't want to regret
anything! Not anything!
The dreams we're chasing
won't be easily destroyed!
So we'll take hold of it right now!
That moment where we can truly shine!
Yes!
Gamgam, it's courage time!
Gamgam, we'll fulfill our duty!
Our passion is blazing!
What's wrong with you people?!
Justice! Valor!
Friendship!
We're the Western Shopping District Heroes!
The WestStoprangers!
Great work! Local Superheroes
Dear Jan:
Wherever you are, I'm sure
you're working hard,
just as I am.
I believe I'll be able to
give these letters to you someday,
so I'll keep on writing them.
I want to play someone old.
No way. I don't do art.
This was originally Wakana
and her mother's song.
Episode 11
Waxing and Waning
I'm everyone's mom.
Almost got it.