The Third Plate
Two
Moon Festival Guide Book
Come get the Moon Festival Guide Book,
hot off the press!
Get one, take one!
Here you go!
Hey, look at this!
Is Yukihira Soma for real?
Yukihira-senpai, I put you
right where you asked.
I had the article about your booth set
Totsuki Academy High School Division 1st Year, Yukihira Soma
right on the next page after
the Chinese Cuisine RS!
He's setting up right in
front of the Chinese Cuisine RS?!
And he's going to serve Chinese food?!
And he had to get his booth listed
right next to their page, too.
It doesn't surprise me one bit.
I figured he'd start something
up to stir the pot,
but I didn't expect him to
take them on head-on like this.
Yukihira, damn you!
You always fire me up!
Bro, you're crushing the guidebook!
Oh, sorry.
This isn't fair!
Why does Yukihira-kun get all the attention?!
Wow, Yukihira-chin!
You look so chill, but you're so extreme.
I hope you won't come to regret it.
Food Wars
The Third Plate
"You know you'll get expelled
if your booth loses money, right?"
When Nakiri said that,
I did get kind of spooked,
but thinking about it, how can
I end up with zero profit?
"Ma" and "La"
I mean, it's a huge five-day festival
that'll have 500,000 people coming.
Well, sure.
Unless you decide to set up shop
right in front of a powerful competitor!
Well, I'm sure it'll all work out.
That doesn't sound convincing at all!
I know how disorganized you are!
Excuse me...
Huh?
Miss Ikumi.
Can you check the paperwork, please?
Sure, hang on.
Ikumi-senpai's so cool!
Wow, Don RS sure is booming these days.
Yeah, we're getting a ton of applicants
from the junior high division.
Nikumi's gotten way more charismatic lately.
She won the Shokugeki against Sadatsuka Nao
without any trouble, too.
(White)
By the way, Yukihira.
Huh?
I'd like to help out at your booth,
but I have to take care of them.
So...
Oh, there's no need, Nikumi.
I'm the one who told you to
give Don RS your best shot.
Right!
But if you run into any trouble,
ask for help!
Okay!
Yeah, what Nikumi said!
After all, you and Tadokoro
are honorary members!
We are?
Anyway, I gotta do what I gotta do.
That's ridiculous, Alice!
Huh?
You don't have to get so mad at me!
The booth application deadline
was a long time ago.
You decide now that you want
to join the Moon Festival?
I may be one of the Elite Ten,
but even I can't help you.
Hmph.
I can grab someone else's booth
location using a Shokugeki.
There are other ways, I'm sure.
You said it was too much trouble
to even bother last year!
Hey, what are you Nakiris fighting about?
Oh, Yukihira-kun.
Don't call us that!
Erina-sama!
Due to traffic,
the contractors handling interior
construction will be an hour late.
I see. I suppose we can't do much about that.
Oh!
I guess you guys time to spare, then.
Huh?
I've been thinking that I'm gonna make
some dishes I used to serve back home.
Can you be taste testers?
What?!
Why would I do something like that?!
Just for an hour, Yukihira!
Erina-sama is very busy.
Hisako isn't vetoing it?!
I can chip in, too.
Thanks!
I've sliced the green onions.
That's as far as I'll go in terms of help.
Sure, thanks!
Hisako...
I'm not wrong. I think she's friendlier
with Yukihira-kun lately.
Hisako...
Yes?
N-Nothing. Never mind.
Here's the Yukihira-Style Mapo Tofu Set!
Dig in!
From what I've seen,
this appears to be a typical dish served
at restaurants for the general public,
Erina-sama.
Hm, I see.
So spicy!
But this won't let you beat Kuga-senpai.
That's because your dish lacks both
ma and la by a significant margin.
"Ma" and "la"? What are
you talking about, Nakiri?
You should be ashamed of your ignorance!
Listen, spiciness in Chinese
cuisine rests upon two pillars.
The fiery spiciness associated
with red chili peppers, la-wei,
La-wei
and the numbing spiciness associated
with Sichuan peppers, ma-wei.
Ma-wei
The two combined are called ma-la-wei.
Huh.
Sichuan peppers...
Nikumi used them during the prelims.
Chinese cuisine encompasses
a very broad range of dishes.
There are eight great regional
cuisines across China,
Anui
Hunan
Jiangsu
each of which developed in a specific
climate and local customs.
Fujian
Zhejiang
Shandong
The ma-la flavor is considered
the distinctive characteristic
Sichuan
of Sichuan cuisine,
which is Kuga-senpai's forte—
Sichuan
Hm, hm.
Crap!
I gave him useful information!
That was really helpful.
Thanks for explaining it to me.
F-Forget what I just said!
Forget everything!
That's impossible.
Yeah, no way.
That's impossible, Erina-sama.
I see.
So Chinese Cuisine RS's mapo tofu has all that
lingering flavor despite
the sheer spiciness of it
because Kuga-senpai is making
good use of the ma-la flavor.
That sounds about right.
His culinary skills are
quite advanced, of course,
but there can be yet another reason
why his spiciness is so addictive.
Huh?
From a biological standpoint,
spiciness is not about the sense of taste,
but about the sense of pain!
Huh, so it's about how much it hurts.
That's right.
Spiciness is not sensed by
the same flavor receptors
that handle sweetness, bitterness,
sourness, saltiness, and umami.
It's sensed by a separate
class of vanilloid receptors.
Extra strong spiciness
also causes adrenaline and beta-endorphins
to be released in the brain.
Those neurotransmitters trigger
feelings of excitement and happiness.
That'd explain why spiciness is addictive.
Yes, it's only possible because
spiciness is perceived as pain.
In medicinal cuisine,
spiciness is said to aid internal
organs in their functions
and also help reduce stress.
I see.
That's why those who wield absolute control
over spiciness are formidable foes.
Kuga-san once said to me that...
When anyone eats my food,
they all sweat a ton and turn
red in the face, you know?
But they all keep eating anyway.
Seeing that is the best.
I love torturing people with my food.
I guess I can kind of relate to that.
When someone eats my food and
smiles because it tastes good
or groans because it tastes awful, it's fun.
I guess that's part of why I cook.
I see he's plenty twisted enough on his own.
Anyway, spiciness can deliver a jolt
of delicious flavor like lightning!
Kuga-senpai is well aware of how
it can bring people to their knees.
That's how he was able to join the Elite Ten.
The overwhelming spiciness of Sichuan cuisine
and its underlying complex flavors—
if you do not have a
means of countering that,
you will never be able to win!
I see.
Nakiri-san said that?
Is your mapo tofu so bad, though?
It's not "bad,"
but it's true that it can't stand
up the spiciness of Sichuan cuisine.
It's a similar to back when
I clashed with Mimasaka over beef stew.
I guess testing is the
only way I'll find out.
First, I'm going to research
the heck out of that spiciness,
then I'm going to figure out
a recipe that'll let me win.
Oh, um...
I thought this might be useful.
I brought Chinese recipes and stuff.
Huh?
Didn't you get invited by
Isshiki-senpai to join in
on the Polar Star Dormitory
booth with the others?
Oh, yeah.
My Regional Cuisine RS is doing a booth, too.
But I turned both of them down.
Huh? Why?
Oh.
Well, I mean, I thought you
didn't have enough staff.
Oh, um... Right!
I might hold you back, of course!
B-But back home, I'd help out with customers,
and I studied up some
during the Stagiaire, too.
I guess I think I might
be of some help, maybe!
So... if I can help you with your booth...
That is, if you're okay with that...
Tadokoro...
That'd seriously be a super big help!
Okay!
Okay, let's cook up something
awesome, Tadokoro!
Yeah!
Hayama-kun!
May I come in?
What do you want?
I have a message.
I, Nakiri Alice, have decided to
participate in the Moon Festival.
Oh, okay.
But the booth application period has ended.
So let's put our best foot forward together.
Huh?
Let's use the Shiomi Research Group's booth
location together, with the three of us.
I have permission from Professor Shiomi.
Huh?!
Please hear me out, Professor Shiomi.
He can continue his work at
the Shiomi Research Group,
but he can only participate
in the school festival
as a high school first year
once in his lifetime!
Once in his lifetime...
It is our wish to create something
memorable together with Akira-kun,
our valued school friend.
Right, Ryo-kun?
Sure...
"Our valued school friend"!
Maternal Instinct
Hayama-kun has friends his own age!
So on that note, please sign this form.
Shiomi Jun
That Jun!
Now do you understand?
Oh, and of course, I will be the leader.
That's not a given!
To heck with that!
Kurokiba, say something!
Once the miss is set on something,
you can't stop her.
Don't give up!
Tough it out!
Just wait, Yukihira-kun!
You too, Erina!
I'm going to one-up you guys at the festival!
I'll have you know that our booth
location is in the Main Avenue area,
so it's not where Yukihira
or Nakiri Erina will be.
What? How tragic.
Polar Star Dormitory
First, saute ground pork over high heat.
Boil firm tofu for two
minutes and let it drain.
Once the ground pork turns
brown and fragrant,
add the spicy flavors!
Take chicken stock and add sweet bean sauce,
chili bean sauce, black bean sauce,
garlic, and chili powder.
How is it?
It's still not enough.
This wasn't the spiciness I
tasted at Chinese Cuisine RS.
Wow, so spicy!
But it's still not enough!
Not yet!
Spicy!
Not gonna let them beat me!
Damn, it's spicy!
I did it, Tadokoro!
Mapo Tofu, Extra Spicy Version!
Try it, please.
His lips are already swollen!
Sh-Shpicy!
Yeah, it's ridiculously spicy.
Okay, let's try some other Chinese dishes.
Twice-cooked pork.
Pepper steak.
Oh, sorry, Tadokoro.
You can take a break.
No, I have to do the tasting!
Sh-Shpicy!
I ate it...
I managed to eat it, Soma-kun!
I knew it,
but it's still a complete failure.
They're just spicy, and that's it.
Beyond all that spiciness,
the Chinese Cuisine RS's mapo
tofu had well-constructed umami.
Um, Soma-kun...
I heard this from Hojo-san,
but the seasonings used
by the Chinese Cuisine RS
like chili bean sauce,
sweet bean sauce, black bean sauce,
and oyster sauce are all
specially-made by Kuga-senpai.
Specially-made?
I think that's why there's so much
umami underlying the spiciness.
I see.
So one of Sichuan cuisine's signature dishes
has been infused with multiple expressions
of Kuga-senpai's culinary convictions.
It's really become a dish that
represents who he is as a chef.
Spiciness, huh.
Skewers RS
Wow!
An Evening of Taro Stew
With Isshiki Satoshi
Indeed!
Our Polar Star Dormitory booth
will be serving taro stew!
Huh.
We'll be using a lot of produce
grown on the Isshiki farm!
An Evening of Taro Stew
With Isshiki Satoshi
The booth sign's well-made, too.
I designed it!
We built it!
Are you sure using a temporary tent in the
high-class Yamanote Area is a good idea?
We're hoping to look rustic and approachable.
We already have a ton of advance reservations
from ladies who attend
Isshiki-senpai's cooking class!
I get that, but...
Why are you dressed like
that, Isshiki-senpai?
Well, traditional taro stew gatherings
are done on a river bank.
So I'm thinking right around there, say...
Does he intend to put a river there?!
We're out of paint!
We need a purchase run, stat!
Anyone available to help?!
Wow, everyone's in all-out prep mode.
Every day after school will be like this now.
It's exciting!
Tadokoro-san!
Yukihira-kun!
Oh!
Isami-kun!
Pop-Up
"Pop-up Trattoria Aldini"?
Huh.
You're doing it with Takumi?
With all of our classmates, actually.
Yukihira!
I heard you're going to
challenge Kuga-senpai.
Oh, yeah.
Let me say this.
You're not the only one who's
grown during the Stagiaire.
Don't think I'm the same man
I was during the prelims!
I'm the one who'll defeat you!
We have to go shopping, Bro.
You hear me, Yukihira?!
You've got to be kidding me!
The menu's already set!
Shiomi Research Group
Creative Curry Laboratory
Why?
Why does it have to be curry?
We're inviting representatives from
Shiomi Research Group's corporate partners!
You can't just do whatever you want!
Then why am I even showing up?!
I have a message from Professor Shiomi.
I'll manage our corporate partners somehow!
Hayama-kun, go enjoy student life!
Jun...
Besides, Professor Shiomi told me to
collaborate with you on the menu.
That's a fun trio.
I wonder if they'll actually
be able to work together.
It's busy everywhere,
but I guess everyone's enjoying student life.
Yeah, it's really invigorating!
Come on, march!
There's nothing invigorating about this.
A one-two, a one-two!
Oh, Yukihira-chin.
Hey.
Is that construction material for your booth?
Yeah, it's such a production.
Our booth's huge,
and the storefront is an
important factor, you know?
It kind of looks grim.
Not at all! We're having fun!
Well, that's good.
Still, if your booth loses money,
you'll be expelled!
I couldn't possibly bear
to see young talent like you
forced to leave the academy!
You're definitely not thinking that at all.
Well, try not to get expelled, at least.
Come on, march!
A one-two, a one-two!
The storefront's also an
important factor, huh.
It's true that when I set up shop
at a summer festival with Dad,
we got more customers when
we were more creative.
Huh?
I see.
Nakiri said it, too.
Sichuan isn't the only Chinese cuisine.
Then maybe, just maybe...
Tadokoro, there's something I need.
Can you help?
What is it?
Chinese Cuisine Culinary Division
Warehouse No. 3
This is what Yukihira wants, right?
Yeah.
Is it really okay to let us use it?
Sure.
I already got permission from the
lead lecturer in Chinese cuisine.
I told you to hit me up if
you needed help, remember?
Thanks!
I wish I could help you out
during the festival, too,
but I'm supposed to help
out at a different booth.
Oh, don't worry about it
after all your help already!
Besides, you're still training for
your family restaurant, right?
Yeah. It's all baby steps,
but I feel I'm building better relationships
with the restaurant staff lately.
I hope I can be like you soon—
a chef everyone likes.
Th-That's—
How'd it go, Tadokoro?
Soma-kun!
Found it! Right here!
Oh, thanks, Hojo!
You're welcome.
Make sure you give Kuga-san a
run for his money with this!
Sure!
Dad, what's this?
It's a stone oven I borrowed
from someone I know.
If we just do pan-fried noodles
every year, it gets boring.
We'll use this to get top sales
at this year's summer festival.
Huh.
We need this to get it all started...
in order to make that.
A Few Days Later
Moon Festival Opening Day
The plum ticket is 500 yen,
the bamboo ticket is 1,000 yen,
and the pine ticket is 10,000 yen!
Customers will use these
tickets at your booths!
Totsuki
They serve as proofs of purchase,
so please don't lose them!
Furthermore, your earnings report must be
submitted before 6:00 PM every day!
Te-he!
Yukihira-kun... Erina, you too!
Hey.
The day's finally here.
Are you all ready?
Well, for now.
I see.
I'm glad.
I'm disappointed that I can't compete
in the same area as you two,
but our booth will beat out the rest of
othe competition in the Main Avenue area.
The two behind you seem to be
suffering from extreme fatigue.
Is your booth going to be all right?
Of course.
Yukihira-kun, don't let
your rival get you down.
Good luck with everything.
Oh, speak of the devil...
We'll now sing the Totsuki Teahouse
Culinary Academy's school anthem.
School anthem? We have one?
Did you know, Tadokoro?
Here in the bosom of the
land of the rising sun,
come ye sharp and bright-souled youths
Look upon the pinnacle of food.
Now, bestir yourselves.
Ah, hone yourselves. (Hone yourselves.)
You are in the sacred land of gourmands.
You are here in Totsuki Academy.
The 92nd
Moon Festival
Tsukassan.
I hope you'll keep your promise?
The time has come!
I now announce the opening
of the Moon Festival!
The 92nd
Moon Festival
If I may say so myself,
Kuga Restaurant
I've created one very
respectable restaurant here.
Indeed!
Just look at Yukihira Soma's
booth in comparison.
Totsuki Culinary Teahouse Academy
Famous Taiwanese
Black Pepper Buns
How dare he even consider
challenging us with such a place!
All right!
This is our first hand to win
against the Chinese Cuisine RS—
the black pepper bun!
Piping hot black pepper buns!
Would you like a hot black pepper bun?
Huh?
Black pepper buns?
I've heard of them!
They're famous Taiwanese street food, right?
Oh, look!
They're plastered all over
inside the stone oven!
I wonder what they taste like?
They have a ground pork rib meat
filling seasoned with black pepper!
Oh, I want to try that!
Me, too!
Give me two!
Thank you!
Thanks!
They're hot!
Digging in!
It's so juicy!
The bun is soft and flaky,
just like pie crust!
The meat stuffing has lots of sliced onions!
The spicy black pepper adds a nice note.
The ground pork's mild richness
and umami just keep gushing out!
Delicious!
Thank goodness.
Soma-kun, they seem to like it!
Great!
Totsuki
Food Wars
The Third Plate
Next Episode: Moon Festival
I hope you savor the next episode!