So, what do you want?
I have two questions for you.
Huh? What are they?
Then here is my first question.
Why did you suddenly decide
to swim in the relay?
Furious All-out!
Why did you suddenly decide
to swim in the relay?
I changed my mind.
You came out here to ask me that?
That answer does not convince me.
You've been fixated on racing
Haruka-senpai all this time.
Your reason was that you couldn't
move forward until you defeated him.
And in the last tournament,
you beat him.
Doesn't that mean you've achieved your goal?
My goal isn't to beat Haru.
And it's not to win
tournaments in this country.
I aim higher. My goal is the world.
The world?
Very well.
Moving on to my second question.
How do you feel about Haruka-senpai?
Huh?
In grade school, you and
Haruka-senpai were close rivals.
I saw old pictures of you guys
when we were at Coach Sasabe's house.
You used to smile all the time.
With Haruka-senpai, Makoto-senpai,
and Nagisa-kun...
The four of you were always
together and having fun.
So what made you change
after going to study abroad?
Why didn't you contact Haruka-senpai
or any of the others after
you returned to Japan?
What happened while you were abroad?
You used to be good friends, so why?
You swam in a relay together, so why?
You must have been thrilled about
swimming in a relay with them!
Aren't you the one who
understands more than anyone
how great that relay was?
Shut up!
I let you talk, and you think you can
spout all the stupid logic you want?!
Why do I have to explain myself to you?!
Because I'm a victim.
I was originally on the track team,
but I ended up joining the swim club.
After watching Haruka-senpai swim,
I wanted to swim like him.
Practice was hard at first,
but it started to grow on me.
Eventually, I was having
fun swimming with everyone.
At prefecturals, I finally
swam in a relay with them.
That was the first time
I really understood relays
as more than just a theory.
I realized how fun they could be!
I can still remember how it felt.
We were finally united as one!
We felt like a real team!
But they all keep talking about you!
Rin-chan!
That's not my problem!
Like hell it's not!
Bastard!
It's your fault that Haruka-senpai
stopped swimming!
Huh?! What are you talking about?!
Haruka-senpai felt guilty about
beating you in middle school!
So why are you people acting this way?!
I don't get it!
You beat Haruka-senpai in your last race!
Isn't that enough?!
Why are you swimming in the relay now?!
What do you want to do?!
What do you want from Haruka-senpai?!
What will it take to satisfy you?!
In that case...
What about you?
You weren't involved in any of this,
so why are you giving me all this grief?!
What do you want to do?!
I...
I want us to become the
best team at a tournament.
I want to swim with them
as a member of that team.
That's all I want.
If you interfere,
I will never forgive you.
Is Rei okay?
I think he'll be fine...
But I'm a little worried.
Damn that Rei...
Doesn't he realize that an athlete needs
to take care of his own health?
Hey, go check on him.
Oh, isn't this the first time
we've gone to Rei's place?
I live nearby, so I've dropped by a few times.
Oh, what kind of gift should we get him?
We should definitely get him a melon!
Muskmelons
There won't be any under 1,000 yen.
Do we go with strawberries, then?
Wasn't it strawberry milk ice
cream that made him sick?
Oh, that's right...
How about bananas?
Should we even be bringing food
if he has an upset stomach?
Are you sure it was something he ate?
Huh?
Or was it what I said yesterday
that's bothering him?
Um...
Heya, Rei-chan!
We're here to see you.
Why is everybody here?
You weren't at practice today,
so we came to see you.
Oh, I was...
Hey, you look like you're gonna be just fine!
Gou-chan and Ama-chan were worried, too.
Goro-chan was worried you
weren't taking care of yourself
with a tournament coming up.
Everybody was worried about me?
Of course.
It was the first time you've
ever missed practice.
It'd be one thing if Nagisa missed...
Hey, what's that supposed to mean?!
Sorry, okay?
Oh, these are incredible.
Are they from middle school?
Yes, but that's all in the past.
But now he has all these swimming books!
You're right!
You've read all of these books?
Oh, yes.
I've got all the theories down.
You're not supposed to say that, Rei-chan.
You'll set yourself up to fail!
Why would you say that?
Rei, did you really go see Rin?
I told them everything.
Sorry, Rei-chan.
It's okay.
Yes, I did.
Was it because I told
you about our past?
No, I had my own reasons for
wanting to meet Rin-san.
But it's okay now.
I'm done worrying about him.
It's not my problem.
Okay, then.
The four of us are a team now, Rei.
Haruka-senpai...
Yep, we need you to
contribute to the team.
That's right!
Every member is irreplaceable, Rei-chan!
Yes!
Let's take a break then!
Melon Bread
Why did you bring melon bread as a gift?
Because an actual melon
would be too expensive.
This is really good though.
Here, Haru-chan.
Open wide.
No, it's okay...
Well? Isn't it good?
Losing moisture...
Are you okay, Haru?!
Hey, Rei!
Bring something to drink! Quick!
Yes, I'll be right back!
Haru-chan?
Haru!
The drink that goes best with melon bread is...
Barley tea.
The Ryugazaki family has been
pairing melon bread with barley tea
since my grandfather's time.
Just bring him something to drink!
Water...
Is Haru-chan okay?
How can you be so calm?!
Haru! Hurry up, Rei!
Oh, sorry!
The Power of Teamwork
Haruka-senpai, I'm coming to help!
Don't die, Haru!
I...
I want us to become the
best team at a tournament.
I want to swim with them
as a member of that team.
That's all I want.
I hope that we can also
become a great team!
Matsuoka-senpai seems really off today.
Did he say anything to you, Nitori?
No, he never tells me anything.
But I'm sure there's
nothing to worry about!
I'm sure he went through much tougher
experiences while he was abroad.
Matsuoka didn't join the
swim team when he first
transferred here from Australia.
Do you know why?
No, did something happen?
Well, the past doesn't matter.
It's performance that counts here.
The fastest swimmer wins.
It's that simple.
Gou!
I'll give you a hand.
Thanks!
Oh, some of my friends want
to go cheer at regionals!
Huh? Why are they
suddenly so interested?
Because you made it past prefecturals!
That's amazing!
A brand new swim club in regionals!
Okay, boys!
Get pumped!
Rei, come on.
Let's practice our exchange.
Yes!
All right!
Keep it going!
Okay, I've taught you everything I can!
Fire it up!!
Iwatobi Swim Club
Persevere
All that's left is for
you to perform your best!
Fire!
That banner is really embarrassing.
That drawing...
Oh! It's the one Haru-chan drew!
I didn't think it'd be used for this.
Iwatobi
Station
Well, we'll head up there tomorrow morning.
Get plenty of rest at the hotel near the venue.
The Roman general Caesar said it best.
If we cross, we will wreak tragedy
upon the world. If we do not...
Oh, it's the bus.
Well...
We're off!
From: Matsuoka Gou
Subject: Big Brother
Best of luck to both sides!
Let's go to nationals!
What is it?
Nothing.
Man, we're all by ourselves in this hotel.
I'm getting nervous.
Yeah...
Haru-chan! Mako-chan!
Ready to go?
What do you want for dinner?
There's only one thing to
eat before a tournament.
Traditional Meal Specials
Pork cutlet bowl!
I think I'll go with tenderloin cutlets.
Me too!
Two tenderloin cutlets!
Got it, two tenderloin cutlets.
The miso mackerel meal.
Got it, one mackerel.
Saw that coming!
I'm thinking the hot pot or pork
cutlet bowl with ankake sauce.
Hm, or maybe the chilled cutlet udon...
One hot pot, one ankake,
one chilled cutlet udon.
What?!
You've got it wrong!
I wasn't placing an order!
That was good!
I had too much to eat.
Practice was crazy today!
That was brutal!
Hey, are those guys going to
be in the tournament tomorrow?
What if they end up in
the lane next to us?
They're probably students
at a local high school.
After all, they aren't built like swimmers.
You sound like Gou-chan.
Right! Let's check out the pool.
Only authorized
personnel allowed.
No luck.
I guess it's too late.
This isn't going to happen, then.
Wait, we might be able to see the pool.
Hurry up, guys!
It's not safe to run around in the dark!
Wow...
It's big.
We'll be swimming in that tomorrow.
Yeah.
I'm getting excited!
Yep!
All done!
Fly High!
Iwatobi Swim Club
What do you think?
So close... If not for the drawing...
Quiet, you!
Girls, you should go home.
We'll be leaving early tomorrow morning.
Yes, we're almost done...
Big brother?
I need to ask you something.
Haru, are you asleep?
No, I'm awake.
Can't fall asleep, huh?
Yeah...
I hope we make it to the final tomorrow.
Makoto.
I appreciate you being here for me.
Thanks.
Haru?!
I'm going out for a quick run.
Wait, now?!
Hey, Rei-chan...
What is it?
You shouldn't eat that squid...
He's talking in his sleep?!
Haru-chan!
Nagisa?
Rei-chan was gone when I woke
up, so I'm looking for him.
What about you?
I'm...
Too nervous to sleep, right?
Not exactly.
I'm feeling pretty nervous myself.
You are?
What if I screw up my dive?
Wouldn't I ruin it for everyone?
I'm worrying about things I
usually don't think about.
Because I get to swim in a
relay with you guys again!
And we'll be racing Rin-chan tomorrow.
That's probably why you're nervous.
It's all thanks to you.
Huh?
You're the one who came up with
the idea of starting a swim club.
Yep, that's right.
I never thought I'd be
swimming in a relay again.
Well, that means you should be
showing more gratitude to me!
Yeah.
Thanks, Nagisa.
Haru-chan!
Hey, Nagisa!
I'm so happy!
This is great, Haru-chan!
Stop it! Are you listening, Nagisa?!
Haru-chan!
Yo.
Did you want something?
I never answered your question.
That's no longer necessary.
No.
I'll give you my answer.
I won't feel like it's over until I do.
You wanted to know how I
feel about Haru, right?
It's true that I was fixated on racing him.
But it's not Haru's fault that
I wanted to quit swimming.
I was pretty shocked when I lost to him.
But that wasn't what did it.
After moving to Australia,
I trained every day and
participated in tournaments.
But I couldn't swim the way I wanted to.
The Olympics were completely out of reach.
I felt more and more like
I was being left behind.
I could only wonder.
Why was I struggling so much?
Why?
Ah...
It was because I swam in a relay.
I ruined myself.
That was the conclusion I arrived at.
After returning to Japan, I
didn't let any of them know.
I didn't talk to any of them.
But when I
swam with Haru that night,
I had a breakthrough.
I wanted to swim again.
When I watched you guys
swim at prefecturals, it reminded me
of our relay.
Rin-san, you...
Your name's Ryugazaki?
I'm going to swim in Samezuka's relay.
I'm going to show you how good I can be.
So do the best you can with
Haru and your other teammates.
But that also means that
you can't embarrass your team.
That's all I have to say.
Sorry to make you come out here.
Welcome back, Senpai.
Did something happen?
No, nothing happened.
Oh, that's right.
The captain was looking for you.
He probably wants to talk
about the relay tomorrow.
Medley Relay
Azuma Yuuki       Ueda Tsuyoshi      Kawamura Tetsuo       Noro Masaru
What?
This will be our lineup
for the relay tomorrow.
Kawamura Tetsuo
You can focus on the 100m free.
Hold on! Why?!
You haven't paid any attention
to your own relay team.
You're focused on something else.
I'm sending our best members out there.
That's what a team should do.
You're not at your best
condition right now.
You can't...
Haru, do you remember
the first time we ran
into Rin at a tournament?
Yeah, we've come a long way since then.
Hey, why are you guys reminiscing?
That's right. We still
have a long way to go.
Next time: Distant Free!
Hey, Haru. What did you see that day?