I'm counting on you then, Millihi-nee.
Sure.
You too, Rebecca.
I'm counting on you to
guard and escort my sister.
You can count on me.
This is a traditional event
held once a year in Pastillage.
The Esnart Arts and Music Festival.
Held in their greatest concert hall,
this is their biggest musical event.
People come from all over
and the entire town is infected
with the spirit of festival.
The princess has also been invited
to perform on stage as a singer.
Esnart Arts and Music Festival
These clothes and shoes
sure are easy to move in.
Yeah, huh?
It's good that you wear
the same size as Nanami.
That's perfect.
I guess the clothes are a little
big, since they're mine.
No, they're just right.
You even made an opening for my tail.
Becky did that.
Is everything okay with the princess?
I talked to her a bit, before she left.
Besides, Becky will be
by the princess's side today.
My walk with Rebecca was so much fun.
I'm glad to hear it.
And what did you do today?
We played catch
and then we both got on Mercurius
and rode through the sky.
That does indeed sound like fun.
It was!
Thank you very much.
We'll get in the bath ourselves,
so you may all go ahead and take a break.
Yes.
I do apologize though.
I know your morning walk
is your time to go out
together with Sink.
I have fun with you, too.
Really?
Of course!
That reminds me.
You're not spending as much
time with Sink as I expected.
Yes. His work and my work are
just so completely different.
But every day this summer,
we've made sure to begin
and end the day together.
In the morning we take our walk,
and in the evening we study together.
We enjoy each day.
Oh, yeah.
You study in your room, don't you?
I can already write all the
hiragana and the alphabet.
That's great!
I always think I'm very lucky
to have Sink as our hero.
Yeah!
So Princess...
Yes?
Have you ever thought you might like
to marry Sink at some point?
Rebecca-san!
I still haven't... I haven't
even considered such a thing.
You say "still", so does that mean
you'd consider it in the future?
That's not what I meant.
No need to be shy.
I think it would be nice, if it happened,
but Sink is from Earth after all.
You're here, too.
It doesn't bother me at all.
If you love Sink and he loves you,
then I support you both
with all my heart.
That's not okay!
After all, you love him, too.
Huh?
You say you're all right with it,
but I bet you'd be very sad
if it ever actually happened.
I guess it would be a lie if I said it
wouldn't make me feel lonely at all.
Sink and I are basically family.
It guess I'm also afraid of
changing what we have now...
Yes.
The truth is, I really like our
relationship right now, too.
It's so warm, and exciting,
and just plain nice.
Being together is so fun and pleasant.
Exactly.
So I'm afraid that we might lose that,
if I try to change something,
and I wouldn't know what to do then...
That's exactly what I mean!
I bet Sink wants
to focus on athletics
and his role as Hero for a while.
I know what you mean.
That's why I let a few years go by
without being able to say anything.
That's me.
Still, I actually like the
way we are now, too.
We're childhood friends
who are more than friends,
but not quite family...
I get just a little bit
of special treatment...
What used to scare me the most
was being the third wheel,
if he ever fell in love with someone.
That I'd have to keep my distance
and give up a lot of things...
Yes.
Which is why you have to be
that most important person for him.
It's not easy though.
I've gotten to like you so much, too.
You're so kind, Princess.
I love you, too!
In the end, it's all up to Sink,
but he just loves everybody he meets.
That's what's so wonderful about him.
He loves everyone,
he's always so positive,
and that's what I love about him.
Yeah. Me, too.
Then again, it's not like I
don't have my problems with him.
Really? Like what?
Like... but this is between us, okay?
Oh really. I can see that.
Well, I just hope he notices one day.
We can't tell him though.
I promise I'll keep it a secret,
so that maybe he'll see it himself.
Yeah. It'll be our secret.
Galette Northeast - Near the Border
Mithha Mountain
Looks like a band of
highwayman-rabbits to me.
They seem to be peaceful though.
Nanami and I caught the ones
who stumbled into Ayase.
This is their original habitat,
so we just brought them back.
Their boss looks sick or something.
Big brother.
Valerie.
Yes?
I'm sorry we kept you waiting.
How's the base of the hill looking?
It seems no harm was done.
We did notice one thing...
Apparently, one of them had
a rather strange form.
She looked like a young girl
and seemed very close to the boss-rabbit.
However, nobody has seen her lately.
The band has split up to look for her
and entered human settlements.
Do you think she's in a
human settlement, too?
I just hope it's not some
kind of dangerous demon.
Ma'am, how about these?
Huh?
Are you all right?
This is bad!
Princess Millihiore, our special guest
at the opening day of our music festival,
has just arrived at Eschenbach Palace.
Her clothing and accessories
are as adorable as always.
The number of people here is crazy.
Even the outdoor seating is full.
There are, apparently, over twice
as many people here as last year.
We'll need to keep security tight.
Yeah!
You won't be going out until pretty
late in the second half, right?
Yes,
so we can relax for a bit.
It's really amazing though,
that you'll be singing in
front of all those people.
I do love to sing,
and I am happy if they're
letting me sing.
But still...
Yes?
I still get nervous when
I'm getting up on stage.
What if I screw up the plan,
or what if I read the crowd wrong?
You'll be fine, Princess.
I got it.
Why don't we call Sink?
Yes? Sink here.
Hi, Sink.
Are you in the middle of work?
Yeah.
I'm helping Rico and the others
set up the vendor stalls.
Is something going on?
Well, the princess is nervous
and she could use some cheering up.
Roger!
I'm sorry to bother you during work.
You're not bothering me at all.
Don't worry, Princess.
Just give it your best.
I will!
I'll try to sing like I always do.
Are you performing here?
Regular guests are not
allowed back here...
Yes?
It's one of the knights.
Is something wrong?
I'm so sorry.
Are you all right, Princess?
Yes, are you all right?
Stop right there, you jewel thief!
No!
These are very precious to...
Cou-sama, the princess, and everybody!
This is an emergency call
to all security personnel.
A young female robber
has invaded Princess
Millihiore's green room.
She was beaten back by Rebecca-sama.
Both she and the princess are fine.
The robber uses magic
to control the bodies of her opponents.
Could this be some kind of demon?
No. If she controls the
bodies of her victims,
then she must be a...
Catch her!
Transform!
Hero Crystal Hero Time.
The Hero...
You're deflecting her control?
Is this the power of the Hero Crystal?!
Now you're going to give
back all the things you stole.
Eclair, let's get her!
Yeah!
She sure is fast!
Judging by her skills, I'd say
she's the child of a local god.
Most likely, a descendant of a cat god.
Local god, you say?
Then we can't be too rough with her.
But we have to get back
everything she stole.
If we're careful, we can
do it without getting hurt.
Then let's go get her!
Fast Wind Blade!
Good job, Eclair.
Oh, that was nothing.
It looks like they caught the thief!
They also recovered all
the items she stole.
That's wonderful!
I guess she really
was a lost local god.
I'm glad she didn't get hurt.
We will make sure to bring this
cat god safely back to Mithha.
Excuse me.
Just one moment.
This is for you, cat god.
I got it as a souvenir
at one of the booths,
but I'll give it to you.
Owwowowowow!
No cat god! You're not
supposed to bite it!
I don't think a young, wild cat god
understands too many words.
Yeah, huh?
I guess, even if we go back now,
we won't make it in time
for the princess's performance.
I guess we can watch a recording.
We'll make it.
Get on!
It's the Hero Super
Express, Hyper Edition!
What he said!
Wow, this is incredible!
This brings back memories.
This is just like when
we first met, Sink.
Yeah, huh.
You've grown up, Sink.
I'm overcome with emotion...
No, no, I think you've
got that a bit wrong.
Normal Hero or big Hero,
they're both great!
Jeez.
Ecle?
Is something wrong?
It's nothing!
There's something in our path!
Evade!
Watch where you're going!
Good evening, everyone!
I just want to tell you how
absolutely wonderful it is
to stand on Pastillage's legendary
stage again this year.
I am so, so very happy
to see you all, again.
We made it.
Quiet now.
The day after tomorrow,
the three nations of Pastillage,
Biscotti, and Galette
will combine forces to
host one huge event.
Of course we will be there,
as well as knights, Heroes,
and everybody else,
all ensuring that it
will be a great event!
Now, please listen
to the Union Fest song,
"Heart Relation".
You were always by my side,
always right next to me.
That's why we could
embrace the same hopes.
I want to stretch
out this hand
and touch you.
Listen to the
first beat
of my heart.
I'm sure
we'll have a connection.
Inscribe
it in the sky.
Gather more courage.
Be strong.
Be strong,
so that we can bind
our hearts!
Under the blue sky...
The echo of the bell...
Listen to it.
The beginning
is right there.
I'm sure
we'll have a connection.
Let it reverberate through the sky.
Gather your love and courage.
Be strong.
Be strong,
so that our hearts
will never part.
The musical festival was a huge success,
but there wasn't much
time to rest afterwards
because the next huge event was upon us.
Finally, tomorrow we have the three
countries' great joint event.
Let's give it all we've got.
Yeah!
It is Galette's pride to win anything
that bears the war moniker!
It is obvious that we will win!
Let's do our best, Sink.
Let's, Princess!
Oh no, my body isn't obeying me...
Union Fest
Princess, even now your
dance moves are so elegant.