Not quite what I had in mind...
Back to the drawing board!
Huh?
Delicious!
It actually turned out to be delicious!
It's a one-in-ten-thousand miracle!
I want to give it to him no matter what!
I've got to give it to him!
"DELICIOUS"
If I'm not mistaken,
today's Valentine's Day, huh?
Well, not that it means much to me.
Not that it really means anything to me...
You were hopeful, were you not?
I was not. Not by a long shot!
Jeez, Shu! As if there'd be
any chocolates in my locker...
There's no way in hell.
My, how modest we are!
Well, let's just pray that somebody will
give us some by the end of the day... comrade!
It's not a big deal, all right?
Awwww, I wish someone
would give me some chocolate!
After all, I've never
gotten any from a girl before...
Will Chitoge bring me some, maybe?
I mean, we are boyfriend
and girlfriend on paper...
And maybe Onodera, too...
Nah, that's never gonna happen, right?
How delusional am I?
As if she'd give me any!
Me of all people!
Morning, Bean Sprout.
H-Hey... Morning...
What? Can I help you?
No... it's nothing.
Is that so?
Oh, by the way, is there
something special about today?
For some reason,
everyone seems kind of giddy.
Huh? You've never heard of Valentine's Day?
Valentine's?
Oh, right, in the U.S.,
you don't give guys chocolate, right?
O-Oh... Valentine's Day?
Right, right... So it's today, huh?
I see, so that's why, huh?
What's up with that?
I hope you're not actually
expecting any from me, are you?
Fake couple or not, I'm pretty sure
I'm not obligated to go that far!
Yeah, I know, I know...
Just as I thought, no joy, huh?
Well, who'd expect her
to do something so maidenly anyway?
Why can't I be honest?
Idiot! Idiot! I'm such an idiot!
What kind of an attitude was that?
I've only made it harder to give them to him!
Why am I like this?
Morning!
Morning, Chitoge! Ichijo!
Hey! Morning!
Morning, Kosaki!
It's such a nice day today, huh, Ichijo?
Yeah! I guess it is!
End of Conversation
Oh, no, what am I gonna do?
I'm out of reasons to talk to him!
Seriously, at this rate,
will I be able to give it to him?
Hmm, Onodera's behaving
exactly the way she always does.
Um! If you don't mind, please accept these!
- She took them!
- Good for you!
What was that about?
What do you mean?
Of course she gave you Valentine's chocolates.
Whooo, whooo! That's our little Seishirou!
Such a chick-magnet!
What do you mean, Valentine's?
What? Don't you know?
Valentine's Day, see, is the day that
you give chocolates to people you hate!
Huh?
But I don't remember doing anything
to make those girls hate me.
So listen, if you go buy
some chocolates for, say, Raku...
and give them to him,
something good might happen to you!
Huh! If that's the case, first of all,
I'm giving these chocolates to you.
Take them!
Huh? I'm quite honored, but...
Hey, Shu! Got a minute?
Huh? What? What!?
What is it?
P-Pardon me!
Huh? Now what was that all about?
Oh, boy...
Sorry, Seishiro. I'm going
to tell you the truth this time.
Huh?
Jeez, what a shock! Who would've
guessed that Tsugumi liked Shu?
I never noticed a thing!
I have no clue what goes on
in a woman's mind...
Master Raku! Wherever can you be?
Hm? Master Raku!
Please forgive me, Master Raku!
For not quite finishing this on time!
Huh? You're not getting away, Master Raku!
Prepare yourself!
Master Raku!
Please wait up!
She really is amazing, that Marika.
Being able to voice
her feelings so aggressively...
Wait, that's totally wrong!
Why am I being such a wimp?
Didn't I somehow manage
to make delicious chocolate, too?
I've got to give it my all!
Please stop, Ichijo!
Huh? Onodera...
Um... I... have something for you...
Onodera! Are you okay?
I'm fine... I'm fine, all right?
Onodera?
Don't worry, I'm fine!
Huh?
I managed to make this, and now look...
I can't give it to him now, not like this...
It's too bad, since they're actually delicious...
I mean really... delicious, you know?
Hmm... she's nowhere to be found.
Just now, Onodera didn't seem
like her usual self to me.
You come back here, damn you!
Come back here!
Please forgive me!
Is that Shu and Tsugumi?
Curses! That guy...
Just how far will he go to ridicule me?
Tsugumi?
Why are you making that weird noise?
R-R-R-Raku Ichijo! What about you?
What brings you here?
I'm looking for Onodera.
Have you seen her?
No, can't say that I did.
Hey, Raku Ichijo. Actually, I have
something important to tell you...
Huh?
Oh, right! Boy, did you shock me good!
I had no idea that you were into Shu...
I'm NOT!
I'm not!
Huh? Are you sure you're not?
Then those chocolates you had...
where'd they come from?
What? Oh, those? A girl from
another class said they were for me...
Huh? A girl?
Come to think of it,
why would she give me chocolate?
Don't tell me she's another one
who doesn't get what Valentine's Day is about...
Or else did she think I was a boy, maybe?
Aw, no, I'm sure that's not it.
I mean...
Even a girl like Tsugumi's getting chocolate!
And here I am with zero...
this is beyond frustrating!
Do you really desire chocolate all that much?
You creatures called men?
Oh, crap! The cries from
my soul were audible...
Raku Ichijo!
O-On Valentine's Day...
I hear there's something called
an "obligatory chocolate" system...
If that's good enough for you...
I don't mind giving you this.
Huh? Are you serious?
Thanks!
That makes me happy!
That makes me so happy!
Even if it's obligatory, I'm totally happy!
Hey, thanks, Tsugumi!
Does it make you that happy?
Yeah!
Oh, man, I'm so thrilled!
After all, this is the first time in my whole life
that a girl has given me chocolate!
First time in your life?
Thanks! I really mean it!
I'll be sure to return
the favor on White Day, okay?
H-Huh? Oh... right...
Hey, almost forgot.
Maybe I should just mind my own business,
but if somebody gives you any chocolate,
don't give it away like you did just now.
Since I'm sure that person mustered up
all her courage to give it to you.
Savor it, all right?
You should mind your own business!
I'm perfectly aware of that.
See you!
If that's the case,
then make sure you savor mine, too...
Oh, crap... I just remembered something awful.
I reeled off that speech to Tsugumi,
but I'm still on the run from Tachibana
without accepting her chocolate!
And yet I went and lectured somebody else...
I'm so ashamed!
At the time, it was just instinct
that made me turn tail and run,
but all Tachibana did was
bring me the chocolate she'd made!
I'm gonna look for Tachibana first and apologize.
I'll take care of Onodera afterwards...
What the heck!?
Wh-What happened here?
What should I do? This is all my fault!
If only I hadn't run off like that...
Well, now, Master Raku.
I am terribly sorry, Master Raku.
I had crafted this for you,
but due to my carelessness, it is now in pieces.
I'm sorry... I got so carried away!
I'll make you another one and bring it in at a
later date, so will you please accept it then?
I feel like my heart's about to shatter...
Sorry! Sorry, Tachibana!
What the hell did I do?
Look at this epic hunk of chocolate
that Tachibana made for me...
And yet I...
Sorry!
Tachibana!
Oh, no, you mustn't, Master Raku!
Putting something so soiled into your mouth...
Just let me eat it, Tachibana!
Otherwise, I can never rest easy!
I really am sorry about this.
Oh, no! Of course I'm happy
that you feel that way,
but if you go on,
it will surely upset your stomach!
Your health is more important to me...
No. No good! Just let me eat this, okay?
Very well. If you insist...
What do you say to this?
To make up for today's chocolate incident,
will you grant me any wish
of my choosing - just one?
If you agree, I'll just let this go, all right?
And Master Raku, please feel free
to forget about this chocolate!
What do you think?
Okay. If that's how you feel about it...
I'll make this up to you.
But I'm still gonna eat this chocolate.
What!? No... that's so unfair, Master Raku!
What difference does it make, anyway?
You mustn't! That's breaking the rules!
But this chocolate tastes so amazing!
I'm only eating it because
I want to, so don't stop me.
You're really being unfair...
Oh, man, I thought my number was up!
Who knew she'd blow her top like that?
You do know it's your fault
for telling her stupid lies, don't you?
You're the one to blame.
Well, now, I don't have a retort for that!
Hey, hey... By the way, Ruri,
aren't you giving anybody chocolate?
Unfortunately, I have no such plans.
Well, then, those Pockys will do just fine,
so let me have them, will you?
After all, it is Valentine's Day!
You really are cold.
Just because you couldn't get your hands on
a single chocolate, don't start pestering me.
Uh, actually, I did get two this year!
I wonder why it is that you annoy me so much?
Come to think of it,
I wonder how Kosaki's been faring?
Kosaki? What are you doing
in a place like this?
Chitoge!
Are those... chocolates? Are you
planning to give them to someone?
What? Huh?
Don't tell me it's someone you've got
a crush on! Who is it? Who is it?
That's not it! He's a friend!
And so I went all-out and made them, but...
Before I could give them to him,
I ruined them myself.
Oh? So you're not giving
that person chocolate anymore?
Hmm... What will I do now?
At the very least,
I know I'm not giving him these...
Then can I have these chocolates?
What? But...
Wow! What is this? So delicious!
I envy you... I mean,
I'm a pretty good cook myself,
but I don't think I could
make chocolate this good!
Thanks.
Aren't you giving anyone
chocolate yourself, Chitoge?
Huh? Me? I...
I do have someone I want
to give chocolate to. I guess?
But I just can't bring myself to do it...
Is it someone you have a crush on, Chitoge?
Huh?
...Yes.
By any chance, would that be...
...Ichijo?
I think I just asked her
something I shouldn't have!
Not, not, not, not, not!
It's so not that idiot bean sprout!
He's just, you know! We're only faking
being boyfriend and girlfriend, so...!
A hopeless dork like him...
I wouldn't even give him obligatory chocolate!
I-I see!
What am I gonna do?
A huge lie just popped out of my mouth!
But I can't say I like him now...
it would be too embarrassing!
I see, for a couple only pretending to be dating,
they just seemed so into each other...
Thank goodness! So that was
just me overthinking it all...
What about you, Kosaki?
Isn't there someone you like?
Huh? I...
Yes, I have someone, too.
Someone I like.
I was really planning to give
these chocolates to him...
But I've given up on that now.
Sorry. I ate one...
Oh, no! Uh, listen, that's not what I meant!
I'd already decided not to give them to him!
Sorry! But it made me happy to hear
you say they were delicious.
But you know, that was such a surprise.
To hear that you had a crush on someone.
Oh, but now that I think of it,
it must be such a hassle!
Since you're pretending to be dating Ichijo...
Huh? Oh, yes, it sure is.
You're the first person, you know.
That I've ever told about liking someone.
This kind of thing really makes
your heart pound, huh?
Me, too! The only people who know
about my crush are probably you and Ruri.
Because I've always kept it a secret.
Oh, really? Is that right?
That really makes me happy!
Hey, then what do you say to this?
Huh?
We're going to go on keeping
this a secret from other people!
And we're going to root for
each other in our respective romances!
And until we both find true love, neither of us
can probe each other about who it is that we like...
Well?
Okay! Good idea! Let's do that!
Okay, then, that's a promise!
Let's both give it our all!
Okay, let's get right to it, then...
Huh?
Why don't we make your
chocolates over again, Kosaki?
It would be such a waste to give up!
Just re-make those chocolates,
and give them to that person!
I'll help, too!
Chitoge...
And I'll do my best to hand
my chocolates over, too!
Okay!
Home-Ec Room
Oh! Oh, no! Look at the time!
Chitoge, you'd better go now,
or the person you like will be heading home!
What? But the chocolates aren't done yet!
You can't stay here!
Or you won't get to give them to him today!
Thank you for helping me out, Chitoge.
I'll be fine! I'm going to hang in here till the
last second, and I'm sure they'll end up delicious!
So I want you to give it your best shot, too.
Right.
Darling!
Huh?
Do you have a second?
There's something I want to talk to you about.
Huh? What's this? Acting so formal...
Be honest... This time, you've got to be honest...
I hear today's Valentine's Day, huh?
Yeah. We did talk about that this morning?
The thing is,
last night, I coincidentally just happened
to make some homemade chocolate, see...
What kind of a coincidence is that?
And since I just happened
to bring some with me,
they're just obligatory, but I guess I don't
mind giving them to you for Valentine's Day.
Although they're obligatory!
You really don't know how to be honest...
But... going out of your way to bring
me your homemade chocolate...
I guess you do have
your good points now and then...
Wait, but are these safe?
Homemade stuff by you...
What the...? If you're gonna
be so rude, give them back!
All right, my bad! I'll eat them, okay?
Hey... I'd say this was
a pretty great effort for you.
Really?
Sure! They're really good!
This tastes like actual chocolate, you know!
Oh? Good for you, then.
I'll be expecting you to pay me
back tenfold, okay? Looking forward to it!
Huh? What's up with that?
Later!
Oh, man...
Well, I somehow managed
to give him the chocolate!
Seriously, to think it takes this much courage
to give chocolate to someone you like?
I had no idea...
I used salt instead of sugar!
That moron!
I've always been the type who only
succeeds once every ten thousand times...
But no way am I giving up!
Because I made that promise with Chitoge!
Th-This is...
I can't find Onodera anywhere...
I wonder if she left a while ago?
Guess I'll head home.
Wait, Ichijo!
Huh?
Onodera! So you were still here at school...
Um... If you don't mind... This...
Would you mind accepting this?
Huh? Don't tell me you're giving
me chocolate? For me?
Yes. I really wanted to give this to you sooner.
But this is homemade...
It turned out pretty delicious,
so try it, please.
If Onodera made it, I'd eat it
no matter how horrible it tasted...
Yum!
Right? It's amazing, right?
It really is amazing, right?
It's awesome!
I've never eaten chocolate this good!
Thank goodness! I've never made anything
this good before in my life...
It might be a one-in-a-million thing!
Huh? Wait a second... were you making
this chocolate all this time, then?
Yes!
C-Could it be that this
chocolate is... for your true love?
It's obligatory!
But it's a slightly special kind of obligatory.
Huh?
S-See you, Ichijo. See you tomorrow!
Huh? Hey, wait...
A special kind of obligatory?
What does that mean?
Since I didn't get much sleep last night,
my eyes are all red.
I wish I could've looked a little cuter
when I gave it to him.