Manaka-san...
There you go, making that
depressing face again.
You don't have to worry so much.
But...
I'm saying...
She'll wake up soon just
like Kaname and I did.
There's no doubt.
Right...
It's been one week since
Manaka-san came back.
Come on, let's go.
Everyone believed somewhere
in their hearts...
Yeah.
What the hell is with
English being first period?
That she'd be the same
as Hikari or Kaname-san.
That she'd wake up soon.
But...
Manaka-san still showed
no signs of waking up.
Episode Twenty:
Sleeping Beauty
That ends our lesson for today.
Those who finish cleaning
first can go home.
I know it's a lot of homework,
but don't forget it.
All right!
What?
Let's get the bathroom
cleaning over with!
Seriously?
Today's the day I'm
gonna catch that Uroko!
Uroko-sama may know a
way to wake Manaka up.
Yeah, considering he's the one
who made everyone hibernate.
Kaname, hurry up!
Oh, sorry about that.
What're you doing?
I'm gonna leave you behind.
I thought that Hikari would be
more panicked about Manaka-san,
but he seems pretty positive.
Is Manaka-san at your house
by herself during the day?
My mom's been getting days off
from Saya Mart to take care of her.
I see.
Damn it.
Where the hell is he hiding?
The water temperature's getting lower.
You think so?
I think it's a lot lower since the
day we found Manaka in Shishio.
Could it be that the Sea God is angry?
About us taking Manaka back?
It's not a big deal.
All we have to do is
come up to the surface
once in a while and warm up.
Hey, Hikari!
You haven't rested since
you came back up...
See? It's no problem at all.
Yeah, but...
Yep. No problem.
Huh?
Apparently Chisaki's here.
She said she'd be late
because of her internship...
Maybe we just missed her.
Sorry I'm late.
Um...
Is something the matter?
I'm gonna go take a look again.
Then I'll go, too.
You don't need to go to Shishio
with the others, Miuna?
I've decided to leave Shishio
to Hikari and the others.
Is something wrong?
I was just thinking that since
we're all the same age now,
it'd be nice if we could
do more things together.
And it'd be even nicer if we
could get closer to their circle.
Yeah, you're right.
Hey, about Manaka-san...
How about stimulating her five senses?
Like stimulating her ears
by playing her a song?
Yeah, that sounds good.
Uroko-sama's nowhere to be found.
Miuna-chan said she met
him in the village.
Let's take a look at the
outskirts of the village, too.
Right, Hikari?
Yeah.
The song's changed.
It reminds me of the
day of the Ofunehiki.
Yeah...
Every day at this time,
I remember that day.
That's it!
Manaka heard this song, too, right?
I think I might have come
up with a good idea.
Oshiooshi Fishery Cooperative
Local Mascot Character Name Ideas:
Oshiosshii
Sea Slug-kun
Narunamimaru
That's a great idea.
Right?
If we let her listen to
things from the festival,
something will like...
Scenes from that day will
come up in her head.
We think that might just wake Manaka up.
But people have been coming and
going quite a bit since then...
Gather whomever you can!
So Itaru-san...
Please!
We beg of you.
Everyone...
All right.
I'll go contact some people,
so could you wait a little while?
I'm back.
Thanks for your hard work, you two.
I'm back, Tsumugu.
Welcome back.
The bath's ready for you.
Okay, thanks.
Be careful.
Sorry to keep you waiting. Let's go.
You guys really are complicated.
Hikari's pretty late.
Chisaki-chan and Kaname
are with him, too, right?
Yeah.
I was a little worried about
those three at first, but...
Chisaki-chan's been coming
by a lot more often lately.
Now if only Manaka-chan would wake up...
Manaka Wake Up
Yeah...
By the way, apparently
Hikari and the others
asked the fishery cooperative
to record the song for them.
-Sounds to stimulate her ears...?
-... from the sea.
-Nostalgic music: like from the Ofunehiki
What?
He's gathering people from
the Ofunehiki five years ago
in the hope that it might
wake Manaka-chan up.
I think Itaru-san was pretty happy
because he called me about it.
Even though he wasn't the one who
thought of it, he's super excited.
I see...
Welcome home.
Hikari?
Oh, I'm back.
Damn it.
I couldn't catch Uroko today either.
Oh, yeah.
We got a lot of homework today,
so let's do it together.
That's right... Everyone
was complaining about it.
There really isn't that much time.
Maybe I'll take some
time off from school.
What?!
That'll give me a lot more time,
and I'll be able to do a lot more.
N-No!
"No"? Why?
I mean...
we're still required to go to school!
What are you being all serious for?
And Mom will be really worried!
Akari's not my mom.
Yeah, but...
Taking time off from school...
If she doesn't ever wake up...
What the hell do you mean by that?
I didn't...
Fine. Got it.
I just have to go to school, right?
H-Hikari!
Wai—
That's not it...
That's not what I wanted to say...
Damn it!
Hii-kun.
Manaka...
You...
I was fine just the way I was.
Because I was gone,
the sea and the surface kept freezing...
And I...
Where's Hikari?
He left for the sea a while ago.
He said he'd go to school
straight from there.
Ketchup!
Hey, Akira! What do you
think you're doing?
And so, the Warring States
era finally came to an end...
And finally, the 260 years...
People who push their own feelings
onto others are awful, aren't they?
Library
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about the
protagonist in this book.
You're not allowed to read books
that don't concern Manaka-san today.
But we've been sitting
here for three hours.
Even my concentration is...
or rather, what are you reading?
It's an actual relevant book.
Learning About Sleep
The True State of Hypnosis
Isn't that a little off?
We don't know where we'll find
a clue about her waking up.
Are you actually thinking about this?
I am!
What are you reading?
Well...
You know, I've been thinking...
Don't princes do that often?
Kiss the sleeping princess?
I think someone should try that
on the sleeping Manaka-san.
Wh— a-a kiss?!
It's not weird.
I think that strong feelings for someone
have the power to change
something drastically.
Strong feelings?
There are people who have that...
Like Hikari.
B-But it wouldn't be good to kiss her
if there's no solid
proof that it'll help.
Well, do you have a better idea?
Not... right now.
Then why does it matter?
But that's—
You sound like you don't really
want Manaka-san to wake up.
You're the one who just said we don't
know where we might find a clue.
I'm being pretty serious about this...
Do I really not want
Manaka-san to wake up?
It's no use.
I guess I'll go look
for Uroko-sama again.
Hoi, hoi!
Ow!
Hey, Akira!
The Ofunehiki Song
Hoi, hoi.
I want Manaka-san to wake up...
That's what I should have been
thinking this whole time.
Was I the only one that
was somewhere else?
Manaka!
When did you wake up?
Oh, it's you, Miuna.
Sorry.
Hikari?!
Hikari?
He must have been exhausted.
I'll have him stay home
from school tomorrow.
You should get to bed, too, Miuna.
It'll be no good if everyone keels over.
Miuna?
You're still here?
Isn't it almost time for
you to leave for school?
Miu has a fever, too?
Well...
let's just say that she does.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Oh, good morning.
Apparently Miuna and Hikari have a cold.
Both of them are absent?
Yeah.
Um...
Are you okay, Kaname?
The sea's cold, and you've been
going in with Hikari, right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I see.
Thank goodness.
That Hikari, trying too hard.
Even though Miuna and I and
everyone else are here, too.
Take your seats.
We're about to begin.
I'll have to take notes
for three people today.
For three people?
Miuna's been taking notes for
Manaka-san for when she wakes up.
Oh, that's why.
I'll help with taking notes.
Eh?
I'll help, too.
Miuna.
Hikari's sleeping pretty well,
so I'm going to take
Akira and go shopping.
Okay.
Keep an eye on the house.
And you told Hikari not to rest...
Do I really not want
Manaka-san to wake up?
This is...
Ow! Hey, Akira!
Hikari, hot.
Get off me.
Hikari, fever.
The Ofunehiki Song
I have to go find Uroko-sama...
I'm gonna be the one who wakes her up...
It's gonna be me...
Hikari is always so straight
and narrow and bright.
The Ofunehiki Song
I'm pretty sure that
his feelings for Manaka-san
make him like that.
And yet I...
I...
It's been reported that just like in
mountain climbing and free diving,
when you put yourself into
dangerous situations,
Water
there's a rarely seen phenomenon,
that in order to stay alive,
To solve why Mukaido-san is still
sleeping and why Shiodome-san has Ena...
your dormant survival instincts
bring changes upon your body.
We believe that your
Ena is also a result
of your dormant sea-person powers
awakening because you were pushed to the limit.
The professor would like
to talk to you again.
Is there a day that works best for you?
Well, Tsumugu?
When do you think we can see her?
One moment.
Miuna.
Can you come out right now?
You awake?
I...
You had quite a fever,
but it's gone down now.
Make sure you thank Miuna.
She's been watching
over you up until now.
What about Manaka?
There haven't been any changes.
Hikari, I understand
how you feel, but...
you should rely on those
around you a bit more.
What the heck?
You're lecturing a sick person?
You're not the only one who
cares about Manaka-chan.
I know that.
You sure about that?
Oh, those...
Kaname-kun and Sayu-chan
brought them by.
So you guys won't be
behind in your studies.
Corn Soup
Here.
Thanks.
You sure you're okay with that?
Tangerine Juice
Yeah.
I like this.
I guess I really am hard to understand.
Huh? Why?
I mean...
The guys from Shishio are
overflowing with emotions.
I've always been a
little envious of that.
You, too.
I don't know about me.
It's probably not a good thing.
Because I'm not like
Hikari and the others.
Before when Hikari saw my Ena,
he said I was just like them.
But... I wonder why...
Why is Manaka-san losing her Ena
and why did I gain Ena?
I'm the only one with different
feelings toward Manaka-san.
I said something weird to
Hikari and upset him.
If she doesn't ever wake up...
I thought of the worst thing.
Do I really not want
Manaka-san to wake up?
Even I...
seriously thought it'd be better
if they didn't wake up.
Huh?
I felt like Chisaki
would disappear from me,
and I was scared.
But in the end,
once they woke up, I was really happy.
"Happy"?
It's weird, isn't it?
But I was happy.
You were scared but happy?
Yeah.
I wonder...
if I'll be able to be happy, too.
It's hard for you because
they're both precious to you.
Both Hikari and Mukaido.
I want to be able to be happy.
I want to be able to say I'm glad
from the bottom of my heart.
You'll be able to.
Apparently they've taken notes
for you while you were out.
Miuna and the others took them for you.
Hikari.
She's going to wake up, right?
Yeah.
She will. No matter what.
Hey, Hikari.
There's something Sayu was telling me.
Sayu did?
Yeah.
Strong feelings for someone have the
ability to change something drastically.
She's pretty sure that you have
powers like that, Hikari.
So...
A-Anyway...
Kiss!
Huh?
Wha...
Wh-What are you saying?!
What am I saying?
Oh!
N-No, that's not it!
I'm saying that you
should kiss Manaka-san!
Wha?! Either way, why would I do that?!
Because it's needed for her to wake up!
That makes no sense!
And why would that need a k-kiss?!
I already told you!
That's not a reason!
Hii-kun!
You're not supposed to
get that mad at girls!
Shut up! It's because she—
Huh?
How was she? How was Mukaido?
She was so energetic, it startled me.
This feels so weird.
Manaka is Manaka.
Looks like you're back...
The Four from Shishio.
Episode Twenty-One:
The Messenger from the Bottom of the Sea