they're gonna bash the Star Rose into the gate!
You're going to ram the
Star Rose into the gate?!
That's right.
But that's...
Captain Amane, issue the orders!
All fleets, concentrate on
defending the Star Rose!
You can't be serious...!
Commander Simon!
I expect the Godinion to
follow that order as well.
Get moving!
Yes, sir.
Daneel, we shall stand before it.
I'm counting on you, Princess!
"Flowers Falling in Space"
Don't tell me
If they do, Commander Simon will...!
Captain!
The purpose of this mission
is to destroy the gate.
That is why all of us have
gone through such lengths.
Isn't there some other way?
Commander Simon has
chosen the best option
that is within our current capacity.
This is currently our best... option?
Make sure to do your utmost
to protect the Star Rose.
If it's destroyed before
it hits the gate,
the Commander's resolve
will have been for naught!
I will put everything I have
into defending the Star Rose!
Let's go!
Absurd!
Do they mean to crash
that into the gate?
Prince Jiart! Prince Jiart!
Please retreat for now!
An enemy ship is about
to crash into the gate!
Prince Jiart!
You're a nuisance!
Right now, I merely wish to hunt!
I want to hunt you!
Fight! Fight!
They're calling!
My instincts are calling out to me!
Fight! Fight... Fight...
Is it awakening?
Is it bringing out the
beast inside of me?
No! I want to protect them!
To protect everyone...!
Fight... Fight... Fight...
FIGHT!
That's right!
I am sure you must understand... ME!
All fleets, enter an
oblique battle formation!
Protect the Star Rose at all costs!
65% of enemy forces have
concentrated on the AHSMB units.
35% are currently
approaching the Star Rose.
All enemies from Quadrants
D to E are fast upon us!
Suruga, concentrate fire
in the EE-8 direction.
Asagi, you take DD-7!
Tamaki, charge in the EA-5 direction!
Roger!
I'm outta ammo again!
You've already burned
through everything, Stupid?
I'll load her back up in a jiff, Stupid!
Stupid!
Jeez!
The charged particle cannon-!
Bros, please prep a heavy laser!
He called us, "Bros"!
Okay! Hurry back on the double!
We'll be waiting!
Blue 1 has too much stress
on its elbow joints!
I don't mean the units,
but the actual people!
Make them relax!
Roger!
Purple 2 has exceeded the
limit of reparability.
Reduce irrelevant information
and distribute the proshesses.
What did she just say?
She meant, "Distribute the processes."
Boss, you aren't drunk, are you?
Nah, she's just been talking non-stop.
When this is over, I'm gonna drink
till I drop, so pick up the tab!
You can have a whole keg!
And here it's completely over-heated...
How come it's still
able to move like that?
The amazing feats
accomplished by an AHSMB unit
unit when at its limits!
Are you going to start
reciting them all?
Prey! I must defeat my prey!
Fear? I am afraid...?
I see... Fascinating!
The way I am moving, it feels like
I’ve become one with Red 5.
No, am I the one being moved?
It's moving me to fight...
To protect itself...
No! I'M the one out here fighting!
Fight!
FIGHT!
Red 5, that is enough! Red 5?
Your body can't handle any more combat!
The captain...
Don't run away!
No, I'm not!
I've got to go back!
Fight! Fight... Fight...
I can't!
Fight! Fight...! Fight...!
I CAN'T!
FIGHT!
It hurts! I can't breathe!
My body won't move!
Despite all of that, I
still want to fight...
...until my life burns out!
Red 5! Red 5, come in!
Red 5!
Izuru... Is something going on?
Tamaki, Suruga, hurry
back to the battlefield!
Requesting emergency support fire!
Kei, please bring Izuru back!
Huh?
If this keeps up, he's going
to keep fighting even
after the Star Rose hits the gate!
And at this rate, he'll...
Please go.
You really are his big brother, Asagi.
Suruga, please cover Kei.
Sure thing!
Ya gotta wait to get a good shot,
but if all you do is wait, you'll
never hit your prey, huh?
That's the ultimate truth.
And me? What about me?
Tamaki, please offer
the Star Rose backup!
Okey-dokey!
Guys, please handle things here!
Miss, go!
Be sure to win him over!
She's supposed to be fighting the enemy.
You can do it, Blue No.1!
He's Blue 1.
What?!
Did you finish restocking your supplies?
I'm here because I'm done!
Hey! Are you trying to kill me?!
You're in my way!
Don't stand in front of me!
How do you get off throwing your
weight around after a late entry?!
Shut up and follow me!
Reining in a bucking bronco isn't easy!
Red 5!
Izuru, can't you hear me?
Izuru!
Someone's calling for me...?
Fight! Fight...! Fight...!
I...
...will fight!
Izuru!
Come back! You don't have to fight.
Come back to us alive.
Everyone is waiting for you!
We're waiting for you to
come back to us alive!
Shut up!
Listen to me!
Off my back! Listen to me!
This isn't like you, Izuru!
Weren't you going to become a hero?
Weren't you going to
become a hero with us?!
A hero...?
Hey, you'd better listen to her!
Kei is doing her best to
talk some sense into you,
even though she hates talking!
Stoopy-poopy-doopy head!
You've got way too determined of a
look on your face for our derpy Izuru!
A combo-jab...?
You're making us want to jab at you!
And here we kept telling you
not to come out and fight!
Space case! Nincompoop!
You're not only short on ammo,
but you're also missing a pair of balls!
You're horrible.
You're the one who's horrible!
That manga you draw is horrible, too!
You really are a failure!
Could you quit hitting me
with the three-combo jabs?
Izuru...! You came back!
Thank goodness!
Don't let your AHSMB
take over you again.
You see, humans are more about
worldly desires than instinct!
Thank you, guys!
Red 5, retreat!
Roger!
I won't let you escape!
Forget it! I am not yet satisfied!
Izuru!
Wherever you go, I shall
follow in pursuit!
That's right!
That's enough! Stop fighting already!
Move it! Do not interfere!
Kei!
Miss!
Purple 2 has taken damage!
Stop it!
Purple 2's damage reading is at 25%!
There are no irregularities in
the pilot's vitality readings.
Where's Star Rose?
Remaining distance to the gate: 400.
He's almost there...
Kei!
Kei, hang in there!
Damn it!
What the hell are you guys doing?!
Hurry over to Red 5 and Purple 2!
Ange! Chandra...!
Please go!
I wasn't able to save
my friends, but you...
Quit spacin' out!
Go crush that Wulgaru bastard
named Desert, Gelato,
Tomato, Potato or whatever!
Dang! None of those were right.
You've got it!
I'm off!
Wait! Hey, wait up!
Izuru!
Guys!
We're pulling back!
Hurry!
Kei, are you all right?
You all came...!
Kei, I wanna eat your
cake again sometime!
Really?
Well...
Guys, head on back-
Look after Kei!
At this rate, he's going
to take everyone down.
But I don't want to die...
I don't want to die here.
Survive...
I will survive!
But I'm not surviving
just for my own sake.
There are those whom I want to protect!
I'm not fighting because
I want to fight.
I'm doing it to protect
those who are dear to me!
And because...
I want to become a hero!
That's what it boils down to?!
What is that?
What's going on?
What does that imply?
Does it mean that Red 5
has taken over the pilot?
No! It's probably the exact opposite.
Izuru has truly mastered Red 5!
This is the JURIA-System's
ultimate form.
Is that its true awakening?
That's right.
It transformed!
You mean its "frame changed".
Marvelous! I shall respond in suit!
Remaining distance to the gate: 100!
Withdraw, Team Rabbits!
All armies, retreat!
Pull back, Kei, Tamaki and Suruga!
What about Izuru?
He will survive.
That's how the JURIA-System
works, right?
Lady Teoria, please hurry!
Lady Teoria...?
I want you to go back.
I will see this through to the end!
Then so shall I.
I swear that we will stop you!
One minute until collision.
Izuru, hurry! Please!
Commander Simon...
Dad...
Red 5, retreat!
Red 5!
Izuru, come back!
What's keeping you?
It's about to ram into the gate!
Izuru!
Commander Simon, please abandon ship!
Now that it has come to this...!
Legatus Dolgana, please retreat!
There is no turning back!
Please wait here!
Daneel!
Lemme handle these pests!
Bite the dust, ya nasty ground beetles!
I'm not done yet!
All armies, retreat! Pull back
before the gate implodes!
Don't pursue the
retreating enemy fleets!
To live and die in accordance
to one's instincts...
In a sense, that is the ultimate way
for any creature to live its life.
May you fare well, Princess Teoria.
Ten seconds until collision!
Stupid!
Izuru!
Come back!
Stupid!
What's keepin' ya?!
Star Rose Galaxy Rest Area
Izuru!
The gate is starting to collapse.
The operation was a success.
This is the moment I
have been waiting for!
I'm not finished yet!
The time to hunt you down is now!
I will survive and return to my friends!
We can still achieve heights
far greater than this!
They destroyed our gate?
I am terribly sorry.
At long last, we have found it.
The gate may have closed,
but a new evolutionary
path has opened before us.
There are heat signatures coming
from the direction of the gate!
Confirming their ID codes!
They're Teoria and Daneel's units!
I am sorry.
I had a hard time convincing
him to abandon ship.
Thank you, Princess.
I've failed to die yet again, Juria.
And I have lost everything.
However,
a new hero has been born.
Where is Red 5... Izuru?
I'm not getting any
readings on my monitor!
Guiliano! Siegfried!
Maximize our broad sensor's
output and find him!
Roger!
Maximizing broad sensor output!
Izuru...!
Izuru!
I'm picking something
up in Sector AE-23!
I've confirmed that it's Red 5!
I'm sending you the coordinates!
Izuru!
Officer Izuru!
Izuru...
He pulled through!
Izuru!
Izuru! Izuru!
Izuru...!