What's wrong?
Your eyes.
It's the same color as your eyes.
The way I felt when I saw this...
This feeling...
What is it called?
"Major Gilbert.
I've been in the hospital
for 120 days now.
My strength has almost recovered.
Movement is still a little difficult,
but I can perform my duties.
Please let me return to my post soon."
KINGDOM OF ENCIEL
SOMEWHERE IN THE CAPITAL OF ENCHAINE
Her existence
was hidden from everyone.
However, people who knew about her
said that she was a weapon.
She would fight if you ordered her to.
She just looked like a human.
She was just a tool...
without a heart.
Lt. Colonel Hodgins.
Come this way.
Huh? Oh.
Sorry.
Oh, my.
Violet!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Where is the major?
Where's Major Gilbert?
He's not here.
Where is he?
Did he return home?
How are his injuries?
His injuries were severe.
Is the major...
alive?
He's...
They've given us permission to
discharge you from the hospital.
Lt. Colonel Hodgins came all this way
to pick you up.
Uh, that's right.
Excuse me. Lt. Colonel Hodgins.
Violet. Relax.
I'd forgotten you were a Lt. Colonel.
I apologize.
It's okay.
Sit down.
Anyways. So, you do remember me?
We've met twice. Once during training
and the night before the battle.
Yeah. You're right.
What were you doing?
I was writing a report to Major Gilbert.
They said that writing words
would be good for my recovery.
Is the major well?
Don't worry, Violet.
He asked me to come here.
So, that means he's fine.
The doctor told me that we won the war.
What post is he assigned to now?
When shall I join him?
Get changed first. I'll have them
send the car in the meantime.
These finally arrived.
They're your belongings.
Looks like they mistakenly delivered it
to an army base far away.
The brooch.
The emerald brooch.
This is everything from the garrison
and the place where they found you.
I have to go look for it if it's not here.
Violet!
It was a gift.
The major gave it to me!
I understand.
I'll look for it.
I promise.
-But...
-You must...
come with me.
These are his orders.
Orders?
I understand.
When will I receive the next order
from the major?
I'm limited to only performing certain
duties because of my current condition.
Violet. Congratulations
on getting discharged.
I didn't know what you'd like, so,
I bought three. What do you think?
I don't need them.
No. You have to choose one.
Pretend that the world is about to end.
Okay. Three, two...
Then... the puppy.
Here.
Why did you choose the puppy?
The major's brother once told me,
"You're Gilbert's dog."
It's going to be a long journey.
The train tracks around here
were damaged during the bombing
and aren't usable anymore.
Have you ever been to Leiden before?
No.
Violet.
Live...
and be free.
From the bottom of my heart.
There you are.
Lt. Colonel.
There it is. The port of Leiden.
LEIDEN, THE CAPITAL OF
LEIDENSCHAFTLICH
Gilbert was thinking about
your future after the war.
He said he wanted to leave you
with the Evergarden household,
his most trusted relatives.
I contacted them,
and the couple said they'd be happy
to take you in.
Welcome.
Let's go, Violet.
This is the lady of the
Evergarden household.
Say your greetings.
A bow would suffice.
Doesn't it take around three days
from Enchaine now?
Yes. Normally, I'd be able
to return in one day.
But the war has been going on
for four years.
It's going to take some more time
to restore everything.
Violet.
Have some tea.
Oh! Sorry. Don't force yourself.
Oh, no! You'll get burned.
It's not a problem. I can't feel heat.
But your bandages...
Quick, we have to cool them down.
-Oliver, bring some ice!
-Yes, madam.
These arms are made of adamant silver.
They're a bit bulky, but they're sturdy.
I'm not accustomed to them yet.
I should be able to adjust soon.
Can you come this way for a minute?
I used these when I was young.
Very nice. Try them on.
Yeah. They look good on you.
Really!
Well, I'm going to get going now.
I have to get back to the office.
Oh.
Violet.
Listen to Tiffany, okay?
It's okay.
Don't worry about me.
Think of me as your real mother.
Tell me anything. Okay?
I...
don't have parents, so,
I don't need any replacements.
Don't say that.
I had a son,
but he was killed in the war.
I can't become a replacement
for your lost child.
Violet. Gilbert's wish
is for you to happily live here.
So, do you understand?
The major.
The major. Why is he leaving me here?
Is it because I lost my arms,
and lost my value as a weapon?
If I just trained a little,
I could still fight!
Violet. The war is over.
I'm the major's tool.
But if he doesn't need me anymore,
then I should be thrown away.
Throw me away.
Throw me away somewhere.
Lt. Colonel Hodgins.
Oh, I forgot to tell you.
I left the army.
I'm not a Lt. Colonel anymore
Then what should I call you?
Call me "President."
This is my company.
I bought an old house
and renovated it a bit.
The first floor is the reception.
Sir. Please write the receiver's
and sender's address on this form.
Please allow three days for delivery.
The second floor houses the office
and the writing department.
Writing?
Yeah.
This department writes letters
at the requests of our clients.
There are still many people
who don't know how to write.
I didn't know how to write either
until the major taught me how.
I see.
I was thinking about starting
a business once the war ended.
The government's postal service
doesn't address the civilian's needs,
so, I thought it would be
a good opportunity.
I have an order for you.
Violet Evergarden.
Gilbert left you with me.
So, I'm giving you orders instead.
You're still useful.
You can work. Here.
Benedict.
What's up, President?
You're supposed to say
"How can I help you, President?"
So, what's up?
-What's up with you?
-You did that on purpose!
This is Benedict. He's a postman.
He's an old friend
from before I started this company.
Benedict, this is Violet.
She's going to work here
as a postman, starting today.
She's just a kid.
She's highly capable
of performing her duties.
I'm going to go to the bank.
Teach her what she needs to know, got it?
Put your stuff here.
Yes, sir.
Your uniform. Change.
Hey, you! H... Hold on!
Oh, it's too big.
It's not a problem.
Wouldn't it be better to take those off?
Is it hard to sort the mail?
No, it's not a big problem.
Sort them just like it says here.
Put them in those shelves.
There's a huge pile of mail,
but no need to rush.
The break room is on the second floor.
Yes, sir.
Bye.
I've almost completed my duties.
Were you working the whole time?
Without taking a break?
I'm used to long hours.
Okay, do you want to try
delivering the mail?
Delivering?
You deliver the letter
to the address that's written on it.
I'm going home now.
See you tomorrow.
"We will discuss financing
after reviewing your performance." Right.
It looks like some companies
do nighttime deliveries, too.
We can't handle that.
Violet!
What are you doing?
I'm delivering the mail.
Uh, mail delivery was meant for tomorrow.
And make sure to take breaks during work.
-You just got released from the hospital.
-It's not a problem.
Yes. It is a problem.
Violet. Go ahead and eat.
I'm going to eat.
I'll take you to the office
once you're done.
We only have space in the attic,
but you can sleep there.
Uh, the Evergarden household
has agreed to take you in...
until you become an adult.
But it looks like leaving you
at the mansion...
It looks like there was a problem.
Hey, you!
I was trying to put it nicely!
How was I supposed to know?
See you tomorrow.
I'll take you home.
What was the last order
you received from Gilbert?
He said "Run away and live freely."
And, I...
You've been in the army
ever since you were a child.
You've spent your life
fulfilling your duties.
You're going to learn a lot of things.
But it might be easier to keep living
if you didn't learn them,
if you didn't know them.
You don't realize
that your body is on fire
and burning up
because of the things you did.
I'm not burning.
Yes, you are.
I'm not. You don't make sense.
No.
You are burning.
I saw you like that, but left you alone.
That's why when Gilbert
left you with me,
I thought this was my chance.
You'll understand one day.
And then you'll realize for the first time
that you have many burns.
Ms. Doll?
No, I'm Violet.
Uh, Miss Violet.
I want to ask you
to write something for me.
Write something?
Yeah. I don't know how to write.
Can you write a letter for me?
What should I write?
Do you want to talk about it here?
Is there a problem?
Uh, well...
I heard that my childhood friend
in the countryside
received a marriage offer
from another man. So...
I want you to tell her!
"You were the first person
who was kind to me.
You were everything to me.
I would have done anything for you."
Go!
"I want to know what you're feeling.
I want to understand
what's in your heart.
Even though we're apart now...
I...
love you."
How is that?
Yes.
"I love you."
Please go to reception on the first floor
for the delivery process.
Sir.
Thank you for using
the Auto Memory Doll Service.
And? Who are you?
How did you know?
Huh?
How did you know
that the man just now wanted to say
"I love you"?
You want to work as an Auto Memory Doll?
Yes. It's still hard for me to hold a pen.
But I can operate a typewriter.
No, that's not what I mean.
I wanted to ask why
you want to do this work.
I want to know!
"I love you."
I want to know what it means!
The major said those words to me
after he gave me my last orders.
That was the first time
I heard those words from the major.
I can't understand...
what that means.
Normally,
people become Auto Memory Dolls
because they understand that.
But...
It's okay.
She had always just followed
Gilbert's orders in the past.
That was the first time
she asserted her own will.
Everyone said she didn't have a heart
and that she was a tool,
but she said, "I want to know
what 'I love you' means."
No way! There's no way
I'm going to let you die!
Stop!
Stop already!
Live.
Violet.
Live, and...
be free.
From the bottom of my heart...
I love you.
Subtitle translation by
Hoday Stearns