Chise...
Chise!
We show no mercy to those who
defile this knoll, Ainsworth.
Let go.
What do you intend to do in that
vile state, you half-made monster?
Let me go.
You call yourself a mage, but you're now far
removed from both us and the humans.
Are you going to become
a freak of obsession?
You fool!
Pitiful child.
My queen...
You've come alone?
This is a branch.
Surrogate eyes,
surrogate ears, surrogate mouth.
Losing a branch doesn't hurt a tree.
Elias, pitiful child...
You say you don't want to be pitied,
but forgive me for pitying you regardless.
She has left you, hasn't she?
Chise... Why?
You were the one who said you'd stay
with me until I was done with you.
You're very much human, but
the way you love is like us.
You shouldn't fight with your spouse,
though at times it may be necessary.
My king, you too?
If you're going to chase after her,
we'll both help you, my beloved child.
My.
It takes only an instant for a human to die.
Titania's brief lovers died the moment
she took her eyes off of them.
So...
When you next catch her,
you must keep her from going
outside, so that she won't escape.
It will be all right. We'll find her
and bring her back to you.
So don't you worry.
Just stay here.
And we'll all live in the
land of endless youth.
No...
Not that.
She thinks the way I do.
You were no different.
It can't be this way.
But that's the way we are.
It's part of who you are, too.
You can't be the only one
who changes the way you love.
Still,
in order to live with her...
If Chise will touch me again...
I have to rethink my ways.
Ruth, do you know where Chise is?
She's rejecting me.
I can't get close to her.
Oh, dear.
Why do you think I bothered
to extend my branches, boys?
The branches of my body
extend to the goddess Morrigan.
They sprout in all places.
You may not like it, but you're
still my beloved children.
To atone for my inability to keep from
pitying you, I shall give you my assistance.
Wrap your thorns around my branches.
Let's bring your mate home.
Alice?
I just got the shivers.
Damn it!
That queen really doesn't
know how to ask for a favor.
Deposit the massage fee here, please.
Thank you.
Marielle.
Phyllis?
Why...
What did you tell those two?
H-How do you know?
Have you forgotten our code?
We must never harm people.
That we must know the ways of
hurting them, in order that we don't.
How much of a saint do you have to be?!
Quit worrying about some strangers
and care more for yourself!
Just give up on me.
I'll leave the coven, too.
You'll be better off without
a troublemaker like me.
You're still a child if you think
you're the only one who is lonely.
Do what needs to be done.
If you were the one who created the
opportunity, it's your duty to help them.
What do you mean by...
Oh, hell!
It hurts...
Help me.
It's that lowly gravedigger's brat.
I heard he talks to the dead.
He's a witch.
He's tainted. Don't go near him.
I'm scared.
I heard that he uses some twisted sorcery.
He reeks. Stay away.
Don't look.
Help me.
Is someone there?
Are you awake?
I'm impressed.
How did you...
I'm Joseph.
And you?
Cartaphilus.
Cartaphilus?
It hurts.
Help me.
Help me,
please.
Me?
Sure.
You can count on me!
Mom!
Welcome home.
I'm home!
I'll help you.
I will.
Only me.
You gravedigger's brat.
Stand up.
You're a witch's child, aren't you?
Joseph...
When you get better,
let's leave this stupid
village and travel together.
And let's live happily together.
Okay?
When you're better.
Hurry.
Get better soon.
Why?!
Why?
Why do you neither get better nor worse?!
I've tried everything!
I, we...
When are we going to...
I wanted to help you.
No one else has ever asked a foul
gravedigger like me to help them.
Joseph...
That's why I...
I just want to live a good life.
Oh, I know.
How did I not notice something so simple?
You don't die.
You don't die, no matter what.
We just have to become one.
Cartaphilus, let's be saved together.
Together.
It hurts...
Joseph...
It hurts!
This person's alive, even in that state?
It hurts. Help me.
Hey, let's go.
It hurts.
Are you all right? Can you walk?
Help me.
Here, take my hand.
Now I can walk properly.
Thanks.
Joseph...
Who is that?
Your curse can't be undone.
It's an old, powerful curse.
Who set it on you?
I don't know.
I don't remember anymore.
Joseph...
Who are you?
What do you want?
Why do you say my name?
Who are you?
It hurts.
Someone help me.
It's so cold.
Cartaphilus? Who was that, again?
Wasn't that the one who threw a rock
at the Son of God and got cursed for it?
Say what?
Cartaphilus...
That's the reason I...
We...
We just want to be saved.
When will it be over?
How long is it going to hurt?
How long do we have to live in pain?
No.
Help.
Somebody!
You saw me?
My...
My past?
I'd forgotten it.
It hurts.
His memories flow into me
because we're connected.
It hurts!
You're...
Why do you look at me like that?
Stop it!
All I need is your arm.
Found you.
Cartaphilus.
Don't call me by that name!
My queen, I trust this ends
your whimsical matters.
Interfering again...
Let's return!
Come on, Chise, let's go home.
It's dangerous here.
You all ought to see what it's like
to decay for two thousand years,
completely unable to die!
What exactly is going on here?
Are you all right?
This guy showed up out of nowhere
and said you're in danger.
Wait, what did you do to your eye?
Why?
This happens whenever it's about to work.
This was the best it's gone
in decades! Centuries!
Why?
Why?!
Now, Chise, let's go home.
Why me?
Why do I have to live through this?!
What did I do to deserve this?!
What the hell is this?
The restless dead.
As many as he's stitched together.
It hurts.
It hurts!
How long do I have to suffer for
a crime I don't even remember?
Shit, how many of them are there?
There's so many.
They won't all fit in Hell.
Help... me...
He's trying to escape
through another channel.
Help me.
Chise?
Sorry, there's something I need to do.
My queen!
I've been rejected again.
Help me!
Come on, get a grip!
Go after her!
But...
Or are you okay with losing her
when she's out of your reach?
Hey, girl, give me some of your magic.
I smell the scent of flames from your soul.
It smells delicious.
I wouldn't mind getting you
across the river in return.
I can't catch up.
Hey, watch where you're going!
Marielle-san.
What are you doing?
You can't come into an alleyway like this.
I was about to come...
You've gotten even worse than before.
Sorry, but I need to go after him.
Oh, all right.
This is my way of apologizing.
A-A bull?
Hang on tight.
Elias, are you there?
Yeah.
I'm really angry at you, still.
Sorry.
I want you to make up for it.
You, too, Ruth.
I want you to help with something.
But for that, I need you to keep a promise.
A promise?
The girl confronts Joseph.
Will she bring an end to the unending suffering
in the city of London, where it all began?
So let's end it.