Do I smell... miso soup?
Good morning.
What?
I wasn't told we were
going to be roommates!
We don't have enough rooms, you see.
But...
She agreed.
It was an order.
Don't you get it, Atsushi-kun?
Get what?
Without any kin,
she is as alone as can be.
Besides, the Port Mafia may
send assassins after her.
That's true.
You should protect her.
Okay, I'll do my best!
If you have the time to mess with Atsushi,
write up the report about your
capture by the Port Mafia!
Atsushi-kun...
Yes?
Write the report for me.
What?
It'll be about the person who
placed a bounty on your head.
You found out who?
According to the Port Mafia's
communication records,
the bounty was funded by
the leader of The Guild,
a North American organization of the gifted.
The Guild is considered an urban legend.
Their agents are said to hold
key positions in finance,
politics, and the military.
They are a secret society who
use their limitless funds
and abilities to plot countless schemes.
Why would such a group want Atsushi?
You need to come see this!
It seems we've been preempted.
Episode 12
Borne Back Ceaselessly into the Past
I'm glad to finally meet you,
President Fukuna...
Fukuda?
Fukuzawa.
That's right!
By the way, was it a bad move to
park the chopper on the road?
You have come a long way
from a foreign land.
So, what do you wish to discuss?
Well, this is a rare design.
And I consider myself something
of an expert in porcelain.
What brand is this?
Royal Blanc?
Or is it perhaps El Zelga?
It's from Shimomura China and
Ceramics, next door.
Oh, my apologies.
Call me Francis, old sport.
I lead an organization called
The Guild in North America.
In addition, I personally own
three conglomerates, five hotels,
an airline, a railway company, and—
Mr. Francis.
I have received reports that
you used a bounty
to encourage the Port Mafia to attack us.
Is this true?
Yes, that was my mistake.
I had no idea that this country's
criminal organization
would be so incompetent.
To make amends, I come bearing
a profitable business deal.
This company isn't so bad.
The neighborhood is aesthetically
pleasing, as well.
So...
I'd like to buy this company.
Don't get me wrong.
I am quite capable of
buying all the properties
visible from here along with your company.
I have no interest in this
building or your employees.
I am only interested in one thing.
You don't mean...
Yes, I do.
Hand over your Gifted Business Permit.
For a group of gifted individuals
to legally open a business,
they need a permit issued by the
Ministry of Internal Affairs'
gifted special operations division.
Those blockheads are about the only
ones you can't buy with money.
After all, we are a secret society
with no official existence.
In order to keep peace with the Ministry
and do what we need to do to find
what we're looking for in this city,
the permit is—
I refuse.
What, this isn't enough?
Then I'll add this.
It's a limited edition model,
made to order with diamonds.
Just as lives cannot be bought with money,
nothing is worth giving up our permit.
The permit is the beating
heart of this Agency.
It embodies the hope of
the special ops division,
as well as the spirit of Natsume-sensei,
who worked tirelessly to
obtain us the permit.
It is not meant to easily fall into
the hands of the filthy rich,
who have dollar bills for brains.
So you're saying there are things
you can't buy with money?
That's the mantra of the poor.
Your bravado is pointless if all
of your employees disappear
and your agency ceases to function.
It'll be too late to change your mind then.
I'll take your advice to heart.
I suggest you leave.
I'll be back.
Our visitors are leaving.
Okay!
I'll see you out!
I'll post a message
in the morning newspaper.
Take a good look at it, old sport.
I always get what I want.
Nice hat.
Oh, really?
Thank you.
Well?
Does it look good on me?
You'd look better in burlap.
What was that for?
Hmph.
First, there was one.
The Following
Morning
Hey, did you see the morning news?!
It's on the TV, too.
Please see for yourself.
A seven-story building
has vanished overnight.
According to one source,
the building housed a front
company for the Port Mafia.
It was allegedly used as
an office by their agents.
So this is the message...
Kenji-kun hasn't been back to
the dorm since seeing them off.
So they'll annihilate
anyone who opposes them,
be they the Port Mafia or the Agency.
Tanizaki, from now on, you're
prohibited from working alone!
Look for Kenji with Atsushi!
Dazai, you're with me!
We need to meet with the president.
We don't know what kind of
gifts they possess.
If you make contact with the enemy,
don't engage them. Run!
Okay.
Pedestrian
Support System
Naomi, you should go back to the Agency.
It's too dangerous.
They can make entire buildings disappear.
Elise-chan?
It doesn't matter where I am.
Please come out, hey.
Right, Atsushi-san?
W-Well, sure.
Atsushi-kun!
Elise-chan, please.
Unlike you, my sister isn't gifted!
She'll hold us back.
Elise-chan?
How dare you!
You said you'd do anything I said!
Where are you?
That was yesterday when you were forcing me to—
Nothing.
Pedestrian Support System
Anyway, it's too dangerous, so go back!
Oh, really?
If you'd like, I can help
you remember your pleasure—
Naomi?
N-No way...
Naomi?!
Where are you?
Where did you go, Naomi?!
Is it an enemy attack?!
Impossible.
I didn't sense anything off.
Naomi!
Be careful, Tanizaki-san!
Where are you, Elise-chan?
Well, I'm in trouble now...
Give Naomi back!
Found you!
Wait!
Let's play.
Welcome, everyone, to Anne's Chamber.
Oh, this is embarrassing.
So many people are looking right at me.
I'm not very good at talking to strangers.
But that won't do.
I have to give a proper explanation,
or everyone will be so lost.
After all, you were all brought
unawares to this strange place.
If I were you,
my heart would be pounding—
Where's Naomi?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I should explain that first.
Your agents are over there.
Kenji-kun!
Naomi!
Damn it!
It won't open without the key.
That one opens, though.
They're all frozen.
Has time come to a stop?
My name is Lucy.
This is a dimension
I created with my ability.
But worry not.
You can leave whenever you want,
through that white door.
That is, if you don't want
your colleagues back.
What do you want?
That's easy.
I just want you to play
with Anne in this chamber.
Come, Anne.
Guild Apprentice:
Lucy M
Ability:
Anne of
Abyssal Red
Anne loves to play.
She's a bit needy, but she's quite cute.
But if you leave through that door,
you'll forget everything
that happened in this room.
Do you get it, now?
Oh, my..
Only three of you are left?
It's not safe here.
You should run.
I'm looking for a girl.
She's lovely, just like an angel.
Have you see her?
No, I'm sorry to say.
I see.
Her name is Elise-chan.
Anyway, ever since we've been separated,
I've been beside myself.
She may be behind that door.
If that's the case,
I'll regret running away
for the rest of my life.
So I'll stay, too.
Okay.
The rules are simple.
Play tag with my lovely Anne.
If she tags you, you lose.
If you can open the door using that key
before she catches you, you win.
I'll return the hostages.
Well?
Who's in?
Can two play at once?
Of course.
It's more fun if we play all together.
We can win if we use Tanizaki-san's
Light Snow ability to project illusions.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Ready, set...
Go!
She's fast!
Caught...
the first one!
Tanizaki-san!
We've made yet another friend.
What a great day, Anne.
What? What's that?
You want more?
Well, then...
Wow, amazing!
I want to see more.
What a strong, useful ability...
I'm sure you were valued highly
from the moment you were born.
I heard you're an orphan.
I grew up in an orphanage, too.
It was a very cold place.
After using ice-cold rags
to clean the whole day,
my fingers would ache for days.
Given my ability,
everyone thought I was a freak.
I heard the Agency was desperate
to find you when you were taken.
How wonderful.
It must be because you have a great ability.
I...
The Guild took me in because they
saw potential in my ability, too.
But there is no room for error in The Guild.
If I fail in this mission,
I will be tossed aside
like a used napkin.
Then I'll be all alone again.
Hey.
Why does it have to be you?
Why can't it be me?
It's so unfair.
You should know how I feel, too!
You should stay in this room forever!
The only way out is to put
the key in that door.
Okay!
I win!
Watch out, boy!
What?
Be careful. The key is important.
I thought I'd win if I opened
the door with the key!
That's right. If you could open it.
I have no idea how to use
a key like this, myself.
So there was no way to
win in the first place.
The real game starts now.
You seem to be a genius at tag,
but I wonder how long your
soul will last like this?
There's no way to counter this.
I'll be caught eventually.
I can't hope to turn the tide now.
I have no choice but to hope that
Dazai-san and the others will come!
You're going to run away,
leaving your friends behind?
Even if he were in this situation,
Dazai-san'd think of something!
But I can't!
No, boy.
Your enemy lies that way.
I wouldn't advise running away
in this particular case.
Er, that is,
if you'd trust the words of your
local neighborhood physician.
If you were to believe her words,
you'll forget everything once
you leave through that door.
You'll remember neither
the enemy's subterfuge,
nor your colleagues in danger.
And the enemy will continue
to press her attack.
I'll teach you something of use.
In game theory,
the optimal strategy is to launch
a total counteroffensive on an
enemy who has attacked you.
Crush the enemy.
But how?
An arrogant enemy who feels invincible
is the most vulnerable opponent of all.
And did I hear right, that
the ones beyond that door
are the very ones who desperately
tried to save you when you were taken?
That's right.
They all saved me.
Are you done with the chit-chat?
Is your motivation back?
It's my turn, then.
That's right.
That is your optimal solution.
It wouldn't be fun any other way.
But...
It's already over.
Another one!
Of course! There are two of you.
Shit!
All right, that's that.
So, what will you do, mister?
Thanks to you,
the tiger didn't get away.
So I could let you go as a
sign of my appreciation.
Or maybe I want to see your expression
when Anne catches you.
Do you want to try me?
What? What's going on?
My legs are trembling
so much, I can't move.
Is this pure malice?
But why can't Anne move, either?
It won't work.
You've already lost.
Look at the door.
What?!
But I know I shut the door.
Why?
You've made one mistake.
This fight was two against
one from the very start!
The moment the door opened,
Tanizaki-san used his Light Snow
ability to create a false door.
Impossible.
And you were able to resist the force
sucking you into the room with
your arms and legs alone?
You misunderstand me.
I am not strong, and I'm not popular.
Rather, I've led a cursed life.
That's why I understand your jealousy
and hatred of others all too well.
I don't really want you
to fail this mission!
I don't want you to lose the place
where you can feel you belong!
But because I'm weak and inexperienced,
I can think of no other way!
What?
This is...
I tied a ribbon to you.
Release your ability and let everyone go!
Or I'll drag you into the room.
Without a key, the door won't open.
That means if you're imprisoned inside,
no one can ever open that door.
If that happens, you won't
be able to return to reality
even if you release your ability.
Am I wrong?
That's...
Our abilities aren't tools of convenience
made to control everyone else.
I know that better than most.
Do you want to be trapped in the dimension
of your own making until you die—
No, even after you die?
I... I can't afford to fail!
I'm going to let go.
You only have that split second
before the door closes to decide.
No, wait!
Um, hey...
If I...
If I can do anything for you...
Um!
Oh, Elise-chan!
Are you okay?!
Where've you been!
I was so worried!
You just up and vanished...
I thought Rintarou would worry
if I suddenly disappeared.
I wanted to make Rintarou cry.
That's so mean, Elise-chan!
But I forgive you, because you're so cute!
Kyouka-chan?
You came to get me?
I was worried.
Thank you.
We'll be taking our leave now.
Thank you for your advice earlier.
So you're a doctor?
Ex-doctor.
Right now, I'm just a middle-aged man
keeping a small group of people in line.
Boy...
A logical, optimal solution exists
in any wartime situation,
no matter how difficult the challenge.
You must not forget that,
especially in times of confusion
when you might feel
inclined to recklessness.
Okay.
Goodbye, then.
There is a way, even in difficult times...
What's wrong, Kyouka-chan?
Kyouka-chan?
Kyouka-chan!
I had a good time.
I wanted to return to my younger days
and use my ability to mow down
my enemies left and right.
You're too old for that!
That's so mean.
I may not look like much, but...
So this is a Guild assassin?
Yes, sir.
The Agency and The Guild...
It seems we are in a challenging
wartime situation, ourselves.
Port Mafia Leader:
Mori Ougai
We need an optimal solution.
The Agency and The Guild...
Ability:
Vita Sexualis
Those who oppose us will be crushed,
and annihilated.
To Be Continued