The Japanese National High School Volleyball Tournament
Miyagi Qualifiers First Preliminaries
No Shoes
Allowed
The Japanese National High School
Volleyball Tournament Program
The Japanese National High
School Volleyball Tournament
Can I get a copy?
Yes.
Go, go, Tebaichi!
Push it, push it, Tebaichi!
That's them. You know, Karasuno.
Karasuno?
They're the ones that played a full set
with Aoba Johsai at the Inter-High prelims
and actually almost beat them.
Whoa, seriously?
Apparently, Kitagawa Daiichi's
King of the Court is on that team.
When does the judging start?
Apparently Chidoriyama Junior High's
Nishinoya is also there, too.
Probably the next one, since we
don't have a match this round.
The guy who was called the best
libero when we were in junior high?
Yeah. But other than the libero,
I think there was one other guy who
kept receiving Oikawa's serves.
I think it's their captain.
But the members of Karasuno don't
really seem that tall, do they?
I'm pretty sure one of them is close to 190 cm,
though I don't think he stood out
much during the Inter-High prelims.
Not to mention, their two
lefts are pretty scary.
They look like power spikers.
And most importantly...
Their manager's cute.
I'm sorry that you have to cheer
from up above, Hitoka-chan.
Or rather, she's hot. Or rather, she's sexy!
Also, there's that one guy...
The tiny middle blocker that
hits those crazy quicks...
Karasuno's #10!
Whoa, what the heck?
He looks like he's skin and bones!
H-Hinata, are you okay?
Yep, I'm fine.
I threw up on the way here, so I feel better.
Of course you'd feel sick after eating
all those pork bowls for breakfast.
It's normal to eat pork cutlets on game days!
And by "normal," you mean...
You dumbass! Hinata, you stupid dumbass!
Kageyama's insult vocabulary
is limited to "dumbass."
I-I'll do my best to widen my vocabulary!
I have that one thing you can drink!
I-I feel like I'm going to puke, too,
after remembering Hinata puking...
Oh, thanks!
Huh?
Go to the bathroom, already!
M-My nerves are getting to me, too...
I thought you were busy concentrating,
but you were actually trying not to puke?!
Shoyo, is this seriously the second
time you threw up on the bus?
You were able to actually hold
it in until the bus stopped,
instead of puking on someone's crotch.
You've really grown up, Hinata.
Is that really the team
that almost beat Seijoh?
Shoyo!
Haikyu!!
Karasuno
Tebaichi
Ohgi Minami
Episode 12: "Let the Games Begin!"
Bathroom, bathroom, bathroom, bathroom!
The time to pee has come!
Bathroom, bathroom...
Ow. Oh, I'm sorry...
The hell are you looking?!
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
He's from...
Ohgi Minami?
That's the team we're playing first.
They won their first match already.
Hm? Oh, you're just a junior high kid.
Huh?
Hey, sorry for yelling at you.
You here to cheer your big
brother on, or something?
My little brother loves that T-shirt, too.
I... I'm first-year at Karasuno
High School, Hinata Shoyo.
We're going to win, and go to nationals!
What? Karasuno?
Don't make going to nationals sound so easy.
Huh? But I mean it.
Shut up, you little—
I'm gonna beat everyone, and go to Tokyo.
Even if you were somehow
lucky enough to keep winning,
everyone just gets crushed
by Shiratorizawa in the end.
Huh?
Let's at least make some good memories.
Higashida
The previous match is over.
Let's go!
Yeah!
Fly
Shut up, morons.
Looks like Ohgi Minami's
a team full of punks.
Did that really come out of your mouth?
Stop making that face.
Nice kill!
Your shaved head is seriously lame.
Seriously, like seriously, seriously...
I'm going forth. Let us play a good game.
Take this, damn it!
Put Your Heart Into It
Nice kill!
Thank you for that opportunity.
Power at Full Throttle!
Pick Up the Ball and Win!
Nice kill!
Everyone on Karasuno has really
high attack power.
Ohgi Minami         Karasuno
Fly
The spring tournament... Karasuno's battle...
Let's play!
...is about to start!
Go, go, let's go! Let's go, Kaji!
Listen up.
All of their third-years are already gone,
but their power has always
been with their second-years.
They also just won straight
through the first round.
Don't let your guard down!
Make sure you're especially
cautious of their #1 on the left!
Right!
Since the Inter-High prelims ended,
you've taken on unfamiliar challenges
and you haven't been in sync.
On top of that, you've lost
about seventy practice games
against the powerhouse schools from Kanto.
But your new weapons that kept failing at
first are finally starting to take shape.
Please get a win that makes up for
all of the frustration you felt.
There is No Victory Without Effort
One Heart
Right!
All right!
Karasuno, fight!
Yeah...
Yeah!
Oh? So you came to watch the game, too,
Ukai-sensei?
Yeah.
I guess that is your
precious grandson's team.
That's got nothing to do with it!
Ukai? Grandson?
You're from Karasuno, too, right?
What are you doing up here?
Th-There's only one manager
allowed on the bench.
You didn't know that?
Oh.
Ah, there's Sho-chan!
I actually just saw them play the other day,
Oh, yeah!
but they have an intense first-year duo.
Sho-chan? Oh, you mean Hinata.
Karasuno might actually make
it pretty far this year.
There's no match that you can't win,
and there's no match that
you'll win for sure.
You can feel a little off,
nervous, or panic...
No matter how strong the school,
their team members are human.
Even the slightest thing
can trip someone up.
Now... let's see how Karasuno will do today.
Asahi-san, nice serve!
All right!
Yay! That was amazing!
Starting with a no-touch ace.
Not bad.
All right...
Let's go!
Ohgi Minami           Karasuno
He changed it up to a tip.
Daichi-san, nice!
S-So fast! It's like he was waiting for it!
I feel like I can see the spiker's
movements better than before.
Asahi-san!
Ever since the first round,
Ougi Minami hasn't been doing quicks
any time the receives were a bit off.
Left.
Tazawa-san!
All right!
Nice, Tsukishima!
How do I put this...
It seems like everyone is hesitating
less in their movements.
It wasn't like they were just practicing
their new moves at the training camp.
They had plenty of practice against
All right!
powerhouse schools that were
all completely different.
Nice receive!
The power behind their serves and spikes...
the diversity in their
attacks... their defense...
Basically anything high-level...
They've gotten used to it...
Far more than before.
All right!
Damn it...
Nice, Kageyama!
Another service ace!
Thanks!
Now it's a set point.
Ohgi Minami
To think that we ended up against a
team this strong so early on again...
Shiratorizawa!
Shiratorizawa                Ohgi Minami
Ushijima! Ushijima!
Come on! We still have a chance!
Let's get hyped up!
Where's your usual enthusiasm?!
Yeah, that right there!
Bring that enthusiasm!
The captain's voice was all raspy
Let's get one!
because he was trying to talk
over Shiratorizawa's cheers.
It's up! Towada!
Even if I went after it,
I wouldn't be able to reach it.
Even if I could reach it,
there's no guarantee that someone would connect next and be able to score.
Even if it did connect, it'd
only get us one measly point.
There's no point going after it...
Ohgi Minami High School
Hey, don't look so glum!
You guys look even scarier.
You guys were seriously
some problem children,
but if you guys weren't here,
we wouldn't have been
able to have any matches.
So thanks.
You guys have the bodies and sense
for this, so keep doing your best!
All right!
Ohgi Minami         Karasuno
Yay!
Sho-chan, that was awesome!
He jumped sideways!
Damn...
I'm gonna beat everyone, and go to Tokyo.
So he wasn't just trying to
sound tough back there...
He really means that he's
going to try to do that.
With that tiny little body, he's
going to try to defeat Ushiwaka.
All right!
Ohgi Minami
L-Let's keep doing our best!
Winning or losing doesn't matter.
What's more important is
that you guys do your best.
Hey! Damn it!
Don't get all quiet!
C-Captain Akki-kun!
You guys are so tough when
it comes to fighting,
but why is it you get so weak
when it comes to volleyball?
Weak?!
I-It doesn't matter how strong you are.
I'm on the second floor, so I'm not scared!
Why did he even come?
You guys get just a little pushback,
and then you give up.
That's what I mean by weak.
This is your fight, so how you handle
it is up to you guys.
But let me just say this...
Being serious, giving your all,
and doing your best...
None of that's lame!
What the? Scary...
Senpai, did you lose your mind?
Sensei!
Yes?
You know, since we came here to fight each
other on the opposite sides of the net,
I don't think we have any other
option than to win and continue on.
Trying to act tough and worrying
more about how we look
is pretty lame.
Towada...
All right, I'm gonna say it.
What?
We're going to beat Karasuno!
We're gonna get through the prelims!
We're going to fight Shiratorizawa!
All right!
You actually just said that!
Well said, big mouth!
So we're gonna try to beat Shiratorizawa?
Bring it on, then!
We're seriously going to win, guys!
Yeah!
Challenge accepted!
Haikyu!!
Fly
All right!
Karasuno                  Ohgi Minami
Yeah!
Yay!
Nice, Hinata!
He did it again!
That first-year duo really is something.
Yeah.
But the second and third-years are
far beyond my expectations, too.
Right now, Karasuno is
on the brink of revival,
thanks in great part to their passionate
advisor and newfound strength.
But that's all because they
have a sturdy foundation.
Foundation?
Last year, just for a short time,
I came to see a practice at Karasuno.
At the time, they had the
ability and dedication.
However, I felt a lack
a confidence in them.
It's like they were
subconsciously used to losing.
They don't look like that now.
When the current third-years
came to Karasuno,
Monthly Volleyball
it was right around the time where
Karasuno being a powerhouse school
became a thing of the past.
I'm sure the gap between their
expectations and reality was pretty big.
They were probably around
during the worst time.
That's exactly why...
The ones who didn't rot and didn't give up,
and are still here now,
have an unwavering strength.
Daichi-san, nice receive!
All right!
Amazing! So amazing!
Karasuno        Ohgi Minami
Whoa. There's a 10-point difference.
All right, let's keep this up to the end!
Damn it, they're strong.
Yeah!
W-We still have a chance! Keep it up!
One more, Kageyama!
All right!
Kageyama's serves are sharp as hell.
Yeah.
Karasuno              Ohgi Minami
And now we're at match point.
Every single time...
We get cornered on the court,
and I always regret how
much we didn't practice.
One more, Kageyama! Nice serve!
It looks like Karasuno
and Ougi Minami's match
is gonna end faster than I thought,
so let's get ready for the next match.
Yeah. Games sure go fast when
there's such a difference in ability.
It's not over yet! Don't give up!
I might just make it...
Or will I not?
Well, we're still second-years,
so I guess we'll have next year...
And that's why you never
get any stronger, damn it!
Connect and finish it!
Damn it!
Tanaka-san!
It's not over yet!
Give me the last one!
I definitely underestimated him.
I thought it was stupid for him to
think he'd make it to nationals.
I'm...
a fool.
All right!
Yay? Did we win?
We won!
So cool!
All right!
They made it through their first set.
Karasuno            Ohgi Minami
Thank you very much!
Ohgi Minami
Great job! You guys fought until the end!
Yeah.
Just so you know, frustration is the
right thing to be feeling right now.
No matter what the fight is,
when you lose, it's only
natural to be frustrated.
I'd go as far as saying even
guys who don't practice much
probably feel frustrated
when they lose a game.
I think frustration is real for anyone.
But...
Those who forget that frustration
after three days will always be weak.
If you waste time
during your three years in high
school, time will completely fly by.
Don't you dare forget the frustration
you're feeling right now!
W-Well, see ya.
I'll come see you guys next
year, too, so do your best!
Captain!
Th-Thank you very much!
Thanks!
#4! #4!
Nice receive!
This seriously messes with
your depth perception.
I just stood next to him in
the hallway and he was huge!
Well, yeah! He's two meters tall!
That's creepy!
It's a weapon... His height is a weapon...
Tanaka looks good with a banana.
Nishida              Kakugawa
Thank you very much!
I guess we know who we're playing next.
Karasuno
Tebaichi
Ohgi Minami
Nishida
Kakugawa
If we win the next game,
we'll get through the prelims
and continue on to the qualifiers in October.
No Shoes Allowed
We're gonna get through no matter what!
Yeah!
So it really is over just by losing once...
And yet...
That guy is two meters!
Two meters is super huge!
201 centimeters and 162 centimeters, huh...
I'm 163 if you round up!
201 centimeters and 162 centimeters...
There's a 40 centimeter difference.
Listen!
F-Forty centimeters is the
same size as Ketty-chan.
That's not that big!
Is that an attempt to cheer him up?
Tekachu is also 40 centimeters.
Note: Fujikujira sounds like a type of whale.
So is a fujikujira.
F-Fujikujira?
What's that?
It's a kind of shark.
Oh...
You're so smart, Tsukki!
Fly
I... want to combine with that shark.
What?
If I combined with a fujikujira,
I'd be two meters tall...
Hey, what are you talking about?
Are you really scared?
Huh?
Let's go!
All right!
H-He really seemed to want to combine
with that Etmopterus lucifer,
but I wonder if Hinata will be okay...
Oh, yeah...
I'm sure he'll be fine even if
he's like that before a match.
R-Right?!
Well, it's finally about to start.
But they're going up
against someone that big.
No, no. That has nothing to do
with how Karasuno is right now.
Right, Ukai-sensei?
Well, who knows?
Wha...
Fly
High school boys haven't finished growing yet,
and their plays aren't complete.
That's why a match can be decided
just by how tall someone is
or if a team has an amazing ace.
Hurry up, Hinata.
B-But...
R-Right!
Height, by itself, is a weapon in its own right.
Seeing how Karasuno
will deal with it...
Let's go.
Right!
...will definitely be worth watching.
So a fujikujira is a kind of shark, huh?
There are a lot of fish with confusing names.
For example, a kinmedai might sound like it's
related to sea bream, but it's a tropical fish.
You really know a lot about fish, Tsukki.
Shut up, Yamaguchi.
Sorry, Tsukki!
Episode 13: "A Simple and Pure Strength"
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"A Simple and Pure Strength."