It was a story of two queens.
It was a story of death and rebirth.
It was the sad tale about these
strange flags and the
heroes involved with them.
There was once a peaceful country that
two beautiful princesses ruled.
But the country was
plunged into darkness by demons.
The goddess in heaven was
tainted by the darkness,
and she entrusted her power
to a boy who was soon to die.
She altered his appearance,
changing him into a single flag.
It was the Royal Flag that was to
change the fate of the kingdom.
The light which would
drive away the darkness.
To drive away the despair
that threatened the kingdom,
the princesses and heroes fought...
But
the knight, magician,
bishop, and ninja lost their
lives at the first gate.
At the second gate,
the samurai fell victim to a
curse while protecting the flag,
and lost all of her memories.
At the third gate, due
to the demon's schemes,
the queen was separated from the heroes,
took the flag, and tried to escape...
If Her Flag Breaks
Flag 9
Someday, it'd be Nice if We Could
all Go to a Festival Together Again
What is this, this here?
It's popcorn.
It's exploding...
I can't believe the common people
risk their lives to make snacks.
I'm sure several people have died just
to figure out how to make this treat,
they have!
It's not that dangerous!
So how long will it take
to get to the castle?
Don't know.
Things were pretty crazy. I'm
sure they'll be coming to get us.
Don't say this to anyone else, but the
Majesty doesn't have much time left.
I might not matter,
but I'm sure they'll do something
to make sure Hakua gets there in time.
The guys from The Council of
the Seven Virtues will, anyway.
What... did you just say?
What's up with these guys?
Don't be afraid.
They're from the Council
of the Seven Virtues.
The crown prince has ordered
me to bring you back.
Yes.
The Council of the Seven Virtues
is a special organization
that rules over the populace,
along with the throne.
They're protectors of the Bladefield,
founded along with the country itself.
The Council of the Seven Virtues...
Mei worked with them, right?
Why are they in this country?
Wow. It's a real castle.
Souta-kun!
Don't worry me like that.
Okiku-nee.
I heard what happened from Ruri.
Don't worry us so much.
I'm glad you're all right.
We weren't sure what to do...
Mei-oneechan helped us
contact the people at the castle.
She was really helpful.
I-I wasn't really worried
about Hatate Souta at all.
Anyway, I'm glad you're all right, Souta-kun.
Sorry, everyone.
Anyway, Nanami, Hakua and I are all fine.
Hakua... You mean her?
Huh?!
A-Aren't you getting a little too
close to the princess there,
Hatate Souta?
I, uh...
Nanami, Hakua.
B-Brother Elia.
Crown Prince.
I'm glad you're all right,
my lovely princesses.
You're Hatate Souta-kun, correct?
Thank you for helping them.
Oh, no. Not at all.
This is our brother.
The Crown Prince, Elia.
He's a nice person that cares for us,
even when our father doesn't
seem to pay us much attention.
Number Seven.
Number Seven?
Are you sure you're not mistaking
me for someone else?
So you don't remember me, Number Zero?
Have we met somewhere before?
Excuse me.
It seems you're not the right person.
You done?
Yes.
All the opposition forces have been subdued.
Now your rule is secure.
Is that supposed to mean something?
You let the opposition forces
know about those two,
and baited them into that
assassination attempt.
And the mere moment they failed,
you cast them aside.
You are the sharpest among
the kings we have seen.
However, we cannot have
your heir be a common fool.
I merely tested them.
And if something
happened to them...
We only need to create new heirs.
But do not worry.
The heavenly destiny they carry...
They may even be the fated rulers.
And you're saying that
this is how you've been
protecting this country?
It is the mission of the
Council of the Seven Virtues
to watch over the world, my new King.
It's me.
Get ready.
Why
is everyone collecting in my room when
we've come all the way to Bladefield?!
This is my first time watching television, it is!
Did they really keep you that sheltered?
Brother?
What type of press conference is this?
My beloved citizens.
My father, who has been bedridden
for the past few days,
Allbad Bladefield,
passed away this morning.
Father had already passed away...
There is a reason this announcement
has come to you all late.
As soon as my father passed away,
the second crown prince and
the other princes below him, in other words,
my brothers, plotted to capture the crown,
and were subdued.
In order to corner me into submission,
they attempted to assassinate the thirteenth
and fourteenth crown princesses.
Fortunately, with help from
good men, they were stopped.
Please wait, your Highness.
If they were trying to obtain
the crown for themselves,
why would they attack the princesses with
the least right to inherit the throne?
That is because the thirteenth and
fourteenth have a secret
regarding their birth.
A secret regarding our birth?
In actuality, their father is not
Allbad Bladefield.
I am their true father.
They are my successors.
Sorry to have you all come,
and then have this happen...
Y-You don't have to worry about it.
My friend's fathers are just like my own.
So does that make us princesses, too?
Princesses?!
I'm Souta's...
It sounds like we're talking
about something else now.
Well, I guess it wasn't my
father, but my grandfather.
After a three-day mourning period,
along with the coronation of the new king,
the town will have a celebration.
At least try to have some
fun there, at least.
She was really cared for,
so I guess she still hasn't worked
out her feelings because of that.
Are you okay, Nanami?
You don't seem too chipper yourself.
What?
I keep telling you I wasn't that close to—
You're upset that you aren't as
upset as you thought you'd be.
You don't have to worry about
thinking you're so emotionless.
The fact you're worried about that
right now is proof that you aren't.
You sure understand what people are thinking.
Some people are good at analyzing
others, especially you.
Except I still can't see
anything with you, though.
Long live the Bladefield kingdom!
Cheers to his highness, Elia!
This is wonderful.
It's almost like I'm in a fantasy book!
It's like we're in a land of dreams!
This is good, Onee-sama, it is.
Pay before you start eating!
I'm glad Hakua seems happier now.
Yeah, you're right.
We finally found you.
You can't just stand around here.
Hurry up. You're almost on.
Whoa, wait!
What's going on?
It seems that they've mistaken you for
the people who were supposed
to be in an event.
I would expect nothing less, Souta-san.
S-Souta-kun.
Huh?
The bride in the parade was beautiful.
It's my first time seeing someone so cute.
They said there's a bride.
How romantic.
How about we go take a look?
Conquest Complete
Y-Yeah.
I might want to get married myself.
M-M-Megu-chan?!
No!
Everyone saw me...
I can't be a beautiful bride now.
You wanted to be a bride?
It's okay. We can just get
Souta-kun to marry you.
I can't be a bride. I need to be a groom.
It's my first time being
in a place like this.
Festivals are such fun, they are!
Hey.
You sure you're not pushing yourself?
Huh?
You were able to tell, you were.
I just kinda got the feeling.
Souta-san, u-um...
Could we talk for a little bit, could we?
Huh?
You seem to be accustomed to trouble,
so I figured you'd be good
for some advice, you would.
Do I really seem that gloomy?
No, not just that.
I... believe I have a
connection to you, I do.
This flag...
I think Nanami would be better to talk to...
No, it has to be you, it does!
I knew it...
It's the annoying girl flag...
When we first met, you saved me...
I'm sure you'll be able to help
me with everything, you will!
She trusts me too much...
I figured I could trust you with anything, I did.
She's jumping to extremes.
We're friends, right?
Friends that can talk
about anything, right, right?
It sounds like she can't live without me...
So what did you want to talk about?
My father...
I mean, my grandfather passed away, correct?
He treated me with a lot of affection.
I imagine everyone is carrying
some pain due to his death,
but when I see everyone acting
as if they've forgotten him...
This might seem a little heartless,
but I believe it's best for people to go about
their daily lives and not
stop because of the dead.
I'm sure your grandfather
would rather see you smile,
than be sad and depressed.
Souta-san...
Yes!
Hakua-chan,
I'm sorry!
We didn't notice you felt that way...
And then we dragged you out here...
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm very happy you're so
concerned about me, I am!
Hakua-chan!
Everyone!
I'm so glad that everyone who
loves Sou-kun has gotten closer!
So I'm a member, too, am I?
Of course!
As long as you have feelings for Souta!
This is what it means to
have a close friendship!
Would you all like to give a cheer?
Yes or no?
That's a good idea.
Hooray! Hooray! Souta-kun!
You can do it, Souta-kun!
Why are they cheering for me and not Hakua?
Thanks for helping Hakua.
I didn't really do anything on my own.
I guess we're headed back to Japan tomorrow.
A lot happened,
but I guess it was a fun summer vacation.
This is...
Are you interested in that inscription?
You're...
I guess I haven't told you my name, yet.
I am Number Zero.
Number Zero...
Number Seven,
Daimyouzamurai Mei's, former superior.
Huh?
This inscription is a fairy tale,
told in the lands from which
Bladefield's founding queen hailed.
A fairy tale.
It was the tale of two queens.
As the heroes fell, one by one,
a royal flag was raised aloft by
the last survivor, a golden haired princess.
The demons fled,
and the kingdom regained the light,
but with the last arrow fired by the demons,
the princess lost her life.
The boy of the flag had received
a blessing from the goddess.
But the boy used that blessing
to revive the princess and
the others instead of
healing his own illness.
He remained in the shape of the royal
flag, never to return to normal.
The princesses and her comrades made this
torn flag the symbol of the country.
It is the story of a boy with no name.
It is the story of hope and despair.
It is the tragic story of a young man,
the hero who turned into a strange
flag and saved a country.
It can't be...
It matches up too closely with my past...
If this fairy tale is a
metaphor for my life,
then that means I will only meet
...destruction...
Is everything I do pointless?
Is the light I've finally found meaningless?
What is the world to you?
Why are you...
Is it a symbol of hatred?
Or do you
love it so much you'd sacrifice
anything to protect it?
I... The world...
It won't go away...
I've triggered every flag I can think
of that can get around a death flag!
But it still won't go away!
It won't go away! It won't go away!
It won't go away!
Are you embarrassed that you
were the only one who survived?
You're the one who killed him!
Give them back! You murderer!
No,
the death flag is gathering everyone's
anger and trying to kill me...
Die.
No one really wants that.
No. No.
Die. Die.
No. No. No.
Die. Die. Die. Die. Die.
No!
I'll take it with me...
I'll take the hatred caused by this flag...
This world...
I'll...
I love the world.
I would easily kill a single
princess for the sake of world.
You couldn't...
Yes, I was behind that assassination attempt.
I wanted to see how capable the
succeeding princesses would be,
and get rid of the opposition
in one fell swoop.
Pretty good plan, right?
You...
Of course,
I would give my life if necessary, as well.
She's serious...
For the world, she'd...
I shall ask you once more. How do you feel?
About the world that didn't need you?
I...
Let us meet again.
I would be happy to
hear your answer then.
I shall praise you for
deceiving us and escaping from your bonds.
However, it is pointless.
Someone like you will never be able to save
Hatate Souta.
Save my beloved brother.
Roar! Gawo!
Have you done the preview before, Hakua?
I'm a Bladefield princess.
I can handle the preview with ease, I can!
That's great.
So what is it, this preview?
I thought that flag was coming!
By the way, next time I'll
start studying in Japan.
I don't think it has much to
do with this preview, I don't.
Hold this for Me.
The Winner of the Beauty Contest is Written Here.
Flag 10
That's a preview!
Roar! Gawo!
If Her Flag Breaks
Watch next time!
Illustration: Tiv