Minori has never asked for my help.
She's asked for advice or for teaching,
but...
She has never asked me to help her.
And now...
Help us, please...
We have a casualty.
It's Rundel Haus.
He is
one of the People of the Land.
Call Karashin!
He'll be in charge here for a while.
There are things even I can't do.
No... In this irrational world,
there aren't many things I can do.
But...
If Minori needs my help...
Contract
Contract.
Tell me the situation.
Rundel Haus was fatally wounded
during the defense of Choushi.
We've cast two revival spells, but they failed.
However, he has a pulse, and he's still warm.
But he isn't waking up.
Where are you, and who is with you?
It's Tohya, Isuzu, Serara, and me.
And Rundel Haus.
We're near the crossroads,
at the center of Choushi!
Is it safe?
There are no enemies in the vicinity.
But near the coast, there's still fighting going on.
We don't know when the goblins will attack...
Shiroe, save Rudy!
I was the one who brought him here...
I... It's my fault...
Please, Shiroe!
Tell Serara to cast a revival spell.
Right.
Stand by for 150 seconds.
Tohya is to watch for enemies.
Isuzu should use an MP-restoration song.
After 150 seconds, you cast a revival spell.
Okay.
The mystical energy that animates humans
and demi-humans is called the "spirit."
Psyche
Psyche is the energy that animates the mind.
It affects things such as magic, as well.
Psyche = Magic Points
It is also called MP, magic points.
Anima
Anima is the energy that animates the body.
Anima = Hit Points
HP... Hit points.
It is also the energy known as "ki."
When someone is defeated in battle,
the psyche and anima are split,
and the flow of information from
body to mind is severed.
Then, the anima-dispersal begins.
Anima-dispersal is when the anima,
the body, is dispersed and vanishes.
Revival magic gathers the anima dispersed
into the surrounding atmosphere,
and reconstructs it.
Regan hypothesized that
revival magic would work on People of the
Land, if used immediately after death.
If it's strengthening his pulse,
his body was successfully restored.
But if he hasn't woken up,
his psyche, the energy that powers his mind,
has begun to disperse, as well.
When the body disperses, so does the mind.
And when the body is completely gone,
the mind has nowhere to return,
making revival impossible.
At this point, People of the Land die.
An adventurer's body is automatically
restored at the Cathedral,
and the psyche, or mind,
is connected to it, so they revive.
150 seconds have passed.
I'm casting a revival spell.
In another 150 seconds, use Serara's again.
I'm on my way now.
Keep alternating for another eight minutes.
Okay.
Right now, all we can do is to stop
the body from being destroyed...
But then what?
Isn't it your job to think, Shiro?
But...
That doesn't mean I can just take you
to see the midnight sun in Iceland—
But I want to see it...
I'm a dreamer.
And you make my dreams come true.
Right?
But still...
I specialize in the study of world-class magic.
Magic that alters the rules of the world...
Akatsuki, take the reins!
Milord...
I've brought the report.
Thank you.
What am I...
How goes the battle?
You seem to have grown quite popular.
She looked at me!
Northerner girls are total angels!
Gotta take a picture... Wait, I can't...
So cute!
Dire wolves.
Probably the huge race.
The Goblin King?
He won't leave Seventh Fall.
Most likely, it's the Goblin General's forces.
Oh...
We can clean up their nest later.
For now, let's murder every single
one of the bastards in Zantleaf.
I don't know if I can really do it.
And even if it does work...
That'll do.
Thanks, Akatsuki.
What's wrong?
The Ocypete has reached Choushi.
But the sahuagin are making landing difficult.
They've begun combat!
Everyone! Reinforcements are here!
Just a bit more! Just hang on a bit more!
Akatsuki, watch our surroundings.
Roger.
Move everyone away from here.
Don't let anyone near, players or monsters!
Leave it to me.
Shiroe...
Shiroe!
Is this him?
Yes.
This is Rundel Haus.
Minori, add me to your party.
Okay.
You're Isuzu, right?
Keep casting Meditation Nocturne.
R-Right.
I'm going to use a new magic spell.
Tell no one about this.
A new magic spell?
If you can't agree to that, either give up or leave.
All right...
Let's get started.
Skills > Shiroe
Undo
Over-runner
Mana-channeling
Mana-channeling.
What is that?
It's an enchanter's skill that absorbs MP from
all party members and returns it equally.
But why?
Tohya                                 Minori                     Isuzu
Serara                               Shiroe                       Rundel Haus Code
Psyche is the vessel of the mind,
and it is also MP...
Meaning...
Rundel Haus Code
Minori, use a revival spell.
Serara, continuous healing.
Okay!
Rundel Haus's MP, his mind, is now
active, but he's still unconscious.
So the link between anima and psyche,
his body and mind, is still cut.
Now it's a race against time.
Revival Incense...
This will turn a dead ally or creature
into a zombie for three minutes.
We'll use it to forcibly connect his
body and mind for three minutes.
Rudy!
Rudy...
Miss Isuzu...
Where am I?
Oh, I see...
I died, didn't I?
Don't look so sad, everyone...
Dying is a natural consequence of battle.
Natural?
Even so, I wanted to be an adventurer.
Don't blame Miss Isuzu.
It was I who begged her to do it.
I...
I knew it, too!
I knew it, too, but I...
I...
Minori...
Thank you, Miss Minori.
Don't let it bother you...
No, I will let it bother me.
Rundel Haus Code,
I refuse to allow anyone who gives up so
easily to call himself an adventurer.
That's not nearly enough.
What have you learned?
What you acquired in the dungeon
was not strategy and tactics,
but the resolve to survive, and the
fortitude to do whatever it takes to do so.
Am I wrong?
Shiroe...
Your resolve is sorely lacking, Rundel Haus!
Then what do you want me to do?
Listen to me.
That's...
A contract?
A contract.
Shiroe, leader of the guild Log Horizon,
establishes the following contract
with Rundel Haus Code.
1. Effective as of the date and time at which
Rundel Haus Code signs this document,
Shiroe accepts him as a member
of the guild Log Horizon.
2. As a member of the guild Log Horizon,
Rundel Haus Code will fulfill his missions
in a manner befitting his position.
3. Log Horizon will provide Rundel Haus Code
all necessary support required for his missions,
to the greatest extent acceptable to both parties.
This includes bestowing the status of "adventurer."
4. This contract is signed in the spirit of mutual
respect and agreement between both sides.
Anything either party acquires,
for the contract's duration,
remains theirs, even in the event
that the contract is nullified.
Two copies of this contract will
be signed by both parties,
and each party will retain a copy.
Shiroe, that's...
A new kind of magic that didn't exist
when Elder Tale was a game!
The secret to cooking that Chief Nyanta told us...
Nyanta
Race/ Cat-man
Swashbuckler, Lv. 90
If you cook it yourself, rather than
relying on the cooking command,
you can make tasty food,
provided your skill level is high enough.
I realized that this applied
to more than cooking.
This is a steam engine!
And...
You're researching whether you can
do something with the scribe skill?
The Fairy King's paper, made from
the best ingredients in the game,
ink from the Time Dragon's eye,
and a contract written by a level-90 scribe.
I don't know what effect this magic
will have on this world.
But...
I've added my signature.
Now it only needs yours.
An adventurer...
This contract contains an element of risk.
You'll be a different kind of being
than you've been until now.
We adventurers are still new to
this world, and we don't know
what we'll be caught up in from here on.
I don't think adventurers garner all
the glory you believe them to.
What I want is to be...
an adventurer.
If I can save people who need my help,
I don't care about the details...
I don't want glory.
I want to be an adventurer.
It's okay.
I'll write it with you.
You need to die once, Rundel Haus.
You'll come back to life at the Cathedral.
A summoned creature, restricted to
characters level 86 and above...
The phoenix.
Now, then... Let's tear them apart.
The main dish is finished.
We'll leave the rest to the
strategic headquarters cordon.
Are you okay, Marie?
Are you really okay?
No...
I'm bushed.
Hey, Naotsugu...
What?
We did good, right?
Of course we did.
We saved the town.
Shiroe, why did you say that to Rundel Haus?
Say what?
About adventurers, and resolve.
"Adventurers"...
When Elder Tale was just a game,
that was just a word we used for players.
But now, I think it's something else.
I think it's the name for my companions,
those who travel the world with me,
to find a dawn no one has ever seen.
Where am I?
Oh...
This is the Cathedral?
Sub Class: Adventurer
Rundel Haus Code
Race/ Human
Sorcerer, Lv. 25
Log Horizon
"Adventurer"!
Sub Class: Adventurer
Class Abilities
Can Revive at Cathedral
Friend List
EXP Bonus
Bank Vault
Detailed Status
Wow.
I did it...
I'm an adventurer!
Just the same as...
Rudy!
M-Miss Isuzu...
Wh-What are you doing here?
Oh, right...
You used a return spell to come back?
What if you had died,
doing something that reckless?
Rudy, you idiot!
Th-That's rude!
Sometimes, you have to be willing
to sacrifice your life for duty, Miss Isuzu!
If I tell you to wait, you wait!
That's not fair...
You wait!
I'm sorry...
I guess I made you worry...
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have done it.
S-Sorry—
I w-won't do it again—
I get it!
I get it! I'll do what you say, Miss Isuzu!
Really?
Really!
I swear to God.
And you're going to tell me
about when you were a kid!
Why? It isn't...
F-Fine.
I'll tell you.
If you do crazy things like that,
you won't survive, no matter
how many lives you have!
I'll remember that.
Then give me your paw!
Huh?
The battle has ended.
Eastal and the Round Table
take a new step forward.
To celebrate their victory, a ball is held.
But Akatsuki is gloomy, amidst the cheer.
Fall is coming to the town of Akihabara.
Next time: The Two of Us Shall Waltz.
The Two of Us Shall Waltz
We will change the world.