Diamond Service!
With Diamond Service, you get diamond-level security.
All bugs and performance issues
will be fixed right away.
And with our newest service, we can link our
control panel to your restaurant kitchen's system!
If you are an industry professional,
we look forward to hearing from you.
Diamond Service!
"Himouto Umaru-chan R"
has been brought to you by this sponsor!
My company sponsored this?!
Well, I'm all set.
You haven't packed a whole lot
if you'll be gone for two weeks...
Anyway, I'm worried about
leaving you alone for so long.
I told you, I'll be fine. Kirie will come by and stuff.
Ah! Is it okay if I order some pizza?
I wanna have a party, Big Brother!
I made some food and put it in the freezer,
but I guess she'd get bored eating just that, huh?
I wanna have a party, Big Brother!
I made some food and put it in the freezer,
but I guess she'd get bored eating just that, huh?
This should be enough, right?
Whoa! You're so kind, Big Brother!
Don't go wasting it.
A business trip on our day off... sure is a pain, huh?
What gives, Tanukichi? You get some spending money?
Ten thousand smackers!
I'll be gone for two weeks, so...
Dude, 10,000 yen isn't enough for two weeks, right?
I could burn through that in a day!
O-oh?
Well then, 20,000 should do, right?
Wh-whaaat?
Blessings upon you, Lord Bomba!
Blessings, blessings!
Still, it could be fun if we think of it as a vacation, right?
Oh, yeah... Hamamatsu is famous for eel, right?
Let's eat some eel!
Eel? Big Brother, what's this about eel?!
Didn't you know?
Taihei's project is to come up
with a restaurant's management system.
The restaurant's an affiliate of our company, so we're
going to Hamamatsu to gather more information.
I'll just buy some eel on the way back...
No fair, no fair, no fair! I wanna eat eel too!
Whoa! That's a tantrum
that sure makes use of limited space!
It's not fair if only YOU get to eat it!
I wanna see those eels too! C'mon, Big Brother!
I thought this might happen,
which is why I didn't say anything...
I wanna see those eels too! C'mon, Big Brother!
Fine. How about we bring Tanukichi with us?
Huh? Is that okay?!
No, it isn't!
Well, let's go.
Ma'am!
So sleepy... it's WAY too early!
Wait, you're not sleepy?
I'm used to getting up early for anime events.
More importunately, why is Kanau here?
She's got nothing to do with this, does she?
Beats me. She's the one
who planned this whole trip, right?
A vacation, with Taihei!
The ocean, huh...?
Big Brother! It's the ocean, the ocean!
She sure did want to come.
Maybe I'll bring her here sometime.
The ocean! That's Umaru's ocean!
I still don't know if she'll be okay on her own.
She's probably eating right about now...
Wait, can she even get up on her own?
Big Brother, how long till we get to Hamamatsu?
A vacation with Taihei...!
A vacation with Taihei! A vacation with-!
What are you doing here?!
Umaru has joined your business trip, Big Brother!
Go home!
C'mon, let me tag along for a bit.
This isn't a game, you know!
I won't go back until I've tasted eel!
You're being way too loud! Keep your voice down!
We'll be gone two whole weeks,
so I'm sure I'll get my chance!
You're being way too loud! Keep your voice down!
We'll be gone two whole weeks,
so I'm sure I'll get my chance!
I want eel!
I feel like... something is going to happen!
Hamamatsu.
Located in western Shizuoka,
it is the largest city in the prefecture.
The area around Lake Hamana to the south
is a resort area famous throughout Japan.
It is easily accessible, and the scenery is remarkable!
Also...
it's famous for its eel!
Umaru, I swear... I'm here for WORK.
What am I going to do with her?
It's not like I can introduce her to Kanau...
This is my younger sister!
She sort of tagged along!
Just wait till it's time to review your bonus...
Huh?! No, it can't be!
Ah! U-um...
K-Kanau? Is something wrong?
W-well, it's about when we're supposed to be there...
I guess I confused 8:00 AM with 8:00 PM.
Wow, what a boo-boo!
I-I'm sorry! I mean, if they say "8:00,"
you'd assume 8 AM, right?
At least we won't have to worry about being late, right?
She's always been the type
to make some huge-ass mistake...
Well, how about we fill the time
by researching the local restaurants?
What?! Sh-should we really break up the group
to do things on our own?
There's a lot I'd like to check out, for future's sake.
For future's sake...?
For future's sake!
I'd like to check out some venues
where we can have our ceremony, for future's sake.
An excellent idea, Taihei! Yes, let's do that!
Uh, okay...
Score! Wanna go play pachinko?
Let's check out Hamamatsu's anime shops!
Big Brother! Jeez, you kept me waiting way too- Gah!
Ow, ow!
I can't believe you came all this way.
Whatever. Let's just go.
But after lunch, you need to leave.
Eel time!
No, it's still a bit too early.
How about... we do some sightseeing?
Note: An "anime pilgrimage" means to visit real-life locations that have
appeared in favorite manga or anime.
Oh, yeah! I wanna do an anime pilgrimage!
They've used a lot of places here in Hamamatsu!
Just make sure you don't bother the locals.
Well, sure. That's just common courtesy!
And we'll be doing NORMAL sightseeing as well.
Yup! Of course!
Oh... the Arch of Lucky Stars!
This says that if two people touch it at the same time,
something good will happen.
That sounds kinda nice...
Wait, wouldn't it usually be COUPLES who do this?
It doesn't say anywhere that siblings can't do it!
And speaking of couples, Big Brother...
Hm?
Just who is... that girl who came with you?
She's my boss.
But you call her by her first name!
You sure have been paying attention...
Note: in Japan, only people who are VERY close will call each other by
their first name. Even married couples often don't - they just say "you."
Your boss, and yet you use her FIRST name? Strange...
Yes, it's quite unusual. How did this come to be?
Why are you talking like that?
Bomba, Kanau, and I...
For better or worse, we've been pretty much inseparable,
and have spent a LOT of time together.
Wait, she's the same age as you, but she's your boss?
She's actually a year younger.
I'm not sure I should be saying this, but...
Kanau is the CEO's daughter.
I'm sure she feels a lot of pressure
being section chief at her age...
She makes mistakes, but I think she's doing her best.
Huh. So you're not lovers...
Of course not.
Wait, you came because
THAT'S what you were worried about?
No, not really.
I-I came because I wanted to eat some eel!
Well, let's go. Let's eat already!
I guess you're right. It's still a little early,
but maybe we should get going.
Sure enough, there aren't many people here this early...
Is researching that part of your job too?
Sorry for the wait. Here's your order, one charbroiled eel!
Wh-whoa!
This isn't farm-raised eel from Lake Hamana,
it's wild-caught, the real deal!
You sure know your stuff...
You tasty sea creature!
Eel in broth is nice too.
Huh? Who's "E. Lynn Broth"?!
Look, just add soup broth and seasonings,
and it will really change the flavor.
Kinda like rice soup, huh?
A rather clean flavor profile, I'd say...
Ah! The flavor of the wasabi
as it passes through the nostrils is exquisite!
Huh? What's with you?
I just...
I was thinking, I'm glad we came.
Yup!
Be careful on the way home.
Okay! And you, have a safe trip!
Uh, I'm already here...
I'll be back soon.
Do your best on the job, okay?
It's not even 6:00 yet,
so we're a bit early, but it'll be fine, right?
Okay, let's go!
Huh?
My, what cute youngsters you are!
Well, you can start by prepping these potatoes.
Um, we're with Diamond Service,
regarding data on your customer-
Here, you will address me as "Chef."
And in the kitchen, the chef's word is absolute.
You will do this for me.
Huh?!
All right, now get moving!
Y-yes, Chef!
Taihei... that outfit looks great on you!
You have one hour to prep 300 of these!
Wait, you came because
THAT'S what you were worried about?
So sleepy... maybe I shouldn't follow him after all.
I wonder why...
If something is bothering you, just ask for advice.
Otherwise, you will regret it!
Huh? Are you hungry?
Huh?! N-no, not at all!
Really? Still, to think there'd
be a restaurant HERE of all places...
Oh, I know! You, me, and Umaru
should come here some time.
Food always tastes better with friends.
Um, there's...
something I'd like to talk to you about.
What is it?
U-um, well... It's quite embarrassing, but...
um, I...
am looking for a particular restaurant.
It's already been a week
since we've come to Hamamatsu.
The staff meal's ready. It's break time.
Okay.
I'll take Kanau her plate.
Huh? Wait, has Alex always called her
"Kanau," by her first name?
Huh. I'm not sure.
Whoo! Delicious as always!
Yes, it really is.
I wasn't sure what would happen,
being made to work in the kitchen...
but being here has made it easier to write my report
and put together a system plan.
The chef and the other staff
have really opened up as well...
DELISH!
Be silent. Rather, just leave already.
You have work to get back to in Tokyo, don't you?
Yeah, but doing that means going back to the grind, so...
Oh, my sweet Bomba. Corporate life is hard, isn't it?
You've got that right!
Or, rather, talking to one another
has helped us all get along.
They just keep giving us more stuff to do!
Our CEO likes to diversify the business,
but it's all totally random!
This very restaurant started up in Tokyo, but the CEO
got a wild hair and, goodness! Now we're in Hamamatsu.
Um, I think that's enough talk about that...
Hey, Spiky-Haired Guy.
Huh?
You know your way around a kitchen, don't you?
Ah, yes. I cook at home.
Home, huh? Are there many of you?
No, just my younger sister.
I bet she's finicky, isn't she?
What?!
I can tell from the way you prep.
The way you peel the potatoes, polish the rice...
all these things you do...
They feel like they're from cooking not for yourself,
but for someone else.
Okay, it's ready.
They feel like they're from cooking not for yourself,
but for someone else.
Let's eat...
They feel like they're from cooking not for yourself,
but for someone else.
Big Brother!
Oh, my! It's not like you to speak so kindly.
Shut the hell up.
Say, why not be a lamb and work here with us?
Huh?
Yeah. You take cooking as seriously as any pro.
No... I have to get back so I can do my cooking at home.
Did I do something wrong in the game, Master?
No, it just felt like someone was gossiping about me...
Still, I'm glad to have been able
to learn from you, Chef.
Everything you've made has been delicious.
He's embarrassed!
Ko-chan, you've got smoke coming from your ears...
Shut up!
"Ko-chan"? You mean, Chef?
Come to think of it, we haven't even heard his name...
I'm Koichiro Ebina.
Ow! Ow!
The same surname as our little miss Ebina, huh?
Still, they don't look or act the same at all.
Taihei?
You're looking for a restaurant?
Yes.
My brother is...
I've heard he's working at a restaurant in Tokyo.
He left home 10 years ago... still, I'm sure he's doing well.
All right, you all! Don't go slacking off
during the afternoon service!
Yes, Chef!
It couldn't be...
The business trip's finally over.
A lot has happened these past two weeks.
Two weeks, and nothing happened at all!
I'm home!
Huh? Big Brother?
Oh, no! It's already been two weeks!
UMARU! I TOLD YOU NOT TO MAKE A MESS!
It's like you've perfected the way you get angry!
Sure enough, it's totally bare...
Oh! You brought back a lot of souvenirs, Big Brother.
I'm going to be giving some as gifts.
I'll do it while I'm out shopping.
I wanna come too!
Th-thank you very much!
I hope you like it.
Yes! I'll treasure this forever!
Be sure to eat them before they expire.
Chef and I exchanged phone numbers...
maybe I should get in touch with him soon.
Something wrong, Big Brother?
Say, have you heard anything about Ebina's family?
Huh? Her family?
No, never mind. Let's just get going.
Sure! But I've never been to Kirie's house,
so I don't know where it is.
Note: Shikuwasa is a form of citrus native to Okinawa.
Well, how about we just give it to her
next time she comes over?
Yeah, good idea.
So, the next house is...
Kirie! We got a souvenir gift!
STOP BARGING IN HERE UNINVITED!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
This is one awesome house...
My friend Sylphin lives here.
Ah! It's Umaru, indeed!
You seem like you're in a good mood, Sylphin.
Indeed, for my big brother has come home!
Oh. And who is this?
This is MY big brother.
I'm Taihei Doma.
Oh, it's that girl from before.
Thank you for being such a good friend to my sister.
This is a small gift from Hamamatsu.
Oh! Hm? I feel like I've just seen this...
Still, thank you very much!
She's a bit strange, but she's nice.
Yup!
I'm gonna go get some cola and potato chips!
No more than two.
Yes, I know!
"Not for yourself, but for someone else."
Sorry to keep you waiting!
The heck is all this?!
There! Take that!
Oh, there's the bonus!
I got you now! I'm crushin' it...
It's been two weeks, huh?
And there's the super rare item!
Bada-bing! Woo!
I didn't play these much while you were gone, you know!
Oh, really?
So she was still able to have fun on her own.
I guess there was no need for me to worry.
What's wrong?
Big Brother!
I was... I was...
I was so lonely!
Really?
I was lonely and stuff!
Okay, I get it.
Big Brother!
Umaru, it's been a while since
we've done the preview together, hasn't it?
Ebina! Thank goodness! I'm so glad to get here and
FINALLY find one of the regular female cast members!
It seems you've had it rough.
Anyway, and now for the preview! Wait, we're out of time!