You made it to Class A, Taichi.
I was playing a third-year from Fujisaki.
I only lost by three cards.
Second place.
I did good enough.
Come on!
Come on!  Come on!  Come on!  Come on!
Read it!  Read it!  Read it!  Read it!
Give it!  Give it!  Give it!  Give it!  Give it!
I do not know where this love will take me
Come on!  Come on!  Come on!  Come on!
You did it...
You did it, Taichi.
Congratulations!
Chihaya Furu
Verse 24
When
I
must
hide...
Congratulations!
Stop crying, Chihaya.  Stand up.
We need to get going
before their match ends!
Come on...
Stupid, stand still.
Taichi's Class A now.
That means...
he's a rival!
Y-You can go on.
We'll stay to cheer for Desktomu-kun.
No, I'm the captain.
I have to support Mizusawa—
Thanks.
Let's go, Chihaya.
Hanano-san.
"When I must hide" is a beautiful poem, isn't it?
Huh?  What poem is that?
Oh, they're starting.  Be quiet.
Oe-senpai is so strange.
She brings out poems like
they're candy or remedies.
When I must hide these burning
feelings, I feel as though my body
is on fire with Ibuki mugwort
You know nothing about
these feelings of mine that burn as if on fire.
Got it!  Yeah!
Huh?
Yes!  One more card!
What?!
Tsukuba made it to the Class D finals?!
Only person who noticed
I had no idea!
When I must hide these burning feelings,
I feel as though my body is
on fire with Ibuki mugwort
We didn't have many empty cards
in our match on the first floor,
so the second floor should still be going.
I hope we can get into the Urayasu room.
What's wrong, Chihaya?
I'm going back downstairs
to cheer for Desktomu-kun.
Huh?  What are you talking about?
The Queen and Arata are playing!
Don't you want to watch their match?!
Chihaya...
Why?
I wanted to watch their match so badly.
I'm scared.
Oh, sorry.
There's no room inside with all the
people watching the Class A final.
Oh, really...
Mr. Kuriyama,
is there really no room inside?
Midori-chan.
Can you squeeze us in?
Oh, hold on.
You two, come with us.
What?  You don't want to watch the match?
U-Um...
If you've chosen to take this path,
there isn't anything you're
better off not knowing.
Midori-chan, there's no room in the back,
so you'll have to go in from the side.
Thank you very much.
banish any lingering memories of the past
Take a seat.  Don't make any noise.
Okay.
There's no water here.
It looks just like a normal match.
Yet...
It's so painful.
F-Five cards to eleven cards?
Shinobu-chan's losing?
Ayase!  Mashima!
They finally made it.
Did Mashima win?
I should have recorded
this match, like Fujisaki is.
I wish I could show Ayase and
Mashima the entire match.
Show them what's transpired...
Show them their karuta...
At the beginning, both Wataya
and the Queen split similar cards.
The positioning benefited
Wataya's cross stroke.
He could move before
unique syllables were read,
and the Queen couldn't do a thing.
She stayed calm though.
She targeted select cards
and took them with her usual accuracy.
But...
The cards she targeted weren't being read.
Wataya Arata had all the momentum.
How?
How does he summon cards this way?
I'm moving my cards.
His card sending is nasty.
His card movement is nasty.
He's as sadistic as Sudo-san.
A perfect cross...
A detailed game plan.
That's not all.
I just have to change the momentum.
I'm only down a few cards.
But...
Why are things going so badly?
Today, I'll have to choose
which cards I can save
and which cards I can't.
I discriminated.
I looked away from everyone.
but for autumn's coming
The fall paddy shacks...
After I determined to abandon
my love, my only regret
Wow, she's fast.
Impressive.
Amazing.
I-I've never heard Shinobu-chan
make any sound when taking a card!
How many cards did she
hit with that swing?
This isn't Shinobu-chan's usual style.
She began moving after the first syllable.
She's taking risks.
Sorry, everyone.
I'm coming for you.
I'll take all of the remaining cards.
The Queen looks so intense.
The Queen has the advantage in speed.
Technique becomes less viable
later in the game.
No, it's not his technique.
What really makes him special is...
It's only noticeable if
you've played against him.
is that I have no way
to tell you in person
Wataya Arata is special because...
The
fall wind parts...
Sorry.
Was that...
Faster than Wakamiya Shinobu?
The Queen reacted first.
Her reaction and swing were very quick.
However, despite that...
He was able to catch up!
With incredible acceleration!
Sorry, Taichi, Chihaya.
Oh, it's okay.
But it's not Wataya Arata's acceleration
or his plethora of weapons that scares me.
It's his relaxed demeanor that gets me.
Chihaya-chan, it would refer to a
top that spins perfectly smoothly.
It almost looks like it's completely still,
focusing its power in perfect balance,
with no lean in any direction...
Strong enough to repel
anything that makes contact,
while projecting stability.
A decorative word used for gods.
"Impassionate."
Chihaya, you need to stay back.
This guy's for real.
A high school second-year.
The Queen was our only hope!!
He just turned seventeen?
I was expecting great things
from Master Wataya's grandson,
but nothing like this!
It's not like Arata was
born a good karuta player.
Arata-kun's making a lot of noise.
He has no trouble with
players his own age,
but he can't do anything
against Murao-kun.
Remember how Coach Wataya always
warns you about your
swing being too wide.
Hey, let's go visit him again...
Visualize...  Visualize...
Visualize perfect karuta.
Did you lose to Murao-kun again?
At the last Kyoto tournament,
you lost because of a foolish error.
Was your mind wandering because
I wasn't there to watch you?
I was focused!
I was visualizing my karuta with you
there watching, but it didn't work!
I couldn't move!
Are you playing karuta with
that scary look on your face?
There's a lot more to visualization
than you realize.
When do you find it easiest
to move around freely?
When did you have the
most fun playing karuta?
For now, I would start with
300 practice swings a day.
What?!
Arata was on the rise when
Master Wataya passed away.
Then he did nothing for a year and a half.
I don't know what it was
that brought Arata back.
All I know
is that after Master Wataya died,
Arata grew 20 centimeters,
and he didn't go a single
day this past year
without doing 500 practice swings.
His body grew enough
that he could play the way he visualized.
Perhaps...
Perhaps he will be
Wait, I'm the
bad guy?
the player who unseats Master Suo?
Forget about that.
The score is 4 to 9.
The Queen's about to go down.
Too much noise...
Why are there so many spectators?
How stupid are they?
Why am I paying so much
attention to my surroundings?
I didn't want to have to
use my brand new Snowmaru fluffy towel.
Round
The Queen is wiping off her sweat.
I've never seen her do that before.
This is my fifth match!
Of course I'm gonna sweat!
My matches weren't easy, either.
I didn't need to hold myself back today.
Shudder
to reveal moonlight, clear and bright
The storm blasts autumn
leaves off Mount Mimuro
An empty card.
to set the Tatsuta River ablaze
Like a boatsman adrift...
Who got that one?
Same time?
I couldn't tell.
The Queen was faster?
She snatched it from the
opponent's lower right.
For a moment, I thought
that Arata was faster,
but she slipped in under his hand.
How was she able to reach so low?
I do not know where
this love will take me
May my lonely nights in bed not be so long,
What just happened?
The cards flew in two different directions.
How is that possible?
Who got it?
They both hit the card,
but...
the Queen won it.
Was Chihaya able to see what happened?
Incredible...
"May my lonely" was just read.
Shinobu-chan had "May my lonely"
and "May the time spent"
at her lower left,
so Arata went for the
entire group of cards.
But Shinobu-chan was able to pick out
the one card she needed.
Shinobu-chan was pulling
on the strings.
How is she able to do that?
Faster...
Lower...
The one with the stronger
ties to the cards
is me, Arata.
That smiling four-eyes
really throws me off.
I have to be careful.
Concentrate.  Concentrate.
4 to 7.
The Queen has cut down the lead.
What now?
Concentrate.  Concentrate.
I feel like crap.
I can confidently say
that this the highest level of high school—
no, the highest level of Class A play.
though you have never known that pain
I'm tired.
Hot.
But...
I can still become stronger.
I can strengthen my ties to the cards.
Stronger!
For you, I head out to the
fields to pick spring greens
while snow falls upon my sleeves
Thank you very much.
The Queen...
Lost!
Your High School Class A
champion, by two cards,
is Wataya Arata-kun from Fukui.
Arata...
He really did it.
After years without a loss,
the Queen has been upset.
You have a fever, Shinobu-chan.
You were drenched in the rain yesterday,
and you were wearing that
thing to keep you cool.
I'm amazed you made
it through the match.
I've always wanted to play
against opponents who
wanted to put up a fight.
Naturally.
I'm the Queen.