Motoba
Episode 9   Umaru and Valentine's
How to Make Basic Cookies
Easy And Fast!
Cute homemade cookies
are perfect for gifts.
How about making a lot
and inviting some friends
over for a home café?
I've been watching you for a while,
but what are you doing?
H-H-Hey!
Are you trying to curse someone?
N-No!
Oh, I get it. You're making sweets, aren't you?
Why would you make sweets when
you don't have any friends?
Did something happen? Well?
Sh-Shut up!
R-Really... Nothing happened.
Okay. Do your best.
<<For Example, When You're On Your Break>>
Creating a
Conversation
with Homemade
Cookies...
I made some
cookies! Why
don't we eat
them together?
What? You made me cookies, Kirie-chan?
Thank you.
You're so talented, Kirie-chan!
I'd love to eat your cookies again.
Let's make them together next time.
They're bitter.
I can't let Umaru-san eat these.
I'll keep them just in case,
and make new ones.
I'll make Master's cookies first.
It worked this time!
Time to wrap them.
Oh, the bags are in my room.
I hope Master will be happy.
These are delightful!
Sheesh, you should really be
more up-front with these things.
Don't just leave them here
without saying anything.
You made these for me, right?
Don't be shy. Just give them to me.
You should've added a little more sugar, though.
Motoba
Huh? What? What's wrong, Kirie?
The Next Day
U-Umaru-san!
Um... These...
K-Kirie-chan! Are you all right?
I-I'm sorry.
Kirie-chan.
You made me cookies?
Thank you.
They're delicious!
These are delightful!
I'm home.
Kirie-chan said those are for you, Onii-chan.
Chocolates?
Oh, no!
Valentines
Homemade Corner
Ebina
Umaruun
It's rare for you to invite
me over, Ebina-chan.
I saw some chocolates at the store,
so I thought it might be nice
to make some homemade ones.
I see.
I was just in the mood for chocolates.
Heartfelt
Homemade Chocolate Recipes
From Friendship Chocolates to
Chocolates For Your Crush
Wahoo!
It should be pretty easy.
We'll just whip some up and....
I'll be right back, Ebina-chan.
Huh?
Onii-chan was home, so I brought him over.
Wh-What's going on?
You know, I was in the middle of doing laundry...
Chocolates look hard to make, so help us out.
You'd prefer it if I weren't
here, right, Ebina-chan?
N-Not at all. Please stay!
R-Really?
Chocolates, huh?
I know how to make them,
but it's probably better if just the girls do it...
H-Huh?
Sh-She has two refrigerators!
Her kitchen's super fancy, too.
Th-This is amazing!
I know! I'll try putting
kakinotane in the chocolates.
There's No Way That'd Taste Bad
Choco
Flakes
Kakinotane
If you don't put too much energy
into decorations and flavors, you can
make homemade chocolates in no time.
You chop it up, melt it, form the shapes,
and you're done.
That's it?
Well, since they're homemade,
you could try out different things
when you're melting the chocolate.
If you make truffles,
you can use whipping cream.
Drool...
If you make raw chocolate,
you can use starch syrup.
That sounds delicious.
And...
When you make Valentine's chocolates,
you melt regular chocolate to make homemade
ones so you can give them as gifts,
but you're not just mixing things in
to change what type of chocolate it is.
You're also mixing your feelings
for the recipient into them.
I thought it might be nice
to make some homemade ones.
I wonder if Ebina-chan wants
to give them to someone.
Eating chocolate
originally began when people
crushed cacao beans and ate them.
Chocolate as we know it today
came to Japan by way of Spain.
He's giving a speech now...
Mix in your feelings for the recipient...
Kakinotane
It's done!
Dear = Love
I wrote "dear"!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What am I going to do?
Now I have to write his name...
What did you put in there?
Kakinotane.
What? You sure that's going to be okay?
It tastes amazing when you eat them together.
These two together are a
combination that can't go wrong.
R-Really?
Don't blame me if it's gross.
If you're gonna be like that, I won't
give you any, even if it's good.
Fine with me. I don't even
like chocolate that much.
Are you done, Ebina-chan?
Yeah.
I-It was for herself?
Well, I did the same thing.
I want cola.
I wonder what anime I
should watch this season.
Incoming
It's from Sylphyn.
UMR-san! It's an emergency!
Huh?
TSF-san!
UMR-san.
Shubaan
I have obtained it.
The Oreomo live event DVD!
Man! I've been waiting for this!
Thank goodness I just happened
to visit an anime store today.
Buri Musume
Anime to Air!!
I had no idea there was an Anumate here...
Puri♥Kyura
This is...
The new Puri Kyura merchandise is out already!
They're all adorable!
These weren't here the last time I came.
Which means she must come here often.
TSF-san, since we're here,
why don't we look around some more?
Shupaaa
Then I shall lead you.
Leave it to me! I shall escort you.
Magical Girl
Kajiki Maguro
I Want to Go Back to Mars Soon...
It wasn't him...
Since we're done shopping,
want to sit down over there?
Indeed.
There were so many things I wanted,
I bought way too much.
I'm glad you like anime, TSF-san.
Japanese anime is so cute and cool.
My elder brother loves it.
Oh, so you two must watch
it together at home.
Huh?
N-No... I watch it alone.
O-Onii-sama thinks of me
as his meek little sister,
so for him to see me watching
anime or playing games...
is embarrassing.
Her face is as red as it was back then.
I have an older brother, too.
Huh? Really?
Shuba
That means we're alike!
So we're not just comrades in gaming,
but we're both little sisters, too!
Huh? S-Sure...
But my Onii-chan doesn't watch
anime or anything. He just cooks.
You should cook with him, UMR-san.
Huh? But cooking is...
It'll be fine!
At first, I didn't really understand anime,
but it's easy to fall in love with
something that your loved one likes.
Shubaan
Oh, no. Look at the time.
I must get home immediately,
or I'll be in trouble.
See you again!
So we're not just comrades in gaming,
but we're both little sisters, too!
All right. I guess I'll make dinner.
Now, then...
Onii-chan, want me to help?
Huh? Why?
Do you have a fever?
Curly, curly, pop!
Umaruun
All right, Onii-chan, I'm off.
Don't be out too long.
U
Ki
Stop
U
Coming!
H-Huh?
Uma... Komaru just left.
You guys had plans, right?
I'm sure she'll be right back...
W-W-We don't.
She didn't have an appointment?!
Oh, I forgot to say it a while back,
but thank you for the cookies.
They were delicious.
Though they were a little burnt.
They were not.
What?!
Huh?
Umaru...
Hurry home.
This is...
incredibly awkward.
I thought she'd been able to talk more recently,
but maybe she can't really talk
when Umaru's not around.
Oh, right. The laundry—
It's evening...
Kirie-chan didn't get to hang out with Umaru.
U-Um...
I-I'm sorry about the cookies...
Um...
Th-The burnt ones...
I accidentally gave you the burnt ones!
I'm so sorry!
Now I get it!
That's why she came over today.
I won so much at the arcade
that I got back late.
I wonder if Onii-chan's mad...
Huh?
Oh, welcome home.
Master!
Huh? Why are you here, Kirie-chan?
She came here to hang out with you.
And yet...
You're home awfully late, aren't you?
Huh?
Aw!
It's okay, isn't it, Kirie-chan?
M-Master...
I think you should have
come home sooner, as well.
What?!
I'm home...
Umaru's asleep?
Jiggly
Pudding
Now Even
More Jiggly
It's empty!
My pudding cup is empty!
Onii-chan!
I didn't eat it.
But it was there before I fell asleep!
Pudding! Pudding! My pudding is gone!
She's exerting so much energy over pudding...
I'm sure you just ate...
No, wait.
I can't accuse someone without any evidence.
I have to set a good example for Umaru.
Umaru, we're going to find out
where the pudding went!
Huh? You can figure that out?
Umaru's Jiggly Pudding Disappearance Case
It'd be easier to just buy a new pudding,
Then just buy me one...
but we must reveal the truth first.
But I didn't eat it.
All right. Explain the
reasons you didn't eat it.
First, I fell asleep before
I could eat the pudding.
That is because I received a message
from you saying that you'd be home late.
Therefore, I
held a feast for myself.
It was amazing!
Objection!
What are you doing?!
You must have eaten it, then!
Hold it!
Order, please, Onii-chan.
Here are some leftover potato chips.
Pudding is dessert that should be eaten last.
Eating pudding before my potato chips
goes against my beliefs!
Like I care!
Pudding is Tops!!
But it doesn't seem like she's lying.
Could she have actually not eaten it?
Upupupupu.
Refutation
More importantly, Onii-chan,
what time did you come home last night?
Huh? Yesterday, I got out of work late,
and went home on the last train...
So about midnight.
Thank you for all your hard work.
Onii-chan, those aren't
your pajamas, are they?
You fell asleep in them, didn't you?
I-It's true that I was really tired last night,
so I just fell asleep...
Psst...
Huh? Come to think of it,
I don't remember much...
Onii-chan hobbles home from work, exhausted.
Umaru...
Wait, I wasn't that tired.
So if there is pudding on the
table when he returns home,
it's inevitable that he would eat it!
Aren't all these representations
of me kind of awful?
All right.
Let's actually eat some pudding.
Huh? Why?
If one of us ate it, that might jog our memories.
Nearly One Hour Later...
All right. It's ready, Umaru.
Why did you make those, Onii-chan?
You could have just bought some.
Huh? Didn't I promise you I'd make some?
Well, whatever. Let's eat.
Y-Yeah.
I'm home...
Umaru's asleep?
Jiggly
Pudding
Now Even
More Jiggly
Umaru, I'm putting the pudding in the fridge.
I'm gonna eat it now.
Hey, do you know how to
make pudding, Onii-chan?
I guess I'll make some sometime.
Hey.
Umaruun
It's delicious, Onii-chan.
You were the one who ate it, weren't you?
Hey, will you make me pudding
again sometime, Onii-chan?
You were the one who ate it, right? Well?!
Pudding ice cream isn't the best,
but pudding daifuku is good.
Though they'll make me fat.
Umaru, look at me!
I want to try pudding dorayaki,
too, I think! Onii-chan!
Umaru!
Next Time
Episode 10  Umaru and Now and Once Upon a Time
It's been a while since I've done a preview.
We've used all the main characters already,
so it's always tough to decide who should do it.
Why didn't all of you girls just go in rotation?
I can see you didn't even think of that.