When Elder Tale was a game,
one goal was to make
the game world a one-half-scale model of Earth.
The Half Gaia Project.
In this world, the land corresponding to Japan
is known as the Crescent Islands of Yamato...
The northernmost area of
which is the Ezzo Empire.
Brigandia's the guild that's bossing
people around in Susukino, right?
Even when this was a game,
they had a bad reputation.
To them, this world must be heaven.
Yes, thank you.
Goodbye.
What did they say?
Marie will talk to Serara.
Roger.
But, my lord...
Why are we meeting them in the city?
Is it unsafe outside?
If we meet up outside and
are wiped out in a fight,
we'd revive in the Akihabara Cathedral,
but Serara would revive at
the Susukino Cathedral.
I understand.
Serara is on
a Brigandia member's Friend List, right?
Yeah.
Her current hiding spot is within a
private zone, so they can't find her.
But the minute she leaves,
they'll locate her and send pursuit.
So she's gotta get out before they catch up.
Akatsuki, I'd like you to hide yourself
with Sneak and Silent Move, please.
No "please," my lord.
Sneak enables self-concealment, while
Silent Move allows motion without any sound.
They're tracker-class skills.
Then, let's get this plan in gear!
Escape
Escape.
Location Search
Target Not Within Specified Area
Where are you hiding, Serara?
How long are you going
to obsess over that girl?
You've gotta keep a tight lead on your pets...
Let them know who's boss.
Demikas!
What's wrong?
Well...
Two guys you don't know?
They appear to be outsiders.
Displaying Serara's location
Susukino: Corridors of Time
Looks like they noticed us.
Yeah.
Anyway, talk about a nasty atmosphere...
This is the place.
Akatsuki, keep watch.
Understood.
Naotsugu, you wait here.
Roger.
U-Um...
Serara
Race/ Human
Druid, Lv. 19
I'm Serara, of the Crescent Moon Alliance.
Um...
Thank you for coming!
Meow.
Wait...
Is that you, Chief?!
Meow.
Oh, my... If it isn't little Shiroe.
Nyanta
Race/ Cat-man
Swashbuckler, Lv. 90
That explains how you arrived so quickly.
U-Um...
Ah, well...
I'm sorry, Serara.
My name is Shiroe.
He's a very smart kid, and a very good one.
If he's here, our plan is sure to work.
I see you still meow all the time, Chief.
What are you talking about?
This is the correct way for cat people to talk.
D-Do you know each other?
I suppose we do.
Little Shiroe used to check me for fleas.
I did not.
I can go back to Akihabara.
But what about Nyanta?
Naotsugu is with me.
And one other, a girl named Akatsuki...
A level-90 assassin.
She's good.
Then little Naotsugu's here, too?
And a new friend?
I think it would be best if
you came with us, Chief.
That's fine.
I have no reason to stay.
Perhaps it is a sign from above,
telling me to go to Akihabara.
Then...
Meow.
Nyanta!
Akatsuki?
Which direction?
They're coming from the north.
On their way, they're searching the town.
But they're close enough to be here in five minutes.
Their leader seems to be an
enormous martial artist.
He's a monk, but...
Like a bear carved out of wood?
That would be Brigandia's guild master, Demikas.
Naotsugu...
I'm here.
I see.
Roger.
Thanks.
Let's go.
We'll take the rear exit.
Londark...
Ah...
So the outsiders really were here for Serara.
Yes.
The transport gate is shut down.
Where did they come from?
Interesting.
It's okay.
They won't attack yet.
Fighting isn't allowed within towns.
They'll wait until we're outside to attack.
Th-Then how will we escape?
Hmm...
If they're letting us leave, then we just go.
That makes things easier...
B-But if we leave...
They might attack us, right?
Not "might." They will.
Once we're outside the no-PvP zone,
their plan is to surround and PK us.
Their first priority will probably be
your confederate, Chief Nyanta.
That will destroy your will and
put you under their control.
I'm almost certain of that.
N-No...
There are so many of them...
They might kill us!
You can't...
Now, now, Serara...
Just leave this to Shiroe, and you'll be fine.
B-But...
We've been looking for you.
Serara...
Chief Nyanta?
What?
If you went one-on-one with
the enemy leader...
A foolish question.
Don't worry.
I won't let them touch you, Serara.
Which of you is Brigandia's Demi-glace?
Now, Shiroe...
Asking something so loudly is rude.
I know which one he is.
It's the excessively huge guy sitting over there.
Hey, Demikas!
It's been a long time, Serara.
You didn't think you could disobey
me and get away with it, did you?
Londark
Race/ Elf
Sorcerer, Lv. 90
If you come back now, I'll forgive you.
Of course, I'll send you to the
Cathedral ten times first!
Demikas
Race/ Human
Monk, Lv. 90
Recklessness is the way of the young.
And tolerance is the beauty of adulthood.
But...
There is such a thing as going too far.
Huh?
You've gone too far.
Reigning in children who stray too far
beyond the lines is also an adult's job.
Come on, I'll fight you one-on-one.
Ridiculous.
Why should I fight you?
Are you afraid to face me alone?
What?!
Sorry to interrupt, Mister, uh...
Delicious.
But it doesn't have to be you.
I'd prefer the one in the gray robe.
Isn't that an artifact drop from
the Fire Lizard's Cave?
You seem stronger.
Have you heard my name, Londark of Gray Steel?
So you have a nickname...
No wonder.
It would be more satisfying for both of us
if the strongest fighters settled things.
We'll have our Chief Nyanta fight you.
Let us finish this.
We can ignore the cowardly meatball here,
as he's too scared to fight himself.
Very well...
If you want to fight that much...
I'll fight you!
It's been a long time...
since I've gotten to devour someone.
Nyanta!
I'd rather the lady didn't see anything too gory.
If you want me to go easy, tell me quickly.
Just keep talking.
Demikas is in the monk class.
One of the three warrior classes,
alongside guardian and samurai.
Many Elder Tale techniques have both
Status/ In Combat
Techniques
Quests
Equipment
Items
what are known as cast times and cool down times.
Shadow Kick
Tiger Echo Fist
Aura Saber
Triple Blow
Dual Fist
Cast time is how long it takes a
spell to have effect, once it's cast.
Cool down time is how long it takes before
you can reuse a spell.
Shadow Kick
Tiger Echo Fist
Aura Saber
Triple Blow
Dual Fist
Aura Saber!
Monk-class techniques have short cool downs.
They chain techniques,
giving opponents no recovery time.
Phantom Step!
Did you think you could defeat me
with those little toy swords?
How rude.
A rapier is a gentleman's weapon.
Demikas                                                 Nyanta
Nyanta's hit points...
Demikas has more HP.
Demikas                                                 Nyanta
But...
The swashbuckler...
It's one of the specialized weapon classes,
and one of the few that can dual wield.
What sets it apart are the bad statuses
their weapons can inflict.
Lowered attack, lowered dodge,
lowered defense.
They can negate an opponent's strengths...
Or worsen their weaknesses.
H-Hey...
Doesn't it look like Demikas is losing?
Stop jumping around, and fight fair and square!
Coming from you, "fair and square" sounds
like a bastardization of our fair language.
Serara...
When I give the signal, I want you to
cast a healing pulse on everyone.
Everyone?
I'm done playing around!
You guys, heal me!
Surround the cat and kill him!
Step on it.
R-Right.
Anchor Howl!
That isn't fair...
Healer teams, heal Demikas.
Right.
Demikas
Race/ Human
Monk, Lv. 90
It's fine...
Take out the guardian first.
Right!
Die!
No... They'll kill him!
Heal everyone! Now!
Right!
Heartbeat Healing!
Druid is one of the healing classes.
Nyanta
Race/ Cat-man
Swashbuckler, Lv. 90
Once they cast a healing pulse on someone,
it remains in effect for a short time.
Oh, no...
I can't keep this up!
My level isn't high enough.
Don't worry about Naotsugu.
Focus on Nyanta.
But... They're both in danger!
If you can't do something, then don't.
Focus on what you can.
Heal!
What's this?
Must be hard to get by
with one crappy healer,
cat...
No, it isn't!
Just shut up.
Your friend, the warrior, is about to go down!
Naotsugu
Naotsugu                                        Nyanta
Shiro!
Ready the spell.
R-Right.
Castle of Stone!
No damage?
Castle of Stone...
This spell blocks all damage
for a ten-second period.
An emergency-defense skill
only available to guardians.
Now.
Cast all your healing spells on Naotsugu!
Okay.
Healing Wind!
Naotsugu
Buying time won't save you, Serara.
Castle of Stone has a ten-minute cool down!
If he's using a skill he can't use
again for another ten minutes,
that guardian must be out of options.
He must be starting to panic.
When the spell runs out, you're dead.
You've made this harder
than it had to be, Serara.
Serara                                    Naotsugu
Quickly...
Heal quickly!
Tiger Echo Fist!
Nyanta!
Think it's about time...
Shiroe?
Here we go, Chief Nyanta.
What are you talking about?
Thorn Bind Hostage!
A root?
That won't work on me!
Got you!
I-Impossible...
Our guild master...
Demikas
His entire HP vanished in an instant?
What did you do?
Healers, heal!
We can still—
Crap...
A single attack
from a swashbuckler could never
defeat a level-90 monk.
Even an assassin, which boasts
the highest attack power
among weapon-specialization
classes, couldn't do that.
Most likely, the secret lies in my lord's spell,
Thorn Bind Hostage.
Those shining thorns deal 1,000
damage to the target
for each hit by an ally.
Destroying all five thorns does 5,000 damage.
Even with the sword damage,
that isn't enough to beat Demikas...
Which probably means that...
Monk, Lv. 90
Thorn Bind Hostage has a
fifteen-second cool down.
Electrical Fuzz
Thorn Bind Hostage (seconds left)
Cast on Beat
Soul Weapon
The swashbuckler waited fourteen
seconds to begin his attack.
He hit nine times.
First five...
One attack takes .22 seconds.
And after he destroyed the fifth,
my lord recast the thorns.
And then he cut four...
I didn't see it clearly.
But that's the only explanation.
But is it really possible?
That must be why Naotsugu
used Castle of Stone.
He knew this was their plan.
For them to work together that way,
without coordinating ahead of time...
I could not do that...
Put away your swords!
We came through the Depths of Palm.
Akihabara and this city are no longer so far
apart as to prevent travel between them.
You're finished causing this kind of trouble!
We've won this battle.
Or do you still want to fight, Demikas?
Shut your mouth...
I'm sending you all to the Cathedral.
Over and over again...
Until you break!
Stop!
Seems you're the one taking a trip to the Cathedral.
Shiroe/ Adventurer
I won't forget you...
Enchanter Shiroe,
I won't forget your face!
Serara, you're coming, right?
Akatsuki!
Let's go.
Time to take off!
We're getting out of here!
My lord...
What is it, Akatsuki?
Nothing.
Let's go home.
To Akihabara.
Yeah.
On their way back to Akihabara,
Shiroe and his friends enjoy a moment of peace.
And then Nyanta reveals a shocking truth.
A secret about this world that will change
everything they thought they knew.
Meanwhile, young children
are spending their days
amidst endless despair in Akihabara.
Next time: Return to Akihabara.
Return to Akihabara
This is our reality.