This is for pushing me off my horse.
This is for leaving me unable to walk.
And this is for being born.
Sylvia-sama! Please, please stop.
This is cruel.
Cruel?
This Norma... this disgusting,
violent, antisocial monster
was my sister.
What could be any worse?
Apologize.
Say you're sorry for being a Norma.
Sylvia-sama is right.
Give us back our lives.
I thank you, Momoka.
You've given us this
opportunity to dispense justice.
It was I who exposed Angelise's
identity at the Baptism Ritual.
After sixteen years, we finally
rid the royal family of this pest.
All that remained was to wait, and hear that
she'd been sent to hell and
devoured by another monster.
But...
Much to my surprise, she did not die.
She might have continued to live on.
That's why, Momoka, I sent you.
It wasn't easy.
Did you think a mere maid would simply
be allowed to meet with a Norma
banished to the ends of the earth?
To see you fighting for Sylvia,
not even knowing you were being manipulated...
That was hilarious indeed.
No.
The Empress died in her foolish
attempt to protect a Norma,
and the witless Emperor was
executed for deceiving the people.
Executed?
Abominable Norma, Angelise,
who carries the royal bloodline.
With your judgment, the cleansing
of the royal family will be complete.
Tonight, this nation will be reborn.
The New Empire of Misurugi.
As Julio the First, Emperor of the Holy Empire,
I demand that this Norma be executed.
Goodbye from the Gallows
Pathetic.
That's what you get for lying to us.
Why?
Why do I need to be executed?
For what crime?
Shut up, Norma.
Don't you remember what you did to me?
I just kicked you around
a little and tied you up.
It's not a big deal.
A little?
That's awful.
It doesn't warrant an execution.
That's if you were a human.
You're a Norma. You're not human.
You made a lot of people
uncomfortable and unhappy.
So you're being executed.
You're telling me to die quietly over that?
Like a farm animal?
It's the Normas' fault.
That's why it's your fault.
Julio-sama says you get the death penalty,
so what's your problem?
Yeah!
Kill the Norma!
It's not her fault.
Angelise-sama didn't do anything wrong.
I found happiness thanks to Angelise-sama.
Hang her.
Why?
Why does Angelise-sama need to endure this?
Momoka.
You...
And those people...
You were the only ones...
...who accepted me without prejudice,
Norma or not.
Compared to that...
Hurry up and kill her.
I want to go home.
Get it on video for me, please.
These are the just, peace-loving
people of Misurugi Empire?
They're pigs. All of them.
They're all unreasonable, ugly, stupid pigs.
Why do we Norma have to go
through so much to keep them alive?
Angelise,
this is for you.
May the light protect you.
Hang her.
The light of the beginning
Sparkle, sparkle
Hey.
Wait.
The light of the end
It's...
The Endless Song.
That's Mother's song.
Don't ruin it, you Norma!
Guards, make her stop.
Sir.
Hey, you, that's enough.
The time flows from the hour glass
This guiding light...
It's all that Mother left me.
I won't die.
The many millions of lives...
I won't give up.
Try to kill me if you can.
Hurry up.
Sir.
This is goodbye, Angelise.
Angelise-sama!
Wh-Why... you!
Huh?
Tusk.
Guards, what are you doing?
Hurry up and restrain them.
That Norma-saver. What is he?
A rebel element.
A Norma-sympathizing terrorist.
Angelise-sama.
Momoka.
Release.
Kill them if you must.
Don't let them escape.
Momoka.
Yes, use these.
It's just like a Para-mail.
Get on, Momoka.
We're escaping.
Okay.
Get them!
Angelise, why you...
Thank you, Onii-sama.
You revealed my true identity.
Thank you, Sylvia.
You showed me the true,
filthy nature of human beings.
Goodbye, beasts from a rotten nation!
After her! After her!
It hurts!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Angelise-sama.
For what?
I feel refreshed, thanks to you.
Huh?
I realized I don't have
family or friends or a home.
Angelise-sama.
But anyway...
Ow!
Well? Are you awake?
Oh, good. Ange, you're safe.
You did it again.
What?
Did what?
Why do you keep burying
your face in my crotch?
Is it a habit? A tic? A sickness?
Sorry, ow!
Sorry.
Um, Angelise-sama, what is your
relationship with this person?
Um...
A special relationship.
What?
Of course! Otherwise, he wouldn't
risk his life to come help you.
Spring has come, even for
my tomboyish Angelise-sama.
As your top maid, there's nothing
that could make me happier.
That's not it.
Ow.
Why were you there?
I got a message from Jill.
Jill?
Commander?
She said not to let you die.
And this.
Don't you need this?
Thanks.
What are you, exactly?
I'm a Knight of Villkiss.
Knight?
A knight to protect you.
You can ask Jill for the details.
I will.
Can I ask you something, too?
Your hair's a beautiful blonde color.
S-So what?
You're blonde down there, too.
Die, pervert knight!
This is where we part.
Are you leaving?
There are things I need to do.
See you.
Thanks for coming.
Huh?
I would have been dead if not for you.
I was trembling.
I'd never heard such a
beautiful, enchanting voice.
It was a nice song.
I'd never heard it before, yet it
was somehow nostalgic and happy.
A strange song.
I'd like to hear it again.
Yes.
Thank you for saving Angelise-sama.
You're quite a lucky fugitive.
Getting a man to give you a ride home...
Jill.
There's something I want you to tell me.
Sure.
But...
Only after you're done reflecting.
Angelise-sama.
Wake up, Ange.
It's no use.
Do it.
Are you sure?
Quickly.
Yes, ma'am.
Are you awake?
Where am I?
You're being informed of your punishment.
Ange of Salia Squad, for your desertion,
you will be placed in the
suspension quarters for one week.
Your wealth and property
will all be confiscated.
This includes the Villkiss, of course.
You have to take responsibility.
You're a deserter, after all.
Hey.
Why?
Why did you run?
Huh?
We've been here since we were babies.
We don't know the outside world,
and there's no one waiting for us.
We don't have a reason to leave.
There's no place for us Norma to go outside.
So why?
Ultimately, it's because
she's different from us.
I shouldn't have trusted her.
Cold.
Shut up.
Hilda.
Stay away.
You're back, too, huh?
Are you okay?
I said stay away.
What happened to your face?
What did they do to you?
You ought to talk first.
Death sentence.
I was stripped down, whipped,
mocked, and hanged.
Not bad.
And you, Hilda?
I was beaten by fifty men.
Wow.
I took 'em all down, though.
Looks like you took quite a beating, too.
Shut up.
Did you meet your mother?
Who knows?
Oh.
No.
Mom!
Mom?
How strange. Are you depressed?
Huh?
Why would I—
Why would I be?
I thought of all people, Mom would accept me.
Huh?
I thought Mom would
forgive me for being a Norma.
But she didn't.
That's what it means to be a Norma.
There's nowhere outside for a Norma to be.
You have your friends here.
Friends?
I don't have friends.
Hilda's back.
Hey, why did you desert us?
Why wouldn't you talk to us?
We're friends, aren't we?
She never thought of us as friends.
You finally get it.
I never thought of you
as friends to begin with.
I was just playing along with you.
Are you serious?
Hey, Hilda.
You should have died.
C-Chris.
Let's go, Rosalie.
Okay.
I bought back all of Captain Zola's stuff.
I don't want you to have it.
I've lost everything.
My room, my money, my reason to live.
Everything.
I wish they'd just kill me.
No.
You can't die.
You're telling me to live?
That's right, you were royalty.
You talk different.
I'm a piece of shit at rock bottom.
And you still tell me to live?
Not to give up hope?
You do?
You'll stink if you die.
Huh?
So don't. Not in this tiny space.
That's it?
That's it.
How selfish are you, you bitch?
You're one to talk, loser.
Hope?
Do you honestly believe such a thing exists?
All that exists is persecution
and fighting DRAGONs every day.
Dammit. It's almost funny.
Those ignorant bastards are brimming
with prejudice and bigotry.
They hear I'm a Norma,
and they reject me like idiots.
Is it that bad that I can't use Mana?
Is it bad that I'm different?
It's all a lie.
Friendship, family, social bonds.
I can't believe I said friendship is
great and bonds are beautiful.
I want to beat myself up.
Dumbass.
Yeah, I am.
Dumbasses everywhere.
The world's rotten.
How about we destroy it all?
Huh?
I bet we could do it.
With our Para-mails and Arzenal's weapons...
How far do you think it is to the continent?
We'll run out of fuel, and then it's splash.
We just have to build something
that can make the trip, then.
What about food?
There's plenty of fish.
Or we could steal from
the humans, if we had to.
And materials?
We'd figure something out.
This world oppressed me,
humiliated me and degraded me.
I'll reject it myself.
This wretched, frustrating,
infuriating world.
It's bullshit.
Huh?
I'm saying it's bullshit. All of it.
Then let's destroy this bullshit world.
The whole thing.
Nice.
I wouldn't mind helping.
There are things I want to destroy, too.
Shine upon me
Upon everything
It spins and spins
Sadness and happiness
Quiz time.
Who's singing this song?
Ange-chan.
Correct.
It's a nice song.
Salia-chan's going to get angry.
Ange is a deserter.
How could you be won over by a song?
That's scary.
Welcome back, Ange.
Resonate now as your true form
Fleetingly, fleetingly...
Hey, Chris.
Above the clouds
Rosalie, you... you wouldn't abandon me, would you?
Eternally
Next Episode Preview
Seems like we're finally friends.
That was predictable. I don't like it.
No one's died in a while.
Normally someone dies when they become friends.
I bet next week—
I'm not your friend, dummy.
Dragon Song
Dummy! Dummy!