This is bad!
It's spewing fire!
I'd heard their fire-related organs
had become vestigial!
Elias...
It's an atavism.
It's become like the dragons
you'd read about in fairy tales.
Elias, he can still go home.
He wants to go home!
He has a place to go home to!
Please, teach me how to help.
Your selfish requests
are never for yourself.
It's all right.
That's why I'm here to begin with.
Thank you.
First, touch the dragon.
That way, you can absorb its magic.
And I'll absorb that
before your body breaks.
Okay.
Alice!
Right!
We're going to draw the dragon's attention.
Thanks.
Over here!
Take this!
This way!
Fire!
Merituuli!
You naughty boy!
We're going back home!
Now!
Here we go.
By the base of its neck.
There's a powerful flow there.
Chise!
It's trying to go outside!
Merituuli, distract it!
Gah, jeez!
This is bad!
It's going to cave!
Chise!
Damn it! Be careful!
Ruth.
Chise, are you ready?
Elias!
Ruth!
Right.
Huh?
The moon looks odd.
Chise, are you all right?
Ruth, how's Elias?
Singed, but he's fine.
We're on our way.
The river.
Wait, Chise...
You don't have to come with me, Ruth.
Go get the others and then come get me.
Chise, you better not be...
It's okay.
Let's go home together.
Idiot!
Chise!
Hey, hang in there!
Ruth...
Where's Chise?
To think it escaped...
Shannon-san...
Why...
How do you feel?
Can you get up?
I'll get up.
Wow.
It might be tight, but don't take it off.
It feels like it's going to burst.
Chise!
Angelica-san.
Jeez, you reek.
She beat you to her, loser.
I'd do the same to my own daughter.
I told you not to try to do
everything by yourself.
I already gave him an earful.
I wonder what she did to him.
How's the dragon?
And the other people?
Everyone went home.
The dragon is sleeping.
Thank goodness.
Elias, are you burned or anything?
You don't realize you're in
worse shape than I am, do you?
Actually, not really.
I know.
Well now, I can't let that lousy
explainer explain, can I?
Lindel-san.
Your arm...
I've forced you into an unenviable role.
I'm sorry.
I only did it because I could.
That's why this is so bad.
You've been cursed by the dragon's powers.
Cursed?
It's going to fester in your body.
It'll attack, torment, and hex you.
No human body could contain it.
Sooner or later, your body will fall apart.
How long will this body last?
I don't know. I'm sorry.
I see.
So...
I've lived with two curses so far.
I was forced to live with them.
One is this, my Sleigh Beggy body.
The other...
As long as I live, it'll
probably never leave me.
Taking on one more doesn't
seem like such a big deal.
You're...
He's angry.
Huh? That's him angry?
I'm sorry.
I can't ask you to forgive me.
Please don't apologize.
This is proof.
That I was able to think of
someone other than myself.
You do have the option of
living on the other side.
But that's...
I'll think about it.
Chise!
Are you sure?
You may cease to be human.
I'm ready for the worst.
I have to do what I can.
Are you sure you should be out?
You didn't tell anyone, either.
I prefer the air outside.
How can you be smiling?
When did you...
Since you tried to leave from the window
and flipped around in the sky.
That's from the very beginning.
My puppy seems to have lost her mind.
I was just pretending to be smart.
Haven't I told you?
You've forgotten to let me know when
you go out, yet you're still well-spoken.
I mean, you didn't reply to me.
I was straightening things out.
All day?
Yeah.
You always try to go somewhere by yourself.
Even though you always offer
me your hand and grip back.
Even though you ask me to come home.
And yet you're going to
leave me, just like that?
It's not like I'm going to die right away.
I don't think.
How was I so optimistic?
I knew this would happen to you someday.
I should have stopped you, but I didn't.
Somewhere inside,
I'm still thinking that you're always going
to be in that home, going forward.
That you would manage somehow.
It's funny.
What is?
At first, we were only using each other.
I never thought this would happen
just because we were together.
Before this, I was sure I didn't want to live.
But so many people helped me,
and I found out that even I could do things
that are worth being thanked for.
I'm not just waiting for someone
to tell me I'm welcome to stay.
I started wanting to stay and
wanting to do something.
Self-sacrifice.
You think that by destroying yourself,
you can earn the right to be here.
E-Elias...
I wonder.
I don't know.
I only did what I did because I could.
I'm not lying, it's just that
there are some things
about humans that we don't
understand ourselves.
Really?
Besides, your puppy is a stupid one.
Her body seems to act before her mind thinks.
Elias, will you help this idiot think of a way
that the two of us can stay
next to each other?
I don't have the same ability to
take action that you do.
But, I can go find out with you.
Please take me with you.
We have to find it.
We have to think
of a way to move forward.
Hello.
I'm Mariel.
Goatherder Mariel.
I'm what they call a witch.
A transaction at the auction?
Yup.
I asked for the dragon's blood
in exchange for money.
It doesn't look like that'll work.
I'm sorry.
You... Your arm...
I'm just going to take a look.
You're so overprotective.
Mariel-san...
Ouch.
Gleaming goddess of the land,
snake-shredding god of storms...
Lend us your hand, your eyes,
for the batting of an eyelid.
What is this thing?
It's so creepy!
A dragon's curse?
Say, do you have any interest
in becoming a witch?
Witches specialize in curses.
If you become one of us—if you join our
coven—we might be able to help you.
No.
Do you really have the confidence to
tell a woman what to do with her life?
Mariel-san, what do I need
to do to become one of you?
Chise.
For starters, join our gathering as a guest.
Soon, if you can.
Open that when you're ready.
I'll be awaiting your reply.
Goodbye.
Hello.
Unbelievable.
Such a young girl?
Here you go.
A card?
It's an invitation to my birthday party.
When's yours, Chise?
Today.
Today?
What?! Where's your party?!
Why aren't you holding a party for her?
Par... tay?
Jeez.
Okay, next year.
You better come up with some plans.
Next year...
What's wrong?
I feel nauseous all of a sudden.
I'm going to the washroom, so...
It's okay, I just came to give you the card.
Take care.
Chise...
All this, just as I'd decided
I don't want to die.
Let's join the witch's gathering.
You're okay with that?
Your apprentice might not
make it through the spring.
It's fine.
What matters more is to
take care of your health.
Thank you.
I have to think about my party next year.
A dragon's curse, huh?
Between my curse keeping me from dying,
and your curse leading you to death...
Things might work out pretty well.
The reality presented at the witches'
gathering was a cruel one.
The mage sets out to save the girl, but...
The only thing that can replace
a life is another life.