I doubt even Shiroe predicted this.
Looks like I won't be able to watch
over them from hiding anymore.
Normally, when you're expecting an attack
on a population center like a city,
you should try to take the fight
as far away from it as possible.
I understand.
Even if you succeed in repelling them,
the damage to the city and surroundings
could make life after the battle very difficult.
Yes!
We can't use telepathy, so keep your party
chat open and bring Isuzu here.
Roger.
The Red Night
The Red Night.
The enemy levels aren't high,
but there are so many...
But we have to go.
Will Roe 2 be okay?
She's stronger than we are!
This way! Hurry!
Don't let go of my hand.
Come on, hurry!
Serara?
They're surprisingly calm.
Come to think of it...
The Odyssey Knights...
They're going to fight the wyverns.
That's why the townspeople aren't worried.
We should hurry, too!
Miss Isuzu...
Miss Isuzu?
I wonder if the battle's already started.
What?
As long as I, Rundel Haus Code,
am here, it'll be okay!
The town of Safil, Miss Minori,
Miss Serara, and you, Miss Isuzu...
The passionate light of my orb of love will—
Now isn't the time to screw around!
Miss Isuzu...
What now?
Wh-What is this?
A Skylark Shoes spell.
At my level, you can't fly,
but it'll raise your movement speed
regardless of bad terrain.
So I'll be faster?
Indeed.
This is great!
I'm a genius, you know!
Don't get cocky.
Let's go!
Yeah!
What is this?
What's going on?
Over here! Look at me!
Over here!
Tohya... Tohya...
Look over here!
My turn next!
Anchor Howl!
Wow, Shunichi!
Let me play, too!
Me, too!
There's no plan, no teamwork... Nothing!
This is crazy.
They're building up as much aggro as they can.
What is this?
What are they doing?
I'm here!
Now, take me!
Damn.
I'm back already.
Go! Go!
This is my third time.
I'm jealous of your paper-thin armor.
What is this?
What are they doing?
That's an interesting idea.
That's a revival device...
Just like the Cathedral,
it acts as a beacon for people
who are coming back to life.
Someone must have invented it.
Quite impressive.
Sis Roe 2?
You look pale, young Tohya.
What are you talking about?
"Interesting"?
That's wrong!
It's insane!
No, it's not insane at all.
It's acting in accordance with this world's laws.
That's not what I meant!
And from the look of it, they seem
quite willing to donate empathion.
If they keep dying that often,
the gathering efficiency will go up a lot.
It's probably a big help to Genius.
What are you saying?!
They're dying!
We have to do something!
They seem to be quite willing, to me.
They desire death.
Their life flashing before their eyes, like a drug.
To be honest, I don't really get it.
This is Londark.
Nothing out of the order in the area.
The magic railways are functioning well, too.
Londark
Race/ Elf
Sorcerer, Lv. 92
Guild: Plant Hwyaden
Message from Lord Londark.
Nothing's out of order.
So even the loser from Susukino
is treated as a noble, as long
as he's an adventurer, huh?
Message from our nightshade servant scouts.
The Odyssey Knights are battling the wyverns.
They don't need to do that at all.
Send out our servants! Half of them!
Yes, ma'am.
Her condition is stable.
Okay, activating.
I'll start synchronization with unit 20.
Beginning EXP monitoring.
Opening party chat.
So it's complete?
We summon nightshade servants that act as vessels
for the minds of People of the Land.
And the experience points they gain
go to the summoner, right?
Seriously?
Of course, even if the servant dies,
it doesn't affect them at all.
In other words, we're giving the People
of the Land temporary immortality.
The way you laugh is creepy.
Don't interrupt me when I'm talking, kid!
Shut up.
Ow. Ow. Ow.
So you use this to raise levels?
That's pretty efficient...
Heh heh, this is fun.
It is not!
Interesting.
You adventurers would call it "power leveling."
Roger.
In ten minutes, we'll begin injecting EXP pots.
That's dangerous! Stop!
Miss Mizufa, Kazuhiko is requesting
that the injections be stopped.
Who cares about that hypocrite?
They're adventurers.
We're People of the Land.
What do immortals know of war?
It's where you go to die.
Right?
I don't understand why you people have
created such an inefficient society.
Hey, what's that?
What are you doing?
Nightshade servants?
Where did they come from?
No! Protect our shrine!
But when it comes to that,
the knowable world is far smaller
than the unknowable one.
The sum of what we can understand isn't
much bigger than the head of a pin.
So it isn't strange at all that I wouldn't
understand something, but...
Damn it!
Tohya!
I-I'm coming with you!
Wolfie!
Some of the People of the Land
couldn't get away in time.
Let's go, Wolfie!
Hurricane Slash!
You sure you don't want to go, Minori?
Who are you, Roe 2?
Where did you come from?
And where are you going?
That's the second time you've asked me that.
Huh?
What were those things?
They just showed up out of nowhere.
When we defeated them, there was
no sign of their psyche dissipating.
Are you okay, Miss Isuzu?
Rundel Haus Code
Race/ Human
Sorcerer, Lv. 58
Guild: Log Horizon
Move Speed Up
Psych Def Up
Aggro Down
Bonus Attack
Are you out of breath?
Yeah, I'm okay.
What about you, Rudy?
It's okay now.
Wait, Wolfie! I'm coming!
We're moving the battlefield to the city!
Nightshade servants have joined the fray.
Kill them all!
If we can ground the wyverns, they're easy prey!
Lure them into the buildings and kill them all.
All of them!
Don't let a single one escape!
Kill! Kill!
And then...
Die!
Hey...
Hey!
Tohya?
Party Chat
Tohya
Minori
Isuzu
Rundel Haus Code
Serara
Roe 2
Tohya!
Hey!
Why are you doing that?
You're...
I thought the Odyssey Knights were
supposed to protect people!
Why are you doing something so selfish?!
Everyone lives here!
We don't live here.
Th-That isn't what I mean.
There are other ways to fight, aren't there?
Why are you getting everyone caught up in this?
And... Why are sacrificing your own lives?
Stay out of this, kid.
You said we were sacrificing our lives?
But in this world, there is no death.
It's impossible to take your own life.
But that's...
We want to go back.
We're going home.
Did you know?
When you die, you can see your family.
When you die, you can see a
little bit of the old world.
You can see that world.
I'm sure that place is somehow connected to it.
If we die, and die, and keep dying...
Someday, we'll be able to go home.
That's not...
I was supposed to get married in the summer.
I was going to quit this game then.
I even went to an open house for an apartment.
I'm going to have a wife.
I can't keep playing around with this nonsense.
When my lease is up, I'm going to move.
She's a real handful, that girl...
She complains every day, because she
wants to leave her parents' house.
I need to get her out of there.
Mentally, she's a little weak,
so I need to take care of her.
You understand, right?
You also hate this stupid farce, don't you?
But there are lots of people
I care about in this world!
This world
is real, too!
Don't be stupid!
A world where you can't die?
That's... That's a game!
A world like that can't be real!
It's because people like you keep living...
Because not everyone is dying...
That we can't leave this world!
Is it that important
whether you can die or not?
Tohya...
Is that...
Hey, are you okay?
Get an ambulance!
The driver's not going to make it...
Tohya!
Can you see me?
It's Minori!
Have you ever died?
Did you ever die in the old world?
Were you ever so close to
death that you may as well
have been dead?
If you've got a problem with me, call the GMs.
If I'm at fault, they'll ban me.
Otherwise, you die, too.
I mean, I understand...
I understand wanting to go home.
But...
Miss Isuzu...
Even so... Even so, we...
That's right.
Everyone... Everyone... Everyone...
is alive in this world.
Even after he couldn't walk anymore,
Tohya was always smiling.
But...
It was because he knew he was powerless.
The world was just too big, too unfair.
And there was nothing we could do.
That was why...
Because he knew that, he tried so hard.
And even now...
Tohya is crying out.
Serara is casting Heartbeat Healing on
every Person of the Land she can find.
Isuzu and Rundel Haus are
protecting the people of the town,
as they come this way.
But even so, there's nothing that can be done.
If you're asking me in a place like this,
you must know the answer, right?
Who are you?
And who am I?
Where have I come from?
Where am I going?
After yesterday, I kept thinking about that.
I thought and thought, but I couldn't find an answer.
I just couldn't get over it.
I couldn't resolve myself to it...
Miss Isuzu...
But I was lucky, wasn't I?
To be born in that world,
to be born to my dad?
Because there was music there.
When I was sad, when I was in pain,
there were so many different songs.
I've always been helped by
someone else, haven't I?
Yet, this is so terrible...
Only forty-two?
That's terrible.
To be unable to sing when you want to cry,
when you're angry, when you're having fun...
Miss Isuzu...
That's why...
Wh-What's the matter?
Let's go, Rudy!
Go where?
Where are we going and why?
We're going to pick a fight.
A fight?
We're going to pick a fight with the god who
only made forty-two songs in the world!
I'm not going to stop until they cry and apologize!
Wait, Miss Isuzu!
Who is Roe 2?
Is that
what I really want to know?
No, that doesn't matter.
No matter who she is,
I want to be friends with her.
That's all.
So I... Who am I?
Where am I going?
Is that...
My wish?
Isuzu?
At some point the rain stopped,
and the town began to sparkle.
A song?
That's Isuzu's wish.
A huge rainbow stands over all the buildings.
Then my wish is...
Shiroe?
Right now, more than anyone else,
I want to show this scenery to you first.
My heartbeat is fluttering.
I want to be a person who can
open new paths, like Shiroe!
Come on! The magic will never fade, even now.
I am Shiroe's student.
And you are our big sister.
Don't be afraid of boredom,
and let's, let's, let's go out!
You came from far away,
and you're going far away.
But right now, you're here, with us!
Yes, what a wonderful Wonder World!
To a place we've never seen before,
I'll take your hand,
so let's go there now together.
On this battlefield, that's your answer?
On this battlefield, this is my answer.
Such a wonderful Wonder World
Even if nothing changes?
I can change some things.
Is scattered all around this town, too.
At a time like this, when Tohya
is lying on the ground?
Even if the future worries me,
if I'm with you, what a wonder it is!
He'll stand up soon.
I doubt your words will be heard.
But you're with us now.
I heard your wish.
Yes.
I like that, Minori.
I like it...
I'm your big sister, after all!
Yes.
Summon.
Yes, we have a duty, as those who go ahead.
It would be very uncool of me to knock
away the hand you're reaching out.
A big sister never abandons her little sister!
An element cluster gets more
stable the bigger it gets.
But it also behaves in a deterministic manner.
And as it does so, it loses little fragments.
That's not a bad thing.
It's natural to want all of humanity to be happy.
But that, in the end, is the beginning of sorrow.
You don't understand?
No.
Your words are so inconvenient.
This limited protocol even limits the upper
bounds of your thinking organs.
You live inside this unfair loneliness,
like it's the stone age?
That's unbelievable...
But the empathions are shared.
This is your style, right?
Miss Shogun,
your servants are being attacked.
What?
What's going on?
So we meet here?
Londark stands in the way.
He, too, is forced into action by the
twisted thoughts of this world.
Why are we here?
Nyanta cannot answer that question.
Tohya, Isuzu, and the young children
struggle as hard as they can
to find the answer.
Next time: Birthday Song.
Birthday Song
I have friends to run with me.