So return to the capital—
What the hell are you playing at?!
Curse you! How dare you take
Princess Melty hostage!
Hostage?
Fellow knights! Justice is on our side!
Destroy the Devil of the Shield!
Resorting to calling me a devil now, huh?
Raphtalia! Filo!
R-Retreat!
Oh no! Run away!
Wanna chase them down?
Nah.
Are you okay, Mel-san?
The Rising of the Shield Hero
The Devil of the Shield
Mel-chan...
Naofumi-sama...
How'd it go?
The altered footage has made its way
to the nearby towns and villages.
Entering them would be too risky.
I see.
Isn't that...
Why'd you try to kill the second
princess in front of us?
Answer me!
I have nothing to say to the devil!
That's a rosary from the
Three Heroes Church.
The Three Heroes Church?
Melromarc's state religion, which worships
the Sword, Spear, and Bow Heroes.
That reminds me... I saw it at the
church in the capital, too.
The three heroes other than the Shield, huh?
You'll learn just how grave the sin of
disturbing our country's order is!
What was that about?
Dunno, but it's probably another
one of the king's schemes.
Thanks to her stupid dad,
we're stuck here with nowhere to go.
My father can't be behind this.
Who else could've ordered it?
My sister, probably.
So she's trying to kill you and
take your place as crown princess?
But the knights who attacked you are
under the king's direct control, right?
It'd be natural to assume he's in on this.
Knowing them,
they want to frame "The Devil of the Shield"
for this whole plot, huh?
Father would never!
What makes you so sure?
Because Father is...
Why stick up for a scumbag like him?
You're wrong.
Mel-chan...
You're wrong!
Why won't either of you understand?
This is no time to be
fighting among yourselves!
Talk to Father one more time!
Naofumi-sama...
I... I can't face Mother like this!
Don't cry, Mel-chan.
I'm here for you.
I've decided.
Oh, Master.
Welcome back.
Listen.
We're going to leave the country.
What will you do?
I'll return to the capital
and talk to Father—
Bad idea.
If you went back now,
you'd only get yourself killed.
But if you decide to stay
with us, I'll keep you safe.
I can promise you that, if nothing else.
Come with us, Mel-chan.
Okay.
We leave before dawn.
Make sure you're ready.
Where are we headed, Naofumi-sama?
I've already got a place in mind.
Master!
You knew it had to be done.
We can't cross these mountains on a wagon.
We'll come back to get it
once this all settles down.
You promise to come back for it?
I promise.
Let's take a break here.
'Kay!
You all right, Second Princess?
Yes.
She must be tired.
Naofumi-sama, what made you choose Siltvelt?
The extra security.
There must be a reason they're trying
so hard to prevent us from going there.
It might be the perfect place to flee to.
Ah!
Right!
Father...
Tell me something.
What happened between you and Father?
What?
But Mother said to treat
the Shield Hero well.
Come to think of it,
I've heard nothing about your mom.
She's the queen of this country.
The queen?
That means she's higher than
Father in the pecking order.
The queen's more powerful?
Melromarc is a matrilineal monarchy.
You mean that king married
into the royal family?
What's so funny?
He acts like he owns the world.
So what if he married into the family?!
But he's adopted royalty?
Let's get going.
They're not over here.
They can't have gone far.
Find them!
Look for them!
Where are they?
They've blocked this route off, too?
Let's backtrack a bit.
There they are!
Over there!
They found us?
Can you run?
Yes.
We're making a break for it
past that big rock!
There's nowhere left to run.
You're are surrounded.
Cease your resistance and release
Princess Melty at once.
"Release"? It's not like I have her tied up.
Quit lying. We have all the proof we need.
Heroes, I'm perfectly fine, as you can see.
The Shield Hero kept me safe.
Hang on. Didn't Naofumi abduct you?
A dastardly plot was behind all this.
I asked him to take me and protect my life.
"Protect"?
What could the Shield Hero possibly
stand to gain by abducting me?
The queen told me...
This is the time for all of us to work
together to thwart the catastrophes.
Our world cannot withstand any
further pointless conflict!
Please put your weapons away.
As she says, this is a setup.
I'll tell you everything I know.
So—
You mustn't listen to him!
That devil possesses a brainwashing shield.
That accursed shield lets him take over
one's mind just by talking to them.
Wha... Who would believe such a lie?
The Three Heroes Church has found that
heretics who worship the Shield have
started popping up in the past month.
The Three Heroes Church again?
The Devil of the Shield called himself
"the Savior of the Heavenly Fowl"
and went around brainwashing
innocent people!
Sister?
Melty, you poor thing!
I see the Devil of the Shield
has already brainwashed you.
I see!
Then Raphtalia-chan and Filo-chan were
really brainwashed by Naofumi, too.
You're wrong!
We've not brainwashed!
If my shield had an ability like that,
we wouldn't be in this
situation to begin with!
But there's no guarantee that it doesn't.
Do you have any proof to convince us?
Naofumi, hand over the second princess.
I promise you she won't
be harmed in any way.
Well, if we can avoid fighting,
that might be for the best.
You're absolutely right, Ren-sama!
Melty's safety comes first!
Come, now.
Let's go home together.
No...
If I go back, I'll be killed!
Come to me, now.
Please!
Help me!
Ren, I appreciate your offer,
but I don't trust that woman
with the second princess.
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
Melty is my dear sister.
I—
You want to be crown princess so badly
that you're willing to kill your sister?
You'll say you're undoing the "brainwashing"
and kill her when nobody's looking.
I bet that's what you're planning!
I did promise to keep you safe.
Filo!
'Kay!
Go!
Air Strike Shield!
Not so fast!
I've called for backup.
There's no escape for you now.
I can't get this off.
Filo-chan!
L-Let go of me!
Huh? I-I've lost all my strength!
I had the royal alchemists make this
so you could stay an angel forever.
As source of thy power, I order thee.
Decipher the laws of nature and slice
through my target like a blade of water.
Zweit Aqua Slash!
I won't miss next time.
Unhand Filo-chan!
Myne-san?
Are you trying to kill Princess Melty?!
She's the one who attacked first.
Zweit Hellfire!
Zweit Fire Arrow!
What the hell is wrong with you? Stop!
If we can't undo her brainwashing,
she'll have to die!
Naofumi-sama...
Can I leave Mel-san to you for a bit?
Sure.
Step back a little.
Come forth, Rage Shield!
Filo-chan...
That shield!
Bring down the hammer of justice
on the Devil of the Shield!
Fire!
Not on my watch.
My turn now!
Annihilate the Devil of the Shield
and his party!
Wait, don't!
What's that light?
What the hell's going on?
Ren...
I know you'll be able to figure out
what's really going on here.
Wait, Naofumi!
Disarming Successful
Yay!
Wait!
She's on our side.
That's one of the Shadows, an espionage
squad under the queen's direct control.
Shield Hero...
This is the first time I meet
you in this form, I daresay.
Wait, "daresay"?
Allow me to get straight to the point.
Shield Hero, you are requested to meet with
Her Majesty the Queen, I daresay.
With the queen?
This commotion has a
deep-rooted cause, I daresay.
We would like your help, I daresay.
This abduction is a setup by those who
find your accomplishments alarming.
Oh, great. More pains in
the ass to deal with.
And? What would I gain by meeting her?
You'll understand once you do, I daresay.
The queen's in the opposite
direction from Siltvelt.
Hey, Second Princess,
do you know this country?
Oh yeah, Second Princess,
you can use magic, huh?
...me that.
What was that, Second Princess?
Stop calling me that!
What's gotten into you?
I have a name! It's Melty!
So why do you keep calling me
"Second Princess," Shield Hero?
Don't treat me like some outsider!
Hey, you call me "Shield Hero," too.
If you don't like that,
I'll call you Naofumi.
So you call me Melty, too.
Come on, Naofumi!
Straight to first names?
Gotcha, Second Princess...
Hey!
Melty.
Happy now?
One more time.
Huh?
Say my name one more time.
Melty.
And don't you forget it.
Also, thank you.
What's up?
It's nothing!
What's that smell?
Everlasting Memory