Stop playing around.
"Hello.
I wasn't sure how to begin,
but for my first word, a greeting is appropriate.
Hello, world.
Hello, Shiroe.
'Shiroe, of Log Horizon.'
When I heard that name, I felt so strange.
Because your memories are still within me.
Just like you are beings who have
come to this world from another,
we have done the same, as well.
My name is Roe 2.
Top Secret
New and Unconfirmed Monsters
Investigation Report
We call ourselves the Navigators.
From your perspective, we are sentient
intelligences from another world.
And at the same time, I'm also your little sister."
What should we make today, Nyanta?
Let me see...
Working hard, Shiro?
I know you just got back,
but can you tell me the details
about this new type of monster?
Stranger
Stranger.
And that's what happened.
The genius of marriage, Camaysar.
That was more like marriage fraud than marriage.
The West Wind girls were the
ones who first found him?
Yeah.
We have access to the girls' information network,
so we're really good at that.
Yes, it's amazing, my lord.
You also knew about it, Akatsuki?
No, not at all.
So what happened?
Well...
A second form?
We'll attack immediately.
Give them to me, adventurers.
Nazuna!
Right.
My beautiful brides...
Ittou Ryoudan!
You guys are as crazy as ever...
We'll show no mercy to anyone
who touches our girls.
Yes, we show no mercy, my lord!
Did you also help, Akatsuki?
No, not at all.
So what is he, exactly?
Is he an enemy?
An enemy, huh?
Since they're attacking us, we have to fight.
Then we just need to protect the town, huh?
Leave it to us.
Leave it to me, my lord.
Ah, thanks.
Come to think of it, he was a weird enemy.
Weird?
Since we came to this world, he's the
enemy most like those in Elder Tale.
Yeah, like it was too easy...
Be my beautiful bride...
It was like a game.
It felt hollow.
Like I was fighting from
behind a computer screen.
Fried rockfish is the best!
Sir Isaac! Sir Isaac!
How can he jump so high?
Sir Isaac, how can he—
Just call me "Isaac."
But...
You know, uh...
I'm Iselus.
Iselus, can you try to be a little less formal?
You're an adventurer, Sir Isaac.
And you're training the knights of Maihama.
I'm just doing it because I want to.
And I'm told that, in Akihabara,
you help my sister, Lenessia.
Taking care of her is the elite glasses guy's job.
He's on a trip now, though.
Then is he an adventurer, too, Sir Isaac?
I told you...
Isaac,
should we let them take a break?
And I told you not to be so informal!
See, Sir Iselus.
Just talk to him like I do.
All right, I'll try.
You guys are seriously...
What's wrong, Isaac?
It's kind of cool! Isaac!
He's so cute!
I swear, you guys, I'm going
to use Sword of Pain Black!
At a glance, he looked like a
normal Person of the Land.
And he was able to judge the quality of ores.
Ever since the Apocalypse,
the prices of material items
have depended on their quality.
So lots of adventurers started
to ask him for appraisals.
But let's say he picked up a rock from the ground
and said it was top-grade ore.
Rock
Effect: Rock
Just a rock
For some reason, everyone would believe him
and buy a simple rock for an incredible price.
In other words, he was a monster
that destroyed things' measures,
their weights, lengths, and values.
The genius of measures, Bagris.
What tipped us off was the "ate a ton
and still felt hungry" incident.
After an investigation, we found out what he was.
We put together a quick half-raid team
and went to get rid of him, but...
I should be able to gain ample empathions from this.
Lightning Straight!
Genius of Measures
Bagris/ Genius
Rank/ Half Raid
The problem was that he could control
distance, speed, skill damage, and even targets.
It wasn't even a fight.
Give me your empathions now.
Just when everyone was about to give up...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
With the help of the Kunie Clan,
I've finished our secret weapon at last!
Oh, you did it?
This is the end, Bagris.
I'll stop your evil deeds.
With...
this Source Vessel!
Source Vessel
"Source Vessel"?
Is that a ruler?
It's a ruler, yeah.
Definitely a ruler.
It is a Source Vessel.
It is a magical device that measures all
things, and fixes their dimensions.
We sealed his abilities, and then...
Tiger Echo Fist!
Something like that.
There was one more.
Tell everyone, Seine.
Oh...
I'm Nyanko Tavern's guild master, Seine.
There was another matter
besides the Genius of Scandal
I told you about last week.
The poisoning incident before the Scale Festival.
The monster behind it, Sislau,
Genius of Plague
Sislau/ Genius
Rank/ Party
called herself the "genius of poison."
At the time, we decided she
might be a new monster
from the expansion pack.
My lord...
Are you tired, my lord?
Why do you ask? I'm not.
Oh...
Shiroe!
Are you done for today?
Minori...
Is your part-time job done?
Yes.
I got a lot of presents today!
"Again today," you mean.
Want me to hold them for you?
I'm just fine.
Air Glasses
Because...
Ta-da!
Magic Bag!
Did you design that, Minori?
That's right.
It really holds a ton!
Wow, Minori! Your feminine power is sky-high!
Okay, let's buy some things to take back.
My lord, I want a red bead bun.
Why not get a gelatin for once?
Do you have a problem with red bean buns?
Well, for some variety...
It's not just a regular red bean bun today.
It's cherry tree-scented red bean.
A seasonal item.
I want strawberry shortcake! I do!
Tetra?
Get off my lord, you half-idol!
I'm not a half-idol!
I'm a complete, galactic, perfect idol!
And Shiroe said he likes it when I hold him!
I did not.
I'll kill you.
Buy me some cake!
Gelatin!
The red bean bun is waiting, my lord.
I'll have the fried rockfish!
Me, too!
Okay!
Hello, Isaac.
Okay.
You've been a lot more relaxed lately.
Oh, please.
You aren't the type to worry about that.
I'll have a cold one and the fried rockfish.
Right!
Another business trip?
Don't say that. This is one of our restaurants.
Of course I'll stop by to see the kitchen.
I could've sworn I told you that this was
a branch of Shopping District 8, Isaac.
I told you to stop that.
Here you go.
Top Secret
New and Unconfirmed Monsters
Investigation Report
It arrived from the Round Table.
Supposedly, it's a report on an
enemy called the "Geniuses."
I've heard of them, but what are they?
I couldn't say...
And it seems like the People of the
Land are gearing up for war.
Things are looking bad everywhere.
The wyvern attack on Safil was
an after-effect of Minami
power-leveling People of the Land.
That might be why he sent us to Maihama.
Shiroe's quite the villain, after all.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah...
It's been almost a year since the Apocalypse.
It has.
I'm sure there are people who want to go home.
Some want it so badly, it's driving them insane.
I understand how they feel, but...
It's hard...
You're helping out?
Yes.
You're so good at this now.
What did they say?
Lately, even if you don't have the
skill, you can do simple cooking.
That isn't all.
It's done!
This is beautiful.
How about the new potatoes?
They've all been boiled, and they're ready to go.
You've gotten a lot better.
Because you taught me!
Maybe we'll have tea while we wait
for the vegetables to cool down.
Okay!
Is it good?
Yes. It's nice and warm.
Today's a very quiet day.
It makes me want to take a nap.
You look like you're having a good time.
I am!
I see.
Are you doing well, Nyanta?
I am.
Okay.
Are you glad you came to this world, Serara?
Um, yes.
You are?
Yes.
Well, I can't see my mom and dad anymore,
and lots of hard things have happened.
But lots of good things have happened, too.
And...
I have a dream of what I want to be, and a future...
You do?
Yes.
I see.
Children aren't invited to be born in this world.
However, all children become young people
and can be reborn by their own will,
choosing their own lives.
Meow...
I'm sure you can make any
dream you have come true.
B-B-But it's a long way away!
Oh, I don't mean I'm going
to give up or anything.
But whenever I look at Isuzu and Minori,
I feel like I'm lacking a little...
Like I'm not good enough.
I think I need to get better at being who I am
before I make that dream come true.
I have to be a fully-grown version of me.
That's what I want to become.
Serara...
Yes!
Just a little is fine.
Every little bit is important.
I'm cheering you on.
So is everyone.
What would Kanami do?
When I think about it, I was lucky.
At the very start, when things were
toughest, everyone was with me.
I'm grateful to Naotsugu and Akatsuki. Really.
You can say "thank you," my lord.
When did you get here?
I flew here.
By running along the roofs.
You're really starting to become a ninja.
I'm your ninja, my lord!
So what's bothering you?
Whenever something bothers you,
you get wrinkles up here that make your
forehead look like an old man's.
Do I?
You do.
Oh, there you are, Shiro.
I'm seeing something on my idol radar!
A night rendezvous!
So are you coming up with another plan?
That's right... Are you coming up with a plan?
Do you need a cute, attractive, and talented idol?
You need a guardian, too, don't you?
You two are in perfect harmony.
Oh, my!
Wh-Wh-What are you saying, Shiro?
The two of us are as one now!
We're like "Tetsugu"!
Tetsugu
Roar
Anchor Howl!!
The impenetrable armor of a Guardian,
Pah!
protected by my responsive heals!
My love for him shines each time he's struck.
In other words, Naotsugu's entranced by my love!
I am not.
You're such a shy boy, Naotsugu.
Well?
It's been almost a year since the Apocalypse.
There are a lot of adventurers
who haven't been able to adapt to
this world, and want to go home.
But there's no way to go home...
Yeah.
So Eins thinks we should save those people.
He wants to take the money
from wealthy adventurers,
and give it to everyone, right?
Will that really work?
I doubt it.
The only way for them to really be
saved is for them to go home.
And...
War's coming to Yamato.
Yeah...
And one of the reasons for that
is our arrival in this world.
Then we need to find a way to get back home.
There's something I need to tell you all.
I'd like to hear it, too.
Of course.
Log Horizon
Older Members Meeting
Be Sure You Knock
A letter, huh?
A love letter?
I wish.
It was from Roe 2.
My second character.
The other body you left on the test
server when this was a game?
The rumor was that the test server
was on the moon, right?
The moon?
Could they even write letters?
And how did it get here?
Minori brought it to me.
She met Roe 2 during their travels.
And... According to this letter,
Roe 2 is the person I've been looking for.
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
Why did we come to this world?
It doesn't make sense, right?
If this really is another world,
there's no way it could be this similar
to the Elder Tale we know.
But it's unbelievable that a game world
became reality, and we went into it.
It's impossible.
As far as we know, technology
hasn't advanced that far.
Right.
And the changes since the Apocalypse
don't make any sense, either.
In this world, physical laws and the
game's laws are all jumbled up.
It's like two different rule sets were
just mixed together randomly.
It's only a game in the weird parts, yeah.
I get the feeling that we weren't
simply sent to another world.
And in this world, there must be a
third party who can explain it.
Someone who isn't a Person of the Land
or a player like us, who can explain this.
They brought us to this world?
What did the letter say?
Roe 2 took over my unused second character...
That is, a body without a soul,
and came to this world.
Who is she?
She calls herself a "Navigator."
A sentient intelligence from another world.
You might say a person from another
world or, perhaps, an alien.
They're artificially created creatures.
Observers
And there are two types.
"Observers" like Roe 2,
Harvesters
and another type called "Harvesters."
These Navigators were created to harvest
a resource called "empathions."
Empathions
What are those?
Unfortunately, she didn't say.
But their society had run out of this
resource and begun to decline.
To resolve this crisis, another world was needed.
And we were created to investigate other
universes that could be searched.
Roe 2 and her kind came here via
what they called the "Match,"
Match
the same way the Apocalypse brought us here.
Then does she know the Apocalypse's cause?
No, it looks like they don't
understand everything, either.
So did they get these empathions?
Well...
"We believe you to be sentient
intelligences of a rank 3 or higher.
Minori and her friends proved that.
Thus, the rights to this world's
resources belong to you.
The Harvesters are given orders
to prioritize harvesting,
but we Observers are tasked with searching.
I don't know if my brother, Shiroe,
will be the one to read this message,
but I recommend acquiring a method
of communication with the moon.
Our community is on this world's moon,
and we are observing the situation.
If you wish to return, we can help you.
Lastly, I'll warn you about the Harvesters.
They are Navigators like us,
but they are intelligences equivalent to rank 2.
In this world, they're using
bodies prepared on the moon
of monsters with powerful combat capabilities.
I recommend extreme caution."
The Harvesters are most likely
the monsters called "Geniuses."
Then why are they after us adventurers?
I don't know.
"PS, Minori...
I tried writing this seriously,
like a big sister would.
May your warm empathions light your future.
From your big sister.
From your big sister."
There are still things we don't understand,
but if we can make contact with
Roe 2's companions on the moon,
we may be able to find a hint to returning home.
Are you going to believe that letter?
I think we can.
You have some reason, right?
When I died in the Abyssal Shaft, I saw it...
That was a beach on the moon.
After reading this letter, I'm sure of it.
That wasn't a dream.
I... I saw it, too!
Those sparkles I saw with you...
I remember, my lord.
If we can get back there,
we can go home!
Lenessia's little brother, Iselus,
the Prince of Maihama.
His birthday party is to be used to introduce him
to the world as the next Lord of Maihama.
But even during this celebration,
the presence of war draws near.
A cowardly shadow is after the young boy's life,
and a black blade of rage howls at it.
Next time: Isaac and Iselus.
Isaac and Iselus
I have friends to run with me.