Oh, man! Oh, man!
Taking off in the middle of the
night is pretty exciting!
Well, you guys were late last time.
Being an idiot must be nice.
You can even sleep on a bus.
What'd you say?!
We'll be arriving at our destination
early in the morning once again.
Ukai-kun and I will take turns driving.
Sorry if I nod off.
Thank you!
It's the middle of the night, so not so loud.
Oh, sorry... Habit.
Do you guys have everything?
Make sure you double-check.
It'll go quickly if you fall asleep.
Hinata and Kageyama haven't really
talked to each other lately...
I wonder if I can...
I wonder if they'll be okay.
All right, Ryu!
All right, we're heading out.
Let's show 'em what we're made of!
Heck yeah, Noya-san! Let's do this!
Just shut up and get on.
Haikyu!!
Hey, hey! Where's the Skytree?
Episode 07: Moonrise
Huh? The Skytree?
Oh! Is that the Tokyo Tower?!
Huh?
That's... Just a normal transmission tower.
What the hell?
Are there no transmission towers in Miyagi?
Pretty sure I've heard
that conversation before.
The transmission towers in Tokyo all look
like the Tokyo Tower to us countryfolk!
That's a rash thing to say.
Also, we're in Saitama.
So that's not... the Tokyo Tower?
So we're gonna be at a
different school this time?
Apparently, the summer training
camp is always at Shinzen.
It's nice and cool here...
But lots of bugs around.
Hinata! Did you grow any taller?!
Lev, shut up.
That's a pretty rude thing to say.
Like I could grow in two weeks!
I grew two millimeters.
All right.
We're gonna switch out members
constantly this time around,
so be prepared.
Right!
Karasuno             Fukurodani
Let's try for no penalties!
Noya-san!
Yeah!
Nice receive!
A chance at a quick...
That weird quick's coming!
Just drop it off... Just drop it off...
Just drop it... off!
It was too short...
What the heck?
That's not like you at all.
I'm sorry.
Damn it...
It feels different when
I'm in an actual match.
All right! One more! Nice serve!
Surprised?
I'm sure you've realized it.
Kageyama's toss is completely different now.
Got it!
This time, it went too far.
His left hand?
He immediately tried to
save it with his left hand.
Nice, Hinata!
He used to panic if anything was off.
Nice, Shoyo!
The toss dropped again...
He's...
He's different now.
Don't mind!
We couldn't help that one!
We'll get the next one!
Hinata and Kageyama
Fukurodani           Karasuno
aren't the only ones who've changed...
Out! Out!
Tsk.
Azumane-san's tsks have so much impact.
That's fine! Keep it going!
Hmm... Splendid.
They're splendidly...
Ah!
...not in synch at all.
Did Karasuno...
Sorry!
...just try to do a synchronized attack?
Sorry! Cover!
Leave it to me!
Jumping from the back zone and
into a libero's jump toss?
Ah!
I jumped too far!
Hey, what's up with those guys today?
Are you okay?
Damn it!
Karasuno            Fukurodani
I wonder what happened to Karasuno.
Maybe they're in some kind of rut?
I think it's the exact opposite.
Because they're crows, they're omnivorous.
It doesn't matter if they're
deep in the mountains,
Kabukicho Ichibangai
or in the middle of Kabukicho.
They eat everything there is to eat,
and take advantage of those
stronger than them to survive.
It looks like they're
Nice receive!
Left! Left!
in the middle of evolving
at an incredible speed.
Bokuto-san!
Yes!
All of them but one, it seems.
Karasuno            Fukurodani
Thank you!
The penalty this time
is Shinzen's special "refreshing sprint
up the grassy hill," apparently.
All right.
Ready... Go!
Here.
Th-Thanks.
Sugawara-san, here.
Nice serve!
Shinzen and Ubugawa are
still in their first set?
Yeah.
Their serves are awesome!
Left!
Whoa, like, fabam!
Serve and block.
Destroy the opponent with
the serve, then try to limit
their opponent's attack space and block.
That's the most ideal method of
attack next to a service ace.
Serve and block...
Damn you, Tarako.
Broccoli...
Stop that! You're being rude to food.
What?!
We amazingly lost all our games.
It's actually sort of refreshing.
I haven't done that many sprints
since Coach Ukai was coaching.
I'm gonna borrow the tablet from Ukai-san
so we can review the
synchronized attack video.
All right.
Sure thing.
I'm gonna go hit some serves.
I need way more practice.
Serves! I'll hit some, too.
Ah, Tsukki! I'm gonna go hit
some serves. Would you—
I'm gonna go take a bath and go to bed.
I-I see. Um...
What?
I was just wondering
if you were gonna practice
anything on your own...
We've already been practicing
more than anyone wants.
Going all out in practice isn't
gonna solve everything.
R-Right...
That's true, but...
Oh, hey, you. Karasuno!
You with the glasses!
Would you jump some blocks for us?
Oh, actually, I'm done for the night.
If you'll excuse me.
What?!
There's no point in practicing
spikes without a blocker!
Come on!
Why does it have to be me?
Why not someone from Fukurodani?
There's no limit to Bokuto-san's
spiking practice,
so everyone runs away pretty quickly.
I'm too busy whipping this guy into shape.
I said I'd jump some blocks!
Shut up!
If you want to continue as a
regular on Nekoma's team,
you need to actually be able
to receive the ball!
He may not look it,
but this guy's one of the top five
spikers in the country,
so it'll be great practice.
So he somehow didn't make it
into the top three, huh?
Don't mind.
Don't raise me up just to
let me get knocked down!
Besides, if you're a middle blocker,
you should practice your blocking a bit more.
Gymnasium #1
We couldn't get one quick right today.
I need to practice.
If we don't manage to make this
somewhat useful by next month...
We'll be in trouble.
Oh! Are you going to practice quicks?
Balls? Want some balls?
Why is she making it sound like
she's offering us a drink?
P-Please!
Yeah.
Haikyu!!
One more!
Straight!
So smart and calm...
But...
Yes!
You just beat all of one blocker.
Shut up!
Well, how about two, then?
Bring it on!
Is he dead?
Here we go!
Four eyes, make sure you
keep that straight in check!
Yeah!
Damn it!
You know, four eyes, you're great
at reading attacks, but...
Your blocks are pretty weak.
Your arms are so frail that
I'm scared I'm gonna break them.
You need to stop the ball like you mean it!
I'm still a growing boy!
I've just started gaining muscle
and getting taller.
Talk like that, and the little shrimp
is gonna hog all the glory.
You guys play the same position, right?
Huh?
I don't think that can be helped.
The difference in natural talent
between me and Hinata is too great.
Ah! Are you practicing spikes again?!
Want me to block?! I can block!
Hey, Lev!
Get your ass off the ground! Time to receive!
Gah! Yaku-san!
What do you mean, "Gah"?!
Come on, get up! You rested long enough.
Well, looks like I'll be in the way,
so if you'll excuse me.
Yeah, I'm totally set!
Hey!
So I'm ready for some blocking practice...
Looks like you stepped on a mine, Kuroo-san.
Oh? Then let's see what you've got.
You pissed him off.
At long last, Kuroo-kun, the master
of provocation, has failed.
Well, I wouldn't have thought that...
Thought what?
The
Unknown
Karasuno's Shrimp is definitely
strange and a threat,
but in terms of technique and
experience, he's like a baby bird.
Plus he's really short.
I never would've thought guy with glasses,
who's far taller and much smarter,
would not only think they're not equal,
but actually think the shrimp
is above his level.
Damn it. I forgot my pads.
Gymnasium #1
One more! One more!
I think the timing's a bit too fast.
Really? Then I'll slow
it down one tempo next.
Here we go!
Sorry. One more.
This is just a club.
Right.
Let's go!
Why do you put so much into it?
It's because you put so much into it
that you suffer later.
Cafeteria
Hey, Tsukishima.
Eat up! Or you're not gonna last!
Nishinoya-san...
At least your stomach's big.
What'd you say?! You little brat!
Here.
Th-Thank you!
Your true self will pay!
H-Hey! Stop! They're gonna break.
Hey, Daichi's gonna get mad!
Karasuno               Nekoma
Go!
Here you go, Hinata.
Thanks!
Everyone!
Fukurodani                                                                                             Fukurodani
Ubugawa
The parents from Shinzen High
gave us some watermelons!
Whoa! That's awesome, Lev!
Can I get one more?
Sure.
Thanks.
Huh? Tsukishima-kun, is one slice enough?
Yeah. Thanks for the food.
I ate way too much once
and got a stomachache.
Sorry, by the way.
About what?
I think I might have pissed off
your glasses guy yesterday.
What?
Wow... Tsukishima actually
helped out with free practice.
Hinata, you suck.
Even if you cornered him into it...
So, what did you say?
I provoked him and said he was going
to lose to your shrimp over there.
I've definitely noticed that Tsukishima
seems to feel inferior to Hinata somehow.
It's Hinata's job to steal the spotlight.
It's my job to keep trouble from happening
while Hinata's rotated into the rear guard.
It's the usual situation, isn't it?
I'm not sure if this is
relevant, but my sister...
By the way...
Huh?
I thought I heard the name during
your training camp matches,
but does Karasuno have a guy
named Tsukishima right now?
Yeah.
The glasses kid. He's a pompous little shit.
Do you know if that Tsukishima
has an older brother?
Huh?
No idea. He's not the type
that'd mention that himself.
When I was at Karasuno,
the same time the boys' volleyball
team was the strongest...
When the Little Giant was there?
Yeah. I thought there was
a really tall guy named
Tsukishima back then, too.
Huh?
Tsukishima has an older brother?
Oh, but I'm not sure.
They could just have the same
last name and not be related.
Hey, we're about to start!
Right. Let's go.
Yeah.
Oh, sorry. One sec...
Karasuno                Nekoma
Go!
This is rough...
Not at all!
I can still do at least ten rounds!
Uh, how about we win?
Yamaguchi, your serve's getting much better.
Th-Thank you very much.
I have to improve my success rate.
Doesn't it bother you, Azumane-san?
What?
That feeling of immense talent
creeping up behind you.
Yeah, well... I guess
I can say I'm not at ease.
I'm sure Hinata's still obsessing
over the title of ace.
That might be true.
Maybe that's why he said he had to change.
But because of that, it seems
that all of us got fired up, too.
If you're not careful,
Hinata's probably gonna bite you
again because he's too focused.
Oh, you mean when we both went
to spike and he jumped into me.
We're in the same boat.
Our positions kind of make Hinata our rival,
so we probably notice more than others
how much he's grown from the
baby bird he used to be.
But I don't plan on losing to him.
Left! Left!
All right!
Karasuno                         Ubugawa
Hey, you totally slacked there.
You need to at least jump!
Well, aren't you alert. My bad.
Tsukishima, it's your serve next.
Sensei, what do you think of Tsukishima?
Right.
I think he's taking this seriously.
Nice serve!
I feel like Tsukishima gets a passing grade,
but never tries for 100%.
It's coming left! Left!
I'm not asking for him to
become more passionate,
Cover! Cover!
#4! #4!
but if he not going to give his all,
I'm gonna have to change regulars.
Nice receive!
Center!
Left!
I need players who can
win a match on the court.
He's the tallest and essential to the team.
All right!
If Tsukishima could become
a strong blocker,
our defense level would go up a lot.
I see.
Cover! Cover!
Karasuno               Ubugawa
Leave it to me!
Got it!
Sorry!
I'm so sorry!
Everyone's so motivated.
Everyone's more motivated now
than I've ever seen them before,
but sometimes it's almost scary.
Collisions like the one other day
can definitely lead to major injuries.
It's coming on the left! #1!
We're counting on you, Asahi-san!
It's a bit short...
It's my ball!
Better than expected...
Whether you're on the same team or not,
the tension you feel as rivals
is essential for growth.
Nice kill, Asahi-san!
That was an awesome spike!
Thanks.
However, if the team became lawless,
everything would be lost.
Karasuno's ace managed
to hold them together.
Maybe I didn't need to worry after all.
Go!
You okay, Tsukki?
You can go on ahead. I'm fine.
Okay. Then I'll go...
More free practice!
Another magnificent total loss today.
He's as standoffish as usual.
Tsukishima?
Yeah.
It really seems like he'd be able
to do much more if he tried, right?
Much more?
Yeah, a lot more...
His 188 centimeters is such a waste!
Hey, four eyes.
Would you help us out with
spiking practice again?
I'm sorry. I'll pass.
Oh. Oh, really? Kuroo.
Aw, man...
I haven't even said anything yet!
Why?! You know the ace from Fukurodani?!
No.
Why did you refuse? That's such a waste!
Shut up.
Unlike you, I don't have endless stamina.
What the heck?
What's Tsukishima's problem?
The ace from Fukurodani invited him
to practice and he declined?
That's unbelievable!
You know, Hinata...
What would you say to Tsukki right now?
Huh?
I mean... Like you did with
Kageyama and Yachi-san.
I wouldn't say anything.
Well, I can't tell if Tsukishima
even wants to play volleyball.
There's no point in trying to get a
guy to play if he doesn't want to.
Damn it! And he's so tall, too!
If I was that tall, I'd do this and that...
Tsukki...
...doesn't hate volleyball,
I don't think.
If he did, he wouldn't have come to Karasuno.
What about you, Yamaguchi?
What would you say to Tsukishima?
Lev! Show me how to spit
watermelon seeds really far!
First, you purse your lips
like you've got a blowgun.
The angle you're gonna spit is 45 degrees.
I see!
And then you bring back your
body like a whip, and...
I accidentally swallowed them!
Episode 08: "Illusionary Hero"
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"Illusionary Hero."