She's so annoying.
And she's so loud, even
though she's tiny.
Who does she think she is,
telling me what to do?
Screw her. Die already.
Oops...
What are you mumbling about?
N- Nothing...
The person staying in the Wave Room
says he won't be needing breakfast.
That damned novelist seriously
thinks it's our fault.
I have an idea. Why
don't we eat his fish?
But I need to keep my stomach empty...
You got something planned?
I-I need to prepare myself mentally.
Huh?
Morning.
Oh, morning.
The revenge meal...
What if she adds stuff like lizards
in addition to the taros?
I'll eat it.
The lizard?!
Won't you?
If you don't like her.
No, I don't dislike her...
It's just that she looks
you right in the eye
when you're speaking to her,
and her voice is really loud...
Episode 3: Balut
I'm a bit afraid of her...
Let's go in.
She...
She betrayed me!
Huh?
I didn't prepare any meals for today!
She'll pay for this...
I'm going to get yelled at ag--
Th-This much taros...?!
Spinach?!
But where is *she*?
That's right.
At that very moment, I was in the
middle of an outrageous situation.
Wave Room
Let's see...
Ah.
Okay...
This goes in that hole.
Dammit!
I was going for a turtle shell
bondage, but it's so difficult!
Umm...
You need to start over here.
O-Oh!
Thanks.
Why am I being taught by
the girl I confined...?
Hey-
Don't worry. I won't
scream or anything.
Oh, you won't?
But first things first.
Why did you tie me up and gag me?
You saw my draft, didn't you?
"The Hot Spring Waitress
and Her Bubbly Training"?
Yeah, to tell you the truth,
I'm actually not a best-selling author.
Figured as much.
I can't write...
I just can't. I can't
put my heart into it.
I thought I'd come up
with some good ideas
if I were to live the cooped
up life I'd always dreamed of.
I was planning on winning an award
with that and make a turnabout, but...
So that explains the draft.
I started writing a sex novel in
order to pay for the bill here!
Sex novel...?
But I can't write even that!
I have no talent!
My life is over!
Come on, don't be so depressed!
It's impossible for one to tell that
they themselves have no talent.
Then...
Can I ask you for a favor?
Huh?
What...?
She wasn't in the hall, either.
Any luck, Beanman?
Disappearing in the
middle of cooking...
I get the feeling this is related to
that novelist's draft going missing.
You mean, there's a
criminal living here?!
Maybe she doesn't like us anymore...
What?
I was horrible to her.
Maybe she went back to Tokyo...
That's quite enough.
Huh?
We won't have any more
customers tonight.
We'll be cleaning places
we don't usually clean.
But Madam Manager...
Oh right, Nako...
M-Ma'am?
You don't have to hold back.
I'll teach you everything, and not
only things related to the inn.
Seems like you're loud even
in situations like these.
Please, don't say that!
Do you still think I have talent?
Is my voice really that loud?
W-Well, I wouldn't say it's "small."
But how can you write about me?
O-Obviously because I've
been watching you.
Don't get me wrong!
I never peeked at you
in the bath or anything!
I'm serious! I swear on the bible!
It sucks, right?
Isn't it boring?
Well, it's too early to judge whether--
I-I want to sparkle!
Don't worry.
Let us rub you up, and you'll
be sparkling in no time.
B-But that's...
Didn't you say you wanted to sparkle?
Huh?!
I've been so out of shape lately!
Mr. Jiroumaru, isn't this...
So, today's cleaning...
Don't need it! Not today!
Okay.
And I was also asked to check
the lightbulbs in this room...
You're persistent!
You guys misplaced my draft
because you're caught
up in stupid things like that!
But...
For crying out loud...
I'm sorry!
I guess it makes sense for there to
be low-class waitresses at
a low-class hot spring inn.
Back off already!
Hey! Why did you show yourself?!
Because you're taking it too far!
Ohana...?
There's no other choice!
Now I'll have to confine you too!
What?
Guess I have no choice but
to tie this old man up-
Blush.
Huh?
Why are you...
No, no, no!
There's no way I can
tie all of them up!
Hang on, Mr. Jiroumaru!
I see.
So he was the culprit behind it all.
That creeper!
I let him off for the
sexual harrassment because
he said he was famous!
He always complained
about our food as well!
Madam Manager, just call
the cops on him already-
The cops?!
Wait.
We can't make a decision
until we hear the truth
from that customer himself.
Are you saying you don't believe me?
That's not it.
But more importantly,
I don't want to doubt a customer.
What? But we saw it all!
Beanman was about to be put
in a turtle shell bondage!
Either way, we'll...
Huh?
That's our truck.
Wait, then who's behind the wheel?
Get back here!
I'm such a good-for-nothing.
Look at me, following the rules
even in situations like this.
I can't break out of my shell...
You! Open up!
Hey!
Son of a...
Huh? Wait-
Mr. Ren!
Get him, Mr. Ren!
Beancurd skin.
What?
What do you say we add that
to next month's menu, Madam?
Sounds good.
Try making it.
Huh?
Kaneko Tofu Shop
This situation isn't as
tense as I'd imagined.
I know, right?
Huh?
Excuse me...
Oww!
No, it's nothing...
There he is.
Where did he go?
You okay?
Somewhat.
Isn't that-
Over there?!
Where?!
Kissuiso
He isn't in here!
Dammit!
Up there!
Hey!
It's dangerous up-
Stay away!
Please, stay away!
I've...
I've been acting all high and mighty,
thinking that I had you all fooled.
But I was seen through long ago.
By the Madam Manager.
I'm so ashamed.
I was taking advantage of her goodwill.
I should just disappear-
It wasn't goodwill.
Huh?
She only said what she said
because it's a part of her job.
Do you honestly think she's
that nice of a person?
H-H-Hang on.
You just ruined the mood.
I'm sorry, sir. She's absolutely right.
Yeah.
Huh?
Madam!
In this occupation,
you cannot doubt the
customer even if you realize
their true background.
Besides,
if you really pay the bill
after winning an award,
we'll be even.
No one knows what the future holds.
As long as you win the award-
No, as long as you don't
give up on winning it,
there's still a chance.
You're still our customer.
H-Hey, that was too cool!
But I can't!
It's impossible!
Im-poss-i-ble!
I'm talentless!
I'll never be able to win an award!
Mr. Jiroumaru!
I... don't want to die!
What?
Hey, we're lending him a hand.
Please hold on to that, Ohana!
Nako!
Hey, don't-
Holy...
Is she okay?
Of course she is.
She used to be called
"kappappa" as a child.
What?
K-Ka?
If I recall, she's been having swimming
lessons since she was three.
Okay, let's go meet up with them!
Nako!
You go girl!
You okay, Nako?
Minchi...
Yeah.
Let me go grab you a towel.
Nako.
I can't even manage to die.
I'm such a...
You're still spouting crap like that?
I'm seriously such a--
You *do* have talent!
I want to sparkle!
What the heck are you talking about?!
It's a line from something
Mr. Jiroumaru wrote.
You, Nako and I are a part of the cast.
What?
And...
We're rubbing each other in
inappropriate places
with the mop, but...
We're what?!
That novel was perverted, yeah,
but you understood things about me even
I never realized myself!
It's not like I even want
to work, but I was upset.
I wanted to do *something*.
Even I didn't understand
where those feelings were coming from.
But you knew, and you told me.
I wanted to sparkle.
Ohana...
I don't know much about novels,
but I think it's important for
writers to have a keen eye.
You taught me something
about me I didn't know.
You're a true novelist!
I'm so sorry!
Mr. Jiroumaru is going to
start working at the inn now.
Hey!
He's going to write to get
the award while paying off
the inn bill with labor.
Anything you eat at the beach
tastes better than usual!
It's not ready yet, sir!
Geez, come on...
Nako!
You were the MVP today!
That was so cool!
Do you want me to teach you?
Huh?
I-I'm sorry!
Being able to swim is sort
of useless, isn't it...
No way! I don't think so at all!
I can't teach you things related
to the waitress job very well,
but I'm a bit confident
about swimming, so...
Hey! Supper's ready!
Let's go!
Okay.
Smells delicious!
Eat to your stomach's content!
Oh, spinach.
Yeah. Spinach goes
well with small fish.
Let me serve you.
Here!
Enjoy!
She ate it!
Ohana?
She really ate it!
I seriously don't get her sometimes.
Yay!
She ate it!
Balut!
B-
Balloot?
Dear, she's...
The splitting image of Satsuki.
Did Mr. Jiroumaru move rooms yet?
Yes.
It used to be a storage
room for futons,
but he'll just have to live with it.
Something wrong, Denroku?
So you knew.
Knew about what?
Knew that Ohana would set things right.
They say, "Sticking goes not by
strength but by guiding of the gully."
Waitress Handbook
This is so difficult!
Time for a break.
I wonder if she's still
practicing her peeling.
An insult other than "Die!"
"I hate you." -> But maybe this is too common...
"Stay away from me!" -> But maybe this isn't harsh enough...?
"Balut" -> Smelly and ugly!
Smelly and ugly!
We have a winner!
Balut!
"Balut."
"A duck egg with a nearly-developed
embryo inside."
"It's a dish, but it's disgusting."
"I can't stand them and I never will."
"That defines how I
feel about her too..."
It's incredible how much
effort she put into this...
It's actually kind of refreshing
to be hated *this* much.
Another inconsiderate text from Mom?
Guess I know where mine came from.
From: Ko
I'm sorry I didn't see you off. Good luck with everything, Ohana!!
Ko...
It was a mysterious feeling.
When I was still in Tokyo, we
texted each other all the time.
But now, it made me so happy.
"Good luck," huh?
Yeah.
I'll try my best.
In order to sparkle here.
Minchi is really popular with the guys.
They're actually more
warmhearted than anyone!
Who are you calling a "plateau girl"?!
Episode 4
Grey Heron Rhapsody