Louise...
Louise, come here.
Even in your dreams,
you want to see me.
I guess you love me so much,
you just can't help it.
Now beg.
Say, "I am my owner's puppy."
Huh?
So that's what he wants me to do.
What a naughty dog.
But I'm a kind master, and
since it's just a dream,
I'll let that one slip.
An unobstructed, flat plain...
And now the mountain range...
Louise, what was that for?!
T-Tabitha?
What are you doing here?
Guarding him.
I'm Saito's knight.
Stay out of this!
This dog here,
dared to touch my breasts and
compare them to a flat plain!
I would be happy about that.
Anyway, it's the truth.
Though mine are indeed a mountain range.
You were awake, weren't you?!
What's important to
remember here is that both
the plains and the mountains
are equally wonderful!
Saito, are you really sure about that?
Well, maybe the mountains are
just a tiny bit more wonderful...
Saito, are you all right?
Professor Colbert!
What are you doing up so early?
I actually came to tell
you something important.
All of you.
It appears that
we're all off again on another
trip aboard the Ostland.
Queen Henrietta has ordered
us all to Romalia.
Romalia?
Louise of the Holy Land
Miss Vallière, you must be so
happy that we're going to Romalia.
Of course! Romalia is the
center of the Brimir faith.
A pious follower of Brimir like
myself is happy just to go there.
Then if you're happy enough as it is,
may Saito and I go on a date?
That's a no.
You scrooge.
The Fire Dragon Mountains
are so beautiful.
Strong and indomitable, just like you.
I-Is that so, Miss Zerbst?
This truly is Halkeginia's
most renowned mountain range.
It sure is beautiful.
Tiffa.
You're sighing a lot.
Is something wrong?
No. I was just wondering
why the princess
would possibly summon me to Romalia.
What do you mean?
She's called for Louise, too.
They're letting us use this ship
and calling it an educational school trip.
We're all here.
The Brimir worshipers never
thought highly of the elves.
It's natural for a half-elf like
you to be a little nervous.
I suppose.
Don't worry.
Nothing will happen.
If push comes to shove, I'll protect you.
Thank you, Saito!
Ladies and gentlemen!
Look!
It's Romalia!
Ladies and gentlemen of the
Order of the Undine Knights!
This journey is a secret mission
for Her Highness the Queen!
No matter what dangers we may face,
so long as I remain your captain,
you have nothing to fear!
Was this really something that big?
Who knows?
Dear students of magic,
I'd like to greet you
at the end of your journey and wish
you a warm welcome to Romalia.
It's been a while, Saito.
Julio!
I forgot you're a Romalian priest.
That's right.
I was asked to properly welcome you.
All right, I'll leave them with you.
I'll show you to the guest house.
Please follow me.
Saito, I'd like you to come with me.
Along with Miss Vallière and Miss Westwood.
Look, it's Romalia's biggest cathedral.
May I ask why only us three have been called?
It is the express wish of our queen.
Hers, and another's.
Another?
Louise, Saito,
Tiffania,
thank you for coming.
Your Majesty!
Was it really okay for us to come here?
Aren't the Tristain coffers pretty empty?
Saito!
Don't worry about money.
Romalia's covering the expenses.
I wish I could be so naïve!
What do you mean?
Julio.
You're being very rude to our guests.
My apologies, Your Eminence.
Seeing them made me feel like I
was back at the academy again.
Your Eminence?
Saito! Put your head down, now!
You are in the presence
of His Holy Eminence!
And who is that?!
So you're Saito Chevalier de Hiraga.
Every bit as unconventional
as the rumors say you are.
It certainly is true that you've
come from another world.
Please, raise your heads.
I'd like to see your faces better.
I am Vittorio Serevare, also known as
Pope of Romalia, Saint Aegis the 32nd.
I'm very pleased to meet you.
Both the Void Mage and her familiar.
Your Eminence!
How did you...?
The tales of your bravery have
reached even Romalia, Miss Vallière.
I've always known that you are the
bearer of the legendary power.
This is such an honor, Your Eminence.
And then you, Miss Westwood.
You're probably not aware of this yourself,
but you are also a Void Mage.
It seems that you have
not found a familiar yet,
but your Mind Wipe magic
is more than enough proof.
So that means I'm like Louise?
And there's another one of you as well.
I am also a Void Mage.
That's right, all three of
us possess the legendary magic
given to us so that we may lead others.
We are kindred spirits.
We are kindred spirits with Your Eminence?
And he is my familiar.
I am God's right hand, Windalfr.
I can freely control the beasts.
That puts you and me together.
You and me?
The three Void magicians
and their two familiars
are in one place at last.
Now I will ask Her Royal
Highness to take over.
Louise.
Tiffania.
We will soon be celebrating
the third anniversary of
His Holiness's ascent.
His Holiness requests your
presence as his shrine maidens
and he will also ask
you to pray with him.
He's asking us?
But what does that have to do with the Void?
We hope to garner the attention
of the fourth user this way.
The fourth?
You know him, as well.
Joseph, the king of Gallia.
The Joseph who...?
That's right.
He is an inhumane man who killed
Tabitha's father and destroyed
her mother's heart.
It's still not dinner time?!
Not yet.
I'd like to show that same
King Joseph something.
Perhaps he will change his
ways if he sees that the other
three Void Mages have joined forces.
He's the one who did something
that horrible to Tabitha!
How could we ever hope to—
If it does not happen,
Halkeginia will face a crisis
as it has never before.
Crisis?
It is the duty of Void Mages
to join forces in order to save Halkeginia.
The reason that the Void Mages
are here points to the fact
that an event is approaching that needs them.
The fate of the world is,
quite literally, in our hands.
The fate of the world?
Please consider whether or not
you will be shrine maidens.
No, Your Highness.
There is no reason to wait.
I will do it.
I will become His Eminence's shrine maiden!
Louise...
Ladies and gentlemen of the
Order of the Undine Knights!
Let us restore our energy for tomorrow!
To Her Majesty, Queen Henrietta!
To His Holy Eminence!
And to us, Undines!
Quite the noisy crowd.
They're just lively, Jacques.
Why don't we make a toast, too?
An excellent idea!
Let's drink to future riches!
Jeanette, order something.
First we've got work to do.
Get everything ready.
Sure, sure.
You're no fun.
I'm off, Big Brother Damian.
Okay, take care.
Louise, are you really going to do
what the Pope's asking?
Of course!
A noblewoman never goes back on her word.
But you know what that guy did to Tabitha.
We have no idea what he's going to do!
Yeah.
You may be right.
But listen, Saito.
I really want to do it!
I mean...
You mean you're totally gaga over him.
No, I'm not!
Yes, you are!
"Oh, Your Holiness!"
Any follower of Brimir would
be starstruck to meet him!
I can't help it!
All I'm saying is that you may have answered
before properly thinking it through.
That's not true! I did—
Well, maybe it's fine for you,
but you might have put Tiffa on the spot.
She's not a follower of Brimir.
She was probably all confused,
having just been told
that she's a Void Mage.
She doesn't have a familiar yet, either.
So that's what this is about.
You don't care at all about how I feel.
All you care about are Tiffa's feelings.
Yeah, but Tiffa...
It's just Tiffa, Tiffa, Tiffa!
If you like Tiffa so much, why
don't you just become her familiar?!
You know, if I could, I would!
Fine! Then there's no
reason for you to be here.
Get out, now!
You don't have to tell me twice!
It must have been quite a shock to suddenly
find out you're a Void Mage.
I still can't believe it.
There's something I want to give you.
Come here.
This...
But why?
This ring was originally passed
down in the House of Albion.
You're the last one of that
blood, and you possess the magic.
This belongs with you.
Why is Saito such an idiot?
Who is that?
I do want to be of help to everybody...
But what should I do?
Miss Westwood.
Professor Colbert!
You're staying here, too?
No, I actually came here on an errand.
I see.
Goodnight, then.
Goodnight, Sir.
Professor Colbert!
May I ask you a favor?
Please show me the ritual
of summoning a familiar!
I just don't get what her problem is.
All I was asking her to do was
to think about Tiffa a little.
Then she says "Well then, why
don't you be her familiar?"
After she was all swooning over the Pope!
You know, Saito,
in all honesty, it makes me happy to hear
that you're fighting with Miss Vallière.
Still...
Yeah?
Since I do acknowledge Miss
Vallière as a rival for your love,
I can say that I don't believe she would
ever be swooning for anyone else.
It's not even possible!
I guess you might be right.
Of course I'm right!!
That means you've got to think this over!
You have to think about why
it's so important for her
to honor the Pope's request so quickly.
Sure, but I've got no clue.
You really don't?
She's the one who was called Louise the Zero.
After she was told that she
could save the world if
she tried hard enough,
do you think she could not try?
I'm going to go talk to her.
Thanks, Siesta!
This is the only time I'm
helping you, Miss Vallière.
The Mirror of our Founders, you're certain?
Shall we take some other goodies, too?
We could get some good money for these.
Don't touch anything but
what we were ordered to get.
I knew you would say that.
I'm glad I followed them.
Too bad Saito's not here.
But against these two,
I'll be fine, even by myself.
Who's there?!
Help! Thief!
Don't do anything stupid.
Brother, she's...
Someone, help!
Did I just hear something?
Someone!
Louise?
Please, come here, Saito!
Let's get out of here.
But...
The mirror is enough for now.
Who are you?
Saito, they're thieves!
What did you do to her?!
Relax.
It's not what you think.
I'll deal with them.
You take that and run.
Damn it!
You're always treating me like a kid!
Stop!
One's coming from above, partner!
Hey, partner!
Looks like this guy's quite skilled.
So what?! I don't care!
The Summon Servant is not
such a difficult spell.
Focus your spirit and then call
on your yet unseen familiar in your heart.
All right.
My name is Tiffania Westwood.
Pentagon of the five powers,
obey my fate and summon my familiar!
You're not bad.
However...
Don't take this personally.
Louise, now!
Huh?
Explosion!
The gate is...
Levitation!
Saito!
Professor, thank you very much.
It was no problem.
Louise,
were you really planning to fight
those guys all by yourself?
It's your fault for leaving
me alone like that.
You're the one who told me to get out.
I was so scared!
But I guess as a Void Mage,
I am responsible for this world.
So I figured I'd have to try, even by myself.
Jeez, you're so stupid.
Who are you calling stupid?!
Okay, maybe not stupid, just reckless.
How dare you talk to your master like that?!
You're right.
You're my master,
so you need to take advantage
of your familiar.
It's your duty to depend on me.
The weight of the world
might be a little lighter if
it's shared between two people.
Saito...
It's not what it looks like, Tiffa!
This dog doesn't care who he
gets it from when he's in heat!
Hey, you're the one who started it!
What?! Are you going to say I asked for it?!
You did!
You're the one who closed your eyes
and made the kissy lips!
I most certainly did not!
Yes, you did!
Did not!
Did too!
Yesterday, I could've sworn
I saw Saito disappear into that portal,
but I must have imagined it.
Did too!
Did not!
Whenever I see him, though,
my heart starts beating so fast!
Why?
I'm telling you, I was not
asking you to do that!
I've got to work hard as
the Pope's shrine maiden!
But I guess I could grant Saito a little
time alone with me before then.
Next episode: Aquileia's Shrine Maiden.
Aquileia's Shrine Maiden
Wait, who or what is Lemon?