I have a reliable friend who can
protect you in my stead.
You do?
I am Ganba Red!
How could I lose my sight
at such a crucial moment?!
Is this it for me?!
You can't give up!
We still have this.
Then we're not finished yet!
Now is the time to release our power!
Congratulations On Your Win!
Shirahamazaka High's
Tanaka Taichi
This is the sword
that holds all of our hopes.
The nationals, huh?
The Eternal Holy Blade!
Turn courage and tears into strength!
Nervous?
No.
I've imagined being here a million times.
Now face your colossal foe!
That's so great.
I'd love to stand on a grand stage someday.
You mean for archery?
Forever! (Forever!) Forever! (Forever!)
No.
It's horses for me.
Horses?
I'd like to be a jockey.
I want to race to the finish ahead of the pack,
on a horse running at breakneck speed.
That sounds cool.
Does it?
Hey! Put a sock in it, you guys.
And it's not time for congratulations yet.
This is only the first round!
We're trying to put you in
a champion's frame of mind!
Right?
Darn right!
Are you going to waste Wien's efforts?
What's with your uppity attitude?
Wakana!
Let's cheer him on together!
I brought you maracas.
Now face your colossal foe!
Go!
Sorry, I'm not feeling very well today.
I think I'll go home.
Episode 5
Throwing Away and Holding On
I wonder if we were being too loud.
You do tend to go all out.
You think?
Hey, why did you start playing badmin?
Don't shorten it.
Would Shirahamazaka High School's Tanaka Taichi-kun
kindly proceed to his designated court.
Good luck!
To arms!
What does that mean?
Taichi, are you ready?
It's a battle cry used during peasant
uprisings in the Edo period.
Yes.
Willing to sacrifice their lives,
they'd pour a nutritious
drink into a sake cup and—
Konatsu!
Here you go.
Excuse me, sir?
Yes?
Please enjoy.
Can I help you?
Do you have this in pink?
Pink?
Sorry, we only have what's on display.
Red would work.
Are you sure?
Oh, hey!
You're home early.
Yeah.
I'll take this one, please.
Certainly.
Beg your pardon, but could I get some tea?
One moment, please!
I'll make dinner tonight.
Ah, thank you.
The register is right this way.
Shirahamazaka
Match won by Wada.
Being in the top eight is pretty amazing, right?!
Yup!
He needed to place in the top
four to go to the championships.
Aww, he was so close!
Tanaka-kun's taking a long time.
I'll check on him.
Buy me a green tea, too?
What?
I mean, good luck!
Hold my bag.
Are you crying?
Of course not!
I was just doing some visualization training,
while it's all still fresh in my mind.
I never want to lose again.
Haruka-san?
Yes?
How long has Tanaka-kun
been playing badminton?
Since around third grade, I think.
He wanted his own racquet the
second I joined the club.
Oh, yeah?
If you've been playing since grade school,
why didn't you go to a high school
with a badminton program?
No particular reason.
I could ride my bike to Shira High and,
at the time, the club had more people.
There was also a player I really admired...
So that player's the reason
you took up badmin?
Stop oversimplifying things!
Oh, hang on.
Here you go.
Oww, that's hot!
They sell hot ones even in the summer,
so you don't catch a chill.
Jeez!
What are you doing?
Yeah, what the heck?
Hey, Sawa?
Do you think Wakana's okay?
She has seemed a bit down lately.
The water's super cold, Mommy!
Wakana-chan?
It is you!
Mrs. Okita...
Call me Shiho.
Had my first spill in a long time.
You're a lifesaver.
But let's keep this a secret from Sawa, okay?
She'll just say I'm getting
too old for this stuff.
Spunkier every year, I tell you...
You seem quite close.
Boy is it hot.
Thanks, you can put it down anywhere.
You must be drenched in sweat.
Would you like to take a bath?
No, thank you, I'm fine.
All right.
Oh, yeah!
One second.
Where was it...
Schoo
Albu
Here!
What is that?
I happen to be an alumni
of Shira High, myself.
Back then, Shira High or Kama High
were the only choices for schools around here.
Found it.
Isn't this your mother, Mahiru-senpai?
Congratulations On Your Victory, Choir Club!
That's her!
I knew it.
She was one year ahead of me.
Here's Takakura-senpai.
Isn't Takakura Naoko the vice principal now?
I'll make a nice copy of that,
so come pick it up sometime.
Thank you!
Were you all in choir together?
Yep!
They took that photo after we won
the national competition.
Your mother never told you?
She wasn't told about her illness?
No.
Because she was in the midst of entrance exams.
I see.
Excuse me a moment.
I'll do that.
I'm back.
Dad, want me to make dinner tonight?
Uh, yeah, would you?
Slow day?
No, it's very busy!
Be more careful.
Sorry, sorry.
I was so scared when
they told me you collapsed.
Everyone's overreacting.
But you'll be discharged soon, right?
I'm going to get a cloth.
You need to take better
care of yourself, Mom.
I bet writing a song with
you would perk me up.
Look!
You could tell me your ideas,
and what you think about—
I don't have time for that!
Exams are coming up!
Then why don't we sing?
I'm not in the mood!
You won't be able to put in your
best effort if you're so grumpy.
And whose fault is that?
Now you're mad at me...
I'm sorry.
Maybe she would've gotten better
if we'd written a song together.
Can you stop fooling around and teach me?
That's not Chorübungen!
When you were little,
we sang together like this all the time.
So what?
Studying is very important,
but music will still be there long after exams.
I hope music will always be your companion,
so never forget how much you lov—
Enough!
None of that matters
if I don't pass my exams!
Strained back?
Yes.
Then if you do Saturday and Sunday,
I'll be there on Monday.
No problem, we have to help each other.
Yes.
Talk to you later.
Bye.
Was that Mr. Touno?
Yeah. It's his back again.
I was thinking of helping him
in the fields next week.
Okay.
Hidehiko-san has an office job,
so he can't suddenly take time off.
It'll take two or three days.
That okay?
I'm not a kid, you know.
Maybe I'll get sushi delivered for dinner.
What?
Dad?
Yeah?
I've been thinking about
getting rid of the piano in my room.
It's not like I use it anymore.
It'd be nice if someone with a
passion for music could have it.
I think that's what Mom would want.
I see...
I only need a little player for my CD's,
so I could get rid of all my extra stuff
and use the space for a bed.
That's true.
I'll make some calls tomorrow.
The Kanto region will see
cloud cover this morning.
A strong low pressure system is currently
moving north from the Ogasawara Islands.
This means that from around noon to evening,
weather conditions will deteriorate.
Hey, if your classes are going to run late,
you should probably take a raincoat.
The wind's supposed to pick up, too.
I know.
Wakana.
Someone's coming to take the piano today.
Okay.
I labeled everything,
so it's all ready.
All right.
Junk
It's done!
What's that?
A goldfish?
It's a whale!
That's a goldfish! A goldfish!
It's a whale.
Goldfish!
No, it's a whale!
Okay then, we'll compromise
and say he's a dolphin.
Does the dolphin sing?
He sure does!
I'm leaving now.
I'll be heading out at 3:30.
If you need me for anything, call.
They don't have the
greatest reception out there,
but you know Touno's number, right?
You can order sushi for dinner, if you want.
I'll be fine.
Bye-bye.
Wakana?
Want to head to club practice together later?
We're celebrating Taichi
placing in the top eight.
Sorry, I have to do some shopping,
so I can get home before the rain starts.
Wakana!
We're celebrating the
badminton competition now.
Tanaka's treat.
Sorry, I'm kind of busy today.
Huh?
I got cake for you, too.
A gigantic strawberry one!
Can't you eat it before you go?
Sorry.
See you later.
Something's definitely up with her.
Maybe she doesn't like strawberries.
I don't think that's it.
Maybe I annoy her?!
That might be closer to it.
I'm home.
Food Money
Dora?
Dora!
Mom!
Hey, Mom!
I told you to put my raincoat out!
Sorry, I'll get it now.
Don't bother.
You should prepare your things yourself.
Do you have the test schedule?
Yes.
You're not forgetting anything?
No.
Bye, then.
Good luck!
Dora?
Wakana!
What?
Don't forget this.
I don't need it.
Go back inside before you're soaked.
I'd like to walk with my daughter, Wakana.
In times of sickness and times of health.
In happy times and sad times.
I truly believe I can write
a song like that with her.
For me, a song is a way to express love.
And Wakana has taught me
so many important things.
If I could put all my feelings for her
into a song, and then sing that song with her...
If I could hear Wakana's song,
then my life
would be absolutely complete.
I couldn't say, "I'm leaving."
Or "I'm sorry."
Or "thank you."
We'll never sing together again...
I'm sorry...
Mom...
Wakana, no!
Wakana, what do you
think we need most?
Episode 6
Laughing and Remembering
Sakai.
Hey, Wakana, are you free now?
Thank you.