The Second Dish
Episode 3
Shrimp, shrimp, shrimp!
Scallops, scallops, scallops!
The Director's taken up the brush!
Who is the victor?
Which one is it?!
The victor is Candidate Kurokiba Ryo!
Kurokiba Ryo
For Tadokoro's dish, the director didn't...
Yeah, he didn't go bare-chested.
Honored guests,
this completes today's program.
The third and fourth matches
will be held tomorrow.
Have a safe trip home.
Let's go get Tadokoro.
Good idea.
Huh?
Yuki?
Megumi!
Huh?
Kurokiba-kun was really scary.
Yeah, I totally get it.
You were like a rabbit
being hunted by a wild dog!
Well done, Tadokoro Megumi.
Hojo-san.
It was amazing!
I didn't think you'd get that far
against Kurokiba!
Great match!
It wasn't just a fluke that you
passed the prelims, huh?
Oh, um...
Good work today, judges.
Your cars are waiting for you.
That way, please.
Grandfather?
Is something wrong?
No... It's nothing.
I need to go to the washroom.
Hmm...
Tadokoro Megumi, was it?
It seems the girl possesses
even greater power
that still lies dormant within her.
I went "bare" before
I even realized it.
The 92nd class is indeed
a generation of prodigies.
The Generation of Prodigies
Hayama-kun!
What are you doing out here?
Nothing much.
I just wanted to feel the night breeze.
Hey, Hayama-kun,
don't get too bent on winning this.
I'm already so proud of you
for passing the prelims!
It's a great stage.
Just try to enjoy it, okay?
A smile like that's only going to get me
even more determined to win.
I will reach the top, no matter what!
Bro, did you pack everything
you need into the bag?
Oh, do you have the victory charm I gave you?
I do.
I bought this pillow yesterday that's
supposed to give you a good night's rest.
Let's do some aromatherapy
to help you relax, too!
Calm down, Isami.
I'm gonna pray that you'll be able
to give it all you've got tomorrow.
Don't worry, little brother.
I've been honing my skills
so that I can face off with Yukihira
again in the main tournament.
Just watch, Isami.
Our Italian cooking will not be defeated!
Please watch me, Erina-sama.
I will be sure to return to you with a win.
You're a good girl, Hisako.
I have high expectations.
For Jun...
For Isami...
For Erina-sama...
I have to win!
We're now on Day 2 of the
Autumn Elections Main Tournament.
This day will determine the final four
to proceed to the semi-finals!
I wonder what heated battles we'll see today!
Soma-kun's late.
Oh, c'mon!
He should be seeing this
to prepare for his next match!
I couldn't get him to wake up.
Maybe I should've just dragged him here.
He pretty much pulled an
all-nighter the night before.
But I heard he's at least left the dorm,
so I think he'll make it.
Hey.
We meet again, Yukihira Soma.
Oh, you're the guy from the prelims.
93 points!
Block A Ranking
Hayama Akira
Yukihira Soma
Kurokiba Ryo
Marui Zenji
Ibusaki Shun
Candidate Yukihira scored 93 points!
He's now in second place!
Oh, sorry, transfer student.
I didn't see you.
There's no need to glare
like that, Yukihira Soma.
I'm just thinkin' we can go to the
tournament hall together, that's all.
Huh?
Yeah, sure, whatever.
Okay, hang on a sec.
This bike reeks of testosterone.
He pretty much screams "punk."
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Yeah, no kidding.
I didn't think you'd be
tying the cover down with rope.
It's more than justified.
I've registered the bike, of course,
and I've subscribed to
a GPS tracking service,
so even if it gets stolen,
I'll find it right away.
Why're you trying to intimidate me
about all that?
"Right down to the last detail,"
is my creed when it comes to cooking,
and anything else, really.
Huh...
For all his bulk, he's a more sensitive guy
than I'd have made him out to be.
I haven't told you my name yet, have I?
I'm Mimasaka Subaru. Remember that.
Mimasaka
The eighth main tournament contestant.
That's a really pretty-looking name!
Mimasaka
Subaru
Right?
And this embroidery was...
No way!
...done by me, of course.
Wow!
The third match is now about to begin!
This match's theme involves
an enviable dish from America
that has evolved beyond
the realm of fast food!
It's the hamburger!
The canonical hamburger involves sandwiching
a cooked hamburger patty between two buns.
Candidates are free to choose
any ingredients and buns they'd like!
Now, let's have the candidates come in!
It's already starting!
Yukihira!
O-Okay, I'll go look for him outside.
Hey, relay this message to your mistress.
The member of the next generation
she'll concede her Elite Ten seat to will be me,
and I'll take the top spot
at Totsuki from her, too.
You would do well to stop that
nonsense from here on out.
I am the one who will succeed
Erina-sama and join the Elite Ten.
Candidate Hayama Akira ended
the Block A prelims in first place
by manipulating numerous spices
to his advantage!
His opponent is Candidate Arato Hisako,
who passed the Block B prelims
in second place
after receiving high praise
for her medicinal curry!
A match between a master of spices
and a master of medicinal plants...
Their specialties aren't the same,
but they follow a similar theme.
It's like a match between
leaves, or something.
Let the cooking begin!
That's... a kebab!
Hayama decided to go with doner kebab!
Turkish food, huh?
Right.
"Doner" means to turn,
and "kebab" means to grill.
By rotating the meat as it's slowly heated,
its melting fat melds with the spices!
Man, smell that great fat!
It looks super tasty!
What's going on with Miss Secretary?
What's with that bucket?
It's moving!
Huh? It's a...
It's a suppon, a Chinese
soft-shelled turtle!
So Miss Secretary's going to make...
...a suppon burger?!
Suppon preparation involves
a four-part butchering technique.
You flip the suppon on its back,
and then, when it sticks its neck out,
you strike.
She didn't hesitate at all!
She's pouring something on
the body after the bloodletting.
Is that sake?
It prevents the blood from coagulating.
I bet she's going to use the blood
in her hamburger patties!
Suppon guts are gross!
Such firm resolve despite
being covered in fresh blood...
Hisako-oneesama, you're so wonderful!
Along with medicinal plant ingredients
such as schisandra fruit and kinshinsai,
I see ginger and Shaoxing wine.
Hmm.
She intends to make rich stock
by simmering even the shell.
Hurry up, Soma-kun!
Hayama-kun and Arato-san are already cooking!
Sorry, sorry.
And who's this Arato?
She is Nakiri-san's secretary!
Oh, Miss Secretary.
C'mon! Where've you been, anyway?
Oh, I ran into a weird guy.
Yukihira Soma.
Family runs a diner.
Draws on a rich imagination
springing from that experience in his cooking.
Yukihira Diner
Has strong pride in his family diner's name.
Cooked char o-kakiage and
souffle omelet at camp.
Height, 171 centimeters;
weight, 57 kilograms.
Blood type, B;
shoe size, 26.5 centimeters.
Slept an average of six hours
and 14 minutes this past month.
In junior high, he was
in classes 1-5, 2-2, and 3-7.
"Down to the last detail"...
Takumi Aldini...
Heir to a trattoria in Toscana.
Father is Japanese; mother is Italian.
Height, 168 centimeters;
weight, 54 kilograms.
Blood type, A.
Sees Yukihira Soma as his arch-rival.
Lives alone with his younger brother, Isami.
Calls home twice a month.
Has a fan club in Totsuki Academy.
Has a fear of heights.
Interested in Japanese food samples.
Sets two alarms before going to sleep.
Has a mole on his left shoulder.
Prefers showers to baths.
Bad at card games.
Underwear tends to have a checked pattern.
And, what he values most is...
U-Um, since our current location is here...
I'm so sorry, Soma-kun! It's my fault!
No prob.
What, did you get lost?
What?
Just watch in my standby room, then.
It's right there.
Yukihira?
Tadokoro-san, too?
Candidate Mimasaka Subaru
Standby Room
Jeez...
Why do I have to be here, too?
Well, why not?
Aren't you done checking your ingredients?
Choose any sweet you want with your tea.
Oh, you don't need to play the host!
What are your thoughts
on this fight, Yukihira?
Oh, I don't know.
I've never seen Miss Secretary's
cooking, either.
What do you think, Tadokoro?
U-Um... Arato-san specializes
in cooking with medicinal plants.
I'm not sure they'd pair well
with hamburgers.
It looks like Arato Hisako will finish first.
She's kneading chopped suppon meat
and innards with ground pork.
She seasoned the meat with salt and pepper.
She used pork caul, the mesh of fat
enveloping pork organs,
to wrap the patty and keep it from
disintegrating while it grills.
Hisako!
Look, Hisako!
The cherry blossoms are so beautiful!
She who possesses the God Tongue.
My wish is to serve her at her side.
To walk close to her,
following her a few steps behind.
To make that wish come true,
I will survive this match and win!
I present to you a dish that will shake
your instincts to the very core!
It is the Suppon Burger!
Now then, will the judges'
reactions be night or day?
The faint sweetness and pronounced elasticity
that steamed buns are known for!
All the downy hairs on my body
are standing on end!
I feel like my body...
...is burning up!
Whoa!
Look at their glow, despite their age!
Is that the power of suppon?
A meltingly tender, meaty hamburger patty...
It's overflowing with the suppon's umami!
The sauce is thickened suppon stock.
The sauce coats the hamburger patty
and creates a rich flavor!
The fresh blood I added to the hamburger
patty warms you up from the inside.
I also mixed dobekkou powder
into the hamburger patty.
Dobekkou is dried suppon shell.
It is used to improve vigor
in traditional Chinese medicine.
So both the sauce and the
hamburger patty contain suppon.
No wonder the judges look so satisfied.
Nay!
The truth of this dish can only be
understood by those who have tasted it.
The answer lies in the gelatin
from the suppon—its viscosity.
You are exactly right.
Viscosity has a great impact
on a dish's perceived richness.
And this hamburger patty contains a lot
of gelatin that has seeped into the stock.
Of all the parts of the body,
the soft palate—
the inner part of the upper jaw—
is most sensitive to physical stimuli.
The viscous hamburger patty and sauce is
providing a sensuous stimulus.
In other words, this dish not only
speaks to one's sense of taste,
but also to one's sense of touch.
It's as though the suppon's seductive
greatness is bearing down upon me!
Roar!
It's deliciousness... is monstrous!
I was in rapture without intending to.
W-W-W-Wow!
I'm so amazed she was able to leverage
medicinal herbs to this degree!
Yeah...
If I ever face her, the depth and scope
of her knowledge will pose quite a threat.
But the victor of this match
will be Hayama Akira.
Eh?
What's going on?
The audience's mood shifted the moment
Hayama began cooking his hamburger patties!
It's not just about
what happens in the mouth.
That's not all there is
to the world of taste.
It's done!
We'll now have Candidate
Hayama Akira's hamburger!
The overpowering scent of meat
is flooding the arena!
Wow! Amazing!
There's piping hot kebab meat
on top of the thick hamburger patty!
Now... Quickly!
All the judges have turned
into ravenous dogs!
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting.
What's your play, Hayama Akira?!
That dish cannot possibly avoid
being heavy and overbearing.
No matter how he may try
to lure people in with fragrance,
if the actual flavors are crude...
I couldn't stop myself!
I've already finished mine!
What?
You chose to use pita bread
as the hamburger bun, I see.
Pita bread...
It's a Middle Eastern bread
which is baked at high temperatures,
resulting in a hollow "pocket"
that is then stuffed with ingredients.
Homemade yogurt sauce was used to
remove the gamey flavor of the kebab,
and to enhance the flavor of spices.
The hamburger patty itself is köfte,
a Turkish "burger" made from a combination
of lamb and beef with plenty of spices.
It's very pungent!
What is going on?
How can such a heavy hamburger patty be...
Allow me to teach you.
There are four components
a hamburger must have.
Buns, hamburger patty, sauce, and pickles.
The pickles' pungent smell and acidity
are what enhances the meat's umami.
Pickles are the hidden star ingredient.
You seem to have substituted
finely-julienned ginger for pickles,
but if you were to ask me,
I'd say that was a weak move.
What?
Then what did you do?
What I chose to act as pickles is achaar!
Achaar: a preserved condiment
with strong acidity
made by brining vegetables
and fruit in mustard oil...
This achaar was made with onions.
The mustard oil's pungent odor
enhances the hamburger patty's umami.
The acidity is provided
primarily by amchoor,
a spice made from dried, unripened mangoes.
I also used lemon juice for added acidity.
For fragrance, garlic,
chili pepper, clove, cumin seed,
black pepper, and paprika powder.
I used honey for sweetness.
There's some ginger, as well.
He used his rare sense of smell
to build the pickles' fragrance
with a delicate touch.
He flipped the heavy fat
and gamey lamb flavors
into something you can't get enough of!
He made the human instinct for food explode!
His talent is not limited
to curries and spices alone.
Hayama Akira, you have the potential
to reach the God Tongue!
The winner of this match is clear!
What I aim to achieve is the number one spot.
No one who's desperate to stay number two
can hope to win against me.
What?!
Everything about you, from your goals
to your cooking... is too small.
I don't want to admit it.
But it's true that when
I smelled his cooking...
...my hidden hunger was forcibly exposed!
HA
YAMA
A
KI
RA
Hayama
Akira
The third match's victor is Hayama Akira!
I... lost...
Hisako...
I am sorry.
Excuse me.
It's almost time for the fourth match.
Those who are not candidates will need
to go back to the seating for the audience.
Oh, right.
I'm sorry, Eizan-senpai!
Yukihira.
I swear I'll settle the score
from our match on the first day of camp
during the Autumn Elections!
You're talking about the match that
Inui-senpai brilliantly declared a draw, right?
Dash
That brings back memories!
I-In any case, I'll beat you for sure!
Eventually, I'll challenge
you to a Shokugeki.
And that's when I will crush you!
There's someone my age who's this good.
If I'd stayed holed up in Yukihira,
I never would've known about him...
You're right, Takumi.
So don't lose no matter what, okay?
Let's see once and for all
who's gonna do the crushing, yeah?
Yeah!
Sure!
Of course, Yukihira!
Still, I'm surprised Mimasaka-kun
could say with such conviction
that Hayama-kun would win, even after
seeing Arato-san's amazing dish...
He's exceptionally talented.
For Mimasaka Subaru,
Totsuki is a perfect playground.
Candidate Takumi Aldini
Standby Room
Hey.
Hands off my tools.
I know you've been sniffing around me
for the last few days about me.
Tell me what that's all about.
Do you really like these
worn-out tools that much?
I bet you can only make crap using them.
Is that meant to provoke me?
I see right through you.
There's something I wanted to ask you.
It's about your little brother.
His cooking instincts have always been
rather lacking since he was little.
It's clear that he is a second-rate chef.
Trailing his older brother
is about the best he can manage.
What's it like to have
an incompetent brother?
You bastard!
Hey, Italian...
We're going to be facing off
mano a mano, after all.
We should try to enjoy it the best we can,
Takumi Aldini.
AV Room In Use
Urara-chan, we have an emergency!
What's the matter, Yua-chan?
I just got a message, and...
We... We have an announcement
for our honored guests.
The next match between Candidate
Mimasaka Subaru and Candidate Takumi Aldini
will be a Shokugeki!
A Shokugeki!
Food
Wars
The Second Dish
Next Episode: The Pursuer
Next episode: "The Pursuer."