All right, we're going to begin the match
between Class 1 and Class 7.
Sports Day
It's Sports Day.
Take it!
Someone, take it!
I want to go home and sleep.
Yamane-san.
G-Go get them!
Kurihara-san!
I-I want to go home and sleep!
Takase!
Is it too obvious I like him
if I cheer for him?
C-Class 1!
It'd be too obvious I like Kanda
if I look at her, right?
Furuya!
Go, go, Onii-chan!
Class 4
Class 1
Yo, Goda!
Looks like it's down to you guys and us.
Noro...
Yo, what's up?
Just so you know, no one with a girlfriend—
You're handling too much.
Can you make the next match?
What?! I can't?!
Why?!
Don't you know the rules?
All right, let's clean this up.
Why?!
Yeah.
Later.
Chiaki, next match is the final, right?
I'll be rooting for you.
Yeah, thanks.
Come on, Kana, make up.
U-Uh...
L-Later.
Chiaki, you ass!
Keisuke, I want to play in boys' soccer, too.
I don't think you can.
You can play.
Ask someone to switch.
Seriously?
But who?
Keisuke, switch!
All right, we're starting the final match.
Go, Class 1!
Goda's mine, Takase!
Sure. Just don't handle the ball.
Go, Class 4!
You got this, goalie.
Yeah.
Come on!
Sugawara-kun's amazing.
Y-Yeah.
Look, again.
You're right.
Look, look!
Why are you telling me, Yo-chan?
Takano, are you watching me?
Come on, why haven't I let go?
I don't stand a chance.
Ow!
Th-Thanks.
I-I was just trying to get the ball.
It would have been ours
if you hadn't touched it!
Oh, please, I helped you!
I don't need your help, idiot!
What's up, Chiaki? Lovers' quarrel?
Shut up!
It ain't!
Heh, all this flirting...
All you bastards with girlfriends...
The ball wasn't out of play.
You tricked me!
Class 4 is going to lose at this rate.
Let's all cheer for them.
Yeah!
One, two...
Go, Class 4!
Get them!
I bet Kana isn't cheering for me.
Well, what can I expect?
We've broken up already.
Chiaki!
Quit screwing around!
Hurry up and run!
Wh-What's your problem?
You call that cheering?
Impress me, you idiot!
Chiaki!
Dammit, Kana, you aren't even
my girlfriend anymore.
You really think you scream that I'm an idiot
without making me want
to act like a boyfriend?
Go, Chiaki!
Safe!
I told you, I'm not letting some
chick's boyfriend take me down!
I'm not going down!
I'm in a sports club. You have no chance!
High five!
The End
Opening Ceremony
So, again, you better watch yourselves.
Long Homeroom
Opening Ceremony
Short Homeroom
Cleanup
Okay.
Suga-yan, is the soccer club busy
during summer break?
Huh? Yeah.
Why?
All rise.
We're planning to go to the beach.
You should come with us.
Depends on club, I guess.
Bow.
Chii-chan's supposed to come, too.
Huh? I'll pass.
I'm shy about wearing a swimsuit and stuff.
So am I, but everyone's coming.
Ayaka-chan, Goda-kun, and Pattie, too.
I don't know.
So is Sugawara-kun.
Later.
Bye.
Come on, Kana, go make up with Chiaki.
O-Okay.
Ch-Ch—
Chiaki, you guys are going
to the beach with us, right?
I dunno, I'm thinking about it.
Are you sure it's okay if I come?
Why?
Apparently, Takano's coming, too.
Wouldn't it get awkward if I came?
I thrive on that awkwardness.
Sugawara-kun's not coming?
He doesn't know yet.
He says it depends on his club.
Okay.
So you two are coming for sure,
right, Yo-chan? Chii-chan?
Yup.
What should I do?
It'll be weird trying to meet Chiaki
once summer break starts.
Uchimura Chiaki
Today
Stay here after class
Will he agree to stay?
Crap, my battery's dead.
One, two, three, four...
Five, six, seven, eight...
There's actually no club work
that day. I could go.
But going to the beach will make me
think about Takano again,
even though I know
there's nothing between us.
Come on, dude.
She doesn't think anything of it, does she?
I'd just be miserable, going when
she doesn't think anything of me.
It doesn't even say he read it.
Did Chiaki actually go home?
Oh, can we practice here?
Hey, Suga-yan, what's up?
I forgot something.
So are you going to the beach or not?
I'm not going.
It'll suck if Sugawara-kun doesn't come, huh?
You still like Sugawara-kun, Yo-chan?
N-No, not anymore.
I knew I didn't have a chance to begin with.
Really?
What about you?
I guess Chiaki doesn't want
to patch things up anymore.
He really did leave.
I guess I'm going to be alone this summer.
Sorry, that was a weird thing to ask.
I'm going to the bathroom!
O-Okay.
It's true that I'm always thinking
about Sugawara-kun these days.
And if Sugawara-kun doesn't
come to the beach...
Huh?
What's wrong, Yo-cha—
Took you a while.
Were you doing something?
You didn't see my message?
Sorry, my battery died.
I was waiting for you,
so we could talk in person.
Why?
You're going to patch things up with me?
No, we've broken up already.
Wh-What's wrong, Sugawara-kun?
I forgot my wallet.
What about you?
Practicing by yourself?
No, Yo-chan's in the bathroom right now.
Ah.
Later!
Aren't you going to the beach?
Honestly, I didn't think you would
break up with me, no matter what.
I got too comfortable.
If we patched things up now,
it would be like that never happened.
It would feel bad.
I don't think our relationship
would last like that.
So let's break up properly.
Once that's done, I want to confess again.
Oh, I decided not to go.
Why not?
Your club?
Nah, I just don't really like
that kind of thing.
You're going, right?
Have fun.
I don't think it'll be fun
if you aren't there.
Fine. Try confessing, then.
I'll reject you a hundred times.
A-All right.
You better mean it.
Okay.
I don't want to lose you anymore, Kana.
Please...
Please go out with me.
Okay.
Shucks.
I'll have to buy a swimsuit
for the beach, then.
Me, too.
Summer begins.