Can't decide...
Morning.
Haru, today's the big day.
Okay!
We officially have four club members now,
and it's warming up outside,
so we will finally begin
training in the pool today...
Hold on!
Could you listen to what I have
to say first, Haruka-senpai?!
Please, Haruka-senpai?!
Come on...
Is this some kind of formula?
Where?
What is this?
Oh.
You know what warming up means, right?
This one means kicking
practice with a kickboard.
Pull refers to when you use a
pull buoy to train your arms.
Is this someone's name?
That's an abbreviation for medley relay.
It's a relay where the four
swimmers swim equal legs
using back, breast, butterfly,
and free in that order.
Back, breast, butterfly...
Back refers to the backstroke.
Breast refers to the breaststroke.
Butterfly refers to the butterfly stroke.
And free refers to the front crawl.
No, free refers to freestyle.
You're allowed to use any stroke.
But the front crawl is
generally the fastest stroke,
so that's what most swimmers use.
There are a few swimmers
who go with the butterfly.
The butterfly stroke?
Yep.
Anyway, this is a solid training regimen.
Did you come up with this yourself, Gou-chan?
Can you stop calling me Gou?
Forget it.
I found that when I was cleaning the house.
It's my brother's old regimen.
Captive Butterfly!
Sit with legs apart and lean
the upper body forward.
Hold 20 seconds.
Bend one arm behind the
head and use the other
to push the elbow toward
the center of the body.
Hold 20 seconds.
Lie down and turn my head while pulling
my knee in the opposite direction.
Hold 20 seconds.
Extend one arm straight while
pulling it in with the other...
Are you that interested?
In my brother's old regimen?
Not really.
You can write down a regimen
and not follow it.
So he is interested.
So cold...
The water's still pretty cold.
Place both hands on a wall and lean forward.
Rei-chan, you're still stretching?
I want to be as safe as possible.
You gonna be okay?
You can take it slow...
There's no need to worry.
I've mastered the theory behind
swimming in the past few days.
I won't embarrass myself again!
Rei...
Rei-chan...
Biceps!
I think you need to start
by learning how to swim.
Let's start with the turtle float.
I'll show you how it's done.
You hug your knees to
your chest and relax.
It's not beautiful.
Just give it a try.
So he can float.
Now, slowly extend your arms
and legs and try to swim.
No good...
What's the problem?
Haruka-senpai...
Why do you swim?
I don't have a reason.
My brother's dream is to
become an Olympic swimmer.
That's why he went all the
way to Australia to study.
That's got nothing to do with me.
Besides, it's just a dream.
Perhaps.
But I think he'll be a little closer
to his dream if he's with you guys.
Like when you swam the relay together.
Finish! Good job!
That last spurt was incredible,
Matsuoka-senpai!
One more run.
What?
O-Okay!
You're amazing, Matsuoka-senpai.
You should stop talking
about how amazing I am
and focus on finding your own style.
I'm a lost cause. I haven't
made any progress.
I guess it comes down to talent.
I was really impressed by Nanase-san
at our joint practice...
Nitori.
Is that really what you think?
They just started up their swim club
and haven't had a real practice yet.
You can tell by looking at their bodies.
They haven't been working out.
Given the condition he's in,
my victory means nothing.
It doesn't count as a win.
Haru-chan! Mako-chan!
Hello!
Hey! Wait, Nagisa-kun!
Look at this!
Ta-da!
Uniforms?
Yep.
We have a swim club now, so we
should get matching uniforms.
That's a good idea.
It'll give our club more of an official feel.
I know, right?
I think we should go with
this design, and this color.
And we can even use an image in
addition to the school emblem.
Are you thinking about putting
Iwatobi-chan on there?
That was the plan.
But it's not beautiful.
I think Samezuka's design
incorporates a shark and a katana.
Theirs is pretty cool!
We could put a real rockhopper
penguin on ours, then.
What do you think, Haru-chan?
B-Beautiful...
Huh?
Forget about buying matching
uniforms for now.
Here!
Is that a new training regimen?
Yes!
I revamped the regimen to account for
the fact that Rei-kun can't swim.
Rei-kun!
Wh-What is it?
Given how much time we have
until the regional tournament,
you have to learn how
to swim within a week.
Within a week?
That's conceptually impossible.
This is no laughing matter!
Yes, ma'am!
If you fail, you won't be able to
complete this training regimen!
Iwatobi Swim Club Training Regimen (Stage 1!)
Rei-kun only: Reduce all sets by half.
7 days to go!
I'll go first.
I can teach you frog style.
The breaststroke.
Or breast, right?
You've done your homework, Rei-chan.
I've learned all of the concepts.
I just need to figure out
how to make it work.
That's all.
Then let's start with your legs.
Wow, Rei-chan!
Your form is perfect.
Naturally.
I'm going to let go, then.
Go ahead.
Wow, your stroke is also perfect—
Huh?
Why?
6 more days!
I'm up next.
If you're having trouble with
breast, we can start with back.
With the backstroke, you keep
your face above the surface,
so it's easier for people
who are scared of water.
I'm not scared of water.
Move slowly.
That's it.
He knows how to float.
Naturally.
My condition wasn't optimal yesterday.
I'm gonna let go, then.
Go ahead.
What am I doing wrong?
This is hopeless.
Haru-chan, teach him how to swim!
No, that requires effort.
Man, don't be that way!
This isn't looking good...
Come on!
That's it!
Miss Ama-chan, do you have any
excellent advice to offer us?
Let's see...
5 more days!!
Okay, let's begin the "Let's figure out
why Rei-chan can't swim" meeting.
Anybody have any thoughts?
The water doesn't like him.
Poor Rei-chan...
That can't be it.
Maybe he's athletically challenged!
Rei-chan's really fast.
And he does well on tests.
So you must be smart.
Do you like mackerel?
DHA...
I know! His head is too heavy!
All that studying has enlarged his brain!
That's enough!
The problem is the way you guys teach!
If I had a proper coach,
I would be fine!
A coach...
There is a coach!
What?
You want me to teach a kid
who sinks like a rock?
Because I used to be a coach?
I object.
I can float, so I do not sink like a rock.
A more accurate analogy would
be to call me a submarine.
Hey, Goro-chan, we want you
to teach him how to swim.
Don't talk and eat at the same time!
I'm a busy man.
Why don't you guys teach him?
Bye.
Didn't work.
4 more days!!
I finally know the reason
why I can't swim!
Really?
You figured it out?
Yes, the answer was
right under my nose.
The answer is...
The answer is?
My
swimsuit!
This speedo is to blame!
I let you borrow that, right?
That's kinda mean.
It is not mean!
The problem is that this speedo is not
streamlined for my body, I think!
I haven't crunched the numbers yet!
He's really big on sticking to form.
Well, I don't see why he can't
buy a new swimsuit.
3 days left!!
So why didn't Miss Ama-chan come
with us to buy his swimsuit?
She worked for a swimsuit
maker in Tokyo, right?
Well, I did ask her, but...
Um, I have something
else to do on Sunday.
Plus, there are other brands!
I have my reasons.
I won't be able to provide
an objective perspective.
What's with the flurry
of random excuses?
There are a lot to choose from.
Fluid mechanics would tell you that
Reynolds numbers and boundary
layer theory are the key points,
but I believe that the color also
plays a psychological role.
I'll also need prescription goggles.
Prescription
Blurry vision may be another
reason for my difficulties.
You can't see without your glasses?
Wait!
I haven't learned any of the concepts!
Hey, Nagisa-kun!
Give them back!
You're going to hurt your eyes!
I'm going to try this on.
Oh, Haruka-senpai is also
looking to buy a swimsuit.
Are you finished changing?
It's clear that this fits me
much better than a speedo.
Rainbow?!
A rainbow for Rei?
I'm accounting for the
fact that each color has
a different psychological impact.
So you don't care about how it looks?
I'm done changing.
What do you think?
Wow, I can't tell how it's different
from his usual swimsuit.
Isn't it the same?
No.
I like the way this one fits better.
Mako-chan, let's try some on!
Changing rooms and muscles...
What? I have to join in?
Get moving!
Now, there's a nice combo
you don't see every day!
Ta-da!
That looks good.
D-Does it look funny at all?
You're rocking it, Mako-chan!
Butterflies have the psychological...
Where did you find that thing?!
This is also good.
Tell us how it's different, Haru-chan!
Delicious.
I'm exhausted.
Now I know how guys feel when they
have to go shopping with girls.
Hey.
Fancy meeting you here.
Captain Mikoshiba...
Are you doing some shopping, Gou-kun?
Please don't use Gou and -kun together.
We're here to look for new swimsuits.
Does that mean my brother's here?
I'm so happy!
Nitori?
Haru?!
Rin!
Ooh! This is perfect for Rei-chan!
Wait, that's another speedo!
I wanted to talk to you.
Come with me.
Haru, what have you been
doing the past three years?
You're better than this.
I'm not better than someone who
just got back from Australia.
Are you mocking me?
I'm not.
You won our race.
It'd be hard not to beat you,
given the shape you're in.
A win is a win.
You won.
Isn't that good enough?
It's not!
I want a real race!
Or else
I can't move on.
You're a pain.
I only swim free.
I won't swim for you.
No.
You're going to swim for me.
In that case,
I want you to promise me something.
If you lose, don't say you're going to quit.
Don't embarrass yourself.
Don't cry if you lose.
I'm not a little kid anymore.
This time, I'll make it clear
how different you and I are.
Try to build some muscle before
the prefectural tournament.
We'll settle things there.
See you at the tournament.
Oh! There she is!
Is something wrong?
It's nothing!
2 days left.
Swimming cap, check.
Prescription goggles, check.
Not a speedo, check.
He looks like a world-class
swimmer from here.
Maybe he'll actually manage
to swim this time.
Yep! I think this might work!
His entry angle is perfect!
Why?!
I'll teach you.
You want to learn how to swim, right?
P-Please help me!
However,
I can only teach you free.
Yes!
Haru's going to teach
someone how to swim?
Bringing in the big guns!
That's everything I have to teach you.
The rest is up to you.
Believe in yourself.
Yes!
Why?!
Genius is one percent inspiration and
ninety-nine percent perspiration.
Isn't that a quote from Edison?
So hard work will always
triumph over natural talent.
I guess he'll have to keep practicing.
However...
You can interpret Edison's quote to mean
that hard work means nothing
without that flash of inspiration,
don't you think?
A rejection of hard work?!
Haruka-senpai...
Do what you want.
What do you mean?
Don't think about swimming.
Just dive in.
I don't understand what you mean.
Dive in with your heart.
That doesn't help.
Go by your senses...
Can you stop using abstract expressions?
How can I learn to swim
as freely as you do?
I'm very frustrated.
Why can't I swim?
Or else
I can't move on.
I'm not free either.
What are Haru-chan and Rei-chan doing?
Nagisa.
Leave them alone for now.
I have a feeling they have a lot in common.
You're right.
Today is the last day.
Since it's come to this, let's have him
use a kickboard in the tournament!
Do the rules allow that?
That's an option.
I don't think the rules prohibit it.
We'll have to look that up.
Somebody's swimming butterfly.
Is that Haru-chan?
But Haru only does free.
It's not me.
Haru?!
That means...
Rei-chan?!
Were you just swimming butterfly?!
It was the only stroke I hadn't tried yet.
Once I tried it, I was able to swim.
What?!
Why?!
Well...
I'm not free.
Did you say something, Rei-chan?
No, I can't explain it either.
Seriously?
Well, I guess it worked out in the end.
Hey, Rei-chan.
Can you do another lap?
Sure.
Hey, if you could take one
thing to a deserted island,
what would you take?
A survival kit, probably.
Canned mackerel.
Why would you limit yourself to one
item when visiting a deserted island?
I don't understand the question.
Next time: Trial in Open Water.
Trial in Open Water!
A deserted island?
Rin!
If I could only take one
thing, I'd take my pillow.
So you're the kind of person who
can't sleep without your pillow.