Kakeru Okikura
Touko Fukami
Yukinari Imi
Hiro Shirosaki
Yanagi Takayama
Sachi Nagamiya
Episode 1
"Fireworks"
Nice!
Wow.
I take everything seriously.
What's this?
Huh? Show me.
Oh, these things have
gotten really advanced.
They were so crummy when I was little.
I've finally found you.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Do you think I can take it
back to Sacchan as a gift?
A bit much, don't you think?
A bit.
Like, I have—
I'd like this one.
Whoa, don't drop it.
Trust me. I have good reflexes, Hiro.
Fine,
but you're paying for it if you break it.
After all I went through to make
sure we can split it completely evenly?
I used to come here every day during
my high school entrance exam days.
Huh? Isn't this pretty far from your place?
This kid gets pumped only when he's running.
He could run forever.
What do you mean, "only"?
This is the last year we're
all meeting up, huh?
Huh?
Why so negative?
We could all come again.
Yeah, next year, and the year after...
We'll be friends forever!
Forever? Who knows what'll
happen in the future.
What?
So we're going to stop being
friends once we graduate? Come on.
No, but I mean,
there's no telling what might happen.
They say that if you say
your wishes out loud,
you'll end up granting them yourself.
So maybe instead of saying "we won't come here,"
we should say "let's come again."
Did you get that from Sachi?
Yeah, so?
Okay.
My wish is that no matter what happens,
my future self will fix it all.
Thanks for waiting.
Thanks.
Two iced coffees.
Yukkii, give me a hand please.
Okay.
Since when is he "Yukkii"?
They're totally best buds.
More toast for the iced coffee customers.
Such a salesman.
Grandpa's so nice to Yukinari.
You can hardly tell who's the grandson.
Yuki-kun's popular.
With the elderly.
What are you talking about?
What about Grandpa?
Why is it so delicious when you eat out?
I was going to stay away from ramune.
Sucks to be watching your weight, huh?
Please don't call it that.
Here, look.
It's sparkling.
The fireworks were so pretty.
Like, boom, bang!
The festival's ending.
Hinode
Bridge
I'm home.
Welcome back.
What do you want for dinner?
Stew.
It's too hot, so no.
What should I make?
This again, Mom?
Why do even bother asking?
I'm leaving.
Oh, wait a sec.
Hina, what do you want for dinner?
I saw some cabbage left over.
That's my girl.
See, all three of us have the same one.
Sorry, I didn't bring mine.
You sure are tactful.
Shut up.
That thing on the door, right?
You could have brought it if you noticed.
You make a fuss whenever I touch
your stuff without asking.
Wait, you went in?
Who was it again that asked me to bring
the reference book you left behind?
Exile and the Kingdom
Camus
So it was you.
David.
David?
Hey, you. Here.
Thank goodness, I thought you'd left already.
Make sure your parents see this.
Thank you.
Such a pain, transferring schools.
What year?
Third.
Same as me.
Sounds tough, transferring in your third year.
Your name?
Hm?
What's your name?
Touko Fukami.
Touko.
He's calling me by my first name?
I saw you at fireworks the other day.
You were buying a bell.
Wait, Jonathan!
Jonathan?
That's the chicken's name.
And then there's Husserl, Confucius,
Roger, and Makuzu.
We're all taking care of them at school,
but I think the ethics
teacher puts in the most time.
Jonathan's from somewhere else.
So that's why it's not fitting in.
They're free-range, so they're so hard to draw.
You could just put them in a coop.
I can't make that decision.
It'd be cruel.
Why isn't Jonathan running away? That's amazing.
Cruel?
It's better if they get to
go wherever they want to.
That's just your own point of view.
Huh?
Well...
there aren't any animals that'd
go into cages on their own.
That's because they don't
have enough options.
Huh?
This is a port town.
There are lots of cats.
Ever considered that they
might get attacked?
They're all full from eating fish!
I think.
I haven't heard about any of
them getting attacked by cats.
What about other than cats?
Jonathan can fly awa—
Huh?
Run!
What's wrong with you?
I thought they could fly away.
Am I friend or foe?
Then I'll protect Jonathan!
Okay? Please and thank you.
I don't know...
Please!
Hello.
How did I get dragged into this?
Over here.
I'll explain in detail tomorrow.
Is Yana-chan okay with this?
It'll be fine. She's not completely heartless.
Thank you so much, Momo-san.
No problem. Leave it to me.
Hey.
She just got her license.
She can't wait to drive someone around.
Tee hee.
Good grief. I never signed up for this, either!
Whoa!
Hey! Why'd you put it in my room?
I texted you.
It might get attacked if it's outside.
Keep the two of them in your room, then.
And I told you I can't check
my messages during lessons.
Don't be so mean. They aren't
in their familiar environment.
By the way,
you should learn how to count chickens.
This is another favor for Touko, isn't it?
You always do everything Touko asks you to.
It's not like that.
I haven't had ramune in forever.
Open it.
Do it yourself. Learn from Touko.
Just do it.
I've...
always wanted chickens.
Yuki,
if Touko told you to die,
would you?
She... wouldn't say that.
I know she wouldn't.
I know! Let's have hot pot today.
Hot pot in the summer. Perfect.
Jonathan,
are you happy right now?
How do you want to live?
Am I keeping you safe?
Dinner, Onee-chan.
O-Okay!
It's mid-summer. Why chicken hot pot?
Have you considered how hot it is?
I just had a craving.
It looks good.
Come on, Touko.
Let's eat!
Why did you just randomly
bring home a chicken?
"Why"?
Well, It was just impulse.
I don't know if I should have.
I got everyone involved, too.
And it doesn't even solve the problem.
There's no difference between putting
him in a room and putting him in a coop.
What does Jonathan even think of all this?
Ah, I guess I fooled myself into
thinking I knew what Jonathan wanted.
We got some good chicken today.
Huh?!
Speaking of chicken, I remember
my first date with Ken-chan.
What happened?
It was our first date, and he was late.
You were the late one. Two hours late.
Huh? I asked you if you waited,
and you said "I just got here."
W-Well, you know...
So what does that have
to do with chickens?
Well, I got caught up copying a
Jakuchuu chicken painting.
Why would you paint a chicken
before your first date?
Aren't there more important things to do?
It's your first, after all.
You're so naive, Hina.
So you're less interested in
Dad than you are in chickens?
Oh, my.
Let's go somewhere Sachi
can go next time.
Yeah.
We went hiking together
last year, didn't we?
Yeah?
Okay.
We can't let the festival end just yet.
That again.
Thank you for waiting.
It's a bit late to get
ready now, so, tomorrow?
You're always so spontaneous.
I'm never taking care of chickens again.
Never, ever.
Seriously, you're unbelievable.
Sorry.
They were cute, weren't they?
A giant tanuki might have gotten
them if we hadn't taken them in.
What? Where the heck do
giant tanuki even live?
Touché.
It's because Yuki let them in
my room in the first place.
Come on, you don't even
know how to count them.
I do, too.
Tell me, then.
Welcome!
Chickens really do crow in the morning, huh?
They didn't lay any eggs.
I wonder if zoo animals are happy.
So,
what made you decide to take them in?
Um... A transfer student...
He's a third year, and looks like David...
You mean me?
What a surprise.
I'll introduce him.
Um, his name is...
Okikura.
David Okikura?
I thought I was doing the
right thing for Jonathan...
And who are you, exactly?
I figured there'd be guys, but...
What's with you?
Touko, I saw
what you saw that day.
I think I'll ask him out.
He didn't pull anything weird, did he?
He did?
What?
What do you mean?
Be open to love!
Episode 2
"Bench"