All right!
We're done for...
This is the end...
Amnesia Effect!
Play The Game...
It's no use.
The wind's too strong.
Let me go!
[Wind Report]
Hakone City, Ashigarashimo District, Kanagawa Prefecture
Strong winds in this area that began after 5:00 PM have peaked and are projected to subside within ten minutes.
The strong winds around Hakone are
thought to subside within
approximately ten minutes.
The wind will die down
within ten minutes.
Let's stay calm and wait.
Don't!
You'll get flung off!
Hang in there!
It'll be okay!
Just a little longer...
In two minutes, rescuers will arrive.
We will save everyone!
I'm scared and afraid.
Please come save us soon!
Help will be here in two minutes.
Please stay calm and follow
the rescuers' instructions.
We'll all be saved!
We're done for!
There's no way we'll be saved!
I don't believe you!
Calm down!
I didn't believe in
GALAXters before, either,
but this saved my life when
I got into an accident.
Have faith and wait.
GALAX won't abandon us!
Help will arrive
in 20 seconds.
Hang in there!
Help will be here
in twenty seconds.
I have faith.
Here they are!
Help has arrived.
It's just like GALAX said.
Yay!
Thank goodness!
We'll now begin rescue operations!
Please let the children
and the elderly evacuate first!
I'm sorry to ask,
but can children evacuate first?
Sure, that's fine.
Of course.
It's okay.
Don't be scared.
Okay.
You're not human, are you?
Okay, this planet is finished.
No one... No one will be spared.
Amnesia Effect!
Go, Bird!
Everyone will go up in a big, red blaze!
Burning Rain!
Everyone believed they'd be saved.
There were lots
of people who use GALAX,
and they explained
what was going on to us.
GALAX's information was accurate.
It seems some of the rescuers
were GALAXters, too.
It was everywhere.
Good work, everyone.
The world has been updated.
There were no victims.
Rui, it was thanks to
your timely decision-making.
Is something the matter, Rui?
I wasn't the one who saved them.
It was CROWDS.
It's all your guys' fault.
Do you even get that?
What do you mean?
You guys are primitive.
Burning....
Go, B-B-B-B-B-Bird!
What?!
Oh, my! MESSY's way too sensitive!
Yeah, isn't it awesome?
MESSY seems to like
changing its shape.
Oh, MESSY's acting weird today.
C'mon, Utsutsu. Try it, too.
I'm dreamy...
Man, we've got way
too much free time.
We've been beating
MESS-chan up all this time,
but we're way too friendly
with this MESS-chan!
Oh, Jou-chan.
You're looking way too scary!
A strange alien?
Yeah.
My powers didn't have any effect.
It's a violent one, too.
It camouflaged itself as a random
passerby and stabbed a lot of people.
Could it also be...
Multiple Assaults in Tachikawa Area
Suspects All Deny Involvement
Suspects Claim  Bodies Suddenly Appeared in Front of Them
...responsible for all of them?
I wouldn't be surprised.
It said,
"No one will be spared."
"Everyone will go up
in a big, red blaze."
and "You're all to blame."
So yeah.
What does this all mean?
It was pretty tough.
You fought against it, Jou-san?
Yeah. I didn't manage
to finish it off today,
but I will, for sure, next time.
Still, something bothers me.
Remember what JJ
said a while back?
He said, "A bird with sundered
wings has wandered in."
Yes.
I've been wondering
what he meant.
It had a NOTE.
A NOTE like this?
Yeah...
You mean, it might be
a Gatchaman like us?
I wonder.
Are there more
Gatchaman than just us?
OD, Paiman, you know
something, don't you?
It was really tall.
Long, tangled hair and
a diamond-shaped tail.
Who is it?
Pai-Pai? D-san?
You're acting weird.
The crazed bird
has appeared once more,
scattering the innocent with iron.
Hands off this one, guys!
How can you say that?
There's already been several deaths!
We don't know for certain
that an alien is behind them!
But if it is,
we have to deal with it,
as Gatchaman.
Listen, do not become involved!
That's a direct order!
I'm talking especially to you,
Newbie! Don't do anything!
Boo!
Sugane, Utsutsu, keep an eye on her!
That will be all!
No more discussion!
Are you scared?
You're pathetic, Leader.
I can't let this pass.
Let's split up and find it.
Stop, all of you.
What?
You, too, Hajime-chan.
Do as Pai-Pai says.
Newbie.
I'm Hajime!
What's on your mind?
What else?
What we should do next?
We have to do something!
I mean, the bad Gatchaman
said it's all our fault, right?
Isn't that really bad?!
Jou-san?
If we don't do something...
Miss, don't worry.
I'll settle the score
with that insane bird.
That's not it!
I'm not talking about that!
I'm dreamy...
It can't be helped, Pai-Pai.
That's all you
could've said to them.
I'm the only one
who understands.
We're done for!
Once it comes, this planet
will be wiped out!
Calm down, Pai-Pai!
How can I calm down?!
I'm talking about it!
It's a demon who's destroyed
countless planets..
And it doesn't just destroy them.
It never gets its own hands dirty.
It loves watching the planets'
inhabitants destroy each other.
If only I'd managed to defeat it...
OD, don't be rash.
You know what I mean, right?
If you spread your wings...
I know.
If that happens,
all will be destroyed.
I know...
I also lost my best
friend because of it...
I don't want to experience
that ever again!
But why did it come
to this backwaters planet
under protective observation?
It probably found out...
Found out what?
A trigger that'll cause humans
to destroy each other.
"Go up in a big, red blaze"...
That must be the hint.
It'll be sure to guide this planet
to destruction, slowly but surely.
That's the ultimate pleasure
for Berg-Katze, after all...
Sugane, I'm going to do it.
Next time, I will beat it up.
Of course. I will come with you.
I only became a Gatchaman
because of you, Jou-san.
I've heard that line
too many times.
Hey, Sugane, come for a drink?
Like I keep saying, I'm a minor.
Oh, right.
Well, off I go, then.
Who knows how long
you can have fun drinking?
Why are the assaults our fault?
I'm kind of hung up over it.
Pai-Pai and D-san were
acting weird, too.
That was the first time I saw
D-san acting so serious, too.
Oh, wow! This area's crazy.
The police are there,
and the self-defense forces
are across from them.
There's the riot police, the fire station,
and the city hall is that way, too.
Isn't Tachikawa going to be okay,
no matter what?
Don't you think, Utsutsu-chan?
Utsutsu-chan, are you
always this quiet?
It's like you're here,
but not really.
That's how...
Huh, what? What's how?
Oh, sorry.
That's how my body is.
Huh? What do you mean?
This body is a copy.
You're a copy, Utsutsu-chan?
I can make any number of copies.
Wow!
I wish I could, too.
You can't.
I can because my body is weird.
Wow, that's great.
It's not great.
I see.
You don't like it.
I don't.
I can't touch anyone.
Because I hurt them.
That's the kind of life form I am.
So even if I'm happy, I soon
want to cry, disappear, or...
Or hurt someone?
Aren't I scary?
Hey, Utsutsu-chan.
What does that streetlight
look like to you?
A streetlight is a streetlight.
From here, it looks
round and smiley.
Utsutsu-chan, you're just
fine the way you are.
That's what I think.
I mean, you're so cute!
I'm happy, no matter what.
I don't want to vanish.
It's all okay!
Liar...
I want to talk to the real
Utsutsu-chan, someday!
What's wrong, Utsutsu?
Head... hurts.
Is Hajime-chan saying
something to you?
I don't want copies anymore...
Yeah.
But we're all like that.
Having special powers is something
to be glad about, but sad as well.
Minomiya Rui-kun.
You have gained the power
to materialize a person's soul.
Th-This is my soul?
Yes, as long as you have this,
all of your wishes can come true.
My wishes....
Good morning, Rui-Rui.
That's a lot of sweat!
Did you have a nightmare?
So scary!
No, not really.
I saw.
You seem to be using
what I gave you.
Yeah.
Everyone seems to say
it's really great.
Do you think you
can update the world?
I'm grateful to you, Alien-kun.
You're welcome, Primitive-chan.
But, you know...
If everyone finds out
that their hope, GALAX,
is in a contract with someone
like me, what would they think?
Confirm biometrics.
Good morning, X.
Good evening, Rui.
It appears all suspects are continuing
to deny their involvement.
No one remembers
committing murder.
They feel it's as though
someone took over their body.
What is it, Rui-Rui? Huh?
Nothing...
Online forums indicate
increased interest
in preventing these incidents
before they happen using GALAX.
But GALAX isn't up to the task!
Hey, Rui-Rui, do you want
to know the true culprit?
It's the human heart!
Heart?
Yes.
The black hearts you
foolish humans all possess.
They're all overflowing
and making people kill each other.
That's why these incidents
will never cease!
It's a crisis!
It's scary!
It's fun, isn't it, Rui-Rui?
Let's start a revolution together.
Okay, I'm off for some
exercise outside.
Bye-bye.
We still have no information
about that alien.
As for Gatchaman, I am scanning
security camera footage—
That's no longer necessary.
They don't exist, after all.
We won't ask for help
from any heroes.
I will handle it, myself.
Your goal has been to have
a bloodless revolution.
I know!
But I can't let it
run loose any longer.
X, you know why I formed
the Hundred, don't you?
I have to make
the world update itself.
My Hundred and you:
We're the ones
who can change the world.
I am going to make
the world accelerate.
Oh, hey. You're working!
Oh, Hyuuga, Kaede!
Hey, wasn't that miracle rescue
on the ropeway yesterday amazing?
Here we go again about GALAX.
That was amazing, yeah.
Right?
If it's that great,
shouldn't we let GALAX handle
police work and politics?
That's not true.
But isn't it amazing
that it can resolve things
before anyone shows up?
It's amazing, but it's not good.
Oh, yeah? Why?
Because that'd be kind of sad
if that's all there is.
Yeah... That's it.
Hajime-chan!
Oh, Baracchi!
"Baracchi"?
It's Kuwabara-san, chief of the
Tachikawa Fire Department.
Hey, Baracchi. You would save
people, no matter what, right?
What?
Even if the world
goes up in a big, red blaze,
you'd save people, right?
Y-Yeah. Of course!
See?
I give up!
Just cry there!
Mommy!
That's...
Hey, stop!
Accident at crossing
before Toyosu Station!
Beginning rescue
operations immediately!
Understood.
A traffic accident has occurred
in front of Toyosu Station.
Many people have been injured.
Will you help?
A traffic accident has occurred in front of Toyosu Station.
Many people have been injured. Will you help?
Eight GALAXters in the area
have agreed to assist.
How horrible!
Can you hear me?
Please hang in there!
Why did it... do such a thing?
Look out!
There she is!
Okay!
It wasn't me!
I don't know anything!
Amnesia Effect!
Rui-Rui, you're teary-eyed!
Too bad! So sad!
I guess you couldn't
be a hero today!
It's finally begun, Rui-Rui!
A festival, festival, festival!
Yay!
Rui, unfortunately, there were
seventeen casualties.
It's my fault.
All my fault!
Why did I get its power?!
What have I been doing?!
What have I been doing
all this time?!
Jou, you're in an
unusually good mood.
Did something good happen?
Nope, nothing really.
It's like you're back
to your old self.
Alan, I haven't changed at all.
As for the suspect in custody,
a housewife, she claims
she doesn't remember anything,
including getting into the vehicle.
She is denying any involvement.
However, witnesses say
she was upset and scolding
her child right before the incident.
Police believe this incident
to be a mass assault
It's it.
Huh?
It's like everyone is stressed out.
and are continuing
their investigation.
Oh, look: "Expectations Higher
Than Ever for GALAX."
It's like our disaster prevention
department might as well not exist.
Like, we're all fine
as long as GALAX exists?
It can't be helped.
The enemy is too strong.
Huh? Enemy?
What do you mean, Jou-san?
Oh, sorry.
Well, what's the point in us civil
servants worrying about it?
Man, what scary times we live in.
I guess we can only
count on GALAX.
Heroes can't be found
anywhere anymore, anyway.
Oh, you going home already, Jou?
Huh? You're kidding, right, Jou-san?
The match isn't finished yet.
Are you running away?
Me? Running away?
Don't be ridiculous.
I just have something
I've got to do.
Hey, Jou-san!
There's a hero right here.
Don't underestimate Gatchaman.