Raspberry Shortcake
Welcome!
Thank you!
We have a new part-timer?
Yeah, she started today.
She says she loves our cakes.
Please teach her everything
you know, Ichinose-kun.
Okay.
My Spring Break
Takeo...
Yeah.
You look way too suspicious.
Do I?
You're worried about her, huh?
I guess being worried is pointless.
That's a sudden epiphany there
I'll just have to be ready, in case
anything happens to Yamato.
Takeo-kun!
Ready
Hey, Yamato!
Oh, there!
How was work?
Oh, it was really fun!
I'm glad you encouraged me to apply, Takeo-kun.
I think their cakes are the best in the world!
Oh?
They're all so intricate.
I have no idea how they're made.
Someday, I want to see them all being made.
Help Wanted
Pâtissier
Pâtissier Assistant
Sales Staff
(High school student and
temp positions available)
Ask staff for details.
They're looking for help.
Huh?
Oh, you're right!
Why don't you give it a try?
Okay, but if I do, I might not be able
to spend as much time with you.
It's finally spring break, too.
It'll be fine, Yamato!
Spring comes every year.
Don't you want to try something
you've always wanted to do?
So this cake is from Les Cerises.
They're pretty amazing.
It kind of looks like it was constructed.
You know, like it's made of plastic...
Huh?
I have no idea where to start eating it
I think he's saying it's like a work of art.
I know!
Isn't it?
I see.
So, like Yamato said, this is a professional's work.
Digging in.
Stare
Oh, it's sweet...
Yeah.
It's a cake!
Why can't I say something
more insightful, damn it?
It tastes kind of complicated.
Right?
Good job, Suna.
It's tasty
It's rich, but not too heavy.
The way they use liquor is innovative, too.
Huh.
There's a company called Mandarin.
There was a competition for
cakes using their liquor!
Wow, Yamato.
Sorry, I'm talking way too much...
No, keep going.
You're such a good listener,
so I just get going, you know?
I guess I really like that about you.
Oh, just listen to me!
I love her.
After my shift,
they said I was relaxed today.
It made me wonder what would
have happened if I hadn't been.
I see.
After you get used to your job, I'll come visit.
Okay, I'll give it my best.
When I visit, I'll buy a bunch of cakes.
I'm looking forward to it, Yamato!
Welcome!
Hey!
No slacking.
Oh, I'm sorry!
Just kidding.
You can ask me anything, if you aren't sure.
Huh?
I'm Ichinose.
You could say I'm the owner's right-hand man.
Wow
Oh, I like baking, too,
but you're so good, I couldn't help but stare!
Do you want to become a pâtissier?
Yes!
It's tough, you know?
It looks fancy, but you need
a lot of elbow grease.
Just wanting it isn't enough.
It's quite competitive, too.
Right...
Well, I suppose I was in competitions and stuff.
Wow.
Well, good luck.
Thank you!
Good job today!
Yes?
Hey, so I was watching you work today.
I think the way you say, "Welcome," is odd.
Huh?
Welcome...
Oh, and you're too slow at packing cakes in boxes.
Welco—
Wel—
Huh?
Be careful, okay?
We wouldn't want our store's reputation to suffer.
The owner told me to teach
you stuff, so that's why...
Anyway, good luck with everything.
I wonder if Yamato's gotten used to things.
I'm sure it's better than on her first day.
Yamato...
Working for pay is tough.
Yeah, you're right.
I'm going to keep trying.
I'll get much faster at packing cakes!
I really like being near cakes,
and watching people make cakes!
I haven't had you come buy any yet, either.
By then, I'll have the job down!
Yamato's tough.
Yeah.
Well, considering how she went after you...
Yamato-san?
Yes?
Don't let what Ichinose-san said get to you.
Huh?
The way you say, "Welcome," isn't odd at all.
Ichinose-san doesn't really listen to others.
He's kind of in his own world, I guess.
He certainly has skills, and he's handsome, but...
Oh, yes.
His technique is amazing!
Anyway, don't take anything he says to heart.
Okay.
I'll be going on ahead.
Good job!
See you tomorrow!
Wow!
Oh.
Is this a new product?
It's so beautiful.
It's like a dream come true!
So sparkly...
I wonder what it tastes like.
Would you like to try?
But I couldn't possibly...
Um...
But I want to.
Fine.
Wow, what am I tasting?
Bergamot?
That's in there.
Right!
Sweet, but slightly sour. Delicious!
An idea a pro would think up!
Thank you for letting me have one.
When will we start selling these?
We won't.
Huh?
But why not?
Because it's a cake I came up with.
Huh?
We can't sell your cakes?
The owner said it's okay.
Then why?
Once, I sold a cake of mine.
They didn't sell out.
I can't stand seeing any of my cakes unsold!
Then, how about I buy any that are left?
I can buy up to three!
Then I'll eat them with my b—those I care about!
Why would you do that for me?
Well, I mean the cake's so wonderful.
I'd hate it not to be shared with the world.
Wonderful
So Wonderful
Wonderful.
So wonderful.
Then maybe I'll have them put three for sale.
Great!
I'll do my best to sell them tomorrow!
I'll do my best!
I'll do my best to sell them!
For Ichinose-san!
I'm looking forward to tomorrow, then.
I'll get going, then.
I'm looking forward to tomorrow.
I'm looking forward to seeing you, Ichinose-san.
Bergamot Citron
Oh, look, a new cake.
You're right.
I wonder what it tastes like.
Oh, I highly recommend that cake.
Okay, I'll get this one.
Me, too.
Thank you!
This girl...
I think this girl
has feelings...
for me...
has feelings for me, after all.
for me, after all.
What was your name again?
Huh?
Ichinose-san, your cakes sold out!!
It's Yamato.
No, I meant your first name.
It's Rinko.
Takeo, you're even more conspicuous that way.
I wouldn't want Yamato to see me.
Oops!
Yamato...
Yamato, working.
I'm glad.
She's smiling.
Okay, let's go home.
Yeah.
Rinko!
Come on, it's break time.
Oh, okay!
"Rinko"?
Did he call her "Rinko"?!
Rin
Who the hell was that?
He was handsome.
Takeo, want to get going?
It's hot out here.
It's only spring,
but from the tan,
you look like a
"Reverse" game piece.
That hurt more than I expected.
Why not use her first name, too?
Why are you so shy?
Wouldn't it make you nervous?!
I think Yamato-san would be happy
if you used her first name.
Makoto...
See!
It just doesn't work!
Wait, isn't this different?
It just isn't for me, okay?
Shut up!
It isn't easy for me.
What's hard for me isn't so hard for others.
Wow!
Thank you, sir!
It was Ichinose-kun's idea.
Huh? Ichinose-san's idea?!
You can have any you like.
Oh, it's nice and cold!
Yum!
It's so cold and tasty!
Wow!
Ichinose-san smiled?
Shisuda Park Bus Stop
Takeo-kun!
Hey!
Here.
What's this? Ice cream?
Yeah, one of the pâtissiers threw a gelato party.
Oh, it was him, over there.
Him!
What a fancy car.
Only geniuses become pâtissiers.
A cool guy.
A fancy car.
I respect him so much.
A pâtissier.
Professional pâtissiers know so much.
What happened between then and now?
I really love my job.
I see... That's good.
Yeah.
Takeo-kun, I brought you the best-tasting one.
Thanks.
Have some, too, Sunakawa-kun.
Maybe I shouldn't have told
her to get a part-time job.
But I can't talk cakes,
and I can't make them for sure.
Is the gelato still okay?
My hands are cold from holding
them for so long.
I really wanted you to have some!
I'm so narrow-minded...
Look how happy Yamato is.
Oh, that feels warm.
Because I'm not confident in myself as a man,
I can't be totally happy for her.
I'm so pathetic...
What's wrong, Takeo-kun?
Nothing.
I'm glad, Yamato...
Good luck at your job!
Okay.
Who would've thought Ichinose-san
would suggest anything like that?
Seeing him talk with Yamato-chan,
I'm starting to think he might be nice, after all.
That was the first time we saw him smile, right?
That's right.
Ichinose-san's wonderful.
Wonderful.
Is this fate?
Is she my muse?
Would the sea...
carry the small man I am, out to open sea?
I kind of get what you mean,
but I don't really get it.
I don't feel this way because of anyone else...
It's because of my inability to use her first name.
And I'm getting hurt because I can't
even overcome that little obstacle.
I'm such a small man.
No, isn't that normal?
Is it?
It's normal to not feel too good about
seeing guys around your girlfriend.
What?
How to put it...
I guess you're just a guy, after all.
Yeah.
I never really thought about how
Yamato might fall for someone other than me.
There might be someone she
gets along with more.
Takeo-kun.
I just never thought about that possibility
Takeo-kun?
because she was always with me, smiling.
I love you!
C'mon, Takeo...
Why do you have to feel so down?
She's only known that guy for about a week.
People don't fall for each other right away.
Right...
Yeah.
You're right.
I love Yamato, so...
Yeah.
That's why I thought everyone
would fall for her, too!
Yeah.
You're totally right!
Maybe your goal for now should
be to use her first name.
Yeah!
Message Inbox
Yamato Rinko
Subject: On Break Right Now
I got used to my work,
so you can come to buy cakes anytime!
Let's go!
Yesterday's gelato was a huge hit...
Jelly, huh? Not bad.
What motivated you to do that?
I thought about how to make
the person eating it happy.
Ichinose-kun!
You've changed lately!
Really?
You have good skills and taste,
but you've been kind of a lone
wolf until now, you know?
But lately, you've become friendly with everyone!
Oh, so how about this?
Do you want to enter?
Pâtissier Competition
If you rank, it'd be great for our store.
And it'd be good for your career, too.
You've been on a roll lately.
Here's my chance!
What do you think?
You'll sign up, right?
I'll leave this here.
Rinko.
Excuse us!
Takeo-kun,
you crack me up.
They know each other?
Which cakes would you recommend?
What's wrong, Takeo-kun?
Oh, I'm just nervous.
The shortcake is our bestseller.
Okay, one shortcake!
But I recommend this one.
Okay, one of that, too!
How many are you going to buy?
Thank you!
Yamato's working really hard.
Yeah...
Were those people just now your friends?
Oh, um...
The taller one is my boyfriend.
Hey!
Break up with Rinko!
I'm a better fit for her!
I know it!
So he does like Yamato.
Uh, sorry.
I'm sorry to come at you like that, out of nowhere.
Are you trying to become a pâtissier, too?
A pâtissier?
Not at all.
Maybe you really like baking?
I've made cookies.
Cookies?!
What kind?
Drop cookies?
Icebox cookies?
Sables?
Biscotti?
Rice crackers.
Rice crackers aren't cookies!
I'm a better fit for Rinko for sure
I'm a better fit for Rinko for sure!
Why are you two even dating?
Well, Yamato was getting harassed
by a groper, so I helped her—
Got it!!
I get it now!
After you helped Rinko out of a tough spot,
she must have seen you as a
wonderful, responsible guy.
But that isn't love.
That's a mistake!
She just doesn't know there are other
men who are a better fit for her!
I am Ichinose Kouki, age 21.
I'm a pâtissier at Les Cerises.
I'm Gouda Takeo, a first-year in high school.
A first-year in high school?!
A first-year in high school?
You must have someone who'd be good for you.
Someone who's more wild, like a gorilla...
A bear would work, too.
Don't you think you'd have better conversations
if you dated a woman like that?
Maybe even share the same hobbies?
Better conversations...
Same hobbies...
I need Rinko,
so please break up with her!
I can't...
Of course you'd say that.
You wouldn't be convinced by what I said.
I was abrupt, as well.
But if Rinko asked you, you'd break
up with her, wouldn't you?
I'll show you and Rinko who's the better fit for her.
I won't let you have her!
You could've talked back to him more.
Well, I couldn't help but think
he might have a point.
It's true that I can't really talk to
her about that sort of thing.
And that there may be others who'd be better.
I'm back.
Oh, you're here.
I am!
Oh, cakes?
Oh, Les Cerises! What's going on?
Takeo gave them to me.
Huh?
Yamato-san's working there part-time now.
Oh, that's perfect for her,
working in a cake shop.
I'm not a huge fan of sweets,
but I'll have some.
I was surprised how even Takeo has
issues with feeling inferior...
Did something happen to Takeo?
You're way too close, Sis.
I don't know if that means he
has an inferiority complex,
but that is a bit worrying...
Sometimes, Takeo can put
himself on the back burner.
Remember when he found a lost dog?
He became so fond of it...
And he stayed with it for a long time.
But the moment he realized the
dog might belong to someone,
This dog has a collar, so it belonged to someone.
he started frantically looking for its owner.
When he finally found the owner,
Takeo held it together and didn't cry.
He said he was happy for the dog.
Do you remember?
Oh, my... What a surprise.
The weather forecast was totally off.
It was sunny till just a moment ago.
Dad didn't take an umbrella with him!
I see.
No one took an umbrella today.
What a downpour...
I'll wait till the rain dies down.
I'll give you a ride.
You're a lifesaver, Ichinose-san.
Where do you live?
Just to the station, please.
Oh, my sister just said she'll
bring me an umbrella.
I'll wait at the store.
Good job today!
The wind's so strong...
I need to hurry.
I have a favor to ask you, Rinko.
Okay.
I'm going to enter a competition.
I need to think up at least
three original cake recipes.
Wow!
Rinko, would you help me?
Huh?
With your help, I think I can win!
U-Um...
I'm begging you!
Okay!
If I can help, sure.
Takeo sometimes puts other people's
feelings before his own,
because he just wants the
other person to be happy...
That's both his strength
and his weakness.
My Heart
Next time: My Heart.