Hatori
You're not going to regret
this later, are you?
I won't.
Hatori Chise
With that, the contract is complete.
Hatori Chise-san.
Can you breathe all right?
Let's go.
I'd heard rumors, but I've
never seen one before.
There are things that are
neither human nor inanimate.
They're different from the
ones that I always see.
I never knew things like this existed.
I don't care.
I just want somewhere to go home to.
This is the product you've
all been waiting for.
A rare item, even among
our current offerings.
Starting at 500,000.
1,100,000!
1,500,000!
1,800,000!
2,000,000!
Look there.
Why is he here?
2,250,000!
I thought he hated being around people.
Anyone else?
Sir...
5,000,000.
It's decided.
I will make you my apprentice.
What's the deal with that creep?
Dunno.
Prepare a reception room.
Wait...
We will be receiving five million pounds.
Who is he, to want to spend
so much money on me?
Age, fifteen.
Ethnicity, Japanese.
She's docile, so she should
be easy to discipline.
I never thought I'd see you at this auction.
However, we must ask you
to follow the rules.
Please don't wander onto the stage—
I don't need your lecturing nor small talk.
You, come.
You don't need to keep your head down.
Stand tall, and look forward.
Understood?
Yes.
I'll be borrowing your lobby.
By all means.
What is he, a monster?
He'll hear you.
Be quiet.
He's neither a conman nor a sorcerer.
He's the real deal, a rarity
in recent times.
I can't believe we let him have that.
That Sleigh Beggy...
Sleigh Beggy?
So you can see them.
Y-You mean me?
You're the only one here with me.
What's your name?
Chise.
Hatori Chise.
My name is Elias.
Elias Ainsworth.
Nice to meet you, my puppy.
It appears that you possess the sight.
How fortunate.
Fortunate...?
She's too much of a burden to take in.
What would people think if we gave
her to an orphanage, though?
She's being weird again.
Creepy.
She scares me.
What a brat.
No...
I've never once been fortunate!
Then let's see to it that you
feel fortunate someday.
I can't have you being so helpless.
Dolls are fine, but I paid
good money for you.
You need to make yourself worth looking at.
Um...
Now, close your eyes and stand close to me.
This may make you dizzy.
Nettles in the shadow...
Ring of holly...
Thoroughly entangle the
branches as a spider's web.
Thorns?
You can open your eyes now.
As expected,
we made it in one leap.
This is my home.
It's also your home, as of today.
W-Wait a minute.
Where are we?
How did we get here from
inside the building?
This is west of London.
A rural area on the outskirts of England.
E-E-England?
And what am I an "apprentice" of?
Oh, here.
You won't need that anymore.
You've become a mage's apprentice.
A mage?
We're an endangered,
old-fashioned kind, mind you.
I welcome you as my
apprentice, Sleigh Beggy.
Or rather... Chise.
No, no, no way...
I can do it myself.
I know how to take a bath.
You don't know how to use it, do you?
Besides, you're filthy, so I'll wash you.
Come now.
You're not a kitten. Stop fussing.
You need to soak to your shoulders,
or you'll never be warm.
He saw everything.
Come out when you're warm.
I didn't think I'd ever
get a proper bath again.
If you ever feel like giving up on life,
why don't you try giving yourself
to someone who wants you?
Well, well, I thought I smelled
something delicious.
It's an adorable human girl.
Fairies?
I suppose we'd be fairies, in human terms.
You better not use such
unrefined words for us, though.
That's right!
Call us your neighbors.
Or your good friends.
Hey, you're a Sleigh Beggy, aren't you?
The Thorn Mage is so silly, taking
in a Sleigh Beggy as his apprentice.
Honey wine, more valuable than
gold coins of ancient times,
more precious than any flower
of the land of fairies.
Adorable.
Our robin.
If you're going to become a mage, we'll
give you all the help you need, my beloved.
Beloved?
Chise.
Are you all right?
You're not overheated?
Yes, I'm fine,
so you don't need to come in.
They're gone.
Have something to eat and
drink so you can relax.
It's like they really do welcome me here.
You look like you have a lot of questions.
I'll try to answer your questions.
It'll be like a bedtime story.
Um, I saw fairies...
Ah, the ariels.
They must have greeted you.
They're attracted to anything new.
I see.
Is it true that you're a mage?
It is true.
So when you say "apprentice"...
I mean "apprentice," my puppy.
Sleigh Beggies are rare.
I was very lucky today.
What is this "Sleigh Beggy"?
If I had to choose a word, a queen bee.
You—or, your kind, Sleigh Beggies,
are capable of attracting and
binding all manner of things.
Specifically, fairies and mysteries.
They're worker bees that are drawn to you
whether the queen bee can see them or not.
Even if she can't see them?
It seems you can see them, but that's
not common among your kind.
They bring fortune and misfortune
upon the queen bee.
Misfortune?
Their kindness and favors don't
necessarily benefit a human.
However, to be loved by them means
that you'll never be without assistance.
You need their help to do magic,
so it's an important trait to have.
You'll surely become a great mage.
That doesn't mean I'll be
ordering you around, though.
But I don't have any right to refuse, do I?
Well, no.
You're free to reconsider, though.
Becoming a mage is just
one path of countless many.
You're like family to me now.
You can depend on me.
Family?
This is an adder stone.
The hole formed naturally
at the bottom of a river.
It'll protect you.
Have it.
Silver.
You must be tired,
so you should turn in for the day.
Would you please show her to her room?
I even get a proper place to sleep.
Family...
It smells strange.
Is it the scent of grass?
Chise.
Chise!
You're the... um, neighbor.
Hey, why don't we go for a midnight walk?
There's a nice forest nearby.
But...
Come on, it'll be fine!
Just for a little bit.
Take a walk, tire yourself
out a little and sleep well.
Let's go.
What a hopeless child.
Well, it'll make for a good lesson.
It's kind of bright.
It's the trail we leave
after we've passed by.
You can see that, too, huh?
Hey, Chise, what's your family like?
I don't have one.
I was taken in by a lot
of different relatives.
Were those people kind?
Chise?
I might not have come here
if I'd come to love them.
Oh?
Hey, we've walked pretty far.
It's fine.
We gotta go even further, if anything.
After all, you don't need
to go back anymore.
We finally duped the Thorn Mage.
What are you talking about?
I need to take you back to our land,
or the others will get angry at me.
It'll be a lot easier than
living in the human world.
Don't worry.
Hey, it just happens to be open.
The Fairy Kingdom is past here.
A super fun world, just for you and us.
W-Wait...
Let's go.
I-I'm going back.
Oh? Back where?
You don't even have family waiting for you.
You might as well live a happy,
giddy life on this side.
You're right.
I have no one.
What's wrong, Chise?
I can't.
I have to go home.
Why?
There's no reason you have
to go back to that house.
No one ever told me that I could be there.
But that man told me...
Even if I'm just a toy,
even if he'll throw me out
when he's bored of me,
he told me I was family,
even if it was just that once.
So...
It looks like my puppy has already
learned where her den is.
Elias.
Curses! How did you know where we were?
She has a collar and a bell.
Be gone.
I'll forgive you just this once.
Next time, you'll be salamander food.
Let's see if a half-baked loser
like you can protect our robin.
You don't need to remind me.
You can change your mind
whenever you want, Chise.
Chise.
That was a good experience, was it not?
Many of them make a habit of
seducing us with sweet words.
Be careful from now on.
I'm... I'm sorry.
No, I should have told you right away.
That's my duty to you, after all.
You're my apprentice.
Depend on me.
He's warm.
But it seems like he's tense—
Wh-What are you doing?
It's easy to get lost
in the forest at night.
Let's go home like this.
To our home.
We'll need to fix up your
arm when we get home.
I can't have my future wife be scarred.
Wife?
Who is who's...
Oh, have I not told you yet?
I bought you to be my apprentice, of course,
but I also hope to make you my bride.
Pardon?
Shall we prepare for our honeymoon?
Huh?
A girl, departing for
London with a sorcerer.
Unfamiliar towns, unfamiliar people.
The world offers a kind hand
to a lonely girl, but...