Count Sebring. Count Raffia. Count Orga.
Thank you all for allowing me to
intrude on your valuable time.
I am sorry for your loss,
Count Troyard.
What happened to Count Saazbaum
is most regrettable.
When he was alive, my father was
greatly indebted to him.
If it is in my power, whatever assistance
you may request is yours.
Thank you, that is most kind.
However, now is not the time to wallow
in individual sentimentality.
Most commendable.
This is the time for the Orbital
Knights to band together
and press forward with
the invasion of Earth.
That is the best way
to honor Count Saazbaum.
Indeed. Our ships must sail forward
together towards the same goal.
Ah, now I see.
You intend to take
the helm, then?
If I may be so presumptuous.
By the way... I understand that
you are to duel Count Marylcian?
I find it odd to be fighting
when we must band together.
Don't you agree, Count Troyard?
No lowly Terran...
No lowly Terran could possibly
be a match for mighty Vers.
Such an assumption
creates an opening.
Which becomes a tear.
And then an enormous hole.
And then it disintegrates completely.
That is the current state
of the Orbital Knights.
You go too far, Count Troyard!
As you are aware,
I am not Vers-born.
However, being an outsider
affords me a certain perspective.
This upcoming duel is also the result
of an Orbital Knight's hubris.
I believe it to be my responsibility
to teach him the error of his ways.
I see. You have a point.
Count Orga!
I am loathe to admit it.
Nevertheless, it is the truth.
Some portion of it, at least.
I shall leave the matter to
your discretion, Count Troyard.
Your attack on Trident Base
was magnificent.
Count Sebring, Count Raffia.
Thank you for doing me the honor of
listening to my many rude remarks.
All cruise missiles appear
to have been intercepted.
Looks like a saturation attack
isn't gonna work.
Count Selnakis' Kataphrakt, Scorching Solis.
The firing range of its onboard beam weapon
extends out to the Satellite Belt,
making air support
impossible, as well.
It's quite the monster...
Message from assault team.
They're about to make landfall.
Launch cruise missiles.
Keep his attention on us.
Getting up close and personal
is the only way, huh?
Saddle up, people!
Get ready to launch, everyone!
Inko? Inko!
Yes?
What's the matter?
It's nothing. Say, Rayet...
What?
There was that manhunt all of a sudden
the other day. For um, Ma... Mazoo...
Count Mazuurek?
Right, him!
How do you suppose he escaped?
Beats me.
I wonder if Inaho knows anything.
Why?
Well, he went to interrogate him.
Did you hear anything?
Nothing.
Oh.
Time to launch. Let's go.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, Inko.
To think that such a simple mechanism
can indicate one's bearings...
Such a device would only work on
a planet with a magnetic field.
Now, then... Count Troyard
and Inaho Kaizuka.
Both are sons of Earth.
Can they be trusted?
So simple, one cannot
go astray, eh?
True of many things, I suppose.
Are you really going to
fight the duel, Slaine?
Yes. I have been challenged,
so I cannot back down.
This happened because I allowed
Count Marylcian's visit.
Not at all. It is thanks to you.
It is the perfect opportunity
to demonstrate my strength.
If I am victorious in this duel,
it will act as a deterrent against
Orbital Knights who oppose me.
There is nothing to be
concerned about.
Your dream might actually
come true one day, won't it?
I have no dream to...
A Terran who had been held in contempt
now holds genuine power within Vers.
I have felt it ever since
we first met.
That you and I were kindred spirits.
Do you intend to hold on to your grudge
against the royal family forever?
Yes.
It's incredibly satisfying to see someone without
a drop of Versian blood in him gaining power.
I think you will never
let go, either.
Of your princess.
You genuinely love her, don't you?
If I may...
Would you let me help you?
I don't mind
if I am only my sister's substitute.
All platoons, report in!
Belgian Platoon, in position!
Maremmano Platoon, in position!
Pottok Platoon, in position!
Lokai Platoon, in position!
Mustang Platoon, in position!
There's no way to evade that
bastard's beam weapon.
Assume you're history
if you're spotted.
Begin operation!
A smoke screen that scatters everything
from infrared to radar waves, eh?
Clever monkeys.
What the hell?!
Fool.
Clydesdale Leader to all platoons!
Deploy on the south bank
and keep that smoke up!
You waste your time...
Fire, fire, fire!
Keep his attention on us!
Don't get hit!
How are we supposed to get
his attention and not get hit?!
Where's Nao?!
Up you go. Be careful.
Rayet.
Okay, I'm patching you in!
Acoustic analysis.
Enemy coordinates pinpointed.
Target is at 29.951103, -90.085579.
Roger that. Targeting location.
Fire.
Firing, roger.
Counting down. Five, four, three, two,
one.
What's that?
Impact. Correct 037, 025.
It came from the sea!
Fire.
Ship cannon fire, eh?!
Missed us!
A beam weapon can only fire
in a straight line.
If we hide behind the curve of
the Earth, it can't hit us.
But since our shells follow a parabola
due to the Earth's gravity,
they can reach
over the horizon.
As long as it's possible
to target the thing.
Correct 283, -472.
Ultra high speed rounds, fire!
Curse them, how are they
targeting me so accurately
without observation satellites?!
Is that it?
The UAVs that were relaying our
laser comms have been taken out!
We can't get through
to Ensign Kaizuka!
Rayet!
Go to tracer rounds.
Fire exactly as I say!
Over there, huh.
Nao!
Bastard!
Tracer rounds, ma'am!
Do you seriously think you can bring
down my Solis from that far?
Yuki, get clear!
Warrant Officer Kaizuka!
Stay back!
Crap!
Second volley! And a third!
Correct 002, 003! Fire!
Kaizuka!
That's right!
Stand right there and
monologue at me!
Be reduced to ash
by my scorching light!
Go ahead and shoot,
you frog-faced bastard!
Yuki!
I'm okay. I just lost an arm.
How about you guys?
We're fine. Ensign Kaizuka is safe, too.
That's great news...
No, it's not.
I told you to get clear. You disobeyed
an order, Warrant Officer.
Hey, don't talk like you're superior to me
just because you're a higher rank.
I am your superior.
No little brother can order
his big sister around.
Clydesdale Leader to all units.
Mission complete. Returning to base.
These are flowers called roses
that bloom on Earth.
Is something the matter?
Are you sure that you want to fight
this duel, Milord Slaine?
I've fought for my life
many times before.
But you...
Are you worried about me,
Miss Eddelrittuo?
You used to glare at me
all the time.
That was the past.
Roses signify many different things
in the language of flowers.
Red roses mean "I love you,"
while blue roses mean "miracle."
Miracle...
But blue roses have
one other meaning.
That meaning...
...might be true.
Let's be off!
Herschel, launch!
Good hunting, Milord Slaine.
Tharsis, launching.
The sight of a lowborn putting
on airs is offensive to me.
On the honor of Vers Orbital Knights,
I shall exact punishment.
Usurping an official post out
of self-interest without cause
disturbs both order
and public peace.
As the man in charge of Her Highness'
safety, I will punish you.
This will be a duel between
Count Marylcian and Count Troyard.
Begin!
You're a slippery devil,
just as the rumors say.
But can you escape from
my Herschel's attacks?
Milord Slaine!
Even with your predictions, not even
you can cope with this many.
What?!
Well, well, you're
fairly clever after all.
Nevertheless!
Futile, futile, it is futile!
The flower language meaning
of blue roses is "miracle"...
But their other meaning
is "the impossible."
Is it... is it truly hopeless?
Will she truly never
wake up again?
Please...
Please give him a miracle!
I see...
So it meant the impossible.
I believe in you!
There are no miracles!
Slaine!
Is running all you can do?!
You inferior scum!
Inaho? What are you looking at?
They're fighting.
Where?
There's nowhere left to run!
You're the one who has
nowhere to run.
The Herschel's greatest weapon
is a simultaneous attack
from all directions.
But here, your attack is
confined to just one.
Material loading tunnels used during
the moonbase's construction.
I've been mapping them out.
I won't be bested
by the likes of you!
Who do you think you are, Terran?!
Victor...
...Count Troyard.
In accordance with the law,
all of Count Marylcian's assets
are to be transferred to Count
Slaine Saazbaum Troyard.
Do you object?
As official witness, I, Barouhcruz,
certify the outcome.
It's over.
You can see everything, can't you?
Yes.
But I can't see what
I really want to know.
Inko, I'm sorry.
I didn't want to get you involved.
Jerk.
In conclusion,
I wish to inform you, the 37 Clans,
the new policy that we shall adopt.
We, who have acquired new lands
and resources on Earth,
do not need to rely on the
Vers homeworld forever.
Children eventually grow up
and they must leave their
mothers' protection
and strike out on their own.
I, Asseylum Vers Allusia,
will take Count Slaine Saazbaum
Troyard as my husband,
and proclaim that I shall create
a new kingdom here in Earthspace.
I always admired you.
You were beautiful, kindhearted,
and beloved by all.
You had everything
that I did not.
But you and I have one thing
in common, Sister.
Royal blood. The Aldnoah activation factor.
It is a power that Slaine
has need of now.
I have decided on Slaine.
And Slaine has chosen me.
From now on,
I am Asseylum Vers Allusia.
I am you, Sister.
So you can let go, Sister...
I'm lying.
Even if you are a puppet,
you are still my sister.
Pleasant dreams.