Morni—
Wakanalia, please help me!
We must combine our strength
to free the sun god, who's
been sealed in Amana Iward!
You were exiled from
the Country of Sound, Musico.
How can you save the world alone?
I...
She's not alone.
Sawania! You came!
I couldn't leave you by yourself, Konacchine.
Wakanalia.
Don't you also wish to take
back the Harp of the Muse?
Yes, but the Country
of Sound and I are...
I'm not concerned with saving the world.
I just want to see what
the three of us can accomplish.
It'll be fun.
You're right. Let's go.
Taking the frog brothers,
Taichi and Wien, along as companions,
they set out for the
faraway land of Amano Iward.
Cue the first song!
I want to play a prince.
There are no princes.
Hey, can I have magic powers?
Why do we have to be frogs?
This is pretty long, Konatsu.
She's right!
And there should be a lot more singing!
I know that!
Weren't you just asking about magic powers?
Don't worry!
We'll save the best for last:
Wakana's grand masterpiece
filling the whole auditorium.
My what?
How's the song coming along?
I'd like to start rehearsals soon.
Well, it's starting to take shape...
It should be done this weekend,
or maybe by the beginning of next week.
I wouldn't exactly call it a masterpiece, though.
Okay, I'll finalize the
script by then,
and we can start full rehearsals next week.
Okay.
Episode 11
Waxing and Waning
I wondered if it was getting a bit long.
You could cut it by half.
By half?!
Agreed.
Choir Club Culture Fair
Beauties and the Frogs
Script - Miyamoto
Song - Wakana
Other Candidates:
-"Amigo! Amigo!"
-"Hauoli"
Come on, you can't be serious.
If you put in some magic here,
Choreography - Sawa
Set - Tanaka
Props - Wien
Costumes - Someone help!
Stage Crew - Everyone
(26 days to go)
this scene would have a faster pace.
What do you mean by sets?
You know, like drawing mountains and
castles on plywood
for the scene backdrops.
So I'll have to draw?
No way!
I don't do art!
In fact, I was told to never draw again.
By whom?
Why won't you even try?
Don't freak out. I'm not expecting much!
It can be grade-school level, for all I care!
Wakana is writing our song,
and Sawa's doing the choreography.
We're all new at this, so
you're not getting out of it!
Capiche?
Yes, ma'am.
Great, then it's settled.
She got her way.
She's leveled up.
Wonderful, Konatsu! I'm gonna do my very best, too!
Okay?
I've put together small figures before,
but this will be my first
time working on props.
Um, 'kay...
Let's talk budget.
Normally, you'd use styrofoam
or styrene boards
We need a picture of this.
for these things, but...
Oh hey, did you bring it?
How much would that cost?
Yes...
Well, that depends on the materials...
Let's sneak outside.
Radiant Melody
Work-in-Progress (Confidential)
Thanks.
I'm still working on it.
Some parts don't quite fit yet.
So it might change...
I just need a rough idea,
so I can start planning the choreograhy.
Man, Konatsu's nuts to make me do this.
Just don't show the others, okay?
Promise.
I can't wait to hear it!
Oh no, please don't expect too much!
It's no masterpiece!
This song came from both you and your mom.
All that matters is that you're happy with it.
Konatsu said grand and all,
but she's just blowing hot air.
I know that.
It's just, writing a song's
a lot harder
than I thought it would be.
If Konatsu wasn't so determined to use it,
I might've put it away by now,
telling myself I'd finish it later.
But now I want to write
something you'll all like.
You know, I think this
will be my first
and last time choreographing anything.
Yeah?
But first, I'll give Konatsu
some embarrassing moves!
Can't wait!
White Festival
Welcome to the White Festival!
Welcome to the
White Festival | Music Stage
Is this the last one?
Yes.
Safety
Are they building something over there?
Huh?
Not that I know of.
The stairs are ten meters wide.
I listened to it!
I can't believe you wrote this!
I love it already.
Can't wait to sing it, so keep it up!
Here's today's picture.
Bye.
Thanks.
Doing my best!
I think I want live accompaniment, not recorded.
Music Practice Room Two
Ta-da!
I thought it'd be best to use some miniatures,
to make sure this is what you'd envisioned.
Wow, they look so real.
Good job! Carry on, Mr. Watson!
Watson?
I also made some drawings of the set.
Good job to you, too!
I haven't drawn in forever,
but I worked while reading manga,
and it turned out better than I thought.
Uh, what is that supposed to be?
A forest and castle, obviously.
That's a castle?
Isn't it upside-down?
That's the least of our problems.
Never draw again.
Art Room
Excuse me, is the president here?
We're all busy getting
our festival pieces ready.
All I need is a rough sketch. That's it!
I'll copy it to the plywood myself.
Have you ever painted before?
How will you apply the paint to the plywood?
Can you actually reproduce
the proper colors from a sketch?
No worries there. She's got low expectations,
so it can look like a
grade-schooler drew it.
Then do it yourself.
You're an idiot.
Hey, Hamachi.
I didn't know you were in the art club.
Yeah. I want to become a manga artist
and live the dream of
living off royalties.
Looking for an artist?
You'd do it?
I won't even shortchange you
by doing some paltry sketch.
I'll do it right, all the way!
Thanks!
But on one condition!
Okita is in your group, right?
I'll trade my services
for a picture of her!
Why?
Man, you really are an idiot.
Because she's got the looks!
Just her, though.
No group photos or shots from behind.
And make sure her chest is visible.
You can take it with your phone,
but try to make it high-res.
I'm back.
Oh, he—
Sorry, but move.
Almost there!
Welcome to the White Festival!
Shirohamazaka High School Culture
Fair White Festival
It's finally time.
Yes.
Luxury Condominium Complex
Construction Project
The project is moving to the next phase.
To ensure that we stay on schedule,
we need the consent of
the teachers and parents.
That's your job.
R-Right.
And yet it seems preparations for
the culture fair continue.
I... I haven't been able to tell them...
Listen, you'd better take care of this.
I'm holding a special assembly
with the teachers today.
I'll be speaking to the parents this weekend.
Any delay would be extremely detrimental.
Do not disappoint me.
Until the vice principal comes—
Ueno-san!
What?
I have a favor to ask of you.
Would you accompany us during our
performance at the White Festival?
Me? Why not Sakai-san?
Our group is small,
and she wants to sing with us.
We're doing a musical,
A musical?
and we need someone to accompany us.
To be honest, you're the only
one I could think of.
That sounds fun.
I know, right?
You don't have time to
play with these amateurs.
We have preparations of
our own to take care of.
This year especially...
Right.
What's wrong?
Usually, by this time,
our song's been selected
and we're rehearsing.
But the vice principal hasn't
told us what we're doing yet...
With all the songs we have to perfect
before the festival,
you don't have extra time.
It might be okay if
it's a song I already know.
What are you singing?
Something Sakai-san's writing.
Writing?!
Yup!
You stupid amateurs...
We're not stupid!
If anything, you're way dumber,
if you can't even pick a song yourself!
But the vice principal's
been acting so strange lately...
True.
She's like one of those time-travelling
robot weapons you see in the movies.
Except now she's run out of juice...
What?
Afternoon, folks. Welcome to the meeting.
Thank you for coming.
If this is about that thing,
I don't need to hear any more.
Um, right. My apologies.
Nao!
Hey! Cut the chatter!
Get in your groups and do your exercises!
Now!
Everbody's too relaxed,
with the vice principal absent.
She's not showing up again today?
It doesn't matter.
We can do this on our own!
Right.
She won't be here again?
That's not good.
It's like a different club,
compared to when I was here.
I'm sorry, we haven't finished
our basic routine yet.
It's fine.
This year's culture fair
has been cancelled.
What?!
We will have to suspend new
student applications for next year.
As you are aware, the declining birth rate
has led to an annual decrease in students.
It's been extremely difficult
for the school to
secure funding in recent years.
And so, we arrived at this
conclusion because we care
about our student body
above all else.
Personally, I am overcome
with sadness and regret,
but with your support,
I would like to keep moving forward.
We will be setting up
temporary classrooms on the
school grounds immediately,
and classes will be held
there starting next year.
About the White Festival Cancellation
The renovations to the main building
will begin in the new year,
and preparations for the school
grounds will also begin then.
We promise that all our
students will be able
to attend their classes,
unhindered, up to graduation.
However, should any wish
to transfer,
we will do our utmost to support them.
White Festival Cancellation Notice
You're still doing that?
Yeah, it's relaxing.
Don't you have to study
for your entrance exams?
Now you sound like my mom.
I'm everyone's mom.
That makes no sense.
You know, you should keep
singing, even after you graduate.
Maybe.
Were you playing badminton?
Yeah.
Hey, what are you guys doing here?
I feel like we haven't met up in forever.
Even though we see each
other in class everyday...
Heading home?
Yeah.
Lucky Tanaka's got badminton,
so he doesn't have to study.
Not that again.
My bad.
Should we go home?
I finished the song!
I want us to sing the song
my mom and I wrote, together!
We might not be able to do
anything about our school shutting down,
but it's not over yet!
Let's have a White Festival!
Mom, I finished the song
we promised to make.
I have faith.
We're going to do this seriously!
Episode 12
Piling Up and Rippling
Horse...
Even then, we're going to sing!