Saito?
I wonder what happened.
Since then, no matter
how many times I call,
he doesn't answer.
I didn't think about it at the time,
but what kind of magic could connect
this room with the queen's?
I've never even heard
of something like that.
A spell that connects you
to your desired location...
We have an emergency!
What happened?
It's...
What's happening?
Why is there hot water
coming out of the ground?
This is the wrath of the land!
We're going to die! I'm so scared!
You're overreacting.
It's just a hot spring.
Hot spring?
A natural phenomenon where
hot water springs from the ground.
It is common to take
baths in this water.
T-Take baths?!
Wow! That feels great!
It's just the right temperature.
I never thought I'd be
able to take a hot
spring bath over here.
It's really good for your skin, right?
There was one back in my village, too.
Skin...
I know! Let's have a party here.
A party?
Yeah.
I've been wanting to invite Guiche
and the others once we
settled down a bit,
but since we're all here,
let's go for a dip.
What?! Get in it together?!
This is going to be fun. Yeah!
Trouble at the Outdoor Bath
Friends, please lend me your ears!
The second in command of our
Order of the Undine Knights
and the new lord of
De Ornierés, Saito,
has invited us to a grand opening party.
Furthermore, apparently
there's this thing called a
"hot spring" on his land.
That's something like a bath, right?
According to Saito's letter,
it's customary in a hot spring to
interact in the nude.
In the nude... That means, of course...
Long live the Order of
the Undine Knights!
I heard that your skin gets so
unbelievably beautiful
after a hot spring visit
that you can make any man yours.
Then Jean will finally be mine.
Tiffa!
You're going to the party, too, right?
Yes.
I'll be able to see Saito soon...
So there's only one tub?
We're going to get in
at different times.
First the women go in,
then the guys go in.
This truly is any man's dream.
Hey!
You totally just pictured
the other girls.
Of course not. Why would I do that?
Screw this hot spring.
I'm not getting in.
Then it's all for nothing.
It was my dream to
get in a hot spring together
with someone I love.
T-Together?!
Yeah. Get in with me, Louise!
A-A-Are you crazy?!
I'd be so embarrassed, I'd die!
Tabitha...
Tabitha!
Wait up, Tabitha.
I just wanted to thank
you for before.
What are you talking about?
Thanks to you,
I was able to make up with Saito.
Really, thank you.
The next time something
happens, I'm taking him.
Tomorrow's finally the day!
Siesta, what are the
plans for tomorrow?
Please rest assured.
I'm going to prepare
a feast true to its name.
Tabitha?
You haven't eaten anything.
Is something wrong?
Thanks for the meal.
Unlike you, my sister eats like a bird.
If that's what it is.
But since the hot spring is finished,
I'd want her to get in, too.
Ow!
I can't believe you.
We have to get up early tomorrow.
I'm going to bed.
My foot...
I don't have time.
If you know that, you have
to lay your egg quickly!
You won't get any more chances!
Aren't you in love with him?!
Then...
I know.
I didn't realize it got so late
while we were getting
ready for tomorrow.
Oh, Louise is already sleeping?
Right now we're alone...
Louise...
I've always wanted to do this.
Don't worry,
I'll be gentle.
Louise.
That voice was...
T-Tabitha?!
Please just keep going.
Huh? But, you? Keep going?
I want you
to have me.
Huh? But, wait, Tabit—
Saito, I know what I said earlier,
but I'll actually get
in the hot spring, too.
T-Tabitha?!
Saito?
Yes!
Care to explain?
It's not what you think!
I mistook her for you and...
Mistook?
I mean, just like you, her chest is...
What about her chest?!
No, I mean, wait!
This is a what you call
an unfortunate accident.
L-Louise?!
Anyone who's like me is out!
Since I'm his master,
naturally I'm by his side.
Since I'm his maid...
I don't think this will work.
How about we settle it
with rock paper scissors?
Why are you in charge of this?
Um... So...
What?!
I have a good idea...
I can't sleep like this.
I just can't sleep without Saito!
No sneaking out.
I'm just going to the bathroom.
Then I'll go, too.
Bathroom!
Huh? W-Wait...
So,
what happened?
Nothing...
Thank you for waiting.
Our guests have just arrived!
Hello, everyone.
Guiche! Guys! Thanks for coming.
So Saito's finally a lord.
That's quite a move up the ladder.
I'm looking forward to it!
The nude interaction.
Yeah, the hot spring feels great.
What? You haven't even kissed him?
Tabitha's not like you, you know.
But if she goes back to Gallia
without having done anything,
coming here was pointless.
Congratulations, Saito.
Miss Vallière...
You're embarrassing me.
What? Someone suspicious?
Over there.
You're right.
That person is the
definition of suspicious.
Give it up, you creeper!
I'm not letting go!
What do you want here?
Your Majesty?!
I've come, too.
Would you be so kind as to show me
the hot spring that makes
your skin beautiful?
So this is the hot spring.
It feels quite nice.
You came here without an escort.
The court must be in an uproar.
It's fine, I left a note behind.
So what brings you here?
If you can't say it,
shall I do it for you?
Huh?
You came here for the
hidden room, didn't you?
Wh-What are you talking about?
No use in denying it.
Saito told me everything.
Your Majesty, you're a liar.
What exactly do you mean?
The Sleipnir Ball.
That was...
Back then...
Back then you said,
"From now on, I will only
show myself as a queen."
And yet...
I can't help it.
I seriously fell in love with him.
Can't help it?
Are you going back on your word?!
Falling in love with the same person
happens quite often, does it not?
Saito is off limits!
I can't back down on that!
I also can't go on without Saito!
I bet you just used your
needlessly sensual body to seduce Saito!
If you're so jealous,
why don't you mature a bit?
How dare you say that after
you laid hands on my man?!
Don't you have any shame?!
I haven't done anything bad.
Just so you know,
our friendship is over if
you get any closer to Saito!
You bitch!
Now you've done it!
Louise!
Let go!
You've always been like this!
When I was playing with
my dolls, you'd say,
"Oh, Louise, those are cute.
Can I have them?"
and take them without
batting an eyelash.
Then you'd get bored and toss
them aside right away.
I bet that's how you
feel about Saito, too!
Saito is different.
And not to mention, I don't think Saito
will ever feel satisfied
with this flat board.
Who are you calling flat,
you thieving cat?!
Milk jugs!
Carpenter's dream!
We haven't had a wrestling match
like this since we were kids.
Just so you know, our score is
27 wins, 25 losses, and
2 draws, in my favor.
No, it's 29 wins, 24 losses,
1 draw, in my favor.
In my favor!
No, in mine!
I'm going to win!
Now it's 27 wins, 25
losses, and 3 draws.
It's 29 wins, 24 losses, and 2 draws.
But I'm not giving up on Saito.
You're still...
Yes. I don't want to regret anything.
Regret?
In this day and age,
you never know when a
lord may lose his life.
Just the other day in Romalia,
both you and Saito were on
the edge of life and death.
That's why I don't want to lie to
myself about my feelings any longer.
Your Majesty...
This felt like when we
were kids. I had fun,
Louise.
I'm also glad I was
able to talk to you.
The queen is here?!
Apparently she came here in secret.
She called for you.
I see. Thanks, Siesta.
Saito, I'm sorry for
calling you out here.
It's no problem. I actually
wanted to talk to you.
To me?
Yes.
Everything that happened
recently is my fault.
I'm sorry.
When I was still living in my world,
I was living a really careless life.
I never got involved in anything,
and just lived day to day.
I thought that's how you
somehow become an adult.
I thought that was good enough.
But when I came here, I finally
understood what I'm here for.
Louise...
Yes.
I realized, when she was gone,
how much I love her.
Even when you have to go
back to your own world?
I'll cross that bridge
when I come to it.
But right now I want to be with Louise.
I want to protect her.
I mean, that's all I can do.
And that is how you really feel?
Yes.
Understood.
But that won't change how I feel.
Your Majesty...
Um, is it really all right...
for me to be in here with you?
Of course it is.
Being nude together without any
regard for standing is what hot
springs are supposedly all about.
But still, I'm really surprised.
I didn't know you had come here.
I thought I'd also work on
my femininity by getting
in the hot spring.
Maybe then...
Saito will...
It's actually true.
My skin is so smooth now.
With this, Saito's sure to be mine!
No he isn't!
You horny maid! Milk maid!
I had decided to give up
on Saito. Then why...
So this is it!
That's what it means
to not hide anything!
Hooray for nude interaction!
What nude interaction?! You perverts!
Voyeur!
Pigs!
Disappear!
Jeez, they never learn.
Miss Westwood!
Tiffa, are you all right?
I kind of feel dizzy.
She was in the hot water for too long.
You should get some rest outside.
Siesta, can you take her?
I'll be fine on my own.
Is this it?
Do you think Tiffa will be
all right being left back there?
It was just the heat.
She'll be fine once
she rests for the night.
Today was fun, huh, Louise?
I was surprised about
the queen, but...
Oh, sorry.
What is it?
Oh, nothing. It's getting
late, let's go inside.
Louise?
Saito, I...
H-Hey! Louise!
Saito...
Louise...
You wanted to get in together, right?
Well, I did say that, but...
Then hurry.
This is embarrassing for me, too.
O-Okay...
What happened all of a sudden?
I don't want to have any regrets.
Regrets?
We never know when we'll
be in danger again.
So I want to cherish the time
the two of us can spend together.
I feel the same, Louise.
And...
It's okay for you to look at other girls.
You can even cheat on me.
But promise me one thing.
Don't die before me.
Louise...
Because I know that
that's the only thing
I wouldn't be able to bear.
That's what I wanted to say.
Don't you dare die before me,
Louise.
Then when we die, we'll die together.
Yeah.
Saito...
Louise...
Wait...
I changed my mind about cheating.
If possible, only look at me.
I promise.
Louise...
Saito...
I think I was born for
this moment, Louise.
What? Why is Tiffa here?!
You promised, no cheating, Saito.
I don't know why she's here!
You pervert!
You should just die!
Help!
Oh no, the Elemental Siblings
are gunning for us again!
What? And elves are attacking, too?!
Next time: Elves from the Desert.
Hey, Saito!
Why are you and Tiffa
alone at an oasis?!
Elves from the Desert