Hey, welcome back.
How'd your date go?
Uh...
It ended before it even started?
What?
I found it when I was going
through some old albums.
Are you Haru-kun?
Nice to meet you.
I'll be taking care of you from now on.
I'm your Aunt Kyoko.
What makes us human?
Education,
language,
tool use, and
love.
I know, Haru-kun.
I'll cast a spell on you.
Yoshida-kun?
Yo, class rep.
Whatcha up to?
I have a meeting for
the cultural festival.
What about you, Yoshida-kun?
Sunbathing Nagoya.
I don't think I've seen you
since you asked about my balls.
Don't mention that!
The Distance
Between Us
So, I've been working
hard as the class rep.
I've been doing what
I can, like you said.
Now I have more little tasks to do.
Why did I get assigned to the
cultural festival committee?
Oh, I learned that from someone else.
Still, I feel better now.
Really?  That's nice.
Uh-huh.
Why is that guy hitting on
a girl at a time like this?
Oh, class rep.
Shizuku shot me down.
Huh?  What?
You told her how you feel?
No, I didn't.
When you asked me how
I felt about Shizuku,
that opened my eyes,
but I guess it's too late.
R-Really?
Goo—
Good luck...
Huh?
If she didn't flat out reject you,
maybe you still have a chance.
You think so?
She looked like she was completely
done with this problem set.
Well, it doesn't matter.
I also learned this from someone else.
"You can't pick up water once it's
spilled, so handle it carefully."
That's why I don't want
to make a mistake.
Banana Juice
That's stupid.
Natsume?
If you have time to spend
thinking of stuff like that,
go tell her how you feel.
Slide while the iron's hot.
Are you drunk?
And you used the wrong...
Banana juice wouldn't make me drunk!
So what if Mitty isn't very responsive?
That's what makes Mitty attractive.
That's why I can relax around her.
She's not interested in me,
so she doesn't call me phony or slutty
or anything stupid like that.
You're such a baby, Haru-kun.
If she shoots you down, keep on trying!
Stupid
loser!
Wh-What's her problem?
I keep getting in trouble
with women these days.
Haru.
Wait.
Never mind.
Haru.
That's nothing new.
Business as usual.
That's no good, Haru.
Honestly, you keep breaking stuff.
It's such a waste.
Screw you, old lady.
Eh?
Hey, stupid kid!
Watch your mouth!
Lemme go!
Mitsuyoshi, stop it.
What?  You're already done?
Wow, I'm impressed.
Good job, Haru-kun.
This doesn't mean anything.
Silly boy.
Why are you denying your own strengths?
Now listen to me, Haru.
Humans will wither away
if they're always alone.
The only remedy would be
to seek out other people.
I hope you find the
right person one day.
I hope you find someone
whose presence is enough
to soothe your pain.
Haru, get that bird off me.
You look like you're
enjoying yourself, Haru.
Yep, I was thinking
about a dead person.
Huh?
"Clean up after yourself."
"If you want to be accepted,
you must first accept yourself."
I wonder why I still
remember all these things.
I love you.
But just so you know...
You're not in love with
me anymore, right?
I know that.
I just want to be with you.
Haru...
Whoa, there!
Oh, sorry.
As soon as I realized that I love you,
I started having these urges.
His actions don't match his words...
Let's go out?
I can see that you didn't
understand a word I said.
But you said that you'd go out
with me if I fell in love with you.
That's ancient history.
I don't see a problem.
This makes everyone happy.
Are you ignoring my feelings?
What am I supposed to do then?
You're the one who said you
just wanted to be with me.
Are you an idiot?!
No man's gonna put up with that!
What are you trying to say?!
Give in!  Give in!  Give in!  Give in!
Leave! Scram! Get lost!
After that,
I began to feel as though I
were in constant danger.
Midterm Grades
Freshmen
1st Yoshida Haru
2nd Mizutani Shizuku
3rd Sawada Riku
4th Kasano Masamune
Why...
Why can't I win?!
Well, I tried a little
harder this time.
Just a little.
Damn him!
I'll win next time!
Am I a distraction now?
No.
I hope you find the
right person one day.
I hope you find someone
whose presence is enough
to soothe your pain.
Okay.
I'll have to try harder then.
Borderline
Above
Average
Yikes, I barely passed.
By the way, Natsume-san has
to take make-ups again.
Sasaki Seminar
Pass Before Graduation
I'll be posting the scores
from the last mock exam.
Let me know if you want
your results mailed.
Kaimei Academy...
The rich kid school.
You didn't do too well on the
last mock exam, Mizutani-san.
By the way, how is
your beloved Haru-kun doing?
You have any nails?
Crap, I forgot the supplies.
I'll make a quick trip to the store.
Oh, what was his name?
Should you really be loafing around here?
Weren't you all hyped about handing out
flyers with Natsume-san
to bond with the class?
Oh, everyone ran away when they saw me,
so she said we should part ways.
Didn't take long for her to turn on me.
I see.
Syoyo Festival
Oh, yeah.
These tickets are for you.
Shimoyanagi-kun gave them to me.
I let my guard down...
Haru, if you touch me
without permission or
get too close again, I'll be upset.
It's your fault for distancing yourself
the moment I said I loved you.
Are you mocking me?
It's because you keep doing stuff like this!
So I should ask for permission first?
No!
Don't make me repeat myself, Haru!
If you refuse to give
me my personal space,
I can't be with you.
How much space do I have to give you?
Around two meters.
Get real!
Can you at least respect my wishes?
Otherwise, I can't feel comfortable around you.
Dammit!
Can't get too close, can't touch her...
Am I a slug or something?
Why does this happen?!
C-Can you blame her?
Your behavior's been very abnormal.
Shizuku.  Shizuku.  Shizuku.
I don't see the problem.
Well, you see...
There's nothing more
repulsive than being touched
by a guy you don't like.
I-Is that how it works?
This is hard...
What are you making over there?
A barricade.
Since a bunch of people will be coming.
I'm naming it Mizutani Shizuku.
You'll get in trouble.
Oh, look.
Mitty's back.
What?
We can't get a spot in building one?
Shh!  Keep your voice down!
Our plan won't work then!
Try harder, Yana!
Wh-Why do I have to do this?!
We can't make any money
if people don't come!
What are you talking about?
Uh-oh.
Crap...
Make money off the cultural festival?
Right.
We can just report our official sales,
and make a little more on the side.
I've heard that all the
upperclassmen do it.
We heard about it from the
ones on the baseball team.
So that's why they were so excited.
In that case, this would
be more effective.
Oh, I see.
You're really smart, Mizutani-san!
I want a fifty percent cut.
But we really need a spot in building one.
Is there a problem?
Everyone wants a good spot,
and Yana's scared of the upperclassmen.
Stupid...
They're intimidating, man!
The third-year class reps
all have scary faces!
You should beat them up.
Then we'll start taking
requests for building one.
3-A wants a spot on the south
side of the first floor.
3-D wants a spot by the
stairwell on the first floor.
2-C also wants a spot
on the first floor.
Second-years don't get no say!
D-Doesn't look like the
first-years have any chance.
I'll kill you, fool!
I-I'm sorry!
Y-Yeah...
1-B wants a spot by the
first floor entrance.
Mi-Mizutani-san?!
You really shouldn't...
1-B wants a spot by the
first floor entrance.
Got a problem?
I told Haru not to go crazy...
Worried
Hey, Yoshida.
If you get too uppity...
assigned to a corner in building 2
Final
What?  That's the worst possible spot.
I'm sorry.
Yoshida-kun.
Yo, class rep.
Are you okay? You're all banged up.
Sure.
I heard that your class
got put in building two.
Yeah, looks like it.
Sasayan and some other guys
went to file a protest.
I have to pull weeds until
the festival starts.
Nagoya
I was wondering...  What is that?
A barricade.
I named it Mizutani Shizuku.
Mizutani-san won't like that...
Shizuku was mad at me.
She told me not to fight
before we went in.
Th-That's not right, Yoshida-kun.
You should be sorry about making trouble
for your classmates.
And, if you care about Mizutani-san,
you should learn to solve
things without violence.
Huh?
Mizutani-san was mad
because she was worried about you
doing dangerous things for her sake.
R-Really?!
I could have sworn she was mad
because I ruined her plans!
B-Bye.
I'll be going then.
I fell in love with the wrong person...
Oh.  Wait, class rep.
You said that you didn't
like yourself, right?
I don't get that.
I don't see what's not to like.
Yo—
Yoshida-kun.
My name isn't class rep.
It's not class rep...
It's Oshima.
Yeah, Oshima.
Yoshida-kun, the other day,
you said that you didn't
want to make a mistake,
but I think I'm willing
to take that risk,
because I'm not ready to give up yet.
When did I say that?
Am I really that forgettable?!
Well, I'm not sure I get it,
but good luck anyway.
Why am I hiding?
Poster Color Set
Paint
Nails
Don't forget anything
Do we really need
That's a relief.
We couldn't get a spot in building one,
three people to buy this stuff?
but at least they moved us to the
first floor of building two.
Sorry, can I stop by my cram school?
What?  We'll come with you.
Fine with me.
Why do they like moving
around in groups?
I bet Haru-kun's feeling
lonely right now.
There!  Learned your lesson now?
Hey!  It's you guys!
Hey, Sasayan!
Long time no see!
Wait, you guys actually go to school?
Natsume-chan is here too!
What were they doing?
Yo, Mizutani-san.
You wanted to check your scores?
Sasaki Seminar
Pass Before Graduation
What?  You're not Haru's girlfriend?
Why not?
How am I supposed to answer that?
The only reason I can give
is that I need to study.
That's a boring way to live.
I don't need you people lecturing me.
Don't lump me in with those fools.
They're no more than idiots.
Don't you enjoy watching people
who aren't as smart as you?
Really?
When I watch them, I feel
like I'm falling behind.
It worries me.
1st Mizutani Shizuku
3rd Yamaguchi Kenji
Well, it certainly feels good
to look down on other people.
That's a boring way to live.
It's okay.
I'm doing the right thing.
We're begging you!
One!  Just one!
Please give us a ticket
to the cultural festival!
N-No way!
I'm saving these for
the new friends I make
at my "Nobody Visits
My Site" offline event!
Sorry, I gave all mine to
my middle school buddies.
Co-ed schools can die!
See?
Isn't it amusing to watch stupid people?
They're pitiful.
Yamaken!
Acting all snobby again?
You people make too much noise.
You can have these.
I don't need them.
If Haru were here,
he would have done the same thing.
You're a goddess, studybug!
Studybug!  Studybug!  Studybug!
Sorry, but she gave them to me.
She never said to share them with you.
Are you a devil, Yamaken?!
Haru.
Yo, Shizuku.
Fancy meeting you here.
Did you enjoy shopping
with lots of people?
I stopped by the batting center,
and Mi-chan-san said that
you went to buy dinner.
Here, this is from Natsume-san.
Shizuku.
Why were you looking for me?
To give you that.
Oh, I see...
I'm not going to fall in love with you.
What's this about?
Are you trying to pick a fight with me?
It would be cruelest to
keep your hopes up
when I already know the answer.
Fine.
I just have to change your mind.
Give me the bag.
There's nothing more
repulsive than being touched
by a guy you don't like.
That was close...
I'm going home!
I didn't make a mistake.
I'm doing the right thing.
I'm doing the right thing...
So...
Why...
Why is this happening again?
Stay calm.  Stay calm.  Stay calm.
Save money
Loan paid off!!
Hey, Haru.
Don't you want any takoyaki?
Nope, you can have them.
What's this?
Natsume gave it to me.
I'm supposed to drink
it if I feel irritated.
Shizuku's so cute.
I'm going home!
What was that about?
Oh, that's nice.
The springtime of your life.
Well... Good luck, Haru.
Yeah.
The coop has been powered up!
A barricade of barbed wire?
How does he get inside?
How does he get out then?!
So this is what it means
to be barrier free!
Next Episode
Come Down to Syoyo Festival!
You're so smart, Tomio.