Hey, Karasuno's switching setters.
Don't get depressed.
We're just changing up the rhythm for a bit.
I'm sorry.
I'm worried about him, but...
If these two break right now,
at the same time...
I said I'd be the one that defeats you!
Hinata, you're gonna get in trouble—
So don't lose to anyone else before that!
The match isn't over yet,
so I haven't lost.
You're going to get in trouble!
Guess I don't have anything
to worry about after all.
Kageyama, make sure you take stock
of things from outside the court,
and use that time to calm down.
Watch how your senpai plays.
Haikyu!!
Hey!
Episode 21: Senpai's True Abilities
It'll be fine. Let's break their streak.
All right!
What?
Jeez, your face is scary.
I was born with this face!
You were all irritated,
and stopped talking as much...
I could tell you were thinking, and stuff,
but if you don't say it out loud,
I don't know what you're thinking.
Wasn't I saying it out loud?
Nope... You were quieter
than in any other match.
For crying out loud...
Damn it. I was so overwhelmed I end up
having to hear about this from him?
Hey, the Karasuno setter
that just went in is #2.
Oh, he's a third-year.
2: Sugawara Koshi
So some genius first-year that just joined
took his starter position?
Daichi, you're not being as loud as usual.
A captain can't lose his composure!
Yeah, I'm sorry.
The only person that can lecture Daichi...
...is Suga-san.
Tsukishima.
I don't know just how good
Mr. Refreshing over there is,
but seeing him up close, the words
"serious" and "polite" seem to fit him well.
Iwa-chan, the defensive block will be low
straight forward where #2-kun is standing,
so it'd be a good place to aim.
Right.
Nice receive!
Tanaka!
Iwa-chan!
I've got to aim...
straight forward where the block is low.
Iwa—
Denied!
I guess they figured out they'd
be aiming straight forward.
Right? Well done.
The blockers switched places right
before the opponent's spike.
Nice block, Tsukishima. Nice, nice!
But you're the one...
Whenever we're up against a strong team,
they usually aim right for me
since my block is so low.
I figured that'd happen this time, too.
I feel so relieved,
being next to someone so tall.
Um, well... right.
Sorry.
Don't mind!
Sorry, Iwa-chan.
Aoba Johsai     Karasuno
Hinata.
Tsukishima, nice serve!
Right.
Nice receive, Kunimi-chan!
Whoa, they totally returned it!
Are they gonna do a quick?
A-quick!
All right!
Hinata, great job!
It's just like you said, Sugawara-san!
Next time their receive
goes directly to the setter,
the center will probably do a quick set.
Don't panic, though. Just jump
a little higher than usual.
Right?
I know I felt frustrated watching
the game from the outside,
but I saw the game more calmly
than I would if I was playing.
The time I wasn't in the game
has been preparation for this.
They seemed to be more fired up now.
Yeah...
It'll be fine.
Huh?
Weren't you worried that Kageyama-kun
would get angry that you benched him,
since he seems so proud?
It'll be fine.
Kageyama-kun's strength
and how well he plays
is because of his great pride,
but even more more,
because of his drive to improve.
Aoba Johsai                          Karasuno
Tsukishima, one more nice serve!
Let's break their serve streak!
Let's see, the next attack...
Right!
Let's go!
Nice serve!
I don't have the ability to do
pinpoint tosses like Kageyama,
so I want to signal what kind
of attack we'll do next.
"The poor third-year that was
replaced by the genius first-year."
I'm sure that's how some
people would see Suga, but...
They're not saying "bring it" or "to me!"
He's not Tobio, so there
won't be any god-like quicks!
Right!
Suga is Karasuno's other setter.
He has run simulations in his head
of what it will be like
when he's actually on the court.
All right!
I'm definitely inferior to Kageyama
when it comes to technique
and physical ability,
but I've spent quite a
while watching our team.
If it were just me against Aoba Johsai,
I wouldn't stand a chance,
but my teammates are plenty strong.
Let's break their serve streak!
Right!
21  - 14
Aoba Johsai         Karasuno
21  - 15
All right!
Don't mind, Hinata.
Hey...
Nice serve!
One point!
Damn it.
Now it's Oikawa-san's serve...
Bring it!
Go!
Got it!
Leave it to me!
Now he's aiming between them.
All right!
He's aiming at the optimal spot!
My bad! I was about to get it!
And I overstepped my bounds. Sorry!
Go!
The front!
All right!
Aoba Johsai                                     Karasuno
Seijoh's at their set point.
Damn.
Just how many points did
that guy's serves get them?
If volleyball had an ultimate play,
it'd be to take 25 points just by serving,
Let's finish this!
Yeah!
not giving your opponent
even a single chance.
That's what a service ace is.
I got it!
Right!
#10 followed by #5 from the right...
No, it's a back attack!
Hanamaki, nice receive!
Hinata, it's coming directly to you!
This is the first time
it's come directly to me.
You suck!
Oh, shut up, already!
Hey...
The timing of Seijoh's quicks seems
to be a bit slower than ours.
Build up just a bit more than usual, then.
Jump!
Back! Go back!
It's out?!
Aoba Johsai                                    Karasuno
We're switching sides. Let's go!
Ow!
So close, Hinata.
We'll stop them next time!
Right!
Damn it, that was close!
They totally got our timing.
Since #2 came in,
even the shrimp, who was just
moving purely on instinct,
is now thinking before he moves.
Rule the Court
Aoba Johsai High School Volleyball Club
Here.
We'll go as-is with our second set.
Right!
Since the most troublesome thing
we're facing is Oikawa's serves,
we'll be changing up our defense
to maximize efficiency with few players.
Aoba Johsai
So Karasuno's attacks...
Since we were assuming that their only attack
was the quick with Kageyama and that #10,
it totally throws us off
when they do normal attacks.
We end up looking toward #10 too much.
Iwa-chan, if you think too hard
when you don't have a brain,
you're going to hurt your head.
It's true that even in our practice match,
all eyes were on Kageyama.
To think they had another special setter...
Sugawara-san!
Yeah?
Kindachi's... Um, Radish's...
Could it be that #12's
quick timing is a bit slow?
I think it is!
He looks, and looks... and then hits
the ball. Or something like that.
Oh, also... I just realized this
when I came into the game,
Now that someone completely unknown,
Sugawara, is controlling our game,
but our opponent will definitely
aim for any holes that we have,
our opponents are in a state of confusion.
so we can use that to our advantage.
It's the gap between him
and Kageyama-kun, right?
Yeah. My original plan was to have him help
the other players regain their calm,
but to think it would also result in this.
We'll definitely be able to use
this in other matches, too.
Kageyama.
Yes?
We... how do I say this, seem to be
in competition over the same position...
I want to be in a lot of matches, too!
I-I do, too, but...
But now that I'm on the court,
the enemies are giants,
and their spikes are directed right at me.
Honestly, it scares me.
Before, I would have let it affect me,
but now you've got my back.
I feel really confident.
The points we get when I'm on the court,
and the points we get when
you're on the court...
All together, they're points for Karasuno.
I'll fight my best,
and you'll fight your best...
That's how we're going to defeat Seijoh!
Right!
Kageyama-kun, are you feeling
a bit depressed?
No, I'm not!
What the heck?!
I was just feeling sorry for
you since you were pulled out!
Just worry about yourself!
What was up with that sucky direct attack?
Sh-Shut up! That was my first time!
As soon as I'm back in,
I'll have you hitting one after another,
so you'd better be prepared!
Karasuno                                        Aoba Johsai
Let's go!
Yeah!
Suga!
Don't you go into overthinking mode, too!
R-Right...
We're gonna take it back in the second set.
And to do that...
We've got to plan for Oikawa's serves.
Oh?
Looks like Karasuno changed up their
rotation a bit for the second set,
and Seijoh kept it the same as the first set.
I wonder why they changed it, though.
All right!
Nice, Tsukishima!
Oh, thanks.
All right! Let's do one more!
Sugawara-san gives you nice
compliments when you get one in!
I see...
It's not like being overly buddy-buddy,
but I think he says what he does
based on the spikers' expressions
and how they're doing that day.
And unlike the second and third-years,
I'm sure for Tsukishima,
there are a lot of things he
doesn't know about Sugawara-san.
"Why do I have to match
what I do with how others are feeling,
especially Tsukishima, that jerk?"
That's what's written on your face.
Th-That's not what I...
But Kageyama,
if Hinata seems to have a hard time
hitting the ball, you switch things up, right?
Yes, because he misses easily.
I think that everyone else also
has their own techniques
and that affects how they hit the ball.
I might sound biased, but...
I think our spikers are pretty skilled.
I think that, too, but...
Then,
if they were all able to hit the ball
with 100% of their ability,
don't you think they'd be able
to break through a block?
One point!
It's the Great King's turn to serve!
Oh?
There're only two in position
to receive the serve.
...Oikawa's serves,
we'll be changing up our defense
to maximize efficiency with few players.
When Oikawa does his super-fast serves,
even the slightest hesitation
or faltering is deadly.
So, we'll use Nishinoya and Sawamura,
the few who recceived his serves, to counter.
It's a formation we've
never used in practice.
But considering it's you guys...
We can do it.
So cool!
The rotation they have for the second set...
The reason they changed things
up a bit from the first set is...
...to bring this rotation around
when it's Oikawa's turn to serve.
In the first set, they were able to get
We're going to break their serve streak!
five points due to Oikawa's
serves breaking through,
Yeah!
and his service aces.
If we don't return his serves,
we won't be able to defeat Seijoh.
Bring it!
Go!
Daichi!
Yes!
Nice receive!
There's something important about breaking
Oikawa's streak on his first serve.
If he makes it, it'll be a heavy point.
It'll be an important point, as well
as a point filled with pressure.
Right now, the one
who's feeling confident from breaking
his streak in the first set is...
Tanaka!
I'm leaving this to you!
All...
...right!
They broke the serve streak!
Well done, Captain.
All right! One point!
Tsukishima, nice serve!
I think our spikers are pretty skilled.
if they were all able to hit the ball
with 100% of their ability,
don't you think they'd be able
to break through a block?
I have no complaints about
the morale of our team.
Seijoh is vastly better in terms
of experience and technique.
Let's get that point!
Yeah!
There's no denying that if they get
ahead again, it'll be extremely tough.
But if we hold on with all we've got,
the momentum will turn our way.
Karasuno                     Aoba Johsai
All right! They're equal in the second set!
All right!
Nice, Asahi-san!
Yeah, but the blockers are keeping up.
Kindaichi, you're starting
to read their attacks.
Yes!
Mr. Refreshing definitely
isn't a weak setter,
but all of his attacks are textbook.
None of the set-ups are reckless.
Karasuno's basic offensive
strength is indeed high,
but we've played a number teams like that.
Now, let's get our lead.
Yes!
It feels like their spikes are going
through our setter a lot more.
Go, go, Hajime! Push it, push it, Hajime!
Yeah.
Nice serve!
Karasuno                           Aoba Johsai
Seijoh just scored multiple points.
A break happens when the momentum changes...
Don't let Seijoh get it now.
Since they changed setters,
Karasuno seems to be using
their left quite a bit.
Their left side is pretty strong,
but that might be easier to face
than #10 when he goes crazy.
All right! One point!
Slowly, I feel like I'm being strangled...
Yet strangely, I feel rather calm,
because panic hasn't affected
my concentration just yet.
That's because our goal is
so clear in front of us.
Go! One point!
I thought that getting benched proved
that you weren't needed anymore.
Back then, I'm pretty sure
that was actually accurate.
Now you've got my back.
I feel really confident.
The things that Sugawara-san
and I can do are different,
but I think our goal is the same.
Left! Left!
Cover! Cover!
All right!
I want to be in it.
I want to be in it. I want to be in it.
I want to be in the game.
I want to stay here longer.
I want to stay with these guys.
Give me the thrill of the court.
I want to fight with these guys longer.
Let me feel out of breath.
Let me stand here.
I want to touch the ball. I want to fight.
I want to throw up a toss
with my own hands...
...over and over.
Then...
...I'll do my best, and you'll
do your best, and then...
...we'll win the match that's
right in front of us!
Nice receive!
All right!
Kindaichi, nice block!
Sorry, Hinata. I think that
quick might have been too slow.
Oh, it's okay.
Ah, Karasuno's #9's been called.
Looks like they're switching setters again.
I think I've probably
only got one more play.
Suga.
Give me the next one.
I'll definitely make it.
Got it!
Nice serve!
Wow.
It's a bit frustrating,
but Hinata's face when he hits my toss
isn't the same as when he hits your toss.
I think you know this, but...
all of our guys are really strong.
Right.
All right. Let's—
Let's Win
Let's win this thing!
Right.
Great job.
You fought on equal ground with Seijoh.
Well, all of our guys are strong.
But you know... Next time, you can
use the center more aggressively.
Right! Thank you very much!
What?
I think the words "next time"
meant a lot to Sugawara-kun.
If we can bring out everyone's
strengths effectively,
we can really fight Seijoh.
But,
to move forward, we need Karasuno's
ultimate decoy to be functioning at 100%.
The only one who can make that happen...
...is you, Kageyama.
Next Episode Preview
Welcome back, Tobio-chan!
I'm going to be giving it all I've got.
Now, now, relax your shoulders.
It's not like you can do much.
Tsukishima! He's meaner than you are!
Are you okay with that?
I'm not exactly competing
with anyone about that.
Episode 22: Evolution
Next time on Haikyuu!: Evolution