Be sure you make yourself heard!
Right!
Right...
Yeah!
Hm... Karasuno definitely seems different.
Sorry!
Oh?
Well, well...
If it isn't Tobio-chan, who was
miserably defeated last time.
We've come to win this time.
I depressed the hell out of you last time.
All that's left is that bastard, Ushiwaka.
I'm gonna have you get out
of the way again, Tobio.
Take that!
Is he really a third-year?
It's way too early to
let Oikawa get to him...
Hey.
Yes?
Karasuno's got another girl.
Yachi-san, I'm sorry!
She's a cute one.
Here.
Yeah... I wonder why
I'm feeling so frustrated.
All right...
Pardon me.
Could you get that?
Crap! Look out!
Fly
So strong...
Here.
Thanks...
Damn, it didn't work.
Karasuno's guard is too strong.
You're such a showoff, Yahaba-san.
Come on! We're about to start warm-ups!
Ow.
A-Are you okay?
Kageyama?
Huh?
Was that guy on Seijoh's team before?
Who knows?
Haikyu!!
Captains.
Let's play.
Episode 20: "Wiping Out."
I guess you're okay now.
Yeah, thanks.
I got to rest a while, so I'm actually fine.
I see.
You seem like you've aged
a bit, Sawamura-kun.
These past four months...
Another penalty?
You guys must love those.
Hey, hey, hey! You on break?
Then let's practice!
Hey, hey, hey...
I've been whipped into shape by
some other ruffians, so...
Dunno what you're talking
about, but good work.
Tails is Aoba Johsai, heads is Karasuno.
We'll receive first.
Then we'll serve first.
Karasuno                Aoba Johsai
Line up!
We're the ones that are gonna win this match.
Yeah.
Let's play!
Hey! I made it in time.
Hey. The match with Wakunan was
pretty brutal this morning.
Really? I wish I'd been able to see it.
Huh?
Heya! I'm Tanaka Ryunosuke's older sister!
Hi!
Tanaka's older sister... They look alike.
They got all the way to the semi-finals.
Yeah.
This is the semi-finals?
Huh? That means...
Wait. So if they win this one and the
next one, they're going to Nationals?!
Isn't that awesome?!
Well, only if they beat the
next two powerful schools...
Go, go, go, go, Seijoh!
This will be the third time our current
team has fought Karasuno.
Each time, Karasuno has surprised us.
I'm not sure things will go
smoothly this time, either,
but if we keep our cool and play,
I'm sure we'll see victory.
Do your best, and fight.
Right!
I hate to say it, but Karasuno's
a formidable enemy.
I'm surprised you're being so honest.
I definitely learned from last time.
If we let our guard down,
we'll get swallowed up.
So we need to go all-out from the start.
Yeah!
All right, so...
I believe...
We believe in you, Captain!
Aw, shucks.
We believe in your serves.
If you miss, you owe us ramen.
I want extra chashu pork in mine.
I'd like a side of gyoza with mine.
No serves that just happen to get over.
Come on, first-years, second-years,
you guys can request, too.
Seriously?!
The crow's broken wing has healed,
and now it's stronger than ever.
The bodies and techniques
you've trained for this day...
Please make sure you go all
out, and fly into the huge sky.
If you're able to do everything that
needs to be done, results will follow.
That's what I believe.
Right!
Ukai-kun...
To be honest, Seijoh's a
bad match-up for you.
As is any team that's calm and collected...
But overcoming them is out only option.
So go overcome that defeat!
Yeah!
Go, go, go, go, go, Seijoh!
Rule the Court
Push it, push it, push it,
push it, push it, Seijoh!
Oikawa-san, nice serve!
Man, Oikawa's serving first?
Is he that good?
Is he?
He's a frickin' cannon.
If Seijoh's able to build
momentum with this serve,
we're going to be in trouble, but...
And that's very likely.
Nice serve!
Shoyu!
Tonkotsu!
Tantanmen!
Do you want me to get it over, or miss?!
Sadly, there's no doubt...
that you're going to get it over.
They were able to get the first serve up!
All right!
I think just touching
that would rip my arms off!
Wait! It's going over the net.
They're gonna hit it!
Nice, Kageyama!
Kageyama's the first
one to touch the ball?
Then they're screwed.
Their attack will just...
All right!
Nice kill.
The ones who just did that
are the most surprised about it?!
Karasuno                  Aoba Johsai
Nice, Asahi! Nishinoya!
Yeah!
Thanks!
All right, let's go,
all-new Karasuno!
Kageyama, nice serve!
One more!
Makki!
That's a really good line.
Don't mind! Don't mind!
So close! We'll get it next time!
Karasuno                  Aoba Johsai
Iwaizumi-san, nice serve!
I'm sure his serves are intense, too.
Bring it!
Damn it, it's long!
Sorry, Kageyama!
Damn, insane serves one after another.
What's with those guys?
Hit it, Kunimi!
Tanaka, nice kill!
Thanks!
I'm surprised he got it in!
Well done, Ryu! Love ya!
Hey, Ne-chan, stop it!
I wanna touch the ball, too.
All right!
Seijoh and Karasuno's match is awesome.
Oh, really?
Nice receive!
Get another one!
Nice, Mattsun.
Left!
All right!
Sorry!
Sorry. It was a little low.
Karasuno                  Aoba Johsai
Tsukishima, nice serve!
Go!
Wow... They're starting off neck-and-neck.
Yeah, but...
I'd love to see Hinata get a
quick over right about now.
Yeah...
Why?
At the end of their
last match with Seijoh,
Hinata's quick had perfect timing,
but it still got completely shut down.
It's something that even we'd never forget.
Nice serve! One more!
I'm sure it's something that Hinata and
Kageyama are never going to get over.
Iwa-chan!
Daichi-san, nice!
It's coming!
All right! He was in a great spot!
It's coming back! Move back! Back!
Cover! Cover!
He's so worked up that
he didn't see the block!
Damn it. I'll get the next one!
Oikawa-san, nice!
Calm it down, you... uh... dumbass!
Is that Japanese?
That goes for you, too, Kageyama.
We're counting on you, Iwaizumi-san!
Damn it, Kageyama... He kicked me for real!
Nice one-touch!
One more! One more!
Got it!
One more!
Go!
That spike, filled with despair...
Break through it!
Now...
We're at the starting line.
Haikyu!!
That #10's awesome!
Karasuno's really strong this year.
All right!
Hinata, nice kill!
That's it, Hinata!
Now...
We're at the starting line.
You kicked me for real, you jerk!
I woke you up, you dumbass!
What'd you say?!
Now, now...
They've picked themselves back up.
But that's only thanks to my advice.
Those two getting more confident
is hardly a good thing.
I know.
Let's take our time and form a strategy.
Yeah!
Karasuno                  Aoba Johsai
This is their first set, but that's
an impressive score against Seijoh.
Yeah. I didn't think Karasuno
would make it this far.
I guess it wasn't just luck last time.
All right!
Daichi-san, nice receive!
Are they just going to counter Hinata's
slide hit with a receive again?
All right!
Nice, Hinata!
It looks like their #10's off-course
spike wasn't just dumb luck.
Don't mind! Don't mind!
Kageyama, nice serve!
Sorry, cover!
We're counting on you, Makki!
Got it! Kunimi!
Right!
Nice kill!
Nice toss.
They did that like it was nothing.
Damn, they're good.
As usual, Aoba Johsai is playing skillfully.
All of their cogs are working
together wonderfully.
Iwaizumi, nice serve!
Yeah! It's frustrating.
Sorry!
All right!
Karasuno                  Aoba Johsai
Yeah!
Makki, nice kill!
We're counting on you.
Hey.
Bring it!
The ones who don't do jump serves aim for...
Got it!
Here it is! The place where the
back line setter comes out!
Nice receive!
Good! It went up nicely!
Hinata, go for another slide hit!
He's going in to block?
It'll be hard to stop it by myself, but...
Don't hit it over here.
You can't, right?
Here it comes! A straight
shot right in the face!
You ignore the cross and wait for a straight.
Kindaichi, nice receive!
They narrowed the course!
Counter!
All right!
So much pressure!
Those third-years are scary!
Nice receive, Kindaichi!
Thanks.
Looks like if we narrow the course,
we can receive it.
I'll give it a shot next time.
You're scary, Mattsun.
Don't mind, Shoyo. It was close.
They've already thought up a way
to counter Hinata's slide hit.
Right.
Seijoh's is playing as well as we expected...
Indeed.
Each of their players is always
thinking up plays and executing them.
That's probably the foundation
of Seijoh's strength.
Karasuno                  Aoba Johsai
But...
Nice receive!
Sugawara-san was saying
that with Seijoh's quicks,
I should wait a little while...
...then jump!
All right!
Got you back!
Don't act so high and mighty
just because you got one.
Yes!
He's learned from his previous experience.
Karasuno's able to handle us
a lot better this go-round.
We can't seem to pull ahead.
Nice receive!
Karasuno                  Aoba Johsai
Great, great, Yutaro! Push it,
push it, Yutaro! One more time!
Rule the Court
And the rotation's gone fully around.
Hey, it's the tears-your-arm-off server...
Oikawa, nice serve!
Just in case, watch the back of your head.
Bring it!
Sorry!
Damn it!
So close! Nice offensive serve!
Next, next!
Lucky, lucky! Let's get another one!
Huh?! What the hell was that?!
He can hit the ball even harder?!
That was basically a spike!
That felt pretty good against my hand.
Maybe that serve was a fluke...
Switch it up!
No, it wasn't a fluke.
Got it.
At least, I don't think it was.
Did he hit it that hard
knowing it was risky?
That was an insane serve.
I wanna try and get it.
What a sound...
I can't... Someone's
arms are gonna fly off.
Honestly, I don't think I'd
be able to get it, either.
It was over here before
we even knew he'd hit it.
But...
Karasuno                  Aoba Johsai
All right!
We're at set point!
Just one more point! Go for it!
Thanks.
It won't be easy to get it over.
Don't put too much strength into it.
Our team is strong when all
six of us are strong.
Hey, seriously? Looks like
Karasuno might get the first set.
Seijoh better think of something
fast, or they might be in trouble.
We're gonna take this set! Keep it up!
Right!
This is no time to panic.
They need to go out there and fight.
Iwaizumi, nice kill!
Karasuno                  Aoba Johsai
Great, great, Hajime! Push it,
push it, Hajime! One more time!
If Seijoh gets one more
point, it'll be a deuce.
They'll just have to go for the break.
Stay calm! Just one more!
We're gonna get this one!
Right!
Just one more point, and we can
take the first set from Seijoh.
Focus on this point!
Points like this are the worst...
Yeah... But Seijoh's got it even rougher.
Seijoh's changing members now?
Right now?
It's that guy from earlier.
Yeah...
I've never seen that player before.
Yes.
He's not a pinch server,
and yet they're bringing him
out for the first time
when their opponent is at set point...
Maybe they're just trying to
strengthen their left block.
Make sure your spikes don't get caught.
Right.
Iwaizumi-san, nice serve!
Sorry, it's short!
Tanaka-san!
One-touch!
Chance ball!
Got it!
Kindaichi...
The moment when gears
moving smoothly together
are intentionally changed...
They become something new entirely.
Like... that #16's spike was all grar, smash!
But I have to wonder why
he's playing volleyball,
considering how evil his eyes look
and how confrontational he is.
Tanaka, all of that applies to you, too.
Episode 21: "The Destroyer"
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"The Destroyer."