So you're finally here, then, you scrubs?
Come, now...
what are you waiting for?
How delightful!
Master, it's time
for the regular debriefing.
Time does fly, doesn't it?
Good job, all of you.
Come back anytime to try again!
Master, what were you watching while
sparring with the prospective students?
Phoenix Festa, of course!
Hu Feng, I just saw the most
delightful boy in the latest match!
Seidoukan's Ayato Amagiri
or something?
In terms of raw talent,
I think that kid was the best!
Such a blast to watch!
Is it too late to ask him to play for us?
Easier said than done.
However, it seems
that his powers are limited.
But that's what makes him
all the more intriguing!
If I'm not mistaken, his next
opponents are Song and Luo.
I couldn't be more envious!
So there you are, Master.
Oh, and you, too, Elder Brother Zhao.
- It's been a long time.
It's the twins, eh?
Shenyun and Shenhua...
So, what did you want to see me for?
Well, at this rate, we're headed for a clash
with Song and Luo in the sixth round.
Being from the Water faction, we just
don't see eye to eye with the Wood faction.
When we do clash with them...
...we might go a bit overboard.
- Just so you know.
Why, you...!
Just do as you please.
My goal is merely
to endow you with power.
I have no interest in telling you
what path to choose.
Master!
I can see why you inherited
the Divine Revelations!
How open-minded you are!
- We are quite impressed!
AYATO AMAGIRI
JULIS-ALEXIA VON RIESSFELD
LUO KUNZHAN
SONG RAN
SHENYUN LI
SHENHUA LI
That said, are you sure
that all will go as you planned?
By that do you mean we do not
measure up to Song and Luo?
Oh, no. But we're not sure if those two
will win through to the next round.
Master, do you believe that Song
and Luo will lose to that Seidoukan team,
even though their weakness
has been exposed?
All I care about is having a good time.
That's what I'm here for.
If Amagiri and his
teammate win tomorrow,
he'll only increase
his capabilities further.
And that's what I'm looking forward to.
After all, that would make it...
...all the more enjoyable!
Divine Revelations
Seidoukan's new phenom
might be saddled with a time limit!?
Seriously,
Who knew that the rumor would
spread like this in a single day?
The players themselves must have
received even more detailed data.
How much do you think they know?
For starters, we should assume
that the match with Irene
gave them a rough idea
of your time limit.
Yeah, probably.
The real issue is
that the word's out about the impact
on you when you release those powers.
"In order to recover
from the physical damage of this impact,
it can be inferred that Amagiri must
stand by for a certain interval..."
I hear that Rewolf is the source
of these rumors!
That wretched Tyrant!
So...
how are you really feeling?
Well, I still have some pain.
But not enough to keep me
from fighting normally.
So you won't be able to go all-out, then?
No... I don't think that's gonna happen.
Very well. In that case,
there are two things I want to confirm.
How can your defense be so formidable
when your powers are sealed?
Oh, right.
If it's defense, I can get by with experience
and anticipation up to a point.
I see.
All right, here's the other thing.
That method you have of releasing
your power for just a second...
Can you still use it, even now?
I think I could pull it off at least once.
Very well, then.
Our next opponents
are Jie Long's Rank #20 and 23.
DIVINE REVELATIONS
They're direct disciples of Jie Long's
student council president,
"Divine Revelations,"
and masters of close combat.
If you were at full strength,
it wouldn't be hard to defeat them,
but frankly, in your current state,
that would be asking too much.
If it were one-on-one,
I'm sure I could hold my own,
but taking on both at the same time...
Which brings me to my proposal.
You have a plan?
What do you think of this strategy?
PHOENIX FESTA
ROUND 5
MATCH #8
Here we are!
The last match of Round 5
of the Phoenix Festa!
Which team will claim
the final berth of the quarterfinals?
Since this year's teams
are of a high caliber,
I'd say every one of them
has a shot at winning it all!
Now, then, why don't we introduce
the quarterfinalists to watch?
First of all, this year's front-runners!
Arlequint's all-powerful,
bleeding-edge puppets, AR-D and RM-C!
They'll be competing as Ernesta
and Camilla's surrogates!
What a shock to see them win after allowing
their opponents to attack for a full minute!
And here are Jie Long's
prized twin demons!
Shenyun Li,
a.k.a. Phantom Fog Disperser,
SHENHUA LI
SHENYUN LI
and Shenhua Li,
a.k.a. Phantom Creator!
With their huge arsenal
of Star Senjutsu combo moves,
they're devilishly hard to beat.
Till now, they've had their way with
all the opponents and gone on to win!
But wait, there's more!
Fighting for the Silver-winged Knights'
pride and honor!
Elliot Forster and Doroteo Lemus
of Galahadworth!
Doroteo's a beast of a veteran.
This is his third Festa.
Elliot is a young prodigy
who joined the Silver-winged Knights
despite only being in junior high!
Seidoukan Academy owns
the Phoenix Festa!
Can they stand their ground?
KIRIN TOUDOU
SAYA SASAMIYA
Kirin Toudou and Saya Sasamiya!
The teamwork between Toudou,
who's adept at close combat,
and Sasamiya, who has sheer firepower...
they're totally in the zone!
But speaking of Seidoukan Academy,
we also need to keep an eye
on the Amagiri-Riessfeld team,
who are up next!
Right!
They sure handed Irene,
armed with the Ogre Lux "Gravi-sheath,"
and her teammate Priscilla,
a resounding defeat!
Meanwhile, all kinds of rumors
have started swirling about Amagiri!
If what's being reported is true,
the disadvantage will be huge!
Has he recovered from the damage
he sustained in releasing his powers?
And will we get to see that performance
from him again today?!
All right! This is the match to watch,
in every sense of the word!
Seidoukan Academy's Ayato Amagiri
and Julis-Alexia von Riessfeld!
SONG RAN
LUO KUNZHAN
And now Jie Long 7th Academy's
Song and Luo have arrived onstage!
Amagiri!
Whether or not those rumors
about you are true,
Luo and I plan to go all-out against you!
To be honest,
we would've preferred to go head-to-head
with you when you were 100%.
But such are the rules
of the team-oriented Phoenix Festa!
Don't take it personally!
Oh, hey, no need to...
We just wanted to let you
know that before the match.
Right...
I see.
So they're true warriors,
through and through.
Who knew guys like that existed?
All right, both teams are now onstage!
They're going start off by testing you
to see whether you can fight at 100%.
And they'll see through it right away.
That it's true.
Probably...
All right! Listen up, Ayato.
This is your mark.
Make sure you remember it.
Right.
The signal's the fireworks, right?
Make sure you've met
all the conditions by then.
Roger that.
Now which team is going to seize victory
in this fifth round match
and head to the quarterfinals?
Match #8, Round 5 of the Phoenix Festa!
Battle...
...start!
Here we come!
I see...
Looks like the rumors were true.
Burst into bloom, Primrose!
Sorry, Ayato! He got past me!
Can you endure this blow?
Whoa!
Amagiri is under siege!
What an unexpected turn of events!
The Song-Luo team's concerted
attack was surely masterful!
No sign of that performance this time,
and he's using far less Prana
than what we've seen till now.
So I guess those rumors
must be true, right?
Come out, Loropetalum!
Could this be one of Riessfeld's skills?
A wall of flames has appeared
out of nowhere!
It's split the stage in two!
I see, so you've separated Luo and me.
Now it's one-on-one.
You believe you have a chance
if it's one-on-one?
To be honest,
I don't think it'll be easy,
but that doesn't mean
I should give up, does it?
That was a stupid question to ask.
Allow me to apologize.
What's the matter?
I see that you've been
over-hyped, Glühen Rose!
This is the skill of a Rank #23?
At Seidoukan, you'd easily
crack the Page One ranks!
Livingstone Daisy!
I see... So that's what's going on.
You're expending your power
to maintain this wall of flames, eh?
But you could've turned this
into a one-on-one battle
without resorting
to such elaborate tricks.
I had no choice.
This is the only way we can win.
Meaning that you have
something else up your sleeve, huh?
To be honest, I admire you.
You may have been focusing on defense,
but to withstand
all of my attacks till now...
If you were at full strength,
our roles might have been reversed.
No, I don't think
I could've held out for so long.
I don't think...
that's necessarily true.
But I couldn't live with myself
if I went on battering you like this.
Out of respect for you,
I shall finish this with my next move.
All right, you'd better hurry!
Or else the battle
beyond that wall will be over.
Are you perhaps implying
that my partner will lose?
In his current state,
Murakumo has no chance against us.
Am I right?
Absolutely.
For Ayato to defeat you
in his current state,
the best he could do would be
to catch you off-guard somehow.
Well, not that Song and I would
ever lay ourselves open like that...
That side, eh?
Even if you protect yourself,
this fist will pulverize everything!
I would advise you to dodge it,
rather than block it.
Julis...
This is it!
Burst into bloom...
No way am I gonna let you do that!
Amaryllis! Twin Blossoms!
Julis's signal!
Badge broken!
E-End of match!
Winners, Ayato Amagiri
and Julis-Alexia von Riessfeld!
It was stunning teamwork
catching their opponents off-guard
and snatching victory
from the jaws of defeat!
No, no, it wasn't quite
that simple, actually.
Meaning?
Song was in close-quarter combat
with Amagiri,
whereas Luo was countering
Riessfeld's long-distance assault.
By switching places, the Seidoukan team
messed up their opponents' timing,
and that's how they caught them
off-guard so decisively.
Really, that was amazing!
Well, we did scratch out a win, but...
Even so, it's significant
that we managed to get through today.
After a full day's rest tomorrow,
you should be able to go all-out
in our next match, won't you?
Yeah, that won't be a problem.
But what about you, Julis?
What about your injuries?
Well, it doesn't seem to be broken,
so it's nothing I can't handle.
Anyway, about our next match...
Even if you're able to go all-out,
our opponents look to be quite a handful.
Yeah.
I agree.
I'm sure you're not here
to offer your congratulations,
so what is it that you want with us?
Actually, that's precisely it.
It was you who came up with that
strategy, wasn't it, Glühen Rose?
Uh, yes...
It was an amazing combination
that couldn't be achieved
unless you trusted each other.
We got trounced today.
You were amazing!
W-Well...
But you must be careful.
Such a strategy will have no impact
on your next opponents.
What do you mean by that?
This is purely a warning.
Just take it at face value.
That's easy for you to say, but our
next opponents are comrades of yours.
Do you really think
I can trust what you say?
Going to the same school
doesn't make us all comrades.
Shenyun Li and Shenhua Li... and us...
LUO KUNZHAN
SONG RAN
AYATO AMAGIRI
JULIS-ALEXIA VON RIESSFELD
We just don't see eye to eye.
That said, we're not about to clue you in
on their weak points, but...
We feel more of an affinity
for you two than for those twins.
And so we wanted
to show you our support.
All right, then, let me ask you again.
Why did you say
our strategy wouldn't work?
Because when it comes to deception,
trickery and surprise attacks,
those twins' talents are prodigious.
They'll see right through
any strategy you come up with,
and they'll be sure to one-up you.
In battle, you two see
your opponents as your equals,
embracing the risks
such a strategy entails.
But those two are different.
They constantly look down
on their opponents,
never exposing themselves
to danger, no matter what.
That's the Li twins' way.
And that's what we can't
stomach about them.
Well, well, well...
First you go down in inglorious defeat...
And now you're poisoning
your opponents with trash talk?
Why, you...
Nice to meet you,
Glühen Rose and Murakumo.
I'm Shenyun Li.
I'm Shenhua Li.
- Pleased to make your acquaintance!
What do you want?
Well, we just felt
that we owed you an apology.
Apology?
Yes, as it seems that our comrades there
put up such a lame fight.
As students of the same master,
we couldn't be more mortified!
Well, I don't think it was lame at all.
It's worrysome for disciples of the Divine
Revelations to be seen as so hapless.
So we're going to show you a world
our older comrades weren't able to.
- The depths of Star Senjutsu, that is!
Pretty unpleasant duo, weren't they?
But including those two, three more
victories, and we stand to win it all.
Three times, huh?
Doesn't seem like a lot,
but it sounds so demanding.
I'm glad you recognize that, at least.
But have you given any thought
to what you're going to ask for if we win?
I can't really think
of anything right now.
Well, I had a feeling you'd say that.
I'm grateful to you for fighting
for me, and to be honest...
Um, it makes me happy.
But I think it's about time you set
your sights on what you want.
That may be true, but still...
Your older sister... what about her?
I'm sure my sister must've had
her reasons for leaving home,
so I'm not going to go out
of my way to look for her.
But the fastest way to figure out
your seal would be to find her, right?
Yeah... Well, that's true, but...
Don't tell me that you...
Yoohoo!
H-Hello!
You came all this way just to see us?
We're sure you're both exhausted,
so we wanted to congratulate you
as soon as possible.
Then I'm gonna open the door now!
Uh, before you do,
you should know
that you have another guest...
Is it all right if we let her in?
A guest?
That's right. To see Riessfeld.
To see me?
Princess!
But you're...
Long time no see!
Flora!
To all you Claudia fans out there...
Long time no see!
Those of you disappointed by my
lack of screen time this episode...
Rest assured!
The true heroine
will appear in the preview!
Episode 14 - Corrupt Ruler
Yes, that's right!
In the preview!