Captain's log, March 3rd.
DRAGONs appeared.
My squad was ordered to engage.
But Ange once again ignored her
orders and acted on her own.
Ange attacked by herself
and destroyed the target.
I've had enough, you scrooge.
We can barely afford our meals
because you keep taking all the money.
What's this?
For your troubles.
Want more?
Don't bullshit me.
All right. No fighting.
Enough, Ange.
Why can't you follow orders?
I'm defeating the DRAGONs, am I not?
That's not the point.
If you keep disrupting the squad—
Fine me or execute me as you like.
Ange!
Maintain discipline and follow orders...
If she can't do that, we may have
to force Ange off the Villkiss.
Log complete.
No additional notes.
Casualties today:
zero.
Salia's Depression
Captain's log, March 4th.
We received a message
from outside of Arzenal.
"Arrived at the southern edge of Galia,"
"but no sign of our friends."
"Planning to continue recon
toward the Empire of Misurugi."
That snot-nosed brat is still alive.
Tusk.
Yeah.
To think it was him that saved Ange...
So it was him that fixed the Villkiss.
Probably.
Are you saying Ange was alone with a man?
Jasmine, you're in charge of contacting Tusk.
We'll need his help again soon.
All right.
So, our problem here...
You want Ange removed from the Villkiss?
She's arrogant now that she
can use the Villkiss better.
Her selfish behavior will
someday put the squad at risk.
Before that happens—
Before that happens, the captain
should do something about it.
You can deal with it.
I'm counting on you, Salia.
Captain's log, March 5th.
Impossible.
Impossible!
How could a human become a Norma's servant?
Norma are antisocial, vicious, uneducated,
dirty, mana-starved
byproducts of human society.
Sure, sure.
Momoka-san, are you
aware of what you're doing?
Yes, I'm happy.
Good for you, Momoka.
You get to be with Ange.
What's up, Ersha?
The festivals are coming up, right?
I want to prepare some
things for the children.
Ange, huh?
I need to do something about her.
What are you going to do?
She's filthy rich. She'll just buy
herself out of any punishment.
Besides, she won't do anything you say.
What's your point?
She looks down on you.
This kind of thing could never have
happened when Zola was around.
Want me to take over as captain?
Everyone's being selfish.
It's not like I asked to become captain.
The usual.
Use the furthest one down.
I can't have you sleeping
in your underwear forever.
I don't mind.
I do.
Jasmine, I'm using the dressing room.
Use the furthest one down.
Squeeze with the power of love!
Making you fall in love!
Bishoujo Holy Knight Pretty Salian!
Charging next to you!
Captain's log, March 5th.
Addendum: Underwent psychological
maintenance to manage stress.
My shining love energy...
...will make you fall in love with me!
Princess?
It was in use.
Sh-She... sh-sh-she...
She saw me.
If everyone finds out about this...
I never thought our captain
would have a hobby like this.
Fine, then.
Am I pressing too much or too little?
I think it's good.
I'll kill you.
What's this about?
Now that you've seen, I'll have to kill you.
I haven't told anyone.
You haven't told anyone yet.
I have no one to tell, and it
doesn't matter to me what you do.
It doesn't matter?
You give me so much trouble,
and it doesn't matter to you?
We're a team!
Yet you keep going on by yourself.
You people tried to
shoot me down from behind!
"Team," my ass!
You never stop them.
You want me to die, too, don't you?
I'm not going to be killed
by the likes of you.
That's why I fight alone.
Quit being so selfish.
Look who's talking!
What "team"?
The fact that I have to be captain,
that everyone's being so selfish,
that you saw my secret,
that you took the Villkiss...
Huh?
It's all your fault.
What?
See, minced meat is better
than croquette for curry—
What the heck is this?
Oh, dear.
Please make Angelise-sama stop.
This is a bath.
So we all have to wash off our dirt first.
There you go.
Have fun, you kids.
Angelise-sama!
Microboobs!
Shut up, muscle pig!
Do you need to fight in the base, too?
This is why I don't like Normas.
It's unlike you.
Whatever.
Fifty pages of repentance essays.
By tomorrow morning.
Why do I have to?
Good morning, Angelise-sama.
It's breakfast time.
I finished your repentance essay last night.
Don't worry.
Angelise-sama.
A cold?
She got cold after her bath.
She'll be on standby until
her fever comes down.
Until then, we'll continue
our missions without her.
How much do you lose on break, again?
One million per day.
Poor her.
Maybe she'll go bankrupt.
We're beginning training.
Captain's log, March 6th.
Training continues without problems.
It seems that without Ange,
the squad's discipline is back to normal.
I want to handle Ange
carefully when she returns,
so that we can maintain this state.
Casualties today: zero.
Good work.
Salia.
How's the Villkiss?
It's always a wreck when Ange uses it.
Maintenance is a pain.
It's a precious machine.
Dammit.
Oh, well! She's keeping the
money and the risks to herself.
Risks?
I can kind of sense the rider's
feelings when I'm working on them.
"I won't let anyone die."
"I'm going to take all the
DRAGONs' attacks myself."
Or not.
You're overthinking it.
But no one's died, ever since Ange
started piloting the Villkiss.
Not one in our squad.
February 14th.
Casualties today: zero.
February 18th.
I'm overthinking it.
Soldiers, to your machines.
Captain to all units.
Ange is away.
The six of us will engage.
Great, what a pain in the ass.
Keep a tight formation once
we enter the combat area.
We'll focus fire to make
up for our smaller size.
Yes, ma'am.
All units ready for lift-off.
Salia squad, lifting off.
Move. I have to go.
No. I won't let you go.
It costs money to feed you.
Angelise-sama.
2800 to Singular point.
Roger.
All units, release safety.
The door's opening.
All units, prepare for combat.
Yes, ma'am.
It's huge.
Oh, my, it's big.
Salia, tell me about the big one.
I've never seen such a thing.
Salia's never seen it?
Then it might be— it's—
A virgin.
A virgin?
No way! This is my first time.
Is this the first time for you, Officer?
It's what we call a DRAGON
we've never seen before.
We'll be stinking rich just bringing
home new information about it.
Let's eat this virgin and go home
to celebrate in a bath of money.
Sounds good.
Salia to Arzenal. Requesting backup.
What? We'll lose earnings
if we call for backup.
Zola never freaked out against a virgin.
Come with me, Rosalie, Chris.
Sir.
W-Wait.
We'll take the earnings for ourselves.
My hair's tingling.
Fire.
It's not as nimble as I thought.
Its back is heavily armored.
Which means—
Bingo.
It's flabby.
Aim for its belly.
Let's finish this quick.
All right.
What's wrong?
Tingly.
Tingly, tingly...
Mine.
Hilda, pull back.
I can't move.
Wh-What is this?
Strong gravity signature
nearby the new-type DRAGON.
Gravity?
No.
All units, assume defensive position.
It's those horns.
Let them go!
I can't move.
H-Help me, Rosalie, Hilda.
Move. How much do you think I spent on you?
Help me.
Salia!
I told them to wait.
I have to keep the squad
from being destroyed.
At worst, we may have to
abandon our machines and run.
Vivi-chan.
Let them go.
Let them go!
Vivian.
At this rate, those three—
Villkiss.
Is it you, Ange?
If you insist on going,
you'll go dressed like this.
I'm so dizzy.
Let's get this over with.
Don't come, Ange.
You'll get caught in its gravity.
Don't worry.
I can handle it myself, as always.
Dammit, all of you!
I've had enough, you stupid bitch!
This DRAGON isn't weak enough
for you to handle by yourself.
You keep going off by yourself.
Listen to your commander
if you don't want to die.
Yes.
Go straight up.
Adjust three degrees right, distance 20.
Which way was right, again?
Other way.
Hold position there.
I think I'm falling, right?
I am.
It's just your fever.
Salia-chan, no.
Now, Ange.
Kick it!
Kick it! Like you kicked me.
Finally.
You did it.
All units, finish it off.
Attack!
So much money. I must be dreaming.
It's not a dream.
So little.
All you did was break its horn.
But we made it, thanks to you.
For my trouble.
I lost money because I followed your orders.
I take back my thanks.
Everyone will find out about your hobby.
Spend the rest of your life in bed!
How could you?
Are you happy?
Y-Yeah.
It's because Ange came that
we made so much money.
Well—
Stop targeting Ange during combat.
We've been through a lot, but we
need to do what we can in this team.
Ange, stop hoarding all the earnings.
You can make enough money without trying.
Commander's orders.
Who'd listen to you?
I don't mind, really.
As long as you don't drag me down.
I don't mind, either.
I would have been dead if
Ange didn't come for us.
Um...
Well, as long as we have this money.
How can you let yourselves
be deceived like that?
Th-That's not it, really.
Traitors.
Hilda.
Perfect.
Let's get going, then.
One, two—
Wh-What was that for?
To wash away everything
that happened before.
Wait, hey.
Captain's log, March 7th.
We defeated the DRAGONs again.
Ange will pilot the Villkiss.
I'm not entirely convinced,
but that's fine for now.
I will do what I need to do as captain.
Until the day of Libertus.
Log complete.
Once again today, casualties are zero.
Damn, I went through hell.
I'm glad, though.
Your fever's gone, too.
What's wrong?
A Mana message.
It's the imperial court secret channel.
Momoka, can you hear me?
Momoka.
Sylvia-sama.
Sylvia.
Did you find Angelise-oneesama?
Is Onee-sama there?
Let go.
Help me, Onee-sama.
Angelise-oneesama!
Sylvia.
Next Episode
Captain's log, addendum.
My secret was exposed today.
My secret thing that I do in my own room...
Horrible script writers that enjoy
exposing someone's privacy like that...
Bikini Escape
I'll strike them down with
my shining love energy!