Haru, stop!
Final Episode
Goodbye Fishing
I'll catch him!
I'll catch him, so you won't go...
Yuki,
goodbye.
Haru!
Thanks, everyone.
You tried so hard for me.
It made me really happy.
Haru, don't go!
It's okay.
Leave it to me.
I'll lure him far away.
Lure him away?
What does that mean?
I'm a fish.
I'll jump into the ocean and lure
him to some ocean far, far away.
Then no one will be in danger.
I won't let you wither.
Don't do it!
What will you do if you
become part of his horde?
I won't let you wither.
But it's the only option left.
I have to go. We can't catch him.
I won't let you wither.
It's the only way.
They're getting closer.
It's okay.
Yuki and the others will do something.
Right, Misaki-san?
Driver, I'm getting off!
What?
Ayumi-chan, grab onto my shoulder.
Yes!
Ow! Ow!
Hurry. If we fall, it's over.
Watch out!
We can't rely on stop lights anymore.
This is Enoshima!
Where is the military strike?
Wait a little longer.
We can't afford to do that.
We've instructed the entire
Kanagawa area to evacuate.
The affected area has
expanded to include Yokosuka.
But some of our men are
still on those ships.
My own underling, Yamada,
is on that fishing boat!
We cannot help some sacrifices.
If this becomes an
international incident,
will you take responsibility for it?
We've sent four members
from the council to Japan.
If you cannot make the decision,
they will make it for you.
I understand.
However, allow me to say this.
Protecting the lives of
my men is part of my job!
You have three minutes.
We cannot wait any longer than that.
Look at that.
Seriously?
That doesn't look good.
What's going to happen?
Who are they?
What are they thinking,
fishing at a time like this?
Everyone...
I'm sorry.
I won't let you wither.
I'm sorry for putting you all in danger.
I'm really sorry.
I won't let you wither.
I won't let you wither!
Today's Events
Companion.
Next, use your imagination.
Imagination?
Feel it.
Haino, haino, haino.
Fishing's something you have
to think about for yourself.
Yoisho, yoishona.
If you make this thing act,
it'll seem even closer to the real thing.
You should be able to
think of something.
Goddess.
I'm a fish.
I won't let you wither.
I won't let you wither!
Hey...
What are you doing?
The goddess!
She worked together with her
companion to fish up the dragon.
Yuki?
Haru, you and Koko knew
nothing about fishing, right?
Yeah.
Haru, do you know how
the goddess fished up the
dragon all those years ago?
No.
I don't know.
Why did you come here?
Why did you come here with Koko?
Because that's how it was
in the past, I guess?
They needed two goddesses.
One protected the fisherman
from the dragon.
So, what was the other goddess doing?
Haru.
You're the lure.
You're the legendary lure!
The entire area from
Enoshima to Kanagawa
has entered a panicked
situation in which people
burst into dance one after another.
According to Alien Investigation
Organization Duck,
the situation created by the
unknown life form is called
the Bermuda Syndrome...
and is responsible for the
incidents of disappearing ships
and memory loss all over the
world of the last few years.
The present incident of individuals
suddenly bursting into dance
is also a product of Bermuda Syndrome.
Grandpa!
However, without any
effective way to combat
the unidentified life form, the
hopeless situation continues.
Grandpa!
Haino, haino, haino.
Yoisho, yoishona.
Tapioca!
I'm the lure?
Me?
Yuki, Natsuki.
Yamada, you have to leave the area.
We're going to fire missiles.
Just wait a little longer.
We can't!
We still have one last measure to try!
Haru, leave it to us.
Don't ever say you'll
go by yourself again.
So tight...
Okay, Haru.
We won't let this line break.
As long as it doesn't,
you'll be able to come back.
Yeah, okay.
We'll be sending you deep,
so you'll need a lip.
And a hook.
What?
The boat's at its limit.
I might be at my limit, too.
Haru, just a little more!
You can do it!
Sorry, but the missiles
will be coming soon.
If we're going back,
we have to leave now!
What should we do?
What?
I won't go.
Even if the world ends today,
I just want to fish.
Yuki.
Natsuki, what about you?
You'll be okay,
Dad.
I'm not going back either.
I hate going home without
catching anything.
Everyone...
I'm sorry.
Thanks, everyone.
I won't be able to protect you anymore.
With this, he won't be able to
control you for a little while.
Yuki, ready?
Ready.
Fire.
Oh my god!
Whoosh!
Okay, let's go!
It's no good!
Akira, rotate and reverse!
Okay!
Haru, this'll be your lip and hook.
Nom.
It's made from fishing line.
It's tough stuff.
Okay.
Take the boat towards him!
Yuki!
This is our last chance!
I know!
I'll get it in one shot!
All right!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Ready, and...
Eno!
Run, run, run, run, run...
Shima!
Jump!
Bowl!
That's not good!
Amazing...
Let's go! The countdown!
One!
Two!
Three!
It's a bite!
Yuki!
Yuki, put the rod in your belt!
Reduce the drag!
Got it!
Yuki, I can feel it, too!
It's okay!
I feel it!
He's fighting, too!
Akira, don't let the line break!
Don't worry, I'm watching!
Tapioca!
This isn't good.
The water gun's effect is wearing off.
It suddenly got lighter.
What's going on?
That song...
Haino, haino, haino.
Yoisho, yoishona.
It's Haru!
Haru's singing!
Yuki, now! Get him!
Haru.
Haino, haino, haino.
Yoisho, yoishona.
Haino, haino, haino!
Yoisho, yoishona!
This is Seishunmaru.
We have successfully fished up JFX.
Please do not fire any missiles.
Yamada, don't worry.
I stopped the missiles
before they launched.
I adjusted the attack time...
because I believed you.
Thank you...
Thank you!
Yamada,
you are the pride of Duck.
It's okay.
He's not scary.
That's right. He's one of us.
I didn't think he'd be so small!
Wasn't that fun?
Do you want to be my friend?
Dry!
Ow! Ow, ow, ow!
Quiet!
What?
Slither, slither.
Down, down, down.
My name is Urara.
What are you going to do now?
I'm going to become the
fishing prince of the world!
What about you, Akira?
I'll be deployed somewhere new.
I hope it's near the ocean.
Our goodbye fishing
trip was lots of fun!
Ready, and...
Goodbye!
We won't lose!
That's right!
Let's go!
Ready, and...
Goodbye!
Take care, everyone!
We had fun!
Was that a UFO?
Oh, my.
Yes.
Goodbye.
It's been six months since then.
The companion caught the fish
and brought peace to Enoshima.
What a beautiful painting.
Now that's a true product of Enoshima.
"Art-o'-shima!"
Welcome.
Take any open seat.
Not making this a cafe
was the right decision.
You can rest, Mari-chan. Sakura's got it.
Thank you.
Hey, Satsuki.
Do you think my brother's
fishing again today?
Natsuki went to America to
become a bass fishing pro.
And Akira...
Fish!
Tapioca, look! It's a big one!
Tapioca found a lover.
And I...
Honey, I'm busy with work! Help me!
I'll be right there!
Boss, never get married.
It changes women.
Did you say something?
Uh, no. Nothing at all.
Welcome, everyone. Come on in.
Well, Haru, maybe I changed a little.
Good morning.
G-Good morning.
I look forward to being
in class with you again.
Yeah.
Me, too.
Haru, maybe I haven't
changed much after all.
I have two transfer students to
introduce to you today,
but one of them must be late.
Could you go ahead and
introduce yourself?
My name is Urara.
I am an alien.
What?
It's him!
Huh?
There.
No one's surprised?
Fidget, fidget. Fidget, fidget.
Uh, hey.
Yes?
Do you want to go fishing sometime?
Maybe I have...
Yes.
changed a little.
Rattle, rattle!
Huh?
Haru!
Why?
Boi-oi-oing.
I'm Haru.
The alien!
Sorry, sorry.
Always with a smile.
Always holding your head high.
Thanks for watching!
The End