Rokuro, Saizo, Isanami.
The three of you will
accompany me to the capitol.
The rest of you will stay here.
What? The rest?
Wait for us here.
Ana, I'm sure the nights
will be very lonely for you.
I won't be lonely at all. Take your time.
What?
You're so cute.
Yukimura-sama, be careful.
Keep it together.
Why are you acting all
high and mighty, monkey?
But Isanami will be worried
if I do not accompany her.
I've got Saizo. I'll be fine.
I'm going, too.
I'd be so bored without Saizo, I'd rot.
I wanna fight Saizo.
You're so annoying.
What'd you say?
He's just like a girl in love.
The power to destroy all living things...
Sword and Fan
The weather's beautiful.
Sit still. You're jostling the horse.
Hey, don't you think we look
like a princess and a lord?
Not at all.
What's your problem? You're no fun.
I wonder how everyone else is doing.
Some of them didn't seem
too happy about staying.
I'm sure Ana must be
crying from loneliness.
Kamanosuke and Seikai were
complaining until the moment we left.
Hey, who's gonna be at the tea ceremony
we're attending in the capitol?
Primarily Maeda, Mori, Uesugi,
and the rest of the Five Elders.
We might even get to see Ishida
Mitsunari and Naoe Kanetsugu.
Oh, and that dragon...
I'm sure the one-eyed lord
of Oshu will be there.
My lord, are you going dressed like that?
Of course I am.
Appearances are important.
But you'd have to be stupid to
go dressed so flamboyantly.
Please have more respect for yourself.
You don't know what you're talking about.
When I said appearances,
I didn't mean my clothes.
I meant my attitude!
I've got to make a good first impression.
With Sanada Yukimura?
Sanada, the man hiding
the Kushimitama.
My lord, do you plan to do
anything in the capitol?
If you and Ieyasu both attempt
to claim the Kushimitama,
won't it attract too much attention?
Don't worry.
I told the old man that
everything he's heard was a lie.
You told him it was a lie?
Well, he's useless.
I promised I'd make it up to him by
putting on a show for him at the capitol.
My lord, what are you planning?
I look forward to meeting
you, Sanada Yukimura.
Food
That was great.
You always eat so much.
Are you guys heading up the road?
Ah, youngster.
We intend to. Is there something wrong?
You can't get through.
The road ahead's been
washed out by the rain.
Are you from around here?
Yeah. It's a bit further,
but you should take the
mountain pass over there.
Thank you for your trouble.
Let's see...
What shall we do, my lord?
We have no choice.
There it is.
Here.
Are you sure?
Yeah, it's to thank you
for your directions.
Isanami, let's go.
Okay.
The smell of gunpowder?
Take care.
See you later, youngster.
She fell asleep.
She's so innocent.
What's innocent about her?
She just follows her natural urges.
She's way too relaxed.
Don't be so harsh.
No one's trying to attack us now.
We're traveling with an obvious target.
I did not expect you to bring her.
I thought it'd be more fun
to have her along.
Lord.
Besides, we're all you're
bringing to the capitol.
How cheap are you?
Instead of bringing an entourage
for the sake of appearances,
I prefer traveling with you three.
The wind feels wonderful.
You're a strange one.
You're more of a playboy than a lord.
Lord, please do not cause any trouble
with the women in the capitol.
What?
That place is nothing without
their entertainment.
Is that your only source of enjoyment?
Of course.
Old man...
What was that?
Rokuro!
Whoa, whoa.
Old man!
Take care of Isanami!
Sure!
What is this?
It's a trap.
Isanami!
Onii-chan?
Your big brother's arrived.
All is well.
Impressive.
What are you doing here?
Isanami!
Stop! Stop!
That was close.
I'll pull you up.
Stop!
Isanami!
Saizo!
Bombs!
You owe me one, Saizo.
Kamanosuke.
What the hell are you doing here?
Can't I be here?
Isanami, are you all right?
Yeah.
Looks like everyone's fine.
But who would do such a thing?
Amazing.
You're the first ones
to avoid all my traps.
You're the boy from the inn.
That gunpowder I smelled...
You did all of this.
That settles it.
Old man, hire me.
What?
You want to become a samurai,
so you've been testing potential
masters by sending them this way.
I'll choose my own master.
I don't wanna work for some weakling.
You all passed my test. I'll serve you.
We passed, did we?
No one sets better traps or
makes better explosives than me.
I can be useful.
Ow.
It's not your decision, brat.
Wah, miss!
Saizo, don't bully children.
Don't be ridiculous.
He almost killed us.
No one was hurt. Who cares?
Go home already.
Your parents must be worried about you.
I don't have any.
Huh?
I don't have any parents. I...
I've always lived by myself.
I bet your parents abandoned you.
It's not uncommon.
Saizo, that's terrible.
Say whatever you want.
I like you.
I will allow you to serve me.
Really?
Yukimura-sama.
Are you crazy, old man?
He's got a lot of guts for a
young boy, don't you think?
I'm impressed.
What is your name, youngster?
Mochizuki Rokuro.
I'm the sixth child,
so that's why I'm Rokuro.
I chose my own family name.
It won't be convenient having
two men with the same name.
We really do have the same name?
I heard you call him that earlier.
I don't care what you call me.
Rokuro's a lame name, anyway.
Lameness aside, there's
only one Rokuro for me.
I know, Benmaru.
Starting today, your
name is Benmaru. Got it?
Yes, sir.
What a cute name.
Sir, Benmaru was your childhood name.
What a waste.
Don't be angry, Rokuro.
Didn't I say I admire the boy's courage?
Besides, no encounter
is mere coincidence.
Isn't that right?
Very well.
Now, Benmaru, I will give
you your first order.
Yes, sir.
We're on our way to the capitol.
Because I cannot take you with us,
I'd like you to wait
at the inn up ahead.
What?
You must obey this order
if you wish to serve me.
Got it?
Okay.
And you two should return to Ueda.
Well, it's what I'd like to say,
but I know you won't listen to me.
Do whatever you want.
Old man!
What extravagant clothes.
I heard he's Lord Date.
Oh, from Oshu.
He's here.
My lord.
You must have had a long journey.
Ichimaru, Niko.
Thank you for meeting me.
Did you walk through the
capitol in those clothes?
It suits me, doesn't it?
Excuse me.
Has Lord Date Masamune arrived?
What?
With the tea ceremony tomorrow,
I have come to deliver a special decree.
What decree?
A weapons ban?
That's right.
The decree has been issued
throughout the capitol.
While I am gone, you must
not draw your weapon.
What are we supposed to do if we
run into Tokugawa or Date's men?
As long as the decree is in effect,
we should not be attacked soon.
You bitch, you ate my food.
It's your own fault for sleeping late.
Shut up.
You will not hurt Isanami!
I'm more worried about them.
I'm counting on you, playboy.
If I draw my weapon,
Tokugawa will use it as an
excuse to punish Sanada, huh?
Kitano Shrine
You are the only one so underdressed.
I don't care. These clothes
are more comfortable.
There you are, Yukimura.
Lord Ishida Mitsunari.
I didn't know you had been invited.
I could never refuse an invitation
from the great Tokugawa.
Did you do something?
Surely not.
You are a difficult man.
You flatter me.
When I sent you a secret message
regarding Ieyasu's behavior,
you did nothing.
Now Ieyasu is attempting
to provoke me into a war,
and swing the balance in his favor.
Don't rush your decision.
Now is the time to establish your position.
At least, that was my understanding.
I don't get involved in trouble.
That's all.
In any case, he's been rather brazen since
the father of the regent passed away.
Even this tea ceremony is nothing
more than a public display of power.
I couldn't agree more.
Naoe-sama.
Lord Kanetsugu, it's
good to see you again.
It's a pleasure to see
you again, Yukimura-sama.
Have you already paid your
respects to Lord Ieyasu?
No, I just got here.
You should go soon.
You'll get to see something
quite interesting.
Interesting?
An arrogant little raccoon
dog thinks he can speak.
I almost couldn't believe my eyes.
You're as merciless as always.
Raccoon dogs should stay in the
mountains where they belong.
I can't believe he issued a weapons ban.
When did he become our leader?
Now, now. We're here for a tea ceremony.
Let's enjoy ourselves.
These sachets are so cute.
Those are pretty, too.
Hey, don't wander off.
What's wrong, Ichimaru?
That girl is the priestess
we had in the castle prison.
What?
That means the bastards
around her are...
Sanada's men!
No. Our lord told us
there's a weapons ban.
Are you saying we should
just let them go?!
Why don't we invite them for some tea?
You're kidding me!
Sorry for the delay, everyone.
We're still awaiting one arrival.
Just wait a little longer.
You're all here.
We're lucky to have
such beautiful weather.
You're late, Lord Date.
We've been waiting for you.
Lord Tokugawa, thank you
for your invitation.
Lord Date, hurry up.
Go sit next to Lord Sanada.
Lord Date!
There is a weapons ban in effect!
What do you think you're doing?
I thought I'd show everyone...
...some swordplay to compensate
for my tardiness.
Sounds interesting. I'll allow it.
The beauty of swordplay comes
out when two swords clash.
Could I have a volunteer to
help me with this performance?
Lord Sanada.
Would you join me?
You're too much.
Wait.
While we are honored by your choice,
my master does not have
his sword with him.
Would it be possible for
you to select another?
I will lend you my sword.
But...
It's fine, Rokuro.
It would be the pinnacle of
impoliteness to refuse his request.
I will perform with this.
On your guard.
What impressive swordplay.
One wrong move and he'll be caught
on the sharp edge of the blade.
Knowing that, Lord Sanada
moves accordingly.
Impressive.
Oh?
Whoops.
My feet can't keep up.
What's wrong, Yukimura?
You look like a fool.
They seem fast enough to me.
However,
you can't run forever!
Lord!
How unsightly.
What?
Yukimura, what are you doing?
You're not a child.
Sorry, sorry.
Lord Date's swordplay scared
my feet out from under me.
Well, then.
All that movement has made me thirsty.
Could I get some tea?
That was quite the show.
People will be talking about that raccoon
dog's expression for a long time.
Masamune must be furious to
be brushed off like that.
What an embarrassment
for the dragon of Oshu.
That was quite the mistake.
You've always got nasty
things to say, Kanetsugu.
I'm surprised you escaped so easily.
What are you talking about?
That wasn't easy.
Lord Sanada.
I have a message for
Lord Sanada regarding...
...the incident at the tea ceremony.
You are to go up to Fushimi Castle
immediately and make an appearance.
Oh, my.
That's completely unfair.
If you do not go,
there will be consequences.
Excuse me.
How one-sided.
With all of Tokugawa's
supporters against you,
you won't be able to talk
your way out of that one.
That must be their aim.
They'll either take your lands
or have you kill yourself.
Yukimura, what will you do?
I'll ignore it, of course.
He got you.
You noticed his footwork, too?
Of course.
He's an interesting one.
That slippery fellow's got me excited.
He looked like he was smiling,
but I could see the boldness in his eyes.
He's more than what he seems.
My lord.
What is it?
The priestess who escaped from us...
...is with Sanada's men here in the capitol.
The Kushimitama is in the capitol?
It's empty!
He can't have gone far!
After him!
Don't let Sanada escape!
Hey, what's wrong?
Why are we going back to Ueda now?
I didn't even get to buy souvenirs.
My apologies, Isanami.
You can get them next time.
I heard he's headed towards Omi!
Follow him! Don't let him escape!
You can't get through here.
It's one of Sanada's men!
Kill him!
Idiots!
Gotcha.
Better safe than sorry.
Taizan Meido!
Bastard...
They can't follow us now.
Don't draw attention to us!
You see? I knew it'd be more
fun to bring Isanami along.
Lord.
Let's go!
Huh? What's that kid doing hiding there?
Hey, Benmaru.
What?
What are you doing here?
I was just out for a
stroll in these woods.
I didn't expect rocks, spears,
or fire to come my way.
Gods, I gratefully
accept your challenge.
Damn it. The pit trap didn't go off.
Maybe I didn't use enough gunpowder.
You're one terrifying kid.
The next episode of Brave 10
is "The Birth of a Warrior."
The Birth of a Warrior
Bring it on!