One winter day,
I found an invitation in my shoe locker
from someone named Summer X.
Invitation for Mizutani Shizuku
We're Having a Christmas Party
Time: Second Friday
Place: Misawa Batting Center
Santa's coming too!!
From the Mystery Sender,
-Summer X
I decided to ignore it,
but the next day, after gym,
it popped up again in my bag.
Since it appeared that
the contents of my bag had been disturbed,
I immediately confronted Natsume-san.
I just wanted to surprise you!
She spat it out easily.
Which brings us here.
Christmas
Chicken!  Chicken!
I am a chicken!
Natsume-san, do you
know what you're saying?
Okay?!
We zip in, then zip right out!
Zippy zip!
Lately...
Well, I guess this is nothing new,
but Haru's been acting strange.
He refuses to leave my side,
like he's scared of something.
Don't run off without me!
Focus on me!
Right, okay.
It gets especially bad once
we're outside school.
He's acting just like he was
when he started coming back to class.
I wanted to have a serious talk
with him before winter began...
Eh?!  Whatcha lookin' at?!
Haru-kun!  Don't hurt Santa!
...but I'm a little hesitant
after seeing him now.
What's wrong with Haru-kun?
I thought he'd be the most
excited about Christmas.
Beats me...
Oh.
Look! This is the place, Haru-kun!
Christmas Special
An Entire Chicken
Welcome.
Ah!
Natsume-chan!
Let's hang, let's hang, let's hang!
I-I can't!
We're about to...
Huh?  What?
Oh, I know!
You're going to a Christmas party!
Hey, lady!  Give us
60 pieces of chicken!
D-Don't order for us!
You can only come if you have
one of these invitations!
Only the chosen are allowed!
Not our problem.
We go where we please.
Because we're bad boys!
Okay, that means we'll
have a total of...
Are you coming, Yamaken-kun?
No, I'll...
He doesn't get to come.
Why not?
I'm coming.
I'm coming and that's that!
No, stay away.
You stay away, Yamaken.
'Cause you said you're
in love with Shizuku.
Fool, I was just joking.
I knew it!
That scared me!
C'mon, Haru.
You can't believe everything you hear!
No kidding.
R-Really?
Oh!
Okay, Haru.
I don't know what just happened,
but let's buy some chicken!
Yeah!
Please wait!
Oh, make sure you get enough for us!
You got it!
Haru-kun, they're using you!
Haru!
You talk way too damn much, moron!
Are you in love with Shizuku?
Is that a problem?
Damn, why did I say that?
What is it?
Door charge.
1,520 yen per person.
How could I be attracted to this girl?!
Thank you.
You're short 20 yen, Yamaken-kun.
You're so anal!
Natsume-chan, where's
the party being held?
Huh?  Where?
Misawa
Batting
Center
Oh?
Oh, oh, oh?
I'm back.
There's a whole crowd.
Is something special going on?
We're having a Christmas party.
What?  Here?
Nobody told me anything.
E-Excuse us...
Whoa, my heart just skipped.
Scary...  That guy's scary...
Scary?  You mean Mi-chan-san?
Well, we got in a fight here
with Haru and the study bug.
Can you stay away from them?
That fool finally made a friend.
Huh?
If I see you here again,
I'll break your legs.
Man, I was so scared.
I bet that guy's totally
killed someone before!
Should we go somewhere else?
Nah, it's okay,
but try to keep it down.
What's wrong with Natsume-chan?
She seems a little strange.
Natsume's always been strange.
She's a bit different from the rest of us.
Oh.
Yeah, got it.
Later.
Oshima-san.
Sasahara-kun.
Natsume-san was worried because
you weren't answering your phone.
Aren't you coming to the Christmas party?
Oh, I was in a meeting...
What Christmas party?
Huh?  Didn't you receive an invitation?
Th-That was from Natsume-san?
I thought it was meant as a prank.
If you're coming, we can go together.
I've got my bike.
Oh, uh-huh...
Sorry, today's not a good day.
Really?  Okay.  See ya.
Uh-huh, sorry.
I really think you should
come, Oshima-san!
It'll be fun!
You're wrong!
Santa is a fairy!
Yeah!
And reindeer are people who did bad
things in their previous life!
Wait!
Don't touch the cake!
Th-The opposite of classy...
Wh-Who are these people?
Hey, kids.
Keep it down.
Yes, sir!
Our apologies, big man!
Big man?
Oh, Oshima!
Female!
Way to go, Sasayan!
Hello!
H-Hello.
Me like!
Me like tall girls!
I dig the glasses!
Oshima-san!  Thank you for coming!
Thank you so much!
Why are you dressed like that?
The plan was for me
to bring in the cake,
but they already ate it...
Isn't that the girl from
the cultural festival?
Your rival's here now.
How are you going to
respond, Mizutani-san?
Rival?
She's in love with Haru.
That's not my problem.
Not her problem, huh?
Does she realize how lucky she
is to be able to say that?
Well, I'm gonna cut the cake now.
Oh, time to cut the cake?
Want any help?
I-It's okay.
I think she's avoiding me.
What's wrong?
Can't blame her for falling so hard.
Even I thought he was kinda cool.
It's not fair.
Huh?
Feels like I lost.
Not that it matters.
Hmm?
Anyway, Haru's participating
in a Christmas party.
He's really settled down.
He looks just like your average
high school student now.
We owe Shizuku-chan big time.
Misawa
Batting
Center
I need to hit the restroom.
Go ahead.
Hey!  Who ate two pieces of cake?!
Oshima-san!
Do you have a boyfriend?
N-No!
Hey, Tomio!
You don't get to hit on her first!
You have phimosis anyway!
Hey!
You're not supposed
to tell people that!
Shut up, idiots.
I can take you!
That's nice!
The hell are you on?!
U-Um...
Get off me already!
You should stop...
Eh?  Want me to knock you silly?!
Somebody should stop them...
I'll jam two fingers up your ass!
Oshima-san, Oshima-san.
Two fingers don't scare me!
I brought a puzzle book!
Wait, right now?
And it's just going
to be the two of us?
Isn't this a party?
First question, what stays still,
but is always running?
You're askin' for it!
Bring it!
Fine!  I'll kill you!
Th-This is a bad time...
Oh, Natsume-san.
Did you get your assignment back?
I know!  A clock!
Yep!
You got it, Haru-kun!
Hell, yeah!
Am I the one who's weird here?
Can you guys stop fighting in here?
Oh, a puzzle book?
Haven't seen one in ages!
Let's play.
Mizutani-san, how can you
study at a time like this?
You're amazing, Sasahara-kun.
Huh?
I don't know how to react to all of this.
You need to stop worrying so much.
Isn't that right?
Yeah, it's safe to just ignore them.
Especially in Haru's case.
Haru, show it to us again!
Oh, you mean that?
And when it looks like things
are getting crazy...
You do this to let them know.
That's too hard...
You went to Kaimei
Academy, Yoshida-kun?
Yeah, for grade school.
What?  That's where
I went to grade school.
I don't remember this guy.
Do you remember the push-off incident?
Huh?
So you were the one responsible
for the mashed-face incident?!
Wait, Yoshida?
You did stuff like that in grade school?
Uh, probably?
I don't really remember.
Sasaki Seminar
Well, I have Shizuku now.
No worries.
Oh?  Are you also attending the
winter session at that cram school?
Are you in the special
college prep course, too?
No, I'm in the normal one...
Oh, how about that?
I'm also taking that course.
You're taking the same course?
It starts next week and runs through
the end of the year with no breaks.
I can't wait.
I didn't know you were so
serious about your studies.
What's that look for?
Can you stop staring at me?
What?  Cram school?
We can't afford it.
Besides, you don't need the help.
I did it again.
Why am I making a competition of this?
It defies all reason.
Have I lost my mind?
Oh, that reminds me.
Thank you for your help, Yamaken-kun.
You helped me reach a decision.
Huh?  What are you talking about?
You gave me some advice a while back.
I've decided to have a
talk with Haru very soon.
Wait!
You've already made up your mind?
Isn't that a little too fast? Hold on!
Fast?  How so?
You should wait!
How is that too fast?
Spend some more time
thinking this through!
I don't understand what you mean.
What?
Please stop bothering
Haru-kun and Mitty.
Eh?
It's not your business, so stay out of it!
...please.
You should stay out of it, then.
Y-You have no chance with Mitty!
She has Haru-kun!
That's creepy as hell!
Ow!  Ow!  Ow!
It's like you guys are still in grade school!
What are you doing?
If that's what you think,
then what about her?
She confessed to Haru during
the cultural festival.
What?!
O-Oshima-san knows her
place, so it's okay!
I'm sorry, Oshima-san!
I didn't mean it in a bad way!
U-Um, I'm sorry!
What should I do?
I can teach you a trick
for cheering yourself up?
I'm sorry.
So you draw a circle
on your palm, then...
H-How about this?
I know this online community that
provides emotional support.
I-It's okay...
Yeah, that.  Thanks.
You have no chance with Mitty!
She has Haru-kun!
It must be nice, Haru.
Sounds like you're having
fun at your new school.
I remember that you always
said you wanted friends.
If I offered to become your friend
in exchange for Mizutani-san,
what would you do?
I don't need you if I have Shizuku.
You didn't need to answer.
I was just joking.
She's mine.
I found her.
What if Mizutani-san says
that she likes me more?
Haru.
What are you doing up there?
Shizuku, are you going home?
Yes.
I'm coming with you!
He wouldn't have...
Yamaken.
Keep your hands off Shizuku.
Were you waiting for me?
It's like a spider's thread.
Huh?
Your hair.
It's long and thin, like spider thread.
You mean like angel hair?
No.
It's that story.
Where God dangles a spider's
thread before the bad guy.
Oh, Akutagawa's story?
It was so sad.
The guy gets partway up before
he's dropped back down.
God shouldn't be so cruel.
It was probably meant as
a test of his conscience.
But that thread was his
only chance at salvation.
Who wouldn't try to shake
everyone else off?
True...
but then the thread snaps
and no one is saved.
Yeah...
Your hair looks strong.
The Christmas party was a lot of fun,
having everyone together.
Yes.
Next up is staying home for New Year's.
Mi-chan said that if you
stay home during the New Year holiday,
you'll have good health next year.
You're already moving on to next year?
Yeah...
Do you have to take that winter prep course?
Can't you study just fine without that?
Yamaken's gonna be there.
You're going to spend your
whole winter break with him?
Is he...
Are you jealous?
Yeah...
So this is jealousy.
Jealousy.
There's no point in telling him
that he doesn't need to worry.
I wanted to talk to you
before the course started.
Right, first...
I have to tell him how I feel.
I love you, Haru.
So you don't need to worry.
I've made up my mind.
You can trust me, Haru.
Th-That means you won't
take the winter prep course?
Hmm?
Huh?
Sasaki Seminar
Pass in One Try
Why are you here?!
Aren't you supposed to
be in love with me?!
I told you not to come!
Stop!  Stop!  Stop!
Get away from her, Yamaken!
Hey!  Are you listening
to me, Shizuku?!
Shut up!
I decide what I want to do!
Don't interfere with my studies!
Shi—
Pity.
This is as far as you go.
Don't come inside, Haru.
...zuku!
Math
It's a good thing Haru's an idiot.
My winter prep course has begun.
Listen to me!
Go straight home as soon as it's over!
Don't go anywhere else!
Hey!  Are you listening
to me, Shizuku?!
You better go straight home!
Straight home!
That's the guy you like?
You must be joking.
Y-Yuu-chan!
Hey, bird.
Take me to the exit.
Hey, is it over there?!
Damn, it's fast!
Next Episode
The Yamaguchis' Son, Kenji-kun
Why was I racing it?