(Where did that even come from, right?)
I decided I'm going to confess to my crush.
I'm going to do it today.
By text.
"Hey, Takase,
I know I'm being a wuss,
but I always freak out
when I try to tell you in person,
so let me say it in a text.
I like you."
delete delete delete...
I can't.
Sender:
No Subject
Kanda Saki
What's up?
It's from Kanda.
Crap, I'm nervous.
"Taking a dump."
Wait, no, she's a girl.
I'm not doing anything.
What's up with you? o:
Crap, I'm nervous.
I gotta do things in order.
"It's not a big deal,
Sender:
Subject:
Kanda Saki
It's not a big deal, but you seem surprisingly
popular with girls. (Emphasis on "surprisingly".)
But you don't have a girlfriend.
Why's that?
Are you gay? (lol)
but you seem surprisingly
popular with girls.
But you don't have a girlfriend.
Why's that?
Are you gay?"
"I'm not popular!
I'm not gay!
I want a girlfriend!"
I'm not popular!!
I'm not gay!! (lol)
I want a girlfriend!! (><)
Yes!
Yes, yes, yes!
Oh, yeah? You want a girlfriend, huh? lol
I want a boyfriend, too! (><)
"Oh, yeah? You want a girlfriend, huh?
I want a boyfriend, too!"
Nii-chan, can I play video games?
Saki-chan, want some peaches?
No thanks!
Why don't you find a boyfriend?
Aren't you interested in anyone? |v•)
"Why don't you find a boyfriend?
Aren't you interested in anyone?"
Actually, I do!
She's not replying.
Was that a bad thing to ask?
Should I confess now?
But by text?
But when am I going to do it if not now?
What if he rejects me, though?
Dammit!
Tell him! Tell him! Tell him!
Wait, this conversation...
Is it safe for me to confess?
No, by text, though?
Urgh...
Someone I'm interested in?
I'm interested in..."
Urgh...
"I'm interested in you, Takase.
Sorry to tell you like this, but I like you.
Please go out with me."
I don't care if you reject me.
Just please don't hate me...
Just please don't hate me!
Can I tell her?
But by text, though?
I mean, this is going well, but...
Are you asleep? Passed out? lol
About what we were saying,
there's actually someone I like.
I like you, Kanda-san.
Please be my girlfriend.
"Are you asleep? Passed out?
About what we were saying,
there's actually someone I like.
I like you, Kanda-san.
Please be my girlfriend."
Send
Cancel
New Message
To: Kanda Saki
Message Sent
tremble tremble
That was a quick reply.
Maybe he sent me something at the same time.
Huh?
"Are you asleep? Passed out?
About what we were saying,
there's actually someone I like.
I'll tell you at school tomorrow.
Can you wait for me after school?"
"You know those people who confess by text?
You know those people who confess by text?
I think that's pretty shitty lol
(Where did that even come from, right?)
Okay, good night!
I think that's pretty shitty.
Okay, good night!"
I think that's pretty shitty...
Someone I'm interested in?
I'm interested in...
I'm interested in you, Takase.
Sorry to tell you like this, but I like you.
Please go out with me.
Nii-chan, I'm going to sleep,
so turn off the lights—
Nii-chan?
Saki-chan, I need the peach plate back.
Saki-chan, are you asleep?
The End
My childhood friend, Nanase,
always looks grouchy.
That's just my normal face.
Childhood Friend
Good job, Kaga-kun!
You found us a really cute new member!
Nah, not really.
That's the next president for you!
Shall I rub your shoulders?
Wait, Sasahara-senpai!
No, thank you!
I'm only here because
I'm interested in stars.
It's not because Kaga invited me.
Oh? Really?
You two seem close,
I thought you were dati—
We aren't!
Nanase and I just happen
to live close together.
This happens as soon as
I say we're childhood friends.
I don't think anything of Nanase.
I don't think anything of him, either.
Besides, it seems Kaga
has a crush on someone else.
Really, Kaga-kun?
O-Of course I don't!
Are you sure?
I can more-or-less tell.
Want me to take a guess?
Hmm?
Sasahara, Sakamoto-sensei's calling you.
And it was just getting good.
Let's come back to this later.
So it is Sasahara-senpai.
There's no way you'd be interested in stars.
You're after Senpai, aren't you?
No, dammit!
It's not any of your business, either!
Why do you keep asking me?
Because I want her to reject you already.
Why?
What did I do?
You started ignoring me
ever since middle school.
Because people supposedly tease you.
Do you like it when people think
we're weirdly attached and stuff?
You don't like it when people
think we're close, huh?
What?
Of course not.
Oh, really?
You don't want people
spreading rumors about us?
What's your problem?
I was doing that for your sake.
What do you mean, for my sake?
You just suddenly started ignoring me.
So did you.
You hated me.
You were the one who hated me first.
Who cares either way?
We both hate each other.
I wouldn't go to the same
school as you if I hated you!
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Kaga, you idiot, can you
still not figure it out?
You don't have a problem
talking to anyone else,
and yet you ignore me.
Th-That's not it!
You were indifferent
to everyone else, though,
so I thought you'd never
be interested in anyone.
Wait, calm down.
Why Sasahara-senpai?
All right, sorry.
It's my fault.
I wasn't thinking about how you felt.
You've been worried for me
all this time, haven't you?
Because, well...
...we've been friends for a long time.
We've been friends for a long time? So what?
You don't get it, do you?
Huh? But...
Do you honestly think I'd do all this for you
just because we've been friends?
B-But you just said you don't hate me.
I absolutely hate you!
S-So you do hate me!
So, what? You joined the astronomy
club just to piss me off?
I'm back.
So, who's Kaga-kun's crush—
Sorry.
The End
I confessed to my crush,
and now we're dating.
But things have been...
...a bit awkward since then.
G-Goda-kun, let's walk home together—
Sorry, Kamine,
I have club work. Maybe some other time.
Watching You From Afar
Maybe we should have stayed friends.
Nah, we've only just started dating.
I need to be more proactive.
What is it, Kamine?
You're still here?
S-Sorry.
I had stuff to do.
I'm sorry I made you wait, too.
I'm here late on days I have club work.
From now on, why don't we—
No, it's not safe to go home late.
I-It's fine.
I have you, too.
Only until my bus stop.
I wonder if he didn't want to go out with me.
I wonder if I'm just
making him uncomfortable.
No, Goda-kun's just a nice person.
He always has been.
Did he avoid me just now?
He did.
Maybe he's worried he might
be sweaty from club work?
Is that it?
It is, right?
He wasn't avoiding me, was he?
Kamine, let's stop doing this.
Sorry, I should have told you sooner.
This is my first time dating anyone.
I didn't know what it's supposed to be like.
But I've been thinking, and this isn't good.
So I want to make this easy for you.
All right.
Sorry.
I probably shouldn't
tell you like this, but...
No, thanks for telling me.
Thanks for going out with me.
I'm sorry.
S-Sorry, I didn't mean to make you cry.
Nah.
Can we go back to how things were?
I guess.
But maybe not exactly how it was.
I know.
This is my fault. I'm sorry.
Why don't we try
holding hands or something?
We're in a relationship, after all.
What do you mean?
Sorry, was it too early?
No, weren't you about to dump me?
Dump you?
I never said anything like that.
I just meant we should stop
being so tense around each other.
Was I the only one who was getting tense?
Sorry, I had the wrong idea.
I, well, thought it would be weird
to start acting like a boyfriend
as soon as we started dating.
So I was trying to act like everything
was how it had always been,
but that's kind of cold, too.
So I've been thinking
about your walk home and stuff.
Was that uncalled-for?
Then why did you avoid me
when I tried to get next to you?
Well...
I was sweaty from club work.
No, actually, it's because I'm shy.
I'm such an idiot.
Such an idiot.
Sorry, I didn't see anything!
No, that was Nanase...
I'm terrible.
I'm seriously terrible.
Yuki, can you take these apples
to Nanase-san's place?
No way!
You go, Mom.
What's the matter with you?
Did you get in a fight with Kaoru-chan?
We didn't, but she kind of hates me.
What?
I thought Kaoru-chan had a crush on you.
Wait, was this still a secret?
Sorry, forget I said that.
Uh...
Next episode: We Don't Need Girls.
We Don't Need Girls