What is this?
It's a gate. It connects the inside and outside.
Outside, huh?
We've never been outside.
That's because we've been here
ever since we were born.
Mom always tells us, doesn't she?
"Don't go near the gate or fence in the back
of the forest because it's dangerous."
That's obviously a lie.
Really?
Hey, Ray!
What do you want to do if you go outside?
I don't know. What about you?
I want to ride a giraffe!
Good luck.
I wonder...
I wonder what this gate is protecting us from.
Everyone, wake up!
Or you'll be late for breakfast!
- Hey, wait for me!
- No way!
Hey! Stop messing around and get ready!
- Emma, I can't get my shoes on.
- I can't tie my shoelaces!
Okay, hold on. Don't cry.
Good morning Don, Conny, and Little Bunny!
- Morning!
- Morning, Emma.
Look, we made it!
Watch out...
I'm going to eat you!
They're at it again.
Morning, Norman! And Ray!
Good morning, Emma.
Morning, Emma.
You're so energetic.
Even though you haven't eaten breakfast yet.
How old are you again? Five?
I'm 11, the same as you guys!
And one of the oldest here!
You're laughing, too, Mom?
Emma, can you give me a hand over here?
But Mom! I'm going to redo my entrance
from the beginning.
Why? I love that part about you.
That I'm five years old on the inside?
The part where you care deeply
about your family.
Thanks, Mom!
Good morning, my dear children.
Let's give thanks that all 38 of you siblings
are able to live here happily, today, too...
Thank you for the food.
Here. Open wide.
It's delicious!
You're acting like a little baby, Conny.
I can, right, especially today?
Yes.
Age 11, type 1.
Answer each question within nine seconds.
We will now begin.
Well, I think I got at least half!
That much? Wow!
I'm jealous. I didn't get most of it.
Are you all ready for the results?
Norman. Ray. Emma.
You three did an amazing job.
You got all of them right! Perfect scores!
Those three are different, huh?
Norman is a genius who has the best brains.
And Ray, an intellect
who can compete against Norman's genius.
Emma has amazing athletic skills, and her learning
ability allows her to stay close to the other two.
They say the House has never had three kids
at this level together before.
No wonder Mom is happy with them.
Norman!
I challenge you to a game of tag!
Run, run!
Come get me, Norman!
We'll outrun you this time for sure!
Right, Conny?
Thank you for always helping me, Don.
You don't have to thank me!
I'll always help you!
Anytime, anywhere you're in need!
Based on the size of these shoe's footsteps...
You let your guard down, Norman!
Don, you always let your guard down.
Don't I always tell you? Your weakness is that
you make quick judgment and lose your cool.
Dang, I got caught.
What the heck? He practically got everyone.
Well, it's Norman after all.
The only survivor is...
...just Emma.
Norman!
I was pretending.
No fair! I was worried about you!
Emma, your weakness is that you're nice.
He caught me again! Why?
So frustrating!
Question.
What does Norman have that you don't?
The ability to plan ahead? Calmness?
Overwhelming intelligence?
Strategy.
If it's about simple physical ability,
you have the upper hand.
But Norman is strong right here. Like no other.
You're playing tag.
It's a game where you compete with strategy.
A simple game of tag?
It's like chess, but using your entire body.
Isn't that right, Norman?
Yeah. But you're a better tactician than me, Ray.
You overestimate me.
Reading the enemy's moves, huh?
But we're not even close
when it comes to Mom.
That's true. We've never beaten her at chess.
Norman!
I want a rematch!
Next game, everyone will be "It" except you!
- Whoa!
- He's losing his cool again.
You caught me.
"You can't go near there, no matter what."
Yeah, Mom is always telling us that.
The gate and the fence deep in the forest
are dangerous.
That's obviously a lie.
What do you mean?
Well, just look at it.
What part of this is dangerous?
The fence is low,
and I don't see anything threatening.
But if Mom is telling us that...
You really love Mom, after all.
But everyone—
Hey! Are you sure you guys are playing tag?
Oh, is the game over already?
We should call it a day.
If we're late, Mom will be worried.
We'll eventually leave this place, huh?
This is an orphanage.
Of course we'll leave eventually.
Before we turn 12.
You know what?
We don't receive letters from anyone.
Letters?
You know, after they leave the House,
no one writes us.
I'm sure they're being considerate
to their foster parents.
But we've all been together
ever since we were born!
Even if we're not related by blood,
we're truer siblings than most.
They must be having so much fun everyday
that they've forgotten about the House.
Then it's fine, right? I'm happy for them.
I want to go outside, too!
What would you do outside?
Isn't it obvious? Get new clothes!
- Not again.
- I mean, come on!
We only have this one uniform!
I read in books that the outside world has so many
different types of clothes! I want to wear them all!
I want to eat delicious food.
I want to go on a date with a cute girl.
Geez, that was rude.
Oh, that's not what I meant.
I want to see a train!
That's a good one!
What about you, Norman?
I want to go to different places
and see things I've never seen before.
Good idea! And you, Ray?
Once I get outside, well, I'd have to survive first.
Such a downer. What about you, Emma?
Me?
You want to ride a giraffe, right?
Did I say that?
Well, I don't really want to leave.
I want to stay here forever!
Hey, that's kind of unfair.
But I'm so happy right now. Right?
Happy, huh?
I promise to write!
I'll write a lot of letters.
I'll never forget about everyone.
When I leave the House,
I want to become a mother like Mom.
And then, I'll never abandon any children.
You love Mom very much, don't you?
Yeah!
I'm slow, and I wasn't as smart as everyone,
but even after I leave, I'll do my best.
I'll have Little Bunny so I'll be okay.
Conny...
I don't want to leave anymore.
I want to stay here!
Conny... Conny!
What song is that, Mom?
Conny!
You're kidding me!
Let's hurry and finish up cleaning.
Conny's already gone!
What should I do?
There's still time.
From the window,
I saw the lights on the gate were still on.
Mom isn't back yet either,
so I don't think Conny has left yet.
- Let's hurry, Emma.
- Okay.
"You can't go near there, no matter what."
I know. Let's get scolded together, later.
Conny?
Is this the truck that'll take Conny?
Actually, I've never seen a vehicle before.
No one's here.
Maybe she'll find it if we leave it in the back.
Yeah.
Norman.
Is someone there?
Hey, did you hear a voice just now?
Probably your imagination.
If it was a stray cat,
I would have caught it and ate it.
You eat things like cats?
It looks so delicious. Human flesh is the best.
No...
Damn! Can't I at least have a fingertip?
You idiot. It's valuable merchandise.
It's not something the likes of us can have.
All of the human flesh produced on this farm
are high-quality meat intended for the rich.
Where's Mom?
Is the Gupna done?
Mostly done, sir.
Another six-year-old...
Lately we've been shipping out
normal quality ones.
But it looks like we'll soon harvest
some high quality ones.
Isabella.
Yes.
Make the preparations
to pluck these three with full scores.
Understood.
Wait. I smell something.
Emma!
Is this place a farm?
Are we all... food?
No, it can't be. Everyone found foster homes.
And Mom...
It was the usual, kind Mom, right?
We were mistaken.
That girl wasn't Conny, right?
That was Conny.
Welcome back. How did it go?
We didn't make it.
Were we raised just to be eaten by something?
Let's escape, Emma.
We have to leave this place.
Don't worry. We can do it.
You, me, and Ray. If it's the three of us...
It might be impossible.
I can't leave them here.
Otherwise they'll definitely get killed.
I don't want any more of my family to die.
It's not impossible.
It'll be okay. Let's run away.
Together, with everyone.
B-But how? How will us kids
run away from those monsters?
Strategy. It'll be the same as playing tag.
That's right.
We'll find a way for all of us to survive.