What are you so angry about?
Hey!
Hey, mage!
I'm sorry for getting in
the way of your experiment,
but humans are a dime a dozen
as far as you're concerned.
I thought they were worthless to you.
You can just take a quick look around
and snatch one right up. Easy.
Right?
How rude! I was still talking.
Come on, you!
Isabelle...
Where am I?
Isabelle, did they tease you again?
It's that man's voice.
This is the appearance that God gave me.
It's not like I can help that
my hair is carrot-colored,
or that my eyes are the color of weeds.
I love you no matter what you look like.
Cheer up.
Let's see....
Ulysse?
Thanks, Ulysse!
Isabelle!
What happened, Isabelle?
A child got hit by a carriage!
This is bad!
I saw them chasing after Isabelle!
I-It's not our fault!
She ran into the street herself!
Wait.
Wait, please!
When is Isabelle waking up?
I haven't heard her voice in a long time.
Isabelle.
Isabelle!
Ulysse, Isabelle is gone.
She's just sleeping.
We're going home.
No.
No, Father.
I'm waiting here.
She's going to be lonely
if she wakes up alone.
Always.
Forever.
It's all right.
I woke up, didn't I?
Chise...
Elias.
Aww... Her materials cost
quite a bit, you know.
Corpses aren't free, nor is
managing the containers.
Cartaphilus.
Don't you dare call me by that name.
You're just a monster that
found a human body.
Elias!
A freak calling another a freak, huh?
What a joke.
I've put a spell on the bullet
to stop regeneration.
Chise, you're alive...
Looks like it works.
I'm in a bit...
Well, I'm in a lot of pain.
But I made it.
I'm surprised.
I'm a little surprised, too.
Chise, am I not terrifying in this form?
I'm going to turn back, so let go.
You're right.
I don't think you could get through
the door being that tall.
You should probably turn back.
You're right...
Silky would be furious with
me if I broke the door.
I'd apologize with you even if she was.
That's reassuring.
This girl has strange taste.
Master!
Alice.
Master...
You idiot!
Don't go darting off like that!
I thought about abandoning
you when I saw your letter.
I'm sorry.
Don't overestimate your own strength.
Think about it.
But!
But...
You wouldn't have...
You're my apprentice and my bodyguard.
A bodyguard ought not to
leave their master's side.
Yes, sir.
You're awful.
The brain's complicated.
It takes a lot of work to fix.
You...
I just want that dog because
he'd make a good subject.
Sorcerers don't step into mage territory.
That was a tacit agreement.
Why do you go after the fairies?
Because it seems fun.
I could make something interesting
if I used a fairy for a chimera.
But fairy curses are a pain to deal with.
That's why I put a collar on that sorcerer.
You monster.
I don't need a dog if it
can't even run my errands.
Isn't...
that...
Isabelle?
That isn't your Isabelle.
I've seen you before.
You deceived Matthew in
Ulthar and killed Mina.
Ulthar?
Oh, the cat experiment.
I think I could get some decent
results if I tried it again.
What do you think?
Chise.
You won't have him.
I absolutely won't let you have him!
What an annoying brat.
Chise...
Anything?
Yup.
Truth be told, you can
do anything with magic.
You can turn rocks into gold,
make fish swim through the sky,
keep harvests from ever rotting.
His words fly through my mind.
But... that's something that must not be done.
I won't let you have him.
You're pretty knowledgeable for a kid.
Tarantula hawks.
They prey on spiders.
But being so small,
they're just going to get eaten.
Chise, stop this!
Your body is...
Mage!
She just ate a little of me.
Chise!
Chise, you mustn't do that.
We must not twist the rules of this world!
Horse and Hattock!
A fairy spell, huh?
Not bad.
Why did I want that, again?
To make a chimera.
Why did I want to make
a chimera in the first place?
For what purpose?
Oh, whatever.
Now, go find him with your strings.
That wretch won't come looking for us here.
Thank you, Blue Flame.
The Thorn of Shadows?
Damn it, you've brought so
much trouble with you.
Buy you don't hate it, do you?
Not really.
Get off my head!
He's a Will-o'-the-Wisp.
A blue flame fairy that lives in forests
and cemeteries, confusing passers-by.
Don't say my name!
That's rude!
Fine, fine.
My blood's racing through my body.
Chise, calm down.
It'll be all right.
Elias.
I'm sorry.
I didn't listen to you.
Be careful from now on.
That's good enough.
Chise!
It feels like my blood's going
to overflow and explode.
You're a Sleigh Beggy, huh?
You're so weak.
Poor thing.
Take my coal.
You'll feel a little better.
It's warm.
You're finally awake, you sleepy dog.
I'm not a dog!
I'm...
Don't be crazy, you dumb dog.
You're neither human, nor an ordinary dog.
Are you still not awake?
Grow up, puppy,
and stop depending on dead people!
Quit whining and go back to
your useful form, church grim!
Your job is to chase the grave
robbers' asses to the gates of Hell.
You're a black dog.
I see.
That's what it was.
I get it now.
No matter how long I wait,
my sister won't come back.
Chise, will you take me with you?
I'll give you my all.
You're one thick-headed dog!
Sleigh Beggy or not, we can't be the
ones to ask a human to make a pact!
A pact?
He's requesting to become your familiar.
The ultimate promise, that you would
share everything with one another.
Your senses, your emotions, even your time.
Time?
If you die, he dies.
No!
It's fine.
I've seen inside you, so I know.
Don't you need to wait for Isabelle?
There you guys are.
Cartaphilus!
I told you not to call me that!
You're so mean.
I'd gotten used to that arm. How inconvenient.
I won't give your arm back.
I don't want an arm that's been
used as an ingredient for a freak.
Hey, he's taken on a dog's form.
That makes him an easier target.
Please, Chise.
If you die, he dies.
I don't want him to take me.
I don't want to be here.
I'd rather be your...
It's okay.
I don't want to be alone anymore, either.
Continue after me.
Tie now the silver thread.
Tie now the roots of our veins.
The holly, so that we may not be separated.
The ivy, so that we may not come apart.
Tie to the yew tree seven times.
Until the day the snake spits out its tail.
Chise, give me a new name.
Take me by your side.
Come,
Ruth.
Oh, dear.
He woke up from his dream of being human.
Good night, Isabelle.
Wait for me until my time with her is over.
Too bad.
So you belong to her now, huh?
Undoing a pact is such a pain.
Why don't you back off, then?
Yeah.
I will.
What's with that look?
You learn to give up quickly
when you live for a long time.
What is the purpose that drives you?
To live without suffering.
I'm sick of rotting away until an end
that I don't even know will come.
It hurts.
It's painful.
Huh?
But why is my body like this?
You don't mind making others
suffer for your sake?
That's right.
Isn't that how living things are?
If that's what you think, you're
neither human nor beast.
You're nothing but a monster in
human form, Cartaphilus.
My name is Joseph, little boy.
See you around.
He's like a natural disaster.
At least disasters are knowable.
Cartaphilus...
It's said that the Son of God cursed
him so that he can never die.
He's a monster that roams aimlessly,
driven only to satiate his curiosity.
And what happened was the result of
being chosen by that monster.
Just why?
My head may have flown if I'd refused.
I had no choice.
I see.
You.
Have you met him before?
Him?
No way.
I see.
Be careful on your way home.
I don't need you to worry for me.
We're going.
Okay!
Now, then.
I have to send them off.
You sure are a hard worker.
My job is to send the living to the swamp.
But my job is also to see the dead
off to the gates to the other side.
This one is artificial, but being so,
it'll bear an artificial soul.
See you!
Well, we'd better head home, too.
I can explain things to you tomorrow.
You must be tired.
Yes.
Your scolding will come
when we get home, too.
Okay.
Ruth.
Let's go home together, Ruth.
Yeah.
From now on, where you go
home is where I go home.
A new friend.
A brief, peaceful rest.
The girl steps into a beautiful rose garden,
her mind still burdened by her troubles.
Speak of me, and I'll eat you.