Hey, there...
Want a walnut?
This is starting to get interesting!
Morning.
Did you get any sleep?
The Rainbow of Albion
Good morning, Commander.
Good morning.
Now, then...
I've requested approval from headquarters
for the observation and protection subjects
on this base to wear these.
So it's time to correct our past mistakes.
Why are you freeing him?
I'm correcting our mistake.
I cleared this with HQ.
Use of Lead Gears on this base is now forbidden!
As Globe's observer organization,
Salty Dog cannot allow this.
I'm in charge here!
The commander's so cool.
My opinion of him just improved.
A-Akari...
What are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
I will introduce you.
This is Akari Yomatsuri-san.
That's the daughter of the commander,
who lived with his wife after they split...
His wife is Governor Yomatsuri,
aboard the Tenkaidou, right?
Hi there, everyone.
I'm the magical girl Akari-chan!
Magical girl?
You're the girl from yesterday?
Yes, she is Code Papillon,
last night's flight director.
What the hell is going on?
She is also an amazingly talented hacker.
She was good enough to try hacking Alonzo.
We can't afford to not have her here.
I've been planning to have her
cooperate with us for a while now.
Akari's a hacker?
A magical girl!
H-Hey...
Wait!
Don't touch that!
Oh, God...
How could he be so cruel to the daughter
he hasn't seen for five years?
He hasn't seen her for five years.
My opinion of him just dropped.
How did li'l ol' me end up a magical girl?
"Li'l ol' me"?
Is she a bumpkin?
My father is the commander of
Globe's Tanegashima base.
And my mother is governor of
the satellite base Tenkaidou.
My parents, concerned only
with their jobs, abandoned me,
and I was always so lonely.
My computer was my only friend...
I know the truth!
Four years ago, I was so excited
that my father was going to spend
my birthday with me for once!
And the reason for his last-second cancellation is
that he actually had a date
with Rita-san right there!
No, s-s-see...
We had to recruit her for this
base as soon as possible.
I'm sorry...
Pathetic, Commander.
My opinion of him just plummeted.
Annou Yams
Annou Yams?
Delicious!
I'm sorry, both of you...
For what?
Keeping you locked in the base all this time.
I really am sorry.
Will you allow me to recruit her?
By the way, I'm not cheap.
Very well.
But she'll stay at my place,
along with the other three.
Do you mean Teppei and Hana?
As well as Daichi-kun?
That's right.
I should have done this sooner...
I'm so grateful that Daichi made me realize it.
The wind on this island feels good, doesn't it?
Yeah, it does.
Hey...
Is this you?
Ah... Yup.
My dad and Uncle Nishikubo were good friends.
So when I was little, I used to stay here a lot.
I loved this island...
That's you, isn't it?
Hey, I'm back.
You're a good cook!
I can't make anything special.
It looks good, doesn't it?
Yeah.
It smells great.
You're cuter when you smile.
Listen up...
From now on, you're family,
and this is your house.
But you're growing boys and girls
living beneath the same roof.
So try to show some restraint.
You know what I mean, right?
Restraint?
Was the cologne in the bathroom
a present from Rita-san?
Don't worry about small things like that!
It makes you a small person.
Um...
I can't find the switch for the steam bath...
We don't have one here!
My restraint!
Restraint...
She has me beat...
She's totally in the lead now.
I love the way this house smells!
It smells old.
But it's got heart.
Welcome back.
So this is a friend of yours!
Did you like the walnut?
You know Pitz?
I saw him at the shrine today.
The shrine?
On this island, there's an old shrine.
And there's a legend about it...
Long ago, a messenger descended from
heaven, leaving behind a huge rock
with an angel sealed inside.
Hey...
Which do you think is a stronger heroine,
a magical girl or an angel?
There are so many stars,
I can't find the Big Dipper.
This island has barely any streetlamps.
It really is amazing...
The Milky Way?
Well, the Milky Way's amazing too, but...
Just two days ago, I was wondering
what to do with my life...
It's all amazing.
It's thanks to that rainbow you showed me.
That round rainbow... I always thought
it was something I'd imagined as a kid.
Hey, Daichi...
Doesn't it creep you out?
What?
You haven't changed.
You always surprise me.
Your Livlaster really surprised me.
So...
This is yours.
Okay, the game's back on!
No!
I cannot allow Daichi Manatsu
to go on any further missions.
Even if it was the Globe Federation's
unanimous opinion?
Doghouse to Pointer.
The fact that the Daichi Manatsu boy defeated
the Kiltgang with his Livlaster
is having a significant effect.
But Impacters other than the Earth
Engine are also capable of that.
Globe is investigating the use of
low-orbit Impacters, as well.
I think eliminating them at close range,
in the stratosphere, is the more reliable way.
But doesn't that risk damaging
the planet's surface too much?
Over.
We are past that point.
Hana Mutou is absolutely necessary
to the Kivotos Plan.
Don't forget that having her
under our control is a top priority
for those of us in the Ark Faction.
Thus, it will be up to you to
deal with Daichi Manatsu.
Daichi Manatsu...
Selling the basic theory behind the Machine
Goodfellows and the designer children
would be enough to earn a fortune.
And CEO Kube gets everything...
But it was the A.I. called Puck that
developed the basic theory, right?
He's got it good.
Hey!
I'm afraid I can't ignore that.
Oh, I mean, uh...
Your secretary, Hitomi-chan,
is totally in love with you.
Why don't you make her yours?
Have any Kiltgang attacked since the last time?
I heard that manned Impacter
is called the Earth Engine.
Last time, I kicked its butt.
If it was running off a Livlaster,
does that mean they can use
the Princess of Blume now?
Have fun tonight.
Approaching-Earth Object sighted!
It's a Kiltgang!
It's been nine years since I last
turned into the real me.
Last time, I underestimated the Earthlings, but...
That's...
The Type-1 that killed Daichi Manatsu's father.
I can use this...
A Kiltgang has appeared within
defensive zone 1, Alpha sector!
It's heading straight for Earth.
Distance 34,000 meters.
Approach speed 52 meters per second!
They want a report about when I got the
Livlaster, but I don't know what to say...
Hey.
Do you need something?
That's cold, Daichi Manatsu-kun.
It seems the Kiltgang has attacked again.
I'll tell you something interesting...
This is...
the type that appeared nine years ago!
No, it's the same one!
Commander,
Alonzo has approved an emergency
launch of the Earth Engine!
They're launching the Pegasus rocket.
The Earth Engine's energy is charging!
What's going on?!
I've forbidden Daichi to launch!
I gave him permission.
Governor, the expansion sequence
has activated again!
What was that?
Daichi Manatsu-kun has already won one battle.
The Kiltgang that's currently approaching Earth
is the one that killed your father nine years ago.
Commander!
What are you thinking,
launching the Earth Engine?
We haven't done any maintenance yet,
beyond swapping out armor!
Well, that is a problem.
But if the need arises,
we have the low-orbit Impacters.
You're overstepping your authority!
Get out of here!
I am denying Salty Dog access to the
control room or any of the secure blocks!
This is the end for Daichi Manatsu.
What's wrong?
Come with me!
Commander, Alpha sector's
Impacters aren't working!
That's really bad...
The relay satellite that sends
the commands isn't working.
I can try bouncing it off another satellite...
Akari!
Leave it to the magical girl!
Logical, logical...
German Impacters, you will do as I command!
"Logical"? That isn't magic...
Impacter Feige's interception
systems are coming on line!
Akari's doing this?
She's controlling the German Impacters from here?
They're a lot more lax than the Thousand
system I took over a while back.
Wait a second...
You were behind the hacking of the
American Air Force last year?
Don't worry about small things like that.
It makes you a small person.
You're kidding...
A voice that resounds throughout infinity
sings a melody of gentle memories.
The light of the promise
I know we once shared.
An earthquake?
Its epicenter is Tanegashima!
This time, I won't underestimate you!
Impacter Feige, lost.
The Earth Engine is coming into
contact with the Kiltgang!
Can you hear me, Daichi?
The Earth Engine still isn't repaired!
Turn back now!
Hey, Uncle...
My dad flew to stop that thing, didn't he?
That means I have to stop it.
Otherwise,
what my dad did will be meaningless!
I won't let you get any farther!
It's moving so slowly...
It hasn't been repaired at all!
I'll rip you apart with my fangs, Earth Engine!
What's that?
A planetary sign?
Albion!
What?
Albion... What are you doing?!
That Kiltgang...
It's a friend.
Hana?
Teppei, is that you?
Are you okay, Teppei?
Yes.
This thing's main system never worked before.
Why did it turn on?
That earthquake was Blume moving.
You did it, didn't you?
I just sang.
Either way...
Maybe it's thanks to God that we survived today.
God?
I've never seen God.
Teppei was able to pilot an enemy robot.
What does that mean?
Globe's Tanegashima base is split
over Teppei's true identity.
And then, two of the enemy launch a bold assault!
Next time, on episode 4 of Captain Earth:
Assault of the Planetary Gear.
Assault of the Planetary Gear
Earth Engine, expand!