Flowers that bloom in the darkness
can only be at ease in the darkness
can only be at ease in the darkness.
The beauty of falling flower petals...
There is no need to let blossoms
fall before they bloom.
Here, sorry to keep you waiting.
Today's curry rice.
Wow, Brother.
It looks delicious!
Oh, right!
Thanks!
The sauce, the sauce.
By the way, Brother.
Did you buy the baumkuchen cake we saw
yesterday at the store near the harbor?
Oh...
You forgot?
Come on! I told you I must have it today!
Oh, sorry.
By the way...
Is this the cake you meant?
Oh, Brother.
You're going to get it!
H-Hey!
Stop!
Ah
Brother...
Must you work while you eat?
I got the interview records
from the city police.
The one with Kyouka-chan.
I heard she was an orphan before
the Port Mafia took her in...
As for why she became an
orphan in the first place,
her parents were killed.
The one responsible was...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I got you a case.
Before that, though, here's a taser.
The Port Mafia's after you, too.
We wanted you to have it for self defense.
Well, I don't think you'll be in
any danger this time, though.
What kind of job is it?
You have to deliver this
envelope with evidence
to a judge in court.
And this is the judge.
Got it.
I've memorized his face.
You're really into this.
Is it because it'll be your first job?
No.
My first job was to infiltrate
a building and kill two people.
I see.
She's always been working.
Demon Snow is an ability to kill.
Only when killing someone does
Kyouka's existence have meaning.
I'll do my best.
We can't go in?
You need a permit.
But it's almost time.
Please sign in on that form
and wait until you're called.
But it's almost time.
Sorry, it's the rules.
Nope, the judge isn't picking up.
I guess there was some miscommunication.
We have to do something about the guard.
You mean get rid of him?
Huh?
First, I'll use my charms to
lure him into a deserted place,
then stab...
We don't do things like that at the Agency!
Then I only know one other way.
Hey!
Kyouka-chan?
Authorized
Personnel
Only
Switch Room
Electrical
Transformer
What the...
What are you doing?
What's all this racket about?
A delivery.
Oops.
Got in... a lot of trouble.
Here.
The president settled things.
He's friends with the judge.
It was going so well up until
the power outage...
So doing that was fine in your mind?
So you're still holding onto that phone.
I had the service provider
change the program.
It's important to me.
About possibilities as we move forward...
If we can figure out the remaining
unknowns about your ability,
and if you can control your Demon Snow
without the voice from the phone,
then you can become an asset to the Agency—
No!
No.
I'm never using Demon Snow again.
Demon Snow,
punish those who teach
Kyouka a world of lies.
Though it is the blood of vermin,
it's still beautiful when it splatters.
Ability:
Golden Demon
Port Mafia Executive
Omisaki Kouyou
Don't you agree?
My dear Kyouka...
Do you know how I worried
for you and felt such pain
that I left you with animals and vermin?
But there is nothing to worry about now.
You need not concern yourself with anything.
I will protect you.
She is not going back to the Port Mafia.
Her strengths are for her
to use in Agency jobs.
I knew I should have come for you without
waiting for Ougai-dono's permission.
I cannot let you stay
here for a moment longer
in this festering lair of hypocrisy.
You must have been led astray
by their beguiling words
and mistaken their world
for one full of light.
But they will eventually ask
you to use your Demon Snow.
Let us return to the place where you belong.
Wait.
Where are you taking her?
The place where Kyouka-chan belongs...
is the Agency!
So slow.
A second demon?
Maybe I'll finish my job first after all.
Die, boy.
No!
Ougai-dono wishes all Agency
operatives to be eradicated.
However, I pleaded for
your life to be spared,
and he agreed to make a special exception.
Come back, Kyouka.
You are a flower born of darkness.
You will only be at ease in the darkness.
No.
I am not a flower of darkness.
She has been blinded by the light.
It is a light you showed her.
But fortunately, all is not lost.
I doubt you would want to stay
if the Agency no longer has him,
even more so if he is killed because of you.
Okay!
I'll come back. So please.
Everything is for you, Kyouka.
You'll understand someday.
How precious you are.
Well done, Kyouka.
I did not sense anything from you.
I saw a bright world.
I cannot go back to a time when
I did not know such a thing existed.
Don't use it, Kyouka.
If you use it, you will...
Demon Snow, defeat my enemy!
My Rocinante...
The roads in this country are too narrow.
We'll just have to walk to our destination.
I really want to finish
this so we can go back.
It's been four years since
I was last outside.
Oh, well!
Let's go.
Our luggage is about to arrive.
This blade is your true nature.
You kill anyone as soon as you
believe they are in your way.
You are like a demon, yourself.
No!
I can understand why you think that.
But a flower that has
bloomed in the darkness
can only be at ease in the darkness.
Why do I know that?
Because there was a woman who
also craved the same light,
but was burned by it and
fell into the darkness.
Come back, Kyouka.
I don't want to.
Despite everything, I still...
You cannot change your true nature.
You justify any killing
to achieve our goals.
If that were not true,
you would not be able to
use your demon like so.
After all, your demon...
killed your parents.
That's...
But why?
No, this is...
He would not understand.
No one who lives in the world of light can.
You no longer have to wield that blade in
search of a place where you can belong.
I will protect you.
Please duck.
Oh, look how it flies!
Are you okay, Atsushi?!
Kunikida-san... Why are you here?
I modified Kyouka's cell so that it'd
send a signal if anyone called it.
Get up.
Why're you acting like a damsel in distress?
A weretiger's supposed to be tough!
Agency vermin!
Don't show Kyouka any more
of your toxic light!
Wow, what great timing.
It's like the split second
before a collision.
If we could've come just a bit later,
we would've had it easy.
Do you want in?
I don't care either way,
but all the stares are
making me uncomfortable.
Ability:
Grapes of Wrath
Guild Operative
John S
Oh, fine.
I guess I'll work for my keep for the Guild.
Guild Operative
Lovecraft
Ability:
The Great Old One
I'm tired.
Ugh, itchy.
Yuck, tired and itchy.
Are they gifted Guild members?
Oh, keep the middle clear, will you?
Our luggage will be arriving soon.
Something's up there!
No!
Fire!
Episode Seventeen
Three Companies Conflict
Come to think of it...
Where is Sir Poe and Lady Louisa?
They have a fear of heights,
so they stayed behind.
They should just die.
That was easy, Reverend.
May God have mercy on the sinful.
Where am I?
I think there was an enemy attack...
That's quite a superb critical
injury you've got there, Atsushi.
Well, it's time for treatment.
I'll use this one today.
The detectives have fully
recovered, physically.
What a helpless lot you are.
Without my ability,
you'd all be pushing up daisies by now.
How are you all feeling?
President...
I'm sorry.
I was there, and yet...
All good.
I'll be out for a bit.
But isn't it dangerous to go out right now?
He's pretty riled up, from the looks of him.
Hey, Elise-chan...
Eating that much isn't
good for your health...
Why?
Sweetness is justice.
Well, sure, but...
I can consider trying on the dress
you bought me earlier, Rintarou.
Do you want seconds?
Boss, we received word that the
Agency got to the scene ahead of us
and took Kouyou away.
We can't take rash action
now that one of the top five executives
has been taken hostage.
Right...
Okay!
Let's kill the president of the Agency!
I prefer assassination.
If we hire outside contractors,
we'll spare ourselves the labor
and we can focus on confronting the Guild.
Hey, Sister.
It's been a while.
It has indeed been a while, traitor.
Boy, is Kyouka safe?
She's missing.
Because of you.
What's so funny?!
Leave her to me.
Dazai-san!
Just leave it, okay?
Well, then.
Sorry to get right to the point,
but tell us where the
Port Mafia's at in the conflict
and what your strategy is moving forward.
Have you forgotten the
Port Mafia's code, boy?
Those with loose tongues die first.
Your subordinates were marked with a brand
that identified them as torture specialists.
On the rare occasion that they ran
into trouble, I would help out...
Can you recall a single hostage who
didn't talk after I asked the questions?
This is not for the eyes of children.
All operatives are to leave
the company building
and gather at the former Bankoudou.
Is that the place that used
to be your headquarters
before you founded the Agency, President?
Only a select few know of that place.
If we cannot keep our location secret,
we'll be crushed by foes
who have superior numbers.
So the president is
prepared to go to war...
I seem to have visitors.
President?
What's the matter?
What's wrong?
The call with the president just...
Could it be an enemy attack?
What?
Then we should go help right away!
The president is fine.
More importantly—
How do you know that for sure?!
Try to grab my hand.
You'll figure it out right away.
That's the first technique
I learned from my master.
I've never won a single match against him.
He's not going to lose to a group
of dime-a-dozen assassins.
Go back to your master and
tell him, "good try."
Continue to target me and me alone!
Well done.
It seems the Agency has abandoned their office
and hidden in a different facility.
It will be difficult to
find their new location.
The Port Mafia have begun to
make their move, as well.
When I was a boy...
I worked for two years to
buy a gun like this,
but I still couldn't save enough,
so I killed four men.
Now, I own the company that makes this gun.
Money is a nightmare.
Every time you obtain something you desire,
you lose something you desire.
Eventually, the world becomes as tiresome
as blue smoke rising from burning leaves.
That's why, John...
my world is so bright right now.
That city will be mine.
Listen, all.
The Port Mafia seeks to
eradicate the Agency.
The Guild seeks to usurp the Agency.
We must protect the Agency
from these two foes.
Dazai, explain.
Yes, sir.
The Guild has substantial financial assets,
and the Port Mafia has
the numerical advantage.
So, we will split into defensive
and offensive teams
and engage in guerrilla tactics.
The critical goal for the defense
is to protect Yosano-sensei here.
Defensive Team: Fukuzawa, Ranpo, Yosano, Kenji
With her healing ability,
as long as we don't die outright,
we will be cured of any injury.
Offensive Team A
Kunikida, Tanizaki
The offense will split into two teams,
and surprise the enemy using
Tanizaki-kun's subterfuge ability
Offensive Team B
Dazai, Atsushi
and my nullification ability.
The crux of this strategy is to keep
our base of operations hidden.
If our enemies were to hit us
here with everything they have,
our defense would not hold.
Boss, our assault ended in failure.
We've put a tail on him, but I suspect...
Very well.
It's all according to plan.
And?
What about the radioactive tracking element
we put on the assassins' clothes?
We're getting a strong signal.
That's the Agency's secret hiding place.
Only one of the three
organizations can survive.
Our only course of action is to fight!
Of course, we'll be the ones left standing.
I'm looking forward to the results.
It'll be a three-way gifted war!
Episode Eighteen