Kiss Him, Not Me
Back to My Original Self!
What Should I Do?
They put up the new Mirage Saga work.
Ooh, Terra x Shion.
I like it! I like it!
There...
Why the hell are
you so confident?!
Don't think about it!
Even if it gets to me,
I can't do anything about it!
We'll have a problem if you
don't start taking me seriously.
Just kidding!
Sorry!
You were just so cute,
I couldn't help teasing you.
Goodness! You sure got me!
Shima-chan, you're such a troublemaker!
Sorry!
It doesn't count! Doesn't count!
Just some normal physical contact.
Snap out of it!
What's this?!
A Valentine's project?
Get Your Valentine's Day Fired Up!
Mirage Saga x PixV
Collaboration
Send chocolates to
a Mirage character!
"Send chocolates to a Mirage Saga character!"
Huge prize for the winner!
Yeah?
Apparently, whoever wins gets an
illustration by the character designer!
Plus, the designer will sign
and make it out to the winner!
It's a one-of-a-kind drawing!
I want it so bad!
First, I've gotta consider the design...
Senpai!
Hello.
Cute Fun
Oh, Shima-chan!
What's the problem? I want
to talk to Serinuma-senpai.
You're too close.
For some reason, I don't want you
within a two meter radius of her.
Why don't you
back off, then?
Senpai, did you hear about
the Valentine's collaboration?
Of course! Are you trying
for it, too, Shima-chan?
Yup!
I knew it. What's your plan?
I'm still thinking about it,
but I've got a few ideas.
And this is just a suggestion,
but how about we test our recipes together?
You!
How could you ask her that?
Oh, it's fine if you two come as well.
Shall we call Mutsumi-senpai
and Shinomiya-kun, too?
Then you'd be at ease, right?
Besides, it might be fun
to see you boys watch us
make chocolates you'll never get.
This jerk!
All right, if you're gonna
go that far, we'll go!
Be my guest!
Character chocolates is
a pretty classic choice.
Yup.
Today's just for prep, so
how about we give it a try?
First, choose a picture you
want to make in chocolate.
Isn't this from my doujinshi?
Yeah. It's a Shion illustration
by Yokoshima-sensei.
Should I have asked you first?
No, no. If I'm able to help
you out at all, it makes me happy.
Shima-chan, thank you!
So what do we do after that?
Then, copy the picture onto
parchment paper with a pencil.
After that, flip it, and trace
again with a chocolate pen.
Then you put it in the
fridge until it hardens.
Then you fill it in with colored chocolate.
And then you take off the parchment paper.
All done!
Look at that!
What an amazing job.
I bet you could seriously win with this!
No! This won't cut it!
Shion's beauty doesn't come through at all!
Shion is more beautiful!
crunch
Munch
Bite
Crunch
Stronger, more ephemeral!
Munch
Bite
Crunch
This won't do!
Munch
Bite
Crunch
Munch
Bite
S-Scary!
Crunch
Munch
Bite
Crunch
Munch
Bite
Besides, I'm sure lots of people
are doing character chocolates.
Mine wouldn't stand out.
Very true. If you want to stand out,
something else would be better.
How about we make it 3-D?
3-D?
Let's see. Something like...
This.
Th-This is it!
Nothing less from Yokoshima-sensei!
Please, will you teach me?
Gladly!
Let's aim for that star together!
Yes!
What's with the mood?!
It's done!
What do you think? Isn't it cute!
I think mine's pretty good, too.
It is.
Why are you three trying so hard?
And...
Why isn't she improving at all?
Huh? Was I always this bad at
figuring out how 3-D things look?
It's like, I start, it doesn't feel right,
and then I just make it worse and worse.
If this keeps up, I might
not make the deadline!
Senpai!
Relax. First, try to have fun with it. Okay?
Yeah. Thank you, Shima-ch—
She's so close!
Hey!
What are you tryin' to pull?
My gut's telling me not to let
you anywhere near Serinuma!
Same here!
All right.
We're both girls, so there shouldn't
be anything to worry about.
Oh, really?
Personally, I think their
gut feeling is dead-on.
If not, what's your motive behind all this?
I like things that are cute and beautiful.
So, I'm attracted to her, that's all.
So you're just into her looks?
Well, obviously, it's not just that.
I mean, if anything,
wouldn't that be you?
It took over 73 hours...
but it's done!
Mu
Nana
Shi
Iga
Wh-Why is it avant-garde?!
It's terrible, isn't it?!
I've worked on it for so long, I can't tell!
It's okay! It's actually pretty good!
It's got a feeling that only you
could bring, Serinuma-san.
Yeah! It's very avant-garde and...
Right! Your eye's drawn to it! It's eccentric!
Eccentric...
Idiot!
No!
Sorry!
Serinuma-senpai,
if it's all right, please submit
mine using your name.
No, no. I couldn't. Look how nice it is!
Isn't the deadline tomorrow, though?
If you want to win, isn't Nishina's
chocolate the way to go?
Mu
Iga
Shi
Well, he does have a point.
Even though I practiced so much...
It's delicious.
Oh, I see...
I...
What?! You ended up
sending in the one you made?
Was there something wrong
with the one I made?
That's not it. It was supposed to
be a Valentine's chocolate, right?
I remembered that chocolate is a gift.
I know it was poorly done,
but I put all my feelings into it.
So I wanted to send that one.
So, Shima-chan, I'm so sorry!
No.
I think that's great.
It's what makes you wonderful.
Huh? No... Come on...
Oh right, I have something.
This is a token of my thanks for
always getting along with me.
This is totally obligatory chocolate.
Yeah.
She's pretty cute, huh?
So you're just into her looks?
If anything, wouldn't that be you?
It was all about her looks at the start.
But, now...
I don't want to give her up.
At that time, I didn't know...
That the day would come where my
feelings would be put to the test.
Serinuma-san?
Y-Yes?
Kiss Him, Not Me
Ka—
Kae-chan?!
Yes?
What happened?! Why are
you so, you know... that!
Well, you know, I had so much failed
Valentine's chocolate left over.
It would have been a waste to toss it, right?
So...
When I ate them all...
I got like this!
Te-he!
Good morning!
Y-Yeah!
Are you feeling okay?
It's not good for your health to have
your weight fluctuate suddenly.
Thanks for worrying about
me! I'll be careful.
Iga
Nana
Nana!
Oh, no! I'll go call the teacher!
Serinuma-san.
Huh?! Shinomiya-kun?!
Get a hold of yourself, Shinomiya-kun!
Someone help!
Infirmary
This is a dream. A dream. A dream!
If I go to sleep and wake up again,
she'll go back to normal.
I have to sleep.
We gotta get her to lose weight!
I get you, but there's
nothing we can really do.
I know she's got a good personality,
and I know she's mega cute when she's thin.
So there's only one option!
I prefer a beauty with a good personalty
over a beast with a good personality!
You're so honest that it disgusts me.
But...
I get you!
Right?!
Uh, sure...
It's delicious!
I can really have all of this?
Of course!
Nishina!
Nanashima-kun, are you okay?
Shinomiya-kun, I'm really sorry.
What are you doing?
Well, she's gotten so round and soft.
I just want to feed her lots and lots!
That tickles, Shima-chan.
Stop it, idiot!
Look, you made him cry.
Don't drive him into a corner!
You know what? Shima-chan was
throwing a party for me.
A party? For what?
I got an email earlier.
It said my chocolate got the special prize.
Wh-What?!
Th-That did?
Apparently the judges really liked it.
That's a lie!
And so, I've been invited
to the award ceremony!
The director, voice actors, and
character designer will be there.
All the staff I admire are coming!
Doesn't it make you want to do
your best to dress yourself up?
Let's get character nails done!
Yeah! Let's! Let's!
Serinuma.
I'll help, too.
You'll meet people you admire, right?
Let's have you meet them looking your best.
Nanashima-kun!
Touched
So first, lose some weight!
H-He said it!
All right!
Five more laps!
That's pretty hardcore.
Gotta push 'em while
their morale's still high!
Hey, why are you doing this?
I do realize she looks a tad
chubby now, but...
Go get your eyes checked out!
I'm gonna die.
Senpai! Let's take a break!
Don't go overboard, okay?
I'm fine! I'm gonna do my
best for Mirage Saga!
Next! I'm gonna do five sets of 20 squats!
K-Kae-chan, you look like you're about to die.
Oh, yeah?
Her figure hasn't changed much,
but she looks so depressed!
And, after that...
Dammit, she's been so
physically active, so why?
Nana. Nana!
Maybe if I add more to her workout...
Nana! Don't push her too
hard. She's exhausted.
If I'm not tough on her, she'll never change!
Besides, don't you want her back to
normal as fast as possible, too?
But, you know how her workout is.
Oh. Shinomiya?
We're gonna change part of your plan.
Sensei, take it away.
What your workout needs...
is "otagei!"
Amazing. Aren't they all audience members?
You see a lot of it at events
for female voice actors.
Isn't it pretty difficult?
It's called "otagei" because
otaku can do it, right?
I could pull it off with a little practice.
Ahem
Look at this.
This is the result!
Iga
Nana
Ni
Mu
Shi
Wh-Why do you look so grossed out?!
No, no. It was great. You're really good.
Look me in the eyes!
You were really good! It looks fun!
Shinomiya-sensei, please teach me.
S-Sure!
All right then, how about
we all give it a try?
All of us?
Otagei is fun because you do it as a group.
And don't you think that'll give
Serinuma-senpai the best support?
Wh-What's happening?!
It's really fun!
And it's a real workout!
Otagei is pretty great!
Yeah! It's really fun!
How about we take a break? It's not
good to push your body too much.
You're right. Senpai?
Huh? I can keep going!
You're all doing it together with
me, after all! I can still go!
What was that sound... just now?
S-Serinuma-senpai!
S-Serinuma!
S-Serinuma-san!
Can we put a stop to this weight loss thing?
Huh? What are you saying?
This happened because
you pushed her too hard.
Plus, you're too aggressive, Nanashima-senpai.
Huh? I was just trying to help!
You're the one who pushed her the most.
It's basically you that got her hurt!
Wha—
Stop.
Nishina-san, you went too far.
Both of you, calm down.
Whether she quits or keeps going
depends on what Serinuma-san wants. Right?
I understand.
I'll take her home today.
What the hell's her problem?
S-Sorry. It's all because I suggested otagei.
Huh? That's not it, dummy.
Good morning!
Oh, Serinuma-san.
How's your back?
It's getting much better.
Sorry for causing such a fuss.
Shima-chan took me to
school this morning, too.
It's only natural.
Oh, what a gentleman.
Thanks for carrying my bag. And sorry.
No. It's only natural!
Don't hurt yourself again, okay?
Five Minute Break
If you need anything,
let me know!
I'm perfectly fine.
Thanks!
Senpai, are you okay?
I'll walk you there!
Between Classrooms
It's right there, so I'm good.
Do you need anything?
Gasp!
Shall I pull down your panties?!
Just let me know!
Bathroom Break
Ka
What should I do? She'll come again!
Come with me, Serinuma-san.
Um, Igarashi-kun?
Sorry. You seemed at a loss when
I saw you, so I just brought you here.
Was I wrong?
To be honest, you did help me. Thanks.
I do understand that she's
worrying about you, though.
Everyone's so worried about me, even though
it's my fault for getting carried away.
I've caused a lot of trouble.
What's the matter?!
I'm pumping myself up again!
Everyone's been helping me so much!
And above all, I was the one who
decided to do my best for Mirage Saga!
So I gotta see this through!
All right! Let's do this!
That's right.
Serinuma-san is always so bright
and positive, and never gives up.
You haven't changed at all.
Where did you go?
Nana. I like Serinuma-san.
Huh? I know that.
No. That's not what I mean.
Right now, I've fallen in
love with her all over again.
Now?
Now.
Shock
Now?!
I finally understand!
Looks are a trivial thing!
It's not trivial with a difference this big!
Get it together, stupid!
You're saying you're okay with this?!
Isn't she wonderful, even now?
Don't start spewing the same
stuff as Nishina, idiot!
You really intend to start working out again?
Yes! Thanks for sticking with me again!
You know I always want to
support you, Serinuma-san.
But if you'll hurt yourself
again, I'm against it.
It'll be okay! I'll be careful, so don't worry!
But, you've still set the deadline
to be the award ceremony, right?
It looks like it's our turn!
Yup!
Have you come up with another lame idea?
It is not lame!
Anyway, why are you two holding hands?
Hmph. To think you don't
even understand that.
Look!
Serinuma can't take her eyes off us!
We know Serinuma reflexively
latches onto anything BL.
So we came up with a plan.
Press against wall
Kiss hand
Lie on top of
Kiss on forehead
Lick ear
A pic of us in any
pose you'd like!
A point card reward system!
Hold hands
Hug
Start
If she meets her quota, we will do
something together in front of her!
How many points is a hug?!
She's taking the bait!
Um, that's a weight loss of 3 kilos.
Ill lose it in 5 minutes!
Serinuma-san. If you push yourself,
you'll hurt yourself again.
Oh, I wasn't thinking.
It's fine to take your time.
Stay at an even pace.
You're quite kind to her.
You think so?
Isn't it natural to be kind
to the person you like?
To be honest, I was at a loss
when I saw her like she is now,
because I thought it was her
looks I was attracted to.
But, before I realized it,
I found myself attracted to
her cheerfulness and honesty.
Now, I can say it for certain:
I like Serinuma-san.
That's why I want to be kind to her,
and do whatever I can for her.
I see.
I have to say, that spirit of
yours might be a bit beautiful.
I reached my goal!
Thanks, everyone!
Amazing! Congratulations!
Oh, good.
Haggard
You sure worked hard.
Nothing less from Serinuma-san.
No, no. It was so hard, and there were times
I got depressed and wanted to give up,
but you were all there to motivate me!
I couldn't have done it without you!
Thanks, everyone!
Nana
Shi
W-We really did our best, too.
Shudder
Sob
I'm glad our hard work paid off.
Ugh, no...
Ear licking?
I get to lick it?
Eep!
I agree, Senpai.
Now all that's left is this,
Igarashi-senpai.
Achievement Bonus: Igarashi will kiss Nana.
What's this?!
I added it to give her further incentive.
Why, you...
Show us that beautiful spirit of yours. Heart.
Excited      Excited
Huh?! W-Wait!
Wha? Ser—Save me!
Shi
Mu
And so, the Mirage Saga Valentine's
Project Award Ceremony
ended without a hitch.
What's the matter,
Shinomiya-kun? You seem down.
There was a fight in my class today,
and I somehow ended up
having to deal with it.
That sounds rough. But why?
I told them fighting is for
people too much free time,
and they didn't take it well.
Oh, I see.
Shinomiya-kun, you don't get into fights?
Let's see... I can't say I much
like getting into arms with others.
I'd rather deal with the iguana.
I see. Iguanas are nice.
Next time:
Let The Shipping Wars Begin!
Look forward to it!
Mutsumi-san, do you never get into fights?