The second group of instructors is here.
The summer training camp is going well.
I'm so happy!
Attack
Attack.
Everyone, why don't we wait until
this afternoon to enter the dungeon?
Miss Minori, why do you think we're here?
Getting as much experience as
possible and raising our levels
in the dungeon is our most important task.
But for the past two days, we didn't
even last three hours before escaping.
That's true, but...
So couldn't we get just as far
if we go in the afternoon?
We can't keep doing the same thing forever.
And that's the problem!
Minori-chan...
So what do we do this morning?
Let's just relax a bit.
Miss Minori,
are you joking?
Come on, Rudy, calm down.
Minori isn't the type to joke around.
"Relax a bit" might be going too far,
but I think we should introduce ourselves.
We already did that.
We all know each other now.
No, we don't.
What?
We don't. It's true.
I don't know anything about any of you.
What you like, what you don't like...
I don't know if you want to
stand at the front or stay back.
And since I don't know, I can't
help you, even if I want to.
Please tell me.
I'm weak, so unless I hear everything
and remember it, I can't help you.
Everything?
I mean everything.
Like, for example...
What's that fire magic you use, Rundel Haus?
That's Orb of Lava,
a ball of molten magma.
But that doesn't tell me anything!
For example, why do you use it?
You have a lot of attack spells.
Why that one?
Why?
Because it's effective.
Why is it effective?
It's one of the most powerful spells I have.
And it has a fast casting time.
It only takes two seconds.
And its cool down is eighteen seconds.
It doesn't take long before you can use it again.
That means I can cast it
once every twenty seconds,
so I can use it many times in a single battle.
Hang on a second.
My class is samurai, and our taunts...
Taunts?
Taunts provoke the enemy.
Thunder Slash is one of the samurai
skills with the longest range,
but it won't reach more than about three meters.
Another attack,
Samurai's Challenge, is close-range
and has an even shorter range.
And? What are you getting at?
Those techniques are taunts,
so they don't actually damage the enemy,
but the enemy will think they've
taken a ton of damage.
I see.
So you use them to draw enemy attention.
Yes.
The samurai has a high defense, so my job is
to keep the enemy focused on
me rather than all of you.
Samurai's Challenge takes two seconds to land.
Just like Orb of Lava.
But its range is no farther than
the reach of my katana.
I get it.
If we both attack the second we're in range...
Yes.
Orb of Lava will hit first.
My attempt to taunt them will be wasted.
That's why all the enemies go after you.
Then, should I not use Orb of Lava?
Just wait two seconds.
In a glorious, elegant battle,
a loss of two seconds can prove fatal.
So then...
Is that where Coward's Fugue can be useful?
What's that?
Sounds cowardly, judging by the name.
Is that a skill of yours, Miss Isuzu?
Coward's Fugue is a skill I just learned.
It's a continuous support song.
Continuous?
Basically, I can leave it running.
It seems to make the damage
dealt by any non-warrior class
appear to be lower as long as it's in effect.
You have a skill like that?
Really?
I d-do... Really.
But it isn't that amazing.
I mean, doesn't it sound kind of useless?
It doesn't deal damage or heal...
No.
Depending how you use it...
I'm glad to have heard that.
It seems I need to apologize, Miss Minori.
I admit my ignorance and
lack of understanding.
No, I had no idea, either.
So tell me all the spells you know, Rundel Haus.
What do you like and dislike about them?
When do use you them?
When would you like to use them?
All of them? That'd take some time, Miss Minori.
We have plenty of time.
Yeah.
Right.
Let's hear them!
Okay, we'll start with the spells I know.
The patrol's approaching.
Five, I think...
They'll be here in about ten measures.
Um, ten measures is... about twenty seconds?
Let's go with what we agreed on.
It'll be fine. I can do this.
Yesterday, we spent all day talking,
instead of going into the dungeon.
Now I know all their skills...
And how they best work together.
Even I spent a lot of my valuable time
listening to what they had to say.
This has to work!
All that's left is to combine those techniques.
Formation, operator, field monitor, patrol file...
Memorize the basics of party
combat I just explained.
I have it in my head...
But what, exactly, am I supposed to do with it?
Well, basically...
They're here!
Lightning Slash!
The first thing you should
consider is our formation.
The basic idea is that our front
line fighter, our samurai,
will draw the enemy's attacks.
But for that to work, we'll need everyone's help.
Take care of them!
Get back.
I have more appropriate spells than
Orb of Lava for dealing with you alone.
Taste the sorcerer's elegant magics...
Lightning Chamber!
Okay!
Why, you...
Tohya
Race/ Human
Samurai, Lv. 30
Log Horizon
His HP is at 64%.
Healing!
The next role to keep in mind is the operator.
It's their job to monitor everyone's status,
but it's a waste for both Serara
and me to heal at the same time,
Tohya
Race/ Human
Samurai, Lv. 30
Log Horizon
so most of the time, I'll leave it to Serara.
Thank you, Serara!
It's starting to hurt, but...
The job of a front-line tank is
to absorb all the enemy hits,
and to trust his companions.
Tohya,
as a man, you must promise to do that!
I know that, Master Naotsugu.
Now, come and get me!
Samurai's Challenge!
Minori, keep an eye out.
Isuzu and Rudy, get ready to attack!
Right!
Yeah.
I'll be the field monitor.
My job is to monitor the area
and tell you if reinforcements
or enemy patrols are coming.
That lets the attackers concentrate on fighting.
Checking the corridor!
No enemy patrols in sight!
All clear.
Get them!
Are they all good and mad now?
Yeah... I had time
to use Samurai's Challenge twice on each.
They won't get to you easily now, Rudy!
That's a load off my mind, then.
Resonance Beat!
Orb of Lava!
Return to the darkness from whence you came!
Wow.
Frigid Wind!
Patrol file! Secure the immediate area!
Patrol file is a way to maintain your
formation and field monitoring.
The first and last members in
line cover each other's view,
so attackers and healers can focus on
their own jobs as the party moves.
Did we win?
No one else is coming.
This battle is over!
Yahoo!
We did it!
This is how it should be.
Just let yourself be happy, Rudy.
I understand, Shiroe.
We just need to talk to one another
and work things out.
It's so simple, but it's more
important than anything,
in order to make members of
a party become true friends.
Thanks so much!
It's so hard to write on this world's paper.
Take as much as you need.
Part of a scribe's job is making paper and ink.
I still need to work on the ink, though.
Oh, the stuff you gave me last
time was more than sufficient.
Just being able to write with it isn't enough.
When this was a game,
didn't you do any quests where maps
or documents were important?
Come to think of it...
A single document can be a magic item.
And of course, making high-level
documents requires
high-level paper and ink as ingredients.
So that's why...
You're copying this map to raise your level, then?
Actually, I need it for something.
Maps written on papyrus and bark
simply don't last long enough.
You seem tired.
I guess making this really is a lot of work...
No, that isn't why...
I mean, maybe I'm tired from that dance.
Ah, then shall we practice, so that
it'll be easier for you next time?
No, I'd rather not.
Any time you want to, just let me know.
Thank you for these.
I look tired, huh?
Maybe she's right.
I'm thinking too much about the wrong things.
Every time we die in this world,
we lose our memories.
Is it possible that we'll forget the real world?
There's so much we don't know about this world.
We don't even know what
we should do from here on...
Good evening, Shiroe!
Hey, there.
I guess things are going well with the dungeon.
You can tell?
I can... By the tone of your voice.
Yeah.
I'll give you the report.
This morning, we entered the dungeon at 7:30.
After around seven hours of exploration,
we left at 15:00.
We went as far as the end of the right fork,
and defeated the Burning Dead at the blast furnace.
That's amazing!
The Burning Dead encounter is about the
same as your party's average level.
It's one thing to do that in the game,
but right now, even for a
veteran party, it's a tough feat.
Yeah!
What about everyone else?
They're all in the tent.
That isn't what I mean.
How did everyone else do?
Um...
Tohya went to the front and drew
all the enemy attention.
That matches what you wrote down...
But this time, we decided to plot out
the fight locations from the start,
move to safe rooms, and split the
enemy into smaller groups.
Pulling.
Yes.
We focused on monsters
with ranged attacks first,
and I acted as off-healer,
while watching the surrounding area.
We concentrated our attacks on one enemy
at a time to wear down their ranks.
Um, am I making sense?
It's fine. I understand.
I can see them in my head...
Following the fundamentals I taught them,
and using teamwork down to the fine details.
It seems like an obvious thing,
but who knows how many little things
they had to figure out to reach that point?
Shiroe? Can you hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you perfectly.
Did everyone else do their jobs?
Of course!
Serara's healing spells are amazing.
She has a huge variety of them.
But I guess Isuzu has the widest skill repertoire.
Almost too many for me to remember...
Shiroe? Are you laughing?
I'm sorry, I'm not.
Honest.
Everyone's started calling Rundel Haus "Rudy."
He's an amazing sorcerer and really handsome,
but he's kind of stupid, and a bit lame.
Handsome, stupid, and lame?
But he's fun to be around!
He's a sorcerer, and...
Wait, I already said that.
Anyway, his magic is really powerful.
It's true that there's a lot we
don't know about this world.
But that's why I must go forward.
And be cheerful like she is.
And do what I can, one thing at a time.
It's really quite a bother.
A bother?
An invitation from a gentleman requires
a certain degree of attention
to etiquette and appearance.
Even on a peaceful afternoon like this.
I'd thought you'd want this.
I assumed you'd prefer this to an invitation
from someone more stiff and formal.
Was I wrong?
I see I was right.
May I invite you again tomorrow?
As you like.
Do as you like.
I feel so much better...
One step in a dungeon, and your
appearance is all ruined.
Yeah, they're so full of soot.
But today went really well, too, huh?
Yeah, I was worried when two
Burning Dead appeared...
You and Rudy worked really well together.
Should that make me happy?
What kind of vague answer is that?
Didn't you say Rudy seems kind of like a prince?
But don't you think so?
Just his looks, that is.
If you ran into him somewhere, he might
look cute enough to make you nervous...
But...
You don't get nervous?
Nope, not at all.
I wonder why.
Stop that. It wasn't that great.
No, it was wonderful.
It was like the sound suffused the air.
Thank you.
I wonder if everyone's getting ready to sleep.
We're getting up early tomorrow...
Tomorrow morning's our last dungeon run.
That's right...
The last one already.
It's been fun, huh?
Yeah.
The food was a little lacking, though...
You think so?
I thought it was good... BBQ and stuff.
What do you normally eat?
Hot sandwiches... Or hot sandwiches...
Sometimes hot sandwiches.
That's nothing but hot sandwiches!
Do you mean hot pollock roe
sandwiches from Ray Parker?
How did you know?!
You like those, too, Miss Isuzu?
I love them!
The way they pop in your mouth...
I know! Just remembering it...
I g-get it!
He's like a dog.
He's like a golden retriever!
What's wrong, Miss Isuzu?
N-Nothing...
I see.
That's why he doesn't make me nervous.
Even if he's handsome, he's a dog.
Are you crying?
Are you sad you won't see me as much anymore?
Well, m-maybe...
Maybe that's why.
If you were in a guild, I could
see you any time I wanted.
A guild, huh?
I'm sorry, but it would be a crime
to tie my talents to one place.
How can he wink so naturally like that?
Rudy's amazing.
But he's a dog.
Even if I'm not in a guild,
many places would want a sorcerer of my talent.
Even after the camp ends, you'll surely
hear rumors of me in Akihabara...
And when you do, feel free to contact
me whenever you like.
That's true.
Then I'll add you to my Friend List.
Let's go for hot pollock roe sandwiches sometime.
Adding you now...
Huh?
Why?
Sahuagin?
The fish monsters?
Marie said they appeared on the coast.
Sahuagin should be, at most, level 20 to 30.
Even the new kids should be okay with them.
What the hell?
I've never seen so many...
Get out of here!
Run to the forest!
Marie!
Shouryuu...
Get back.
We have to call back the groups
camping in the forest!
Yes, but...
I'm the Crescent Moon Alliance's combat leader!
Do what I tell you!
All right.
Why?
Why did this huge army appear from nowhere?
A sudden assault by demi-humans.
Huge armies of goblins and sahuagin.
Even so, the People of the Land's nobles
and the Round Table cannot put aside
their differences to work together.
And Tohya, Minori, and the other
young players take action.
Next time: Return of the Goblin King.
Return of the Goblin King
Always look thirty seconds ahead.