Eek! It's so cold!
Well, it is the end of December.
If we go like THIS, it doesn't feel so cold, right?
Yes! It's quite warm!
Shbaa!
Yet this, indeed, is what makes a Japanese winter!
Note: They're standing back-to-back like this as a sort of children's game
where a song is sang.
In snuggling, we become as warm
as steamed buns! Behold! Indeed!
Note: They're standing back-to-back like this as a sort of children's game
where a song is sang.
Oshikura-manju, osarete naku na
You cramped steamed buns, don't cry when you're pushed!
Sylphin! What do you think you're doing?!
Oshikura-manju, osarete naku na
You cramped steamed buns, don't cry when you're pushed!
Ebina, even you?!
Oshikura-manju, osarete naku na
You cramped steamed buns, don't cry when you're pushed!
Now then, give it all you've got, Kirie!
Oshikura-manju, osarete naku na
You cramped steamed buns, don't cry when you're pushed!
Jeez! Cut that out!
Oshikura-manju, osarete naku na
You cramped steamed buns, don't cry when you're pushed!
Usually, I feel a little sad
at the end of the year, but, strangely...
Oshikura-manju, osarete naku na
You cramped steamed buns, don't cry when you're pushed!
Right now, I don't feel sad at all!
Oshikura-manju, osarete naku na
You cramped steamed buns, don't cry when you're pushed!
Umaru, what do you want for dinner tonight?
I can have anything at all? Well then, I want pizza!
I didn't say "anything," but still... Pizza, huh?
Step 1 will be a brick oven.
What makes you think we have to start
by making a brick oven?
We can just have it delivered.
Why do you always take the easy way out?
Making things by hand gives it a taste all its own.
Huh? But delivery pizza was handmade
by the people at the store, right?
If I can get some delicious stuff
without having to make it myself, that's fine by me!
I mean, look, Big Brother! Look at all this pizza!
I see. So that's your thought process, huh?
IN THAT CASE!
B-Big Brother?
Listen up, Umaru: Tonight, your way of thinking
will be turned on its head!
What's got him so much more fired up than usual...?
Stir, stir, stir, stir!
Whisk, whisk, whisk, whisk!
Sure enough, he's fired up.
'Sup, Tanukichi?
I took Taihei up on his offer to come by, Sensei.
He invited you...?
This will be my first time to eat something made at home.
Taihei's cooking is totally delish!
S-so, could this be...?
Yes!
Note: A dish of fried batter with cabbage and various meats.
It's okonomiyaki!
Wait, that's not pizza at all!
Okonomiyaki is a Japanese-style pizza, right?
No, it's not! It's totally different!
Jeez, I was REALLY in the mood for pizza tonight!
Pizza! Pizza! Pizza! Pizza!
Hey, what should we use for our first ingredient?
Pork? Beef? Or how about chicken?
Pizza! Pizza! Pizza! Pizza!
Hey, what should we use for our first ingredient?
Pork? Beef? Or how about chicken?
Pizza! PIZZA! Pizza? Pizza! Pizza! Pizza! Pizza!
Pizza! Pizza! Pizza! Pizza! Pizza! Pizza! PIZZA! Pizza!
Well, I say we go with shrimp or squid, or a seafood mix.
Pizza! Pizza! Pizza! Pizza! Pizza! Pizza!
Pizza! Pizza! Pizza! Pizza! Pizza!
Huh?
Taihei, let's hear what you think.
We've gotta start off with meat, right?
No, it must be seafood, right?
Wouldn't it be best to start off with something light?
Note: A pungent dish of fermented soybeans.
I know! How about natto? It'll go great with scallions.
Huh? Natto?! A man's gotta start with meat, dude. MEAT!
I don't care for natto myself...
Then let's go with meat!
No, seafood!
Do you have a preference?
Ooh! Speak up, Tanukichi!
Please!
Huh?
Um, uh...
Well, for okonomiyaki...
a MIX is the only way to go!
Shrimp, squid, and octopus!
Oh, so much seafood!
And on top of that...
Pork belly and beef tendon and cheese!
You wanna put MORE in?!
Finally, we meet the meat! Hold on:
this goes way beyond your regular mix!
Well, I guess it's time to flip it.
Umaru, you want to do it?
Huh?
Sure!
It's a revenge match from that time we did pancakes!
You have to get it in the air and flip it over.
Tanukichi, you gonna be okay?
Do your best, Sensei!
You did it, Tanukichi.
I expected no less, Sensei.
And so, the Umaru Special...
is done!
Well, let's eat.
It sure looks tasty.
You KNOW this'll be delicious!
I'm sure.
Here you go, Umaru.
'Kay!
ULP!
DeLishUsS!
Sh-she's melting right in front of us!
Sensei, have some cola!
AAAAH!
She exploded!
Well, I'll be making a lot more,
so Bomba and Alex, have as much as you like.
DeLishUsS!
Right? It's good to make things yourself, right?
Yup!
Hey, Big Brother...
C'mon, get this as a Christmas present for me.
20,000 yen?! Why is this game so expensive?
It's a limited edition, with the same design
as the game it comes bundled with.
You want this even though you already have the game?
Well, it is Christmas and all...
It totally looks like he'll buy it for me!
Huh?! You're going to work on a Sunday?
What about my Christmas present?!
The end of the year is always busy.
I'll buy something on the way back.
Till then, clean things up around here.
Ebina will be coming over, right?
Umaru, I'm really looking forward to tonight.
Yup! We'll play games...
Um, no, I mean we'll all eat cake together.
Cake! But...
I'm sorry, Umaru! My family actually said
we should all get together this year!
And my mother made a reservation at a restaurant.
It would have been even more fun
if Kirie and Sylphin could have made it, huh?
Yeah...
Still, my brother will be happy that you've come.
Huh?! H-he'll be happy?
Yup! He said that making food
for a Christmas party makes it extra special.
Huh? I-I guess so, yes.
I-I'm happy too.
I haven't given Taihei a present since his birthday.
There's so much I can't thank him enough for...
You got my brother a present?!
Yes! And there's one for you as well.
O-oh, thank you!
What will YOU be giving your brother?
I thought maybe you and I
could buy him a present together.
Oh, well, if you don't mind.
I tried thinking of what to give him, but it was so hard...
What did you get for him?
U-um, well...
Ah! I'm sure he'll like that!
Hmm, but what should I get him?
It didn't occur to me to get HIM a present.
What would he even like?
Yeah, that looks great.
That will be my present to you, Ebina.
No, I couldn't!
It's my pleasure.
I've always thought a cap would really suit you.
I-I'm not so sure...
Thank you very much!
Thank you, Umaru. So, I guess it's my turn.
This is your present!
You brought it with you? Thank you!
Can I open it?
O-okay. But, actually I...
Ah! This...
I've always thought a cap would really suit you.
So it's a cap exchange party?
Looks like it...
What should I do? This is so much fun.
I never thought giving and receiving presents
could be this much fun.
I wonder what sort of present
would make Big Brother happy.
Merry Christmas, Big Brother!
Ch-Ch-Ch-Christmas!
Whoa! Wh-what the-?!
I thought you'd be waiting at the house.
The both of us ambushed you!
H-h-h-ello!
Nice to see you, Ebina.
I bought you a present, Big Brother!
Huh?
Here! It's a brand-new frying pan!
A-and an apron.
Thank you. That makes me happy.
Well, let's all go buy things for tonight's dinner.
But before that, what kind of present
do you think you'd like, Ebina?
Huh?! A-a present from YOU?!
Just don't forget about mine, Big Brother!
My younger sister Hikari is a little strange.
Hikariiin.
First off, she's a slob.
She loves bread, and is always snacking...
And for some reason, she likes spinning around.
Stop that, Hikari!
When did she start to get like that?
I feel like she's been hiding something from me recently.
Is this a rebellious phase? She's that old already?
I guess it's our home environment.
Maybe it's all my fault...
I'm home.
Big Sister!
When will that Big Brother from before be coming back?
Huh?
I want to see Big Brother again.
L-look, it was a coincidence
he came here in the first place.
But you both go to the same school, don't you?
Oh, no. She's being really pushy today!
He's at the top of his class?
I'm taking AP classes while he's in the regular curriculum.
It was the award ceremony
that led us to becoming friends.
And he gave me so many compliments,
saying how well I'd done!
Would Big Brother praise me if I got an award too?
I think Taihei got the same sense of destiny!
Of two geniuses colliding!
Wh-what?!
You were picked as the top student, and got an award?
Yup.
Hikari, you...
You're my little sister all right! You're a genius!
I want to be praised.
I'll do it! I will! You've done so well, Hikari!
I want... Big Brother to praise me.
Huh? B-Big Brother?
Yes. With this award, he will praise me.
WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
I want... Big Brother to praise me.
Just wait, Hikari. I'm going to get you
the greatest Christmas present of all!
Calm yourself, Kanau. This is no big deal.
You're just inviting him over for Christmas for a little bit.
Inviting him... to my house?
Say, you got any plans tonight?
It's Christmas Eve but you're free, right?
I'm having dinner with my family.
You two go home and spend time with your families.
I can't!
There's no way. No way!
If I couldn't even ask him to go out to do something,
there's no way I could ask him to my HOUSE!
I never learned how to invite people over
in my AP classes!
I'm home...
Welcome back, Big Sister.
Hikari, it will be Christmas in two days, so...
How about you and I have some cake
and watch a movie?
Are you going to rent one again?
Eh?
Last time, you went out to rent a movie
when I was asleep and spent Christmas on your own.
N-N-NOOOOO! SHE SAW MEEEEE!
Happy...
...New Year!
Heartfelt wishes for a good year.
Indeed!
Thanks for inviting us over today.
Your house is amazing, Sylphin.
It's the picture of the New Year!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Hyaa! Hyaa! Hyaa! Hyaa! Hyaa! Hyaa! Hyaa!
I like the mood within Japan during the New Year indeed!
"Mood"?
How can I put this?
The stores are closed, and you can
lounge about as much as you like!
I get that!
Shubatan!
Shuba!
Sylph, one mustn't lie on one's back
while wearing a kimono.
Shbaaa!
Yes, Mother!
I'm sure you're all tired from ringing in the New Year.
No, we're fine. More importantly,
thank you so much for the kimonos.
Thank you very much.
No, not at all. Now then...
Go on, please help yourselves.
Thems were some good vittles...
This is no time to be lying about, everyone!
Sylphin...?
I've put together various New Years' items
so we can all enjoy this day!
Note: Well-known board and card games, respectively.
Wow! Sugoroku, and Karuta! And kites!
You've got so many things.
Are these well-known?
You got all these not knowing what they are?
This paddle or what have you is pretty indeed!
Note: A traditional paddle game.
Hanetsuki! I've never seen it before.
This is my first time too!
You don't see it too often, do you?
We had it back in my house.
How do you play it? I want to try it, indeed!
Oh, I see. So, basically, it's tennis.
I understand completely!
I'm telling you, it's different. It may look like tennis,
but the rules are different.
You must not allow the shuttlecock to drop.
Ah, I see.
Those two sure do get along, don't they?
Yup.
I have learned the rules!
Indeed, now we should form our teams!
This is my first time to be on a team with you, Umaru!
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Let's hurry up and put an end to this.
K-Kirie?
Okay, here goes. One, two...!
H-hyaa?
We need only not drop the shuttlecock, yes?
Then, here goes!
Canzone Sylphin Smash!
What's this? There was no rebound.
A paddle is completely different from a tennis racket.
So then, how about we introduce a game of Penalty?
A game of Penalty?!
Kirie, what will you draw?
I-I can't draw! I can't bring shame
to Umaru's beautiful face!
Let's stop this! No more Penalty!
But, I want to play this "Penalty Game," indeed!
A-all right. Let's do it as a one-on-challenge.
It's like an extra inning, yes?
Ebina, have a seat with me.
O-okay.
Hyaa!
Sylphin said this already, but...
New Years' sure is great, huh?
Yes!
Umaru, here's your New Years' allowance.
For you, Tanukichi.
Here, Sensei.
Here, Master!
No, no, that's fine!
All combined, that's 35,000 yen.
Up till now, I would've just gone and spent all this, but...
this year, you'll find that I'm a SMIDGE different.
And so...
I gave my greed the smackdown
and decided to save it, Big Brother!
Oh.
I exchanged it all for 500-yen coins,
so it's made me feel kinda sorta rich!
You didn't have to change all that for coins, did you?
Still, it's pretty grownup of you to save it all.
I know, right?!
See? This way, it's hard
to spend too much at once, right?
I get it. Yeah, that does make it a pain to get money.
Wh-what's with you?
I was just thinking, maybe you'd like to add to the piggy...
But those are YOUR savings, right?
I-it can't be!
Wh-where could my money have gone?
I can't think of a single reason!
There are way too many reasons!
This is the end!
She's really suffering...
But this time, I'm not going to help her out.
It's for her own good.
What should I do? I promised everyone
we'd all do something together.
Big Brother!
But just this once.
Still, in this day and age,
what can I do with only 500 yen?
Times have changed since you were young, you know.
Also, YOU may not have any hobbies,
but don't go thinking everyone is the same
and they don't spend money!
So, how about a bit more for the piggy?
Wh-wh-why you...
HIMOUTO!
I'm sorry, Big Brother!