Your Majesty.
If I may, you don't have to go yourself.
This is a crisis that may affect the
country's—no, the entire world's survival.
I've not become so feeble in my old age
that I must simply wait here for news.
As you wish.
I apologize for the trouble.
Oh, no.
We wouldn't have it any other way, my lady.
We shall now put down
the traitorous Three Heroes Church's Pope,
Bisca T. Balmus, and his followers!
Yes, my lady!
We leave immediately! Move the cavalry out!
Please, just survive a little longer, Shield Hero... and Melty.
The Rising of the Shield Hero
Battle of Good and Evil
High-Level Multi-Caster Defense Magic:
Cathedral!
Thunderbolt Slash!
Thunder Shot!
Filo! Raphtalia!
Right!
'Kay!
High Quick!
Heal my target!
Zweit Heal!
One more time, Filo.
'Kay!
You're coming too, Motoyasu!
Motoyasu-sama!
Zweit Aqua Shell!
Sister, focus!
Motoyasu, attack me when
we get near the Pope.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Let's go!
Now!
Fine!
Eat this!
He dispelled that curse in an instant?
Curses are meaningless
within this Cathedral.
After all, this is hallowed ground, blessed by God.
What strength!
Do you hear me, Bishop?
In order to show the might of God, I need
further prayers from the believers.
But sir, almost a third of them
have already run out of mana.
If they keep going,
their lives may be in danger.
Is that a problem?
This is a battle between God and the Devil.
Perishing as martyrs here
is the greatest honor for one of the
Three Heroes Church's disciples.
As you say.
Everyone, provide the Pope with more prayers!
How could he say something so awful to
the people who trusted and followed him?
They'll probably still
follow his orders, though.
Indeed.
We are one in body and soul.
With their prayers and the sacred
weapon's greatest attack,
I shall grant you all complete purification.
It is the greatest mercy
that God may bestow.
This feels wrong.
He's building up mana.
If the light reaches all
the way up to the top...
...a huge attack will follow, right?
Hey, can't your shield
do something about it?
Huh?
I mean, your shield seems overpowered.
Look here...
True.
You're underleveled compared to us,
and yet you're keeping up with us.
Isn't that because of your shield?
You idiots just aren't making
good use of your weapons!
Got any special skills?
As if there'd be...
What is this?
The Shield of the Curse Series
is like a double-edged sword.
Don't use it anymore.
Naofumi?
This will be quite the gamble,
but it could work.
See?
Will you use that power again?
Yeah.
It went fine before, so I'm sure
I can come back this time, too.
Okay. I believe in you.
Me too.
You made the right choice in
releasing me from my shackles.
Let the anger take you over,
and you won't suffer.
I... refuse!
I won't let your anger overtake me!
It isn't simply my anger, the anger of a dragon.
It wells up from within your heart.
What?
Your anger at being set up.
Your anger at the shame and
humiliation you were put through.
Your anger at being continually persecuted,
not even being given a chance to defend yourself.
It is all your own.
Mine?
Release every last drop of your
pent-up anger and hatred.
Every last drop...
Hit your foes with all the
anger you have felt until now.
I'll give you the power to do that.
Power!
No! I can't fall for his words!
This power...
It tasted sweet, did it not?
With the power of the cursed flame,
you could make your foes submit
and walk all over them.
It was pleasant, was it not?
You felt fulfilled, did you not?
That's...
Show your rage! Seek more power!
And burn everything in your path!
Burn...
I'll burn everything!
Very nice, human!
Your rage puts even mine to shame.
Hey, Naofumi!
Please don't tell me you really
became the Devil of the Shield.
Naofumi-sama!
I'll burn everything.
If I burn it all down, it'll be over.
Naofumi-sama!
I can let my anger take over
and destroy everything.
Master!
I have the power to do that now.
I'll use it to...
Naofumi!
You're so annoying! Don't try to stop me!
Master, do you really hate everything?
What is this voice?
Did your travels with us
truly mean nothing at all?
Travels?
I was terrified at first.
I was sure you would treat
me like an object, like everyone else.
But you were nice to me.
You cared for me.
You scolded me when I went wrong,
and protected me.
That is why I vowed to stand with you.
You raised me since the moment I was born.
You gave me the wagon, and all
the fun and neat things in my life.
You gave me everything I love.
You were stubborn, never listened
to me, and kept making fun of me.
But when you promised to keep
me safe and did just that,
and saw me for the person I am
and not just as a princess,
it made me so happy.
That's right. I was on a journey...
With friends I held dear
and swore to protect.
You're never open about your feelings, so we can
never tell what you're thinking.
But we do know that you
care very deeply for us.
I love you, Master.
So I'm gonna eat up all
your bad feelings.
I'll do all I can to share in your pain.
I'll cut through all your sorrow.
After all, I am your sword.
Naofumi-sama!
You guys...
Thank goodness. You came back to us again.
Master!
Stop causing us so much trouble.
I'm sorry! I hurt you all again!
They weren't wrong.
The path you chose
and the road we traveled down
were definitely the right ones!
Raphtalia...
I'll eat up your negative
feelings again and again!
Filo...
If you understand, hurry up
and come up with a plan.
We're in the middle of a battle.
Got it, Melty.
You okay?
It wasn't the same berserk mode
as in the last Wave, was it?
Help me out.
Help you?
Please.
I never expected to hear
those words from you.
Can we win?
I don't know, but it's worth a shot.
I was saying we should
fight together all along.
Motoyasu?
I-I...
Fine! I'll do it!
We need to prove that friendship
and strong bonds will always prevail.
It seems you were up to something,
but everything is ready now.
This is goodbye, Devil of the Shield!
Even if you're the Devil of the Shield,
I'm amazed you could stop the
Cathedral's full-power attack.
Immense power always comes at a price.
And if your divine power comes
at the cost of your disciples,
your life alone won't be
enough to pay for it!
That shield...
Let's go!
Right!
Yeah!
Thunder Shot!
There's more!
Wind Arrow!
Zweit Aqua Shot!
Zweit Air Shot!
Don't let the enemy recover!
High Quick!
You won't get me with the same trick again.
We're only decoys!
Meteor Sword!
Ren, Raphtalia, get in close
and block his field of vision.
Meanwhile...
Zweit Power!
I can't believe I'm taking
orders from Naofumi.
Damn it!
I'm taking this out on you!
Air Strike Javelin!
"Friendship and strong bonds
always prevail," huh?
Shut up!
Just go take him out!
May this sacred flame cleanse everything!
Phoenix Blade!
As source of thy power,
the Shield Hero and I order thee!
Decipher the laws of creation,
consume the flame, and give me power!
Wrath Fire!
He did it!
Let's finish this!
Yeah!
Wait!
Something's off.
Chaos Spear!
State of Emptiness.
What?
Motoyasu-san!
Th-That's one of my spear's
advanced skills, a counter!
That weapon can even mimic
the advanced skills?
The sin of defying God demands
more than cleansing!
What'd he do?
Stay away!
No...
Stop! Stop it!
Damn! What the hell's going on?
Is this...
An illusion, yes!
He used some kind of skill
to cast an illusion!
You've lost your chance to accept God's mercy.
Now, only despair awaits you.
Be crushed under the weight of your mind!
Everyone, watch...
Naofumi-sama!
Raphtalia!
You will be annihilated,
leaving not a speck of ash behind.
There won't remain any proof
that you ever existed!
As source of thy power,
the queen orders thee.
Decipher the laws of creation,
surround my target in a cage
of ice, and capture him.
All Dritte Fall: Icicle Prison!
It can't be!
Her magic pierced the walls of the Cathedral?
Hurry up and get him!
Foolish sinner, I sentence you to cast
your screams unto the heavens!
Within the dragon's jaws born from my flesh,
become an offering to the
gods as you howl in pain!
Blood Sacrifice!
Why...?
A fitting end for a devil.
In the end, he was consumed
by his own power.
Be thankful, filthy Devil,
that God still sees fit to purify you.
Why? Why is this happening to me?!
I am God's apostle!
The Pope!
This can't be!
Did we... win?
No... The Cathedral and the pope...
This battle is over.
Accept your defeat and surrender.
It's the queen's forces.
Yeah.
Naofumi-sama!
Hang in there!
Master!
He's lost so much blood,
and then there was that skill...
I think Naofumi gave up his own life to...
No... Naofumi-sama!
Naofumi-sama!
Answer me, Master!
Hang in there, Naofumi!
I won't let the Shield Hero die.
Mother!
I'm terribly sorry I couldn't help in time,
Shield Hero Naofumi Iwatani-sama.
You are...
I am the Queen of Melromarc,
Mirelia Q. Melromarc.
Naofumi's Triumphant Return