Composing Message
Eat up.
That's a ton of chocolate.
Misaki-senpai stayed up late
last night, working hard.
Today's Valentine's Day.
And...
Good morning.
G-Good morning. You're up early.
Yeah. I can't relax, so I
figured I'd get going already.
I see.
See you later.
Aoyama!
See you later!
The day of Aoyama's audition.
Hello.
The artist we asked to
do the cover is ill!
Nanohana Hall's popularity
is up recently, so...
Yeah, so would you be able...
to work up a cover right away?
In color.
Color?
Yes, color.
Would yellow be all right?
Yellow?
A single color spread is
certainly avant-garde, but no.
It's a cover! It's a challenge!
A challenge... Right.
Why did I only tell her
I'd see her later?
I should've sent her off with
something more helpful.
Shiina, it's time to get—
Shiina, you...
You got ready by yourself...
I-Is that the fashion now?
It's a sock, but I only found one.
They don't automatically
exist in pairs, you know!
And please don't tell me you've gone
commando under that skirt...
Are you wearing panties?
A very colorful pair.
You don't need to give me the details.
Then, let me see what's in your bag...
Looking in a girl's bag is
a horrible thing to do.
What's gotten into you?
What are you going to
do if you forget—
I have everything important.
What do you mean by "important"?
I even packed my fighting spirit.
I don't know what you're
talking about, but whatever.
I won't look.
You can look tomorrow.
Huh? What's different about tomorrow?
Continuing to pry into her affairs
would be very uncouth, Sorata.
Rita?!
What are you doing here?
If you'd contacted us,
we'd have come to get you.
You didn't tell us you were coming.
I know.
I've been busy with my work,
but I forced some time off to come here.
Today's Valentine's Day.
For girls, this day is a challenge!
Challenge?
I'd love to stay and enjoy our reunion,
Mashiro, but it'll have to wait.
I'll see you later!
You won't escape, Ryunosuke!
Wh-What's the ex-freeloader doing here?
I guess we should head to school.
Let's go.
Kanda! Kanda!
Ryunosuke!
Good morning.
#17 Valentine's Day is Chocolate Day
It's so cold.
Aoyama?
To: Dad
I'm going today.
Aoyama, you didn't go to your audition?
I can still make it if I go after class.
There's no reason to skip school.
I see.
Yeah.
Um, sorry.
Huh?
About this morning, too.
I have no idea what to say to you.
It's okay. I'm not expecting
a great pep talk from you.
Besides, you've given me courage.
To: Dad
I'm going today.
Sending Message
Courage?
Yeah.
You proved that hard work is rewarded.
Aoyama.
Kanda-kun, do you remember our promise?
Huh? What promise?
You know, after the audition...
Good morning, Sorata and Nanami.
Miyahara.
I heard the news.
You have an audition today?
Yeah.
Do your best, Nanami, star of the
General Education Department!
Miyahara, you're exaggerating.
Good luck.
Chocolate
The word chocolate comes from the...
indigenous Mexican word
"xocolatl," meaning bitter water.
Message Received
Shiina Mashiro
From: Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
I'll be waiting on the roof after school for you.
So, listen up, everyone.
Don't give chocolate to the one you love.
Shiina.
Kanda-kun?
Even if you claim that you're
conveying sweet feelings,
Uh, nothing.
it's originally bitter water.
Could it be...
I have everything important.
Whose idea was it to write "chocolate" with
kanji meaning "sugar growing old"? Gross!
Was Shiina going to give me chocolate?
Give up already!
Normally, I'd expect men to
cry tears of joy if a girl as cute...
as me was this determined to pursue them.
Ryunosuke, what don't you like about me?
Everything!
Anyway, I'll make sure you take my chocolate.
And I'm telling you I won't!
If I accept one of your demands,
who knows what you'll ask for next?
Don't paint me as some kind of terrorist.
That's exactly what you are!
On Christmas Eve...
I was really happy to get an
email from you, but was that—
It was just a New Year's card.
The Japanese are conscientious people.
It didn't mean anything.
Oh.
Okay, that's all for today.
Well, I'd better get going.
Okay, be careful...
Kanda-kun, you're on
cleaning duty, aren't you?
Here, take this.
See you later.
Hey.
Aoyama.
Come on, hop to it.
They work me like a dog at
Sakura Hall and at school.
Misaki-senpai?
Senpai.
Kouhai-kun.
What are you doing?
Is that for Jin-san?
Yeah.
Third years can come
and go as they please,
but Soichiro-kun promised to bring him in.
The Student Council President?
Yeah. That's why we're waiting here.
I see.
I saw you making all kinds of things,
but that's a pretty small chocolate.
What?! This isn't good enough?
It won't convey my love?!
No, actually, this one looks
more like you're serious.
Give it to him, Misaki-senpai.
I'm rooting for you.
Yeah, I'll do my best!
Misaki, you've got a good kouhai there.
Yeah, he's the best kouhai-kun ever.
There.
I wonder if Shiina's waiting up there.
Incoming Call
Aoyama Nanami
Aoyama?
Hello?
What am I going to do, Kanda-kun?
I'm done for! I'm screwed!
Calm down, what—
The train! It's stopped!
They're saying there was an accident!
They don't know when it'll get
going again! I'm done for—
Calm down, Aoyama.
Have you contacted the training school?
They'll understand if you explain
the situation to them, right?
I told them, and they said they
could push back my audition, but...
they said it had to be today.
If I don't get there by six,
all the other auditions will be over.
Aoyama, which station
are you at right now?
What? At the next one over...
Can you get out of the train?
Yeah, I'm calling you from the platform.
Then, wait for me outside the ticket gate.
I'll be right there!
Shiina, sorry! I'm going
to be a little late!
The number you are trying to
reach is currently unavailable.
Please leave a message after the tone.
I'm gonna be a little late.
Aoyama's in trouble.
It's cold out here, so wait in a classroom.
That was close!
Oh, it's you, Sorata.
Miyahara, let me borrow your bike.
What?
Aoyama's train isn't running!
Her audition is today and
she's stuck at the station!
Anyway, I'm in a hurry!
Nanami, huh?
I understand.
Get on!
Miyahara? You could just lend it to—
Just get on!
Hey, you two! Riding double isn't allowed!
We'll come back so you
can yell at us later,
so just let it slide for now!
Hey!
Miyahara, let's switch.
Don't underestimate me!
Understand the power of love!
"Of love"?
I'm at my limit!
You take over!
Go by yourself!
Hey, Miyahara. What did you
mean by the power of love?
Correction:
The power of a loser's love.
Nanami rejected me.
What? Hey, wait.
What do you mean she rejected... What?
Come on, just go!
Thanks.
Ride like the wind, Sorata!
The one Nanami called
when she was in trouble...
was you!
Aoyama!
Kanda-kun!
Aoyama, let's hurry and get a taxi!
We can't. Everyone else is getting taxis.
There won't be any for a while.
Okay, get on!
What? We'll never make
it in time on a bike—
You've work hard for the last
two years, haven't you?!
We said we'd work hard together...
Pursue our dreams together!
I won't let you quit here!
Kanda-kun.
Take me there, Kanda-kun!
Take me to the audition hall!
It's time for my flight.
I really didn't have the time to come...
But I wanted to at least see you today.
Please tell the other
residents of Sakura Hall...
that I'm sorry I couldn't tell them goodbye.
Tell Mashiro I'm sorry, too.
P.S.,
Our kiss at the airport...
was my first kiss.
I guess he didn't come after all.
Sorry for making you wait in
the cold with me, Hau-hau.
Wait. You don't know yet.
I'll try calling Soichiro-kun
and get him to call Mitaka.
It's fine, really.
What?
I'll have plenty of other
chances to go after him!
I know! I'll buy you a bun to
thank you for staying with me.
You can have a pork bun, a red
bean bun, or even a pizza bun.
Now, let's bun!
Misaki?
Bun!
This has happened before.
Aoyama!
Y-Yes?!
Do you want to practice your script?
What?
Since we're riding a bike,
it's harder for us to hear each other.
We'll have to speak up, so it'll be good
for practicing your projection, right?
Kanda-kun, you're always so kind.
Sure.
All right.
Um, what did you want
to talk to me about?
It's actually pretty important, I guess.
He's always so close to my heart.
There's actually something I've
always wanted to tell you...
Really?
Yeah.
I...
I've always... always...
I've always loved you.
I love you.
Aoyama. I, u-um...
How was that? Was it believable?
Oh, yeah. You surprised me.
Y-You're right. There's no way...
This is close enough.
I think I'll make it.
Thanks, Kanda-kun. See you later.
Aoyama.
Shiina's still waiting for me!
I can't...
My legs feel so weak...
One last spurt!
If she's still waiting for me...
Today is Valentine's Day.
Shiina!
She left already...
Shiina.
Sorry I'm late.
You always break your promises.
I told you, I'm sorry.
When it's just the two
of us, call me Mashiro.
S-Sorry, Mashiro.
You can have this.
B-Bamboo shoots?
Valentine's Day is chocolate day.
Thanks.
But you could've waited until
we got back to Sakura Hall.
I wanted to do it normally.
Normally?
There were lots of girls giving
their chocolate to guys on the roof.
Even in the manga Ayano gave me.
I'm not normal.
That's why I haven't
understood you recently.
Me?
You're so far away.
F-Far away?
You're saying I'm...
You get along well with Yuko.
That's because she's my sister.
Then, what about Nanami?
Aoyama?
You went to Nanami's side today.
Of course I did.
Today's an important day for Aoyama.
It was an important day for me, too.
You didn't say to me that
we'd work hard together.
Together?
But you're already a professional.
You're leagues ahead of...
That's it.
Shiina's always been
running way ahead of me.
She's so far ahead,
I can't even see her back.
But I'm not the only one who can't see.
If Shiina looks back,
she can't see me, either.
I was looking forward to this, too.
Sorata?
I thought you might give
me some chocolate.
After I received your text during class,
I couldn't wait for school to end.
Really? Does the chocolate
make you happy?
The bamboo shoots are my favorite.
Good.
Mashiro.
I-I don't want you to
catch cold. Let's go home.
Sorata.
Can I hold your hand?
Actually, never mind.
What?!
Why would you say that?!
Because...
Because it makes me feel uneasy.
My heart is pounding.
Mashiro...
You've always been so far away.
But now...
Sorata...
Your heart is pounding
because you're alive.
What about you?
I feel even more alive than you!
We're home.
Welcome back.
Aoyama, you're back already?
How did your audition go?
Yeah.
I think I did everything I could.
Dinner's ready.
Misaki-senpai said we're having
a Valentine's pot sticker party.
Why pot stickers on Valentine's Day?
She even forced Akasaka-kun
to help her wrap them.
Nanami.
Where's Rita?
Huh? Rita-san?
The ex-freeloader went home.
What?!
Rittan was here?!
Why didn't you stop her
from leaving, Dragon?!
She seemed busy. Not much I could do.
But she came all the way to Japan...
Something happened,
didn't it, Akasaka-kun?
Well, I suppose everyone
has a secret or two.
Nothing. I'm sure Rittan
will be back again real soon!
Anyway...
Let's eat some delicious food!
Misaki-senpai?
Now that I think of it,
I wonder if she managed to give
her chocolate to Jin-san...
She might be right.
No matter how close
you are to someone,
there are some things
you just can't say.
Oh, yeah.
That thing Aoyama said this morning...
Kanda-kun, do you remember our promise?
If I pass my audition, I want you...
to listen to what I have to say.
I love you.
What's wrong, Kanda-kun?!
N-Nothing, nothing!
Hold up. I'm reading
too much into this.
Aoyama couldn't possibly
feel that way about me.
But...
It should be one or the other.
Sweet or salty...
Chocolate pot stickers?
Mashiron, you got the lucky one!
Didn't your mother tell you
not to play with your food?!
There's even garlic in it.
That's disgusting!
It doesn't taste very good.
Is this what you meant by
Valentine's pot stickers?
We're aliens!
In space, there are lots of twinkling stars!
#18 First Love with an Alien
And then, there's dark matter.
An inexpressible and terrifying feeling.
Hey, do you think I'm sparkling right now?