Next up is the weather forecast
for the Kanto Region.
Due to areas of low pressure
coming in from the west,
some areas may experience
rain this evening.
There.
That should do it.
If you plan to go out, take
an umbrella with you.
Why are you leaving Sakura Hall?
I feel like, if I stay in Sakura Hall,
I'll start to hate myself.
Hate yourself?
That's why I'm leaving Sakura Hall.
I intended to leave from the start.
Isn't the deadline for the
New Artist Award coming up?
I'll be rooting for you!
Until I leave Sakura Hall,
I'll still look after you.
Don't worry.
Since then,
Shiina has been working
through the night, every night.
Drawing and redrawing...
drawing and redrawing
over and over again.
On the morning of the deadline for
entries to the New Artist Award,
she finally finished her manuscript.
After you eat, get some rest
The only cats who still need
owners are Nozomi and Hikari.
Goal: Escape from Sakura Hall!!
Unfortunately, the Milky Way
will not be visible tonight...
I've finally taken the
first step toward moving back...
into the regular dorms...
Kouhai-kun!
Take this!
Wh-Why are you dressed like that?
That's all you have to say?
Huh?
You idiot!
I hate you!
What?
Stupid...
What's going on?
You're so naive.
She wanted you to tell her how
cute she was, how you couldn't bear it,
and how you wanted to play
"naughty administrator" with her.
Some of that is definitely sexual harassment.
Here.
She said we're celebrating Tanabata.
For Kouhai-kun: Make a wish upon
the night sky. What is your wish!?
Misaki gave me one for you, too.
What?
Sakura Hall Tanabata Festival
So...
There are a lot of kids, aren't there?
Kids tend to flock to Kamiigusa.
Wow.
Does it really fire?
Maybe it's because her
mental age is close to theirs.
Onee-chan, I want to hang one up!
All right! I'll lift you up!
Higher!
Okay! Higher, you say?
A little higher.
If you touch her, you'll be crossing...
the River Styx instead of the Milky Way.
Jin! Come write something, too!
I want to hang mine over there!
Okay! Let's go, let's go!
I wish I could fire laser beams
Even though it's not signed,
it's obvious who wrote this one.
How's this?
A little more!
A little higher!
This isn't Tanabata anymore.
What are you, a little kid?
You can do it! You can do it!
I wish he would look at me someday
You don't know?
I don't know what to write.
You worked hard.
Why don't you wish you'll
win the New Artist Award?
That's not necessary.
I see. Why not?
I'll win it on my own.
You're amazing.
What's amazing about me?
You're just brilliant, that's all.
I can't see the stars.
You're right. We can't.
The clouds are still in the way.
Still?
I'll go hang this on the tree.
Huh?
I want to hang one, too.
Do it, do it!
I should've wished it wouldn't rain.
I can't give this to her...
Well, now Orihime won't
get to see Hikoboshi!
And they'll live happily ever after!
Make sure you take a bath later.
You'll catch cold.
Incoming Call: Iida Ayano
Hello?
Say, Mashiron...
She's not wearing that necklace.
Huh? Oh, right.
But that wasn't a date,
it was a misunderstanding...
I understand.
Shiina?
I wasn't selected for
the New Artist Award.
What?
I-It's okay.
I'm sure you'll do better next time.
There's no reason to dwell
on the New Artist Award.
What am I saying?
Besides, you've got
an editor, don't you?
I don't want to say these things...
You're on a whole different
level from those others guys.
So, it's no big deal if you
don't win the New Artist—
I'm going back to my room.
Mashiron...
Kouhai-kun—
Hey! Kouhai-kun!
Jin...
I'm the worst...
What's so bad about you?
Did you hear that Misaki's new anime...
had its public debut?
Her new anime?
That thing she showed us at
Shiina's welcoming party?
It's been well-received.
Made it to a million hits in just three days.
She's already received ten offers...
to commercialize her five-minute anime.
Everyone was looking forward
to Misaki's new work.
But I...
I'm the only person who
wanted her to fail.
I actually wanted her
to crash and burn.
You must see right through me.
I'm actually a little relieved
Shiina wasn't selected.
Shiina worked so hard to
win the New Artist Award.
I knew that, but...
The thing about talent...
is that it unconsciously
wraps up and destroys...
everyone around it.
The closer you are to it,
the more it tears you to shreds.
There are people who live
in a place that ordinary men...
can never reach.
It's a world above the clouds
that we can't even see.
That's the kind of world they live in.
I don't think Misaki-senpai
cares about talent or ability.
I agree.
But I don't know how to
accept the difference...
between Misaki and me.
Until the day I can proudly
stand by her side,
all I can do is struggle in vain.
Jin-san...
Jin-san, do you like Misaki-senpai?
Do you want to go get some ramen?
It's on me.
Do you think Shiina will be all right?
It might be weird for me to
worry about her now, but...
What's wrong with feeling both ways,
if it's how you really feel?
Things like this are never simple.
Sakura Hall Tanabata Festival
An Introduction to Programming
Programming Practice
Skills Necessary for Programming Games
Huh?
What are these?
Akasaka Ryunosuke: I don't need those books anymore.
Kanda Sorata: But why did you give them to me?
Akasaka Ryunosuke: Because I thought you
needed them. They're a parting gift.
He stays cooped up in his room,
but he knows how to read a situation.
Akasaka Ryunosuke: I don't need those books anymore.
Kanda Sorata: But why did you give them to me?
Akasaka Ryunosuke: Because I thought you
needed them. They're a parting gift.
Akasaka Ryunosuke: I don't need those books anymore.
Kanda Sorata: But why did you give them to me?
Akasaka Ryunosuke: Because I thought you
needed them. They're a parting gift.
Kanda Sorata: Akasaka, I have a question.
Kanda Sorata: But why did you give them to me?
Akasaka Ryunosuke: Because I thought you
needed them. They're a parting gift.
Kanda Sorata: Akasaka, I have a question.
Akasaka Ryunosuke: What?
Akasaka Ryunosuke: Because I thought you
needed them. They're a parting gift.
Kanda Sorata: Akasaka, I have a question.
Akasaka Ryunosuke: What?
Kanda Sorata: Do you think getting close
to prodigious talent will destroy me?
Kanda Sorata: Akasaka, I have a question.
Akasaka Ryunosuke: What?
Kanda Sorata: Do you think getting close
to prodigious talent will destroy me?
Akasaka Ryunosuke: I don't know what
you're talking about.
Akasaka Ryunosuke: What?
Kanda Sorata: Do you think getting close
to prodigious talent will destroy me?
Akasaka Ryunosuke: I don't know what
you're talking about.
Akasaka Ryunosuke: But, at the very least,
Boo!
Don't talk about being destroyed...
until you've read those books so
thoroughly, you feel like you're done for.
Sincerely, someone who prefers
Senpachi to Kinpachi: Maid-chan.
I hate to admit it, but you're right.
Until I feel like I'm done for, huh?
Sakura Hall
Please Knock
Mashiron's Room
Shiina.
I'll leave your breakfast here.
No one ever cleans this stuff up...
What are they going to do when I'm gone?
I wish I could fire laser beams
I wish for Sorata's wish to come true
Sorata's wish...
Haven't you heard the expression:
"Let your face smile,
let your heart cry"?
What does she mean by my "wish"?
This is the same.
Taken literally, it's
a nice, positive phrase.
Career Plan
What's going on in her head?
But the truth is, it secretly
hides a great sadness inside.
Well, that's all for today.
Kanda-kun...
I took the day off work—
Um, I mean, I've got the day off.
Let's go look for someone
to take the cats.
Oh, yeah.
Thanks for everything, Aoyama.
Once Nozomi and Hikari are
gone, you can finally move.
Kanda-kun.
Hmm?
Are you sure you want to do this?
What do you mean?
Well, just by looking at you,
I can sort of tell...
Do you have a minute?
Huh?
What was that?
Crazy way to hit on someone.
"Stolen love"?
Kanda-kun...
Poor Aoyama...
Uh, um...
Can I help you?
I like sweet things.
Oh, I see...
What?
I like the union of sweet and salty flavors.
Uh, I... I see...
How is Shiina-san?
She's depressed.
Here. Read this.
Nanohana Hall?
Shiina-san's art is perfect.
Her only weakness is her stories.
So I told her to use
events actually occurring...
at Sakura Hall as reference.
Wait, what is this?
Shiina and my roles are reversed?!
Hey!
Just keep reading.
The boy who couldn't even choose...
his own underwear
actually had a clear goal.
On the other hand, the heroine...
can't find anything she wants to do.
Then, some stuff happens...
The problem is what happens next.
What?
As you can see,
this powerfully abrupt
ending isn't a happy one.
This is the main reason Shiina-san
failed to win the award.
The heroine is leaving Nanohana Hall...
Goodbye.
I told her over and
over again to fix the ending.
But she wouldn't listen to me.
What?
She said it was your wish.
Yes, yes!
An ending that captures the
careening drive of youth!
It's sending shivers down my spine!
This might work...
My wish?
Chihiro-sensei!
Huh?
What's wrong, Kanda?
Did you forget something?
What?
I have to start here.
See you later!
What was that about?
Career Plan
Suimei University of the Arts: Media Studies
I see...
My wish is...
Shiina-san, is this what you want?
What I want?
You should write the ending you want.
The ending I want.
That's right.
What's the ending you want to see?
Goodbye.
My...
My wish isn't to leave Sakura Hall.
Becoming a Programmer
I was putting pressure on myself.
I was just running from Sakura
Hall... from reality...
My wish is...
Shiina!
You can stay there. Just listen to me!
There's something I want to tell you!
I submitted my career plan!
I want to go into Media
Studies and make video games!
I'm even thinking about participating
in a development audition!
I'm home...
Huh?
I want to be a game designer.
I've always been interested,
but I was too scared.
I kept thinking about what
would happen if I failed.
I kept lining up reasons not to do it,
like "it's a waste of time,"
or "I'll just get my feelings hurt,"
and gave up on it altogether.
But watching you made
me want to try harder.
Someday, I'll be like you!
Shiina...
You were up drawing all night again.
You really are amazing.
I... I want to stay at Nanohana Hall!
I want to stay at Nanohana Hall...
This is the happy ending
you really wanted.
What is this doing here?
Answer it.
What?
You answer it.
Oh, come on!
Yes, this is Shiina's cellphone.
What? Oh, thanks for earlier...
Shiina. Shiina.
Wake up, Shiina.
You're going to make your debut.
Your debut?
No, you idiot. Yours.
You didn't win the New Artist Award...
but if you fix up your manuscript,
they'll print it in next month's issue.
It looks like you've already
fixed them, though.
I wonder why...
I should be happy, but I'm crying.
Why?
Congratulations.
We'll have to celebrate your debut.
Then, I have a favor to ask of you.
What's that?
Call me by my name.
Shiina?
Not that one.
Hey! No, I can't do that!
I've never called a girl by her first name!
You call Misaki by her name...
She's an alien!
And Chihiro.
She's an Amazon!
Then, what am I?
Well, you're...
It's not fair.
Mashiro.
I knew it.
You knew what?
I can't tell you.
What does that mean?
Naive!
You're naive, Sorata!
That's youth for you!
It makes your heart race!
I'm sweating over here!
H-Hey, how long were you guys listening in?
There's something I want to tell you!
Gasp!
From the beginning!
Oh, no! What is it? Tell me, tell me!
Isn't there something you
want to tell us, too?
Come on, come on. Don't be shy.
Bring it on!
Show us how you really feel!
Sorry for causing such a fuss.
Please let me stay...
Let me stay at Sakura Hall!
Mashiron, congratulations
on your debut!
And kouhai-kun, welcome home!
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
I pretended it was someone else's
fault that nothing happened.
But I was wrong.
If you put your mind to it,
you can change the color of
your world in an instant.
Sakura Hall is a haphazard
mix of all different colors.
I wish for Sorata's wish to come true
It'll probably never change...
#04 A World of Changing Colors
Hikari is female.
#05 The Serious Girl of Sakura Hall
Hikari says she has a hunch that...
there'll soon be more females.