Oborozuka Shopping District
Big End of Year Sale!
Big Sale
Oborozuka Shopping District
Big End of Year Sale!
Tatsuda Butchery
This place is full of people today.
The New Year's right after Christmas.
Special
Sale
5 Tickets per
Turn
What's that?
It's a lottery.
I want to try.
Hmm, we'd need tickets.
Lottery
Tickets
I have some.
Lady Tohru, is that magic?
No, I received them during my daily
shopping here at the shopping district.
You've blended right in.
5 Tickets per Turn
Special Sale
Okay, you get three turns.
Grand Prize | Pair of Hot Springs Trip Tickets
1st Prize | Big Screen TV
2nd Prize | Cleaning Robot
3rd Prize | Warm Kotatsu
4th Prize | ¥10,000 Oborozuka Shopping District Voucher
5th Prize | ¥5,000 Oborozuka Shopping District Voucher
6th Prize | ¥1,000 Oborozuka Shopping District Voucher
Grand Prize | Pair of Hot Springs Trip Tickets
1st Prize | Big Screen TV
2nd Prize | Cleaning Robot
3rd Prize | Warm Kotatsu
4th Prize | ¥10,000 Oborozuka Shopping District Voucher
5th Prize | ¥5,000 Oborozuka Shopping District Voucher
Grand Prize | Pair of Hot Springs Trip Tickets
1st Prize | Big Screen TV
2nd Prize | Cleaning Robot
3rd Prize | Warm Kotatsu
4th Prize | ¥10,000 Oborozuka Shopping District Voucher
Grand Prize | Pair of Hot Springs Trip Tickets
1st Prize | Big Screen TV
2nd Prize | Cleaning Robot
3rd Prize | Warm Kotatsu
The grand prize is a hot
springs vacation, huh?
Hot springs.
Hot springs would be nice.
I'll land the hot springs!
Don't use magic.
I know!
Here's your consolation prize. Pocket tissues.
Here are your tissues.
Last one! This time I'll win!
Huh?
Hmm?
Congratulations!
I did it!
Third prize! You'll be set for
the cold winter with this.
You've won a warm kotatsu.
Oh!
Kotatsu?
Are you going anywhere, Yamashita-kun?
Deadline
Home to my family in Hokkaido.
I'll buy you some nama
chocolates as souvenirs.
Nama chocolates...
What about you, Kobayashi-san?
Going home to your family?
No. You?
I have Winter Comiket at the end of the year.
Aah.
The train's leaving now.
Oh, you're right.
Happy New Year!
A lot of stuff happened this year.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
This year's work is finally over.
Well done.
Kobayashi, do you have
to go to work anymore?
Nope. I'm off until the third.
Oh!
You're always so busy, so please take
it easy over the holidays.
I plan to.
This is heaven. I'm glad we won the kotatsu.
Right?
I need to start preparing
the New Year's dishes soon.
I even borrowed the tools to
pound mochi and soba.
You don't have to go that all-out.
It's a maid's responsibility
to take charge and make sure
the seasonal events are carried out.
Oh, do you need to use the restroom?
It's such a pain.
Tohru, you're a maid. Go for me.
Huh?
Oh well, guess I'll go.
Oh, Miss Kobayashi, could you hit
the switch on the rice cooker?
Pass the remote.
Huh?
What are you doing?
Oh.
This is New Year's curry.
Delicious
Tomato
Curry
Mild
Honey
Curry
Sun Curry
Mild
Is it—
It's mild.
Sun Curry
Mild
- December 29th -
The New Year's parlor trick tournament
will be on January 3rd.
You can look forward to several outstanding
guests performing in our competition!
Our huge New Year's bargain sale starts soon!
Doors open at 6:30AM on the 1st!
- December 30th -
So I can just pound the New Year's
soba tomorrow before we eat it, then?
Tohru, isn't this a lot of work for you?
No, these are my natural duties as a maid.
Hmm, but I feel like we're
forgetting something.
Oh, a guest.
Who could it be?
Hmm?
Who indeed?
Tohru-chan, good afternoon!
Tohru, they're calling for you.
Well, if I have to...
Yes, yes. Hello?
Oh, Miss Sasakibe.
Good afternoon.
Umm, I made too much candied
sweet potatoes with chestnuts.
Have some if you'd like.
Well, we didn't make any of those.
Thank you very much!
Oh, hold on one moment, please.
Here's some mochi we pounded.
If you put it in your freezer
you can keep it from molding.
Oh, thanks!
Good job.
It's nothing.
Yes, yes. Hello?
Oh, Mr. Yana. Good afternoon.
I got a lot of mandarin oranges from my home.
Have some. They're sweet.
This many? Thank you very much!
Please hold on a moment.
Please take some of our mochi.
Good job.
It's nothing.
What is it?
Going by the pattern thus far,
as soon as I climb under again...
Well, then...
Mr. Sone. Is this a rooster?
Yes, next year's animal.
Thank you very much.
This rooster is well made.
I'll put it on display right away.
Here's some of the mochi we made. Have some.
Nyom, nyom...
Good job again.
Well, we received this from Mr. Sone.
Rooster!
Oh, the zodiac animal?
What's a zodiac animal?
There are twelve animals
in the Chinese zodiac.
Zodiac Animals
Rat, Ox, Tiger...
Rat
Ox
Tiger
Uh, what else?
Rabbit, Dragon, Snake, Horse, Ram,
Rabbit
Dragon
Snake
Horse
Ram
Monkey
Monkey, Rooster, Dog, and Pig.
Rooster
Dog
Pig
Is that a spell?
I'm surprised you know.
It came up when I was searching the
net for all things New Year.
But I still can't accept it.
How so?
Well, they say the order of the
animals was decided by who
reached God fastest on the
morning of the new year, right?
Oh, yeah, there is that story.
The Rat stole first place by
hopping a ride on the Ox.
God
"Seriously!?"
What is it that you can't you accept?
Okay, stop right there!
It's impossible for a dragon to come after
an Ox or Tiger, let alone a Rabbit!
I can't accept it at all!
Well, it's just a story.
Oh, this mandarin orange is sweet.
Tohru.
Yes?
Well, umm...
For getting along with the neighbors,
and everything else you've done...
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
It tastes like you.
It doesn't.
Oh, right!
I thought I was forgetting something.
Here.
New Year's Greetings
New Year's Cards?
Yes. I bought them.
I haven't written one of these in years.
Candy Grab
- December 31st -
How do you feel about your
first performance on the show?
Well, I wrote my lyrics down on
my hand so I wouldn't forget them,
I had the noodle shop owner in the
shopping district teach me the trick.
but my palms are so sweaty
they've all disappeared.
Wow.
Kobayashi.
Put my kimono on.
A kimono?
Apparently she promised to join
Miss Saikawa on her first shrine visit.
She lent me a kimono so we
can wear them together.
A kimono, huh?
It's not too tight?
No.
All right, all done.
Oh!
Incredible, Miss Kobayashi.
That's like a magic trick.
A long time ago my mother
taught me the trick.
Nice. It looks cute.
You want to wear one, too, then, Tohru?
Huh?
First Shrine Visit
I'm glad my kimono fits you.
With a kimono, you can adjust
the size for the chest, too!
Yeah.
These past few days we've been losing
to the temptation of the kotatsu,
but going outside for a change is nice.
Yeah.
Fresh air.
It's a little cold.
Kanna-san!
Saikawa.
So cute!
Warm.
Oh, you're here, too?
Why are you here?
Should I not be?
I ran into Elma over there.
I heard you could eat lots
of unusual food here.
Lucoa-san, what's with your kimono?
Well, it is New Year's.
I wanted to go traditional.
S-Stop it!
What's your idea of traditional?
Hey, Kobayashi-san.
Oh, that looks good on you, Mr. Fafnir.
Yeah, it does.
Hmph.
Let's hurry! Before the amazake's gone!
Well, shall we go?
Yes!
Episode 11
Year End, New Year! (No Comiket Bit This Time)
Fried Chicken
Amazake
It's delicious
1 Cup 100 yen
So sweet.
It's a nostalgic flavor.
Delicious Amazake
Really?
Yeah. I used to drink
something like this often.
It takes me back.
Oh, and because you got
drunk you and your sister—
Evil-Banishing
Arrow
It's a pretty charm.
Mhmm.
Hey, Kanna-san. Want to buy matching ones?
Matching?
Yes.
O-Of this r-relationship charm.
Relationships
A charm, huh?
You want one?
Academics
An academics charm...
One I made would work way better.
You don't need any charms, Shouta?
I'm from a family of mages.
I'll achieve my desires myself!
How cute!
S-Stop it!
You bought an evil-banishing arrow?
It might be useful for
researching new curses.
How'd Comiket go?
Thanks, we sold out.
You're as popular as ever, huh.
Looks like Faf-kun's "Curse Anthology 2"
didn't sell any though.
He produced a second after the
first didn't sell this summer?
Miss Kobayashi.
What's that?
Fortune Telling
Number Twelve
Great Blessing
Luck
Georgie, you got great blessing!
It's a blessing too great for a maid.
You should have it, young lady.
I'm fine. It's your luck, Sis—... Georgie.
Miss Kobayashi, look! My fortune!
Huh? Which one?
Fortune Telling
Number Twelve
Great Curse
Luck
Great curse.
This is my first time seeing it.
What does it mean?
Your wishes will prove difficult.
The one you wait for will come.
That which you've lost, won't be found.
I don't really get, but it
sounds like a great curse.
Though I guess it also means things'll
only get better from here.
Yay!
Hey, isn't it almost time?
Huh? Seriously?
Seriously, seriously.
I wonder what's going on.
Saturday, December 31st
Oh, this year's almost over.
Time sure flew by, didn't it?
Thirteen, twelve,
eleven, ten, nine,
eight,
seven,
six,
five,
four, three, two,
one!
Happy New Year!
Tohru.
Happy New Year.
Happy New Year to you, too!
Be happy.
May Dad's lower back
get a little better.
May I become
great at soccer
Land a job.
Cherish
our family.
Young lady, are you all right?
I'm just a little cold.
Kobayashi, can I invite Saikawa over?
Huh?
Since it's warm under the kotatsu.
Why don't we take this chance
to invite everyone over?
We have plenty of food, too.
Sure. We should let Saikawa-san's
and Shouta-kun's families know.
Well then, everyone, let's go!
Here's the ozouni soup, everyone.
What's this? Did you make this?
You don't have to eat it
if you don't want to.
Tohru and Kanna made the mochi.
You went all out.
Well, since you made it,
I'll eat it for you.
Thanks for the food.
Slurp
It's good!
I learned the seasoning from
Miss Kobayashi's family.
It's not mild, huh?
I'll make some sweet red bean soup later, too.
Tohru.
What meat is this?
You get a special treat, Miss Kobayashi!
I've told you countless times
not to put in your tail.
But it's about time you tried it, isn't it?
It's a new year after all.
It still won't happen next
year or the year after.
Eh?
Just climb in with us.
Okay.
The kotatsu's the best.
Kotatsus are nice. Maybe we'll buy one, too.
Do as you please.
Oh!
I got to see the first sunrise of the year
with Kanna-san, so this should be a good year.
It's just a sunrise.
The first sunrise of the year is special.
There it goes.
Yes.
- January 2nd -
Now, every year on January 2nd,
it's the annual Tokyo Bay Ekiden!
I want to watch anime.
Which team will win today's race to Nagaura?
That's on break until the new year's over.
Eh?
Well, I understand how you feel.
Tohru, pick it up.
I can't step away right now.
What do you mean?
It's closer to you, isn't it?
Aah, fine.
- January 3rd -
Now, today's Tokyo Bay
Ekiden, on January 3rd.
The contenders for the win have
been narrowed down to two teams!
Are these people running the
same race as yesterday?
No, today they're running back from Nagaura.
Boring.
Want to play a game?
Uh-uh.
I'll do my homework.
Homework?
First writing of the year, huh?
Mhmm.
What are you writing?
Anything works.
Ko...
...ta...
...tsu.
Kotatsu
Kotatsu, huh?
Looks fun.
Lady Tohru, you, too.
Are you sure?
Mhmm.
Okay!
Mom
What should I write?
Something you like?
Hello?
Lady Tohru?
Oh, right.
Mom?
Happy New Year.
Oh, Happy New Year.
I got your New Year's card today.
Oh, I guess it didn't make
it for the 1st, huh?
It's the first time you've ever sent a card.
Yeah. Everyone doing all right?
We're well, we're well.
It went out of bounds!
Lady Tohru, don't worry.
Sounds lively.
What do I do?!
I have some friends over.
So you're having fun, then?
It's fine to keep going.
All right, here I go.
Yeah.
I'll call again sometime.
Give everyone my regards.
Yeah. Later.
Miss Kobayashi
You wrote it.
Yes.
Who was on the phone?
My mom.
Huh?
She said all my folks are doing well.
I see.
New Year's ending soon.
Miss Kobayashi, you weren't going to
see your family even for New Year's?
Hmm.
Every year, I spend New Year's
sleeping off the year's fatigue.
It's not like I'm on bad
terms with my family.
Occasionally we chat on the phone.
Is that how it is with human families?
I think it's different for everyone.
In my case, living over here's
the life I've grown used to.
I think I understand.
What about you?
You could go back if you wanted to, right?
You're not going to go see them?
Living here with you is my
life now, Miss Kobayashi.
Yeah.
Oh!
It went in nicely that time.
Yeah, it fell right...
Ah.
New Year's Money
New Year's money?
I completely forgot.
It's my first time receiving any.
Mine, too.
It's my first time giving any, as well.
Well, I'm off.
Take care!
I'm gonna have a good first dream.
One, Fuji Lucoa!
Two, Hawk Lucoa!
Three, Eggplant Lucoa!
Stop it!
Next Episode
Lady Elma, I received New
Year's money from Kobayashi.
Oh, good for you, Kanna.
I received New Year's money from Kobayashi.
New Year's money.
All right! I'll give you one, too.
Episode 12
Tohru and Kobayashi's Impactful Meeting!
(We're Raising The Bar On Ourselves)
Oh!