Coffee Shop
Ta-da!
The script for the Hitotose Troupe's
first performance is complete!
Here you go.
Thanks.
Here, Hina-chan.
And Mayu-chan.
Thanks.
Yeah. I like it.
All right!
The ending might change, depending
on how the production works out,
but that's the general idea
that I want to go with.
It's amazing!
For this part...
Let's see...
You look really happy, Mayu-chan.
Well, now that the story's
come together, that means...
...we can start trying on costumes, right?
Pa-Pa-Parade
Used Bookstore Hitotose
I went out and got the perfect
costumes for each of you.
I'd love to see you try them on right away!
You're in quite the rush, aren't you?
When do most troupes do this?
Right before the show, I think.
They call it the "parade."
Parade?
Not that kind of parade!
Huh? It's not?
The "dress parade" is when
the actors line up with their costumes on
to check everything over.
So it can't really be done
until right before the show.
Huh?
There are some things you can't check on
until you've basically finished all rehearsing.
Huh?!
No way! No way!
I want to play with all of you
in cute costumes!
Right now!
She's reverted to a child...
I want to! I want to!
If you want to do it that badly,
I guess we'll have to.
Peek.
Cute!
It suits you.
I don't usually wear stuff
like this, so it's new to me.
You don't work in the coffee shop at all?
I helped out once,
but it was too hard to resist
the urge to sneak bites.
Staaaaare
Makes sense.
Plus, skirts just feel too weird on me.
Really? But it looks so nice.
But it's so loose and billowy,
it's hard to move around in.
I can't run off at full speed.
I don't think you'll have many opportunities
to run at full speed in the shop...
Hina-chan, you've been helping out
in the coffee shop a lot, huh?
Are you used to wearing maid uniforms?
Yeah. It doesn't embarrass me
as much as it used to.
That's why I got this one
for you, Hina-chan!
Ta-da!
She's a bunny girl!
Wow... That's really cute.
Hina-chan, you look sexy!
Isn't it a little too revealing, though?
I-It's okay!
I just need to think of it
as the coffee shop's uniform!
Why are you forcing this?
So cute!
I thought Yua-chan would
look cute in an apron dress.
Yeah, well, I look cute in anything.
When we stand together like this,
you really stand out, Hina-chan.
Huh?
You're right...
That's not true at all!
When we put Hina-chan and
Yua-chan together...
See?
They look like they're from
Alice in Wonderland, don't they?
R-Really?
This doesn't seem much like
a fairy tale to me...
Alice and the rabbit, huh? I get it.
That just leaves...
Wow!
Aki-chan has such a nice figure,
it was hard to decide.
That looks great!
Beautiful!
Something like this could work, too.
Rawr.
Or even this, actually...
They're all so cute, I can't choose!
None of those are even
in the script, though.
Yeah, I know!
Also, also...
I think something like this will look good
on Hina-chan and Aki-chan, too!
Hey, those are basically just underwear!
I think they're really
frilly and cute, though.
Mayu-chan's out of control.
She's taking this way too far.
But if these costumes
will make our show better...
Why would you go that far?!
Do you actually want to wear that?!
Well...
The truth is, um...
My mom is coming to visit
Hitotose Manor soon.
What?!
I wanted her to see our first performance...
So I want to put on a good show
and put her mind at ease.
I'm sorry it's such a selfish reason, but...
We can't show Hina-chan's mom a messy shop!
I have to clean up, fast!
Is there a certain way
your mom likes her meals flavored?
I'll start practicing it now!
Do you think we should wax the floors?
Good idea!
I want to get brand new bookshelves, too!
While we're at it, should we
remodel the kitchen, too?
Then we should change the wallpaper.
You guys need to put all that effort
toward rehearsing!
Sheesh.
You should've told us that earlier.
Don't be a stranger.
We're all partners in the Hitotose Troupe.
Of course we'll help you.
That's right, Hina-chan.
Just leave it all to us.
Let's put on a great performance,
for Hina-chan's mom!
Yeah!
Thank you, everyone!
Now that that's all worked out,
why don't we have a toast?
And we can have a snack while we're at it...
It's a little early, but
why don't we have dinner?
Yay!
Here you go.
Thank you.
U-Um, who's going to do the toast?
Oh...
I think the Hitotose Troupe's principal,
Hina-chan, should do it.
Huh? Ah...
Go on, don't be shy.
We've all got our drinks.
I can't wait any longer.
O-Okay!
Th-Then...
To the success of the
Hitotose Troupe's first performance!
Cheers!
I don't need to study Japanese!
Or so I thought when I did my test
and got an awful score! (I really did it now)
I'm sure they'll want to see my score when I get home...
...To think that I got that score in Japanese...
...What am I supposed to tell my mom?
I'll just keep it a secret until my science test comes back, since I'm good at that...
It'll be okay... It'll be okay... Right?
Coffee Shop
That looks good!
Would you like some?
Yeah! Thanks!
Greetings.
Are you having a costume party
today or something?
No, um...
I came because I heard you
had finished the script.
Yes, so we were having a bit
of an early dress parade...
Sensei, would you like to wear one, too?
Mayu-chan's switch
just got flipped on again!
So this is the route you're taking.
I've been hoping to ask for your
advice since I started writing it.
Yes, we do have limited stage space.
This has been such a fulfilling day!
There's still one costume left.
That's a lovely dress.
Yeah, like one a princess would wear.
Mayu-chan!
Yes?
Since we have this, why don't you try it on?
Huh?
You did say you wanted to be a princess.
Huh?!
And it looks like it's just your size.
Huh? Huh?
You're so cute, Mayu-chan!
It looks great on you.
It's like it was made-to-order!
You really do look like a princess!
Argh! I feel so embarrassed!
What's the problem?
It suits you!
Well...
Shall we do a reading right now?
Huh? Now?
We only have a few weeks
until the performance.
We can't afford to waste a single second.
But if we start now,
it might get too late
for you to get back home.
No need to worry.
I came prepared.
Y-You had every intention of
spending the night here...
Tomorrow is Sunday, which means...
An impromptu training camp!
That's very sudden...
Go on, all you change into your pajamas.
Huh? Why?
This play takes place in a dream land,
a wonderland.
Don't you think pajamas would be
the best costume to set the mood?
Um, that's not a "dream land."
It's a "wonderland."
That sounds kind of interesting!
I'll go change right away!
A pajama party...
I guess Ruri-chan really
does like this sort of thing.
Uh...
But I didn't bring pajamas or anything...
Don't worry. Leave it to me.
You can borrow my pajamas.
I have some very nice, grown-up ones
that would be perfect for you.
Who in the world are you?
You look just like a child.
You're not kidding.
Huh?
Oh, sorry...
Despite how I look, I'm an adult!
Oh! You look so young,
I thought you were a child.
Maybe that's a little too grown-up...
Yua-chan?
The Hitotose Troupe's First Performance
A Strange Tale in a Strange Land
Starting today at 5:00 PM
Please come watch!
It's finally show time...
I'm worried.
Everything went perfectly
in rehearsal, but...
Hinako!
Long time no see!
Mom!
How've you been? I missed you!
How's school?
You've grown a bit taller, haven't you?
U-Um...
Are you eating properly?
Um...
That's a cute costume!
Hinako
Wink at me!
I love you!
Hinako
Please look
at me!
I brought some things to cheer you on.
Do you think it's enough?
To cheer me on?
Oh, it looks like there's some time
before the performance.
Huh?
I'm going to check out Tokyo.
Take care of my things, okay?
O-Okay...
Well, Hinako...
Break a leg!
Your mom's so outgoing, unlike you.
Huh? Your mom went sightseeing?
Hinako
Wave at me!
Wink at me!
I wanted to meet her.
As your landlady,
I was hoping to talk to her.
Sorry...
My mom has always been very active,
outgoing, and dynamic...
She's the exact opposite of me.
W-Well, lots of kids are
nothing like their parents!
My mom was a tea ceremony instructor,
so she was strict about manners.
We don't have the same taste
in clothes, either.
It's no fun.
My dad is a free spirit,
so I need to do a good job
running the shops.
For you, that's a pretty
serious problem, huh?
Yay! Amigo!
The Hitotose Troupe's First Performance
A Strange Tale in a Strange Land
Starting today at 5:00 PM
Location: Coffee Shop Hitotose
The Hitotose Troupe's First Performance
A Strange Tale in a Strange Land
Today at 5:00 PM
Do come in!
Reserved
Seat
Welcome to Hitotose!
Have you decided what you'd like to order?
This is what we're recommending today.
I ran after the white rabbit.
I was so busy running after it,
I somehow ended up upside down mid-air!
I'm going to hit the ground!
I closed my eyes tight and braced for impact.
Poof
Huh? It doesn't hurt...
Actually, it feels rather fluffy and soft.
And more than anything...
"It's very warm..."
When I lowered my face into the fluff,
I heard a mysterious voice.
"Hey! Don't fluff me without permission!
Startled by that voice, I looked up.
I gently pet the warm, white object...
This fur is...
"Rabbit fur...?"
I heard the voice again.
"Come on! I have to hurry
to the Queen's palace!"
I still couldn't see who the voice belonged to,
but it was probably this fluffy object.
"I'm sorry for fluffing you without permission.
But all I can see is your fur.
I can't see the ground at all.
I don't even know how to get down."
Hitotose Troupe
Full House!
We're sorry.
All seats are filled.
The audience seats have really filled up.
Are you all right?
I-I'm still okay right now,
but I feel like I'll get nervous
when I see my mom...
Greetings, everyone.
I'll be watching your performance
with my mother today.
Hello.
Oh! I've seen her on TV!
I think she's a model...
Everyone in Sensei's family is famous.
Hina-chan is already a scarecrow
after seeing Sensei's mom!
Why would you get nervous from
seeing someone else's mom?!
Well, I would recommend this.
Will you flambé that with brandy, then?
Oh, I'm sorry, but we don't serve
alcoholic beverages here...
Okay, breathe in...
And out.
It is kind of nerve-wracking to have
our families watching, isn't it?
I didn't really like Parents' Day
at school when I was little, either.
When I had to read out loud,
...held his umbrella over the fox.
I'd accidentally hold
my textbook upside-down.
The fox looked at the old man in surprise,
Oh, but I had the whole book
memorized, so it was fine.
then it barked happily.
I once forgot my lines
when I was on the stage.
I got through the rest
by ad-libbing, but still...
Th-That's right! If you keep
wishing and never give up,
your dream will come true!
Yeah, because you're both geniuses...
Actually, if you tell yourself
it's okay to mess up,
you won't get as nervous.
R-Really?
I once messed up during a dance recital
and fell into the audience,
but I got right back on the stage
and kept dancing until the end.
Even I, the great Yua-sama,
messes up sometimes!
So don't feel bad!
Yua-chan, you're amazing!
I never would have recovered
from something like that!
Just imagining it makes me start shaking...
Crap! It had the opposite effect!
No, listen! What I'm saying is that
you don't have to be afraid of messing up!
Hina-chan.
Just remember our play
at the culture festival.
The culture festival?
Yeah. Remember the handkerchief?
Actually, you're right. That
somehow worked out okay, didn't it?
That's right.
So you shouldn't be afraid
of making mistakes.
You succeeded in making
Hina-chan feel better!
I know I mess up all the time, okay?!
We'll be there to help you, so don't worry.
Let's show your mom how cool you can be!
Y-Yeah!
L-Let's do it!
Yeah!
That's right.
For the sake of all these girls
who are supporting me,
I have to make our
first performance a success!
I psyched myself up
before coming out here, but...
Hinako! Knock 'em dead!
Hinako
Hinapon
LOVE
I'm right here watching!
Your mom's on your side!
She really is making me nervous!
Yay! Yay! Hinako! Go! Go! Hinako!
Hina-chan's turning into a scarecrow...
Uh...
Before we start, I'd like to say
a few words as the shop owner.
Our shops, Used Bookstore Hitotose
and Coffee Shop Hitotose,
Hina-chan, look at that.
produced this play for the
entertainment of customers
Huh?
1) Where am I?
What is this place I've come to?
2)Why, hello.
visiting during the shopping
district's stamp rally.
Cue cards made with the shop's menu rolls...
This is our theater troupe's
very first performance,
Mayu-chan was up all night making them.
but we hope to earn your future support
as we move forward from here.
Just look at Mayu-chan standing up as
tall as she can to show us our lines,
Also, our stamps for the stamp rally
and it'll soothe your soul.
can be collected at the table
outside the shop,
That's what you meant?!
Don't just stand still all day!
I'll move first, so you just follow me.
so please visit it later.
They're doing all this just for me...
That's right.
I'm not standing on this stage alone.
Where am I?
What is this place I've come to?
Oh? And who are you?
Allow me to welcome you, miss.
Welcome to a land so exciting,
you'll be unable to sleep.
Welcome to a land so fun,
you'll be unable to leave.
Welcome to Wonderland.
I'm going to show my mom
the best play I can put on,
with my wonderful friends!
When you can't do it right, lie down on your back and breathe.
You can tell that your stomach moves up and down,
rather than your lungs.
This is abdominal breathing!
When you get the idea of how to do it lying down,
try doing it again standing up!
Try at least 10 times a day
Point
With abdominal breathing, visualize that
you're releasing your breath into your stomach
rather than your lungs when you breathe!
I'm sorry, everyone!
I'm the principal,
but I put you all through so much trouble...
We got everything
back on track, so it's fine.
The audience didn't seem to mind, either.
But...
You weren't moving at all in the beginning,
so I thought you were playing
a scarecrow or something.
But then you acted out your part
until the very end.
You did so well.
You're grown up, Hinako.
Mom...
Isn't that great, Hina-chan?
You've put your mom's mind at ease.
Yeah! Thanks!
It's because of all of you!
I'm so glad I came to Hitotose Manor!
Well, it's time to catch
my bullet train, so I'll be going.
Huh?!
Girls, take care of Hinako for me!
She's like a storm.
From One Year to the Next
Lots of things have happened
since Hina-chan came to Hitotose Manor.
I hope next year will be a good year, too.
Next time, "From One Year to the Next."