Hey, do you think people avoid
us when we come through?
You're just too intimidating.
Really?
But we aren't doing anything!
Oh, yeah... I heard there's a real
intimidating guy at Shuuei High, too.
Right! I've heard of him!
Someone who saw him said he's over two
meters tall, like a new species of bear!
I heard he almost killed someone
right in front of the cops.
No way!
That's only a rumor.
People keep exaggerating.
It's just like an urban legend!
Right, yeah...
No way he's two meters tall.
Yeah, and a new bear species? Please...
I saw an urban legend!
He's totally over two meters tall!
AHHHHH
Crap!
He saw me!
He's gonna strangle me!
He's gonna eat me!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I arrived just now, too.
The urban legend has a girlfriend!
My Christmas
I'm Gouda Takeo, a first-year in high school.
It's now winter,
but I still feel like I'm in spring.
And soon...
It'll be Christmas soon!
Yeah.
Christmas... With Yamato.
Hey, Takeo-kun...
About Christmas... Can we celebrate
with my friends and yours?
No one seems to have any plans.
Christmas with everyone...
I see.
I hadn't thought of that.
That's a good idea. Okay, let's do that!
Okay!
She's right.
I'm already a happy man, anyway...
Class 1-6
Whoa, a Christmas party with girls?
That'd be a first for me!
The day has finally come!
It'd be my first time since elementary school!
This year, I won't have to walk
through the streets, crying!
Long live, Yamato-san!
What a goddess!
Yamato, they're super happy.
Thank you.
Suna, you should come, too.
I knew you'd say that.
Takeo?
What's wrong?
Um, so...
Can I tell Nanako-chan at that Christmas thing?
Nanako-san?
Tell her what?
Well, tell her that I want to ask her out.
C'mon, read between the lines.
Since when?
So, can I?
Sure, why not?
Should we ask Yamato for permission, too?
Yeah, we should.
Please do that, thanks.
I see, he likes her now.
I hope you'll be happy together.
Give it your best shot!
Inbox
From: Takeo-kun
To: Yamato Rinko
Subject: Christmas
It's all good.
Everyone's happy.
Takeo-kun and his friends are on for Christmas!
Thanks, Rinko!
Let's exchange gifts!
A thousand-yen budget?
I want to go karaoke!
Nice!
Rinko...
Is Kurihara-kun coming, too?
Kurihara-kun? I'm not sure.
I'll try asking right now—
No, you don't have to ask!
You sure?
Rinko...
What does it mean if a guy
tries to hold your hand?
Huh?
Doesn't that mean he likes you?
That's what I'd think.
Well, actually...
Kurihara asked for my contact info,
and we went to a movie once...
And he held my hand.
What do you think?
Huh? Huh? I see!
Um, doesn't that mean he likes you?!
No, you can't be sure...
He hasn't said anything definite.
But wait!
If he didn't like you a little, he wouldn't
have asked you to the movies!
How do you feel about Kurihara-kun?
Huh?
Well...
If he asked, I guess I could go out with him.
Anything I can do to help?!
Huh?
No, it's fine.
Want me to ask Takeo-kun about it?
No, don't worry about it.
What should I get as a present?
Man, I need to work more hours.
Sorry, Takeo-kun!
I was waiting over there...
I love her.
So a reservation for twelve,
on December 24th, at 4 PM?
Yes.
Please wait a moment.
Look, Yamato!
There's a big Christmas tree in the courtyard.
Wow, it's beautiful.
Oh, the Christmas tree can
be seen from all the rooms.
It's even better at night!
Oh, and there's a story about that tree.
At the very top, there's one star
that's different from the rest.
Oh, that one.
Huh?
You can see it all the way
from here, Takeo-kun?
Wow
If you pluck that star and ask someone out,
they'll say yes.
Well, it's cold and your hands go numb,
so you can't really climb up there.
It's high and scary,
so no one's ever managed it...
Oh, but I think you might be able to.
No, I don't need it anymore.
So, you have your reservation,
but which karaoke room would you like?
That star should grant someone else's love.
Um, hello?
I'm so looking forward to Christmas!
We've all been talking about how we'd
like to exchange gifts and stuff.
That sounds good!
By the way, is Kurihara-kun coming?
Yep.
Oh, is Nanako-san coming?
Yeah.
Good, good.                               Okay, okay
You wouldn't hold hands with someone
unless you liked them, right?
Yeah.
Right, I should check in with Yamato.
Thanks~
Thanks!
Yamato, Kurihara said he likes Nanako-san.
Eh?
He'd like to ask her out on Christmas.
Is that all right?
Yeah, sure!
Let's give them plenty of
opportunities to be alone!
Yeah, that's right!
Let's help them out as best we can!
Okay?
Okay!
Good luck, Kurihara.
It's going to be a merry Christmas.
Christmas with Nanako-chan.
Kurihara
Yeah.
Christmas with Nanako-chan.
I'm over the Moon!
Hi!
Been a while!
Wow, Nanako-chan, aren't you
cold with bare legs?
Wow, great!
It's nice and big.
Sweet!
Hey, look outside.
Oh, wow!
There's a huge Christmas tree in the courtyard!
Toward the top of the tree, there's this
one star that's different from the rest.
They say if you take that star
and then ask someone out,
the person will say yes.
Huh...
That's way too high!
How many meters is that?
Hey, don't you think that
only Takeo could get that?
Nanako, can I sit next to you?
Ayu, sit here with me!
O-Okay.
Wow, I'm sitting next to Nanako-chan.
Lucky me!
Okay, Merry Christmas!
Cheers!
Nanako-chan, I can pass you
anything you want to try.
Thanks.
Oh, let me pour it.
He's meticulous.
I should try to learn from him.
What's wrong, Yamato?
You don't like it?
No, I don't like spicy food...
It was spicier than I expected.
I'll eat it for you.
Let me have it.
Eh?
Hmm?
Is this an indirect kiss?!
Sorry.
It's fine.
Takeo and Yamato-san make such a good pair.
Do you ever think about wanting
a boyfriend, Nanako-chan?
Huh?
Well, sure, like any other girl.
I bet you have high standards!
I think they're normal.
Really?
I bet they're sky high!
They're normal. What's your problem?
Kurihara...
What's he going on about?
Isn't he going to ask her out?
Hey, why don't we go see the Christmas tree?
Let's go to the courtyard!
Good job, Yamato.
You're trying to create a good mood.
So pretty!
It's much bigger than the one at home!
You guys have one?
Yeah, it goes up to the ceiling.
Wow! Can I come see?
Me, too!
No way...
I want to see.
Same here!
The girls can!
Hey!
Hey, let's take a photo.
Yeah, let's!
Okay, Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas!
It's pretty, but it's also super cold out here!
Let's go back inside!
Let's exchange presents!
Yeah, let's.
Come on! What're you waiting
for, Nanako-chan?
Kurihara...
What am I to you?
Huh?
Um...
Hey, close the door already!
Um, a friend?
Sorta?
Let's go!
You'll catch a cold!
Kuri
Na
We put everyone's presents in this
bag and tied ribbons to them,
so pull one ribbon each!
There's no way to tell who'll get whose present!
Okay!
Let's figure out the drawing order!
Should we just do rock-paper-scissors?
First comes rock...
I'm first.
Sunakawa-kun, just pick whichever you'd like.
Okay.
That's from me.
Thanks.
Next!
Um, okay, this one.
Oops!
That's Nanako's...
Maybe this one, then.
I'm next!
Pick this one.
Huh? O-Okay...
Oh...
Huh?
Is this from Nanako-chan?
Wow!
I picked Nanako-chan's gift!
Yay!
Hey, can I open this?
Xavier!
Okay, Nanako, you're next.
Um...
Okay, this one.
That's mine!
It went to Nanako-chan!
It's fate!
All right!
Let's sing, guys!
Yeah!
I don't really do songs,
so I'll just be on the tambourine.
I'll be on the maracas today, too.
We're the cheerleaders.
Can't catch up, but I want to.
Oh, this song's Kurihara's favorite.
Can one of the girls sing with me?
Nanako, you're good at this song, too.
I want to hear Nanako sing!
Yeah!
Here's the mic.
Yay, a duet!
I wish love would work out like sweets,
as long as you follow the recipe.
Come on, Nanako-chan!
I wish the distance between us would change
with time, just like meringues do.
Look this way, you two!
Calm and—
Yeah, take our photo!
A two-shot with Nanako-chan!
What's with you guys?
You're acting all weird!
Oh, really?
Can't catch up, but I want—
Suddenly, there's a story. Give me an answer.
The more clumsy and awkward we are...
I'll go!
Hey, shouldn't you go?
Okay.
Nanako!
What's wrong?
Hey, girls...
What're you doing?
You're here, just the two of you?
But it's Christmas!
Come join us in our room!
Huh?
I think I've seen her before...
Hey, have we met before?
This way, hurry!
Right! She's the urban legend's girlfriend!
Takeo-kun!
Hey, what happened?
Whew, that was scary...
Are you all right, Nanako-chan?
Why didn't you help me yourself?!
I hate that about you!
Nanako!
Wait, Nanako!
I shouldn't have told you!
Don't try so hard to get us together!
Not everyone can be like you guys,
all lovey-dovey and head over
heels about each other, okay?!
Sorry...
Takeo-kun...
I was wrong...
I guess this wasn't helping her at all.
I should have been more considerate
of Nanako's feelings.
You're right.
I was wrong, too.
My feelings are my own,
but that has nothing to do with how others feel.
I can't do anything about how they feel.
I really have to be more careful...
We have to learn how to just watch
over them without interfering.
Yeah.
That's what Sunakawa-kun did for us.
Like Suna.
Right, like Sunakawa-kun.
Being kind enough not to do anything...
To have the heart to watch over them
without saying anything—that's it.
Suna...
Where is she?
Well, for now, let's go back.
I mean,
how could one of me beat three of them?
I just thought it'd complicate things
and risk getting Nanako-chan hurt
or put her in danger, you know?
Be kind enough not to do anything.
I'm not that manly,
Have the heart to watch over them
without saying anything.
and I'm not as strong as Takeo.
Not that I have any confidence that
I could've talked my way out of it,
like Sunakawa might have.
Maybe I'm just below average in every way.
Be kind enough not to do anything.
Watch over them without saying any—
Or even lower, actually.
But maybe she wanted you to help, anyway!
Don't quibble!
Do you really think that?
I can't do anything about this now,
but you still can!
You're a man!
Incoming Call
Rinko
Rinko, I'm so sorry about what I said—
No, I'm sorry!
Nanako, you should know that Kurihara-kun's...
Go!
Thanks!
What are you doing, Kurihara?
Um, Kurihara-kun wants
to get that star for you!
Huh?
Hey, come on!
You okay?
Stop it already.
Kurihara!
You should stop.
Hey!
Hey, quit it!
You can't do it.
How many times have you already fallen off?
I'm gonna take that star and
ask Nanako-chan out...
When Yamato-san told us about the star,
Nanako-chan looked like she
wanted that to happen!
I acted like it was nothing because
I felt self-conscious about it...
I'm not strong like Takeo,
but I do want to show the girl I like
what I'm capable of as a man!
Kurihara!
Nanako-chan!
I got the star!
I'm not strong like Takeo...
I'm a pushover, and I tend to
just go with the flow,
but I do like you, Nanako-chan!
Please go out with me!
I'm not honest about my feelings like Rinko.
I can't bake cakes,
and I can be hard to get along with.
Is that okay?
I like that about you, too!
I like how you're a pushover, too!
Hey, 'grats.
Congrats, Nanako.
All right, a celebratory toss!
It's nice.
Huh? Me, too?
Hup!
Thank goodness...
I'm so relieved.
Yeah.
Oh, right.
Takeo-kun, this is a separate gift.
It's a stollen.
Oh, thanks!
Merry Christmas! Just kidding.
I love her.
Merry Christmas!
I love her so much.
Hup!
Closing Ceremony Today
Well, I always thought she had nice legs,
but when I just blurted it out
during our skating outing,
it totally rubbed her the wrong way!
When she looked at me like I was a worm,
I just fell for her right there.
I see.
And on the train ride home,
I didn't want to make any more wrong moves,
so I'd thrown both hands up in the air.
She was giving me this wry
smile that was so cute...
Oh, speak of the devil... It's Nanako.
"Nanako"?!
Hi!
I was just about to call you.
Wait, are you watching me?
Oh, no way!
I wouldn't do that!
So that's how...
...Nanako is...
...when she has a boyfriend.
Yeah.
I had no idea.
Yeah, I'll be waiting.
Later.
Osamu said his winter break starts tomorrow!
"Osamu"?!
We're all on winter break.
I bet Nanako and Kurihara-kun will
have their first kiss really fast.
Yeah, definitely.
Oh, a kiss?
We already had it.
Eh?
We kissed on our way back from
the Christmas get-together.
He just rushed me.
So fast!
Huh?
What's wrong, Rinko?
I wonder if I'm just not attractive like that...
What?
Tell me! I can help!
All of a sudden, she's acting superior
My Birthday
Next time: My Birthday.