Mornin', Hikari!
You're up early.
Yeah, I thought I'd head
to the store today.
I see.
I'm heading out!
What the heck?
And here I was looking
forward to leaving together.
Are you going to go end things?
Give up on the guy from the surface.
So you are a man of the sea after all...
I know.
Despite the sins the people...
The people of Shioshishio
since long ago...
The sacred fire is the
soul of the Sea God.
Uroko-sama...
The sacred fire is letting us know.
The sea and the surface should
make their boundaries permanent.
Eventually, the surface will...
The saltflake snow is just a prelude.
Though Akari is solely up to you.
It is not up to me.
Akari's life is her own.
Oh?
Since long ago from the
beginning of time...
Episode Five: Hey, Sea Slug
Chisaki's going to be late?
Yeah, she said she's not feeling well.
She didn't look like she was
feeling well on the way home yesterday.
It's pretty serious.
Serious?!
Nah, that's not what I meant.
If you tell a red-bellied sea slug
about feelings you can't tell anyone else,
it'll tell you what's going
to happen in the future.
Green...
Manaka's a really good girl...
And compared to that, I'm...
I need to do something
about my feelings for Hikari.
You're late.
Well, you're late, too.
We had a huge haul this morning.
We've been able to get a ridiculous
number of golden-eyes lately.
Where's everyone else?
I was late, so I had them
go ahead without me.
I see.
I'm really sorry about yesterday!
About what?
"What"?
Do you like Hikari?
Wh-What are you...
Well, yes, I do...
I mean, we're childhood friends,
and we've been together forever,
so he's like family...
I see.
Will you be a sea slug for me?
Huh?
I like him more than just
as a childhood friend.
But if I keep on liking Hikari,
I'm going to keep becoming
someone I don't like.
I'm not going to be able
to forgive mysel—
Stop.
Wait!
Manaka!
I-I'm sorry!
I was worried about you,
so I went back and...
I didn't hear anything, okay?
Like about me liking Hii-kun?
Right. Like about you liking Hii-kun.
Please forget about that, Manaka.
Huh?
Please, just forget about that. Okay?
But...
Please!
O-Okay...
Got it...
Hey, don't try to touch
me anywhere funny.
I'm not!
Come on, take this more seriously.
Don't blame me if you mess up
during the sports festival!
Wh-What?
You smell sweaty, Hikari.
I don't want to get close to you.
I don't want to get close to you either.
Ow!
Hey, sea girl, you're stepping on me!
Chii-chan...
I said that hurts!
Saya Mart
Akari.
I'd like you to hear me out.
Triangle
I think it's better if we break up.
I don't want to hurt Miuna-chan anymore.
You came to say that as
well, right, Itaru-san?
That's...
I've been wrong all this time
ever since Miori-san died.
Always Smiling
Saya Mart
All this time...
Aka-chan!
Miuna, you're heavy.
Hey, what's for dinner tonight?
Hey, Miuna.
Thanks for coming by all
the time, Akari-chan.
You don't have to
trouble yourself though.
It's fine.
Seeing Miuna-chan brings me happiness.
Happiness'll be a hundred yen!
What? You're charging me money?
It wasn't a lie.
Miuna-chan is very precious to me...
I wish things could
have stayed that way.
I wonder if it'll be okay
if we tell her about us.
It'll be fine!
Miuna loves you, Akari-chan.
And of course, I do, too.
Uh, well...
But it was a mistake...
Miuna!
"A mistake"...
Please don't say something so sad...
I didn't come to break up with you.
I just think we acted too fast...
Miuna likes you, too,
so if we just take our time—
No...
There's no need for time.
You've known what needs to
be done for a while, right?
Miuna-chan.
Wait.
It's okay.
I'll go away somewhere.
So you don't need to worry anymore.
I'm sorry for putting you
through so much pain.
Go Aw
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is Sakishima...
Can you ask Uroko-sama if there was a
small girl that fell into the ocean?!
Huh? Akari?
What are yo—
Miuna-chan hasn't come home yet!
Miuna?!
Her friend hasn't seen her either!
What am I going to do?!
This is all my fault!
It's my fault that Miuna-chan—
Calm down, Akari!
I'll find Miuna for you!
What are you talking about?!
It's already late, so leave
the searching to the adults...
You should be—
Don't treat me like a kid!
Huh?
No matter how much you
try to act like an adult,
you'll never be able to replace Mom!
Huh?
So... Hurry up and go be Miuna's new mom!
Hikari...
I confirmed with Uroko-sama.
She didn't fall into the ocean.
She's fine.
Old man...
Go.
All right, I'm hanging up.
Hikari!
Where the heck did she go?
I think only the area
near the mountain is left.
It's been getting chilly at night lately...
I wonder if she's okay.
Damn it, talk about a problem child.
Nothing less from the daughter
of that lecherous old ma—
What the hell do you think you're—
Don't say bad things about my dad.
Miuna!
Miuna-chan!
I'm not going home.
But...
your dad and everyone else
are really worried about you.
They're not worried.
Everyone's worried enough
to go looking for you!
I'm alone.
What should we do?
Oh, we have a futon for guests!
Miuna can't go to Shioshishio!
It is chilly at night,
but it's summer...
Miuna-chan!
Triangle
Akari!
Akari! They said they found Miuna!
Huh?
The fishery cooperative got
a call from Hikari-kun.
And apparently he wanted us to
leave everything to him for tonight.
He really... found her...
Akari? Are you all right?
I'm in love with you.
I love Miuna-chan and Miori-san as well.
Hikari dumped me, but I love him, too.
I love you all.
Akari?
It's just as Hikari says.
I'm a child.
I'm greedy.
I want to have everyone that I love.
I know what I should have done, but...
I just can't give up!
I don't want to give up!
Yeah...
I don't want to give up on
all of us being happy either.
Hey, I got some!
Oh, thanks.
Where'd you get all that?
This place was in business
until this spring,
so the pots and plates were left as is.
Huh.
Chisaki, you better make
a better meal than me.
We need to gut these.
Chii-chan...
Kaname and I will work on this,
so Manaka, could you go get
some more fish with Miuna-chan?
You too, Hikari. This isn't nearly enough.
Yeah, yeah.
Is this edible?
Oh, a sea slug?
I guess you could eat them, but...
Yeah...
I guess red ones are really rare.
So I guess the one the
other day was special.
Red ones?
You can eat the green ones, but
the red ones are for talking to.
If you tell it things that
you can't tell anyone else,
it'll tell you things or something...
Yeah...
Even if it doesn't,
I guess it can make you
feel a little better.
I know about something like that.
There's something I was
using instead of a sea slug.
Go Aw
Huh?
If you find a red one,
what will you tell it?
This is my special
miso soup, so eat up!
When I find a red sea slug,
what should I tell it?
You always make this whenever
something happens, Hikari.
Yeah, I'm starting to wonder
if that's all you can make.
I wonder... what I want answers to...
Then you make something!
Thanks for looking with me.
You sure it'll be okay?
Yeah, somehow things will work out.
See you.
Yeah.
Oh. S-See you.
They're pretty amazing,
aren't they? The stars.
So, hey...
Akari's a good person.
I know me saying that might
not mean much, but...
So don't hate her.
Nope. I'm going to.
You say you're alone,
but you have all these
people who love you.
I don't.
Yeah, you do. I mean—
I don't!
I don't want there to be!
The way you write Miuna
is "beautiful ocean."
Miuna
Mommy loves the ocean.
If you love it, why are you
living where there's land?
Because I love you more, Miuna.
I love you too, Mommy!
I love, love, love you!
That tickles!
What the hell do you
think you're doing?!
I can't swim!
Why?!
Mommy's from the sea!
Why can't I swim?!
Stop struggling!
You smell like Mommy and Aka-chan.
Aka-chan?
You mean Akari?
When Mommy died, I was full of
sad feelings in my stomach...
Like I couldn't breathe...
Aka-chan always stayed with me,
and I really started to like Aka-chan.
But... when they said Aka-chan
might be my new mom,
I got scared.
If Mommy... something that I love...
if they were taken from me again,
I wouldn't know what to do.
I don't want that sad feeling
in my stomach again.
If I didn't love them,
I wouldn't be so sad!
So... So I...
If you don't love them...
If you don't love them,
it won't be painful.
You might actually have a point.
Huh?
I can't really talk.
I sort of think it might be easier
not to love someone, too.
But, you know...
I don't want to think that it's hopeless
or useless to love someone.
Wh-What?
Do you have someone you love, too?
Well, yeah... a lot of them.
A lot?
Uh, yeah.
And now I like you a lot, too.
Hey! How long are you going
to hold me like this?
Oh, right...
Th-There you go.
Are you a dolicon?
"Doli"?
I heard that people who like grade
school girls are called "dolicons."
From Sayu.
That's lolicon, not dolicon!
And I'm not like that!
There's something I want
you to help me with.
Huh?
My... sea slug...
Saya Mart
You're early, Akari-chan.
Oh, well, I couldn't sleep, so...
My jaw hurts...
I wonder if I chewed too much gum.
Akari!
Stupid! Stupid Miuna!
A-Akari! Calm do—
Of course I'm not going anywhere!
I'm not going anywhere...
I'll always be by your side, Miuna!
I'll always be by your
side with Miori-san!
With... Mommy?
Yeah!
I can't replace Miori-san.
Even if I wanted to...
But...
I want to stay next to you as myself!
I'll be right here!
So... you stay as you are...
And please... let me stay
by your side forever...
Don't Go Away
Your eyes, Aka-chan...
They're so blue, and your
tears moving like waves...
They're so pretty. They're like the sea.
Miuna...
I...
love the sea.
Good grief...
Who's the kid here?
You're so big, Hiradaira-san.
I wonder where my strike zone is.
Apparently today's the
perfect day for Tomoebi.
That's way too fast...
Episode Six: Beyond Tomoebi