I...
Apology by Armed Detective Agency Member
Tanizaki Junichirou
I... I...
I'm so sorry!
Huh?
Though it was for your exam,
I was so rude to you.
My name is Tanizaki Junichirou.
I work as an assistant
of sorts at the agency.
Please, it's all right.
He's not a bad person, really.
And this is—
His little sister, Naomi.
Y-You're siblings?!
I'm not sure I see a family resemblance.
Oh?
You doubt us?
Of course we're siblings by blood.
We're quite similar, especially this part.
Right, brother?
Oh, but...
Don't pursue this line of
inquiry with them too far.
Atsushi reads
between the lines.
Er, okay...
In any event, brat,
today you have joined the ranks
of our Armed Detective Agency.
Do not be a burden to anyone,
nor shame the Agency's good name.
The rest of us are committed
to that, at least.
Right, Dazai?
Would you strangle me with these
fragile, delicate fingers?
Are you going to smear mud on the Agency's
name right as I'm saying we never would?!
You bastard!
Don't bother asking for
her help all the time!
I'll crush your neck with my own bony fingers!
By the way,
Two Senior Colleagues
Shaming the Agency's
Good Name
what were both of you doing
before you joined the Agency?
Uh, no real meaning behind
that question, by the way.
Take a guess.
Huh?
Oh, it's a game we play often.
The rookie tries to guess his senior
colleagues' former occupations.
Well, it's part of their training
as private investigators.
Tanizaki-san and Naomi-san... were students?
Oh, bingo.
I'm impressed.
How did you know?
I heard you are a part-time worker,
and I thought you might still
be a student given your uniform.
Tanizaki-san seems close to
me in age, so... just a hunch.
Honesty is a virtue.
What about Kunikida-kun?
Who cares about what I used to be?!
Public worker?
An official?!
Close.
He was a teacher.
A math teacher.
Huh...
Of course you'd use the
law of exponents here!
I can totally see that.
It's all in the past!
I don't even want to think about it.
What about me, then?
You, Dazai-san?
Yes, me.
Well...
Dazai-san was...
It won't work.
I have no idea.
Don't bother, brat.
His former profession is one of the seven
mysteries of the Armed Detective Agency.
The first person to get it
right receives a reward, right?
A reward?
That's right.
No one's been able to guess right,
so the reward's just ballooned.
Ballooned...
Reward!
B-By the way,
how much has this reward
ballooned to, exactly?
700,000 yen total.
Seven Hundred Grand!!
Seven hundred grand?!
Oh!
The Man has a fire
lit under him ——
S-So if I get it right, I can claim it?
at the thought of a
700,000 reward ——
Currently penniless.
For real for reals?!
A suicide proponent is true to his word.
Atsushi-kun looks excited.
His determination is admirable.
Seven hundred grand will be mine!
Speculator?
No.
Writer?
Nope!
Office worker?
Wrong!
Researcher!
No.
Lawyer?
No!
Journalist?
Boo.
Carpenter!
Nope.
Fortuneteller!
No.
Pilot!
Wrong.
It's all random...
Interpreter!
Non, non!
Yeah...
Japanese Chef.
Booo.
No way, doctor?
No way.
Shinto priest!
No!
Actor!
No! But...
That's flattering.
I bet you were just wandering
around doing nothing.
Nope.
I would never lie about this.
Do you yield, Atsushi-kun?
Then you can take the check.
What?
If you don't have enough on you right now,
you can start a tab.
After all, it's the
Agency's go-to restaurant,
the Vortex.
Yes, this is Tanizaki.
Yes, okay.
Got it.
We have a job?
Yes.
The client's already at the Agency.
Well, it's time to work.
Let's save the guessing
game for another time.
So...
You've mentioned that you'd like
to request an investigation,
but what manner of investigation
are we speaking of here?
Beautiful...
You're a lady as ephemeral and
elegant as a lotus blossom.
Would you be willing to join me
in a double suicide—
What?
Ah.
Apologies for the disturbance.
Don't worry.
Please disregard what just happened.
Please continue.
Regarding my request...
Y-Yes?
Wow.
She's managing to carry on as
though everything's normal.
Well, it seems there's
recently been a group of
distasteful people loitering in
my company building's back alley.
And by distasteful, you mean...
They appear to be dressed in rags.
Some of them have been heard
speaking a foreign tongue.
They must be smugglers or some such.
The military police may police all they want,
but they keep multiplying
like rats on a ship.
They're unavoidable in a port town.
Right.
If we had some evidence that
they're running afoul of the law,
we could reach out to the military police.
So...
You want us to stake out the
place and get that evidence.
Brat.
Huh?
You go.
What?!
It's a simple stakeout job.
Besides, smugglers are mostly harmless.
They're usually only good
at making a break for it.
It's the perfect first job for you.
But...
Tanizaki, go with him.
If he's going, I'm going, too!
Rookie Detective
Nervous About
His First Job:
Nakajima Atsushi
Hey, brat.
It's not that I lack sympathy for
your unlucky, ill-begotten life.
As such, I'll give you one hint
for surviving in this city.
Don't run into him.
If you do, run.
Who is he?
A mafioso.
Though we call them that because
we don't know anything else.
They're a vicious criminal organization
who claims the port as their territory.
They're called the Port Mafia.
They're the most dangerous bunch in
the underground world of this city.
Of them, the one in this photo
is a very dangerous man beyond
even this Agency's reach.
Why is he dangerous?
Because he's gifted.
His ability happens to be of the ruthless
sort specialized for slaughter.
Not even the military police
stand a chance against him.
I wouldn't want to fight him, either.
What's his name?
It's Akutagawa.
I found a bag on the ground.
I think it's been lost by its owner.
Ah, lost and found.
Then if you could fill out this form...
Hm?
I've seen you before.
That's impressive.
I've already been found out.
Wait, is he the wanted fugitive?!
Stop!
The military police of this
city are a distinguished force.
Excuse me,
could help me find—
Wanted
Akutagawa Ryuunosuke
Ability: Rashoumon
Yokohama Gangster Paradise
Done.
Next...
You can't do a double-suicide alone...
Hey, Dazai.
What about the job?
I'm waiting for a sign from above.
Huh?
With two, you can...
Double-suicide... Double-suicide...
That's scary, all right.
It's not funny.
All this talk about vicious
mafia and how you can die...
I'm not sure I'm cut out for this.
Well, even I've been able to manage.
You'll be fine.
But you're also gifted, right?
Your ability must be different
from my own useless one...
I wouldn't set your expectations too high.
My ability's not suited for combat.
You have a wonderful ability.
I love it.
Stop, Naomi.
Not here.
Oh, are you talking back to me?
I wonder what mouth's saying
such cheeky things...
We're here.
Huh?
This way.
It's kind of creepy.
That's strange.
Is this really the right place?
Um...
The name's Higuchi.
Higuchi-san.
Smugglers are a cowardly bunch.
They'll always have an escape route.
But this is a dead end.
If anyone came after them
from that direction,
they'd have nowhere to run.
That's right.
I apologize. I led you into a trap.
My real target was you!
Port Mafia:
Higuchi Ichiyou
Akutagawa-senpai.
Akutagawa?!
I have them, as planned.
Excellent.
I'll be there in five minutes.
She's...
...with the Port Mafia!
Brother... Are you okay?
Naomi?
Naomi!
God, what should I do?
Oh, right! Tourniquet!
Atsushi-kun, do you have
a tourniquet on you?!
No, first, I have to clean the wound...
No!
I have to get her to Dr. Yosano.
We... We have to take her to the infirmary!
Atsushi-kun, get her legs!
My investigations have already revealed
that you are a non-combatant member.
Let's have you follow the noble
princess to the afterlife.
What?
You two-bit thug...
How dare you hurt Naomi!
Ability: Light Snow...
Light Snow
Snow at this time of year?
Atsushi-kun, stay far back.
This one... is mine to kill!
What?
My Light Snow ability
transforms the entire space
with snowfall into a screen.
What?
I have overlaid the background
scenery onto my image.
You can't see me anymore!
I may not be able to see you,
but bullets can still hit you!
Wrong.
Die!
Fear death.
Fear slaughter.
Those who desire death
have an equal desire to die.
Therefore...
Don't run into him!
If you do, run!
It's nice to meet you.
I am Akutagawa,
one the Port Mafia's dogs, as is she.
Akutagawa-senpai!
I can handle this myself.
I believe my orders were to
take the weretiger alive!
And yet here you are, gunning everyone down.
You useless cur!
Stand down.
I'm sorry.
Take the weretiger alive?
What are you after?
My target has always been you
and you alone, weretiger.
Your fellow agents lying there
just got caught in the crossfire.
This is because of me?
Indeed.
That is your karma, weretiger.
You will cause ill for everyone
around you, just by being alive.
Get out, you good-for-nothing!
The world would be a better place
if you'd just die in a ditch somewhere!
You'll never find a place where you belong!
My karma?
Ability:
Rashoumon
Rashoumon.
I missed on purpose that time, of course.
But my Rashoumon has poor taste.
It devours anything and everything.
I intend to take you alive,
but if you continue to resist,
I'll take your leg next.
Why...
Why me?
Is this my fault, too?
Do I make everyone around me
suffer just by being alive?
A... Atsushi-kun.
Run, Atsushi-kun.
They're still alive.
Today you have joined the ranks
of our Armed Detective Agency.
Do not be a burden to anyone,
nor shame the Agency's good name.
Choosing death over surrender...
How tiresome.
That move wasn't half bad.
But in the end, it was a fool's last stand.
I told you.
My black beast is indiscriminate.
It devours anything and everything.
It consumed the very space bullets
were attempting to cross to reach me.
Neither spears or flames can reach me
without a space to traverse.
How is anyone supposed to attack him, then?
And I am a man who keeps his word.
Quit crying, brat!
Only children who have parents
to take liability for them
are allowed to cry without reservation!
A child abandoned by his parents
has no license to cry!
That's right...
I've been abandoned countless
times over the course of my life.
I was never allowed to cry,
no one ever accepted me,
and I never had a place I could call home.
And yet, I...
What?
His right leg regenerated.
This is how it should be.
Akutagawa-senpai!
Stand down, Higuchi!
What?
Senpai!
You...
The bullets can't pierce its skin...
Rashoumon...
Rashoumon
Agito
Agito!
I was supposed to take you alive...
This is...
So I just ripped apart a mirage... then...
Rashoumon...
Murakumo
Murakumo!
No Longer Human
Okay, that's enough!
What?
You're one of the detectives...
Why are you here?
I'm the type who can't stop thinking about
what a beautiful lady might be up to.
I decided to secretly listen in.
Impossible.
Back then...
You had already seen through
my plans even then.
Come on, wake up, Atsushi-kun.
I don't want to carry three
people back at the same time.
You think we'll let you go alive?
Don't, Higuchi.
You can't win.
But, Akutagawa-senpai...
Dazai-san, we'll retreat for this round.
But the weretiger will be
the Port Mafia's someday.
Why?
Simple enough.
That weretiger has a bounty
on him from the black market.
The bounty sum is seven billion yen.
Now, that's very generous.
We'll pay a visit to your
Agency at a later time.
The Port Mafia will claim that seven billion.
Is that a declaration of war
on the Armed Detective Agency?
Try it... if you dare.
You are an insignificant
small-scale operation,
whereas we are this city's
darkness made incarnate.
We have connections in this city's
politics and economy at every level.
An agency with a dozen or so operatives
will become ashes along with your entire
office in less than three days' time.
No one has opposed us and lived.
I know all that.
Indeed.
You know that better than anyone
being an ex-Port Mafia member, Dazai-san.
I heard, brat.
There's a bounty on your head to the tune
of seven billion on the black market.
Wh-Wh-What should I do?
Maybe the Port Mafia will
come raid the Agency.
But why me?
You caused this.
Think about what you can do.
What I can do?
Next time on Bungo Stray Dogs, episode 4:
The Tragedy of the Fatalist.
Episode 4: The Tragedy of the Fatalist