I can't find the will to do anything.
It's summer.
There should be plenty to do.
She only needed to be
an apprentice as a pretense.
So I bought her without much thought, and
I observed her without much thought.
I didn't think I'd need to do much more.
She was quite unusual,
and she was surprisingly quick to warm up to me.
But...
She doesn't speak much.
Seeing her that way, I'm filled
with two indescribable sensations.
Elias...
I was asleep.
It's done?
Is it done?
Lindel-san.
Then let's add the final touches.
You become sleepy because you've
unknowingly been using your magic.
The things we make are imbued with magic.
Ainsworth should have
taught you these things.
It's because I can't ask him.
I don't like giving him trouble.
Taking care of youngsters
doesn't even count as trouble.
You have no idea how much of
a pain in the ass he's been.
Years went by, but he still was terrible
at skiing, his soup was always burnt,
he never learned to restrain himself, and
he could never handle fire adequately.
You're far more deft and quick to learn.
What is that bonehead even...
Now, then, with your hair and this...
Gems?
I was given these by an
acquaintance a long time ago.
These stones are said to have been bathing
in sunlight and moonlight for a thousand
years at the bottom of a lake.
They're shining.
It's dim, but it ought to be enough to
light the ground beneath your feet.
I took the liberty of wrapping
it around the outside.
It has a beautiful sunset color, after all.
This is your wand.
Take good care of it.
Okay.
Where am I?
Hello, little mage. It has been some time.
You're...
Thank you for turning my
branch into your wand.
I'll use it well.
Where are we?
Why are we here?
Because we've established a bond
of fate through the wand.
A bond of fate?
We're at the border between travelers
and those whose travels have ended.
Those on the other side
and those on this side.
Those whose paths never
meet can intersect here.
So this is how it appears to your eyes.
What a beautiful path.
Does it appear differently to your eyes?
I am already dead.
I depend on the vision
of your excellent eyes.
You always appear unhappy, Chise.
How about it?
All that's here is an old geezer.
Why don't you try talking
to yourself out loud?
I've become greedy.
At first, I was content knowing I might
get kicked out at any moment.
So I tried not to depend on him.
I was comfortable, because
I knew he thought nothing of me.
Because he called me family,
even if it was only for show.
But...
at some point, it began to upset me
that he—Elias—wouldn't talk to me.
I became lonely and scared.
I don't know why I couldn't stay distant.
That way, I wouldn't have had to be worried.
I could have given up, no matter
when he'd thrown me out.
I realize it's tasteless of me to respond
when you're just talking to yourself.
But is your Elias someone who
would suddenly throw you out?
Has he said such a thing?
Has anything happened, even
once, to give you cause for worry?
No.
Then you need to stop worrying
as though the sky is falling.
But he might change his mind,
even if he's okay now.
He might get bored of me.
Just like she did.
Once he doesn't need me...
Shall I speak aloud to myself, too?
I'm thankful to Chise's mother and father.
When a creature is struggling to survive,
it often abandons or kills its young.
If it can stay alive, it can
have another child someday.
Still, Chise's mother released
her hands off of her neck.
Why?
Why did she not kill Chise?
Why did she kill herself instead, despite
wishing she hadn't given birth to Chise?
How would I know?
Because Chise came to see me, I spent
my last moments flying through the sky.
There were people and creatures
that were saved by Chise.
A child was saved because
Chise called them over.
To value oneself so little,
as though one were disposable,
is to say that those of us they've
saved are just as worthless.
That's not...
I...
I wasn't even trying to do that.
Be that as it may,
there are times when a simple word spoken
or a hand offered saves another.
So I find myself wanting you
to be proud of yourself.
You yourself, because you were able
to offer your hand to someone.
And I thank your mother and
father for leaving you with us.
Nevin...
You said my name.
Thank you.
It's a lovely name given to me by Lindel.
Hatori Chise,
you are free.
Even if you should be burdened by a curse
and eventually fall, that, too, is your choice.
Therefore, I want you to think—not for
another—but about what you want to do.
That wand is my wand.
No matter where you are,
it will light your way.
You can go anywhere.
Myself, Lindel, even that child of thorns...
Everything is connected, and all will return
here to set forth on a new journey.
Nevin...
It's only a brief farewell.
Oh, right, you should be quick to
say what you wish to say or hear.
Some words ripen with age,
but some also lose their color.
Chise.
You seemed out of it.
Are you all right?
I met with Nevin.
With Nevin?
Thank you for the wand and shelter.
I have to return home right away,
so I'll be going now.
I'd like to thank you later.
I don't mind, but what's happened?
There's something I want to tell Elias.
I want to make the best of the
encouragement he gave me.
All right.
I'll call Gwee.
Ruth.
Chise.
I can go anywhere.
Everything is connected.
Then...
Please.
Connect me to him.
Are we going?
We're flying.
I'll help you.
I'll give you a hand.
Let's fly there.
The wings of flame will
take us around the world.
On these wings...
Oh, dear.
I thought she was a quiet girl, but
she might actually be a wolverine.
Chise.
I was supposed to come home the way you do,
but the fairies were...
I... I mean, my wand's finished,
so I wanted to come home early.
So I got their help and used magic.
See? Lindel-san finished it for me, too.
You sure are pretty reckless.
Welcome home, Chise.
I'm home, Elias.
I thought so.
Do you have any idea how far
the land of dragons is?
You're an idiot to try to come by magic.
An idiot...
I thought I'd be fine,
especially with the wand.
Just get some sleep.
But...
I can't wait to tell him.
It's warm.
Mom.
There's a scary thing.
You're right.
You can't let it scare you, though.
The more scared you are,
the more you'll attract.
But I'm scared.
Don't worry.
Dad will keep them away.
You say that, but you were
scared stiff at first.
Shut up!
You're a big sister now,
Chise. You can handle it, right?
Yeah.
Good for you, Chise.
Good girl.
I was dreaming.
Mom wasn't crying.
She wasn't even angry.
I forgot that had even happened.
Morning, Chise.
Morning, Ruth.
What's going on?
Oh, this is bad.
They need to get lost. My urge
to chase them is rising.
Oh.
It looks like you had a good dream.
Yeah.
Stare...
Morning, Silky.
Chise.
Morning.
Good morning, Elias.
Good thing you woke up in just two days.
What's going on?
It's shearing season.
It's strange.
Until just recently, I could have never
imagined being in such a warm place.
But...
Now...
Chise.
Coming.
Delicious.
The girl returns to the mage,
and the story begins anew.
What does the visitor in
the moonlit night bring?
Is the master of the house available?