Hey! Welcome back.
I thought you'd be back before us.
What are you doing?
Throwing an after-party.
Not a review session?
Yeah, you could call it that.
Go get changed.
All that talk about sportsmanship...
In the end, they just play dirty.
I know. I understand how you feel.
Someone elbowed me as soon as we started.
Someone pushed my back.
It made me lose all desire to run.
Everyone's desperate to secure a good position.
If it's a race for the best time,
we should run one at a time
and then compare results.
They can't do that.
Kakeru, you don't get it, do you?
Huh?
These complaints.
There was no one running near you.
You were running alone.
That's not true.
I felt bad to be wearing
the same uniform as you.
It was fantastic.
You finished third in your first race.
I heard lots of people asking,
"who was that?" after the race.
Yeah. Everyone was talking
about you, especially the girls.
Lucky. I wish I had the girls' attention.
Kakeru.
Good work.
Yeah!
Run with the Wind
How did we do?
How were today's results?
What did you guys think?
He doesn't want to comment.
It didn't go as well as I'd hoped.
It was fun at first.
But I couldn't get the right pace.
It really hurts when there
are winners and losers.
Isn't our goal to achieve official records,
so we can run in the Hakone Ekiden qualifier?
Since none of us did, it was a crushing defeat.
Huh? Didn't Kakeru and Haiji make it?
You don't need to count them.
We should. They're on the team.
I didn't even beat my personal
record from practice.
Races and practice are different.
If anything, experiencing the
difference was a major achievement.
We'll overcome that in
our upcoming practices, and...
Running like this...
We will make it in time running like this?
Of course.
In two weeks, we'll attend
the Kikui Uni track meet.
We'll practice even harder to prepare for it.
Even harder?!
We'll start on a new training
schedule tomorrow,
increasing both distance and speed.
Can't we have tomorrow off?
I agree. You need to cool down after a race.
There's no need to rest an entire day.
Long distance running is
all about practicing every day.
I don't mind starting right now.
Right now?
I've been drinking.
I'm saying we should be taking
today's results just that seriously.
We're running at Hakone, aren't we?
Hey, what's gotten into you?
Don't worry. We all intend to.
Then what are we doing now?
A review session?
This is just a party, isn't it?
I thought it was a review session.
Me, too.
You had too much to drink.
I think this kind of thing is necessary, too.
Yeah. After all, we're a team.
We'll practice hard starting tomorrow.
I'm telling you, we should take tomorrow off.
I think it's supposed to rain.
Your jeans do absorb a lot of water.
Don't be ridiculous!
Dangerous Character
It's not that I don't understand how you feel.
But I understand how they feel, too.
It takes courage to face something head on.
That's something you should
have by the time you start.
Sure, you do.
It's amazing that you were
able to compete with Fujioka.
You must've been incredible.
Not at all.
There was nothing I could
do during that final lap.
There was nothing we could
do from our first lap.
That's why we should be
taking this more seriously.
Hey, Kakeru. What should I do?
Huh?
I'm too heavy.
Should I shed some flesh or shed some bone?
Issues of build are—
They exist.
You know that, don't you?
Running today reaffirmed something for me.
My body's not suited to long distance.
I ran every day,
but it was a close race between me
and King, who took some time off.
Is that why you quit running?
In high school, yeah. My coach told me to quit.
Oh, I don't resent him for it.
If anything, I felt relieved then.
But that means you were frustrated, right?
That's why you told me.
It means you can't give it up.
Maybe you're right.
I was frustrated, but it's also
the reason I was happy, too.
That feeling when you start...
I never thought I'd get to taste that again.
Then you should keep running.
Let's both give everything we have.
Where's Kakeru?
He went ahead without us.
Seriously? So we're back to how we started?
He wants to run at his
own pace starting today.
Nico-chan Senpai said he wanted
to try running at his own pace
during morning practice, too.
What? You sure he didn't just skip?
Kurahara!
Shut up!
It sounds like this thing
is groaning! It's creepy!
But my legs...
My butt is cramping.
You're gonna curse us!
You guys don't need to be here.
Yeah, but we can't move anymore.
Maybe we can take a bath tomorrow.
Let's do that.
Isn't that what you said yesterday?
I found it.
A treadmill?
Yes.
Ugh, but it's expensive.
Is that what you've been shopping for?
Yes. There must be a cheaper one somewhere...
Hurry it up. You should go to Yuki's room.
He'd never let me in his room.
You're right, especially
not if they went with you.
Jota, right there.
I'll try the same spot.
Oh, it's so good.
That's gross!
Why are you in such a bad mood?
Is it withdrawal?
Anyway, Prince, does this
mean you want to run now?
No, but he's been pestering us
to practice all the time.
I'd like to at least be able
to read comics while I do.
This mouse is so hard to use.
No, it's not a mouse!
What is this?!
What? Shut up already.
This!
Yikes.
It's so I wouldn't accidentally smoke.
It's just like Rikiishi!
Huh?
Are you a fan of Joe?
That's not what I was trying to do.
What's Rikiishi?
You don't know, you idiots?
He's a boxer. Joe's first,
and greatest, rival.
In order to lose weight, he didn't allow
himself to drink a single drop of water.
He's a legendary boxer who ultimately
died while standing in the ring.
Whoa.
That's it?!
What? Nico-chan Senpai, are you okay?
Don't die while standing
during the Hakone Ekiden.
Don't say such ominous things.
You've touched my heart.
How?
I won't be beat!
I'm gonna buy a treadmill!
Finally!
Add to Cart
The buy button is so far...
Go, go, Prince! Go, go, Prince!
Shut up! Go to the second floor!
Stay out of my room!
Our fixed-pace runs are twice as long.
The build-up runs have increased a lot, too.
I considered each of you individually.
We'll increase the intensity
of practice in any way we can.
Let's try it. I'm sure we can do it.
Yeah.
Hold on. Is that okay?
Build-up runs are speed training, right?
They're exhausting and hard on your legs.
What?
Yuki, you finally feel like running?
No! I'm just worried about you guys!
I knew you cared.
If we injure ourselves, we'll have nothing.
Yuki's right.
Some of you will struggle with build-ups,
so I've incorporated interval runs, as well.
What?! You're adding more?
Were you listening to what Yuki said?
Let's do it. We're wasting time.
Let's split into two groups.
You can do it. You've got this, Prince.
I can do it?
What do you think I can do?
Run on the left!
Ugh
Clear the path!
Okay...
What?
Are you running tonight?
Are you going jogging tonight?
Oh, uh...
We're exhausted from practice today.
Then, even though we've stepped up
practice, we won't have gained anything.
But...
We were jogging at night for other reasons.
The fan club, right?
Have you been gaining members?
Slowly.
But I'm too exhausted to recruit.
Kakeru, behind you!
Hey, watch out!
Be careful.
Practice lasts until we get home.
Teacher says the field trip
lasts until we get home.
You've got energy to spare.
I'm really thinking about quitting today.
Let's keep going. We shouldn't
quit what we've started.
He sure is fast, isn't he?
Whoa!
It's so hot!
This is it! This feels great!
The bath is hell,
but the sauna is pretty bad, too.
Don't forget to hydrate.
I'm sure you know, but Nico-chan
Senpai's pushing himself too hard.
Kakeru's egging him on.
Egging him on?
He used to run track.
Having a fast guy tell him he can do it
probably makes him feel like he can.
I think it's dangerous.
What's the hardest part about section 8?
Too easy. The Yugyo-ji Temple Slope.
Correct.
Yeah!
What else? What else you got?
Oh, uh...
King seems to be doing well.
When he mentioned the Ekiden
in his afternoon interview,
it was apparently received very well.
It's working for him.
Thanks for the food.
That was quick.
Did you get enough to eat?
Sure I did.
Food tastes better since I stopped smoking.
It's important to let your muscles rest.
I'm fine. I got plenty of rest this past month.
Lead the team with him.
With him?
Aren't you going for Hakone?
Oh, right. Prince.
The twins told me you
were looking for a treadmill.
Yes.
My family's got one they don't use.
I'll have them ship it here.
What?!
You should've said so sooner!
That's great, Prince.
Is... Is such a miracle possible?!
They're keeping it in the shed.
They were going to throw it away.
Oh, god!
What's wrong?
Nothing. When one door shuts, another opens.
That's not quite right.
Oh, God!
Ogre Shipping
Chikusei-so
My alphabetical order, my alphabetical order...
This is surprisingly new.
And it's free?
You got a great deal, Prince.
Let's turn it on!
I-It's too fast! Slow it down!
I can't! I can't!
Wow! I've never seen Prince move so much!
I can't do this!
Wow! Oh, wow!
What is that sound?
I'm going to the field.
Damn it.
You can do it!
Keep it up!
Two weeks until the next meet, huh?
How are you feeling?
What is this? An interview?
I'm getting into shape right now.
14:50:02.
That's crazy fast.
Okay.
Joji, don't give up!
You can pass him!
Wait. Are you sure that's right?
Huh?
50:02? I don't think that's possible.
What? But...
That's the same as two weeks ago!
It doesn't make sense!
What's his problem?
Fine.
I'll run it again. Time it correctly this time.
Kakeru!
Keep to the schedule.
And Hana's times are accurate.
Sorry.
What?
You don't need to run at the next meet.
Only the members who haven't
achieved official records will attend.
Why?
Is it because my time hasn't improved?
In that case, it's better that I run.
If I run, I can get back in shape.
It's pointless.
You can't see yourself right now.
Then where can I leave my record?
There's always more track meets.
In the first place, we've
focused our aim on Hakone—
Are you telling me to waste an entire year?
It'll all be for nothing
if I don't leave a record.
Are records everything?
What?
Is running for you all about speed
and abandoning those who fall behind?
We're competing.
We're not even guaranteed to run
in the Hakone Ekiden qualifier.
Matching their half-assed speed
won't make me any faster.
No one here is running half-assed!
Why won't you try to acknowledge
that everyone's trying their best?
Is it because they're slower than you?
Is speed the only thing that matters to you?
Then there's no reason to run.
Ride a bullet train. Ride a plane.
They're faster.
Wake up, Kakeru.
It's not enough to just chase speed.
It's... futile.
What?
Are you guys fighting?
You weren't sleeping?
I got thirsty.
Excuse me.
Kakeru. We're not done talking.
Prince.
If you're only able to achieve
the same time at the next meet,
will you quit the team?
What?
Please. For the team.
Next time: "Mismatched Runners."
Mismatched Runners