My name is Shinka Nibutani.
I am a Year Two student
at Icho Private High School.
I'm a little bit of a klutz,
and can be stubborn...
...but everyone says I'm very dependable.
Okay, time to go.
Oh, Nibu. Morning!
Morning.
Morning, everyone.
What? We had math homework?
Haven't you done it either, Becky?
I was counting on you.
Fukachi? Becky?
Would you like to see my notes?
Are you sure?
MATH
Shinka Nibutani
Here.
Thanks, Nibu!
I have no boyfriend. It's so lonely.
No straight-out copying, okay?
But to be honest, I'm not all that
interested in romance right now.
Yeah, I know.
Aren't these answers above
your grade, Fukachi?
After all, I have a grand dream.
What do you mean by that?
Yes, my grand dream.
A dream I want to become reality
during my time in high school.
STUDENT COUNCIL ELECTION,
PRESIDENT OF STUDENT COUNCIL,
VICE-PRESIDENT, TREASURER, SECRETARY
I'll tell you what it is.
Working for the student council work
is very rewarding.
You devote yourself for benefit of
everyone in the school.
Would anyone like to be a candidate?
PRESIDENT OF THE STUDENT COUNCIL
You can do it, Shinka!
Dreams can come true!
85TH ANNUAL STUDENT COUNCIL ELECTION
I was going to stop there on the way home.
What do you say?
Shinka Nibutani
Backers?
That's right.
Would you write your name on this register?
I guess I could do that.
The Election For President Of The
Student Council (Queen Maker)... Of Purity
Okay, thanks.
School: Wicked Lord Shingan, S Class
Name: Rikka Takanashi
What is that girl writing?
Also, now that I'm a candidate...
...I won't be making any appearances
at Club Whatchamacallit.
You could at least remember the name
of the club you belong to.
Image is important in an election.
If people knew I belonged to that club,
it would harm my reputation.
Why the student council of all things?
Weren't you working hard in the theatre club?
That place is lacking somehow.
Not again.
I don't know what it is. The magnetic field?
The spiritual wavelength?
It just doesn't feel right.
Maybe the guardian spirits are
taking a different position on it.
Can you hear yourself?
Naturally, that has nothing
to do with chunibyo!
I was only speaking in general, that's all!
Well, I won't try to stop you.
But you keep going on about your reputation.
People are already talking about you.
Like how you chased after a freshman,
dressed as a witch.
And how you threatened a freshman with
physical harm, dressed as a martian...
...and how you were trampled by a freshman,
dressed as a bug.
They could think you're a complete weirdo.
Those freshmen are all the one and the same!
In other words, she is my only problem.
Sanae Dekomori, servant to
Wicked Lord Shingan, is here!
I will defeat you today, once and for all!
Ow. Speak of the devil.
What were you secretly discussing?
I can only assume that you were
plotting petty wickedness!
Why would I do that?!
On this day, my attack power is doubled!
Prepare yourself!
Take this! The Mjolnir Megaton Hammer!
I already calculated your range.
Nice try!
What?
Did you see that? Now you are mine!
What're you doing?
NURSE'S
OFFICE
Do something!
Who, me?
I'll be going from class to class...
...to introduce myself as candidate
to the freshmen after school.
She'll be sure to interfere if she's around.
So you say.
You can do this.
Just get Takanashi to tell
that idiot to knock it off.
So you're telling me to ask Rikka?
You're her boyfriend, right?
You're going out, right?
"Rikka, if you love me..."
"...you'll do this for me."
One little whisper, and she'll do it.
I can't say that! And why the heck
do I have to do that for you?!
Help me!
I helped you lots when you
told her how you felt about her.
Sure, but nobody asked you to.
I went all the way to Rikka's parent's
house to help you, didn't I?
Sure, but nobody asked you to.
And what about that last date?
Nobody ever asked you to!
"Ghelzonianses."
Where did you hear that?
Takanashi said she found it among
your notes the other day.
It's the Dark Flame Master's
secondary form, right? Ghelzon...
Stop it! In all of my dark history,
that is uniquely embarrassing!
Is it? Okay then...
Far-East Magical Napping Society -
Summer Thereof
Why am I doing this?
Ooh, the Dark Flame Master has descended.
It would appear, that due to the urging
of the Wicked Lord Shingan...
...the Dark Flame Dragon that
resides within me has become active.
Ooh! Is this an omen of your
transformation into Ghelzonianses?
Uh, no, I...
...no, it'll keep.
Especially this evening.
At twilight, my heart will
pound like a hammer...
...and my entire body will heat up
like a raging fire!
Be still, my arm!
Understood. Leave it to me.
Not yet! It's too soon!
Dekomori will join you in battle!
Be destroyed, real.
Blow up, synapses.
Banishment, This World!
You came, Wicked Lord Shingan.
Forgive me. I cannot seem to control myself.
Is the Dark Flame Dragon...
...attempting to absorb you,
Dark Flame Master? If so...
Avalon Smasher!
Wait!
Where is Dekomori?
She vanished!
Did she fall through
the loophole of the parallel world?
She just kind of ran from the room...
...when I mentioned that Mori Summer
was visiting the freshmen's classrooms.
This is bad!
Don't!
We must do something before the
Dark Flame Dragon overtakes you!
Avalon Smasher!
Wait! Wait!
Yuta, hold still. This
will require careful aim.
I'll be going now.
Her classroom is next.
I hope that Togashi is keeping her
in check like I asked.
Yes! She isn't here! Thank you, Togashi!
2-4 Shinka Nibutani
Pleased to meet you.
My name is
Shinka Nibutani from Year Two...
...and I am here as candidate
for president of the student council.
I am here today to present my candidacy.
This really takes me back.
This was my classroom last year.
On the day of the entrance ceremony
,
I actually came to this classroom by mistake.
Okay, the connection is made.
Now all I have to do is impress them
with my dependability.
Anyway, I can be a bit of a scatterbrain...
...but I love my school more than any...
U-um, well...
Well, I love my school more than...
...anyone!
I hope for your honest vote...
Ow!
Your honest vote for Shinka Nibutani.
Thank you for...
...for your time!
Togashi!
You're blaming me?!
Of course I am!
To add insult to injury...
...you were being mushy with Togashi
in the club room!
Watch what you say!
Kumin-senpai, I wish you wouldn't
leak incorrect information.
But you were trying to summon
the Dark Flame Dragon.
Going "Ooh! Aah!" the whole time.
Enough of the impersonations.
I will not allow an imposter
to rule the campus!
You guys are disturbing the other patrons.
Rikka, make Dekomori stop.
That was close.
Order yours without in the first place!
Hero?
Shichimiya!
Stop that!
Sorry, I couldn't help it.
Shichimiya?
Sophia!
Mori Summer! Long time no see!
You go to the same school as Hero.
Are you 1,216 years old now?
Are you the Devil?!
W-w-who might you be?
My name is Catherine Suzuki.
You chose to be a half?!
So you transferred to the middle school
Nibutani was attending?
Yeah. As a magician
who has lived for 1,200 years,
Mori Summer fought in this world
alongside the magical devil girl.
Don't worry.
As long as you abide by the teachings
in the Mabinogion...
...you can save everyone in the world.
Really?!
Yes, so you must pray.
I made this crystal potion for you.
Wow, thank you!
Sophia, I am sure the angel is nearby.
Yes!
Stop!
Stop it, Nibutani! The wall is innocent.
I guess that means that you're really
Mori Summer, Mori Summer.
Be wary, Kumin.
The magical devil girl
has been known to use illusion.
Exactly! She couldn't
possibly be the true one.
What? But Mori Summer is 100% Mori Summer.
I declare it to be so on Satan's name. Look!
Would you look at that!
Stop it!
Are you really still doing
that stuff at your age?
Grow out of it already.
The magical devil girl is eternal!
The words "Grow out of it"
are not in my dictionary!
It's really her?
No, this isn't enough to
determine her legitimacy.
Mori Summer is far more noble...
Th-this hand accessory.
It's the same!
The multicolored gemstones are unmistakable.
Which means...
Huh?
My name is Sanae Dekomori.
I am a Year One student at
Icho Private High School.
In this world, I am 15
years and 8 months old.
Morning, Deko!
Oh, good morning!
We start out with Phys Ed.
Yes. Mornings are difficult
due to lowered magical power.
I have been proactive in the battle
in the parallel world as
my master's servant...
Magic?
Oh, come on.
...until I had a shocking encounter!
I'm sorry, I must go ahead.
Um, sure.
Yes, until my chance encounter...
...with the mentor of my soul, my other master,
Mistress Mori Summer!
Good morning!
Morning.
Mistress Mori Summer?
Dekomori respects Mori Summer
only second to myself.
Naturally, she calls her Mistress.
I told you, Deko.
I can't tell people who I really am...
...so you can't call me Mori Summer.
You're right. Very well, Nibutani-senpai.
Yes, well done.
Now I, Dekomori, must head to class.
I will come to see you on my breaks, Moris...
I mean, Nibutani-senpai!
I'm amazed!
I guess, but it's exhausting.
She keeps coming to see me
on every single break.
Wouldn't she obey you if you told her
to keep her distance?
I tried already. This is what happened.
Mistress Mori Summer...
Mistress Mori Summer, do you...
Do you not like me anymore?
Um, no, it's not that.
Why does she have to cry?
That girl is way too edgy.
I just knew it, Mori Summer.
You do like Dekomori.
What makes you say that?
But won't this make the student
council election easier to do?
Well, sure, she'll probably listen
to me if I ask her not to interfere.
Student Council Election
Special Edition
Not that. Ask her to help you...
...and I'll bet she'll be really helpful.
Remember how she said she was
popular with the freshmen?
Dekomori is an excellent servant.
As her master, I would be willing...
...to temporarily put her at your disposal.
But if you did that...
...she might just stay on as
Mori Summer's servant for good.
I see. This is my chance
to ask her to assist me.
What?
Of course! Please allow me to assist you!
Really?
Yes! For I know.
Mistress Mo... I mean, Nibutani-senpai.
Once you are president,
you will convert this
school to Shangri-La protected by the spirits
as it is recorded in the Mabinogion.
Keep that secret!
Everyone will find out who I really am.
Yes, you're right.
So can I count on your help then?
Yes, ma'am!
Good afternoon, everyone.
I am Shinka Nibutani, and I am a candidate
for president of the student council.
Thank you for your support!
I will make three promises to you,
to make your student life even better.
I am Makoto Isshiki, and I am a candidate
for president of the student council.
Vote for Makoto Isshiki!
Now, it is done.
Wow, you're good at artwork too.
I Am Serious About Your Future -
SHINKA NIBUTANI
Nibutani-senpai's poster is kind of sublime.
You can tell how much Deko
respects her by looking at it.
Yeah, for sure.
Yay!
Thank you. I owe it all to you, Deko.
I never dreamed I would get
so much freshman support.
Yes, ma'am! You have a 70% approval rating!
When did you guys become such good friends?
I-I didn't do anything.
What are you saying?
I, Dekomori and Mistress Mori Summer...
...have been bound together by
the holy ribbon for over 300 years!
Isn't that right, Mistress Mori Summer?
What? Uh, yes. That's right.
Dekomori, the moon looks blue tonight.
We will summon the demon beast
and go hunting together.
Really?
But...
I am terribly sorry!
Today, I have an important meeting to attend
with Mistress Mori Summer.
I will accompany you on the
very next opportunity, I swear!
Sorry about that. Well, let's get going.
Yes, ma'am. Goodbye.
Togashi?
Oh, brother.
Rikka?
All right. I'll look at it with you.
Really?
But only after you've done your homework.
For some reason, you say
the same things as the Priestess.
Are you in collusion?
No!
So, this is your room, Mistress Mori Summer?
It looks very common.
Mistress Mori Summer, do you keep your
true identity secret from your family?
Y-yes.
And you can bear the loneliness?
I am impressed.
Th-thanks.
Now, about my campaign speech
for the all-candidates' debate...
Yes, I am halfway through writing it.
Yes, this should work.
Thank you so much!
Also, um...
I made cookies.
Hey, is this me?
Yes.
D-do you like them?
These are good.
Really?!
What a relief.
I didn't notice it through all of her
spiteful comments...
...but she's surprisingly
genuine and thoughtful.
She might actually be really nice.
LOCKED
AWAY
My name is Mori Summer.
I am a magician who has lived for 400 years.
I have heard the whisperings of the spirits,
and have come to grant you my council.
Mistress Mori Summer...
I finally met you.
What is it that troubles you?
Please confide in me.
Deko, no cell pics.
Just one photo.
Please allow me this one photo
of your glorious presence.
Deko.
I beg you! Just this one photo!
Just this one!
Oh, all right.
Mistress Mori Summer!
Master!
Master... Master...
I'm sorry about everything till now.
C'mon, stop crying.
Appear to me, Demon Beast!
Reveal to me the resting place that I seek!
At this rate, Nibutani really is
gonna win the election.
President of the student council.
President of the student council?
Shichimiya?
Are you the Demon Beast? Yuta, stand back!
Hey, no pulling!
Yuta, the bath is ready.
85TH ANNUAL STUDENT COUNCIL ELECTION
ALL-CANDIDATES DEBATE
A man always strives to reach the top!
A man always has ambition!
I, Makoto Isshiki, will go to the top
to be your dictator!
Thank you!
85TH ANNUAL STUDENT COUNCIL ELECTION
ALL-CANDIDATES DEBATE
Isshiki, where are you going with that?
We're next. Are you nervous?
Did you remember to bring the draft?
I'm fine! I have the draft right here.
Yesterday, I revised the previous version
of the speech
to convey your information to the masses
with more accuracy...
85TH ANNUAL STUDENT COUNCIL ELECTION
SHINKA NIBUTANI SUPPORT SPEECH
Sanae Dekomori
...and to change public perception.
Now the draft carries
a much more powerful message.
What? Oh.
Next up is Miss Sanae Dekomori, who is
Shinka Nibutani's campaign speech manager.
Here! I'm going in.
Candidate for President of the Student Council,
Year Two, Shinka Nibutani
Good afternoon.
I am Sanae Dekomori, and I am
Shinka Nibutani's campaign speech manager.
I will now convey the words spoken by
Mistress Mori Summer...
...warm and beneficial words,
to you, comrades all.
Chapter one, paragraph three.
The world is composed of love's
divine providence.
85TH ANNUAL STUDENT COUNCIL ELECTION
ALL-CANDIDATES DEBATE
I have spent the last 400 years
observing the internal workings
of the hearts of mankind.
War. Hate. Strife.
I can't help but wonder why mankind
continues these actions?
Join me, everyone.
The spirits are always nearby
delivering their love!
Stop it!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Senpai?
Nibutani...
The critical hit?
85TH ANNUAL STUDENT COUNCIL ELECTION
RESULTS: PRESIDENT: Hitomi Ubushiro
DROPOUT: Shinka Nibutani,
Makoto Isshiki, Kenta Tanaka
Nibu didn't come today?
I think she stayed home.
Far-East Magical Napping Society -
Summer Thereof
I nearly fell for her deception!
Just like that?!
Of course!
The Mabinogion is gospel!
The words of this book caused her to suffer!
Proof that she is an imposter!
Exactly.
You are the only master for me, Master.
My master!
My servant!
Good for them.
This is good?
Nibutani?
She's gloomy.
Give that back.
You showed yourself, imposter!
Shut up! That Mabinogion is to
blame for everything!
Hand it over!
Do not talk righteously to me, imposter!
Just hand it over!
I will never give it to an imposter!
Milk - Full Of Calcium
Just give it up already! Got it?!
Stop! Stop it!
It's much more relaxing this way.
You find this relaxing?
Now hand it over!
To Be Continued