Let's go!
Doryo Bridge
Feels so good!
Next!
Kousei! Go!
I don't think so...
You'll go if you're a man!
It's gonna change
your whole world!
But I have a lesson...
My mom's gonna yell at me...
*Irritated*
Shoulder wheel backdrop!
Tsubaki?
Kousei?
Hey, he can't swim!
Kousei!
He came to!
Again! Again!
Aha! He's addicted now!
Kao-chan, we came
to pay you a visit...
Kou         Tsubaki         Watari
The nape of her neck!
Ever heard of knocking?
Her skin's so fair!
Delete that memory!
Oh, wow, what a shock.
Now I can never
be anyone's bride!
Totsuhara University Hospital
You really threw us a curve,
getting hospitalized like this.
Well, my dad's so over-the-top.
I'm only here for routine
testing, just to make sure.
Have you ever passed
out like that before?
It's the first time.
I've always been a little anemic,
but this is a good chance
to get thoroughly tested.
I guess I pushed
myself a little too hard.
You know, all that violin practice,
not to mention chasing after
Mr. Escape Artist... all week long!
*Looming*
*Drip Drip Drip*
The stress of not being able
to rehearse together, and all...
That's right, that's right!
It's all your fault!
Kaori and I didn't make
it to the next round.
Unprecedented. One mishap after another.
A no-brainer for disqualification.
Ineligible. Performance interrupted.
The worst possible scenario. All my fault.
You haven't said a
word of reproach.
Hey, let's get going.
We shouldn't outstay our welcome.
Whaaat? I'm gonna spend the night!
Okay, Kao-chan, see you at school!
Come on!
Bye!
I'm staying over!
No, you aren't!
Hey...
Have you been playing the piano?
It would be so much easier if
she just chewed me out.
No. I haven't been playing.
Why not?
It's like... I have nothing to
offer but my piano playing...
Is that a bad thing?
Do you think you'll
be able to forget?
Gray skies.
Totsuhara University Hospital
Looks like rain, huh?
Hurry up, hurry up!
What, you're not there?
What were you talking
about with Kao-chan?
Huh? Oh, not anything major...
Then you shouldn't mind telling me!
Keiko-chan?
It's me, Ryo-chin. Yeah, yeah.
You busy right now?
Is playing the piano all I have to offer?
No, not at all. You have lots
of good qualities, Kousei.
For example...
Oh, hey! Look
at that! The sky!
A sunny spell.
Do you think you'll
be able to forget?
Did you see me make the shot?!
You gave me a heart attack.
What's that?
I'm sending this to Kaori-chan.
Let's stop by the
hospital tomorrow.
I hear she's getting
discharged the day after.
Let's get her a
present on the way.
So he already knows
her email address...
I bet she'll get a
kick out of that!
I'm gonna pass. You
should go by yourself, Watari.
I'd feel awkward.
I'm the one who made a
fiasco out of her competition.
And besides...
But...
You were the one she leaned on.
Kousei...
But that's only because I'm
the one who can play the piano.
That's all there is to it.
No other reason.
Hey, I know. I know that, but still.
I know that but
you'll never know.
Don't hold back because
of me. Let's go together!
We might catch her naked again!
Watari! The captain shouldn't be slacking!
Just watch all the
dazzling plays I make!
Someone's pretty pumped up.
You got that right!
Our final tournament's
about to start!
And besides, after witnessing that spectacle,
how can I not get all fired up?
The way you two were that day...
It's burned into my mind!
I'll never forget it!
Do you think you'll
be able to forget?
The piano is just one part of you.
But in that moment, without a doubt...
The piano was everything to you.
And you're trying to rip that away by force.
As if you were plucking off your limbs...
That's why it hurts too much for you to bear.
Your face says the suffering is so painful,
too painful to bear...
Do you think you'll be able to forget?
No, not a chance!
Because you and I are
living for that moment.
You were great,
middle school duo!
Because you're a musician, just like me.
Good job, pianist!
Unprecedented. One mishap after another.
Even so,
the people here won't ever forget us.
I won't forget.
I won't forget, even if I die.
Thank you.
It's all thanks to you.
Because you accompanied me.
Because you played the piano for me.
Thank you, Kousei Arima.
She's merciless.
That unbending gaze.
Even from the back,
she won't let me give up.
Please support me!
The one who was being supported...
...was me.
Thank you. Thank you.
I see... So I
passed out again.
First... Oof!
Safe!
Lucky!
What the heck was that, Tsubaki?
Yay!
Little kids are so gung-ho!
I know, even though
the water's so cold.
Yeah, but you used to dive from the
"Courage Bridge" all the time.
Not to mention, always
shoving Arima-kun off it...
Kousei!
That was no biggie!
Kousei always laughed it off himself.
I wouldn't call that "no biggie."
Sure it was.
I know it for a fact.
Did something happen
between you and Arima-kun?
N-N-N-Not a thing! Don't
say freaky things like that!
Nailed it...
Well, okay, then.
I mean, being upbeat is
your only saving grace.
But yesterday and today, you kind
of haven't been yourself. Tsubaki...
Your eyes are cloudy.
Hey!
If it isn't Kashiwagi and Tsubaki!
What a coincidence!
Yo, Saito-senpai!
Long time no see!
Hey, check out that uniform.
Now that's a high school student!
I haven't seen you
since graduation.
You burning up the league as usual?
Oh, I'm on fire! How about you?
It's tough being a first year
again. I'm nothing but a gofer.
And if they'd just let me play
shortstop, I'd be the best, you know?
The former captain of
our baseball team.
Totally hot, dependable, and the
one all the girls dreamed about.
So unlike someone else I know.
A complete tool,
not to be depended on...
No one's idea of a dreamboat...
It's okay. It's okay.
I do know that Kousei has lots of good
qualities besides playing the piano, after all!
Looks like rain, huh?
Cloudy weather.
Your eyes are cloudy.
It's okay. It's okay.
So why am I feeling
so uneasy, then?
Hey, Tsubaki?
Yes?
This was no coincidence, see.
The former captain of our baseball
team. Totally hot, dependable,
and the one all the girls dreamed about.
I dreamed about him, too.
But I was never able to tell him,
and my love melted away with the
snow on graduation day, and it was over.
That's the kind of
love I thought it was.
I'm happy. I'm so happy.
Look, I'm serious
about this, okay?
And yet why... why isn't my
heart sparkling, I wonder?
I bet if this was
back around graduation,
my heart would've been
sparkling like a starry sky in winter.
So she's out of the hospital.
All right.
Don't get the wrong idea.
She just needed an accompanist.
Hop, skip, jump! Hop, skip, jump!
As if you can see right
through me, into my heart...
Hop, skip... hop, skip...
Always, out of nowhere, you...
Hop...
Skip...
...jump!
...just show up.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Isn't it obvious?
Playing hopscotch.
She said she was
waiting for someone.
Yeah.
Shh! Shh!
There.
Why are you holding out your hand?
My gift for getting out of the hospital.
I'll take it now.
No gift?
That's horrible of you!
Watari-kun gave me flowers!
And you're the one who made
such a mess of my performance!
When I was gunning to win it all!
You liar!
Don't make women cry!
This is why men are so...!
All right, then! I'll do something for you, okay?
You'll do anything I ask?
Sure, sure.
No matter what?
No matter what.
Yippee!
I knew it...
Hmm, what should I ask for?
I know!
Enter a piano competition.
It's your turn now.
There's no way I can do that.
Why not? You were
playing fine that day.
Are you still afraid?
There you go again,
looking down!
We're all afraid, you know...
to get up onstage.
Maybe you'll mess up.
Maybe they'll totally reject you.
Even so, you grit your teeth
and get up onstage anyway.
Something compels us...
moves us to play music.
Is it like that for you, too?
Everything you say and do...
it all sparkles so brightly.
It's too blinding for me,
and I end up closing my eyes.
I'm a guy...
...who hurled my precious
sheet music away.
I don't deserve to
be a performer.
I played with all my might because I
wanted my mother to get well, and yet...
There are tons of musicians
in the same boat. I'm sure!
Ones who think, "I'll be darned if I do
this," or "Why don't you play it?"
And yet, you pick it up again...
and you sit before that score.
That's how...
...you create the most
beautiful lie of all.
We're still only 14, you know!
Let's pull out all the stops, and dive right in!
Like this!
Bombs away!
Glug!
She survived!
Ooh, that was scary!
It feels so good!
I've always wanted to try that!
Everything you say and do...
It all sparkles so brightly.
It's too blinding for me, and
I end up closing my eyes.
But I can't help
aspiring to be like you.
Do you think you'll be able to forget?
That moment, when my
music reached them...
Go!
It's gonna change your whole world!
There's no way I
could ever forget that.
Huh? No way...
Onii-chan!
There you are!
Scary stuff!
There's no way I
could ever forget.
Because I'm a musician,
just like you.
Gray Skies
Huh? Where are your glasses?
Oh!
Episode 6
Way Back
Watch Again Next Week!