Naniwa Bay, now the flower blooms, but for winter.
Here comes spring, now the flower blooms.
Did you watch last night's episode?
Uh-huh, you bet!
Have you heard?
One of the new students
is the younger sister of the model Ayase Chitose!
No way!  I'm a huge fan!
She must be super cute!
Yeah!
Really?  Let's go check her out!
Which class?!
Class 2!
But she's usually in the lobby during lunch!
What?
Please come see Ayase Chihaya in class 1-2!!
Ayase Chihaya...?
Let's start a competitive karuta club!
A competitive karuta club?
Excuse me.
E-Err...
1, 2, 3, 4!
The hell?
Track pants?
Look at the belt.
Ayase-san!
Just look at yourself!
Have you no shame?!
What?
You're the one who told me that
I shouldn't do this with a skirt on.
If you're going to wear track pants,
take off the skirt!
Also, you're only allowed to
put one flyer on the board.
Don't take it off here!
You keep trying to start a karuta club,
Right, everyone was saying how she's pretty,
but you always fall asleep during classical literature!
but it's wasted as soon as she talks or does something.
Beauty in vain...
Chihaya Furu
Verse 1
Now
The
Flower
Blooms
Let's start a competitive karuta club!
Nobody's come to see me.
Chi-chan.
Forget about karuta.
Do track with me again.
It'd be a waste to just quit
after qualifying for the
city meet in short distance.
Is karuta that idiom card game?
It's not.
Track was just a way for me to meet people.
Meet people?
What's that supposed to mean?
Hey, we need to hurry to practice,
or the seniors will yell at us again.
Uh-huh.  See you later, Chi-chan.
Wait up!
Faster!
Sorry.
That one senior is so scary!
It must be nice to have teammates.
I figured that high school was where I could
find other players and focus 100% on karuta.
That makes you the Queen, Ayase-san.
None are left who know me
Back when I really enjoyed karuta...
Takasago pines...
They call you "beauty in vain"
because you just plop yourself on the ground.
...can never replace them.
Chihaya.
Taichi?!
That's awesome!
I never thought you'd come to this high school.
I figured you would stay at
that fancy academy for high school with the free ride.
And spend three more years commuting
an hour and a half each way?
By the way, that hurt.
Anyway, I think it's more surprising
that you made it into a good public school.
Taichi, you've grown taller.
But we're practically the same height!
Don't get too cocky!
I'm still gonna grow!
As am I.
You can stop!
Taichi!
What?
Taichi!  Taichi!  Taichi!
What's wrong with you?
Chihaya, you probably aren't
very popular with the guys.
Chihaya.
Hmm?
Say...
Excuse me for a second.
Yeah, it's me.
Right now?
I'm at the station.
Yeah, not yet.
Huh?  You're waiting at Bubaigawara?
Fine, fine.
I'm hanging up.
Your girlfriend?!
You have a girlfriend?!
Am I not allowed to have one?
Oh.
Oh...
Wh-What's wrong?
Was it that big of a shock?
Uh-huh.
W-Well, I'm only with her
because she asked me out.
I'm not really attached to her or anything...
Maybe Arata's found something more important to him than karuta.
Huh?
What's that supposed to mean?
Taichi?
Have you been in touch with Arata?
No, I didn't get a New Year's card from him.
Arata wasn't in last year's national tournament.
I was on the track team in middle school,
so I've never been to the Omi Jingu tournament.
Nothing wrong with track.
Huh?
I'm planning on doing
something else in high school.
Karuta was just a hobby.
What?  You're not gonna play karuta?!
We're even in the same high school!
I spent most of my time in
middle school playing soccer.
We're not gonna play karuta forever.
None are left who know me.
This poem was about losing old friends.
As long as we keep playing,
we'll see each other again!
I just know it!
Chi-chan!  Hurry up!
Wait for me!
Three years ago, in Tokyo,
before I found my passion...
Hey, hey.
How did your sister do in the beauty pageant?
Oh, she made it to the final round,
and her picture will be in the newspaper tomorrow!
Really?  That's amazing!
I wanna see!
Chihaya's sister is really pretty.
Yep.  Don't you agree, Taichi?
Sure.  She's the opposite of you.
Hilarious!
Aw, man.
Reflexes are the one area you can match me.
Don't forget height.
Hey!  You wanna make something of it, Chihaya?
Yeah!
Oh, sorry.
That transfer student never talks.
Really?
It seems he doesn't have any friends, either.
You should probably stay away from him.
I've heard that he snacks on bugs.
What?  For real?
Someone from Class 2 saw it!
He has holes in his socks, too.
We don't need him in our class.
Hey, Chi-chan.
Hmm?
Look at this.
We've been taking notes on
Wataya-kun's Fukui dialect.
Wataya Lexicon
Hay, hay -> Hey, hey
Yah, yah -> Yeah, yeah
Stick it -> No idea
Lez -> Let's
Canker -> ??
But he doesn't talk much these days.
We can't add to the list.
He doesn't wanna share.
I know...
Then, the other day...
If I were in Wataya-kun's shoes,
I wouldn't want to talk to people who kept
taking notes just so they could laugh at me.
That wasn't our intention.
I know.
Oh, really?  Sorry.
Nah, it's okay.
Really?
Hey, you forgot your directions.
You'll need this.
I memorized it.
You memorized it?
This is your first day!
Hey, wait!
You have 200 stops!
Don't make any mistakes!
Area 2, District 5.
Fujiwara, plus five across the street.
Osawa, Fujimiya, Yamamoto...
Uchiyama's subscription was canceled.
Yokota Cooperative.
101, 103, 203, 204.
Next is Ayase.
G-Good morning.
Thank you!
Sis!  Sis!
You're in the paper!
Wake up!
Japan Sports Paper
Japan's Most
Beautiful Girl
Grand Prix
13 Years Old
Look!  There's your picture!
Right here!
As a footnote.
Why is that bad?
It's amazing that you made it to the final fifteen!
Can I have this picture?
Whatever.
The winner has a better body, I guess.
You always say the first thing
that comes into your head!
Chi-chan, I saw the paper!
Your sister's amazing!
Yep!  She's amazing!
Wow, she's really in the paper.
Your sister's so pretty.
Wow...
Yeah, the two of you might be sisters,
but you still look like a boy.
Good morning.
Sit down.
Hundred Poet Memorization Sheet
Did everyone fill out their Hundred Poet sheet with stickers?
If you memorize all one hundred poems,
you should take the test.
We'll have the students who've
I don't think so.  How many did you memorize?
learned their poems participate in the karuta tournament.
Only ten.  What about you?
Fifteen.
Same difference.
Don't be such a snob.
Chihaya, how many did you memorize?
Only half, I think...
Yeah, yeah.
You're a better student than I am.
Mashima-kun, you've already
memorized all of them?
That was quick.
You can do anything.
Okay, quiet down!
Actually, Mashima-kun isn't the only person
in the class who memorized
all one hundred poems.
The other person is...
Wataya-kun!
No way!
Wataya-kun took the test
after school yesterday.
He got all 100 poems on the first try.
Amazing!
Round of applause!
Really? In one go?
Will you participate in the
karuta tournament next month?
Uh... yes.
Hmm?
Good morning.
The paper boy!
I remember now!
You delivered our paper this morning!
That's amazing!
Paper boy?
Grade schoolers aren't
supposed to be working.
Um, Wataya-kun?
Is this true?
I help out from time
to time when I'm asked.
He must be poor.
Doesn't he wear the same pants every day?
Hey, Taichi.  Isn't Wataya-kun amazing?
He's delivering the newspaper!
Okay, quiet down.
Everybody should try their best to
memorize all one hundred poems.
Wataya-kun!
Bye, Mashima-kun.
Yeah!
Um...
Well, I...
Oh, oops!  Sorry about
ruining your only pair of pants!
Taichi!
Don't have anything to wear tomorrow?
You can borrow your mom's skirt...
I didn't think you were such a mean person!
Well, why do you keep taking his side?!
Everyone's gonna start ignoring you tomorrow!
I don't care!
I'm gonna ignore you, too!
I mean it!
I said that I don't care!
Don't come crying to me later!
You'll pay for this!
Wow, this place is falling apart.
Oh!
Umm, sorry!
I always say the first thing
that comes into my head!
That's why my sister
kicked me this morning...
U-Um...
You know, you can talk.
I'm not taking notes.
It's freezing.
Wh-Why...
Why were you waiting for
the newspaper this morning?
He spoke!
My sister was in a beauty pageant,
and I couldn't wait to see the article!
Look, right here!
My sister's in the back!
Wow, that's really something.
Isn't she pretty?
Isn't she awesome?
My dream is to see my sister
become the top model in Japan!
You can't call that a dream.
Your dream should be about yourself.
Don't take someone else's.
That wouldn't be fair to your sister.
Wh-What?!
Do you have a dream, Wataya-kun?!
Your own dream?!
Huh?
Isn't this Hundred Poets?
Do you know how to play?
Well, we have a karuta tournament
at our school every year.
You know, the one the teacher mentioned.
L-Lez play!
Huh?
What?
Wait!
I'll play, but we need someone to do the reading.
I have a tape for that!
What?
Why is he so excited?
Um...  How does this work?
Line up 25 cards in 3 rows.
When the first verse of a poem is read,
you grab the card with the second verse.
I've only memorized around 50 poems...
Well, it's just a game.
What was that look?
Shall we begin?
Huh?
S-Sure.
The storm...
Huh?
Oh, oops.
to set the Tatsuta River ablaze
Another card got stuck.
May I live to see the day when
when the fisherman who
casts his nets can seem dear
The world offers no change, I pray,
H-Huh?!
What's going on?!
Is this how you play karuta?
He's fast!
Fast!
So fast!
I'm mad.
I'm really mad.
I should at least be able to take one card...
Oh.
are joined at river's end
I know the first verse for that card.
"Swift waters parted by the jagged rocks"
One card.
It's just one card.
I have to get it!
Swift...
...waters parted by the jagged rocks
are joined at river's end
I did it! I got a card!
I beat Wataya-kun to a card!
Thank you very much.
What happened?!
You're too good!
But you were able to take a card.
Only one card!
B-But, I had fun!
In Fukui, everyone played karuta.
That's not the case in Tokyo.
I usually play by myself.
By yourself?!
While listening to the tape?!
the red that is
the Tatsuta River
Karuta isn't very popular in other countries.
Well, it's not an easy game.
But that means...
If you become the best player in Japan,
you'll be the best in the world.
The best in the world?
My dream is to become
a karuta master.
are joined at river's end
Master...
Dream...
the red that is the Tatsuta River
Chihaya is a good name.
Huh?
Look, this is your card.
the red that is the Tatsuta River
The first verse for this card begins with Chihaya Furu (Impassionate).
This is the card you pick up when you hear Chihaya,
so in my mind, it's the Chihaya card.
That's how I see it.
I'm home!
Oh?
Arata, is this a friend?
Oh, a girlfriend?!
Mom...
the red that is the Tatsuta River
Arata's girlfriend, would you like some yams?!
No, thank you.
Impassionate gods have never seen
He was so fast.
His dream...
the red that is the Tatsuta River
On the day I first played karuta with Arata,
I learned about more than just karuta.
I discovered Arata's passion!