120 minutes after the operation began.
Everywhere I look, all
I can see are Wulgaru!
Black 6, are you all right?
I'm just starting to get pumped up!
I'm gonna have a blast taking
out all of these bogeys!
Black 6, don't lose sight of the goal.
Our mission is to launch
our markers into the gate.
Gosh darn it! If we knew
this was gonna happen,
we shoulda gone with them!
The three units in the vanguard
have been completely surrounded!
The enemy is composed of two fleets,
but the number of ships is
double what we normally see!
Notify all fleets!
Excluding Star Rose's Escort Force,
everyone is to offer Team Rabbits
their utmost support straightaway!
This isn't going according
to plan at all...
I never dreamed this might happen.
As soon as we enter
range, commence fire!
Roger!
I'm sure you must be worried
about Asagi and the others,
but you can't run out after them.
That's why the captain wanted to
keep you somewhere she
could keep an eye on you.
That's right!
I want to go out and help,
but I'm staying here, too!
I know.
I have every intention of
fulfilling my own mission!
It's just...
Don't you think this is a bit much?
Izuru, you have a past record
of going against orders, so...
"Operation: Heaven's Gate"
30 minutes before the operation.
After analyzing the data that
Team Doberman retrieved,
we deduced that the gate's energy
control system is located here.
Our mission's ultimate goal is
to destroy this control system.
If we do, the gate will destroy itself.
Team Rabbits, your mission is to
approach the gate without
drawing the Wulgaru's attention
and fire these target markers
into the control system.
All of Earth's forces will
use your target markers as
a guide for where to fire.
The forward units that will
charge the gate include:
Blue 1, Rose 3 and Black 6.
Purple 2 will serve as a
mid-fielder and Gold 4 will
offer support from the rear.
All units will be equipped
with the target markers.
In the end, I don't care who tries
to shoot one into the control system.
Once you make a direct hit, Team
Rabbits' mission will be over.
We've been assigned a critical role...
If we fail, they won't be
able to destroy the gate.
Once we fire the marker,
I suspect the enemy fleets
will come out after us.
I should think so.
Earth's fleets will be
quick to engage in battle,
so pull away from the gate
as quickly as possible.
As you're already aware, Red 5 can't
participate in this operation.
Asagi will be the leader.
Understood.
Team Rabbits, blast off!
Big Brother, fight!
Fight!
The Straggle Laser is entering
position preparatory to fire.
Energy circuits, connected!
It's currently advancing
toward the first stage.
After we destroy the gate, there
is no saying what may happen.
But if everything goes
according to plan,
casualties will be at a minimum.
Really, it all rests on
how my brother responds.
Are you referring to Pleguzes Jiart?
He discovered that Lady Teoria
has allied herself with Earth.
We are unable to predict his next move.
I am prepared to face my brother,
although I do not know if I
am capable of stopping him...
I can see something!
Is that the gate?
Ma'am, look!
Something just came out!
Did they lay an ambush?!
No, it doesn't look like
they're in a battle formation.
We probably bumped into them
right as they were setting out!
What are they doing here?!
My, my! Did they come
to vandalize our gate?
I'll have to torture
them to the fullest.
Everywhere I look, all
I can see are Wulgaru!
Black 6, are you all right?
I'm just starting to get pumped up!
I'm gonna have a blast taking
out all of these bogeys!
We have to get near that gate somehow!
How the heck is "somehow"?!
I'm on fire!
I'm on fire! I'm friggin' on fire!
Team Rabbits has crossed the half line.
Remaining distance to the gate: 50%.
However, due to the enemy's
current interference,
their progress has
decelerated tremendously.
This encounter was like getting
thrown a curve ball...
But I suppose we're lucky that
we took them by surprise.
Gold 4, support the forward three
units with long-distance sniper shots!
Purple 2, send the enemy
fleets' coordinates to Gold 4.
Kei, also include the order of priority!
Roger! Sent!
Wow, most impressive!
Asagi, Tamaki, Ange, you just sit tight!
That's Gold 4 lending us a hand!
Suruga's pretty good!
The enemy's formation is falling apart!
Now is our chance to split up!
Got it!
Let's go!
We have to succeed, no matter what!
For Izuru and for Earth!
Purple 2, Gold 4, advance
with Earth's fleets!
Roger!
It would appear that fleets from
several of the economic
powers are trailing behind.
Are they trying to conserve their
forces at a time like this?
Ignore the lagging fleets
and proceed forward.
They won't be able to
remain quiet once we
start to inflict damage
on the enemy fleets!
Fire!
The fleets in the rear
have begun to advance.
They won't want to explain
why they have zero
accomplishments once
the operation is over.
Continue the bombardment!
If Team Rabbits doesn't reach
the gate, Earth is finished!
Amazing! It looks like
a fireworks display.
All of Earth's forces
are working to help us.
I'd say the Fail Five have
gone up in the world.
A whole bunch of them just showed up!
I'll draw their attention!
I want you to head for the gate.
That unit's here!
That's the one that took out Patrick!
I wonder if that blue unit is tasty.
What are you doing?!
This defeats the whole point
of me being the decoy!
My, would you like to dance with me?
Tamaki, come back!
I will help Tamaki from here.
Continue toward the gate!
Got it.
Tamaki, don't do anything crazy.
Lutiel's fleet is
beginning to fall apart.
They are going to break our defenses!
Curse you, Lutiel!
It is not yet time for you to fight!
Tighten the formation!
Force the Earthlings back!
Break the enemy fleets into groups!
Focus your fire on the weak
points in their formations.
Launch the carrier-based
units! Protect Blue 1!
Don't let him near the gate!
Not on my watch!
We have received orders
from King Galkie.
He says to assist both
Dolgana and Lutiel's fleets.
Apparently the Earthlings have
invested their remaining
forces in this battle.
Sir, so it would seem.
Inform me when my lamata
makes an appearance.
I will leave the fleet
in your hands until then.
Prince Jiart, are you
not going to sortie?
Small fry may contend
with the small fry.
Very well.
We shall have a private
party of our own, my lamata!
The Straggle Laser is currently in
its second stage preparation to fire.
Energy charged at 80%.
It will be ready to fire momentarily.
Blue 1 is exploiting openings
in the enemy's fleets
to head toward the gate.
He has already passed the quarter line,
so he has a fourth of the way to go.
How is the battle progressing?
I would have a hard time saying
that things looks favorable.
The Earthlings are certainly dominating.
However, if they cannot reach the gate,
all will have been for naught.
Rose 3 is throwing the enemy's
formation into disarray.
Blue 1 is approaching
the gate by himself!
Increase fire! We can't
afford to let them die!
A mid-range gun battle, huh?
This feels like a boxing
match, doesn't it?
As in whoever stops moving
first gets pummeled?
Delivery! I've brought
rice balls for everyone!
It's the lunch lady...
Shion, you decided to stay, too?
They needed the extra help.
Everyone has to do whatever they can!
Yeah, but still, a delivery...?
Is this really the time for that?
Eat while you still can.
I imagine we won't have time
for food before much longer.
I'd like something low on calories...
Okay. I made a healthy set
with pickled plums, natto,
and saké lee pickles.
Uh, well, I don't really like natto...
I'll take that!
Do you have anything with foie gras?
I'll take the saké lee pickles!
Okay! I'll hand them out to everyone.
Great! I appreciate it.
Izuru, you have a job of your own to do.
Th-that's right!
Here is your tea!
Thank you.
Here!
Thanks.
Here! Here!
Danke schön.
We should all go hang
out when this is over.
Yeah! Oomph!
This is Gold 4! I need more artillery.
Please send me some additional weapons.
Do we have any backup weapons?
Rather than mount whatever
we have lying around,
let's link our ship's Weapons
Control System directly to Gold 4.
It'll be quicker that way.
Let's split Godinion in half
and use the front half's Battle
Module as a moving fortress.
It's programmed to handle
situations just like this!
Got it.
Detach the Godinion's
front Battle Module and
entrust Gold 4 with the
Weapons Control System!
Roger!
Asagi...
Everyone, fight!
Whoo boy! It's okay if
I cut loose with this?!
It'll be more efficient if you link
with Purple 2's control system
than if we tried to manage it from here.
I'm currently synchronizing with
his Artillery Control System.
Resetting the range of my radar.
Tamaki has engaged in combat.
She's up against...
...the fighter that took out Patrick!
Is that why Tamaki is so bent
on goin' after that unit?
But she's upsetting the enemy's
formation in the process.
It looks like the enemy is
trying to protect that unit.
Maybe some big shot is piloting it.
Tamaki will never give up.
If we play our cards right,
we can throw the enemy
into even more chaos.
Cool!
I'm on it!
Aw, jeez! All you do is
run around and around!
Do you think you stand a chance
if that's the fastest you can go?
This dance is over.
Tamaki, now is your chance!
Got it!
That attack was hardly beautiful.
You are taking this too far.
Focus on defending the gate.
I'll leave that to you.
I just managed to find
a fascinating lamata.
I take it you mean to
defy King Galkie's will?
I suppose I'd best go.
Wait!
Blue 1 will reach the
finish line momentarily.
You can do it! You're almost there!
I wonder if you will
show me a good time.
Tamaki was just fighting
this unit a minute ago...
She couldn't be...!
He dodged?!
I won't let you get away!
Tamaki, Ange! You're okay?
Blue 1, I'll deal with this unit.
Now hurry toward the gate!
Roger that!
Did you think that together
the two of you could stall me?
Damn it!
You were fairly beautiful.
Direct hit!
Anticipated movement will be
in the 2:20~2:25 direction.
They're trying to snipe me?
Pickled squid guts power!
I really couldn't call that beautiful...
Serves ya-
The mission isn't over yet.
The enemy fleets are converging
over there. Hurry!
Let's go!
Go to Hell!
Move it! Move! Move! Move!
Go! Go, Blue 1!
Blue 1 is approaching the finish line!
The enemy is gathering to intercept.
All ships, advance while
continuing to fire!
Asagi...
The Straggle Laser's
energy is fully charged.
It's ready to fire at any time.
Link the command sight to
Blue 1's target marker.
Fire at full power the second
the marker makes contact.
Asagi!
Show 'em who's boss, Asagi!
Go, Asagi! Don't screw this up!
Blue 1 has reached the finish line!
He will enter firing range momentarily.
You can do it, Asagi.
Asagi...
Big Brother, fight!
Fight!
Go!
We've caught the marker's signal.
Fire!
The energy we fired has vanished!
The attack has been
rendered ineffective.
The gate appears to be undamaged.
What?!
No...
Asagi...
The Straggle Laser's shot is complete.
What happened...?
It appears they have developed
a high-energy barrier.
The enemy fleets appear
to have taken damage.
I never knew the gate
had such a thing...!
However, the gate itself
is completely unharmed.
A great many years have passed
since we left the Wulgaru.
Straggle Laser, all systems are normal.
We should have expected them to
We will hereby begin
recharging the laser.
change the system to some
degree or another...
What does it mean if there
is a high-energy barrier?
I suspect that it will render all
energy-based weapons ineffective.
We know that the marker hit its target.
Regular artillery should
still work on it.
All of the ships have been
equipped with missiles,
but who is to say whether that will be
enough to destroy
something this massive?
The attack didn't work?!
Damn it all to hell!
Why not? Hey, why not?
You gave me a fright,
but it's all over now.
Crap! We're completely surrounded.
"Arlea Yakuta Esto"