I haven't smelled tatami mats in a long time.
Huh?
Where am I?
What happened last night?
Do you remember nothing at all
from when you were transformed?
What are you talking about?
But your right hand's still there.
Right hand?
It's been so long...
...since I slept under a roof.
What?
What?!
Huh?
Um, uhh...
Okay, I'm taking the call.
I'll do it right now!
Right this second!
Which button am I supposed to push?
Um...
This one? C'mon, hurry up.
Gosh, which one is it?
H-Hello?!
Good morning!
Oh, Dazai-san.
Today's another fine day.
How's the new dorm?
Great, thank you.
Compared to sleeping outdoors, it's heavenly.
That's good to hear.
The change of clothes at your pillow
is a gift from everyone at the agency.
Thank you so much for everything.
By the way, Atsushi-kun,
I apologize for asking
this out of the blue...
but there's been an emergency.
An emergency?
Yes, there can be no delay.
Please come to the specified
location immediately.
It's a crisis!
Only you can help.
O-Okay, I understand.
Are you ready, Atsushi-kun?
Yes.
First, when you leave the room,
make sure you close the door.
Look behind you!
Behind me?
Um...
What's this about?
What do you think?
Maybe I'm hallucinating this morning?
Wrong!
Is it an enemy attack?
Did you get caught in a trap?
I got in myself.
Well, you see...
I heard that there's a way to commit
suicide by getting stuck in an oil drum,
Diagram
Securing the feet is the key.
so I decided to give it a shot.
But now that I have,
I'm just suffering without
being able to actually die.
Not to mention, now that I've
wedged myself this deep,
I can't get out on my own.
I think I might die.
I see...
But it's a way to commit suicide,
so you should be able to kill yourself
if you stay that way, I think?
I like suicide,
but I don't like suffering or pain!
Why would I?!
Also, I only learned this after the fact,
I see.
but it wasn't a suicide method...
It was a torture method!
There.
My name is Nakajima Atsushi.
Just the other day,
I turned into a tiger and went on a blind rampage
and this man, Dazai-san, helped me.
While Dazai-san is this kind of person,
those people with supernatural powers
all belonged to the Armed Detective Agency.
Nakajima Atsushi!
You'll become one of us.
From this day forth, you'll be a
member of the Armed Detective Agency.
That was painful.
I owe you one, Atsushi-kun.
Without you, I would've
snapped in two at the waist.
Didn't you ask your other coworkers for help?
I called them, sure.
I told them I was on death's door.
But then everyone was all
like, "Congratulations."
How's that make you feel?
I'm not surprised.
Jeez.
Anyone gifted with supernatural powers
has something wrong with them inside...
Gifted, huh?
Dazai-san.
Everyone at the Armed Detective Agency...
the private investigators, that is...
They're gifted, right?
Right, they're an armed force
taking on antagonists the police
don't stand a chance against.
I don't stand a chance at
joining the agency, then.
You're gifted just fine.
It's true that I have the supernatural
ability to turn into a tiger,
but I have absolutely no control over it.
I just transform unaware.
I can't will myself to
transform into a tiger.
So I don't think I'll be
of any use, even if I join.
I really appreciate the offer, though.
I'm sorry.
What's your plan, then?
I think I'll look for a job
I can actually handle,
though I don't think it'll be easy to find.
I have an idea for a potential job.
I can help you get it, if you'd like.
Really?
A Certain Bomb
Thank you so much!
We're going to meet the guarantor
who'll introduce you to the job.
I'm sure he'll like you.
What's the job?
No point spoiling the fun.
Well, there may be a test of sorts.
Huh?
A test?
Atsushi-kun, can you write?
I do know how to read and write.
Then you'll be fine.
You'll be just fine, I'm sure.
I guarantee it.
Thank you!
You'd better thank me!
Just leave it to me,
and everything will be fine!
After all, I am Dazai...
The one and only whom the agency trusts
and the populace adores!
There you are, Dazai!
You bandage-squandering machine!
N-Nice nickname there, Kunikida-kun.
Bandage-Squandering Machine?!
That stung, just a little.
Who's the one and only one
the agency trusts, huh?
You're the one and only one
who we get complaints,
curses, and grievances about!
Huh?
Calls about complaints, curses...
and grievances?
What?
Since when did I ever get a complaint?!
Ideal
Call in August:
"One of your employees has been
caught in an offshore fishing net."
"Can you come retrieve him?"
Call in September:
"Some weirdo's got himself
buried on my farm."
"Could he be one of yours?"
Th-Th-Th-Th-Th...
Call in the same month:
"Pay your tab, okay?!"
"All six months' worth!"
That's impossible...
Who knew you were so good at imitating
other people, Kunikida-kun?!
You bastard!
Stop ridiculing me!
I wonder if it's actually a good idea
to have him help me find a job...
Oh, right!
I wasted a whole minute
dealing with this idiot.
Let's hurry to the agency!
Why?
We have an emergency!
A bomber's taken a hostage and
holed himself up in our office.
A bomber?
Um...
What?
The agency's on the fourth floor.
That's not what I wanted to ask.
Let's take the stairs, just in case.
Excuse me...
Quiet!
Oh, sorry.
Let's go, Atsushi-kun.
What?
I can't...
I can't take it anymore...
It's all your fault...
The Armed Detective Agency's fault.
Where's the president?
Bring the president!
If you don't...
I'll blow everyone to kingdom come.
A personal grudge?
That's inconvenient.
Yeah...
Why am I here?
The bomber seems pretty
furious at the agency.
I don't think I'll be of
any use. May I go now?
We do attract a lot of ill will.
You're ignoring me?
Besides, that's a high explosive.
If the bomber acts on his
threat and detonates it,
the whole floor's as good as gone.
Oh no...
We may be able to mitigate the
force of the explosion somewhat
if we can find something to cover the bomb,
Safety First
but given the circumstances...
I can't believe he took a woman
as a hostage, the coward.
Who's the girl?
She's Naomi-chan, a part-time
office assistant.
A part-timer?!
Then she's a completely innocent bystander!
What should we do?
Why don't we let him see the president?
He'll try to kill the president!
We can't let the president walk
into a situation like that!
I'm glad he's out on a business trip.
Then there's only one method...
Are they going to use their abilities?
Huh?
Go, go.
C'mon, go!
Hey.
Calm down, boy.
Stay away!
I only want to see the president!
If you do anything funny, I'll blow this up!
Okay.
I know who you are. You're Kunikida!
I bet you're trying to
make me let my guard down
and use that annoying ability of yours!
Well, fat chance.
Get up on the desk on all fours
and keep both hands where I can see them!
I-If you don't do as I say,
I'm taking you all down with me!
This isn't good.
Because of his personal grudge against the agency,
he's done his research on all
the members' names and faces.
If I go, it'll only provoke him.
Hmm... What to do?
I just got a really bad feeling...
A-tsu-shi-ku—
No.
I haven't even said anything.
I already know what you're going to say.
Listen, Atsushi-kun.
You're the only one here who's not a formal
member and who the bomber won't know.
But even if I were to go,
I wouldn't be able to do anything.
It'll be fine.
We just need you to distract
him for a short while.
We'll do the rest.
Let me think...
Knowing you, how about you
put on an off-putting act
as a worthless human being?
Here are some props.
Trust me.
Scuffles on this scale
are child's play to the Armed
Detective Agency, Atsushi-kun.
S-S-S-Stop!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What could you possibly accomplish?
I... I bet this would make your parents sad!
Who the hell are you?!
S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S...
Scary
Sorry!
You're not with the agency.
A-A-As you can tell,
I'm just a newspaper delivery boy
who happened to pass by!
And what's a delivery boy
got to do with any of this?
No matter how much you might hate them,
you shouldn't take hostages or blow up bombs.
I'm sure there's something to live for.
Like what?
Huh?
Wait a minute...
Did you just start that thought
without thinking it through?
What's something to live for?!
T...
What?!
S... S... Sure, that's true.
T... T... Tea on rice!
You can eat a lot of tea on rice!
You can sleep somewhere
with a roof over your head!
When you go to sleep at night,
you can wake up to a new day!
And every day is a new day!
But...
If you blow up, neither you
nor I will see another new day...
because we'll be dead.
I know that!
What?!
Um...
I think you should reconsider.
I mean, if you die...
You're really dead!
I'm sure you might wish
you were dead sometimes,
but there are people who keep on
living, even if the going's tough.
Oh, people like me!
I have no family and no friends.
I even got chased out of an orphanage,
and I have nowhere to go,
and no hope for the future...
Besides, I even turn into a tiger.
Yeah, that's right!
It's true that, like you say,
I lack redeeming qualities,
and everyone'd agree that
I'm the scum of society.
But I still manage keep on living
without going all postal about it!
Good job, Atsushi-kun.
You have acting like a worthless
human being down to an art form.
So why don't you toss that bomb aside,
and we can look for jobs together?
Okay?
You already forgot you're pretending
to deliver newspapers?
N-No, I'm not exactly looking for one...
Now, Kunikida-kun.
I know!
Ability:
Doppo Poet
Doppo Poet...
Wire Gun!
Wire Gun
Crap...
Get him, Kunikida-kun!
Like I already said, I know!
One down!
All right. Good job, everyone.
"One down," you say?
"Now!"? "Secure him!"?
You're all talk and no action!
What choice was there?
You lost at rock-paper-scissors,
Kunikida-kun.
You bastard...
Well, all's well that ends well, isn't it?
I've heard that if you're too neurotic,
you'll get a lot of wrinkles
and your aging becomes accelerated.
Is that true?
Go on, take notes.
"If you're too neurotic...
...your aging becomes accelerated—"
I'm messing with you.
Bastard!
Stop ridiculing me!
All of you...
Crap!
Stop making fun of me!
I swear, anyone gifted with supernatural powers
has something wrong with them inside...
Thirty seconds left until detonation?!
Hey, brat!
No way!
Kunikida-san!
What should I do?
We may be able to mitigate the
force of the explosion somewhat
if we can find something
to cover the bomb...
Something to cover the bomb...
Something...
Anything?!
Atsushi-kun!
What?
Huh?
What am I doing?
Idiot!
Brat!
Jeez...
I figured he was stupid,
but I didn't know how stupid.
He has the talent to become a suicide maniac.
Wouldn't you agree, Tanizaki-kun?
Sorry.
Are you okay?
Huh?
Aw, brother!
Are you all right?!
What?
Tanizaki Junichirou
Ability: Light Snow
You were so wonderful as a villain!
His Younger Sister
Tanizaki Naomi
I had the time of my life
being tied up and threatened!
Please continue where we
left off, once we get home.
So the part-time person was
in cahoots with everyone, too?
Brat, you should blame Dazai.
Barring that, blame yourself for choosing
the wrong person to help you find a job!
Then is this the job...
I told you there was a test involved.
As in, an entrance exam?
That's right.
The exam has been completed
without much ado, president.
I see.
President?
Since Dazai said there
was a capable young man,
President of the
Armed Detective Agency
Fukuzawa Yukichi
Ability: All Men
Are Created Equal
I had him test your mettle.
Well, I recommended you for hire,
but since you've been designated
a major threat by the ward,
there was disagreement among us as
to whether we should take you in.
But Dazai said...
President.
Suppose the most gifted person
in the world appeared before you,
would you hire him?
Power doesn't make you
a member of the agency.
That's why I recommend him.
So, president... What is your decision?
I'll let Dazai decide.
You can trust me.
W-Wait a minute, Dazai-san.
So the job you meant to
introduce me for was...
You apparently passed the test.
Welcome to the Armed Detective
Agency, Nakajima Atsushi-kun.
Congratulations!
I'm glad I was able to help.
Oh, please, no.
I can't possibly join a workplace
as violent and reckless as this.
Not just anyone would use their body
to shield a bomb to save everyone.
That's right. I was really impressed!
You'll be fine.
But...
Secretary
Haruno Kirako
So, president, do you actually
want him to join the agency, then?
Oh, a tea leaf's standing straight up...
I think something good
will happen, president.
Ouch.
Still, well...
If you still refuse, we can't force you.
But then, I can't help but
worry for your future.
We'll need you to vacate the company dorm...
You don't really have any specialized skills,
nor do you have friends or know anyone...
That'd make finding a job very difficult.
Besides, you are a wanted tiger.
Should anyone learn of that,
at best you'd get fired from your job.
At worst, you'd be captured and shot dead.
Sh-Shot dead?
Now, if you were with this agency...
it'd be a different story.
Th-Then that means...
We look forward to working
with you, Atsushi-san.
Don't we, brother?
Follow the rules, brat.
Well, now that's been settled...
You've got to be kidding me.
The weretiger has been found.
Episode 2: Yokohama Gangster Paradise