I've brought Daichi Manatsu.
Come in.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
What are you talking about?
There was a small delay in
the development schedule,
and unfortunately, I took it out on you.
It was quite childish of me.
I'll leave the Machine Goodfellow trials to you.
I've informed Technology and Research Division 3.
Welcome, Amarok-sama, Malkin-sama.
I can't understand why Kube
wouldn't be in his office
in the middle of the day, either.
And the way he's acting is strange.
What are you talking about?
Why did Kube's attitude suddenly change?
Did losing Legacy drive him nuts?
No, he has other stock satellites.
It was a nice way to irritate him, but...
Did you do something?
I used subliminal messages to make him
fall in love with Hitomi Makino.
He was so focused on being
humanity's next leader,
he was in a constant state of tension.
His time with Hitomi Makino
has released that tension,
stabilizing his psyche.
He got suckered into dating someone,
and it improved his mood?
So that's all the man he was.
Well, if it doesn't interfere with
our activities, that's fine.
Leave it to me.
Puck does not lie.
The security cameras are watching.
I'm enjoying giving them a show.
You're so mean.
I had no idea having a body was so much fun.
"If it doesn't interfere with
our activities, that's fine."
That self-confidence makes manipulating
both Earthlings and Planetary Gears simple.
Cheerful!
Pounding!
Heart!
Here I am, everyone!
It's me, Ai!
I love you!
I love you all so much, I could eat you!
And someday, I really will!
Ai! Ai! Ai!
Ai's really changed...
What happened?
With a flower in my hand, held up to the sun,
like a dancing butterfly...
I want to see you.
Let us go on a journey
toward gentleness, toward warmth.
That we can't just get it whenever
we want is inconvenient.
It's just until we turn into Kiltgangs again.
We can analyze internet posts to find
areas with strong destructive impulses.
It's easy.
Is the fluctuation index high
for people around here?
I can't believe you're calling a top idol somewhere
hard to reach like this.
We're all finally here.
Siren-sama, please forgive us for
failing to conquer the Earth.
I never thought we would all
see each other as avatars.
Not everyone is here.
Now that you mention it, where is Albion?
He's gone.
Gone?
What happened to him?
Albion destroyed his own Ego Block,
and ceased to be a Planetary Gear.
I hadn't heard that.
He has become a soldier for Earth,
who resists our invasion.
And he also uses a Livlaster.
He may be our greatest threat.
He destroyed his Ego Block,
and became a Neoteny?
That isn't all.
The Princess of Blume has
become a Neoteny, as well.
Our plan originally called for her to
be able to fire a Livlaster, but...
I can't believe the Blume
is now an enemy weapon.
It feels like there are many problems.
Siren-sama, do we have the energy gathered?
This time, it will only be one.
Let me do it.
I'll break past them.
Very well.
We are the Planetary Gears.
We reveal the dream of the world.
They say Pitz's condition is stable.
What did the commander say?
It's my fault that Pitz got hurt,
and we can't predict the enemy's actions.
Did he yell at you for that?
It's okay. That wasn't it.
Then what was it?
Well...
It seems that after Pitz got hurt,
we can no longer use Hana's singularity
to predict where the enemy
will use Orgone energy.
We cannot predict it like we have been any longer.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I'm not interested in blaming you for that.
I'm sorry to call you here from the hospital.
In regard to Hana Mutou,
it's less critical to our position that
she's lost her predictive power
than it that she can fire a Livlaster,
and that she used the Blume.
And every group that realizes
Blume has been activated...
Will come after Hana, right?
The Midsummer's Knights
have achieved their greatest goal
as an independent attack group.
You will now proceed to the next stage.
The next stage?
You'll go back to what the Intercept
Faction is meant to be doing.
We will put Operation Summer into effect.
Operation Summer?
Our next mission.
What is it?
How are you doing?
I brought you a watermelon.
Hey, you already have one!
I bought one!
Way to go.
Where have you been?
A shrine.
After all, I haven't been back
to Tanegashima in a while.
I may not look it, but I'm very traditional.
I'm a Japanesque magic-user!
What do you do at a shrine?
Talk to the gods and make requests, I guess?
The gods?
I don't believe in them.
I've never seen one.
Is it possible to see a god?
Do you also go to shrines, Captain?
Yep.
On New Year's or certain summer festival days.
Festivals?
What are they like?
You don't know?
They're fun.
There are all these stalls.
Stalls?
Places that sell good food and stuff.
Good food?
I want to go.
Let's go.
Once our mission is completely done.
Let's go to a festival together.
A festival!
So, what's the mission?
Don't you think Hana would look
great in a kimono, Captain?
I asked the gods for help with the mission.
You really do know everything.
Operation Summer?
The fights between you, the Independent Attack
Force and the Machine Goodfellows,
were partially an attempt to buy
time to prepare for this mission.
The Intercept Faction intends to the
enemy fortress carrier Oberon,
in orbit around Uranus.
That is Operation Summer.
When I chose this place, I was
as careful as possible.
But if they come here, take care of them.
I know.
Everyone's here.
If even Aiatar can't do it,
we might need to think of a plan.
Abreaction.
What are you thinking about?
I was thinking about Albion.
Why would he destroy his Ego Block?
What kind of life did you lead for the
seventeen years until you awoke?
I suppose there was lots of bad stuff.
But it wasn't all bad?
For me, it was mostly bad stuff, too.
I'm still mad about being used by others.
I still can't forgive them.
But...
By absorbing the Earthlings' libidos,
it means we're using them.
Where did Lappa go?
AEO confirmed.
It's a Kiltgang!
Manifestation point is within
defensive zone 2, Beta sector.
Call Tanegashima immediately.
Any effect from the solar flare two days ago?
Not yet.
A Kiltgang has appeared.
It's Type-5!
Aiatar?
I told you to rest!
We can't right now!
Distance 35,000 kilometers.
Speed 50 meters per second.
It's heading straight for Earth.
They're both hurt, and the Earth
and Nebula are under repair.
Activate Flare Engine launch sequence!
Flare?
Activating Flare Engine launch sequence.
This is Hana Mutou.
Orders confirmed.
Hana's going to launch?
I'll go, Commander!
Hana underwent the same training
as Teppei for a long time.
And this was her suggestion.
But...
My shooting score is higher than Teppei's.
It's my fault you two were injured.
Please let me go.
Hana...
Make sure you come back safely.
That's my condition.
Roger!
Expansion sequence activated.
The Flare Engine's energy is charging.
The Pegasus has purged it!
Flare Engine, expand!
Adjusting relative vectors.
Delta RV 3.2, 2.6, 0.7.
First expand!
Tidal attractor functioning normally.
Delta RV is within threshold.
Combine robustness at maximum.
Second expand!
Preparing Orgone connection.
All systems are go.
Final expand!
An Impacter that isn't in our data?
Another one?
In this business, there are always new girls.
That's why it's so hard to survive!
Hana!
I'm fine!
Calm down.
Stay calm... I can see them.
No...
I can't hit her?
She's jumping around.
Wow.
She's predicting the enemy attacks?
Does her really precognition really rely on Pitz?
Of course, I don't think she's lying...
She probably thinks it does,
but maybe it's actually her own singularity?
Just like my magic?
No...
I don't know about that.
Just as Rita-san says,
that instinctive precognition can
probably be used for attacks.
Hana!
Just attack her!
Roger!
I'll take your cheer like a vampire!
A barrier?
No.
Aiatar can absorb the beam's energy?
My attacks aren't working!
Delicious.
So this is the Livlaster's Orgone energy!
I can feel the power rising inside me!
Right now, I'm filled with Orgone energy.
You can't escape me.
I've got you.
Calm down, Hana.
I'll help you!
Commander!
The Coronal mass ejection is sending a
stream of charged particles toward us!
The solar flare from two days
ago is showing up now?
Radiation density is increasing.
The electrical circuits are saturated,
and we can't communicate!
Hana!
The end!
A CME storm?
I can't see anything.
But...
I know where she is because
she absorbed my energy!
She's coming.
Communications are back on line!
The Kiltgang has been successfully intercepted.
Hana...
Seems my prayer was heard.
As planned, I'm returning the
dummy capsule to Earth.
Thanks.
You want them to believe the Flare
Engine is back on Earth, right?
Yes.
Just keep Hana for three days.
In ten days, we'll begin Operation Summer.
This footage of Oberon was
just taken by Cassini 3.
It's emitting a light?
Nine days ago, when the Type-1
attacked for the first time,
we saw this light, as well.
We must not forget the tragedy in which
the Type-1 wiped out Daedalus Base.
This time, the light is brighter
than nine years ago.
A full-scale war will exterminate humanity.
Yes.
That's right. Human weapons
haven't once succeeded
in destroying a Kiltgang's
real body, its Ego Block.
That the Intercept Faction grows arrogant,
after temporarily stopping the
invasion, is the real threat.
Blume has already activated.
It's almost time for our plan, to create
a new future for humanity.
Harvest season draws near.
Then we should stand up and act.
A new observer has been sent to Tanegashima.
A scary woman, a female leader of Salty Dog.
Then two Kiltgangs attack.
The Ark Faction uses their trump card,
the unmanned Impacters Cerberus,
to intercept them.
But...
Next time, on episode 17 of Captain Earth:
The Knights of Midsummer
The Knights of Midsummer.
Belly Button Forte is back!