They said they got a fiefdom,
so I was expecting, well, you know.
This is the middle of nowhere.
I don't mean to be rude,
but I wonder about the previous owner,
letting this place go like that...
The old master died ten years ago
and since he had no heirs,
the land went into the
keeping of the queen.
That's why...
The young folks have
all given up their land
and gone to the cities.
All you've got left are
old-timers like me,
scrabbling along to
keep the land tilled.
This region is actually renowned for
its dry land, since it
produces great grapes.
Good work, everyone!
Already acting like a
feudal lord, I see.
I'm not acting!
I really am a feudal lord!
The lord here is Saito, right?
Saito Chevalier De Hiraga...
What else was there?
Saito Chevalier De Hiraga De Ornierés.
That's it!
Still, I was pretty shocked.
I never expected to see
you here, Tabitha.
Is it true that you're
going to become a queen?
Oh yeah, I wanted to
ask about that, too.
What are you going to do?
I haven't decided yet.
So what are you doing here?
It's pretty obvious!
Sister wants to hatch an egg!
An egg?
I think she's talking
about becoming pregnant
with someone's child.
P-P-Pregnant?
I want to be pregnant, too!
I-I think I should go practice
my sword fighting techniques.
Hey, where are you going?
Wait!
I won't be ditched!
I'm going too!
The new lords sure are
a vigorous bunch.
It would be nice to see a
successor born soon.
The Maidens of De Ornierés
It's quite a nice hall
for a country mansion.
Those look delicious!
Well, you know what they say.
The way to a man's heart
is through his stomach.
Right!
This is more a dump than a basement.
Look at all these books!
Tabitha is going to love this.
I don't think she's really in
the mood for reading right now.
I've never seen her like this.
You're right.
She came here because
she wants to be close to Saito.
She won't have any freedom once
she ascends to the throne.
But here she won't be able
to avoid seeing those two together.
Doesn't that hurt?
That's love.
You know on a rational level,
but you can't help yourself.
You're right.
This feels so good!
How can you be so laid back
about this whole thing?
We've finally got our own house,
but we might as well
still be at the academy.
Those are so pretty.
Saito, look!
What's wrong?
Is there something on my face?
No.
Then what's wrong?
Why are you staring at me like that?
I was just thinking
about how happy I am.
Seeing you smile makes me happier
than anything else in the world.
Oh, come on.
What are you talking
about all of a sudden?
It's the truth.
When I first came here,
I wanted to go back to
my world all the time,
but now, I feel like not
going back would be okay, too.
It's because you're here.
Saito...
I couldn't feel like
this with another girl.
You're the one who makes me happy.
Saito...
Louise...
I'm sorry!
That's not it.
I'm just sorry they're so small.
If that wasn't it,
does that mean it's okay?
Can I ask you for a favor?
What is it?
Will you say,
"The little meow-meow wants to be
teased by the big meow-meow, meow."
Of course that's too much.
Will you be gentle if I say it?
Of course!
Th-The little meow-meow wants to be
teased by the big meow-meow, meow.
And can you tell me how?
Well... Um...
You can do what you like, Saito. Meow!
Lunch is ready, meow.
This idiot made me say it!
Please stop! Ouch!
I'm sorry!
I'll never do it again!
That was delicious!
It really was.
Excuse me.
There is someone here
to see Miss Louise.
To see me?
Who could it be?
Ow!
Damn you, little Louise!
I've heard all about the indulgent
things you've been doing!
Here you go.
Leaving school with a man
before getting married,
trying to live in a villa with him...
Don't expect me to ever acknowledge
such a filthy relationship!
I don't have to listen to that from
someone who failed to get married.
You'd make the House of Vallière
the laughingstock of the country
if the third daughter
lived with someone
with a dubious background!
We're going home.
Saito is not dubious!
He is a real nobleman!
He received this land as a reward
from Her Majesty for
saving His Holiness!
I don't care, we're leaving!
Please wait!
Elder sister...
You have no business
calling me your sister.
Maybe not now.
But I plan on visiting
your mother and father
in the near future.
I'm gonna make Louise happy!
I mean, I will make her happy!
Saito...
There is no way a daughter of Vallière
is going to get married to a
faux-nobleman who can't
even speak properly.
Th-Then...
I will make Saito into
a proper nobleman!
If he was a nobleman who you
could take to any court,
there'd be no problem, right, Eleanor?
You'll never take "no" for an answer.
Fine.
Cram the proper behavior
for a nobleman
into his head before I return.
If I'm not satisfied, you're
coming straight home with me!
Is that understood, Louise?
Perfectly.
Looks like she hates me.
Wh-What was that for?
You mean, "Please teach
me proper manners
from the ground up."
Go.
We're starting already?
What do you think?
I'm going to make you noble,
from top to bottom.
Nobody's going to be able to
raise a single complaint against you.
How many times do I have to tell you?
You bow like this.
Now you try.
No, no, no!
May I have the pleasure of this dance?
The way you extend
your hand is common.
The way I extend my hand?
Walk slower.
Like this?
You're not a cow!
Moo.
Stop screwing around!
And stop mooing!
Are you really going back?
Yeah. I was planning on staying over,
but it looks like they're quite busy.
And we did get the grand
tour of the place already.
But isn't it too late to leave now?
I'll take you back.
We might as well take
her up on the offer.
Thanks a lot, Tabitha.
Siesta, tell those two we said bye!
No, no, no!
You're doing it all wrong!
You've got absolutely no class!
Start from the beginning.
Did you hear me?
Do it again!
I'm done.
What?
I said I'm done.
I mean, it's weird that you're
trying to change my nature.
But my sister, Eleanor...
Who's going to live with me?
Not your sister, Eleanor.
I don't want anybody
to make fun of you!
I don't care if people make fun of me.
But there's no reason we have
to go that far just to live together.
Just do it.
If you want to be with me,
you need to act like a nobleman.
At this rate, I'll be taken home.
What are you talking about?
Are you saying your sister's opinion
is more important to
you than my feelings?!
I didn't say that!
Well, I'm not a nobleman!
You're so stubborn!
I could say the same about you!
I can't sleep in the
same room as someone who's not noble.
Go find yourself another room.
This is my house, and I'll sleep
where I damn well please!
I probably shouldn't
have said those things.
Hey, pal,
what's with these dusty lodgings?
I figured the basement is
where I belong,
since I'm not a lord and all.
Why do you sound so bitter?
What's all this lord talk, anyway?
Can't she just be with
me because she loves me?
Just the way I am...
Ow.
Is even this chair
making a fool of me?!
Huh?
Wow...
Saito?
He's not here either.
Saito?!
Where did he go?
What's this?
Is this some sort of hidden room?
It's a mirror.
I don't remember this hallway.
Sa—
What's Her Majesty doing?
Y-Your Majesty?
Saito!
Wh-What's going on?
I'm not sure myself.
I opened my closet and then
I saw you in the mirror.
The moment I said your
name out loud in surprise,
Saito...
I was here.
It looks like there is some kind
of spell cast on this mirror
and the mirror in my room.
H-How about first we find
you something to wear?
But I really was surprised.
Who would have thought my bedroom
in the castle is connected
to this mansion.
I wonder what for.
Looking at how this room is built,
I think it might have
been for a mistress.
A mistress?
Yes.
The couple lived upstairs
and the secret trysts were held here.
Trysts...
I would have never imagined that my
grandfather had a side like this.
He was regarded as a very strict king.
I suppose he had little choice
in who he had to marry.
I was also told by my mother
that I should marry.
Countless times.
Marriage...
I've already given up on ever
marrying someone I love.
Still, when it comes down to it,
it's hard to convince my heart.
Marrying for my country...
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to say in
a situation like this...
So you won't tell me that
I shouldn't get married.
Of course not.
You're in love with Louise.
I don't know...
...what I was expecting.
Well, if you don't want to,
then you shouldn't.
It's weird to marry
someone you don't like.
Are you saying that out of pity?
Or...
I...
Even if it's only once in a while,
if you would meet with me like this...
Don't you feel the same way?
So that's what's going on.
Then let's meet here again.
But I... I have Louise.
I understand that.
But the other me keeps saying
that doesn't matter.
I feel like I've been dreaming.
What's up, pal?
Did you fight with your girl again?
What do you mean?
Wait, was Louise down here?
Yup.
Then she ran out with red eyes.
Could she have...
Louise!
About the princess...
That was just...
I'm happy for you that
she feels the same way.
Until now, I always thought
I knew everything about you.
I guess I was wrong.
But that's not what happened!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I didn't notice until now.
Louise...
Don't give her too much trouble.
Louise!
Shouldn't you go after her?
I don't have the right to do that.
It's better this way.
It is...
Isn't the weather today just
beautiful, Miss Vallière?
She's gone!
Maybe she ran away with Saito!
I'm sorry we kept you here.
But, by the same token,
we were actually able to talk.
Give it your best
so that you won't regret anything.
Louise?
What are you doing here,
dressed like that?
Did you and Saito already
have a marital spat?
We didn't have a spat.
I broke up with him.
I mean, I can't compete
against the queen.
It turns out I don't have many places
to go at times like these.
How did it end up like this,
Saito?
I need to talk to you.
About what?
Are you serious about leaving Saito?
It's none of your business.
Then I'll take him.
What?
I'm the future queen of Gallia,
so I can have whatever I want.
Whatever?
You mean you'd force him to...
Are you serious, Tabitha?
And if I am?
Tabitha, what are you talking about?
I could marry him, too,
if that was my wish.
M-Marry?!
I'll make him happy.
Tabitha, wai—
What was that all about?
Kirche?
Do you know why Tabitha said that?
Tabitha understands Queen
Henrietta's feelings.
They're one and the same.
They are?
You're not free to love
when you've got a kingdom
on your shoulders.
That makes them that much more
scary when they're serious.
They'll throw all their
pride away and go for it,
even if it might not make Saito happy,
or if it meant turning
friends into foes...
If someone would go
that far for you, I guess even
Saito can't complain.
Are you ready for that, Louise?
I was thinking that if Saito
really did love the queen,
I ought to respect that.
Well, if that's all it
takes for you to back off,
then that's how serious
your feelings were.
That's not true!
To me, Saito is... Saito is...
Winning at love is
about being honest with yourself.
Or so I like to think.
I want to go back to my old world.
If I can't be with Louise,
there's no reason for me to be here.
Saito!
Louise!
What are you doing here?
You're the only one for me, after all.
But I...
I don't care how the
queen feels about you.
I want to be with you.
You mean, you forgive me?
Just this once, you hear?
That's the face I love seeing.
That's right.
I'm the only one who
can make you happy.
Louise...
Saito...
What is this room, anyway?
It's haunted, so I'm exorcising it!
Nail!
Yes, ma'am!
It's your fault for not
holding it down properly!
Hey, Saito, what's a hot spring?
What, a place where you feel very good?
And being naked there
is the proper behavior?
Next time: Trouble at the Outdoor Bath.
You can't be naked with anybody else!
Trouble at the Outdoor Bath