Wow!
Incredible!
I can't believe it!
There are so many people at Yunosagi!
People also visit from
outside the prefecture.
Oh yeah, the wishing plaques!
Fret not. We all have them.
Isn't it a little too early to give up?
What is your prob—
FM: Ko
Sub: (non title)
[Arrived?] in Yunosagi just now.
Sorry, I need to go pick up Ko!
Wait! Should I drive you?
It's fine! Go and fest it up without me!
She's a noisy one, as usual.
Is it okay to let her go?
I don't see why not.
What did you write on it?
"I want to become a bullet train!"
What do I want to become?
I may not act like it, but I'm
actually pretty pragmatic.
I don't live with the
greatest role model.
No...
No!
Enishing,
I just saw—
Hey, do you think this is fine?
Didn't I say that we can say anything to each other?
Hey, Mom, will you buy
me a caramel apple?
Stop joking around.
Buy one yourself.
Cheapskate. You're just like Ohana.
You mean, Ohana is just like me.
"I want 5,000,000 yen."
"I want skinnier ankles."
People and their desires.
You shouldn't look at
other people's wishes.
But it's fun.
Jeez...
Mom.
Check this out.
I want to be Sui Shijima -Ohana.
I found a goal.
I want to be like the Madam Manager,
who takes pride in her job
and works her hardest,
but is a little childish and
never forgets her first wish -
her first dream.
But I couldn't find that goal on my own.
Everyone's bonboris
lit my way toward it.
Well... I guess I lost.
But that just means
I need to fest it up.
"Fest it up"?
Haven't you heard Ohana use it?
Fest it up, eh?
What did you write?
Don't look!
Just a peek!
That's wonderful, Minchi!
Nako!
Hey—
Come on, Tsurugi! Just a peek!
Stop laughing!
Come on!
I hope to catch up to Tohru someday -Minko
I'd like to pave for higher grounds as a chef. -Tohru
You'd better run fast, or you
won't be able to catch up to me.
Balut!
Ko, you came...
Of course I did.
You came...
You look nice in that outfit.
Ko...
Hm?
Well, umm...
I...
I want to eat yakisoba!
Okay.
One yakisoba, please!
Coming right up!
No...
I... I have to tell him!
Don't you think the yakisoba at night stands feel special?
Y-Yeah.
It's different from the stuff you buy
in stores or the ones you have at home.
I like...
Yeah, I like the ones
at night stands better.
...you!
I like you!
I love you!
Here you go.
-Thank you!
Festivals are meant to deliver
all wishes to the sky.
Dear...
I felt like I've been running
alone ever since you passed away.
But I was wrong.
I have a granddaughter
who dreams to be like me.
If it were possible,
just one more time...
Just one more time...
Finale
To Bloom One Day
I'm going to be staying with my son.
So much time has passed, when I thought
I was just standing by the boiler.
I should probably be preparing
to see the afterlife soon.
I don't plan on ever forgetting
the precious memories
I have of this place.
I thank all of you from
the bottom of my heart.
I also thank you, Madam Manager.
It was a pleasure working with you.
Enjoy your stay with your grandchildren!
It was a pleasure.
Mom, if you don't mind.
I want everyone to hear this.
I realize that I still
have so much more to learn.
I can't catch up to
Mom, or even my sister.
We just weren't born with the
same level of talent, I guess.
Mom!
Sorry.
I asked you guys to follow me,
but I'm not capable of that yet.
Mom, I agree with you on
shutting down the Kissuiso.
Enishi...
But only temporarily.
I don't want it to end forever.
I'm going to study and train in
order to reopen it someday.
And when that time comes...
Can I keep the name, "Kissuiso"?
I want to make an inn that'll
make you happy, Mom.
Young master, when that time comes,
I'll be happy to lend you a hand.
So will I, Mr. Ren!
Me, too! I'll leave my husband behind!
Dummy...
Me, too!
The dumber your kid is, the cuter, right?
Yeah.
Let's drink tonight!
Yeah!
Sounds good!
Hey, you'd better drink, too!
I'm underage...
Stop acting so goody-goody!
Tohru!
Don't stay too long, okay?
If you're going to do something,
be sure to write me a report afterwards.
Mom!
Maybe I'll go peek later.
Don't.
Aww...
Hey, Mom?
What are your plans now?
I'm going to be working at a
friend's place for a little while.
Why don't you come to Tokyo with Ohana?
I'd rather not.
I plan on staying here and
working as a waitress.
Work?
I also realized something.
I'm better at doing things myself
rather than ordering people around.
Mom...
I'll fest it up, too.
I'll continue being that mother
you hate so much, for your sake.
Thank you, mother.
Umm...
No, you have to fold back this part.
Oh... Right.
Sorry you had to be in this room,
and accompanied by a weirdo.
It's totally fine.
I'm actually feeling a bit guilty
that I get to stay for free.
It's okay!
She was actually sort of happy because
she claims I never invite friends.
But you were right, this
inn is really amazing.
Both the inn and the
people who work here...
You found them all, didn't you?
Found?
Watching you made me realize that
places aren't there to begin with.
You need to find them
and build them yourself.
Ko...
I'll find my place, too.
Hey...
If the places we belong
happen to be the same,
Ohana...
D...
D—
What are you doing?!
This is my room...
Don't you think Ohana's
boyfriend looks so sweet?
Yeah?
He's just lanky.
I feel so bad for Tohru that
he lost to someone like that.
It's not about winning or losing!
Oh... Right.
Kept you waiting!
Huh?
Weren't you going to sleep
in the Madam Manager's room?
Nah.
This is where I
belong in the Kissuiso.
It's my first time ringing
a bear-repelling bell!
I hear they often emerge
during this season.
Wow, it's cold.
The convenience store is so far away.
The pajama party continues
to the next day!
Oh, we forgot to buy meat buns...
So beautiful...
Hey...
I was wondering why it had
to be the Kissuiso for me.
Well, maybe it's because
you can be with Tohru.
No!
Well, yeah, but that's not it!
My... My dream.
It has changed.
Huh?
I just wanted to become a chef.
But now...
Now, I want to become Kissuiso's chef.
Minchi...
You're amazing, Minchi.
I don't know about my
dreams just yet, but...
I want to come back to
the Kissuiso someday.
The place where many dreams are born.
Where many dreams are born...
It's beautiful.
We were there, weren't we?
Don't talk in past-tense.
We're still there. I'm sure of it.
Yeah.
And we will be, in the future.
Kissuiso
Okay, slowly now.
Don't worry about it. Leave it to me.
Thanks.
People agreed to preserve
the Kissuiso as a
historical structure
in the Yunosagi area.
I bid farewell to the time
that passed by so quickly,
and at the same time, to the
time that seemed so long.
We...
Matsumae!
I'll text you!
I'll come visit you!
Bye, Sui.
Goodbye.
Dear...
I...
I thought you'd already left.
Oh...
I sort of missed the train,
and there's some time
left until the next one.
I wanted to thank the Kissuiso
and say goodbye to it.
Oh, did you know?
This wooden part right
here looks like a face!
Oh, this part, too.
But this one is like...
When I first came to the Kissuiso,
I thought it was like something
out of a fairy tale.
And just as I'd expected, a
lot of crazy things happened.
So many things occurred in a day.
But that's because everyone
was festing it up, wasn't it?
If a lot of people get
together and fest it up,
it's only natural that
many things happen.
What creates events are
everyone's individual feelings.
So...
It doesn't have to be here.
Events can be created anywhere.
Ohana...
But still!
But still, I'll return someday!
Ohana.
If you're going to come back someday,
keep these logs updated
for Denroku's sake.
R-Really?
If you don't want it, then it's fine.
I'm not giving it back!
I...
I'll write the rest for Beanman!
That's why...
That's why, I'll return...
Yeah. I'll be waiting for you.
Okay!
I'll be waiting.
Mom, it's time to get up!
Don't be late for your meeting!
I'm off!
Have a nice day!
I'm probably still a bud.
But that's why, I stare
up at the sun so high.
I quench my thirst with water.
I'm a bud that's trying to bloom!
The End