Tokyo-Hakone Round-Trip College Ekiden Race
Tsurumi Relay Station
Section 9 > Section 10
The enthusiasm of everyone who's
rushed here to Tsurumi Relay Station
after Fujioka's Section 9 comeback
has reached its peak.
Everyone's excited to see how
anchor and first-year Minami will run.
Rikudo captain Fujioka Kazuma.
The record-breaking way
he runs is absolute perfection.
The undisputed champion of four
years demonstrates his full strength
as he hands off his team's sash.
Rikudo/Fujioka Fourth-Year
>>> Minami First-Year
His time is...
Section 9 New Section Record
1:09:00!
Finishing in exactly 1:09:00,
he sets a new section record!
With his new Section 9 record,
he adorns himself with excellence.
Congratulations. You crushed the competition.
You don't mean that.
You were strong and steady today.
I could never catch up.
But Kurahara might.
Kiyose.
How far are we meant to go?
Motorcycle cam here!
Does Kurahara have no limits?
Kansei Kurahara Kakeru First-Year
He appears to be accelerating
in the final stages of the section!
Is there even a finish line that lies ahead?
But you can't quit.
Right?
Have fun.
He'll become even stronger.
Fujioka awakens Kakeru,
and Kakeru spurs on Fujioka.
But what about me?
Run With The Wind
Daiwa crosses the relay station.
Has the team returned to form?
The next team to enter
the relay station is Kita Kanto.
Marunouchi North
Kita Kanto's Higure climbs three ranks.
They'll surely be back next year.
Is Kakeru not there yet?
It's way too soon.
Tokyo-Hakone Round-Trip College Ekiden Race
Kansei's coming next!
Wasn't Kansei part of the simultaneous start?
With ten minutes to make
up on the second half...
Haiji.
I shouldn't be saying this
before it's over, but I had fun.
Did you?
Me, too.
So as long as you make
it back in one piece...
Just kidding.
Go ahead. Run as much as you'd like.
I will.
I've experienced a runner's high before,
but this is different.
I feel powerless.
I feel comfortable as though
I'm dreaming, but also anxious.
My body moves on its own,
leaving my consciousness behind.
Haiji!
That night, when you passed
before my eyes, I had a thought.
“That's my dream right there.”
“It's taken shape, and it's running.”
You made such an impact, I wanted to scream.
What I'd been struggling
to achieve was right there.
You are the ideal form I never reached.
Did you know?
When you run, I see a single
white line of light at your feet,
like a shooting star.
In The Wind
Kakeru!
You did it, Kakeru!
You did it!
Kurahara Kakeru's time
is an unbelievable 1:08:59!
Kansei Kurahara Kakeru First-Year
Section 9 New Section Record
He's broken the section record!
Kansei's Kurahara Kakeru breaks
Fujioka Kazuma's 1:09:00 record
a mere eleven minutes later.
The difference is only one second,
but it's the biggest shock of the race.
Kurahara Kakeru overwrites the section record
and goes down in Hakone Ekiden history.
This rookie has put the brakes
on the happy ending
of four-year track champion Fujioka.
Happy ending?
It's not over.
Kurahara, could we get a comment?
Kakeru!
At least wipe off your sweat, Kakeru!
We need to get there before Haiji!
Hurry, Prince!
Please stop sprinting!
Come on! Run!
I don't want to run anymore!
Tsurumi Relay Station
Section 9 > Section 10
Rikudo
Boso
Daiwa
Kitakan
Manaka
Yokohama
Dochido
Kikui
Saikyo
Tokyo Sport
Top 10 Seeded Schools
Akebono
Kansei
Kofu Academy
Nihonbashi Tech
Teito
Jonan Bunka
Eurasia
Shinsei
Kanagawa
Tokyo Academy
OP Student Association
Here are the overall times
at the end of Section 9.
First place, Rikudo, 9:53:51.
Second place, Boso, 9:55:22.
And Kansei's time is 10:06:27.
Our overall position is 12th.
1 Rikudo
2 Boso
3 Daiwa
4 Kitakan
5 Manaka
6 Yokohama
7 Dochido
8 Kikui
9 Saikyo
10 Tokyo Sport
Top 10 Seeded Schools
11 Akebono
12 Kansei
13 Kofu Academy
14 Nihonbashi Tech
15 Teito
To get into the top 10 and earn a seed,
you'll have to finish 1:02
faster than Tokyo Sport.
But your target, Tokyo Sport,
is currently running behind you.
Right now, the numbers
are all we can rely on.
Listen closely: At three kilometers,
Tokyo Sport's one kilometer time was 3:05.
You're running at a 3:03 pace.
In other words...
This painkiller is permitted
in-competition.
It will suppress the pain and inflammation.
I can't tell you not to push yourself,
but no matter what happens—
I have teammates who brought me this far.
I'm prepared.
Guys!
Hana!
Who's a good boy?
Nira, this is the first time
I've been glad to see you.
How could you say that to him?
Huh? Where's Joji?
Who's a good boy? You're a good boy.
You're so cute.
He's on his way here with King.
Oh, I see. I hope he gets here soon.
Joji, too.
Uh, yeah. And King.
Hana, I have a question for you. Do you mind?
Tokyo Sport's pace might be slowing.
I'll check.
What?!
Section 10 10km Point
Tokyo Sport's pace is slowing.
Keep it up.
Sorry for making unreasonable demands.
The skies always looked
like this back home, too.
Always cloudy.
Kiyose
Honey.
Not today.
Practice starts on this day every year.
He's him.
I'm me.
Haiji.
Don't lose your head.
I want to run after all.
I finally understand.
Whether I run or I don't,
it hurts just the same.
Even if I fail, I want to do what
my heart desires here.
Kansei University
Track and Field Club
You're a cursed man.
Wherever you are, it always
becomes the course you'll run.
You'll need ten teammates first, though.
I'll do it.
I'll create the ultimate team.
Are you watching, dad?
This is the team I met.
Kansei's Kiyose Haiji pulls head
of Yokohama and increases his pace.
He's running to pass on the hope
the ten of them built to future generations.
They are the ultimate team.
The hope I finally seized.
I lost hope once.
I felt betrayed by myself
and the entire world.
But I was wrong.
Running returned to me in
an even more beautiful form.
Can one man be so blessed?
I'm happy.
I could cry.
I am truly happy.
Even if I can never run again,
I love running!
Tokyo-Hakone Round-Trip College Ekiden Race
The temperature in Otemachi,
Tokyo is 0.4 degrees.
The snow has stopped,
but the wind continues to blow.
The first runner will be arriving
at the Yomiuri HQ finish line shortly.
Pain killers?
Yes, this morning.
Should you be saying that?
Wouldn't you guys rather know?
I knew it. He's sweating too much.
Now that I look closely,
his expression is stiff, too.
He won't listen if we try to stop him now.
Tokyo Sport shows no signs
of backing down, either.
Everyone's desperate.
Let's trust him.
Haiji will show us
the ultimate goal we're aiming for.
Deflecting the pressure
from the other schools,
Once again, Rikudo rises to the top
Minami! Final spurt!
of the Tokyo-Hakone Round-Trip
College Ekiden Race.
They've won again.
This is the power of a champion.
They gather around Captain
Fujioka to celebrate their victory.
Boso
Daiwa
Kitakan
Manaka
Kansei
Yokohama
Haiji, Yuki calculated an estimate.
At this rate, you'll be six seconds
short of Tokyo Sport and tenth place.
Three kilometers remain.
The rest is up to you.
Tokyo-Hakone Round-Trip College Ekiden Race
Kansei
It's Kansei Uni.
Fifth to arrive in Otemachi
is first-timer Kansei University.
They've achieved an unprecedented
fifth place finish with only ten members.
They finished last in Section 1, but they
steadily climbed the ranks until Section 5,
where they fell behind again
after a shocking loss of speed.
In today's second half, they were
part of the simultaneous start.
With impressive teamwork and
a section record, they overcame adversity.
They are a truly miraculous team.
Kansei's participation made
this an exciting race, indeed.
You asked me once what running is.
You said you wanted to know what it is.
The answer is you.
It's you.
Kansei University places
a remarkable fifth in the second half.
With a time of 5:34:32, they've
completed the Tokyo-Hakone race.
Tokyo-Hakone
8 Kikui
9 Saikyo
10 Kansei
Top 10 Seeded Schools
11 Tokyo Sport
Tokyo-Hakone Round-Trip College Ekiden Race
Well? Did you get to see the top?
By the time the cherry blossoms bloomed,
Demolition Notice
Chikusei-so
the ten of us gathered
at the dilapidated Chikusei-so,
which was scheduled to be demolished.
It's exploitative.
Just thinking about you working
brings tears to my eyes.
How about you, Musa?
I'm happy to give you advice.
I'm staying in grad school for another year.
Thanks for waiting.
We brought more drinks.
Hey, fourth-years.
We came to say our goodbyes.
You guys came?
Everyone's following their own path.
Land of the Gods
Steepest in the World
Let's drink today, Kakeru.
Okay.
Haiji's begun running a new path, too.
Think it'll work out?
I'm not sure. It is a new team.
But you'd be coaching a works team, right?
Sounds exciting.
Just tell us already. It's been three years.
Yeah, it's been long
enough. Which one was it?
No way! Was it written on my face?
Promise me you won't tell anyone!
I promise.
So, uh... Which is it?
What?
Which one do you like, Hana?
Which one?
That's between me and Hana.
Get him, boys.
What are you guys doing?
How's the new team?
It's stronger than back then.
Yeah.
Really?
You can't go back in time.
Just as old records are overwritten,
we keep moving forward.
Sometimes it makes me sad, but that's...
I'm excited for this winter.
Me, too.
Chikusei-so
Hey!
It's time! Break's over!
What? Just a little longer.
You're fourth-years now.
Pull yourselves together.
That's my favorite thing about her.
Hey, we agreed no shenanigans
until after we graduate.
Let's go.
Yes, sir!
The wind is blowing.
And we defy it by running.
Believing the answer we seek lies ahead.
What is strength?
What is running?
What is living?
It's all beyond the wind.
Hope resides within our hearts.
Look. The road is right before your eyes.
So we run again today.
We'll run to the edges of the earth.
Hey, do you like running?