I can hear cats meowing.
Say, you cats have nine lives, do you not?
Since you have so many,
why not spare one for me?
Are you awake?
Morning, Chise.
G-Good morning, sir.
You gave me a shock.
One moment you collapsed,
the next, you'd fallen asleep.
S-Sorry.
Was I that tired?
Uh, where are we?
It's the train to our next
honeymoon destination.
Come in.
There is a messenger here to see you.
Bring them in.
This train is not meant for humans.
A cat?
Pleased to meet you, sir mage.
Word travels fast.
Rumors spread a hundred miles
a day in the cat world.
He spoke.
Perhaps that would be surprising for
a cat on its first or second life,
but this is my seventh.
There would be something
wrong with me if I couldn't.
First? Seventh?
Haven't you heard?
Cats have nine lives.
Nine lives?
Exactly.
We cats become wiser with each life.
We too have the idea of "countries" and "kings."
Our King of Cats awaits at Ulthar, sir mage.
There are a lot of cats here.
That's why it's the Kingdom of Cats.
Here, there have historically
been many cat lovers
and none who are cruel to us,
so naturally, our numbers grew.
There are some other
reasons as well, though.
Barney! Where the heck have you been?
The King wanted me to take a look,
so I was on patrol, Jasper.
You have a scent that takes me back.
You smell kind of like the mages
that I used to see around.
What an overly chatty animal.
Shut it, you prickly Thorn Mage.
I'm not going to scratch up
your bride, so don't worry.
Even cats know about this?
Cats' rumors can easily make it
to the other side of the world.
She just looked at me.
Oh, yeah. Where's this King?
Right next to you.
Hello, mage and apprentice.
You're the King of Cats?
Yes.
My name is Molly.
You must be Chise.
You struck me as odd, choosing to
pair bond with this cranky man.
Shut up.
Pair bond...
I'm glad to see you both here.
I don't know what I would have done
if they'd sent a sorcerer instead.
Would it have been bad if we were sorcerers?
We hate sorcerers, lady!
They're skeevy, lawless lowlifes!
I don't wanna be anywhere near them.
I know you were sent here by the Church.
I wish I could tell you that there
was nothing wrong with our land.
However, we're in a bit of trouble.
You'll help us, right, mage?
That's why I'm here,
although I wish I weren't.
Hey, who are you, miss?
E-Elias...
Who were you talking to outside my house?
Oh, no. I just noticed
the cute cat on the wall.
That's our cat.
Isn't she pretty?
Molly, it'll be time to eat soon.
Come inside, okay?
My owner.
I've looked after her since she
was born, so she's like my child.
She's a cute girl.
I'm proud of her like she's my own daughter.
Elias.
I hate kids.
They don't even have magic,
but they have a strong ability
to perceive the essence of a being.
Sometimes, they can see through me.
I might as well go investigate.
Where are you going?
Something doesn't feel right.
Well, then, I'd like to show you around.
Long ago—so long ago that even we, with our
nine lives, don't have many tales to tell of it—
there was a man here who enjoyed killing us.
Killing cats?
Run as we may, hide as we may,
we were captured,
and our lives were snuffed out.
It was the first King of
Cats who ended that.
The first king gathered the remaining
cats, and together they attacked.
They clawed him apart, chewed
him to bits, drank his blood,
and left not even a trace of him.
Each generation of kings pays for
the reverence we receive by sacrificing
several of our lives in
order to hold the corruption at bay.
That's the price we pay for our veneration.
Look really carefully.
I'm sure you can see it.
It's filth.
The corrupt state of souls
that were never cleansed...
The corruption has been trying
to escape in recent days.
It seeks maniacally and indiscriminately
to take the lives of both cats and humans.
I must not allow it to emerge,
even if it kills me.
For the girl's sake?
What mother fails to protect her own child?
It would be unthinkable, at least to me.
Yeah. I guess.
Chise!
Don't take this personally.
Mina.
Matthew.
I'm home, Mina.
Shouldn't you be in bed?
I'm fine, Matthew.
Here.
Wow!
There were lots of them
blooming by the garden.
I wanted to show you.
Thank you.
How's your fever?
You're still burning up.
Come on.
Shoo.
Get off your butt and go catch
some mice or something.
What's his problem?
That cat seriously only likes you.
I heard there's a wandering
sorcerer in town right now.
I'll ask if they have any good medicine.
I'm sorry, dear.
I always do this to you.
You don't need to apologize.
You've always been prone to sickness,
but I knew that when we got together.
Now, get some sleep.
You better not be knitting
socks or coats like last time.
Fine.
See you soon.
If only I had nine lives, like a cat.
This was my sin,
and my punishment for resting
my laurels on his love.
Who are you?
I suppose you could say I'm the
core of this corruption.
Core?
This man is affixed to me. He won't let go.
It's my fault that he's become
such an abomination.
This man...
Matthew.
My husband.
Please.
For his sake,
and mine...
Wait, I don't know anything yet—
Chise.
Chise!
Elias.
I'm sorry I didn't come sooner.
Are you all right?
Can you breathe?
Yes.
What happened to the one who
threw Chise into the pond?
She gave off a flash and vanished.
There was magic residue all over the place.
It looks like someone's
trying to get in our way.
I'd like to give you time to rest,
but Chise, I have a task for you.
For me?
We need to do something about that, soon.
I want you to cleanse it.
Containing it only delays
the inevitable problem.
We don't need the magic to contain
it, but magic to cleanse it.
Magic to cleanse it?
I haven't had you practice
magic properly yet.
But I believe you can do it.
If I can't, will he lose faith in me?
If you think I can,
I'll do it.
You heard her, King of Cats.
Understood.
I'll clear the place of
as many people as I can.
I'm counting on you two.
Yes, ma'am.
At night, then, when
there aren't any people.
This is a mantle purified with snowmelt.
We use frankincense in the censer.
Let's use a branch of gorse
in place of a staff.
You would normally need
your own chant and staff.
But we'll have to make do.
Is your lecture going to take a while?
An ariel.
It's been a while, Chise.
They'll be a great help for our task today.
Although I don't look forward to it,
especially after what happened.
Cleansing and extinguishing
is what we're good at.
The wind clears away everything.
Meat, bone, even trees and boulders.
We weather it all away.
So we're the best ones for the job.
Speaking of which, why is it me and not you?
I hate to admit it, but I'm not
good at this kind of magic.
My essence is shadow, after all.
I'm not compatible.
It's all right, Chise.
All you have to do is picture it in your mind.
Just wish for it to disappear,
like a spring wind
blowing away the cold winter.
The ariels will guide you from there.
Okay.
Chise, love the world.
The world you lived in may
not have been your ally.
But it wasn't your enemy, either.
Your key is already in the silver lock.
All that's left to do is to open it.
Then again, that's just something
someone once told me.
Do you love this place, Elias?
Sure.
Will he lose faith in me if I fail?
But...
For his sake, and mine, kill us.
How could she say that
with such a calm voice?
How did they end up the way they did?
Don't worry.
Stay calm.
Do I have to wipe them out?
I'd appreciate it if you wouldn't move.
You're from earlier.
Ariel!
Sorry, we have a use for that thing.
We can't let you get rid of it.
No wonder I smelled something unfamiliar.
Renfred.
I'm surprised you remember my name.
It looks like you take good care of her.
Is it because she's your precious
test subject, Pilum Murialis?
Test subject?
Chise! Don't listen to him!
This glove is made of iron fibers,
which you hate so much.
Squirm, and you'll get hurt.
Ariel!
Why would a mage do such a thing?
Mage?
You're mistaken.
I'm a sorcerer.
Poor girl.
Even the fairies are deceiving you.
Deceiving me?
She isn't deceiving you.
We detest lies.
Indeed.
All you do is conceal the truth.
That's how you put this
unfortunate child on a leash,
to try to use her to satisfy
your own curiosity.
Why don't you tell her of the
fate that awaits a Sleigh Beggy?
Of the death that will soon come to her?
Death?
My death?
The girl's heart is rocked by the
truth with which she is confronted.
Will the despairing child's decision
bring an end to the tragic obsession
lurking deep in the Kingdom of Cats?
You mustn't look inside!