Shiina-san?
It's time to get up.
Let's do your laundry.
Shiina-san?
Kanda-kun, I'm opening the door!
I'm opening the door, you hear?
There you are.
Shiina-san, get up.
Shiina-san.
You can't sleep in a boy's room!
Where's Kanda-kun?
I need to scold him.
Sorata?
Where's Sorata?
That's what I just asked you...
When you've finished eating
that, we'll do your laundry.
A-Aoyama!
Uh, um...
Good morning, Kanda-kun.
Huh?
I didn't expect you
to be sleeping in here.
It's your fault for letting
Shiina-san sleep in your room.
Well, I...
H-How about you, Aoyama?
Did you get any sleep afterwards?
Don't worry about me.
Anyway, Kanda-kun, aren't you
busy writing your pitch?
Shouldn't you be sleeping in your bed?
Oh... I'm fine.
Thanks to you, I'm making
good progress on it.
Really? That's good.
Shiina-san?
It won't come out.
That's because you haven't
taken the cap off yet.
Huh?
What's wrong, Shiina?
Shiina-san?
Shiina-san must prefer Kanda-kun...
No! I'm the one on Mashiro Duty!
#06 The Blue After the Rain
"But, O, what damned
minutes tells he o'er,
Midterm Presentation: August 10th
William
Shakespeare's
Othello
Who dotes, yet doubts,
suspects, yet strongly loves!"
The presentation's coming up.
I'm starting to get butterflies.
Momoko, you've been practicing a lot,
so it should be a cinch for you.
But who knows what'll happen
in the actual presentation...
Anyway, I'll be happy as
long as we can have fun.
That's my Momoko!
Hey, Nanami, have you
got your lines down?
Nanami?
Huh? Uh, yeah... I guess.
We're counting on you, Nanami.
Let's all work hard so that
our whole group passes!
S-Sure.
I need to work harder.
I'm home! I did a little
shopping and ran late.
We're having omelet rice tonight!
Yeah, it's quick and easy.
You think omelet rice is easy, Nanamin?
Your womanly charm level must
rank as high as the Himalayas!
You're exaggerating.
I'll go get kouhai-kun and Jin!
It's my job, so I'll do it.
Well, then...
It's too perfect.
Shiina-san, dinner is...
Is this when her magazine goes on sale?
It's the same day as my presentation...
It's not far off now.
Shiina-san, I fixed your button.
Can you put out your laundry, too?
"O, beware, my lord, of jealousy;
It is the green-eyed monster
which doth mock—"
"Which doth mock the meat it feeds on."
Nanami's on edge.
Stressed because you haven't
hit your chick magnet phase yet?
No—
That's an urban legend anyway.
I just said no—
Wait, seriously?!
I really believed it.
Well, in your case,
it's more an issue of whether
you realize it's happening.
Um, Jin-san, do you have a minute?
So, what is it?
It's about Aoyama.
Did she confess her feelings to you?
Do you enjoy teasing me all the time?
Yes.
You're worried about Aoyama-san?
Worried isn't the right word...
Aoyama's smart, and she's better than...
the average person at most things, but...
But I think she should stop
trying to do it all herself.
We're all living under the same roof,
so I think we should
help each other out.
That's totally different from
my impression of Aoyama-san.
Never mind.
But Aoyama-san must have her own
feelings on the matter too, right?
She's found her goal, and had to
face her parents' opposition.
She's been alone since she left home,
so she probably thinks
she needs to handle...
everything by herself.
Besides, there's Mashiro-chan, too.
What? Shiina?
She has to come to terms with that herself.
Are you telling me to leave her alone?
That's what I would do.
I don't know what you'd do, though.
Thinking is good for you, kouhai-kun.
Please don't call me that.
Sorry...
Osaka Art Colleges
Osaka?
Jin-san, what's this about?
Exactly what it looks like.
I'm not going to Suimei.
I'm going to an art school in Osaka.
What? What about Misaki-senpai?
It's not as though we're dating.
But...
Don't say anything to Misaki.
I'll tell her myself.
Don't look so stressed.
Just act like you never found out.
It's that simple.
I don't know how to act around
Misaki-senpai anymore...
What's wrong with you, Jin-san?!
What do you mean, "how to act"?
How long have you been there?!
Only for a minute.
Is something wrong with Jin?
No! I mean... I was talking
to him about my pitch!
We didn't even mention
you for a millisecond!
Me?
Uh, u-um...
I see...
M-Misaki-senpai?
Hey, kouhai-kun.
What do you think I need to
do to make Jin look at me?
"Let's Make a Game!" Pitch
Train Train (Temp.): Original Train Puzzle Game
Downloadable Mobile Phone Content
Entry No. 780411: Kanda Sorata
Senpai, what do you want from Jin?
What do I want?
The things that lovers do...
I want to kiss him.
I want to walk hand in hand with him.
I want him to hold me.
But I don't know how to make it happen.
How does everyone else manage it?
Kouhai-kun, help me.
Senpai, you're cute, so you'll be fine.
Do you wanna play some
games to cheer up?
To pick a fight with me...
You've grown up!
Kouhai-kun, let's play a lot during
the rest of summer vacation!
For me and Jin, it'll be
our last summer together!
Aoyama-san?
Are you all right?!
Don't push yourself too—
I'm sorry! I just tripped.
I'm so clumsy.
Mashiron's
Magazine
On Sale
Nanamin's
Midterm
Presentation
Okay! 10, 9, 8...
7!
Your entry has been submitted.
You...
Sorata.
Ouch...
What's wrong?
Nanami's acting strange.
What?
Aoyama!
What is it?! Mashiron, what's
wrong with Nanamin?!
Aoyama-san?
Nanamin?
Hey, Aoyama! Are you okay?!
Aoyama, you...
I'm going!
I'm going today...
Please, let me go!
This sure is bad timing...
I knew working so hard would
catch up with her eventually.
Isn't her presentation at
her training school today?
She probably tried to leave
early so we wouldn't notice.
It looks like she intended to go.
We can't let her go.
I feel sorry for her, but...
You're right...
I would go.
But, Shiina...
If Nanami wants to go, let her.
Let her go. Please.
Nanami worked hard.
She stayed up late every night.
I know that, but...
Please.
Shiina!
Take your time.
You guys sure are loud.
What's all the fuss about?
Aoyama?
What's wrong?
Nothing's wrong!
Let me see you.
You're going out with this fever?
You should rest.
I don't want to.
I don't care what you want.
Go back to your room and—
The taxi's here!
Hurry!
The princess is mine!
Hey! Hey, wait!
Sorata, the rest is up to you!
Mitaka? What are you doing?
Got it!
Nanamin, get in! Kouhai-kun, hurry up!
Okay.
Go, go! Get in!
Let's go, Shiina!
Okay!
Go forth, taxi! Go, go!
Mitaka! Don't try to cop
a feel in the chaos!
But where there are boobs, I have to...
Don't talk about them
like they're mountains!
Aoyama, are you okay?
Uh huh...
Thanks. I can make it the
rest of the way myself.
I'll be here when you're done.
Okay.
Aoyama-san?! We've been
looking for you! Hurry!
Sorry.
Do you want to go to a cafe?
I'm staying right here.
It'll be a while.
But...
It's my fault.
Huh?
Nanami was exhausted.
It wasn't your fault.
I need to apologize.
Don't bother.
I'm sure she'd only get mad.
You're right.
We left the house in a hurry.
I guess we should buy an umbrella.
Crap...
Do you want to go buy it together?
Sorry! With everything that's been
going on, I forgot it was out today!
It's okay.
It's not okay.
I don't care much about release dates.
Nanohana Hall
Look. It's here.
You're not going to look?
I already know the story.
Yeah, but...
aren't you happy?
I'm very happy.
Well done today.
It's raining.
Let's sprint to the station!
You've got to be kidding!
Aoyama...
Wait, Nanami!
Do you know how much trouble
you caused everyone?
Sorry.
If it was going to turn out like this,
you should have just stayed home!
Let's go home.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for causing so much trouble.
It's fine.
I couldn't do anything.
After you went through the
trouble to bring me here...
I practiced so hard for today.
I let it all go to waste.
I'm the worst... I'm despicable...
It's fine.
It's not fine.
Kanda-kun, you told me that I couldn't...
That I was pushing myself too hard...
I took so much upon myself,
thinking I could do a better job.
But I was just being stubborn.
I'm a stupid idiot!
It's okay, Aoyama.
I don't care if you ignore what I say.
Don't say that.
Smile and tell me I'm
just a stupid little girl.
If you don't... if you don't, I...
Don't say that!
If you're stupid, that makes
the whole world stupid!
What's wrong with you?
Don't be so ridiculous!
Kanda-kun...
You're doing your best.
We understand that.
Why... Why would you say that?
If you say that, I...
I've...
I've been waiting for you to say that!
Nanamin was pushing herself too hard.
She's hard on others and herself.
Or at least, she always tries to be that way.
I finally understand why
you said your impression of her...
was totally different.
I guess she was always fighting something.
Her parents' opposition,
or maybe her own nature.
Maybe she couldn't rely on anyone.
If she gave in to weakness even once,
she thought she'd end up
giving in again and again.
I guess that's what made her stubborn,
and made her put pressure on herself...
If you finally understand that,
that may be its own reward.
Is Mashiro-chan still with Aoyama-san?
Yes...
It seems she has her own
feelings on the matter, too.
Thank you very much.
Good morning.
What is that?
Samgyetang.
I figured a special hotpot would
be appropriate for this occasion.
"Special"?
Because Nanamin showed us weakness!
Weakness...
Anyway, samgyetang isn't
the same as hotpot.
If you sweat the details,
you'll never be a chick magnet.
Hey, Torajiro. What should I do?
How should I know?
Yeah, but what happened
yesterday was embarrassing.
They saw me crying.
I know I had a fever,
but I couldn't stand...
You clung to him the whole time.
It wasn't on purpose!
Don't be such a tease.
Go for it already!
T-Torajiro?!
That's Torajiro?
C-Can't you knock?!
I did. Besides, it was already open.
Did you...
I didn't think you were the
type to talk to pillows.
Don't tell anyone, okay?
This is terrible!
Here.
I guess you can't take
the bowl in that position.
Here.
If you don't hurry, it'll get cold.
O-Okay...
It's good.
You should thank Jin-san.
Anyway...
Yeah.
She held my hand all night.
She seems to feel responsible.
It's not...
Besides, Shiina understood
you better than anyone else.
What?
If Shiina hadn't said anything,
I would have stopped you, but...
She said if it were her, she'd go.
And to take you there.
She begged us all.
She must have been
watching you work hard.
I see.
If I hadn't gone, I would
have regretted it.
I see.
When I look at Shiina-san,
I realize I still have a long way to go.
Huh?
She stays up late every
night working on her manga.
She redraws it over and over.
I assumed talented people
didn't have to work hard.
How can I catch up to that kind of talent?
Catch up...
Don't stare!
What?
At Shiina-san's sleeping face.
Oh, right...
Don't look around the room, either!
Or at me.
What am I supposed to do, then?
And don't get too close to me...
That kinda hurts.
...because I haven't bathed.
I said the samgyetang tastes good.
Good morning, Shiina-san.
Nanami, are you okay now?
Yeah, thanks to you.
Kanda-kun.
About Mashiro Duty...
I'm sorry, but honestly, I don't
think I can keep doing it.
I just can't manage it.
I understand. Thanks for relying on me.
Huh? I'm the one who
should be thanking you.
I'm sorry, Shiina-san.
Mashiro.
I want you to call
me by my first name.
Okay, Mashiro!
Good night.
What?!
Hey, Shii— Mashiro?
Kanda-kun, do something!
You're on Mashiro Duty, aren't you?
Mashiro Duty has passed from Aoyama Nanami
back to Kanda Sorata. -By Kanda Sorata
P.S. - Kanda-kun, I'm sorry for everything.
I forgot to tell you something, so I'm writing
it here. If you do anything weird to Mashiro,
I'll never forgive you! -Aoyama Nanami
There's nothing we can do now.
Nothing will wake her.
What? Wake up, Mashiro!
Mashiro!
Kanda: Mashiro Duty
Sorata.
Dry me.
Okay.
Congratulations on your debut.
#07 Her Homesickness
Yuko's coming!
Yuko is coming.