"When winds blow," Chihaya-chan.
Chihaya-chan, when this poem
was written 800 years ago,
they must have felt very refreshed.
the only sign of summer is the
ritual purification in the waters
They could
probably hear the wind blow...
Silent waves creep closer to the
Suminoe shore, and when night falls,
Got it!
Kana-chan,
I remember.
Speaking of dreams,
there's "Silent waves"!
in my dreams, I creep closer to you
Megumu-chan...
Let's...
have a good match!
Chihaya Furu
Verse 13
In
my
dreams,
I creep
closer
to
you
I couldn't take the one-syllable card on
my opponent's lower right last
time, but I got it this time.
The opponent's lower right one-syllable
cards are always special.
You're taking a card from
right under their nose.
It's so fun!
Ayase's got the momentum now.
That speed confirmed it.
The neural signal goes straight from
Bellatrix's ears to her fingers.
That's the only way
to explain her speed.
And another one-syllable "S" card,
"Swift," was on the opponent's lower left,
but she went straight for "Silent."
That takes guts!
That felt very clean.
I hit the corner.
I was never able to take
a card that way before...
Chihaya-chan, that was a nice attack.
Yep!
The moment you celebrate,
you lose your focus...
My own home is...
As the years pass...
No...
What a waste.
That was a waste.
As always...
Good, Megumu isn't
letting it get to her.
She didn't let the loss
of a one-syllable card
from her own side influence her play.
I can see why she was the
West representative.
Akashi Girls' ace and moodmaker...
The match will be decided by
Ousaka Megumu's performance.
One more card.  Keep it going.
Yes!
I've never played anyone
so calm before.
the sight of a midnight moon
I can't remember how to catch momentum.
So spring nights are short...
S-Same time...
Don't back down!
Fight for it!
I-I think I got that card...
Huh?
I'm not telling you to force
her to give you the card.
Even if you end up losing it, the point
is to make her feel uncomfortable.
Throw her off her game.
I'm sorry!
We touched it at the same time,
so it should go to Megumu-chan...
I'm sorry!
Really?  You can have it then.
What?!
She really gave it to me!
Oh, no!  Oh, no!  What do I do?!
So spring ends...
That was a failure.
She was the one who was
thrown off her game.
She's not made to contest cards...
I need to step up.
I have to step up!
I must step up!
I have to...
The atmosphere and audience make
it difficult for me to move.
A mountain stream...
An empty card!
That was close...
Hanano...
According to Hanano's notes,
the girl with a ponytail had a
towel from an Aoi Ryuji tour.
Is that the towel she
was talking about?
She actually recognized it?
Aoi Ryuji is a singer who's
known for his sappy love songs.
Most of them are about broken hearts.
Which means...
These are the cards...
I know that my heart...
I have to take!
I wanted that card.
I heard that this person is Class C,
but he's tough!
I'm going to find my momentum
in my first match today!
I defended that card!
Let's take the next one, Mizusawa!
Yes!
Hanano-san, you're very observant.
Thanks.
While it brings me no joy, the
road beyond Mount Oe is too long
They did it!
Everyone got my "While it brings" card!
The momentum is shifting this time!
Momentum is when...
...you take consecutive cards!
Simple-minded
After I heard...
She's so stable...
I got it!
Don't worry.  Just start with one card.
Aim for that one card.
Yeah. Sorry, Megumu.
She's so composed, even on this stage.
Megumu is amazing.
But I've been with her
for a such a long time
and I still don't understand
what she's thinking.
I got everyone excited
about making her Queen,
but how does she really feel about it?
Does she want to become Queen?
Chihaya isn't able to
take consecutive cards.
Her deficit is growing steadily.
Chihaya, you just have to win.
Bring home the win!
Did I say the wrong thing again?
This is different from last year.
A year has passed...
A whole year.
on a long September night,
and then I saw a dawn moon
The sky is the road home
for the holy maidens,
An empty card.
She moved immediately, but she
was still able to pull back.
Impressive...
She didn't fall for Ousaka-san's quick reach.
Oh, excuse me.
Good Luck Megumu
She's savoring the moment!
This is the glory of youth!
That headband is now an
Ousaka Megumu trademark!
She used to be the only
one who wore one...
I made these for Nationals.
Let's all wear them.
Huh?
This is to thank you for
the one you made me.
Megumu-senpai...
A beautiful display of friendship!
I'm so glad to be a karuta advisor!
The reason we worship Megumu-tan
is because of the gap in her behavior.
Our lenses know the truth.
Whew, I'd look pretty dumb
wearing a headband by myself.
It was a good idea to have
everyone else join in.
Swoon!
may the wind bring clouds
to extend their stay
The storm will soon carry...
She went below my hand.
She took it.
She'd been losing all of the "The" cards,
but that was a clean win.
Has she figured out something?
That was...
Okay, on to the next card.
One card at a time.
Yes!
This is a team match,
so why am I the only one saying anything?
Queen?
Not interested.
I'm sending a card.
fades to reveal fishing nets in the shallows
What?  "The hazed early dawn mist"?
That's a long multi-syllable card.
Why?
Normally, no one would send that.
Multi-syllable cards are supposed
to be a weakness for her.
Is she sacrificing that card?
so I wish for a memory
of you to take with me
For you, I would have given up my life
A different multi-syllable card!
Megumu?
The speed when she took
that one-syllable card...
The way she broke my cover...
I can feel her screaming:
"I will become Queen!"
I'm not interested in becoming Queen,
but I have to beat her now.
Swoon!
She broke her opponent's cover.
There are plenty of players who can
take certain cards really fast.
To win, you have to overcome
your weaknesses instead of
relying on your strengths.
How much time has she spent practicing?
My point is that you're too sloppy
about covering your cards.
Like this!
How many times do I
have to repeat myself?
You'll never become Queen if you
can't conquer your weaknesses!
now together, I guard it dear
I did it...
You'll do better if you listen
carefully before moving.
I'll help you.
I did it,
everyone.
I did it.
I have to beat her.
The momentum...
...is shifting...
Snap Snap
Taking multiple pictures in silent mode
I hear the beating of cloth...
Got it!
I protected mine!
Same here!
Ditto!
All right!
A-Again...
She couldn't take three in a row.
Megumu-tan celebrated...
Megumu-tan isn't telling her team
to focus on the next card.
Interesting...
This is a high level,
back and forth game.
I'm pleasantly surprised.
She's got good game sense,
and a broad field of vision to boot.
She's watching every card.
No matter what I do,
she's always perfectly calm.
I'm sending a card.
fades to reveal fishing nets in the shallows
She's returning that multi-syllable card.
Th-This is getting good.
That girl's gotta be a sadist.
The hazed early dawn mist
over the Kawagiri River
The card she just sent?!
She was able to set up a
low cover on my side.
That was bad.
I know how to keep people
from breaking my cover.
I've been practicing with
everyone to beat the Queen.
I'm not interested in
becoming Queen though.
But I have to win to
make everyone happy.
I have to beat you now.
Is she mad?
She's strong.
I still have work to do on
multi-syllable cards...
It's tough.
However, I've realized
something, Dr. Harada...
It seems like there are more
people watching our match now.
Akashi Girls'...
I thought that Ousaka Megumu was
the only threat they had.
I was a little excited about my first
match against an all-girls school.
May I see you never forget...
She's strong!
As strong as a boy!
Ousaka is our engine,
but the other girls have also improved.
After all, they've been practicing
with Ousaka to help make her Queen.
It's possible to become this
good if you're motivated.
Akashi Girls' is now a team that's
improving themselves for Ousaka's sake.
Youth...  It brings a tear to my eye...
Megumu stopped providing vocal support.
Is her opponent that good?
The storm blasts...
I was a moment late.
I need to do better...
One millimeter...
One spot...
The green border...
Feel sorrow wash...
I don't remember her having
such a fast motion.
Ousaka moved before she did,
but she still took it.
That reminded me of...
Megumu-chan...
Megumu-chan is me.
Stop taking cards with your speed.
She's who I'd be if someone
hadn't taught me better.
though autumn is not mine alone
A night spent waiting...
The emotions experienced...
She finally took three consecutive cards.
There's nothing flashy about her swing,
but it's accurate.
My lead...
My lead is almost gone!
Okay!
One card!
One card at a time!
I was too loud!
I'm not used to this kind of thing.
Yu-chan...
The sight of the lonely moon...
She swung that hard on an empty card?
She might as well be a guy...
Too manly!
Megumu,
I don't know what you're thinking.
It's possible that you don't
care about becoming Queen,
and you just wanted to
have fun with everyone,
but...
Megumu, I'll secure our first win,
so you can take it easy.
I still don't know what
Megumu is thinking.
Queen...
Scary...
Tough...
Bad...
I'll be playing in the Queen
match qualifier this year.
After all...
After all, how can you not
enjoy becoming stronger?
Megumu-tan, you're a very gentle girl.
You want to make everyone happy.
You want to fulfill their expectations.
We know that you're working
hard for those reasons.
But honestly,
we want to see you succumb
to your own desires.
As I wait...
We touched it at the same time!
But it was on my side, so I get it!
All right!
Trit-Trot
That was mine...
It was mine.
I won that card.
Trit-Trot
But we touched it at the same
time, and it was on my side...
I was faster.
I could tell.
What?  But...
No, I won that.
Megumu...
I was slightly faster!
...is contesting a card!
You can take it then.
She doesn't know how to
contest a card, period!
I knew it
Don't be ridiculous, Yu-chan.
The leader of this team is me.
The person who can make
everyone happy is me.
The one who will challenge the Queen
is me!
What?
I've never seen Megumu
like this before...
I gave up the card she contested,
but that makes up for the earlier one.
It's fine, Ayase.
Just be your usual self.
Okay...
Time to attack!
Mizusawa!
Yeah!
Okay, one card!
One card!
One card at a time!
Y-Yes!
Everyone's watching our match.
The two teams are even.
The tension...
The pressure between the two teams is clashing.