Madam Manager! Madam Manager!
I'll call the young master!
All I ever hear you say
is "the customer."
Because that's
what this job is all about.
We'll find out who the mystery guest is
and show them the time of their life,
resulting in us scoring
high in the rankings!
I can help out with the
preparations for cooking,
but I can't cook anything yet, and I...
I can't be of any help,
so...
All customers are equal,
thus, we need to treat
them all equally.
That's what Madam Manager lives for!
That's what Kissuiso stands for!
Episode 9
The Longest Day at Kissuiso
The train stationed at
platform 9 headed for Morita will be
leaving soon at 14:15.
Sorry for interrupting while
you're all having a great time,
but I'd like for you all
to check out a performance by the
newlywed wife's friends!
Here we go!
Huh?
I don't see him.
Sorry about that!
Tohru?
Umm...
He's about this tall,
and his hair is kind of messy!
Well, maybe it isn't today!
Umm, please let me look at the attendance list?
We can't really...
Sorry to bother you.
Oww...
Nako.
Did you bring tea snacks for
the customers in the Camellia Room?
No, not yet.
Sorry.
Excuse me...
Yes?
I believe I asked earlier for
a yukata with a larger size.
I'm so sorry!
I'll be with you right away!
Thanks.
Yes, of course!
Please get the tea snacks now.
O-Okay!
Hello?
Ohana?
About Tohru?
Yes, she asked if someone had any information,
like which room the ceremony is in.
I have no idea...
I remember him saying it was
his old classmate's wedding.
That's it.
Figured as much.
Sorry, and thanks, Minchi.
Mr. Ren, I've finished
cutting up the vegetables!
R-Right!
Hello? Ohana?
Sorry, we only know that the
wedding is his old classmate's.
What do I do...
There's no way I'll find
him at this rate...
K-K-Ko-
Ohana?
Y-Yeah.
Umm, sorry I wasn't able
to answer your calls.
Don't worry about it.
You seemed to be busy.
Is everything all right?
Y-Yeah, I'm ok...
I mean, not really.
Huh?
So I left the inn,
saying I'd find Tohru.
I'm such an idiot.
I didn't even have a plan.
And even if I were to bring him back,
there's no guarantee
things will go well.
I'm sure they will.
Think about it.
Have you ever thought things
out before doing them?
But things have worked out till now.
Ohana...
Ohana, if you did it, believing
that was the best idea,
it'll definitely work out!
That goes for anything
else in the future!
Ko...
Yeah!
You're right, things
will work out somehow!
Thanks, Ko!
Okay... I'm glad I was
able to be of some use.
You're awesome!
You're awesome, Ko!
You called me right as
I was feeling down!
Oh, sorry, did you need something?
Well.. Not really, but...
Where are you now, Ohana?
At the ceremony hall.
Oh... right.
And where is this ceremony hall?
It's out in the city.
The hotels in this area are gorgeous!
Huh?
The city?!
Yeah.
Wait, where are you, Ko?
I hear something in the background.
I-It's nothing...
It's nothing...
Thank you so much, Ko.
You're always so kind to me.
You always cheer me up.
Even though we're so far away.
Listen, I'm actually-
I'll try my best!
I can't be acting depressed
when you're cheering for me!
Right!
Yeah!
I'll find Tohru for sure!
I'll turn this game around!
Good luck.
Win the game, for my sake, too.
What are you talking about?
You need to win, too,
if you're in a pinch!
Yeah, you're right.
Later.
What am I doing?
Huh?
I get the feeling that Mr. Onodera,
the person in the Paulownia Room you're in charge of,
has been here before.
When would that be?
I think two years ago.
That's before I started working here.
What's that?
Found him! Mr. Onodera!
Look!
Wow, you're right!
So, what is this notebook?
Oh, no!
It's written here that their
daughter doesn't like fish!
I'd better let the kitchen know!
But the notebook...
Do you mind telling me the
age of the newlyweds?!
W-What?
Please, the age of the newlyweds!
I don't need the attendance list!
Just their ages!
Please!
Finally found you...
W-Why...
How?
It's all thanks to Ko...
Hey, what the heck?!
Please go back with me, for Ko's sake.
What are you talking about?!
Let's see...
The train back to the city...
...is 40 minutes from now.
Ohana?
Ko?!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
What?
What do you mean, "what"?!
I can't say it enough times!
I was able to find Tohru!
It's really all thanks to-
Hey, what are you doing?
S-Sorry! I'll be right there!
Be right where?
Hey, Ko?
Where are you going?!
Huh? Back to the Kissuiso, of course!
This is where the real work begins.
I need to prepare myself!
Sorry for the hassle.
I'll text you later!
I'm glad...
Coming, coming!
Hello, you've reached Kissuiso.
Order a massage for the
customers in the Moon Room.
Right now!
Time is money!
And I'll need you to take care of the
customers in the Wave
Room during dinner.
I'm sorry,
Roger! I, Jiromaru, will
demonstrate my best work!
we are unfortunately fully booked tonight.
Oh...
No, it's fine.
Thank you.
What am I doing?
Sorry to make you wait.
A helmet?
The staff at the parking
lot lent me one.
Uh... Sorry, I figured
everything would go well if
I were to bring you back.
You were supposed to be enjoying
your friend's wedding too.
I'm sorry for...
You came here thinking this
would be for the best, right?
Yeah.
Then I'm fine with it.
If you trusted me enough to think
that I'd make everything work,
I'll have to do just that.
What?
Okay, let's go!
I got the feeling someone
told me those same words before.
Hurry.
Okay!
Thank you, Tohru!
What?
Thank you!
Hang on tight!
Umm...
Pardon me!
Inside this oversized helmet was
a scent unfamiliar to me.
So this is what a boy's
hair smells like?
Ko's hair, too?
Well...
According to Minchi,
Mr. Ren is a bit...
different today.
Okay.
Tohru Miyagishi, reporting for duty!
I apologize for being late!
Mr. Ren.
Right. Get to work right away.
Yes, sir!
How did you find him?
It's all thanks to Ko.
Who?
It's a long story.
Then whatever.
Isn't that where you're supposed
to say, "Doesn't matter. Tell me"?
Get to your workstation already.
Do you mind letting Minko
do the frying, Mr. Ren?
Not at all.
Minko!
Okay!
Fry up the tenpura.
Huh?
What, you can't even do that?
What have you been
watching all this time?
Right! I mean...
Yes, I can do it!
I'll do it! Please let me!
Okay!
I felt like I heard the noise of
something starting to operate.
I see.
Is that notebook helping out?
Yeah!
The Madam Manager really is amazing.
I know, right?
Well, I do keep a notebook
of my own, too.
Really?
What? Stop acting so surprised.
Okay, let's get to work!
Umm, Tomoe...
I know.
All customers are equal,
thus, we need to treat
them all equally.
That's what Madam Manager lives for!
That's what Kissuiso stands for!
Right?
Yeah!
I made a mistake.
Bamboo
There.
This is our inn's special meal.
Special bamboo.
Please enjoy!
Thank you.
Please enjoy your stay.
This is so good!
We're done over here, Mr. Ren!
Okay. Now I need you
to do the kneading.
Yes, sir!
Six... Seven... Eight...
The sound has changed!
Right!
Do you mind tasting my fish tenpura?
Sure!
Here.
It's good. Go with this.
Thank you!
Did you note how the oil sound
changed when it was ready?
Yes, sir!
Oh, you were here.
W-What are you doing?!
I was feeling warm and delighted.
What's that supposed to mean?!
Warm, huh...
Well, for her first time,
it was indeed well-done.
I wasn't talking about the
taste of the tenpura.
So, what do you want?
I came to grab the tenpura.
Give me a second.
They'll be done soon.
Hey! Are you enjoying your night?
Y-Yeah...
Are you sure you're enjoying yourself?
Yeah, that's the spot...
Good night!
See you tomorrow.
See you!
And this is how
we were able to get through a long day
without the Madam Manager.
Ohana, the customers in the
Moon Room are leaving.
Okay!
Thanks for everything.
We'll be awaiting your return!
We're bound to score high
if those customers are
the mystery guests!
It doesn't matter who
the mystery guests were.
We gave our all to every
customer, after all.
Yes, but scores are important.
Exactly.
Okay, Ohana, you've still
got some work left.
Okay!
Was this the last of your luggage?
Thank you so much, dear.
You didn't have to do that.
My pleasure. Did you enjoy your stay?
Of course.
I'm glad.
My daughter suddenly said yesterday
that we were going to be staying here,
so things were pretty hectic.
Oh, I see.
Apparently, it had to do with her work.
Mom.
Oops, maybe I wasn't
supposed to say that.
Nah, it's fine now.
You had a good time, right, Mom?
Yeah, I was able to rest so well!
Thank you very much!
Okay, let's get going.
Let's.
Oh.
Let me help.
Thank you.
Ko, it didn't matter who
the mystery guests were.
We treat every customer equally.
Hey, Ko?
It was thanks to you that I
was able to work so hard.
Thanks.
Koichi?
Yes?
The new item that came in yesterday...
I'll bring it right away!
Seriously?
Yeah!
As soon as she saw my
face, she almost fainted.
Imagine how I felt.
That's mean. I was desperate.
This is good!
Yeah, I know!
Guys, she's back.
Thanks.
Welcome back, Madam Manager!
Glad to be back.
No, that's not it, Ohana!
You can't do everything by yourself.
Come home, Ohana.
The Kissuiso can run without me.
Episode 10
Slight Fever