I've lived in this world for a long time.
I see. You're leaving.
Be well.
Oh look, it's the failure.
Don't bother with him.
This is my daughter, Angelica.
Hello.
Poor half-assed monster.
Nice to meet you, though we may
not know each other for long.
The only one who would look just at me
was you.
Have you heard? A dragon went on a rampage.
Where? London?
I heard a human child tamed it.
Not bad.
Who did that?
It's that Sleigh Beggy who can talk to us.
Here, work on this, please.
Okay.
Oh, wait.
I'll leave a note for Tory, too.
Are you okay?
I don't think I've slept much since then.
So you aren't okay.
Do you need anything?
A bowl of mashed potatoes.
With plenty of bacon.
They had leek soup at the cafeteria today.
A mug full.
Got it.
Thanks.
What else did I have to do?
Pick a date to return the dragon,
contact them, and then...
You seem tired.
I hear Master's voice.
Meri.
Lindel.
I'm sorry to exhaust you like this.
It was necessary.
You can't leave that place.
Not until we find the next caretaker,
or the dragons go extinct.
You're a kind child.
Hey, I'm only here because I couldn't
come to like the new times.
But...
Don't be so conceding.
What have you done wrong?
I couldn't become a mage.
I wanted to be of use to you.
I'm a half-assed failure.
If I can't do this much,
I have no right to be here.
He's tired himself out and become a child.
Silly you.
Really, first that redhead, now him.
Humans are strange.
Why not just run away from what upsets you?
It's like they put effort into
making themselves suffer.
I'll never figure that out,
no matter how old I get.
Now we just need to sleep?
That's it?
Those are the instructions on the invitation.
We just have to do what it says.
Let's have faith in it for now.
Thank you for coming.
Marielle-san.
Greetings, young ones.
I am Phyllis, high priestess of the coven.
I'm something of a coordinator.
This person's grown roots...
Thank you for your invitation.
Thank you.
Marielle has told me that you're looking
for a way to rid yourself of the
curse without killing the dragon.
Yes.
My apologies, but we have no
knowledge of how that may be done.
Phyllis!
Marielle, I appreciate your sentiment.
However, it would be uncouth
of us to ask for their aid
when we can't grant their wishes.
But...
Aid?
I attempted to seal away the curse
that has bound me to this tree,
but I failed.
Marielle is trying to use your
dragon's power to save me.
Don't mind me.
All people eventually perish.
But...
Um...
Worry about yourself for now.
It is right to save yourself
before you save others.
I have lived for a long time.
This state of mine is
something of a testament
to the fact that I was able
to lend my hand to others.
Some of them weren't worth helping.
Indeed.
But we have no way of knowing
what the future will bring.
Everyone has the freedom to choose their
own path and decide who they'd like to be.
Someday, that young lady there may
cure someone else of their curse.
I will remain here, eagerly
awaiting such happy news.
Someone I know said something similar.
Oh, it's nice to know another agrees.
All right.
As long as the dragon lives, if we
don't even consider killing it,
we can neither undo nor return the curse.
Is that correct?
As far as we know.
I apologize for turning you away
after you've come so far.
No.
I thank you for allowing us
to join your gathering.
Thorn...
As my apology...
It's difficult to have to choose
one or the other, isn't it?
We might not have gained
anything from that,
but let's keep trying.
Yeah.
I'm going to go help with breakfast.
The only thing that can replace
a life is another life.
Are you going somewhere?
Ruth, you would choose Chise
no matter what, would you not?
Of course.
Denizen of the wind, you're
there, are you not?
Yes.
What a lovely evening.
Lend me your ability to
see and smell the wind.
Consume as much as you'd like.
My, how generous.
I like the way you taste.
Ainsworth?
Simon.
Glad I bumped into you.
I wanted to give this to Chise-kun.
Has there been some good news?
Why?
You have a clearer air about you,
like you have a goal in mind.
You've seemed quite listless for
the ten years I've known you.
I suppose so.
This may be the first time I've been
driven to accomplish something.
Ah, Elias!
Perfect, I was about to go hang out.
Yeah, this is perfect.
I don't have to search for you anymore.
Count to seven and eight...
In the dream in which the child sleeps.
Let's find and count the flowers.
Mommy will give you a bouquet of flowers.
What an awful smell.
Ariel.
Long time no see.
You idiot!
What happened to your body? You look awful.
You wouldn't have ended up like
this if you'd come with me.
You idiot.
It's nothing.
I'll be fine soon enough.
It's like you've been reborn.
I decided to be more positive.
Good girl.
Ariel, you wouldn't have worried about me
if I hadn't been a Sleigh Beggy, would you?
So what?
Elias is up to something.
Without telling me.
By himself.
We agreed to do this together.
Ruth might be in on it, too.
So...
I want someone who will do as I say,
no matter what happens to me.
Right now.
Why me?
You like Sleigh Beggies, not me specifically.
Otherwise, you wouldn't side with Elias, right?
You're not wrong, but I like you too, Chise.
Thanks.
I guess that means I can't give you the job.
So you're going to ask the same
thing of someone else?
No way.
What are you about to do, Elias?
Chise won't last.
This is the only way for us not to lose her.
Well, Ruth?
The answer's obvious.
Elia—
Stella!
Why—
I'm sorry.
Elias...
Ruth...
Sorry.
When you wake up, everything
should be better.
No... don't...
Nevin.
Don't worry.
You'll be able to stand and catch up.
Your ability to do so is growing.
But I'm really scared.
I don't want to know what
I'll find when I catch up.
What Elias is trying to do.
What is he doing?
It doesn't matter.
What matters is to always be
clear on what you need to do.
Why do you always come for me?
I'm not guiding you at all.
The me that exists here is the me that
you've allowed to live inside your heart.
You are the one guiding yourself.
You need not drown yourself in hardships.
Fly strong across the stormy oceans.
What is it that you've decided you must do?
First, I need to know what
Elias is trying to do.
Now, go on.
Everything will better when I wake up,
when I haven't done anything?
Nothing so magical has ever
happened to me before.
Silky.
Thanks.
Ruth.
Get Chise.
Yeah.
She's awake.
That's odd.
You called me a monster,
and now you do this?
You...
Elias!
If I'm a monster for serving
myself at the expense of others...
Then I knew it! You're a monster, too!
Elias!
Help me, Chise!
Stella.
Elias wants to sacrifice me in your place.
He says he's going to transfer
your curse to me.
He's going to kill me.
Chise, get away from her.
She's...
Elias.
Elias, really?
Stella, I'll catch up to you later.
Run as far as you can.
O-Okay!
Chise.
Don't come near me.
You don't go, either.
Sorry.
About what?
For trying to sacrifice
Stella in your place.
I wanted you to let me think
about this together with you!
I never promised anything.
Wh...
Are you...
I'd decided if it had to be
done, it would be Stella.
You look at Stella with a different
expression than you do me.
I can't stand that.
That's why...
As long as you'll live, I'm happy.
You were no different.
Ariel.
Chise!
You aren't going anywhere.
You fool.
Stella.
Car...
Joseph...
Shucks, you got me.
Why are you doing this to Stella?
Let's make a deal.
A deal?
If you agree, I'll give you a spell
that'll ward off your inevitable death,
and I'll give this girl back.
Well?
If you don't...
You understand, don't you?
Chise!
Come on, they're going catch up.
Well?
Chise.
I can't be with you as you are now.
The girl parts ways with the mage.
She follows Joseph down into
the nightmare that torments her.
Forgive me.
Forgive me, Chise.