I've prepared all I can.
Now, I just have to do it
the way I practiced.
I don't ever want to feel like that again.
Finish it!
Boom! Whoosh!
Rat-tat-tat-tat, kaboom!
Senpai, I'm guessing you're
feeling a little better now?
B-B-Boom!
B-B-Blammo!
Crack! Boosh!
Excuse me...
Oh, Nanamin! What can I do for ya?
Um, I was wondering how your
work was coming along...
My heart's just pounding!
Isn't love wonderful?
Love?
Yeah, the script Jin wrote!
I thought it was an action story...
Huh?
Nothing.
What's wrong, Nanamin?
Senpai, could I borrow this script?
Huh?
I'd be grateful if you let me
use this for my audition.
When?
February 14th.
Oh, Valentine's Day!
So, what's it for?
Out of three scripts, I'm allowed to
perform one I've chosen myself, so...
Yeah, I'd love you to perform it.
Use it however you like.
Thank you!
I'm an ally of all hardworking girls!
Okay, it's time for me to work hard, too!
Boom! B-B-Blam!
Whoosh, whoosh, whoosh!
February 14th...
#16 I've Always Loved You
Incoming Call
Kanda Yuko
Onii-chan, good morning!
How can you be so energetic
this early in the morning?
It's you who's not energetic enough!
The Suimei exam is on February
13th, so I'll be staying...
with you the night before.
Okay, okay.
You agreed! You don't usually
accept things this easily!
You'd show up even if I told you not to.
I'm hanging up—
You're so cold! You're as cold as ever!
Today's an important day for me.
I'm presenting my pitch.
A pitch?
What's that? Does it taste good?
Yeah, it's delicious.
What? Really?
Don't take that seriously!
It's a test, sorta.
So you've got a test too, huh?
I'll share some of my energy with you.
You can do it!
Thanks.
Kanda-kun, you look pale. Are you okay?
Your presentation's today, isn't it?
Huh? Yeah, after school.
Sorata.
You can do it.
Th-Thanks. I'll give it my best shot!
Give me a break.
Why are you getting so fired
up on a cold day like this?
Sensei, good morning.
How was Australia?
Forget about that, Kanda.
You haven't even started yet,
and you're stiff as a board, honestly...
Love
Don't worry about being perfect.
What? But I need to do my best...
You don't understand.
I'm telling you to not try so hard.
The new year has begun, but...
The principal goes on forever.
Yeah, forever.
Misaki-senpai?
It's you, kouhai-kun.
What are you doing here?
Huh? Jin-san...
What's up?
That's...
What are you doing?
No one can top my bullfrog impression!
Don't sound so smug about that!
Come on, Senpai. You want to
talk to Jin-san, don't you?
I'll be right back.
H-Hey, wait!
Hey.
Jin-san, aren't you coming
back to Sakura Hall?
Nope. I'll be staying at...
the former Student Council President's
place until after the exams.
Hey, nobody told me this!
I just told you. Thanks.
I didn't agree to it!
Sorry.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Soichiro-kun.
Hau-Hau, I see you've only
got eyes for Soichiro-kun.
Of course. He's my boyfriend.
How innocent.
I wish I could have experienced
a love like yours.
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm not.
Anyway,
I wouldn't want to hog
the precious little time...
a couple gets together before graduation.
Jin-san.
That's the situation.
Let Misaki know for me.
You.
If you're done here, do you mind
taking that bullfrog with you?
Oh, sure...
I'm surprised the former
Student Council President...
knew that was a bullfrog you were doing.
Kouhai-kun, I'll do it.
Huh?
I want to move forward!
So you've got to give it your best, too!
All right!
All I can do is face them with all
my energy, anxiety, and insecurity.
Aoyama Nanami
To: Kanda-kun
I know this might only put pressure on you,
but I still want to say it...
You can do it!
Leave it to me!
Send
At least I can text her that.
I'm Kanda Sorata. Thank you for your...
Fujisawa.
Oh, sorry.
I've never seen anyone actually...
hit their head on the mic before.
I just witnessed a rare sight.
I-I'm sorry...
I'm telling you to not try so hard.
I'd like to explain my "Rhythm
Battler" pitch to you.
It's a rhythm action battle game.
Rhythm Battler
Genre: Rhythm Action Battle Game
Players attack by pushing buttons
in time with the music.
The goal is to defeat the enemy
character before the song ends.
Moving on, I'll explain
what the controls are.
Attack by pushing the buttons in time with the music!
Perform combos to achieve high scores!
The combined effect of video and
music makes this project unique.
Once the player has completed
a song, he can play back...
the video and upload it
as a stylish music video.
Fujisawa, if you were to make this,
Recently, it has become
possible to download music...
how much would it cost to develop?
and video using smartphones
and mobile devices.
Well... Including debugging costs,
probably around 100 million.
What if you outsource it?
Individuals can also easily upload...
Probably 10 million for a prototype...
and 70 million to finish it up.
People would probably make faces no
matter where we tried to market it,
their own videos to express themselves.
but at 2,200 yen a unit,
we'd break even at...
Particularly good videos actually receive...
a greater number of views and
thus garner more attention.
around 45,000 units.
I suppose that would make our
sales target 100,000 units.
In other words, I believe these videos
will do much to promote the game.
I see.
Finally, I would like to
summarize my concept.
Stylishly defeating your enemies in time...
with the music is the core of this project.
I hope to create a game that
exhilarates the player...
and allows them to share
that feeling on the Internet.
A game that is both fun
to play and fun to watch.
This concludes my pitch presentation.
Thank you for listening!
Thank you, Kanda Sorata-san.
Unfortunately, we've concluded
that it'd be difficult...
for our company to release your game.
I see.
However, would you be
willing to let our staff...
help you polish your game?
In other words, you've partially passed.
What? I, um...
When you get home, send us an email.
Game Director
Fujisawa Kazuki
Once we're ready for you,
we'll decide on a date
for our next meeting.
Okay!
The presentation was a huge success!
This is all thanks to you guys!
Thanks!
All right.
I did it!
Cheers!
I know there's no point in
asking, but I will anyway...
Why are we having red
rice and motsunabe?!
Because we're celebrating!
The motsunabe shows respect to Hakata!
Encore, Hakata!
I knew it was pointless asking...
Okay, I'll serve up some for everyone.
It's like eating okonomiyaki
with a spatula.
Kanda-kun, congratulations.
Thanks.
I'm glad you're celebrating with me,
but it takes time for a pitch
to actually go through.
I haven't actually succeeded yet.
Then, we'll have to plan a bigger
celebration when you actually pass.
Thanks. I'll do my best!
Most people don't even make it
to the presentation stage.
Yeah.
Oh, that reminds me.
Thanks for the text, Aoyama.
Sure. I hope it didn't bug you.
It really motivated me.
That's great.
Text?
Yeah, just before my
presentation, Aoyama...
sent me a text telling me I could do it.
Wait.
For what?
Who knows?
Shiina Mashiro
No Subject
You can do it
Shiina, what kind of joke is this?
You said texts motivate you.
If you're going to text me now,
you should be saying "Congratulations."
Your reaction was different
for Nanami's text.
Of course it was.
Is this discrimination?
No!
You only give Nanami special treatment.
Have you forgotten that I give you
special treatment every day?
Anyway, thanks for the pitch
illustration, Shiina.
It made it a lot easier
to explain my concept.
Really?
Yeah.
That's good, but...
What?
Nothing.
It's your turn next, Aoyama.
Huh?
Good luck with your audition.
When is it?
What's wrong?
Actually, there's a favor
I want to ask of you...
Would that be okay?
What did you want to talk to me about?
It's actually pretty important, I guess.
There's actually something I've
always wanted to tell you...
I...
I've always...
Always...
I've always loved you.
I love you!
Uh, um...
Well, um...
I-I feel the same way.
I-I also l-l-lo...
I can't do it!
H-Hey! Don't be so
embarrassed about it!
You're making me embarrassed!
Y-Yeah, but...
We're just acting, remember?
R-Right...
Okay, let's take it from the top.
Sure.
What did you want to talk to me about?
It's actually pretty important, I guess.
Watching Kanda-kun and Aoyama-san
together makes you feel gloomy?
What do you mean by gloomy?
I get this weird feeling right here.
Hold on.
What?
This is an important time for you.
Read these and study them.
And pour all that gloom into your manga.
Pour it into my manga...
What?! Nanami, this is your chance!
Oh, gimme a break.
Mayu, you say that every time.
But it says, "I love you"
in the script, right?
Why don't you use it as an excuse
to confess your feelings to him?
She's right.
If Kanda agreed to help you,
it means he's not against the idea.
Valentine's Day is coming
up, so it'd be perfect.
No, no!
It's just for my audition!
I can't go into that with impure motives!
You're always so difficult.
Just do it.
February 14th is Valentine's Day
What did you want to talk to me about?
It's actually pretty important, I guess.
There's actually something I've
always wanted to tell you...
I've always...
Always...
Why don't you use it as an excuse
to confess your feelings to him?
I can't, I can't, I can't!
Wh-Wh-What?!
Mashiron?
You're working hard, too.
I love you!!
Please accept this!!
Valentine's Day...
Let's move forward with
this game concept.
Rhythm Battler
Okay, thank you.
By the way, that illustration
from your presentation...
Who drew that?
Oh, that's Sakura Hall's...
I mean, someone living
in my dorm drew it.
Sakura Hall?
You're one of Chihiro-sensei's
students, then.
You know Chihiro-sensei?
Yes, we were classmates.
What? Really?!
Her cousin drew that illustration!
I see...
Did she also work on Nyapollon?
Yes, she helped with that.
Fujisawa-san, you came
to see Nyapollon?
Yes, it was a lot of fun.
I hope you'll bring that same
passion to this project, too.
You bet!
This month's Nanohana
Hall is really interesting.
Good job, Mashiro-san!
It's all thanks to my advice!
I'm so excited to see her!
Good evening!
That was delicious!
Misaki-san, thanks for making the joyanabe.
Good luck on your exam!
Yeah! I dedicate this brain
of mine to Suimei High!
I think Suimei would be in trouble
if it dropped to your level.
You're so mean, Onii-chan!
Mashiro-san, this month's volume
was super-interesting.
Yeah.
You perfectly captured how boys and girls...
get nervous as Valentine's Day approaches!
You can do anything if you put
your mind to it, Mashiro-san!
Why are you acting so condescending?!
Valentine's Day is the day after tomorrow.
That's what's going through your head?
Shouldn't you be worrying
about tomorrow's exam?
Yeah, but...
Kouhai-kun, Valentine's Day
is a special day when girls...
are allowed to display their courage!
Misaki-san, nice one!
That's right! Misaki-san,
you're on my side!
She's making it by hand?
I hope she gets to give it to him.
I'm home.
Yuko-chan, welcome.
Good evening.
Aoyama, you left your laundry on
the rack, so I folded them for you.
You didn't need to do that...
I thought you'd be late
coming home again today.
Thanks.
Should I heat up some rice for you?
The bath's ready, too.
Thanks. I'll eat first.
O-Onii-chan, what's your
relationship with Nanami-san?
What do you mean?
Why are you doing all these
things for Nanami-san?!
Something's not right!
Something's definitely not right!
Sorata does things for me, too.
That's because you can't
do them yourself!
There's something I've always
wanted to tell you...
I've always...
Always...
Nanami-san's the one I should be
worried about, not Mashiro-san.
You both act like a couple that's
been living together for two years!
Where did you pull such
a realistic number from?
Sorata.
M-Mashiro-san, you're
dressed too immodestly!
Run, Onii-chan! She'll attack you!
Why aren't you wearing any clothes?
Because you weren't there.
You realize I'm setting out
a futon for Yuko, don't you?
Sorata, you can do it.
Yeah, but I can't warp
or split myself in two!
I'm a normal human being!
Sorata, how long are you
going to keep looking?
What?
At my embarrassing appearance.
What?!
That's right, Onii-chan!
You dirty, nasty pervert!
Don't come here dressed like
that if you know how you look!
What are you going to do if I lose
my cool in front of my sister?!
Onii-chan, you're a brute! A real brute!
Wh-What're you doing, Onii-chan?!
Why are you talking like that?
I'm all shook up!
I'm just drying her hair.
"Dry" not to stress!
You're lying!
It looks like you're getting intimate!
It's nothing to make a fuss about.
We always do this.
Don't make it sound worse
than it already is!
This is too mature for me!
I'm worried about my test tomorrow!
It's okay. You can do anything
you put your mind to, Yuko.
How condescending!
Good luck on your exam.
Thanks!
You can do it, Yuko-chan.
You can do it.
Thanks, everyone.
Oh, before I forget...
Here, Onii-chan!
It's a day early, I know.
What's this?
Mom helped me, but I made you
some homemade chocolate this year.
I've got to go straight home after
the exam, so I'm giving it to you now.
Okay, thanks.
I won't lose to you two!
Onii-chan, good luck!
Huh? Me?
Tomorrow's Valentine's Day!
Who do you really like,
Mashiro-san or Nanami-san?
Dad wanted me to tell you to
stop being so indecisive!
See you later!
Sorata, you're blushing.
So he is.
What did Yuko say?
She didn't say anything!
How suspicious.
There's nothing suspicious about it!
Suspicious.
They say repeating "cacao mass"...
over and over will make
you feel like an adult.
#17 Valentine's Day is Chocolate Day
It seems eating too much chocolate
doesn't actually make your nose bleed.
Not being by Ryunosuke's side on
Valentine's Day is some awful "cacao mass."