Final check of internal Kivotos systems.
Communication systems.
Electronic systems.
Engine systems.
All systems green.
Transferring control authority to Kivotos.
Boost capacitor has reached
engine ignition threshold.
Thruster engine is idling.
Kivotos hangar entrance opening rate
is presently at ninety-three percent.
Releasing docking bolts A0 to F10.
Kivotos thruster ignition confirmed.
Output is rising.
Guidance beacon signal response is excellent.
Kivotos following specified coordinates.
The Kivotos can function as
an independent spaceship,
but it only has standard rocket
propulsion, of course.
Theoretically, it's possible for it
to undergo hyperspace transport
while docked with the Blume via Entangle Link.
But this will be our first time actually doing it.
This is risky...
Navigation system.
Autopilot.
Directional transmitter system.
Check.
Avionics okay.
This will be the first time someone from
Earth has experienced an Entangle Link.
We can't predict what effect it will have
on the two Earth crew members.
We have no data on it whatsoever.
But the captain and Akari will be fine.
That is what I think.
Is that your intuition?
Yes.
I'll trust it.
Come to think of it,
what happened to that thing they
were developing on the lunar base?
You really do know everything.
Lunar base?
The Planter Unit.
Planter Unit?
Originally, Hana was the one at
greatest risk with the ark plan.
Hana couldn't leave the Blume on her own.
The ark plan would try to force the Blume to move
without regard for her safety.
I didn't like that.
That risk is still here.
However, they were developing
something called a Planter Unit
on the lunar base, where there isn't
much brain wave resonance noise,
which would transfer Hana's brain wave resonance
and bioinformatics to the Blume externally,
allowing it to be controlled remotely.
Commander Nishikubo was developing it,
so that if it became necessary
to use the Blume, we could
minimize the risk to Hana.
I'm fine.
I've got the captain.
Then what's the Planter Unit's status?
Only Commander Nishikubo knows that.
But if there were even a one-percent
chance that it would work,
he would have told you about it.
Yeah,
I guess you're right.
Pointer screwed up.
Yes, he screwed up.
The future of the chosen boys,
humanity's hope for survival,
is being cut off by the Intercept Faction.
That's how it seems to me.
But the cold sleep block is still
aboard the Tenkaidou.
Rewinding the clock to the
ark plan is still possible.
There's still time.
But they will launch the Blume soon.
We cannot let that happen.
It is we who will use the Blume.
It doesn't matter if it gets a bit banged up.
We must retake it, no matter what.
Eternal life...
If I really had such a thing, what would I do?
It is truly a hard question for a
snob like myself to think about.
For example, whatever it is you enjoy most today,
like that delicious wine...
What must you do to enjoy it forever?
Or how to enjoy time with beautiful ladies.
I think that is what I would think of.
To consider it a bit more realistically,
in my case, if I were to live for eternity...
I may be a little irritated by the
size of the world I have to live in,
and the fact that there are still
so many things I do not know.
Yes.
First, I'd be irritated.
This may not be the answer you're
looking for. Please forgive me.
Puck does not lie.
Ah, I got that wrong.
As Kube Masaki, send that as my
answer to Peter Westvillage.
Understood.
Amarok and the others' full-scale attack...
...is about...
...to begin.
The Operation Summer
Now, let's get started.
Bugbear and Setsuna-sama will soon
return with the last capsule.
It's nearly time.
The last night on Earth.
The end of this planet, huh?
This planet wasn't that bad.
Nor was this avatar body.
That crêpe truck we ran together
was pretty fun, wasn't it?
What are you talking about?
He'd feel irritated first, huh?
Commander.
We're in contact with the Kivotos's
bridge and the Tenkaidou.
Commander, we heard about the Planter Unit.
Akari again?
That isn't even close to complete.
The research team did their best, but...
I'm sorry.
Thanks, though.
I heard that you made it because
you were concerned about me.
You can be pretty nice sometimes!
G-Governor Yomatsuri!
But it's true.
DEFCON 1?
Everyone, this is an emergency.
Over the last one hundred and twenty seconds,
the phenomenon we saw in Tokyo where
everyone within a given area goes into comas
has occurred in no fewer than twenty-five places.
We can assume that the Planetary Gears
have been gathering high-density libido
on a scale unseen up to this point.
According to a report that's just come in,
Alonzo's predictive simulations suggest
there's a 99.98% chance that all the
Planetary Gears on Earth will launch
a full-scale attack in Kiltgang form.
99.98%?
A full-scale attack?
Seven Kiltgangs attacking at once?
And it could happen right now?
Commander.
I understand there's no time to waste.
The Midsummer's Knights will now launch the
attack on enemy fortress carrier Oberon,
in orbit around Uranus.
Protect the Earth.
Roger.
They can do this, right?
Yeah.
Let's go swimming again, Teppei-kun!
Roger.
We'll be back, Governor.
Hana!
We'll be back, Mom!
I'll be waiting.
Teppei-kun,
take care of Akari.
Right.
Wipe out the enemy, and come back safely.
Those are the terms of success for this mission.
Got it?
Roger!
Daichi?
The anniversary of Taiyou's death is in a week.
Let's go visit his grave together.
Right!
For sure.
It's a promise.
They're the team we hoped for.
That's what I think.
Yeah, you're right.
Everyone, you heard the situation.
At this very moment,
the enemy might launch an attack
with seven Kiltgangs.
Our ship, the Blume, will head
for the fortress carrier Oberon,
in orbit around Uranus.
If I concentrate on the Entangle Link,
I can't use the Blume's normal weapons
or change our course at all.
Don't worry.
We'll protect you.
Leave it to us.
Okay.
I'm going to the Blume.
Hana, are you sure about this?
Captain?
When this mission is over,
let's go to a festival and eat
a candy apple together!
Hana?
Captain...
When you destroyed that debris back there,
I thought to myself that you've
become a real captain.
You should have it, as proof
that you're the captain.
I'll be a real captain
when this mission is successfully completed.
Until then, keep it for me.
Got it.
Hana, can you hear me?
I can hear you.
Can you use your Livlaster?
I can.
I'm starting up the main engine.
Okay, I'll let you handle the timing.
Let's save the Earth together, partner.
Yeah. Leave it to me, partner!
Looks like they're attacking
with the Blume, after all.
They have the Blume and the Livlaster.
Ai's failure with that debris plan hurt us a lot.
What?
It's all my fault?
Does Albion really intend to destroy
the cocoon and all our Ego Blocks?
I don't really know.
Does Albion intend to die here,
in this solar system?
If the cocoon is destroyed, we won't
be able to go to other systems
after eating all the Earthlings' libido energy.
But it appears they're bringing
their usual group of friends.
Daichi Manatsu and Akari Yomatsuri, too?
If their minds can handle the Entangle Link,
it's possible that they'd take them.
Well, having a Neoteny around would be helpful.
I can't imagine an Earthling being able to
withstand an Entangle Link's hyperspace transport.
Their weak minds are less than human.
How arrogant are they?
Well, it doesn't matter.
This will be good fun before our attack.
An Impacter has appeared in front of the Blume.
Omega sector.
Distance: 150,000.
An Impacter?
The Garm Engine...
A massive Impacter developed by the
Ark Faction to capture the Kiltgangs.
It must be Salty Dog.
At a time like this?
Didn't we tell you we'd protect you?
You concentrate on the Entangle Link.
Roger.
Teppei, Akari...
Let's go.
Roger.
We will now begin Operation Summer.
In terms of size, that monster's
as big as the Tenkaidou.
It's entering our firing range, Captain.
Mid-sized Impacters are splitting
off from the Garm Engine!
It's Cerberus!
Cerberus?
I'll head out in the Earth.
Take care of the ship, Teppei.
You understand, don't you, Captain?
If something happens to you,
Hana won't be able to leave the Blume.
Yeah, I know.
A beam cannon?
The Earth Engine has left the
ship and engaged Cerberus.
It's leaving the Blume behind.
The Blume has engaged the Garm Engine.
That's the Livlaster DC's barrier.
Wow.
He can use it from the Kivotos.
I guess we can't damage it from long range.
It'll hurt us, not being able to
use the Blume's weapons...
What do we do?
Form a strong image in your mind
of the place you want to go.
I can see it.
Akari,
it's connected.
We can jump soon.
Roger.
Captain, you heard that, right?
The Entangle Link will begin soon!
Hurry!
That stupid kid thinks he's a hero.
Don't interfere with our plan to save humanity!
Why are you interfering?
This mission is
to save Earth!
We're entering the Entangle Link?
But the captain isn't back yet.
No...
Hana?
I can't stop...
I can't control it anymore!
Captain, hurry!
Don't let them escape, Garm!
Hana...
When this mission is over,
let's go to a festival and eat
a candy apple together!
Yeah,
it's a promise!
Get there!
Oh, no!
I can't dodge it!
Daichi?
Time to get up.
Okay...
A dream?
I woke up to find myself in my room.
I'm Daichi Manatsu,
a second-year high school student.
And summer break starts tomorrow.
A normal, everyday life.
But why?
The wind in this town feels wrong, somehow...
And I keep thinking about the
dream I had last night,
but I can't remember it.
Next time, on episode 23 of Captain Earth:
A Midsummer Night's Dream
A Midsummer Night's Dream.
Earth Engine... What's that, again?