I'll rip you apart with my fangs, Earth Engine!
What's that?
A planetary sign?
Albion!
What?
Albion... What are you doing?!
Teppei, is that you?
Albion appeared...
And it interfered with me.
What?
Something bad is about to happen.
We need to check this out.
Assault of the Planetary Gear
Having a summer break like this is a nice change.
Hey, Pitz.
Want a watermelon seed?
You're too worried about Hana to eat, huh?
Just like Daichi?
I'm worried about Hana...
But what about Teppei? Will he be okay?
It won't do any good for you to get depressed.
That's true.
Belly Button...
Belly Button Forte!
Well? What do you think?
Wh-What do I think? What are you doing?
This is the beautiful, beautiful Akari-chan
showing you her belly button
as a magic spell to make you feel better!
Belly Button Forte!
See? You feel better, don't you?
Yes... A little, maybe.
Okay...
Then let's bust our way in!
Last night's earthquake was caused by
movement of the ship on the sea floor.
We believe she used her own body
as an energy relay circuit
to activate Machine Goodfellow
Aramusha's main systems.
We know she has an unknown type of organelle
in her body that we Homo sapiens don't.
Our hypothesis is that the energy she used
is a variant of the Orgone energy
that is stored on the Blume.
These are the results of the mental
health test, the forensic psychiatry test,
and the thought examination system
that we conducted this morning.
He was very cooperative with all the tests.
Good morning, Teppei.
That Machine Goodfellow you used last night
was secretly taken from Macbeth Enterprises
during the Kanda incident.
At the same time as you, in fact...
We knew it was able to recognize you specifically.
That's your own personal
Neural Maneuver System.
I didn't know.
Until yesterday, that is.
Macbeth Enterprises
ostensibly developed it as a man-machine interface
for the latest mobile weaponry, but early on,
we realized that it had a greater function...
No, that it had been developed for
an entirely different purpose.
But we didn't know what it was for.
Were you controlling that Kiltgang Type-3
that appeared in the Earth Engine's combat zone?
No, I don't think you were controlling it...
You were that Type-3, which is
still floating in Alpha sector.
Weren't you?
Thank you... That's all.
He was the Kiltgang itself?
What do you mean?
Until yesterday,
Teppei had the mentality of a 17-year-old
boy who was born and raised in Japan.
Looking at him, I never doubted that for a second.
But what about now?
I'd be very interested to learn about
his memories and consciousness,
now that he's become a Kiltgang.
This fact constitutes a threat.
It is of grave significance in determining
the course of the battle from here on.
Commander!
Until we have more information,
this matter is classified top-secret.
That goes for HQ, too.
Of course, you realize that decision is outside
your authority to make, right?
To me, the most important fact is that
Teppei's Kiltgang saved the Earth Engine.
You aren't going to the base?
First, we need to eat.
You just ate that watermelon...
That doesn't count.
How about a crêpe? They're good!
Want one?
Okay, I'll take a banana crêpe.
I'll have a mango crêpe.
Coming right up.
Your belly button won't become magical
if you show it all the time.
Or maybe it will?
Here you go.
Thanks!
Want some, Pitz?
Here you go.
Thanks.
Hmm?
You shouldn't waste food.
That's right.
That's a big trailer.
I travel around Japan selling crêpes.
Today's my first time on this island.
The wind feels good here, doesn't it?
The wind?
Does it?
Can we come in?
Just a second...
Okay, you can enter.
Those look good.
They are good!
Hana's undergoing a physical
exam at the medical center.
Where's Teppei?
Room 45, in block C.
That's the interrogation room.
Stop touching things without permission!
Oh, that place...
It's kind of depressing.
Fine... Go and see him.
Aren't you being a bit soft?
When I was a kid, I was kind of proud of this.
But once I realized how strange being able to
make a rainbow appear over my hand was...
I avoided doing it again.
I pretended I couldn't do it anymore.
I often dream,
but when I'm awake, it feels more like a dream.
Somehow I knew that the real me
wasn't the person I am now.
But you're you, right?
Thanks. You saved me.
You really surprised me this time.
I heard your crêpes are really good.
But you can't enter without permission... Sorry.
You can't give us permission yourself?
Maybe we'll just go in ourselves!
I can't change the base's security measures.
You know, you can't fool a machine, right?
If you go in, something scary will happen.
Well, I wouldn't want that.
What?
What's going on?
It's easy to fool machines.
Too easy.
My cute little bunny has taken
over their defense system.
This is...
What is this?
What's going on?!
The base's antipersonnel fortress
system has been shut off...
What?
Something's happening in block C!
They're after Teppei?
Rita, Thunder... Come with me!
A direct attack on HQ itself?
Salty Dog? The Ark Faction, maybe?
No, I haven't told HQ about Teppei yet.
If they're after Teppei, that means...
I have a bad feeling about this.
You're Alaya, right?
No... I don't use that name.
Well, your avatar name doesn't matter.
You're Albion, aren't you?
His memories haven't returned?
That's impossible...
He abreacted into the Kiltgang.
Right?
I've been looking for you.
I was really worried about you.
Why did you interfere yesterday?
Are you a traitor?
No way.
Teppei!
Don't move.
Where's Daichi-kun?
Over there!
Daichi!
Throw down your weapons and surrender.
You're outnumbered.
I'd rather not waste food.
Yeah...
These guys' libidos will eventually feed us.
They're...
Daichi-kun!
Good, he's alive!
Then, are you two...
Who are you, anyway?
The crêpe seller, right?
I am the Planetary Gear Amarok.
And I'm the Planetary Gear Malkin.
Do you regard Earth's humans as food?
Yeah, basically...
But that's what the people of this world want.
I'd rather not waste food,
but if you want to fight, I won't hold back!
Logical, logical...
Be careful. The antipersonnel fortress
system is coming on line.
Logical, logical! Bye-bye, naughty rabbit!
Okay!
Hang in there!
She deactivated my rabbit?
This really is a bit scary...
Then let's run like rabbits!
Wait!
Stop!
What is that?
A mobile weapon?
Let's wreak some havoc, Tenrohsei!
That's their mobile weapon?
Stop it!
Albion...
Stop doing this!
It's me you want, right?
If you come with us,
we won't hurt any of them.
Not that they'll survive long either way.
Daichi?
Where are you going, pretty boy?
You're trying too hard to look tough.
You belong here, with all of us!
Daichi!
What do you think you can do here, Earthling?
I'm saying...
He's...
Teppei is one of us!
Neoteny?!
I won't let you have Teppei!
Moco, he got me...
We're leaving.
I've never seen that Livlaster before.
That isn't the one from the Blume.
It may have materialized here.
That'd make it the Livlaster Tanegashima.
But I can't believe a neoteny appeared
from one of the Earthlings.
Maybe Albion really does want to betray us?
He couldn't.
The feeling of being a Kiltgang...
That's a sense of pleasure he can never give up.
They're a terrifying opponent.
They looked like young children.
Are they the enemies we're fighting?
No matter how they look,
if their Kiltgangs reach Earth,
we lose.
Oh, welcome back.
Akari-san's amazing, Commander.
She's the one who brought our
defense system back on line.
Was she?
So, where is she?
She said she was tired and going home.
Akari Yomatsuri.
Teppei Arashi.
Hana Mutou.
And Daichi Manatsu.
What do you think, Science Chief?
What do you mean?
When you look at them, don't you feel something?
Feel something?
All I can say is that I have no logical proof of it.
You want to feel something, don't you?
You want to feel that something in them.
The Kivotos Plan team is in artificial sleep
aboard the Globe Orbital Base Tenkaidou.
One of them, the person who
gave Teppei their genes,
is targeted by strange enemy spies.
Teppei decides to...
Next time, on episode 5 of Captain Earth:
Starry Sky's Picture Book.
Starry Sky's Picture Book
Earth Engine, expand!