It was a cliff.
A cliff?
It wasn't a height that we could jump from.
Sister wasn't lying,
and the demons didn't underestimate us.
With that cliff,
security wouldn't be necessary.
So that means we can't escape from the wall?
Well...
there is a way.
So I tried going to the edge of the wall.
It split into two more walls.
One side continued along the cliff.
The other wall was the side of our House.
The angles were about 60 degrees each.
The inside of the two walls,
where it splits, were nearly symmetrical.
I saw the same scenery in front of me.
It means this Grace Field House is on
a hexagonal property surrounded by a cliff.
And the lot west from our Plant Three
is probably the headquarters.
That lot was the only one with a bridge.
If we're surrounded by cliffs, then crossing
the bridge will be the only way to escape.
Norman!
Mom is calling you.
- Tell her that I'll be right there.
- Okay!
Well, I should get going.
W-Wait a minute!
Norman!
I'll give this back.
I didn't use it.
You...
So you were planning to return
from the start, huh?
You said so yourself, right?
That we'll stay alive together!
But you were already planning to...
Yeah. Sorry, I lied.
I can't afford to make a mistake.
Because I can't let anyone die.
If I run away, the plan will deviate.
If it deviates even a little,
it'll be problematic.
I don't even want a chance of losing.
It's pointless to argue.
I won't change my mind.
I did what I can today.
I'm leaving the rest to you.
Make sure the escape succe—
Wait, Norman.
So warm...
Thank you for everything.
Because of you two, I had a good life.
I had fun.
I was happy.
I was fortunate.
Damn.
Damn it.
Damn it!
Hey, Norman.
It's still not too late to run away.
Run and hide in the forest.
Like I just said,
I'm not going to change my mind.
See you.
You've caught a cold again.
No more snowball fights, okay?
We can't play with Norman?
Not until he gets better.
So listen everyone,
don't enter the infirmary for a while, all right?
Okay.
E-Emma!
I came to visit!
Why? You can't come in here.
But Norman, you always feel lonely
every time you get sick.
I didn't want you to feel sad.
I'll talk so you don't have to, so let's hang out!
No, we can't. You'll catch my cold.
I won't.
I was told that I don't get sick.
Oh, Emma!
When did you sneak in?
What would you do if you got sick, too.
But Ray said I'll be fine.
Ray?
This book said idiots don't get sick.
In any case...
you can't be here.
Don't go near the infirmary anymore.
Understood, Emma?
Okay.
I'm back!
- Emma, you can't...
- Here, this is for you.
A cup?
Ray taught me how to make it.
Emma!
Geez, you really don't give up, do you?
He said we can talk by using these!
Hello?
Norman, can you hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you.
Ray!
Amazing! Now we can talk
even though I'm out here! Yay!
If you yell like that,
you don't even need the string phone.
Oh yeah.
Thanks for waiting, Mom.
Sure. Let's go, Norman.
Everyone's waiting.
- Don't get sick, okay?
- Good luck.
Norman!
Sherry, please don't cry.
Instead of a crying face,
send me off with a smile, okay?
Okay.
Norman...
Phil.
Can I count on you to help Emma in my place?
Yes.
Emma, where's Ray?
The infirmary.
He said he didn't want to see Norman off.
I see.
Don. Gilda.
Take care of Emma and Ray, okay?
O-Of course. Leave it to us!
Emma.
Take care of everyone, okay?
Okay, everyone. Goodbye.
Norman!
Thank you for everything.
- See you later!
- Good luck!
- Norman!
- Bye!
Norman!
Emma.
I'll distract Mom.
Please, run!
Idiot! I know you're reckless,
but this is too far, Emma!
This isn't what you should be doing right now!
Shut up! I won't let you go!
A fight?
Why can't you understand?
I'm not wishing for any of that.
I just want you to send me off with a smile.
Please understand how I feel.
No. I just can't respect those feelings!
Especially if you don't even want to go!
You're crazy, Emma.
Reckless and unreasonable.
Naïve and immature.
But honest.
That's why...
That's why I...
It's time, Norman.
Okay, Mom.
W-Wait!
Emma, calm down.
I understand that you're sad,
but you're getting too hotheaded.
If you cause another commotion, I'll kill you.
Give up.
Mom, is it all right...
if I say my last goodbye to Emma?
Yes, of course.
Come, Emma.
Emma.
Thank you.
I'm sorry for tricking you.
Don't get anymore injuries, okay?
And don't be reckless.
Eat properly, okay?
I'm leaving the rest to you.
It'll be okay. Don't ever give up.
Emma!
Your suitcase is empty.
Yeah, almost.
Because no matter what I put in,
I can't take it with me.
You wouldn't have ever ran away.
I knew it from the beginning.
It's praiseworthy. You're doing the right thing.
Now I can ship out Ray and Emma
when they're mature.
Until the end of the time that was decided,
happily inside home, right?
Yes. Spending a happy lifetime.
Hey...
are you happy, Mom?
Yes.
I am happy.
Because I was able to meet someone like you.
This way.
Can you wait in this room for a little bit?
Good morning, my dear children.
Remembering to appreciate that all 37 of you
are able to live here happily...
Thank you for the food.
Emma!
That one flew up high! Super high!
Emma looks so sad.
I've never seen her look like that before.
Yeah.
It's not just Emma.
Ray, too.
He's been really depressed.
They both must be lonely.
Well, the three of them were good friends.
So, what did you want to talk to me about?
We have to decide what to do, right?
From this point on...
I don't care.
Let's die here.
It's impossible. We're surrounded by a cliff.
And the only bridge going out
is in the headquarters.
Besides, I'm tired.
I'm really tired.
Then what about this?
I don't need it.
You can have it.
If you want to run away, then run.
I'm dropping out.
Sorry, Emma.
Emma.
Ray, come on!
Sorry.
I'm sorry, Don. Gilda.
I did knock.
You didn't hear it?
You poor thing.
You're in pain. You're suffering.
Norman is dead, and Ray's a mess.
You can't do anything on your own.
You must be extremely despaired.
Now, you will never be able to escape.
Just give up.
The best way to not suffer from despair
is to give up.
You suffer because you resist.
Simply concede.
You'll feel much better. It's easy.
Listen, Emma.
If you desire it, I'd like to recommend you
as the candidate to be Mom of this farm.
A candidate to be a Mom?
Yes.
Become an adult, have a child,
and if they approve your abilities,
you can come back to this House
as a Mom or Sister.
You have the qualifications for it.
If you desire it,
I'd be happy to recommend you.
"Who would become such a thing?"
Is that what you thought?
But then, what can you do?
You can't do anything. You can't save anyone.
You can only curse death.
A cycle of suffering.
Live and strive to become a Mom.
Accept the despair
and free yourself from the pain.
No. I can't do that, no matter what.
Fine. Then you can writhe in agony
as you await your death.
You all cannot escape.
Think about that as much as you want.
We did it!
Wait for me!
Emma.
Ray.
What are you doing at this hour?
It's my last night,
so I'm saying goodbye to the House.
Ray, it's your birthday tomorrow, right?
Yeah, tonight's the last night.
Tomorrow, it's goodbye.
Hey, Emma.
Did you really give up?
You haven't actually given up, have you?
Emma.