A Day at the Marui House
We're leaving!
Bye.
I think you'd better stay home today.
I'll go...
There's gym...fifth period...
You come home right away
if you get any worse.
O...kay...
And dress warmly.
Warm clothes...
F-Futa-
Good morning, Youngest-san!
Boy, you're really working that aura today!
Hey.
Man, Youngest-san's aura really sends
shivers up your spine, huh?
Chiba, she's right behind you!
Where?
RIGHT behind you, turn around!
Probably just a ghost or something.
That would be all the more
reason to turn around.
A ghost?! Where where where?
No, it's not...
Is that really Futaba-chan?
That cold's sucking the life out of her.
Let me write purification
spells on her body!
Oh shut UP.
You can't go to gym.
Can too...
This HAS to be Youngest-san!
That's so rude.
Maybe I'll go home instead.
See? Nipples only ever runs
up to Youngest-san.
But she's right...
Th-There's two of them!
Can you not even see her without the aura?
F-Futaba-chan!
N-No...
She passed out too!
We need to get them both
to the nurse's office, now!
Full recovery!
I just needed to sleep it off!
Well that was easy.
Where's Youngest-san?
She's got a fever, they're sending her home.
Did your cold transfer to her?
Wait a sec...
If that cold made Futaba as weak as it did,
who knows how bad it'll
affect Youngest-san.
Probably so bad she'll be able to
curse us with a single glance!
Hito!
Hit the deck!
You okay, Hito?
Who's the babe?!
P-Please, be my friend!
Please!
That's one hell of a cold.
Mitsudomoe...
This's the cat you were talking about?
We feed it every day.
Yeah, yeah.
Tonight's the night we convince
dad to let us keep it!
It'll never happen.
It said "Meow, I wanna live with the Maruis!"
It did not!
You bring a cat into this house
and there's a real chance it could get hurt.
See, I told you so! I knew it'd never happen.
It'll be fine!
Besides, the kitty even said, "Meow,
I wanna live with the Maruis!"
IT DID NOT!
Well, if that's what the cat said
I guess I've got no choice.
Really?!
Hey!
Yay, hooray!
That stupid cat didn't say a thing!
Did so.
Geez...fine, do whatever you want!
The Next Day
This is way too much.
Why do I have to carry
this stupid cat stuff...
You keep complaining but
you're still helping.
I just happened to have some free time!
The...the kitty's not here!
Even that cardboard box is gone.
I'm sure a really nice, kind
person picked it up.
Hito...
Do something!
What?
I know!
See, one pet's more than enough
for the Marui household!
Oh, it's saying "please train me
to be an obedient slave!"
I did not!
Don't just go back to normal, stupid!
All right then...
Here kitty kitty kitty!
Hey cut it out, you're making a mess.
She's fully transformed...
Oh come on, you're ignoring me now?
You were my pet to begin with, you know!
Come on, shake hands!
Cats don't shake hands.
Need something...that works on cats...
Jackpot!
Now for my ultimate trick,
silvervine powder!
S-See? I win, she's my pet!
I'm home.
How'd...
Aah, I picked it up by the river
on the way home from work
but the cops took me in for
questioning three times,
which is why I'm late.
How sweet.
Too heavy...ouch! Get off!
You two are really getting along today!
I don't want a pet like this!
Mitsudomoe!
Serious Squadron!
Gachi Rangers!
It shines.
It flies.
Now you can battle monsters
all by yourself!
Serious Squadron Gachi Rangers!
The Serious Alloy Gachi Red analog model!
Analog model...
Ooh, Serious Alloy Gachi Red!
Another toy? You're such a baby, Hitoha.
Ooh, the belt shines!
Ooh, the head launches!
No, kitty-
I'm super nervous this week because
I'm going around visiting parents at home.
A strong link between the home and school
environments is essential
to a good education!
Of course, now I'm on
my way to the biggest hurdle of
my career, the Marui house...
Who knows what'll happen.
What the hell's that aura?!
I don't wanna go I don't wanna
go I don't wanna go!
Err, where's your father?
At work.
Still? You told him what time
I was coming to visit, right?
I told him "be back by 5
o'clock" this morning.
This morning...
If he's busy, he's busy,
but you could've at least told me
when a good time would've been.
There is no good time.
Home visits are very important!
How impertinent.
I'm THIS close to getting
really mad over here.
So where are Mitsuba-chan
and Futaba-chan?
Dunno.
I'm only gonna wait ten more minutes!
You're going to impose on
me for ten more minutes?
I wanna leave now...
Be my guest.
Stop reading my mind!
What?
Do you mind if I watch television?
Go right ahead.
I have just one goal I want to achieve,
to be the best teacher you've ever seen!
Sometimes I'll have to get strict
with the student body,
but one day all the kids will look up to me!
Hold it, wait a sec Yabecchi,
you'll never make it, not in a million years.
Micchan told everyone "that
lousy bum's my slave"
and they all thought she was being sincere-
Turn that off!
I am such a wuss-
A cat!
You got a cat! I love cats.
Stupid cops, making me late...
Why'd she want me to be
home by five, anyway?
How cute...
You're such a sweet little thing...
That's a man's voice.
W-Who's there?
I can't get enough-
C'mon, stop-
Ooh, you're extra soft down here!
Not there, stop!
Him...!
That's enough, hands off now, please.
Oh come on, I wanna play some more.
That's enough, please don't touch me!
Aww come on, don't be shy...
I'll murder you, you stinkin' scumbag pedo!
Hey, where're you going?
To do my homework.
At least leave the cat to keep my company!
Don't follow me.
Was that your father?
Something tells me that's not him...
A burglar? He's out for blood...
No, umm...he's...
It's locked!
Not this one too!
Our room's the only one that's open.
Umm...
All right, you stay hidden under the covers!
Don't worry, I'll protect you.
I'm trying to tell you, he's-
Hide!
It's the burglar!
Forget it, I'm scared too!
D-Dad...
Hitoha! Are you safe? Did he hurt you?!
Dad?
Oh, so you're their father!
Wow, I was sure you were a burglar!
Let's say I was...what's that make you?
Huh?
I, err...uh...
You see...
I see what?
H-Hitoha-chan!
P-Please, hear me out! I'm actually
Hitoha-chan's teacher-
That makes it even WORSE!
He hasn't given me any trouble...
What happened at the triplet's place?
Actually, I think I have a pretty good idea.
Mitsu...domoe...
Yabecchi's Room
That was the worst segment ever...welcome
to Yabecchi's Room.
Today's guest is the youngest
of the Marui triplets...
Where's Hitoha-chan?
Why do you always pop out
from under my legs!
I don't want to disappoint.
Well I've got a weak heart, so knock it off!
You didn't even try to help
me in that last seg-
Settle down
Today's guest is the youngest of the
Marui triplets, Marui Hitoha-san.
Today's guest
Marui Hitoha-san
What interesting topics will
we talk about today?
Time's up.
Goodbye.
Yabecchi's Room - Fin
Mitsudomoe?
She wins 3rd prize! Free tickets
to the amusement park!
Micchan! Amusement park,
amusement park!
YES! My era begins now!
She wins the GRAND prize! An all
expenses paid trip to Hawaii!
That's awesome, lady!!
I've never seen anyone win the grand prize!
My era is OVER
Sometimes lady luck decides
to side with you!
Please, my karma's so good
this is totally normal.
Only two...
Do I go with Futaba?
No, no, I won't go if daddy's not coming too!
Or Hitoha?
There's no weight limit so
you'll be okay, you pig.
W-Wait...
T-The gondola will tip over,
don't move a muscle...
I'll never make it.
Then again, she probably
won't wanna go anyway.
Amusement parks are for
babies, like your panties.
I can't wait to go with you, Micchan!
You don't mind?
Why would I? Or do you not want me?
Guess I have no choice!
Just don't go crazy, okay?
Okay!
Wow, you won a lottery prize?
They're for this Sunday.
Tokyo Domeland, huh?
Yup, Futaba and I are-
I wanna come too.
Tokyo Domeland has Gachi Rangers
events every Saturday and Sunday.
You can meet the actors, get autographs,
take pictures with them...
Wow, you sure know a lot.
I did a lot of research...I've been
wanting to go for a while...
I wanna meet them too!
And see Gachi Pink's boobies!
Well, I guess we can afford one more tick-
That reminds me!
I've got plans with Sugisaki on Sunday!
Gotta get a little face time with the servants
every now and then, you know?
You two babies can have the tickets,
I didn't even wanna go in the first place.
Huh?
The next day
Where're you and Sugi-chan
gonna go, Micchan?
We're, uh...
Hey Micchan, those tickets you won...
So get this!
This Sunday we're taking a
day trip up to Hokkaido!
Oh awesome, Hokkaido!
Why're you talking to Mitsuba, Futaba?!
Say it to me!
You must be really excited, huh?!
Right?
Just so we're clear I'm not
getting you any souvenirs.
Yeah, just so we're clear I'm not
getting you any souvenirs!
I heard her.
Is she interpreting?
Yeah, crab, potatoes, sea urchin,
all that good stuff!
Yeah?
The heck? You're being a zillion times
more annoying than usual!
Look.
This ticket admits TWO people
So these tickets are enough
for four people to get in!
Well Futaba...
Right, you, me, Micchan can't come...
So daddy and one more...
Shin-chan!
Futaba...
Hey Shin-chan, come with us to the
amusement park this Sunday!
Whoa, where'd that come from?
I mean it sounds cool and all...