Speak in a Confrontational Manner
What's this? Some kind of joke?
What do they mean by "confrontational"?
I guess... talking badly about each other?
Then, you're an idiot...
If you don't have a sundae with me,
I'll hate you.
I can do that anytime, damn it!
Day of the Promise
I couldn't sleep.
Then tomorrow evening, at eight...
Will you join me for coffee, in my room?
Yes.
I-I'm nervous.
Nervous, nervous!
This is the first time I've ever
invited someone to my room.
What if there's an awkward silence,
or I end up saying something rude again?
Th-Thank you.
My pleasure.
He's the same as always.
That's right...
No need to overcomplicate things.
Sorinozuka, you're spraying soup everywhere.
We're just drinking coffee together. That's all.
Huh? Oh, sorry, sorry.
Just stay calm. Stay calm...
Eat in human form. Where are your manners?
It's more comfortable this way.
Miss Ririchiyo.
I shall peel the grapes for your dessert.
I already told you I can do
that stuff for myself!
But then your lovely, delicate
fingers would get stained.
At this rate, I won't be able to eat
anything by myself anymore.
Exactly.
That is why
I shall...
No.
He really is the same as always.
Keep calm.
Keep calm...
Chiyo?
The day's only just started, you know?
I don't think I'll be able to take the pressure.
Why did I say eight in the evening?
I should have made it right after school.
Isn't this milk coffee too sweet?
Not at all!
No, I have my plan.
I picked that time for a reason...
Chiyo?
She's so weird.
I'm going to make my first coffee with
Miketsukami absolutely perfect!
That's why...
Speak in a Confrontational Manner
What's this?
Some kind of a joke?
What the hell is this?!
That's more like a line from a
cop drama than confrontational.
Hey, you...
Nice boobies.
Your boobies are nice, too. Damn you!
They're really doing that...
So you think you're too cool for this, tranny?
Now that's confrontational.
Gold Assortment
So what are you doing here?
There are so many delicious things here.
I'm sorry, but I have shopping to...
So delicious!
I told you...
I have shopping to...
Here.
Are you even listening to me?
I guess I'll have to...
This is the only—
I-It isn't too bad.
These are so good.
Here.
But this is the last one.
This is so good.
I suppose I could say it isn't too sweet,
with a balanced tartness.
That's so good.
The fruit has a proper texture.
It's quite juicy, with a well-rounded scent.
I guess I'd say that it isn't not tasty...
Don't Talk
What's that?
Who knows?
Some kind of joke?
Just so you know,
it wasn't me.
Are you saying you wrote that?
What? Do I have something on my face?
If you're doing something silly again,
I'm gonna get mad.
Do I have something on my ears?
Ears?
Can you get it off?
Now, now...
Why are you apologizing to me?
Did you get it off?
No, no.
Then, I'll see you later.
Yes.
Bye.
All right!
Delivery for you.
It's a musk melon!
Thanks.
A mask melon.
Once you eat it, you'll be...
It's not M-A-S-K, like things worn on the face.
It's M-U-S-K, as in the scent.
It has a musky fragrance,
which is how it got its name.
It's a wise tranny!
Are you mocking trannies?
Just give me the melon.
It's perfect.
Now I know why I set the time
for eight in the evening.
To get everything ready,
and make it all perfect.
I still have four hours...
There's too much time left.
It's Roromiya.
Hello?
Studying for a test?
Doesn't this take you back to our youth?
It does indeed...
You aren't that old.
This is so wonderful.
Sitting here, beneath the lush greenery,
with two beautiful, studious girls...
Two, together!
I'm here, too!
Hey, what are you guys up to?
Watanuki's class has a quiz next week.
Huh... So that's why you're all studying?
I had some time left.
I only accepted the invitation
to kill some time.
What a brat.
Time left? You have something to do later?
Naturally.
I'm not like you.
I guess you're busy...
Manchu Han Imperial Feast
Quarter note
Hideyoshi Toyotomi
Photosynthesis
Perry
Perry.
Perry...
No, it's a math problem.
They won't ask about Perry on a math test.
Manchu Han Imperial Feast
Quarter note
Hideyoshi Toyotomi
Photosynthesis
Perry
Perry?
Fine...
Then, why don't I give you a history question?
Who was the fifteenth shogun,
back when the black ships sailed into Japan?
Three.
Three?!
Oh...
I want to be a pencil!
Huh?
Is anything wrong?
This is a pretty tough problem.
Ah...
May I borrow your pencil for a moment?
If you take the number here...
I see.
And then, you get this.
You're not a bad teacher.
It is an honor to be of service to you.
I was too ashamed to meet you
without any education,
so I studied on my own.
I am glad I could be of use.
Good for you.
Not that I'm one of those
who believe you need a degree
to be respectable.
You're studying pretty hard...
...for a delinquent.
Yeah, because I won't let that
damned fox's partner beat me!
You'd better get ready!
With this test, I'll pay you
back for the walk rally!
He's still thinking about that?
Watanuki, you're so petty!
Shut up!
Oh, you're going to pay me back, huh?
Well, I suppose I can't deny your spirit.
Shut up!
I'll make sure you'll never be able to
run your mouth like that again!
It's on!
He's really getting worked up.
Sorry, but I don't get into stupid, petty com—
I have a great idea!
Everyone's here today, anyway.
So why don't we settle it now,
rather than next week?
The inaugural Ayakashi Kan Partner Games!
Partner Games?
Everyone will team up with
their partner for the games.
Huh?
Wait... You're saying we have to play, too?
And I'm the organizer.
So I can't participate this time.
Sob, sob.
Then who's going to be my partner?
Me.
Uh... Well, I guess I'll do it!
Then let's begin the first game!
It's called "What's Inside This Box?"
What's Inside
This Box?
That's it. I'm out.
You won't play with us?
When rabbits get lonely,
they die.
Wait. I'll play.
Weight.
Smell.
Sound.
Does she know the goal?
Probably not.
Explaining......
That's what the game is about!
There could be bugs inside?!
So what is it? What is inside the box?
What is it?
Well, ah... You have to guess.
So I can touch it, right?
Oh, Sou... Sou... Sou... Sou!
Blush
There aren't any bugs or anything
dangerous in the box.
Good.
Talk about over-protective.
The correct answer was a scouring brush.
Scouring Brush
Team Shirakiin-Miketsukami Pass
And now for Team Watanuki and Karuta.
Watch this, Karuta!
I'll...
Huh?
Karuta?
A lobster.
She's good!
The correct answer was a spiny lobster!
Spiny Lobster
I need some wasabi and soy sauce.
She's strong!
Team Watanuki-Karuta Pass
Now, Team Nobara!
Go on, then!
We're really doing this?
Seriously?
I sure am!
Step right up!
But I get freaked out easily.
Ugh, what is this?
It's gummy... Freaky.
Konnyaku Gelatin
The correct answer was konnyaku gelatin!
Sorinozuka, you're quite normal.
What? Are you saying I'm forgettable?
No, you're comforting.
Team Nobara-Sorinozuka Pass
And now, on to round two!
It's time for the Partner Quiz!
Partner Quiz?
You answer questions about your partner!
It's an exciting game that tests the bond
between your partner and you!
Questions about your partner?
Will I be able to answer anything
about Miketsukami?
This is going to be difficult...
My first question is to Karuta!
What are Watanuki's favorite
things about school?
I'm a delinquent,
and delinquents have no favorite...
He likes the athletic festival,
the culture festival,
and the school marathon.
And he likes field trips.
Well, if I'm forced to participate,
I guess I will!
That is absolutely correct!
And the next question is to Watanuki!
Where would Karuta like to go for a date?
A d-date?
Karuta!
I guess I could take you out
to eat something good...
Okay.
They're in their own world!
Then, the next question goes over here!
Karuta, Karuta...
Yo.
What does Nobara Yukinokouji's favorite word...
Maniac!
What does that word mean?
Sexy?
No!
Are you listening?
When I say "maniac,"
I'm going from this...
to this!
Yes, maniac.
From this...
to this!
Yes, maniac.
Karuta looks best in thigh-highs,
not knee-highs!
I don't get it.
Look.
From this...
to this!
Yes, maniac.
From this...
to this!
Yes, maniac.
And for your information,
Ririchiyo isn't tsundere. She's tsunshun.
Well done.
Depressed
After her hostility, she gets depressed.
So she's tsunshun!
Don't get them mixed up!
You're really getting into this!
Please don't create a category for me.
It's a shame about Nobara.
She has the looks...
Those feet! Those tiny feet...
They're not even feet, they're tootsies!
And now, a question for you, Nobara!
I don't care about men!
Well, then.
I have a question for Sou.
That was harsh...
Oh? How so?
Yes?
Here it comes!
Is Chiyo
Cat Person
a cat person or a dog person?
Dog Person
If I had to pick one,
she would be a dog person,
but she likes cats, too.
I chose one because I had to.
But I believe she likes both.
Chiyo?
He's correct.
When it comes to food, she prefers
easy to digest foods, with carefully
selected ingredients.
She dislikes strongly flavored or greasy foods.
I guess I really do have that preference.
She also avoids spicy food or
things with a grotesque appearance,
such as sea cucumbers.
Miketsukami...
In terms of clothing,
she prefers black, white, gray, blue, brown.
If the color is too strong,
she tends to choose less bright fabrics.
Enough.
She generally sleeps seven hours a night.
She usually takes her bath
directly before going to bed.
Stop!
One of her true pleasures is to read
a bit before she goes to bed.
Miketsukami, stop!
If you'd like to know,
right now she's reading...
Enough, already!
I'm very sorry.
I simply could not control myself.
Learn to control it. You're an adult.
But thanks to all that, my turn never came.
All right!
Time's up!
The end!
But we don't have a clear winner!
Want to continue by yourself, Watanuki?
What good will that do?!
Th-Then,
will you meet me in my room, at eight?
I will.
Chiyo's been on edge since this morning.
On edge?
But I'm glad she's gotten more comfortable.
What do you mean?
She means to relax, relax!
I don't get it.
Don't Talk
Is this one of Natsume's pranks again?
Did Natsume do this?
I-I didn't think of that!
You are very cute.
Not the point!
Don't Talk
So, how long are we not supposed to speak?
How long are we not
supposed to speak?
Huh?
You really are very cute.
May I take your picture,
to commemorate this?
Again, not the point!
We're in the lounge, so we can speak now.
What was that?
Another paper?
Read the other side out loud.
Assignment One
Draw the Shape of Tokyo
Assignment One: draw the shape of Tokyo.
What's this now? A quiz?
Whose prank is this?
You didn't do it?
Or the flyers in the hall?
What? It wasn't me.
Chiyo, it saddens me that you'd suspect me.
I-I'm sorry...
But then, who's doing this?
Let's see...
The winner gets a Blu-ray recorder.
Will someone bring me a sheet of paper?
You're doing it?
What shape, exactly, is Tokyo?
Someone once told me it's
shaped like a potato bug.
A potato bug?
I saw one, not long ago.
You saw one here, in the city?
I saw one in a Friday night movie.
Done.
Now I know what you saw.
Do you really think Tokyo looks like that?!
Yeah, it isn't like that.
It's more like...
This.
You've totally forgotten the task at hand!
You're pretty good.
Ren-ren, you're good!
You think?
Yeah.
You're getting further from
the original objective!
There's another one.
Assignment Two
What's the Antonym of "Antonym"?
Assignment Two: what's the
antonym of "antonym"?
Idiot
Not Participating
Spectating
It's "synonym."
Smart
Now, the prize for the quiz is a
seven-day trip to Hawaii, with Master Kage.
Wait, Master Kage?
Don't tell me...
Wh-What's going on?
That's right... It's me!
Master Kage...
Then, those signs...
So you finally figured it out.
I see you're unable to hide your
surprise at discovering it was me.
Thank you for welcoming me,
my human toilets!
Don't worry... It's not scary.
It's Karuta Roromiya.
Next time, on Inu X Boku Secret Service...
Hold it!
Didn't expect me to take over
your announcement, did you?
I, Kagerou Shoukiin, have taken
over this time slot!
I am going to enjoy toying
with and shaming you!
Are you shivering yet, my human toilets?
Meat
Oh, you're quite the sadist, trying to turn
off the screen while I was talking.
You, who butted in... You, too!
You, eating that rice cracker,
The Unfaithful Dog
you're a masochist disguised as a sa—
Mask melon... No, maniac!