I always thought it was kinda boring...
that every day was the same.
I pretended it was someone
else's fault that nothing happened.
But...
This is terrible...
Waking up to a cat's backside...
My adolescence is too
terrible for words.
Waking up to a human's backside
has its own problems, too.
Goal: Escape from Sakura Hall!!
Misaki-senpai, please
don't sleep here!
I want to be a bride when I grow up!
One of the rules of this world is that...
spouting nonsense is only
acceptable if you're sleep-talking.
Welcome home, honey.
You're back early.
Are you a bride already?
Would you like dinner? Or a bath?
Or maybe...
a loincloth?
This isn't a sumo ring.
A brush?
Just get to the "Me?" part already!
However! Let's play a game!
Using that conjunction
makes no sense!
Let's pick up where we
left off yesterday!
Not to mention, school starts today!
Okay, how about a
rule that requires me...
We have to get ready!
to take off one article of
clothing every time you beat me?
You look ready to protect your eyes.
Get super excited!
This is just another
part of being young!
Let's climb the staircase to adulthood!
It's a lust connection!
Hey, Kanda.
Sensei, what's with your
provocative cleavage?
The entrance ceremony's today!
Ceremonies are generally social
gatherings used for finding a man.
Are you planning to put the
moves on the new students?
You're such an idiot.
Toolbox
There might be some
hot single fathers there.
Anyway, here.
Huh?
Sakura Hall
Why do I have to fix this broken sign?
Hey, look, this is Sakura Hall.
Suimei University of the Arts
Oh, the place where they stick
all of Suimei High's problem kids?
That's right...
This is Sakura Hall.
Sakura Hall
A collection of all the problem
kids at the high school...
affiliated with Suimei University of the Arts.
Or in other words...
Kouhai-kun!
I'm pretty hot without my clothes on!
In other words, a den of freaks!
Bam!
The resident of Room 201:
Third year fine arts student,
Kamiigusa Misaki.
Kamiigusa Misaki
Fine Arts - Third Year
Has Alien Qualities
Designed, animated, wrote, and edited...
her own anime all by herself,
which was commercialized
and became a smash hit!
Kouhai-kun, you can't call
yourself a man if you run off...
before we even get started!
Come! Let's leap into the world
of carnal desires together!
Carnal desires?!
Hey, Sorata.
I'm back.
The resident of Room 103:
Mitaka Jin
General Studies - Third Year
Has Bourgeois Ladies' Man Qualities
Scriptwriter on Misaki-senpai's anime,
and General Studies student, Mitaka Jin!
However!
I'll call you later.
He comes home the following morning...
in a manner unfit for a high school student!
Let's see... Tomorrow I've got
the race queen Suzune-san,
and this weekend, it's
Rumi-san, the office lady...
And I'll see the young
wife again next week.
Young wife?!
Someone else's wife?!
Well? Are you done yet?
Art teacher, Sengoku Chihiro:
The supervisor of Sakura Hall.
Sengoku Chihiro
Supervisor
Has Amazon Qualities
B: Ambition
W: Dreams
H: Hopes
She's currently exceeded level 30...
and is looking for a husband!
I'm 29 years and 15 months old.
Subject: Shut Up
Sender: Akasaka Ryunosuke
Ryunosuke-sama has received
work from S Company.
He is currently in the
process of developing...
sound-compressing middleware.
If you bother him, he will
send you a virus, lol!
From: Maid-chan.
M-Maid-chan?!
The resident of Room 102:
Akasaka Ryunosuke.
Akasaka Ryunosuke
General Studies - Second Year
Has Hermit Qualities
A second year General Studies
student and programmer...
who already has contracts
with major businesses!
The auto-reply AI mail program
he created called Maid-chan...
"Those who ask rude questions such as 'How old are you
supposed to be?' (Sorata-sama) will be firmly punished."
-I am not "supposed to be" anything! (duh)
is his only connection
to the outside world.
He will send you a virus, lol!
Looks like we shouldn't bother him.
Do you want to go again?
Don't!
Then, there's me, Kanda Sorata.
Kanda Sorata
General Studies - Second Year
Ordinary Qualities
A General Studies student with average
looks, average intelligence,
and no remarkable qualities whatsoever.
When you finish the sign,
stop by the faculty office...
during lunch or whenever to let me know.
Oh, and don't be late for school.
You're one to talk!
Chihiro-chan, good luck
with your spouse hunt!
If you can't find anyone,
kouhai-kun said he'd marry you!
I never said that!
Damn.
For the time being,
my current goal is...
to escape this place!
To escape Sakura Hall!
Goal: Escape from Sakura Hall!!
Suimei University of the Arts High School is
divided into General Studies and the Arts.
Our arts program is further divided
into music and fine arts...
I'm exhausted...
You get all the bad luck.
Oh, Miyahara.
A person of average willpower...
could never handle living
in that den of freaks.
You can say that again.
And?
How long are you going to stay
in Sakura Hall, Kanda-kun?
Aoyama...
Oh, Nanami. You're in our class, too?
If you don't leave soon,
it'll be too late.
You still haven't found
anyone to take Hikari,
and you've taken in
six more, haven't you?
You must have no integrity.
You keep bringing
girls back to your room?
Don't say things that'll
give people the wrong idea!
They'll think I belong in Sakura Hall!
It's ridiculous. That day...
I've made up my mind.
I'm taking her home with me.
What?
But you can't keep her
in a regular dorm.
I'll do everything I can to
find an owner for her.
I'll just hide her until then.
What if someone finds her?
I'll cross that bridge when I come to it.
But, in the end...
Principal
You must choose between...
abandoning the cat or
leaving the regular dorms...
and taking up residence in Sakura Hall.
What? Sakura Hall?
Very well.
I will go to Sakura Hall.
Kanda-kun?!
Sakura Hall
If you keep getting more cats,
you'll never be able to come
back to the regular dorms.
Kanda-kun...
But ever since I took in Hikari,
I've been finding cats in
cardboard boxes everywhere!
Meow, meow, meow...
I can't help but take care of them!
You're definitely cursed.
Cursed or not,
I can't just leave them there!
You're such a nice guy.
Huh?
What?
I-In any case, if you
really want to get out of there,
you need to think more constructively.
Here, it's for Hikari and the gang.
Conveni-Mart
Chikuwa, huh?
I picked up some of the things...
we couldn't sell at the
convenience store I work at.
It's not normally allowed,
but they made an exception.
You've got a lot on your plate.
You're holding down a few jobs
at the moment, aren't you?
Yeah.
Do voice acting schools
really cost that much?
Guess so.
You're amazing, Aoyama.
You came here from Osaka on your own,
and you work so hard.
There are chances for me out here.
General Studies  |  Arts
There are training schools,
and Kamiigusa-senpai let me
do some voices for her anime.
These aren't experiences
you'd normally get.
In that case, why don't you move...
into Sakura Hall and take my place?
Th-That's a different matter.
I'm not talented like Kamiigusa-senpai
and everyone else.
I need to work hard in my own way.
Oh, Kanda. Good work.
Did you fix the sign?
Yeah, it won't budge an inch now.
What about you, Sensei?
Did you have any success
at the entrance ceremony?
There weren't any hot single men.
I did exchange numbers with a
few hot married men, though.
And you call yourself a teacher?!
At least be aware of your profession!
It's shocking!
I forgot that before I even
left my father's testes.
That's the first time I've ever heard
a woman say the word "testes!"
Testes aside...
Here.
She's my cousin,
and she'll be staying in...
Sakura Hall as of today.
Shiina Mashiro
She's coming over from England.
Her name is Shiina Mashiro.
What? She's staying at Sakura Hall?!
That can't be good for her upbringing...
Meet her at the station at six o'clock.
And pick her up after school, too.
I have to run another errand for you?
What is this, a quest?!
Are you some kind of RPG barkeeper?
There, there, there.
Hello.
Hey, you're Kanda's kid!
The mackerel's good today.
Hello.
Sorata-kun! Good timing.
I just fried some croquettes,
so take some with you.
Thanks.
Sorata-kun, it can't be easy for you.
Fukuoka, was it?
You should have gone with your parents.
Well...
Don't be stupid!
A time comes when a
man's gotta become a man!
Ambition! It's all about ambition!
Flower Clark
Isn't that right, Sorata?
"Boys Meet Ambitions."
That's right. Meat. Eat your meat.
Ambition, huh?
I wasn't thinking anything so daring...
Maybe I really should have
gone with my parents.
Hey...
What color do you want to be?
Me?
I've never really thought about it.
Then, think.
I haven't decided what I
want to do in the future,
but for now, I guess I'm iridescent.
Iridescent?
What about you?
What color do you want to be?
I've never really thought about it.
What kind of answer is that?
At this moment in time,
I'm probably white.
Just like your name.
I'm Kanda Sorata.
Chihiro-sensei asked me
to come and meet you.
Chihiro, you say?
How old is this photo she gave me?
She's at least three times older...
But...
somehow, I knew it was her.
Sorata...
Sorata is nice.
It has a beautiful ring to it.
I like it.
Welcome to Sakura Hall!
We're having negima hotpot tonight!
Here we go! Ready and boom!
Thanks for the food!
Eat up, Mashiro!
Here at Sakura Hall,
we always celebrate
by throwing a hotpot party!
Oh, there he is.
"Please place Ryunosuke-sama's
portion in a separate bowl,
and cover it with plastic wrap."
"No onions. From: Maid-chan."
Negima without onions?
Wouldn't that be just "ma"?
Here, Mashiron.
Have a thick, slimy one.
If you don't bite it
carefully and gently,
hot juice will squirt out everywhere!
Squirt!
Cut it out!
What? What's with that
innocent reaction?
Convention dictates that
you can only get excited...
by vegetables until your
second year of middle school!
I don't believe you two!
So, you're from England, Mashiro-chan?
You're going to attend Suimei High, right?
Unbelievable.
A transfer.
She's a second year art student.
Art?
Let's see...
Her height is 162 centimeters
and her weight is 45 kilos.
From the top down, that'd make her
sizes around 79, 55, 78.
Huh?
You think her breasts
are a little small?
Don't act so disappointed.
With such a small waist,
her breasts will look bigger with no
clothes on than the numbers suggest.
Believe me.
What is wrong with you?!
Hey, Hikari!
Sorry, she's usually really friendly.
What's gotten into her?
I will now screen the Mashiron...
welcoming anime I made!
When did you make that?
Wait, you knew Shiina was coming?
Switch on!
Mashiron!
I've been waiting for you to come...
to Sakura Hall, boom, whoosh, bang!
Let's be friends forever, whoosh!
Okay, rat-tat-tat, boom, boom!
Nice to meet you, Mashiro!
The voice-over and the content...
have surprisingly little
to do with one another.
How is this a welcoming
anime for Mashiro-chan exactly?
You just wanted to do a quick
screen check for your new animation.
That's also correct.
Did anything bother you?
Well, actually...
If anything, it was kinda amazing...
What? That's all?
The timing of the last explosion.
Could you shift it back four frames?
You're so right.
It does come in a little early.
I could add some in-betweens or...
Why don't you add some white frames, too?
It's hopeless once they start with that.
Ah, I see. In that case,
I should probably make the
lighting effects stronger here.
They're usually a ridiculous pair,
Is the high contrast just
for film processing?
but they get serious when it
comes to making animation.
Yeah. I thought it'd work with
some color correction, but...
It's no good. She must
think I'm worthless.
If she's studying art,
she must be unbelievably talented, too...
What's wrong, Hikari?
You're awfully moody today...
Goal: Escape from Sakura Hall!!
I always thought it was kinda boring...
that every day was the same.
But, after taking in a pure
white cat over the summer...
and coming to Sakura Hall,
I finally realized something.
It wasn't the days that were boring...
but myself, for being like someone else.
Yahoo!
Jin, try and catch me!
I'll pass today.
You're all up early this morning.
So we are.
Um, Sensei...
Why did Shiina come to Sakura Hall?
Couldn't she have stayed
in the regular dorms?
Dreams
Because this place suits her.
You'll look after Mashiro, won't you?
Well, it is her first day.
I'll at least show her the way...
Listen. Make sure you take
her there properly.
Make sure you take her
there responsibly.
That was kinda creepy...
Second Floor Girls' Dorm
No Boys Allowed
I don't have a choice.
Orders are orders.
Hey, Shiina.
If you don't get ready
soon, you'll be late.
Huh?
Please Knock
Mashiron's Room
Hey, it's morning!
She seriously isn't answering.
Hey, I'm opening the door.
Shiina?
A burglar? No, tornado damage?
Hey, Shiina!
Shiina!
Where are...
Manga?
It's incredibly good...
But...
What is this?
They ran into each other on the way...
to school and fell in love?
Where did the romantic rival
who kept dropping hints go?
It's over already?
This is...
U-Um, Shiina-san?
Could you please wake up now?
Hey, it's morning. It's morning.
Morning will never come again.
No, it's here!
Don't say such scary things!
Good morning.
You're so loud.
Hey! What are you... you...
What?
Put some clothes on!
Why are you naked, anyway?
Are you one of those people?
I wonder why I'm naked...
Try to remember!
I got in the bath...
You got in the bath! Then what?
I took out my clothes...
You got out of the bath!
Okay, now you just have to put them on.
I took everything out.
Okay, stop!
Is that the reason
this room is so chaotic?
After that, I figured it
didn't really matter.
What kind of thought process is that?
If you took your clothes out,
then wear them! Here!
Are you decent?
Yes.
Listen, I know you're from England,
and I'm sure there are some
cultural differences, but...
What's decent about this?!
Put your clothes on already! Hurry up!
What about my underwear?
Put them on!
But which ones?
Don't make me choose for you!
Then, I won't wear any.
You have to wear some!
Wear some! Put them on!
Please put them on!
Here, pass!
These panties aren't cute.
They're yours!
Oh, crap! Hey, hurry up!
I'm ready.
Your head! I mean, your hair!
Go fix it in the bathroom.
While you're at it, wash your face!
What is this?
My image of Shiina is
slowly crumbling...
Sorata.
Are you finished?
Hey!
Hey, you! Put something on!
Some kind of underwear!
You didn't put anything out for me.
It's my fault? Don't you
think that's kinda weird?
The floor's wet.
Do you have a custom of
bathing in the morning?
Damn that lazy teacher...
She pushed all of this onto me!
Iridescent.
What?
You mentioned it.
Is that a color?
Oh, yeah. It's sort of rainbow-colored,
but it means an ambiguous color, I guess...
Why are you asking about that now?
Sorata, you're interesting.
I took in a pure white
cat over the summer...
and moved into Sakura Hall...
And...
that spring...
Sorata.
We'll be late for school.
You're one to talk!
I met a pure white girl.
Sorata, you're so domineering.
Use your own legs to run, then!
#01: Cat - White - Mashiro
Today's panty forecast is:
#02 I Drew a Picture
Green panties represent...
a possible storm brewing.