I send you my greetings, Elder Sister.
It has been four months since I left Japan.
In answer to a request from Lord Horikawa himself,
I am acting as a spy in London.
Oh, a "spy" is something like an onmitsu or a ninja.
Morning comes late for a spy.
We often work deep into the night,
so we are much like owls.
I wonder why Westerners sleep
so high off of the ground.
And they don't remove their footwear
when they come inside.
This makes their feet stink.
S-something stinks!
This girl is Beatrice.
She is the daughter of a baron,
and she and I are in the same year at school.
What is this smell?!
It's you, isn't it?!
How rude! I bathe every day-
That's not what I meant!
You brought something in here, didn't you?
Last time it was those rotten beans...
Oh, do you mean my natto?
What is it now? Meat?
Or is it fish?
Vegetables.
We call it nukazuke.
It is delicious.
All the students in the dormitories eat breakfast together.
But...
To be honest, the food of this nation is not very good.
At eight in the morning, class begins.
Miss Todo.
Answer this question.
I just haven't learned English very well yet.
It's true.
Nine o'clock.
Time for training. They call it "physical education."
Physical exertion is my strongest suit.
Ten o'clock. Music.
Today I demonstrated an instrument from Japan.
That is to say...
It's the only instrument I can play.
Eleven o'clock.
Art.
(Sneak, sneak, sneak...)
Excuse me! That's going too far!
It was not well received.
Twelve o'clock. Time for a midday break.
We all leave the classroom and spend our time freely.
What's that?
Fencing.
Whoever hits their opponent
above the waist with a sabre wins.
Western swordplay?
Fascinating.
Miss Chise, wait!
Many pardons!
What? You want to join the team?
I wish to contend with you.
Contend?
If you mean a fencing match,
you'll need to issue a formal request.
Formal request?
Oh, yes!
I've heard of this! I happen to have one with me.
Disgusting!
What are you doing, Miss Chise?
Yuck!
What?
I had heard that, in the West, when requesting
a contest of different martial arts,
you throw a white turnip at your opponent.
That's for a duel!
And you don't throw turnips; you throw gloves!
Is that so?
I beg your pardon.
I did feel that something wasn't quite right.
Forgive me.
I shall return to throw a glove at-
What is wrong with you?!
I've had enough of this!
Masks are acceptable, as well?
Then to a fair fight.
Have at you!
I'm not dueling you!
This can't be happening.
Two different fighting styles!
Captain! You can do it!
You little-!
Hey! What are you doing!
Ladies! Stop it this instant!
Then you just defeated Professor Krauss?
I love it!
This is no laughing matter!
We eat our midday meal outside.
It is a stylish affair in these parts, known as "lunch".
It serves him right.
That Krauss always had a dirty look in his eye.
This is the leader of our band of spies, Dorothy.
She has a positive personality.
Her alias is 17 years of age, but...
Oops.
...I must say it is quite a stretch.
You do be standing out too much, Miss Chise.
You only just transferred here.
You shouldn't attract so much attention.
This is Ange.
She talks like a bumpkin, but that is only an act.
This woman tells lies constantly.
I apologize. I shall be careful in the future.
You're in an unfamiliar country. It can't be helped.
In fact, I think it would be more unnatural
if she blended in.
That... may be so.
See?
This is the princess of this nation.
She is even more of a mystery than Ange.
Why would the princess of one kingdom
act as a spy for an enemy country?
And is she not afraid to cross such a perilous bridge?
What is it?
You are always smiling.
Does it look fake?
No...
It's alright.
People always tell me they can't
figure out what I'm thinking.
Nothing is wrong with you!
You're just too perfect at everything,
Your Highness.
But you might say it's hard
to tell how you really feel.
When she pinches her collar, that's the sign
that she needs to tell us about a mission.
Princess has bodyguards surrounding her
even at school.
And one of them reports on her activities
to the Home Secretary.
The lavatory is the ideal spot for clandestine meetings.
Oh, Princess. How do you do?
How do you do, Miss Lily?
Lily Gaveston.
The daughter of the Kingdom's Chief Justice.
She, too, is one of the Home Secretary's collaborators.
She has not been trained as a spy...
But she is the same sex as Princess,
and in the same class.
This actually makes her the bigger nuisance.
I see you're with the Natural History Club again today.
G-good afternoon, Miss Lily.
Good afternoon.
And who are you?
I-I'm Ange.
Oh, I'm so sorry. I just can't remember
the names of people I don't associate with.
How unsightly.
If you dislike Ange, you would do well
to come out and say it.
Your senseless sarcasm
diminishes the quality of your character.
Princess.
I think you should choose your friends with more care.
But I thought of you as a friend.
Are you saying I should reconsider?
Th-things are fine the way they are!
When we carry out our spy work,
we use this underground passage.
There are so many cars,
and airships.
You would never behold such a sight in Japan.
Big, tall buildings, like castles, line the streets.
When I go into town, I cannot avoid
the painful reminder of how different our nations are.
Yes, please tell the Master that his wife
wishes him to stop by Piccadilly Circus.
Beatrice's throat is equipped with advanced technology
that can mimic any human voice.
Yes.
Beatrice's throat is equipped with advanced technology
that can mimic any human voice.
Yes. Excuse me.
Beatrice's throat is equipped with advanced technology
that can mimic any human voice.
She herself is good with machines,
which makes her a reliable ally.
We were right.
The president of the Privy Council WILL be there.
Will they?
Now all we have to do is find out
what their secret meeting is about.
Rain.
Perfect. I can use it to my advantage.
Dear Sister.
That is known as "a woman's weapon".
Unfortunately, it's one I have yet to acquire.
Oh, no!
Where is this rain coming from?
Well, I'll go in from the roof.
Chise, you're on standby.
There is surprisingly little for me to do.
Ange says it's better that way, but...
Isn't it only natural that I should want to be useful,
as a member of the team?
I have regular interviews with Lord Horikawa.
Delicious!
This kintsuba is exquisite!
I had it sent here from the capital.
Of course. The capital.
Of course it's so good!
By the way, Chise.
What do you think of Princess?
Dear Sister.
My task is to investigate the Commonwealth.
In other words, I am spying on the spies.
I have determined her to be a clever, resolute woman.
Will it succeed?
This "Operation: Changeling".
I have only been with them a fortnight.
I would like more time to form a proper judgment.
I hope you don't think me a coward, Chise.
Our nation is still small.
Of the Kingdom and the Commonwealth,
we must determine which horse will win the race
and ride it, or we will have no future.
Understood.
Please, do not worry, Dear Sister.
I promise I will find the information
that will benefit our nation.
I will be useful.
It is funny because it is so fitting.
This IS a place where chrysalides
emerge into adulthood.
She's a commoner, isn't she?
Obviously she's after the money.
Hey. Out of our way.
Oriental.
Don't you speak English?
This butterfly is about to leave its cocoon.
If you were not all spread across the path,
you could easily pass behind me.
Indeed.
That's one way to do it, or...
Now there's no reason for you to stay there.
That's my big brother. So logical.
You villains.
I'll let you in on something, Oriental.
That chrysalid represents all of you.
You lot had better behave yourselves
until you get your own wings.
Do you think they even CAN get wings?
When a man speaks too much, he appears a fool.
What?
I challenge you to a duel!
You will atone for the crimes of insulting
my homeland and stamping out a small life!
What? What are you on about?
Just ignore her, Brother.
I am serious!
Chise?
Looks like she's gotten into a fight.
Not again, Miss Chise!
Stop it. A duel is a fight to defend one's honor.
No one would stake his honor
on a fight with an oriental girl.
What are you doing, Miss Chise?
I am preparing to duel this knave!
Miss Chise!
Don't do it!
It's too dreadful, so it is!
But...
A duel?
That's hardly a peaceful solution.
Princess.
Well, well. So you were a friend of the princess.
I'm not interested in a duel.
It was your little oriental friend who wanted to fight.
But you gave me reason to!
Stop it, Miss Chise!
Have you forgotten your duty?
Learn to pick your battles!
I have no intention of embarrassing
one of Princess' friends.
Let's go.
Chise.
Spies don't attract attention.
I apologize.
Dear Sister, I've done it again.
Come in.
I can tell by the look on your face
that you didn't expect to see me.
Oh.
I apologize for my behavior earlier.
Ange and the others must be appalled.
That's true.
Have you come to reprimand me?
No, quite the opposite.
I've come to teach you our country's rules for dueling.
What?
There's more to it than throwing a white glove.
To start, you need someone to act as Second.
The role of whom is to negotiate
with the other party's Second
to determine the date, time,
and method of the duel.
You'll also need to prepare a witness and a doctor.
You must choose a location
where there won't be many people.
And-
Wait.
Stop a moment!
Were you not opposed to dueling?
There are times when a person has to fight.
If you're going to do it, you absolutely must win.
Do you understand, Miss Chise?
Allow me to review the rules.
You will stand ten paces from each other,
and fire three shots from your pistols.
Mr. Cameron, the challenged party,
has asked to go second.
You will take turns, with Miss Chise firing first.
The first to injure the other wins.
Should all six shots miss, bygones will be bygones.
You both agree?
Of course, Princess.
I have no objections.
I've prepared some Robert Wogdon dueling pistols.
For your approval.
In a duel, fairness is valued above all.
That is why we each use the same weapons.
N-now, I, Lily Gaveston,
of the Gaveston Law Lord bloodline,
will stand as witness to the outcome of this duel.
Will both parties please take your marks.
A witness is chosen who is not aligned with either side.
Still, there was no need to choose HER.
That's far enough.
Hey, Oriental! Can you shoot a gun?
I wouldn't blame you for crying.
Kung-fu isn't allowed, after all.
Dear Sister.
The people here know nothing of the land of Japan.
It's sad, I suppose, that this is where our country stands.
The Seconds will come to order.
Ready...
Begin!
They deliberately use old-fashioned guns,
to make it difficult to hit our targets.
I am told this is because otherwise, differing levels of skill
would make the contest unfair.
It IS an old gun.
These things happen.
Isn't that right, Witness?
What? But...
Or can you prove that the gun has been tampered with?
Well...
My turn.
Here I go, oriental woman.
Miss Chise!
Dear Sister, this is what THEY call "fair".
I do have two shots left.
So let's see you quaking in your boots.
Now it is my turn, correct?
Don't tell me you're going to THROW the bullet at me?
Indeed I am.
Brother!
Damn her!
Witness!
W-we have a winner!
In accordance with the rules-
Wait! You can't possibly count that magic trick!
Keep going!
Y-yeah! This duel isn't over!
Make it fair, Witness!
B-but...
I will continue.
If you wish to go on, then fire.
However, on my next turn,
I will aim between the eyebrows.
Enough!
You win, Oriental!
Can't you hear me?
Ruddy bumpkin doesn't even know the rules of dueling!
Mr. Cameron, your apology!
Alright!
I'm sorry!
I apologize for insulting your country,
and I take back everything I said!
Challenger! Do you accept the apology?
Doctor!
See to my brother.
R-right away!
Don't crowd me! You're so annoying!
Don't push yourself.
Here, hold on to me.
It's nothing! I'm fine.
Let's go!
Well done, Miss Chise.
They didn't come.
What?
Never mind.
It is nothing.
What do you think of Operation: Changeling?
We last spoke a mere week ago.
The plan will not progress so immediately.
Regardless, I would like to hear your thoughts.
The Kingdom is pressuring us to settle this treaty.
I would like to use your information
to help me determine whether to accept their terms.
I...
Where were you?
We're having a meeting.
Understood.
Princess?
Isn't anyone here?
Miss Chise, congratulations!
East side!
Congratulations, Miss Chise!
West side!
What is this?
What are you doing?
Dohyo iri.
Huh?
I heard that when a samurai wins a duel,
this is how they celebrate.
This is how they do things in Japan, right?
It's, um... very unique.
Do you like it, then?
I see Japan is still an unknown nation to the people here.
Forget Japan, YOU'RE the special one.
Troublemaker.
You attract a lot of attention for a spy.
But it felt great when you talked back
to Lily in the lavatory.
Besides, it's thanks to you
that our mission went so smoothly.
That's right. I saw no problems with Princess today.
Yes, that's right.
While you were off having your duel,
we snuck into Lily's room.
Sure enough, she was hiding a direct telephone line.
We took the liberty of tinkering with it, just a little.
Is that why you weren't present at the duel?
Anything unusual?
Maybe all the hullabaloo about a duel.
I told you about that weird oriental runt.
Are you gonna take that from her, Chise?
If you ask me, everyone here is a weird Westerner.
Well, not as weird as the Black Lizard girl over there.
I'm normal.
I'm not so desperate to be in secondary school
that I would hide my age.
I told you it's part of the mission!
Besides, I can still pull it off!
With enough makeup.
I'm only three years older than you!
Lord Horikawa, I hereby report.
In all honesty, I do not know
if Operation: Changeling is possible.
However...
What I do know is... I want them to be victorious.