Then this machine was-
Yeah. The demon we
saw 15 years ago.
I always figured it had been annihilated
in the damage of Heaven's Fall.
Capt. Magbaredge!
What in the world... is that?
Confirm that the ship
is fitted out.
Check its fuel, weapons,
and munitions.
Yes, ma'am!
Deucalion. That's this ship's name?
Why do you suppose such a
fine ship was abandoned
without ever sending it
into battle?
Reserves are still working! If we can
feed it power, it'll be good to go.
Fuel level is...
I'm not sure!
What kind of report is that?
There's no fuel gauge!
Oh, so that's it.
That's why this ship
was abandoned.
Surely you don't mean...
An Aldnoah drive.
Hey, civilians aren't
allowed in here!
Please leave imme-
My apologies.
Who are you?!
There is no cause for alarm.
I am your friend.
You're...
I command you in the name
of Asseylum Vers Allusia!
Aldnoah, awaken!
Well? Are we in a more
talkative mood now?
What is your objective?
To what end did you
go to that island?
Perhaps he has had enough,
Count Cruhteo.
We needn't show pity to a member
of a lower race, Count Saazbaum.
If he dies, we learn nothing.
He sought an audience with the emperor,
heedless of the risk to himself.
That is remarkable.
I would know his intent.
Intent?
As if this child
is capable of thought.
Milord Cruhteo. We have
located the wreckage
of an Orbital Knight Kataphrakt
on the island.
What?
We believe it to be that of
Countess Femieanne's Hellas.
How can that be?
What was Countess Femieanne slain by?
A waste of time, eh?
Abide, Count Cruhteo.
Tell me now! If you do,
I will put you out of your misery.
Continue to suffer, then.
So this is the bridge...
Deucalion... A flying battleship.
Nina, what makes it fly?
That Martian thing, uh...
Aldnoah?
Yeah, that.
Are the helm controls like a normal ship's?
Can you handle this thing?
The FCS has been adjusted so it
feels the same when I steer.
Should you be away from
your post, Calm?
What's the big deal if I want
to look around a bit?
Besides, there's no
bigwigs around.
Hm? Where's Inaho?
In the bigwig's office.
With the Martians.
Martians...
Yeah. Thanks to her, this ship's
Aldnoah drive is working.
What?!
The Mars Knights plotted your assassination?
I find that hard to believe.
Capt. Magbaredge, if we disclosed this information,
perhaps the Mars Knights would stop attacking.
Our communications satellites and
telecom bases have been wiped out,
and long-range transmissions are impossible
thanks to their jamming signal.
If we're going to try to get the word
out that the princess is safe,
there's no guarantee that the proper
agencies would get the message.
You believe it would make us the target of
the Mars Knights who plotted her death?
Our plan all along was to go to United
Earth HQ in Russia to regroup, anyway.
Very well. Until we arrive, we will
see to your safety, Highness.
Thank you.
Now, Kaizuka Junior.
Inaho Kaizuka, ma'am.
And you...
Rayet Areash.
You two were aware of this,
yet neglected to inform me.
I'm not a soldier. I'm not
obligated to report to you.
And you, Junior?
I didn't neglect to inform you.
I deliberately didn't.
Watch what you say! You're putting
yourself on very thin ice.
I asked him not to.
Someone working with the
assassins might be aboard.
Eddelrittuo!
We can't trust you Martians, either.
A nation that latched onto
an archaic feudal system
that relies on the superscience of an
ancient civilization called Aldnoah.
Commoners who are obsessed with proving
themselves in battle to win social standing.
And nobility who casually betray them
and grind them into the dirt...
How can you possibly
trust people like that?!
I don't trust them.
All Martians are the enemy!
No matter how far science advances, these
procedures always remain primitive.
And at times... are all the
more effective for it.
Do it.
Does it hurt?
Now, then...
What is the matter?
Oh, has that loosened
your tongue?
Have you... sworn loyalty...
...to Princess Asseylum?
Continue.
Yes, Milord!
Impudent boy...
And how are we feeling?
Lousy...
Glad to hear it. The medicine
seems to be working.
I can't believe that coming here
triggered a relapse...
I'd feel a lot better if
you'd give me some booze.
That's not the sort of medicine
you pester your doctor for.
I hate this...
"Birds"?
Yes, Milady.
Animals that fly
through the air...
When we reach Earth, I will be
able to see them, won't I?
Yes. Progress is slow, but the scars
of Heaven's Fall are fading.
Nature is powerful, and when
an area is depopulated,
it immediately begins
to reclaim it.
Depopulated?
Yes. As opposed
to urban areas,
plant life reproduces abundantly
in devastated regions, and...
It is sad, isn't it? That we are
unable to thrive together.
Not at all! With forethought
and hard work, it is possible!
Do you really think so?
Yes! It is possible for us
to thrive together!
Well, Terran? Do you feel
like talking now?
Count... Do you care for
the princess?
What?
Are you... her ally?
Yes. Of course I am.
Now, speak.
As punishment for your crime,
I shall give your compatriots on Earth
a taste of even greater horrors.
I knew it, you were lying...
You want an excuse to go
to war with Earth...
Her Highness wished for
peace with Earth, but you...
You are exploiting her death...
...to crush her dream...
Do not invoke her memory
so lightly, you filthy Terran!
Sey-
No, Princess Asseylum.
I do not mind you
calling me Seylum, Inaho.
But I mind!
From now on, add
"Your Highness" to that.
Eddeltittuo.
But, Milady!
I do apologize. This is her way
of looking out for me.
So, what is it?
Well, I ran into someone
on Tanegashima who-
Hey, Inaho!
You knew that there were
Martians hiding among us?
Yeah.
Where are they?!
I'm gonna avenge Okojo!
I am the Princess
of Mars you seek.
Come again?
I deeply regret that so many of your fellow
Terrans have been injured or killed.
I assure you, this war
is not what Vers wants.
I am doing all I can to bring this meaningless
conflict to an end as soon as possible.
Uh... Sure.
Do your best, okay?
What are you blushing for?
You're as red as a lobster.
Where did you guys
come from?!
Didn't you say you were
going to get revenge?
Didn't you say something about
all Martians being the enemy?
I never said any such thing!
There are good Martians and bad
Martians, same as everywhere else!
Right, Inaho?
Back my play, man!
As I said, there's no
trusting Terrans...
You have saved me countless times
since we arrived on Earth, Inaho.
Thank you so much.
I wasn't fighting for you
in particular, Seylum.
It's because I was drafted. If I don't
fight, it puts me in danger, too.
Nevertheless, that does not change
the fact that I owe you my life.
Thank you.
That Martian that I met on
Tanegashima was looking for you.
And he was scared that you
were being exploited.
Could it be...?
There are some among the enemy
who think that you are still alive.
I suggest staying
on your guard.
What's that?
A good luck charm given to me by a dear
Terran friend when we arrived at Earth.
By a Terran?
The son of a scientist who
visited Mars to study Aldnoah.
I heard all manner of stories
regarding Earth from him.
About the sea.
About the sky.
About the creatures
who live there.
As I heard these stories, I grew
more and more enamored of Earth.
As a result, I wanted more than
anything to come to Earth.
And I wished to establish
peaceful relations with Earth.
That creature,
could that be... a bird?
Yes, a black-tailed gull.
An animal that flies through the sky!
They really do exist, don't they?
It is just as you said, Slaine!
My life was saved by Princess
Asseylum that day...
If it weren't for her,
I wouldn't be alive now...
So this time, I will
protect you, Your Highness!
I mustn't divulge that
she is alive...
I won't let those who hope to exploit
the princess have their way...
Be they Martian...
...or Terran.
I...
How regretful Princess
Asseylum must be...
To put her faith in inferior scum like
him and lose her life as a result...
Milord Cruhteo.
What is it?
We've discovered something on
the island that we can't explain.
The wreckage of another Kataphrakt, one not
belonging to Countess Femieanne.
This is the one that fell
to Earth 15 years ago...!
The Deucalion...!
It can't be!
The unit's Aldnoah drive
had been removed.
What?! No, it is no
cause for concern.
They cannot activate
the Aldnoah.
What is so amusing?
Nothing...
Enough of this.
Kill him.
Not yet, Count Cruhteo.
He makes a mockery of the
proud Orbital Knights.
I will spread your ashes
here on Earth.
Answer me, scum!
What made you laugh?!
Answer me. Without Aldnoah, the Terrans could
not have been the ones who slew Hellas.
This is your punishment for what you've
done to Her Highness' beloved Earth...
Preposterous. They have no one
capable of activating it.
Only a handful of Versians
have come down to Earth,
and the only ones possessing
the right of activation are...
It cannot be.
Princess Asseylum?!
Is the princess still alive?!
Speak! Is she unharmed?!
Answer me, damn you!
If she were...
What would you do?
Assassinate her again?
What?
Was it not you who gave Sir Trillram
his orders? To kill the princess?
You dare suggest I-
"If we let her live, my entire clan and its
followers will be branded as traitors."
Why, you... You claimed to have
seen his death, as I recall.
Yes. I shot him.
Then he did not get caught
in the meteor bombardment...
In the Nilokeras, with its
dimensional barrier?
I won't let you have your way...
Her Highness... will
smash your plans.
Princess Asseylum... is alive?
That is impossible.
It can't be!
You learned the truth and went out in
search of the princess on your own?
Telling no one, for fear
of alerting the traitors...
Alone, without support...!
Willing to risk being captured
and killed by us...
Forgive me, Slaine.
You have proven your loyalty
a thousand times over!
See to this man's injuries!
Yes, Milord!
I, too, swore loyalty
to Her Highness...
Those traitors who dared to lay
a hand on her Highness will pay!
Put me through to
United Earth Headquarters!
Offer a cease-fire and request their
assistance in locating the princess!
We will identify those who made a mockery
of the Orbital Knights and punish them!
Milord Cruhteo! An object
is approaching from orbit!
What? Another meteor bombardment?
No, Milord!
Given its rate of deceleration,
it is far less dense!
It is adjusting its entry trajectory.
Estimated landing point is...
...this Landing Castle!
What happened?
That's... the Dioscuria!
Count Saazbaum?
I see... It is all clear now!
The mastermind of
the assassination plot was...
Ready my Tharsis!