We've cleared Warning Line One.
I didn't think she'd still be alive.
I thought we'd lost Vivian and Ange.
Where were they all this time?
On the other side of
the Singular, apparently.
No way.
A parallel universe and another Earth...
A world of DRAGONs—no,
of genetically modified humans.
They can be reasoned with, unlike our humans.
Maybe we should ally with them.
With the DRAGONs.
The DRAGONs' objective is to take back Aura.
The Sea of Parting
I was told that if they succeed,
all energy will be cut off,
The humans' flow of Mana will stop,
along with the entire world.
They won't be able to open singularities,
and there won't be any need for Para-mails.
Right now, all we Normas are doing by
hunting down DRAGONs is obtaining more Mana.
We can stop fighting this stupid war.
But Salako's invasion operation failed.
The casualties must be pretty severe.
Cooperating with them would be the
best way to achieve both our objectives.
The enemy of my enemy is my friend, eh?
I see.
Y-You're kidding, right?
They killed so many of our people.
They're monsters.
Cooperate with the DRAGONs?
You're out of your mind.
Talk to them and you'll understand.
It's no use. They aren't trustworthy.
I don't care about Aura or whatever.
Do you think Libertus will be over
just because we save a single DRAGON?
We have to kill the man who's playing God,
Embryo, and destroy this world.
That's the only way to free the Normas.
You haven't forgotten, have you?
That you were betrayed by your
country, your siblings, your people.
That you hate all humans.
That you want to destroy this world,
with its discrimination and prejudice.
Wasn't that what you wanted?
That's...
You've gone soft.
Did the DRAGONs brainwash you?
Or have you become a woman?
If you want to play with your
boyfriend in a pink flower garden,
do it after our mission is accomplished!
But Jill, it's true that we lack
sufficient fighting strength.
Thanks to Salia betraying us.
Ange.
Can you contact the DRAGONs?
The Villkiss can travel to the other
side without opening a singularity.
I think.
That's grand.
Isn't it worth at least considering
an alliance with the DRAGONs?
Jill.
Fine.
I'll announce our strategies
after I'm done evaluating our intel.
That's all.
Believe it or not, she's happy.
Since you came back in one piece.
Rest well tonight.
Delicious!
I love your cooking, Momoka.
I missed this terrible Norma food...
Are you sure you're not going to turn
into a DRAGON without your candies?
Nope, apparently.
That's impressive technology.
Oh, yeah! Everyone over
there had wings and tails.
How come I don't?
I chopped them off to disguise you.
You're awful!
I see the Aurora's still operational.
You know about it?
It's the Libertus flagship
built by the Ancient People.
We fought Embryo on this ship.
The beds are a little small,
but rest assured, it's very comfortable.
Ah, that's good.
There's nothing good about it.
You went missing in action,
and then came back with a man.
And a male Norma? Seriously? Jeez.
Actually, I'm not a Norma—
How selfish can you be?
Sorry, Hilda.
What are you getting all pissy about?
Nothing.
Things were really bad
after you left, you know.
Yeah, they were. Arzenal collapsed,
a lot of our people got killed,
and Chris and the others joined the enemy.
Why?
Why did Salia and the others join Embryo?
That's what I want to know.
They shoot as us mercilessly.
They aren't our friends or anything anymore.
Then it's just you girls
doing the fighting now?
Yeah, so?
I'm surprised you haven't sunk yet.
The ship, that is.
Are you trying to start something?
It's thanks to these girls' hard work.
Nonna, Marika, and Mary.
We didn't have enough troops,
so these novices got promoted to riders.
They're good, thanks to my strict training regimen.
I'm so happy to get to meet you.
Huh? Me?
The ace of the First Squad!
Vivian-onee-sama, right?
I've always admired you.
I'm a huge fan.
Oh, yeah?
All right, eat up!
Come on, guys!
You never said that to me!
What's wrong?
Oh, I'm just worried about
Alektra... I mean, Jill.
Alektra Maria von Loewenherz, was it?
Everyone knows about her.
The commander spilled everything.
About her identity, and about
the so-called "cause" of Libertus.
Everyone, by now you must have witnessed
enough human cruelty and
heartlessness to make you sick.
I will surely defeat Embryo and free
us Normas from this cursed fate.
Until that day, I will hold
your lives in my hands.
Alektra said that?
I understand her enthusiasm, but it
was too much. It was off-putting.
What do you know about her?!
Officer?!
You can call me Emma-san.
Emma-san.
You reek of alcohol!
She's been like this ever
since she's been on this ship.
What can I do? I almost got killed!
By my fellow humans!
Yet, yet...
The commander let me onto this ship.
After all the terrible
things I'd done to you Normas.
She's the only person
in this world I can trust.
Don't you think so, Perolina?
All right, that's enough.
The officer's right, you know.
Huh?
The only person we can
trust is the commander.
The only one in the world.
It kind of stings.
There's some seawater mixed in.
Hilda.
Did you gain some weight?
Huh? Really?
Where?
Here, for example.
Hey.
Really. You didn't contact us at all.
What was I supposed to do?
You had us really worried.
Yet you were off with that man.
So, did you do it?
Huh?
With him.
What?
I haven't.
Really?
I swear.
Jeez.
What's wrong with you?
Welcome back, Ange.
I'll set this wretched world
straight and free the Norma.
Watch me make a world without discrimination.
A fair world, where you can all live happily.
Tusk...
Alektra...
Who's there?
Oh.
Oh, er, this ship's full of girls.
I'm not sure where to go.
I was thinking of sleeping in my machine.
Huh.
You're up late doing maintenance, huh?
The Villkiss is finally back.
I need to fix it up really well so
we can start Libertus whenever.
Oh, yeah?
All right, done.
I'm going now.
Yeah, good night.
It was you that fixed the
Villkiss when Ange fell, right?
Yeah, I guess so...
I wanted to thank you for that.
So thanks, Knight of the Villkiss.
Fix it up really well, huh?
That's right. Go crazy, Alektra...
Embryo.
Did you sleep well?
Yes.
That's good.
Now, I'll give you a mission.
Contact the DRAGONs and negotiate with them.
Demand the formation of a unified front.
What's wrong?
I'm saying we should fight together,
just like you suggested.
With the DRAGONs.
Seriously?
I decided that the most
efficient and rational way
to end Libertus is to
cooperate with the DRAGONs.
Ange...
Now, here's the mission outline.
What's this?
Signals from the markers we attached to
their ships during the fight
with Salia and the others.
I made them.
This is their return location,
according to their marker signals.
The Empire of Misurugi.
The Dawn Pillar.
Embryo is most likely there, too.
That means the Dawn Pillar
is our final objective.
Aura should be there, too.
That's encouraging information.
We'll first reduce their forces.
Ange, have the DRAGONs attack the
Empire of Misurugi from the southwest
and lure out the Ragna-mails.
Meanwhile, the Aurora will travel deep enough
to avoid being detected by the Ragna-mails.
We'll make it a pincer attack by surfacing
behind them while they fight the DRAGONs.
After the enemy forces are eliminated,
all forces will storm the Dawn Pillar.
I see.
But the DRAGONs will suffer heavy casualties...
That's how diversions work.
What about Salia and the others?
What about them?
Aren't we going to save them?
We don't need tools that betray their users.
Tools?
But it's Salia...
Everything is a tool for Libertus.
The DRAGONs, you, even me.
The DRAGONs?
What's your scheme?
What will you actually make the DRAGONs do?
I won't follow your
orders unless you tell me.
A pincer attack with the DRAGONs?
The Aurora will actually surface here.
While the DRAGONs are
fighting the Ragna-mail,
Ange, you'll rush the Dawn Pillar
with the Para-mail troops.
There, you will kill Embryo.
What?
So the DRAGONs are sacrifices?
We can't risk the Villkiss.
It's too important.
Hell no!
I won't cooperate with your wretched mission.
Then I'll convince you to cooperate.
Momoka...
If I open the decompression chamber hatch,
your maid will be crushed
instantly by the water pressure.
Jill, is this your doing?
I wasn't told about this!
Ange routinely violates orders.
It's simply a precaution.
Alektra.
If you want to save her,
you'll accept and carry out the mission plan.
Do you know what you're doing?
In light of Libertus,
everything is a pawn and a tool.
That maid is a tool to manipulate you.
You're a tool to manipulate the Villkiss.
And the Villkiss is the ultimate
weapon that will kill Embryo.
Bullshit!
Release Momoka. Now!
That's insubordination.
Stop, Alektra!
Now, let's hear your answer.
You've changed, Alektra.
Your answer?
Go to hell!
Do you I have to hurt you
to make you understand?
Wh-What is this?
Ange!
Here!
Gas.
What the hell?
What the?
It's Tusk's Plan B!
Here we go.
Oopsie daisy!
That bastard leaked something...
Ange!
Tusk, you...!
I didn't want to do this.
Will the Knight of the Villkiss
stand in the way of Libertus?
I'm not the Knight of the Villkiss.
I'm Ange's knight.
You horny brat...
Momoka!
Angelise-sama!
Sorry.
You'll wake up in a while.
Aurora surfacing.
We've got a sonar reading.
It must be that ship.
Understood. We'll be right there.
We'll escape in the Para-mails
as soon as we're at the surface.
Be ready.
Roger!
Deserting again?
Jill.
You're not getting away, Ange.
Not until Libertus succeeds.
You can't pull off Libertus
without me, can you?
But you don't care about what I want?
Tools don't need to want anything.
You're ignoring what I want
and forcing me to fight!
That's what humans do to Normas!
Obey my orders.
I'm the commander.
You're the lowest of the low.
Let's fight.
What?
Salako never did anything as
cowardly as taking hostages.
If you win, I'll do as you say.
Angelise-sama!
Tusk, back off with Momoka.
Be careful, Ange.
Godspeed, Angelise-sama!
You're still selfish, at a time like this!
You're the one being arrogant!
Libertus isn't over until we defeat Embryo.
Do you think that's worth any sacrifice?
That's exactly right.
What's the point of a fight like that?
You ought to understand, Princess Angelise!
The world took everything from you.
You were thrown down to rock bottom!
You must understand my anger!
You're me.
You'll kill Embryo and complete Libertus!
So we can take back everything!
I'm me.
Putting yourself in someone else's hands...
You're empty, aren't you?
No one knows what's right.
But I hate the way you get things done,
Alektra Maria von Loewenherz!
Shut up!
Why?
Why don't you understand?
Because if we do it your way,
I can't have Cafe Ange.
What?
That's enough, Jill.
You lost.
What are you going to do now?
I'll do it.
What?
Her way was wrong,
but we still need to free the Normas.
So I'll do it.
I'll make Libertus happen.
With the help of people who trust me.
And with the people I trust.
The sky's so pretty...
Okay, Tusk, fire!
We have to get to Salako's.
Huh?
The Villkiss can't fly
unless it's in danger.
So come on, hurry!
But—
I'll do it, then.
What was that?
There you are, Ange.
Next Episode
I haven't gotten fat, I swear!
Wait, is that why you made that big escape?!
No way! Am I losing all my screen time again?
Hey, take me with you!
That's what you get for
calling me fat, stupid.
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Tuner of Time
I'm going to cry.