Miuna. You're going to
catch a cold, so let's...
I've got sand in my mouth, damn it.
Uroko-sama doesn't hold back at all.
Not to mention, Dad...
Hey, Hikari.
Maybe you shouldn't—
You're not wrong at all, Akari!
Even I understand that,
so why can't the adults...
I'm not going to give up!
Not on dad, not on the Ofunehiki...
And not on you, Akari.
Hikari...
Akari! Hikari-kun!
Itaru-san!
Miuna-chan...
Episode Eight:
Beyond the Wavering Feelings
Thank you for the food.
Hikari-kun, this is really good!
I just fried them up.
Oh...
But this octopus looks really cool.
It's only got four arms.
It should have eight.
It's because you're eating too fast.
Are you okay?
S-Sorry...
No! Not that one!
Huh?
Don't use that one.
This one is Itaru-san's.
And for you...
I wonder if there's any more spares.
Hold on one second.
Hot!
I know!
We need to go shopping
for a few things now.
We have only two futons right now...
Oh, I'll be staying at a friend's house.
Huh?
I don't want to impose.
I think if I go to Tsumugu's
place now, it'll be...
Hikari!
All right, the guys will sleep together
and the girls will sleep together tonight.
Huh?
I see...
My father is the chief priest,
so considering he has the village's
future to think about, I don't blame him.
But...
I think I really should go
to the sea with you, and...
I... don't care if I
can't go back to the sea.
Even if it's something
everyone disapproves of.
If we can all eat hot meals together,
tell each other about our days,
and be together...
That's all I need.
Akari...
Miori would sometimes
look at the sea, too.
I don't want you to go
through the same thing.
Let's have them forgive us,
and get their blessing...
And get married properly.
So warm...
I really am happy right now.
I'm really happy.
Damn it!
What's so wrong with the
two of them being together?
Are you having trouble with your Ena?
The hell?! Don't surprise me like that.
Oh, this is just in case...
I mean, I don't want to
dry up while I'm asleep.
Mommy... used to do that a lot, too.
What's wrong? You can't sleep?
Aka-chan... said they disapproved...
You were listening?
I also... disapproved for so long.
Go A
But...
That's not how I feel now.
It's not, but...
I couldn't do it again today.
It's embarrassing saying
it to someone's face, huh?
Maybe there's something
else you could do.
Something other than words.
A present?
Hey, good idea.
I don't have school tomorrow,
so why don't we go to the
city and look for something?
Huh?
We can have Manaka and
the others help, too.
It's settled, then.
Miuna?
Huh? Where'd she go?
Oh, Miuna went outside—
I'm back.
Where were you?
Let's go.
What are you carrying?
Did your leg shrink?
Of course not!
B-Bathroom!
So my clothes are a bit big after all.
Hurry up!
I didn't know you guys
got along so well.
N-Not really.
It's just normal.
Huh.
So is that what they
mean by boyfriend shirt?
Sh-Shut up!
What are you all dressed up for anyway?
Well, you said the city, so...
D-Does it look weird?
Wh—
Anyway, we're not going to go play.
Right. Thanks for having us, Miuna-chan.
I'll do my best!
By the way, shouldn't we get going?
Oshiooshi
Huh?
H-Hii-kun! The train's about to leave!
I know!
U-Um, how much is it...
By the way, if we miss that one,
we'll be stuck here for an hour.
Hey, help me look!
Six hundred forty yen.
Huh?
Are you guys going to the city, too?
I see. So for Hikari's older sister.
Yup.
Oh, I have some plum-flavored kelp, too.
Thanks.
Hey, Tsumugu.
If you know the city pretty well,
after you're done with your
errand, could you lead us around?
Sure.
Really?
We're counting on you.
What are you doing?
You really can't smell the ocean here.
Yeah...
If we get lost here, our
Ena might be in trouble.
It's not salt water, so
there's no point jumping in.
T-Tsumugu-kun, are you psychic?!
You're just too easy to figure out.
Could that be...
Places with that mark
have salt water for Ena.
They have places like that?
We Have Salt Water.
There aren't very many,
but some places even have a space
where you can use the water...
And some places just have the
salt water out free to use.
Huh.
That's pretty different from Oshiooshi.
I had no idea.
Hey, Miuna.
We're gonna leave you behind.
Everything's so shiny!
They're so pretty.
Do you see one you like?
U-Um...
It's so expensive!
H-Hii-kun!
Er, I mean...
there are tons of these just
lying around in the sea.
It might be hard finding
something here.
But there are other shops, too, okay?
Yeah.
Did I... do something?
Hey, Chisaki. Over here.
R-Right.
Oh, no...
I-I lost weight, too...
We'll meet back up at the top.
Got it.
Sorry... Making you come with me.
It was the seventh floor, right?
Yeah...
What the heck? Everything's up top.
Let's use the stairs.
What? Wouldn't you use
the escalators usually?
Um, i-is your sister... Akari-san okay?
Yeah, despite everything.
Girls are pretty strong after all.
I see.
Akari-san decided on her own, right?
To leave the sea for the surface...
I wonder if she was able to decide
because Itaru-san was there for her...
One day...
One day, Manaka might...
She might leave for the surface, too.
What am I saying...
I don't know for sure yet,
but if that happens, I'm
going to support her.
Huh?
But why...
You always try so hard
to protect Manaka...
What are you talking about?
Hikari!
You've always liked her, right?
Manaka...
Wha?!
This would probably
look good on Akari-san.
Oh, this one, too.
But it looked so good with the pendant...
It's cute because of this one piece.
It can't be helped, with this temperature.
U-Um...
Pardon me,
could we see the pendant
on that mannequin?
Oh, sure... Here.
Oh...
Thank you very much.
What should I do...
Does it have to be an expensive one?
He's nice to everyone, isn't he?
T-Tsumugu-kun?
Yeah, Tsumugu.
What do you think about him, Manaka?
Huh? A-About him?
Why?
Just because.
U-Um...
Tsumugu-kun... can see
things that I can't realize.
I see.
So that's the real you.
I think... that's really amazing...
Yeah, really amazing...
I see.
Manaka, you're able to
say what you think now.
You... think so?
So lame.
But I've decided that
I'll support her...
That I'll give up...
At first, with Tsumugu...
I thought there'd be no chance
with a guy from the surface...
But I was only thinking about myself,
and I didn't think about
her feelings at all.
But then I saw different sides of Manaka
and there was the
whole thing with Akari.
So I decided that I want
to make Manaka smile.
But...
I don't think that means you
need to disregard your feelings.
You don't have to change, Hikari.
If it's something that you've decided,
I want to support you.
But...
I think you're fine as you are...
Chisaki...
Sorry!
I can't put it into words well.
You really are a good person.
Thanks.
That's not true.
Never mind...
The fee for support is ten
Gori Gori-kun Rich Bars.
What? Seriously?
Sorry to keep you guys waiting.
Hii-kun! Chii-chan!
Did something happen?
Miuna-chan made up her mind.
But...
You want an advance?!
On twelve allowances?
What brought this on?
If that's not okay, I'll work!
Maybe at Saya Mart or at a
cafeteria, or at Triangle...
"Work"?
Couldn't this wait until
Christmas or your birthday?
Oh, all right.
I got it.
Just make sure you come
home before it gets dark.
I guess it's hard to be the male parent
when girls get to be about Miuna's age...
I'm terribly sorry,
but the pendant in that poster
is currently sold out...
I see...
Apparently they don't have
that pendant anymore.
Do you want that pendant that badly?
I want one...
with a shell from the
sea I love so much.
So it just has to be like that one?
What should we do?
They might have it at another store.
Really?
Yeah. Let's look for more.
Yeah.
You heard them.
Let's go!
Okay!
I think it's up ahead somewhere.
All right, we'll go there then.
Miuna, we're going to the next one!
What are you doing?
I can't let you dry up!
Huh?
Hikari, did your Ena dry up?
No, my sandal came off...
Huh?
This is...
It smells like salt.
So that's why this morning...
I'm... sorry...
Could I have some, too?
I'm a bit dry.
Could I get some, too?
Me, too!
Take that!
Miuna-chan's getting wet!
Oh, sorry...
By the way, what about the
thing you needed to get done?
Oh...
I can do that whenever.
You sure?
All right!
Now that our Ena's recharged, we're
gonna find it no matter what!
Yeah!
Saya Mart wouldn't have a cute
one with shells, would they?
I hope they have one somewhere...
Fish scales.
A long time ago,
I collected some fish scales
and gave it to Gramps,
and he said, "What's this?"
But Gramps has them with him even now.
I think what'd be most important to
Hikari's sister is the fact that you chose it.
-The thing you love!
-The thing I love!
They're late...
I think I'll head to the
station after all...
I've got sand in my sandals...
I want to hurry up and take a bath.
Miuna-chan!
Aka-chan...
Go on.
Miuna-chan?
Here...
You're giving this to me?
We looked around stores all day...
but we couldn't find one...
So you worked hard to make me one?
Yeah.
This sea shell...
we all worked hard to find it.
I wanted to give you the
thing I love, Aka-chan.
Would you have preferred something else?
No...
this is perfect.
This makes me the happiest.
Thank you, Miuna-chan.
Looks like all that snot-dripping
didn't go to waste.
Wha...
It's not dripping!
When you found that,
you had snot dripping
and you were all sticky!
That's not true!
Hey! It so was!
Wait!
All drippy and sticky!
It was not!
I was just sticky from the salt water!
I... want to do this properly.
Not just be together, but properly...
Yeah...
Properly...
Wait!
It's snowing...
Yay! It's snowing! It's snowing!
Saltflake snow...
on the surface?
I heard the saltflake snow
fell on the surface...
The village is different than usual...
The surface...
The sacred fire is going
out faster lately.
I wonder if the Sea God is mad...
What... is this?
Episode Nine:
Unknown Warmth