Stop.
I want to go home.
I want to go home!
That girl, Hatori Chise,
is officially dead in Japan.
So I chose a location
here and plugged her in.
Thanks, Adolf.
No, I'm glad you told me.
Sleigh Beggies are valuable.
The ones with potential and ambition
are treasures, aren't they?
Of course.
Go home!
Don't you like it?
I don't want to drink with you!
It's a Christmas gift from Alice.
Just one shot, then.
You got a minute?
Tory.
What's up with you?
You both look terrible.
Couldn't you come in here more quietly?
Hey, you're drinking.
Don't mind if I do.
I never said you could touch that.
You still haven't fixed that arm of yours?
Cartaphilus, was it?
Have you had contact with him since?
Nope.
Lucky you.
Hook me up.
Here we go again.
A sorcerer that's been
wandering for centuries, huh?
Eternal life is a timeless theme.
What a pathetic dream.
You're so stuck-up.
Brilliant, but you'll make
enemies being like that.
I don't need more than
a few people on my side.
Anyway, anyway...
Tory, that's too much!
Come on, just a little!
No!
I'm not brilliant.
If I were brilliant, I wouldn't have
let myself be threatened by him.
What the heck?!
This is hilarious!
That's going to go on for another
four hours, at least. Good luck.
What the heck?
What a huge pain.
Drink with me!
Help me!
Don't tug on me!
Huh?
What is this, it's not just Adolf?
Merituuli.
A fairy?
He's my former master's familiar.
London...
Weird, I don't feel groggy.
I'm not coughing, either.
I'm neither warm nor cold.
Hey, are you all right?
Ow!
Sorry, thanks.
Cartaphilus.
You know my name?
Huh?
My name...
Was my name Cartaphilus?
Miss, I can see through you.
Are you a ghost?
You need to go where you belong.
Right?
Otherwise, it's just not right, is it?
I'm...
Ow!
I'm sorry!
Sorry! Sorry! I'm sorry!
But...
But, he...
Carta—
I don't have such a cursed name!
Cartaphilus...
I'm...
I'm Joseph.
Help me.
Forgive me, Cartaphilus.
What do we need to do to be saved?
That wasn't a dream.
Who'd you go to see?
It's him...
Cartaphilus...
Help me...
I can't get his voice out of my ears.
How many days has it been now?
You've only been sleeping for two days.
So, why is Lindel-san's Selkie here?
You're finally awake.
Hey, you're awake.
Alice.
Why...
I'll go let everyone know.
We've got a nasty situation...
A pretty bad one, actually.
Huh?
Can I just pick out any outfit for you?
Th-Thanks.
By the way, Alice, how old are you?
Eighteen this year.
Oh, that's fine, then.
Morning, Chise.
Good morning.
How do you feel?
Well, thank you.
How about you?
I've never been able to get a good
look at a living Sleigh Beggy!
I'm so glad I got to meet you.
Thank you for being alive!
U-Um...
Alice.
I hate to admit that he's my colleague,
but sorry about my colleague.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Adolf Stroud.
Long time no see.
Sorry about my disrespectful
behavior last time.
It's fine.
I'm Tory Innis.
You can call me Tory.
We're from the college.
College?
You haven't heard?
You can cut the small talk.
Can you get to business?
As we've already explained to him,
dragon hatchlings were poached
from the land of dragons.
Two were taken.
The poacher left this behind.
What's that?
It's a transportation device I made.
Cartaphilus is likely behind this incident.
He seems to have stolen the know-how
behind the device when he took my arm.
This is my failure.
Master...
Don't worry about that.
I understand well that you
didn't mean for this to happen.
The question is why we need to join you
in finding Cartaphilus and the dragons.
You have a friendship with the land of
dragons, and you're familiar with Cartaphilus.
Why is the college in the business
of looking for dragons, anyway?
Lindel-sama and the
college have an agreement.
With Lindel-san?
Could you help us to bring the dragons
back to Lindel—to your friend?
He's bound to that land.
This is for his sake, too.
Elias...
Nope.
Why not?
This isn't our business, and it's dangerous.
But...
Have you forgotten how fragile your body is?
I think you've forgotten, too, Elias.
It was also extremely
painful and agonizing,
that day.
That day?
"That" day?
You're right, we're neither
obliged nor responsible.
But unlike us, the dragons left the
land of dragons against their will.
I don't want those kids I played with
to suffer.
All right.
I'll cooperate.
Th-Thank you.
Have you changed a little?
So, do we have any leads or ideas?
None on where Cartaphilus might be.
We have Lindel maintaining contact with
the dragons, but things aren't very clear,
possibly because they
aren't fully conscious.
I think Cartaphilus is in London.
Why?
Well, it's a hunch.
Stroud-san, do dragons
sell for a lot of money?
Ye—
They sure do!
A lot of money.
Then it's possible...
Sorry, can someone lend me a phone?
Yes?
Oh, it's you.
How are you?
That's great.
Yes.
I'm in Paris right now.
Depending on price and terms,
I may take on your work.
Come on!
Pull it tighter!
Mr. Seth.
Long time no see, Chise-san.
Oh, and Mr. Ainsworth?
I believe magic and sorcery are
not allowed at the auction.
That's what I heard, so I'm using
neither magic nor sorcery.
I just reassembled the whole thing.
It's neither me nor Simon.
Who's face is that?
I'll choose not to hear all your names.
Um, if it's possible, I'd
like to contribute this.
Oh, this is...
Excellent.
We'll make this the first
item of the afternoon.
And then we'll move on to the main auction.
Is that all right?
Yes.
The dragon auction begins at 6 PM.
Until then, feel free to do as you please.
You sure do sell whatever you want here.
Chise-san, here.
A checkbook?
And a card.
Half of the value of your sale
price is deposited there.
Half?!
You were both a product
as well as an exhibitor,
so that's your share.
Dragons are expensive.
Please use that if the college's
funding is inadequate.
Thank you.
Money, huh?
Come to think of it, this money
really belongs to Elias.
You have a different aura about you.
You've grown taller, too.
You're different from when we last met.
I've changed in some ways,
and stayed the same in others.
The most important parts
of a person seldom change.
You're stubborn after all,
for better or worse.
What's up?
What were you talking about?
Hey, want to come to the college?
There's someone at home who
gets lonely when I'm not there.
Glad to see you're not easy.
If there's something you want
to say, say it out loud.
You haven't told her about
the college, have you?
She's not going to the college.
So there's no reason to tell her.
What did you do with the messenger?
Did you destroy it?
It's unlike you to be so fixated
on a Sleigh Beggy, Renfred.
It's not that I'm worried
about a Sleigh Beggy.
I'm worried about the
future of a human being.
She may be fine now,
but how far is she going to grow if
she's forced to be dependent on you?
Is that for us to discuss?
We find someone without direction, burden
them with a chest full of knowledge,
and force them onto a ship that
takes them into the future.
We act as if we've shown them a path,
and make them believe it's the only path.
The two of us aren't very different, are we?
Let me guess. You never wanted
to be a sorcerer, did you?
Did someone force you?
Don't you dare choose my path for me.
That girl is mine.
That's what Chise wants.
It'll be interesting to
see how long that lasts.
Living creatures change,
whether they desire it or not.
A-Awkward, huh?
Yeah.
That pile of bones doesn't get it, though.
There's a ton of people who
can only tread their own path,
even when they're shown rails to follow.
Do you tread your own path?
The paths form where I choose to tread.
It's nice to be young.
We hereby begin the six o'clock auction.
The northern land of dragons is sealed off.
It was there that this purebred,
winged dragon was raised!
Starting at 800,000.
810,000.
820,000.
850,000.
900,000.
900,000!
920,000.
One million!
The college can manage up to 1.5 million.
If we go over...
I know.
Who's the exhibitor?
Him.
1,220,000!
A proxy.
1,250,000!
Or a proxy for a proxy.
1,250,000.
That person's looking at me.
1,500,000.
1,500,000!
How high shall we go?
As high as you know my balance goes.
All right.
1,600,000!
They're gone.
1,700,000.
Anyone else?
Do we have anyone else?
Hello, young lady.
Is something wrong?
No.
No one else can hear me.
Don't worry.
Who are you?
A woman that you could make use of.
Is that good enough?
Use you?
1,800,000.
1,850,000.
1,910,000.
1,930,000.
1,970,000.
Please do it if we're at our limit.
Otherwise, don't.
It's too bad this is only
a verbal agreement.
Please don't go home with any regrets.
Well?
2,600,000.
2,900,000.
This looks promising.
We're at 2,900,000.
Anyone for more than 2,900,000?
Damn it, that was reinforced
with a specialized spell.
How did it get out?!
I don't know.
We've never had this happen!
It's not...
...in its right mind.
Chise!
He wants to go home.
He's scared.
He's so miserable.
You can hear the dragon's voice?!
It's all right.
Those aren't your emotions.
You don't need to let them take you.
Shit!
The dragon's sorrowful howls echo
through the skies of London.
The girl makes a decision to save the
dragon, but it was far too brutal.
It's okay.
Let's go home together.