Collecting visual data of Karen.
Accessing news director's computer.
A girl with a eye patch?
I saw her. She was eating ramen here.
Occasionally talked on her phone.
Just an ordinary young girl.
Terrorist? That girl?
What did she do this time?
What?
Stop pestering me. I don't know anything.
But here, look, I have this
top quality Kobe beef.
Sweet and tender in your mouth.
What do you think?
No thanks!
Gunfights happen all
the time around here.
A woman who shot the machines?
I saw her before. I forgot
how she looked, though.
This? My wife's present
for my birthday.
What? What did you say?
I don't remember
giving you this.
Oh, forget it. It's nothing.
You took the store's
money again, didn't you?
Sorry.
I always bring trouble.
Bye.
No problem. Live long, you hear?
Thanks for coming!
Get it here cheap!
It'd normally cost you 50,000 to 100,000,
but I won't ask you to pay that much today!
Humans and machines
are good friends here.
We live in peace in this area.
Peace is the best!
That's why the
prices are so good.
Hey, quit filming!
I'd never seen anyone
that fast and strong.
She's impossible for
us machines to predict.
Who the hell is that?
Who?
Don't flatter me.
You'll embarrass me.
Karen can manage them somehow.
She gives us that hope.
As for me, I'm...
at the end of my copies.
Hear the machine gun sing.
That's my last song, I suppose.
I can't sing here anymore.
They wouldn't let that slide.
That felt good.
There were times when I thought
about him wherever I was.
For him, I put my lipstick on.
For him, I put my perfume on.
For him, I sang.
Just because I was young, I guess.
But people would never love
me the way I expect.
That's common sense, but
it's common sense that I lack.
So I decided to love just myself.
I thought...
"if only he would die."
Forgive me.
For what?
Everyone's just living as they please.
Please sing for me one more time.
I called the police.
What?
I told them that you're a member
of the revolutionary army.
You bitch!!
Death was my card. What about hers?
I heard from Xiaogang.
You're with "Eleven."
Isn't this a Wizard Gun?
You know about it?
I've heard about it, but this
is my first time seeing one.
How did Karen end up having that gun?
It was 4 years ago.
I destroyed machines using
my only weapon, speed.
This bullet rained down from
the shining sky, and hit me dead-on.
Just be patient!
You'll end up dead if I miss.
You're awake.
You treated me. Why?
No need to thank me.
But I want to ask:
who exactly shot you
with this horrible thing?
I got shot from the sky.
This bullet is cursed.
Cursed?
A powerful curse.
But it wasn't you who was cursed.
You're alive, after all.
This bullet chose you.
You could say the curse
chose to let you live,
but it's a cursed bullet nonetheless.
At the end of the day,
you're just a wingless bird.
You cannot fly by yourself.
But I take this as my fate.
I shall give you wings.
Take it.
Take it!
Release the power sealed
in this cursed bullet!
To live as an abomination
from hell: that is your fate.
Therein lies the answer.