Start of the Rainy Season
Um, hello.
Oh, Kiriyama.
Huh? What's wrong with Hina?
She just has a nosebleed.
You're probably surprised
to see her covered in blood.
No, don't look at me!
Sis, get me a bath towel!
Okay, okay.
This is embarrassing! Don't look at me!
SNIFF-SNIFF
There's nothing embarrassing
about a nosebleed.
Just calm down.
Oh, look at these big peaches!
How delightful! I love peaches!
There're so many. Weren't they expensive?
Um, did something happen to Hina?
Kind of, at school...
It's complicated.
Hina...
Don't look at me!
And there.
It's okay. Everybody gets nosebleeds.
It's no big deal.
Really?
Yeah.
Do you often get nosebleeds?
Wait, come to think of it...
REALIZATION
Sorry. I don't.
- I never have.
- You liar! Idiot!
The type that does
as he's told
Trying not to look
I bought some peaches.
But maybe ice cream
would've been better.
Peaches are good. I like peaches.
I see. That's good.
The cat's heavy! Can you move it?
Oh, okay.
LONG
No, I'm gonna stay here!
Rei...
Yes?
Thank you.
Sure.
Well, we're going to the supermarket
for the sale.
Keep lying down for another 20 minutes.
Okay!
STAMPS
MAIL
About Hina...
Apparently her homeroom teacher
talked to her after school.
Why? Why is this happening?
Ms. Kawamoto, why aren't you
getting along with everyone?
"Why aren't I"?
It's always been like this.
I told you then, about Sakura!
Don't raise your voice to me.
Honestly, Ms. Kawamoto,
why can't you be more cooperative?
Suddenly, everything went red.
It wasn't just because of the sunset.
So until just a little while ago,
she was furious and crying hysterically.
She must have been frustrated.
My mind went blank too when I heard.
I thought, "How terrible."
Hina...
Maybe I'll get called in for a talk soon, too.
I'm the only one at our house who can go.
I wonder if the other girl's parents
will come, too.
Can I hold my own against them?
I'm so worried.
What'll I do if they turn out to be
those "monster parents" you hear about?
*Sending to you via imaginative video
How dare your kid accuse
our cute daughter like that?
And if that happens...
...should I unleash Monster Grandpa?
What have you done
to my granddaughter, damn it?!
And if that doesn't work...
...there's the ultimate weapon!
Aunt Misaki!
Shall we come to an amicable resolution?
The Shadowy Monster
of Ginza *** Street
One way or another!
What should I do? My alma mater
will be engulfed in a sea of flames!
Aaaahhhhh
U-Um, Akari?
It'll be fine.
It'll be fine. Hina didn't do anything wrong.
Besides, there are so many people
I can rely on.
I'm sure it'll work out.
Her hands...
I'm here too!
HERE TOO
He yelled!
Dangerous! You're dangerous!
Hey! Who are you?!
GASP
Sorry about this! Quiet, Chibi and Meg!
Sorry to bother you!
Be quiet, Pochi! These people
are in the middle of something!
HERE TOO
PFFT
A-Akari? Are you laughing at me?
WUFF
BARK
RAR
That was loud.
But...
...thank you.
If something happens...
I'll be counting on you.
Okay?
Yes. Of course.
I'm ready for anything!
At last! At last, we made it this far.
One more win for both of us
and we'll make it to the finals!
But a powerful enemy is lying in wait for me.
Last year's...
No, the Newcomer King
among Newcomer Kings! That man!
NEWCOMER
Because of that regulation for participants
being 5th dan or lower and under 26 years old,
that Junkei Yamazaki has been
the Newcomer King for the last four years!
*Sending to you via imaginative video
If this keeps up,
he'll be the eternal Newcomer King!
Eternal Newcomer King Celebration
I don't know if that title
would be an honor or dishonor.
It's a dishonor, of course.
To all of us newcomers!
Yeah. Sorry.
You're right... for once.
Don't say "for once"!
You better not lose either,
to the Irritated Prince of the East!
Break him into pieces!
Subaru Hachiya
(5th dan)
He's been doing well lately,
which has made him even more irritated.
Personality: The more he wins,
the more irritated he becomes
(three-stage reverse sliding scale)
Attack: Fast Play/Tongue-Clicking
Favorite Pieces: Bishop, Rook
Hachiya, huh? I didn't know.
I don't like that tongue clicking.
Be careful.
Especially right now.
I heard he's gunning for us.
Why?
Why?!
Because you and I are the princes
of the next generation, of course.
He's worried
that we'll steal his princely position!
What's that?
Don't laugh! It's true!
It even said so in Modern Shogi!
Kiriyama.
This is a variation on the Cheerful Rook
from the study group, but...
Silver to 3-2, Silver to 3-7, Pawn to 4-4,
and for Pawn 3-5, Pawn same,
and Silver to 4-6?
Also, a variation to the Bishop Exchange
with the same pattern,
how's Promoted Bishop to 2-8,
Promoted Bishop to 4-4,
and Promoted Bishop to 3-9?
But would Pawn to 2-2, Gold same,
Silver to 3-3 be difficult?
Um, also, uh...
Nikaidou.
What do you think about Rook to 6-9?
Nikaidou!
You'll be fine.
Kiriyama.
That aside, you're going to Osaka tomorrow
a day early, right?
So go to bed.
Right.
It's more important for you
right now to stay healthy.
Yeah. Got it.
Thanks.
When I opened the window,
mixed in with the smell of the river,
was the scent of rain.
What is Hina doing right now?
Is she able to sleep all right?
I'll be counting on you.
Even when I do my best, I go nowhere.
I can't do what normal people can do.
I want to help.
And yet, I don't know how I can be helpful.
But, I have no way of being helpful,
other than this.
So I want to win.
I want to win.
Even if it's just with one thing,
I want to be strong for them.
That's right.
I...
...want to be needed.
Start of the Rainy Season
Hachiya
If something happens, Ill be counting on you.
At that time, when Akari's cheeks and voice
were lit up by the setting sun...
I can't get them out of my head.
For the first time, I feel desire for something.
And it isn't an innocent desire.
Whether that's a good thing or a bad thing...
...I don't know.
Nevertheless...
...I want to win right now.
I want to win, no matter what.
The Newcomer Tournament semi-finals...
If I win this match, I'll go on to the finals.
My opponent is...
Don't stomp around, Hachi.
Sorry.
Subaru Hachiya, 5th-Dan.
Twenty-three years old, Class C-1.
Out of all the professional shogi players
in their 20s, he's the most promising.
He's trained at his workshop to become good
at playing fast and aggressively.
Tongue-clicking.
Shaking his legs.
Tapping his folding fan.
His nickname is the Irritated Prince of the East.
In this world, strength is everything.
If you're strong,
everything will become justified.
It's now 10:00. Please begin.
Let's have a good game.
But...
...it kind of bugs me.
A Cheerful Central Rook, huh?
So he intends to come at me hard and fast.
I'll take this challenge.
That was fast!
He really plays fast.
Makes me wonder if it's on purpose.
TAP TAP
TAP
TAPTAPTAP
And he's noisy.
TAP
TAPTAP
TAP TAP TAP
I can't let it get to me though.
It'll make it harder to focus.
His defense is strong on the side.
So that means I just have to go from above.
If that's what he'll do,
then I'll go Knight to 8-6.
Fast play, tongue-clicking, leg-shaking...
How can I put it?
Does he have to do all this to play shogi?
How can he think it's okay to behave like this?
How can he sit there and not think about
how his opponent will take it?
An edge pawn?
"Against the Edge King, push the Edge Pawn"?
Like that'll do the trick?
The freedom must be nice, behaving as you like
without sensing the other person's mood.
He's so slow it's getting me irritated.
As long as I've got a dragon in this row,
I'm going to be faster.
Annoying.
Man, he's annoying.
It's like I can hear the voices in his head.
I bet he thinks the world revolves around him.
H-He's sacrificing his bishop?
What?
What's going on?
BISHOP
I can't afford not to take it.
But if I take it, I'll be one row off.
Then the edge will be...
He'll be able to swing the edge?
Where did I make a mistake?
Where was it? I didn't see that Bishop coming.
Is he going to checkmate me?
No. A faster move...
Isn't there a fast move?
An even faster move?
I lost...
Noisy...
If he'll get a bad temper when he loses,
he should play more slowly.
Kiriyama!
You did a lousy job
removing that "bee's nest!"
You made him buzz even louder!
Be more cognizant
of the other players around you!
Wait a second, me?!
Who suddenly starts poking the hive
with a stick?
That was on purpose, wasn't it?
There're a lot of other ways to deal with it,
like wrap it in a bag and fumigate it!
BUZZ BUZZ BUZZ BUZZ
I-It's my fault?
That Hachiya-bee is always buzzing!
He has been since elementary school!
It's too late to change him now!
So we've all given up! Got it?!
All you can do is bag him
before he starts to buzz! Geez!
As you get older, it's harder to focus.
So be more considerate!
We were playing an important match here!
The next term's seed is on the line!
When you're older, it's tough
starting a tournament from square one! Get it?
I really want to make it past this round!
I lost though!
Uh, okay.
Everyone's so noisy buzzing around.
Sheesh, youngsters these days.
Hachi is too easy to understand,
but Kiriyama, you're too hard to understand!
You should live so you're easier to understand.
Like Hachi.
After all, you're both similar on the inside.
Please don't compare me to him. I'm not—
You are like him!
You think the world
revolves around you, don't you?
Why? What?!
SLAM
Well, shall we head out?
Good luck, Kiriyama.
Hang in there.
This is where Hachi really takes his time.
See you!
Okay, the post-mortem...
GRIND GRIND GRIND
RUMBLE RUMBLE RUMBLE
Let's make it a thorough one!
KYAAAAA
Tongue-clicking. Leg-shaking. An attitude.
Despite displaying all of these things,
he's surprisingly loved.
TEAR TRACKS
Subaru Hachiya, 5th-Dan, 23 years old.
TAPTAP
TAP TAP TAP
TAP
Even after that, Hachi hung around Kiriyama
and made him engage in a post-mortem
at a family restaurant until the wee hours of the night.
As the world revolved around him,
"I can't understand it."
He yelled that a million times.
GOBBLE GOBBLE
TAP TAP TAP
We're not alike! We're nothing alike at all!
Hachiya
Next Episode Preview
Episode 30
What the hell is that?!
But this is a school!
I lack knowledge.
You're just a second-year
high school student.
I'm not useful!
I'm a teacher!
I did my best...
Don't underestimate a teacher!
So please teach me, Mr. Hayashida!
ILLUSTRATION:
RIEKO NISHIHARA
Kiriyama, you're not thinking
of going home soon, are you?
Excuse me! One more parfait!