Tsuritama Episode 1
Long ago, a five-headed
dragon lived in this ocean.
The violent dragon caused much
suffering for the people.
Eventually, a black
cloud covered the sky,
bringing a deep, deep darkness with it.
Just when everyone had given up
and thought the world would end,
something happened.
A single ray of light
shone down from the sky.
An unearthly beautiful princess
arrived riding on a purple cloud.
The woman smiled, and her smile
illuminated our dark world.
Odakyu Katase Enoshima Station
Well, then.
What are you gonna do?
So pretty!
How was it?
Did you find anything good?
Sakuragai, sakuragai.
Haino, haino, haino.
Yoisho, yoishona.
Yoishona!
Sanada-kun is transferring today.
I'm sure you're all very sad,
but he has to leave because
of his family's work.
How many times have
I gone through this?
Let's hear from Sanada-kun one
last time before he leaves.
Right.
I have to say something.
But I never know what to say.
I didn't make a single friend
or any fond memories.
Um, thanks for... everything.
Don't look at me like that.
Please.
Crap.
It's happening.
Help!
I did it again.
You shouldn't be carrying
something so heavy!
Oh, welcome home.
I'm fine. This is the last one.
How did it go?
It was all right.
I see.
Keito-san!
Landlord.
Here's something to eat.
Oh, thank you.
I'll be so lonely without you.
We were only here a short while,
but thank you for all you've done.
Let's go, Yuki.
Where are we going next, Grandma?
A wonderful place.
I'm sure we'll find something good there.
Enoshima Bridge
What's wrong?
Panicked Fishing
Here?
Yeah, isn't it great?
Yeah.
And that's where I'll be working.
Amazing.
What do you think?
This place is amazing.
I can see the ocean.
Are you really going to school?
You could start tomorrow instead.
It makes no difference if
I go today or tomorrow.
I see.
I hope you make lots of friends.
I'll be fine.
I'm used to transferring by now.
See you later.
Yuki.
Smile, and hold your head high.
That's it. There's a nice smile.
Whitebait bowl?
Looks like they serve it raw or boiled.
Sky...
Tree!
Yuki          Keito
There.
Good.
What about this place?
Hello.
I'm Haru.
Haru-kun.
What a wonderful name.
Yuki Keito
I'm an alien!
Oh, really?
Haru Yuki Keito
I'll live here.
Will you promise me something, then?
Promise?
Tapioca.
Why do you think he came here?
You're right.
He's probably just another tourist.
He's not that old yet.
If I give up my seat,
he'd probably be offended.
Crap. I can't give up my seat now.
But if I don't, he'll think I'm cold.
What am I gonna do?
What am I gonna do?!
But I have to...
Thank you.
Not at all.
What?
She's laughing.
They both go to my school.
They must have seen everything.
I'm still fine.
I'll get it right this time.
We've got two transfer students today,
but I guess one of them's running late.
Could you go ahead and
introduce yourself?
Yes.
Sanada
Yuki
This introduction will decide everything.
Calm down.
Just do it normally.
Normally.
Nice to meet you.
My voice!
Nice to meet you. I'm Sanada Yuki.
I'm from Osaki.
I've transferred more
times than I can count,
but I'm still not accustomed
to introducing myself,
so sorry if I seem a little awkward.
Good, keep it up.
I just...
What just happened?
Don't panic.
I saw the ocean on my way here.
You can see the ocean from Enoshima.
Hey, everyone knows that already!
The ocean's really big,
the sky's beautiful,
and the air is really nice.
Enoshima is a wonderful place.
Yes, good. Very good.
And...
And? Why'd I say "and?"
I haven't thought about
what to say after that.
What am I gonna do?
Just say something.
What should I do?!
Thank you.
This is fine.
I'll just calm down and go my desk.
I hope you'll all be nice to Sanada-kun.
That was great.
That was probably the
best I've ever done.
I'm sure he'll have trouble at first,
and I expect all of you to give him a hand.
Oh, no.
Don't look!
Nothing's happening!
All I did was stand up!
Who is he?
Fishing?
Why?
Be careful with that.
I'm Haru.
I'm an alien.
What?
Did he just call himself an alien?
There you are.
Yuki!
How does he know my name?
All right, a bite.
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on.
I can't do anything.
Stop looking at me.
Crap, here it comes!
He's terrifying.
What's wrong with his face?
I'm not angry or anything.
This is just the face I
make when I freak out.
I can't help it!
Sakuragai, sakuragai.
Haino, haino, haino.
There's something off about those two.
Yoisho, yoishona.
But they make a good team.
Haino, haino, haino.
Yoisho, yoishona.
Come on, let's go. Let's go fishing!
Cut it out already!
So, how about it?
Why would I go fishing?
Yuki, your hair looks cool.
Let's go fishing.
Hey, Yuki.
Let's be friends.
That face isn't cool.
Huh?
What am I doing here?
It's the kid from this morning.
Hey, alien.
Misaki.
What is he doing?
What's this guy's problem?!
That guy...
The alien and the hannya.
What are they doing here?
Good morning, Natsuki.
Yo.
Boss, come here.
We're in the same class. We're friends.
No, we're not.
Hello.
Our part-timer's pretty amazing.
Fishing Prince
The fishing prince?
Weird.
Is he good at fishing?
Of course.
Among high schoolers,
he's strong at the national level.
Hey, Prince.
If you call me that at
school, I'll kill you.
I don't wanna die!
Hey!
Seriously! What's with that water gun?
Prince, you'll teach
us to fish, won't you?
Who are these guys?
No. I'm not with him!
Like this?
No, that's how you fish with bait.
This is how you use a lure.
Fishing's for old guys.
It seems so boring.
You're amazing, Prince!
If you're not gonna fish, go home.
Yuki's gonna fish!
No one asked you to say that.
Have you been listening?
That's how you fish with bait.
You have to throw your
lure where the fish are.
I don't know the first thing about this.
Why is he so angry, anyway?
What should I do? What should I do?!
Why is he so angry?
This guy's hopeless.
It's so strong! What is this?
A fish? Seriously?
You can do it, Yuki!
What am I supposed to do?
He can talk.
Raise your pole!
Raise it? How am I supposed to do—
That idiot!
I can't do this any more!
Like this!
Turn the reel!
The reel?
Come on, come on, come on!
This thing?
It's huge!
Shit!
It's jumping.
A sea bass will shake its
body to unhook the lure.
Don't panic, or you'll lose him.
Lose him?
It means he'll get away.
How was it, Yuki?
Isn't fishing fun?
I'm home.
A lot of things...
happened today.
I'm sure I'll forget all about it soon.
Let's be friends.
Welcome home.
Where did you get that?
I went fishing.
The line broke, and it got away.
But that's amazing.
It was your first try.
Did you go by yourself?
No, I went with a kid from my class.
A friend?
No.
He's not really my friend.
Coming.
I'm home!
Welcome home.
What?
Is this your friend?
That's right.
We're friends now.
Grandma, what's going on here?
As of today, Haru's going
to be living with us.
That's right.
Isn't it a wonderful idea?
Haru suddenly appeared
before me that day.
I never dreamed it would happen.
Yuki!
Hey, let's save the world together.
Save the world?
What's he talking about?!
I didn't think
we'd actually end up saving the world.
Not in the least.
Continued in ep 2
See you next time