Souta-kun.
Good morning,
Good morning...
Huh?! Why are you in my room?!
I just walked in.
Why all the noise...
We just woke up and you're trying
to get down and dirty already?!
No, no.
This is what they do in France.
You're French?!
How did you unlock the door, anyway?
I borrowed the spare key
from Kikuno-senpai.
Why does Okiku-nee have
the spare key to my room?
She said that sisters can
do that sort of thing.
What the hell?!
I heard that men really like it
when girls wake them up in the morning.
You should wake him up with me
so he'll be really happy!
You're triggering all the
fun "events," aren't you, Souta?
Why are you complaining about me?
Huh?
Oh, good morning, each and every one.
Th-This had to happen.
This is how men strengthen
their friendships.
You perv.
Perv!
That's not it!
Why are you in my room, Megumu?!
I was pretty sure I went to
the bathroom last night...
Oh, yeah!
I was half asleep, so Kikuno-senpai
helped me back to my room.
Behind all great mysteries,
there is a sister.
Sou-kun, breakfast's ready.
Hm?
Sou-kun's surrounded by women
so early in the morning.
Your sister's so proud!
She planned all of it.
I-I'm a guy, though...
Kikuno-senpai will do anything
to make sure Souta is happy!
She's ruthless!
Wh-What was that?
If Her Flag Breaks
Flag 3
Leave it to Me,
We Have a 99.9% Chance We're Going to Win This Athletic Meet
Mahougasawa Group
What's this?
A-A girl?
Operation system check: OK.
Each part operation check: OK.
The main system start.
Hello world.
She's speaking English! She's robot!
I guess Akane thinks all the
robots come from America.
Nice to meet you.
I have been assigned to the
Quest Dorm cluster as of today.
My name is Ninjabayashi Ruri.
She's speaking Japanese!
She's a robot!
So the language doesn't even matter!
It's a pleasure—
—to meet you all.
I'm sorry about that.
There was a slight error
in my connections
due to the shock of falling
in that container.
Wrong way.
To continue,
I was dispatched from
Mahougasawa Electronics
to help Akane-ojousama with her life here.
She pretended like nothing happened...
Mahougasawa Electronics?
So she's related to
Akane-chan's family?
Just call me Akane.
You don't have to add the "ojousama."
In order to abbreviate your name,
I need to be in administrator mode.
Would you like to enter your password
and change me to administrator mode?
Yes or no.
I don't know the password!
Password is incorrect.
Would you like to enter it again?
Yes or no.
I don't know the password!
Would you like to enter it again?
This is going to go on forever!
Now Sou-kun has more girls in his life.
Your sister won't know
what to do with herself.
Sou-kun, remember to restrain
yourself!  You can't just jump at the girls.
I'm sure that's why she was sent here.
The daughter of the
Mahougasawa family is
staying here in a dorm with
men, albeit just one.
Yeah, I can see why they'd worry about
having her live with a guy who acted
like he just rode into her life.
You may have just rode in,
but it was on a thoroughbred!
I still just rode in, though.
But you're acting like you'll
be sent for slaughter.
That was a strangely real example.
Have I been accepted into this cluster?
Yes! We'd be glad to have you!
"Right," right?
I don't see the problem.
The more the merrier.
Men are ready for anything!
Well, if everyone insists...
I welcome you, Ruri.
Ruri-chan is blushing!
Just like a real human!
I'm not blushing.
Really? You look like—
I'm not.
You couldn't have gotten
Ruri's flag, too, did you?
I don't think robots have flags...
I think, anyway.
Oh, no.
We have to hurry.
We're going to be late
if we don't leave soon.
That was quite the
commotion this morning.
Nanami-chan, that's my bag.
Sou-kun, this is the perfect chance
for me to carry you on my back.
I think I'll be fine by myself.
Anyway, Ruri-chan, could you
watch the house for us—
Let's get going.
As you can see, I'm fully functional.
All right, let's play our lunch show's first number!
That's some nice electricity you're using.
You sure got settled in
quickly your first day.
You're a good girl,
so I'm glad you got along
with everyone in class.
I think someone here should follow Ruri's lead
and become a bit better themselves.
Sorry I'm a bad apple.
What are you saying?
You're nice, Souta-kun!
Don't berate yourself, Sou-kun!
I'll wash your hair when
we take a bath later!
If you're a bad apple,
I'll be a bad apple, too!
Must be nice getting
so much love every day.
Sorry to interrupt the song,
but we have an announcement
from Seiteikouji Mimori,
the student council president.
My beloved students, Hatagaya Academy!
Student Council President
By the way "Hatagaya Academy" is an
original earth-shattering
greeting that I invented.
What?
Anyway, it's almost time
for our school track meet,
and I want to scale it up this year.
Track Meet Week
I'm calling it the Track Meet Week.
It's a week-long event that
has all different types of
events that take place from
morning all the way through the night.
It's a huge, non-stop event.
The students will spend
a week dueling it out,
and the best team will
be designated MVP!
This is great!
It sounds so fun!
I'll be able to see Sou-kun
kicking butt for a week!
I'm so happy!
I know, right?
What events are you guys doing?
I'm going to do the three-legged
race with Sou-kun!
No, that's no fair!
I want to do it, too.
Me, too! Me, too!
You guys always look like
you're having so much fun.
Man, with all of this going on...
...I really don't have
time to think about much.
We've discussed things,
and we've decided to wrap you up,
put Megu-chan on top of you, and then
Kikuno-senpai and I will drag you
while we do the three-legged
race together.
Is that some kind of torture?
They forgot what they were
after in the beginning.
Hey. I was looking for you guys.
I'm glad to see you all
getting along again today.
Yes, we're very grateful for
your having fixed the Quest Dorm.
Though, granny was the one
that helped the most.
Right. So anyway,
About Quest Dorm...
Sorry. You might get shut down after all.
What?!
Student Council President—
I mean, our tentative chairwoman.
Apparently this Quest Dorm
only has five residents.
It doesn't make sense to run this
facility with so few people.
It's also co-ed.
I'm so jealous—
I mean this is untenable!
Don't cry!
We weren't trying to
give you a hard time.
We were just discussing
the situation...
I was just faking it.
Why you...
It's sad that you're taking your
problems out on someone else,
just because you didn't have
fun while you were younger.
Y-You shouldn't have said that!
It's a co-ed dorm because we
haphazardly decided to let him
transfer in when all the male
dorms were already full.
Also, the members of the
Quest Dorm have strong bonds
and trust one another,
much more than any other club or dorm.
It would be sheer foolishness
to attempt to dismantle that.
There's not a single good
that would come from it.
I wouldn't be surprised if they
got MVP in the school meet.
You think so?!
No co-ed team has ever made MVP!
So envious!
There'll be too much flirting going on
for them to get anywhere!
I see.
So if they don't make MVP,
we shut down Quest Dorm.
We expel Hatate-kun from our school.
Sure. I'll accept those conditions.
We didn't say anything like that...
I'll show you the ultimate team!
This is your fault!
Now, let's show those crazy adults your—
What do you mean Sou-kun
might get expelled?!
I-I-It'll be fine.
I-I-I have a plan.
Okiku-nee, I think that's enough, don't you?
Sou-kun, you're so kind.
Your sister's so happy to see you've
grown up to be such a great kid.
I was so scared!
You guys don't need to join them.
Well, I was just pretending to cry.
I've verified that your tear
ducts are fully dilated.
In addition, there seems
to be some moisture
that was expelled from the
lower part of your body.
I didn't wet myself!
A-Anyway, you know how it is.
I've got you some excellent
help for the meet,
so cut me some slack.
Help?
Someone with excellent leadership skills
that will help you all become MVPs.
Anyway, I'm going to
stop by the restroom—
I mean the student council's office.
It'll be okay!
When you get expelled, I'll go with you!
I won't leave you alone, either.
We'll ride the harsh seas
of society together as men.
You're expecting me to get expelled, huh?
I wonder who the help's gonna be.
Maybe another dorm mate!
What if it's a scary guy... Huh, Souta-kun?
Discipline... is needed!
I'm in class 2-F, Eiyuuzaki Rin.
I will be entering
Quest Dorm in order to
make sure you become MVPs.
I normally wouldn't want to
work for some weakling who
gets pushed around by a bunch of girls.
However, I owe the president a favor.
I do not wish to be here, but I will
do the job to the best of my ability.
Your typical "hates men" flag...
Now, now, Rin-chan,
you'll scare the kids if you're too angry.
Okiku. I don't even understand
why you're here.
What's the point of being
around this random guy?
I know him, so he's not random.
He's random.
Rin-chan was in my class last year.
We talked to each other,
even while I was overseas.
You only ever talked about your neighbors
and brother in your letters.
Sou-kun this, and Sou-kun that...
Wait a second...
That's Sou-kun?!
That's right.
So you were able to see him again?
I'm glad for you.
But that doesn't mean I'm going to hold back!
Since you're the only man here,
I'm going to work you as hard as I can!
Uh, well, Megumu is male, too...
Oh, yeah. Megu-chan was here, too.
I nearly forgot myself.
Amending data:
rewriting gender from female to male.
Male?
He's cuter than I am.
Whatever!
Anyway, I'm just here to help you get MVP!
Understood?!
Rise!
What's going on...
It's not even six yet.
You're trying to become
MVPs looking like that?
Straighten yourselves up!
Why are we up so early?
Isn't it obvious? We train.
So what happened to Okiku and Ruri?
Okiku-nee only wakes
up when she wants to,
regardless of what's going on.
Oh, yeah, I remember that.
We need to at least get Ruri out here.
I am currently operating in sleep mode.
There are twenty minutes remaining
before I am finished charging.
After which, it will take five
minutes for a system refresh.
Please wait twenty-five minutes
until I am operational.
R-Right.
You're not very good with electronics?
Th-That was rude.
I'm great with them!
I can type texts with one hand!
This is also water resistant.
Pretty cool, right?
Strangely cute.
Anyway, we don't have time!
We need to start training.
Hurry up and change!
Run faster! Faster!
We're working those biceps.
Now, pull ups...
Become the bunny!
What an exhausting day...
Hm? Where's Sou-kun and Rin-chan?
Rin-senpai said she was
going for another run,
and dragged Souta along with her.
Rin-senpai's a Spartan.
Let me take a short break.
You're tired already?
Guys are useless.
You're pretty strict.
I'm trying pretty hard.
Trying pretty hard so you can
live surrounded by women?
Ridiculous drivel.
Oh, no! For some reason, Megu-chan's...
I don't know why Okiku and the others
are working so hard for you.
Neither do I.
Why are you acting like this doesn't
have anything to do with you?
The dorm will be shut down
and you'll be kicked out.
Yeah, I know everyone's
working hard for me.
Yet everything feels so surreal.
Maybe it's because I've
been alone for so long.
Nothing but trivialities
and complaints from you.
You're a pathetic man.
What type of a guy do you like, anyway?
Isn't that obvious?
I wonder if Rin-senpai has always
been hard on men like that?
There was a boy she was really
close to when she was younger.
I think his name was...
His name was Souda.
He's the only man I like in the entire world.
You're going to become my lackey today.
Not happening.
You're a wimp, Souda!
Don't call me Souda!
Every boy knew I was better than them,
and Souda was the only one
who'd try to face me head-on.
And eventually we
did everything together.
I felt like I could do anything
with him by my side.
Souda!
His name was Souda.
He will be forever my best friend.
Listen,
there are some men in this world you
could never dream of living up to.
That's a coincidence.
I used to be called
Souda a long time ago.
It's a small world after all.
I think I'll tell him about you.
We moved apart, but I still text him.
You've got mail.
I was just talking about you, Souda.
It got me to thinking about our past.
I miss you.
Huh?
Rin...kun?
Sou...da?
You were just
a kid bully!
When did you start
dressing like a girl?!
I was always a girl!
And you, you used to be lively
and straight-forward...
Why are you all pessimistic,
like you've given up on life?!
Are you okay?
No fair...
Huh?
This sucks! Why are you
like this only now?
You keep getting more manly...
Huh? Rin-kun...
You hate me now, don't you?
I don't...
Of course you do!
I kept saying all those
bad things about you...
I was an insufferable woman.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
This is what happens when a
pathological love
drives someone to insane actions...
The "yandere" flag...
I don't want to get involved, but...
I-It's okay.
My friendship with you wouldn't end
just because of something like this.
Really?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, you're right.
You're Souda!
Souda! Souda!
Huh?
The "conquest complete" flag?!
Rin-kun, why...
Why are you so easy...
So Sou-kun was Rin-chan's
childhood friend, Souda.
Running into a childhood friend.
It's like fate!
Why didn't you two notice?
So what happened?
Well, he was embarrassed about
being called Souda and all.
So I've been calling him Souta now.
It looks like you're talking about
the scene that just happened.
I've recorded it.
Would you like me to replay it?
Yes or no.
No! No!
Well, could you give the file to me—
I've deleted it.
Is everyone ready?!
Yes.
The fate of Souta and Quest Dorm depends on this battle.
We cannot lose!
Right!
Yeppers.
Of course!
I'd imagine so.
Roger that.
Now, it's time for track meet week!
Let's go!
Right!
Roar! Gawo!
Why have a school track meet for a week?
How about we make it an hour instead?
We might as well just have PE, then!
The longer it is,
the more Souta can cheer me on!
Hey, Souta. Don't stare at
me with such passion...
I can't even see flags,
and I can tell how easy hers is.
Flag 4
We're Almost to the Goal. The Track Meet'll End Just Fine.
Roar! Gawo!
Will you watch next time? (Yes/Yes)
If Her Flag Breaks
Illustration: Kuroyuki Kazuki