Bra, Bra, Pig!
Lemme see, lemme see!
Maybe just a little.
How cute, Sugi-chan!
Yoshioka Yuki
An eager to please girl
who loves love stories.
Trademark: Shoulder length hair
You're lucky...I wanna wear a bra too!
Miyashita
The only well-adjusted person in 6-3
Has yet to learn that
no good deed goes unpunished.
I picked it out yesterday while
I was shopping with my mom.
Sugisaki Miku
A bourgeois girl
who loathes Mitsuba
Isn't that a little flashy for you?
What, you got a problem with my taste?
You must wear bras too, right Micchan?
I...of course!
What kind?
Umm...
The kind with hooks?
Y-Yeah.
Let's see.
I'm not showing you anything!
I'm not a pervy exhibitionist like you!
P-Pervy?!
I'm not a future hooker like you! Later!
What?! I hate you!
They're so expensive!
Can I help you, young lady?
I-I-I'm fine, thanks!
Give me boobs!
I'll pay whatever they cost!
Sorry, I'm sorry about that!
Where's Hitoha?
She bought a three-pack of
panties and went home.
Ah.
Are you getting new undies too Micchan?
Nope, not today.
M-Micchan, are you moving on
to the more grownup stuff?!
It's not that big a deal.
You are, you're buying big-girl panties!
No, not THAT!
You ARE growing up.
Finally realized you can't wear baby
animal underwear forever, huh?
Shut up!
Lemme just get something
and get out of here.
What's cheaper...
These would look great on you Micchan!
You butthead!
Could those three possibly
be any more annoying?
I can't stand any of them.
H-Hide, hide, hide!
Mitsuba's such a brat!
Come on, Sugi-chan.
You've gotta admit she
runs her mouth a lot.
They're gone...
Futaba...Futaba, where are you?
Whatcha doing on the floor, Micchan?
You dope...
Miss, I think Micchan wanted
some grownup underwear.
Do you?
For the last time no!
What, then?
A-A bra...
These should do...what would you like?
Something cheap...and cute.
What size?
Si...
A-About this big?
Oh, is this going to be your first one?
The sizes go according to
your bust measurement.
You're trying to buy a bra when you don't even
know how the sizes work? What a loser!
Poor Micchan.
She's not ready.
Micchan wants grownup undies!
Let's fit you, shall we?
I-I changed my mind!
Young lady!
I'm never coming here again.
That was fun, huh?
Th-These-
They must've gotten caught in her hair!
Micchan, you didn't!
You have to go back and pay for those!
Don't become a dirty thief, no matter
how badly you want grownup panties!
Wait, these were stuck in y-
Come on, we'll go apologize to the lady.
Would you just list-
I knew you wanted them!
You don't even NEED a bra yet!
I'm so sorry!
Micchan just really really REALLY
wanted grownup panties!
Please forgive her!
Mitsudomoe...
Our class hamster Nipples is staying
at our house this weekend
while Yabe-sensei cleans up his apartment.
Boy, you two are joined at the hip.
To a disturbing degree.
Look, she likes my panties!
It's love at first sight!
Nipples, Nipples!
She won't eat...
Whyyyy?
Nipples!
I wore your favorite panties today!
The hamster panties!
Hey-
Let's leave behind Gloomy Gina over here
and go have some fun together!
Wait! Don't leave me for
that silly fake print!
Remind me, WHO was it that's being passed
over for a silly fake print again?
Hmm?
HMMMM?
Abject despair, how wonderful!
I can't take it, I'm so happy!
I still say between E and F is the best.
No way, the bigger the better!
Wh-What're you doing?!
H-Help-
Stay back!
I'm going to shred these panties
and then kill myself too!
Permission granted.
Really?
Hey!
It's all because of them that Nipples...
Don't, I'm sorry!
It's all their fault...all their fault!
I can't do it...
There's nothing uglier than
a jealous woman!
Now accept your loss!
Farewell...my Nipples...
What, these are the same
panties from yesterday!
Hey!
When you have them on, the hamster....
Before
After
...looks more like a pig!
She's saying "sorry."
You jerk...
Don't feel bad, Eldest. I like panties more
when someone's actually wearing them.
Me too!
Me too.
M-Me too..
I knew it.
Shin-chan!
Per-vert! Per-vert! Per-vert!
Am not!
Can we PLEASE start class now?
Nipples...
Your bra's so cute, Sugi-chan!
It's the finest haute couture, probably
the only one of its kind in the world!
I bet the people who lovingly sewed
that bra would drop to their
knees and weep if they knew
YOU were wearing it.
What?
Oh well, you'll probably
NEVER need one anyway.
I-I could use on, believe you me!
I just...umm...
I'm too poor to buy one!
Micchan...
Oh my, both your chest AND your
bank account are at zero, then?
My chest isn't a zero!
But her pride is...
Futaba-chan, we're not swimming
until after warmups!
Are you listening to me?
Everyone begin!
One, two, three, four...
Two, two, three, four...
See...I'm...0.8 centimeters bigger...
No...I'm...0.5 centimeters bigger...
Admit it...I win...
You admit it!
You're really flexible!
What a pointless argument.
POINTLESS?!
Pointless, I say!
Forget your little mosquito bites,
you could be debating global warming
or something that actually MATTERS!
Easy, man...
Wow, I've never seen Chiba
so unconcerned with sex!
Fine, we'll have Futaba examine us and
determine the winner once and for all!
Futaba?
Futaba can read a bust size by sight
to within a tenth of a millimeter!
They're the same cup size, but the right
girl's 0.82 centimeters bigger.
That's pretty amazing, but she's your
sister so she'll pick you anyway.
Nah.
She's more stringent about boobs
than the manliest man!
Man
Including me!
She's a GIRL.
All right, all right.
And the loser has to speak to the winner
like a servant for the rest of their life.
Deal!
Futaba, c'mere!
I don't think she can hear us.
Ugh...
Hey Futaba, stop!
Stop-
How do you stop that thing?!
Dunno.
I WILL stop you!
I'll make you examine our boobs
and declare me the winner!
Boobie inspections?
I knew she could hear us!
I'm in! Boobie inspections!
Time for you to lose!
Don't hate me when I win!
Can we PLEASE do our lesson?
Where are the boobs?
Sugisaki
Marui 1
6-3, Marui 1.
6-3, Sugisaki.
Good job Futaba, you read
the kanji correctly!
I did it!
So where are the boobies?
Girls Locker Room
This isn't over.
I have it in the bag, though.
Oh whatever.
What?
Bingo!
Hey-
All I have to do is wear your bra
and it'll be obvious I'm bigger!
No, give it back!
Let's see...
Hey!
No...it's so tight!
It...can't be...
I'm the clear winner!
Start groveling like a servant!
Say "-sama" after my name!
Drop to your knees whenever I pass you by!
It keeps getting worse...
Another slave to add to my ranks...
What're you doing?
That's a real bold fashion statement.
Sweet!
Unhook it.
Hmm? What?
I-
I said unhook it.
I'm afraid I can't hear you.
Unhook it.
Unhook WHAT?
What did you need me to do, Miss
modern pervo fashionista?
Unhook it...
UNHOOK THE BRA!
Mitsudomoe.
Sugisaki-san's bra is probably too tight because
the underwire doesn't fit right.
Under-what?
The part right under the actual breast.
It's the top part that's tight, isn't it?
Ex-actly
The only reason it's tight is because of the
extra fat you're carrying, you **** pig!
I really wanted say that, but she's
so pitiful I just couldn't do it.
Mitsudomoe.
Tomorrow is parents day!
I'm gonna read my essay,
it's called "My dad!"
Oh, I can't wait!
You're COMING?
Everyone's just gonna get the wrong
idea and you'll be arrested, AGAIN.
I do end up going to jail constantly even
though I never do anything wrong.
Arrested for delivering forgotten panties,
called over while out shopping,
bringing them home from the park
and accused of kidnapping.
If I'm walking alone at night, I get taken
in for questioning every time.
Please don't embarrass me at school, okay?
How can she say that to her fath-
No! Dad HAS to come!
Please please please!
Maybe if you shave and wear a suit.
I thought it made me look thinner...
Not one bit, it's just suspicious!
At any rate, if you show up like that
I won't even speak to you!
Why do you hate me...
Wanna take a bath?
Goodbye, beard...
Stop, you stupid fly!
H-Hey...
You shaved yet?
Just about to start!
Aww, it got away.
Get ALL that cleaned up,
don't leave a single hair!
All cleaned up...ah ha!
Parents day
Hello?!
There, I shaved EVERYTHING
just like Mitsuba wanted.
I'm a top-class dad no matter
how you slice it!
The black suit's very slimming and
the sunglasses really look sharp!
Is he a bodyguard or something?
How scary!
I DID tell him to shave his BEARD,
but why did he do his HEAD too?!
Forget talking, I can't even look at him!
So keep working hard, dad.
That's it!
Next is Mitsuba-chan.
Coming...
"I Love my Dad."
Th-This is Futaba's, I must've
taken it by mistake!
H-Hey, Futaba!
Couldn't eat another bite...
Something wrong?
Um-Uhh, no...
Uhh, I!
I love my dad more than anything!
He's strong, big, kind, and even though
he's really scary when he's mad,
we take a bath together every night!
Sometimes we even sleep together!
Seriously?
Didn't expect that.
When I grow up I wanna marry my dad!
That's all!
Wow, you were very straight about how
much you love your father, good job...
I'm...I'm such a fool, thinking
she hated me...
Mitsuba...
I love you too!
Next is Futaba-chan...Futaba-chan!
My dad is dirty, smelly and I hate him.
He does nothing but laze around on
his days off - he totally sucks.
His farts stink and I wish he'd
hold it once in a while.
All done.
Daddy!
I love you daddy!
Futaba...
That's him!
Freeze!
Stop or we'll shoot!
Wait, you've got it all wrong!
I'm here for parents day!
Like you could actually
be someone's father!
Get up!
Stop resisting!
Just listen to me!
Futaba! Mitsuba! Hitoha!
Huh? I thought I heard my dad...
It's time for field day!
Sugisaki and Yoshioka, you two
need to get in the spirit.
The flying beads of sweat, the
surges of youthful energy,
and the glory of victory!
Get pumped!
Episode 6
Hats and Underwear Go on Your Head!
Business as usual.
That's Miya-chan for you.