My name is Kyouka.
I've killed 35 people in 6 months.
Infirmary
My name is Kyouka.
I've killed 35 people.
I don't want to kill anyone else!
You've brought trouble
back with you yet again.
She's a lost cause.
The girl's a well-known assassin.
She tricks targets into lowering their
guard with her young appearance,
then annihilates entire organizations.
She accomplished too much, too quickly.
It was only a matter of time
before she was caught.
But...
whoever is taking advantage of
her ability is the one to blame.
Gifts don't necessarily bring
happiness to their wielders.
You know that better than most.
She's awake.
Do you think we can question her?
Yeah, that shouldn't be a problem.
Are you okay?
Um, this is the infirmary at the Agency.
How're you feeling?
You remember me, right?
Girl, tell us who was behind this plot.
The Port Mafia forces are just like a snake.
Unless you cut off its head,
it'll just keep coming.
Answer me.
Who's your superior?
K-Kunikida-san.
Tachibanadou's boiled tofu.
Boiled tofu?
It's really good.
You want us to get you some?
I'll talk after you do.
Oh.
Sure, that's a small thing.
Hey, you...
What?
Menu
Seconds!
Kunikida-san...
I'm not paying.
Crap...
What would you like to order, sir?
Just water, please.
Well?
The Port Mafia took me
in when my parents died
and I became an orphan.
They wanted my ability, Demon Snow.
Demon Snow only follows orders
coming through a phone.
This is the cell phone.
The battery's been taken out.
So the Port Mafia made
good use of your ability
and turned you into a deadly assassin.
Why didn't you just toss
the cell phone away?
If I put up any resistance,
I would've been killed.
Besides...
Even if I'd left the Port Mafia,
I had nowhere else to go.
Who was manipulating Demon Snow
through that phone?
A man called Akutagawa.
I see.
I'll head back to the Agency to report.
Brat.
Turn the girl over to the military police.
But if I do that...
With a kill count of 35,
she'll be sentenced to death.
Even if she went back to the Port Mafia,
she'd be killed as a traitor.
But...
What, are you going to save her?
A fugitive wanted for execution,
and a traitor to the Port Mafia...
Do you have the resolve to shoulder
full responsibility for her?
That's...
Brat.
I'm not telling you to reject empathy
for someone who's fallen into misfortune.
But misfortune of her sort is
plentiful in our world.
You only have room for one on your boat.
If you try to save someone you can't save...
you'll both end up sinking.
But...
If that's true...
Episode 9:
The Beauty Is Quiet Like a Stone Statue
Why did Dazai-san help me?
You can't do a double suicide alone...
But you can do it with two...
Oh, you were here?
I believe you know what manner of fate
awaits those who are chained here.
This brings back memories.
I remember when you were a rookie.
You have committed grave sins.
You suddenly abandoned your mission,
vanished,
only to reappear as an
enemy to the Port Mafia.
It's hard to believe, coming
from a former executive.
And from your former superior?
Not even you are invincible.
As long as I don't use my ability,
I can hurt you.
I can kill you any time I want.
I see.
You've climbed up through the ranks.
I'll say this to you now,
but it was a challenge to train you.
You were a slow learner,
and you always disobeyed instructions.
Not to mention that useless
ability of yours...
Your fake bravado will only
last for a few more days.
In that time, we will obliterate the Agency
and seize the weretiger.
Your execution will then follow.
Look forward to learning
of your organization
and your subordinates' demise
with clenched fists and teeth.
I wonder if you'll actually manage that.
My new subordinate is
far superior to you.
Chinatown
I ate too much.
Y-You did.
I'm glad I had enough money.
You only have room for one on your boat.
If you try to save someone you can't save...
you'll both end up sinking.
Take her to a military police outpost.
Don't let her figure out what you're doing.
If we go there, she'll be
sentenced to death...
Chinatown
Let's go.
Go where?
Where are we going?
Huh?
Where are you taking me?
Wh-Where?
Well, so...
Um...
Wherever you want go, of course.
Don't you have somewhere
you want to check out?
You know, somewhere a girl
your age would like to see...
For example...
A date spot! Maybe?
S-See, I've gotten the rest of the day off.
I doubt you've had many opportunities
to have fun outside.
A date?
Yeah...
A date with you?
Huh?
Oh! Um!
I don't mean anything by it...
Um...
Er...
Let's go.
Oh.
Okay.
Whoa!
What a giant baseball field!
It's the Yokohama Stadium.
Oh, so this is it?
I've seen it on a map.
It's the Yokohama Port
Opening Memorial Hall.
Huh.
Kanagawa Prefectural Museum
of Cultural History.
Huh.
Yokohama Customs Headquarters.
You know everything, huh?
I have the map and building
structures memorized.
Oh, I know this one.
It's the Yokohama Red Brick
Warehouse, isn't it?
The crepe place here's great.
Let me have a bite!
Yum, delicious!
Oh, yeah, it's popular.
Naomi-san said they make great crepes.
It wasn't on the map...
I want to try...
What?!
B-But you ate so much boiled tofu...
I have a second stomach for that.
I got the plushie I wanted...
There's just one more place I want to go.
Okay, okay.
She's really being proactive.
Here.
Yamanote Police Department
Minatonomieruoka Park Police Station
I've had more than enough fun.
And it should've just ended
with the boiled tofu.
But if you get caught, you'll...
I'll probably be sentenced to death.
I've killed 35 people.
That I'm still alive is already a sin.
Besides, even if I return to the
Port Mafia, I'll be executed.
Executed?
We wouldn't execute you...
You've fulfilled your mission.
Hey!
What're you—
"I got the plushie I wanted."
A transmitter is implanted in your body.
Your whereabouts and
every action are known to us.
We're going home.
Where am I?
Atsushi-kun has been abducted.
The brat?
Now, of all times?
Yes.
The Agency's in a total uproar due to
a recent ministry staff escort job.
We don't have enough hands
on deck to look for him.
Do we know where he is?
Oh, yes.
Based on eyewitness statements,
he was attacked on the
street in broad daylight
and shoved into a truck.
Their destination remains unknown.
That's not good.
They have many dedicated smuggling routes.
Transporting a lone individual
without anyone laying eyes on him
would be a piece of cake for them.
We must help him somehow, or he'll...
Help him? Why?
He was abducted because he's a weretiger
and they want the reward, right?
So, it's personal.
We're not his foster home.
He didn't join us so we'd protect him, either.
But Atsushi-kun is one of ours.
No.
Rampo-san is right.
We shouldn't be the ones to take action.
Kunikida-san...
Shouldn't we inform the police?
Atsushi is wanted as a
designated major threat.
If his status with us becomes known,
the Agency will take a hit.
Um...
It sounded like you wouldn't make
a decision in a million years
if you kept going with the shoulds and
the coulds you all seem to love,
so I called him!
President!
I am so sorry.
As soon as our work is done,
I'll gather information with Tanizaki and...
That won't be necessary.
Listen up, all of you.
Our newest member has been abducted.
Everyone work on finding him.
I order the current task suspended
until he has been safely returned to us.
Suspended?
But there is the escort job...
I'll contact the client.
Don't worry.
They owe me enough that I can afford
to let a minor official wait.
President, are you sure about this?
About what, Rampo?
Well, if you think about
the rationale behind it—
One of our own is in danger.
We must help him.
What greater rationale do
we need in this world?
Kunikida.
Sir.
Bring him back to us in three hours.
Understood!
If I predicted correctly,
by now they should be...
It's about time.
Plotting as usual?
That voice...
Port Mafia Executive
Nakahara Chuuya
This is nice.
This is a great view.
Ability:
For The Tainted Sorrow
It rivals even a masterpiece
worth ten billion.
Wouldn't you agree, Dazai?
Gross!
Man, gross!
I like your reaction.
It makes me want to strangle you.
You haven't changed at all, Chuuya.
Oh?!
What's that supposed to mean?!
I've always wondered about this,
but where do you get your embarrassing hats?
Say what you want, vagabond!
I bet you're still going on and on about
suicide despite your age, aren't you?
Yeah.
At least pretend to deny that.
But now, you're just a sad little prisoner.
It's enough to make you cry, eh, Dazai?
No...
It's actually a little too convenient.
You may be able to deceive
that apprentice, Akutagawa,
but not me.
After all, I'm your old partner.
What's your play?
My play? It's just what it looks like.
Get caught, and wait to be executed.
There's no way the Dazai I know would be
caught through bad luck or gross negligence.
If you were that foolish,
I would've killed you long ago.
You're overthinking this.
Besides, why'd you come
here in the first place?
To harass you.
You toyed with me all you wanted back then.
But...
There's usually payback for
it ten times over later.
I don't know what you're planning,
but fight me, Dazai.
I'll crush you right
along with your schemes.
Chuuya...
Yeah?
So you could've escaped any time?
You, stop my plans?
You must be joking.
I'm liking this turn of events!
Scan through all the security
camera footage in the city!
Everything from the past six hours!
Oh, right!
Where's the Chamber of Commerce
and Industry ledger?
Here.
Oh, this is no good.
This doesn't have any comic strips.
Kenji-kun!
Yes?
Can you look into whether there are
any good homicide cases nearby?
Sure,
but the president won't
be happy with you later.
Never mind, then.
Here!
This photo was provided by one of the
tourists who witnessed the abduction.
You can find trucks like that anywhere.
Yes.
The license plate was fake, as well.
But there are only a handful
of places in Yokohama
that can do this kind of vehicle work.
After Kenji went around to all the
repair shops we could think of,
they were more than happy to tell us more.
The truck's owned by Karma Transit.
They're mules who started off
in the smuggling business.
So they can tell us where he was taken.
Yes.
They're the only ones
outside of the Port Mafia
who might know everything
about the abduction.
Tanizaki is on standby at the site.
He can go in any time.
Understood.
I'll infiltrate the building now.
What's the sitrep?
It's quiet like the bottom of a lake.
There are no signs of anyone—
wait!
Karma Transit
We've been had.
They were one step ahead of us!
Hey, what's the matter?
They were prevented from talking to us.
They're all dead.
It's Akutagawa.
What are we going to do?
Our only lead just went poof.
Rampo...
It's your turn.
Do I have to?
Rampo-san!
Please, just this time!
Rampo, if you manage to bring the
rookie back safe and sound...
Will I get a special bonus?
A promotion?
There's no need. After all...
I'll give you praise.
W-Well, if you're going that far,
I guess I don't have a choice!
All right!
Ability: Ultra-Deduction!
Ultra-Deduction
Hmm, I see.
Atsushi-kun's location is...
here!
The vessel's traveling at 20
knots toward the open sea.
He's still alive... at least for now.
The sea...
They're shipping him overseas, then.
That's not good.
Once he's out of the country,
we can't touch him.
Kunikida...
Use this.
It's the Agency's high-speed
vessel docked at port.
Bring him back, no matter what.
Understood.
I will now go rescue Nakajima Atsushi!
Don't die, brat...
Do you know what it's
like to be at the nadir?
It is an infinite darkness
where no light shines.
Weretiger, teach her what it's like.
To help no one,
to be counted on by no one,
and to live in hiding,
trembling like a worm.
Akutagawa, this ends now.
I can't forgive you for this!
Neither can I!
Next time on Bungo Stray Dogs, Episode 10:
Episode 10
Rashomon and the Tiger
Rashomon and the Tiger.