Earth... Our blue, shining planet.
But Earth was never as peaceful as we thought.
If your dad ever dies...
Daichi?
Time to get up.
Right...
Today, the first semester of my
second year of high school ends.
In other words, summer break starts tomorrow.
I thought he quit the track team
to focus on his studies...
Has he picked up any bad habits,
like staying out late?
No, nothing like that.
I think there has to be some reason
why his grades have fallen so much.
I've been playing in my room a lot.
Sure, I was playing video games and stuff.
But I spent more time reading
books, or on the internet,
studying things that interested me.
But that isn't what they call "studying."
It's just playing around.
I realize that.
You have to start thinking about
what you'll do after high school.
Do you have any dreams or anything?
Like following in your father's footsteps?
Sir...
Yes?
His father has nothing to do with his future plans.
Sometimes...
I think there's something wrong
with me, with the way I am.
But, most likely, I'm only imagining it,
and I'm actually just trying to escape
because I don't feel like studying
the stuff they assign at school.
Wow, Daichi...
Kagawa!
You're working?
My family owns this place.
Is it okay for me to come unannounced?
Don't worry. My parents aren't home.
Come in.
Oh, it's Daichi-kun.
I found him at the arcade.
Oh? Sasaki and Aizawa?
You're amazing, Daichi-kun!
R-Really?
Hey, let's invite Daichi-kun, too.
If we do, I'm sure Ayano will come.
Having lots of people will be more fun!
You're right.
Hey, we're going to a villa in Izu.
You guys want to come with us?
A villa?
Will the old guy with the glasses complain?
He isn't really your father, right?
How did you know?
Daichi's father was an astronaut.
I'm amazed you know that.
"Was"?
He died.
This footage was taken by a local resident.
Strange Rainbow Seen
Over Minamitane
This strange rainbow circle appeared
in the sky over the town
of Minamitane in Tanegashima for
about five minutes, before disappearing.
Is it you?
And now, the national weather
forecast for tomorrow...
Daichi-kun?
What's up?
Sorry... I won't be going to the villa.
But...
Thanks for inviting me.
No Entry
It's huge!
Hey...
What is that blue thing on your chest?
This?
It's called the Blue Star.
My dad gave it to me.
It's very pretty.
By the way...
What is a "dad"?
When was it
that I began to hate the wind
that blows in this town?
Is this the Albion Rainbow?
Yeah, definitely.
Moco-chan!
Tomorrow, you'll finally be able to
pilot that Machine Goodfellow!
Yup, so I heard...
Finally, I'll be able to be useful.
You two are always together.
What, are you an item?
We are not!
We aren't like that at all.
Really?
Then on our next day off, let's go on a date.
Aw, I might take you seriously.
You'd better!
It's harvest season.
We finally found the last person,
and the Machine Goodfellow will activate.
We are the planetary gears!
We reveal the dream of the world.
This is getting interesting...
His temperature is down to
thirty-eight degrees Celsius.
Glad to hear it.
But his singularity is causing
this phenomenon, isn't it?
Then he was an avatar, after all.
Hey, did you see the news yesterday?
That rainbow circle, right?
I wonder what it was...
Weird weather?
Seriously?
Strange Rainbow Seen
Over Minamitane
I've seen that rainbow before.
Does it hurt?
Not at all!
Anyway,
if you can do something that surprises me...
I'll give you this!
Would you be surprised
if I jumped from a spot higher than that fence?
No way... You can't jump from that!
W-W-Wait!
It doesn't hurt at all.
Are you sure?
I promised, right?
Then, if you can surprise me, I'll return it.
Well?
The wind on this island feels good, doesn't it?
My name is Daichi Manatsu.
I am Teppei Arashi.
Hey, Daichi... Want me to show
you one last amazing thing?
Amazing?
That really is amazing, Teppei!
You're strange, Daichi.
How?
Welcome to Tanegashima
The Island of Romance!
I'm back.
I got a call from Toshiaki-san...
He said your letter didn't say where you'd gone,
but he thought you'd probably come here.
Once you're done here, head home.
Hey...
Did my father really die in an accident?
Analyzing NEO!
This...
appears to be an AEO!
This is the Star Emblem.
Beginning emergency launch sequence.
Wait, Taiyou! Think of Daichi-kun!
Right now, this is the only thing
we can use as an Impacter!
Hey, Tsutomu...
Hope means believing that the future
will be better than today...
And real hope can only come
from the choices you make!
Taiyou...
I'll stop it...
Because I'm a captain!
Tsutomu, look after Earth for me.
He...
Your father... He was a wonderful captain.
Captain?
Daichi!
If your dad ever dies...
He'll die with a smile on his face.
Ever since my dad died in space,
I've never returned to this island.
I think the last time I saw Teppei, and her,
was three months before that.
This way...
Over here.
You can get in through this door.
But it's locked...
Isn't there another way in?
That night...
Teppei said he'd show me something
amazing, so I followed him.
At some point, everything went dark.
And then, beyond the darkness, I saw her.
She never wakes up.
Is it you?
Hey, what is that thing?
Are you okay?
Daichi...
What's that?
I never saw them again.
Of course it's locked...
Now, what do I do?
When I think about it,
it's kind of scary to come here alone...
I'm really high up!
Oh, no... Am I completely lost?
I really should know better than to follow her.
This is Setsuna's capsule.
I'm sure you realize this,
but with this much, you can't stay out there long.
Don't waste time.
Got it.
High-density libido charge!
Abreaction standby.
It's been so long since I was my real self!
I'm seeing an Entangle Gate and an AEO!
Emergency message from Governor
Yomatsuri, on the Tenkaidou.
Our observation satellites have detected
an Approaching-Earth Object.
It matches the Kiltgang's manifestation pattern.
Understood.
AEO's manifestation area is
within defensive zone 1.
Lambda sector, distance 360,000 kilometers.
Defensive zone 1 center Impacter deployed.
The Russian base's Markovs have already
activated their intercept systems.
I got on...
Hey, how far down does this go?
The power went out?!
Where are we?
What's that?
What was that?
Is that thing heading toward Earth?!
No!
If it reaches Earth, something terrible will happen...
Right?!
Mode change.
What do I do?
What am I supposed to do?
What can I do?!
What's this?
What are you doing there?
I'm surprised...
Do you know what that thing you're holding is?
Are you a captain?
I'll ask again.
Your father... He was a wonderful captain.
I don't know if I'm a captain or not...
But I have to stop that thing falling from space!
All Markovs are lost.
The Kiltgang is heading straight for Earth.
Current distance 32,000 kilometers.
Speed is 50 meters per second!
Any other Impacters within the Lambda sector?
Governor!
Expansion sequence has activated.
What?
Constructing satellite chamber.
Tidal Combine Gate creation is now possible.
Course set.
Initiating countdown.
5...
4...
3...
2...
1.
Sky Gate, Marine Gate, Road Gate...
Coordinates are all green!
Commander!
Alonzo has begun the Earth Engine
emergency startup sequence!
What?
The Pegasus rocket's launch pad is opening!
Emergency scramble fuel cartridge loaded!
Pegasus rocket taking off!
The Earth Engine's energy is charging!
It's Orgone energy.
Where's Teppei?
What about Livlaster?
Teppei Arashi isn't in the medical center.
Livlaster Blossom located in the storage room.
What's going on?
The Pegasus rocket is purging Earth Engine.
Relative vector adjustment...
Delta RV, Sigma 3.2.
2.6.
0.7.
First expand!
Tidal attractor functioning normally.
Delta RV is within threshold.
Combine robustness at maximum.
Second expand!
Preparing Orgone connection.
All systems are go.
Final expand!
The Engine series has expanded?
Then someone who can use
the Livlaster has appeared?
To those of us in the Ark Faction,
this is a serious concern.
We must not give those in the
Intercept Faction any cause to hope.
I agree...
Especially those at Tanegashima.
Teppei!
The Earth Engine Impacter...
My first battle in space...
And I'm getting my butt kicked!
Then, a mysterious flight director saves me.
Who are you?
A passing magical girl?
Next time, on episode 2 of Captain Earth:
The Name of the Gun Is Livlaster.
The Name of the Gun Is Livlaster
Earth Engine, expand!