GDF Base on the Front Lines
"Undina" Air Space
<"The primitive beings!
Hunt them down to the last one!">
The UOA and EEU armies have evacuated!
We've lost contact with the Third Asteroid Unit.
Firewalls for Bases 1 through 3 have collapsed!
A Wulgaru ship is approaching
the transmission satellite!
Transmission satellite destroyed!
I can see that!
Lt. Smith, please head to the
Command Room immediately.
At this rate, Undina Base is doomed.
The UPI Army should fall back like the others.
But if they break through...
We should protect Undina with our lives.
As things currently stand,
we cannot defend the base!
Do you want everyone to die in vain?!
Calm down.
Your decision please, Commander!
We will retreat. The UPI Army
will abandon Undina Base.
Commence the evacuation plan immediately.
Please provide fresh soldiers!
I know. Simon!
Allow me to introduce you.
This is Commander Simon
from the secret service, MJP.
MJP...?
Majestic Prince
"Sortie"
Commence mock battle!
I can handle this on my own.
Huh? Asagi?
I'm going, too!
Huh? Tamaki, wait!
Let's draw in closer before
we commence the operation!
You're too fast!
Tamaki!
Unit 1 has been shot down.
Ditto for Unit 2.
And Unit 3...
Morons.
I'm dyin' to shoot those punks down!
You have received the worst scores
yet again, Team Rabbits!
Just what I'd expect from the Fail Five!
Don't get started!
It's true that we got the worst score.
And you shouldn't have tried
to be a big shot and charged ahead.
The thought of attacking as a team
had totally flown out of your head.
You're not one to talk, you wannabe sniper!
How dare you load live ammo onto a practice unit!
That's against the rules!
Live ammo?
Even a newb could see that
they're practice shells based on their blue coat job.
How could you be a student here
and not know that?
Kn-knock it off!
Just ignore them.
But-!
Are you all right?
I'm sure you are aware,
but you have the lowest grades
yet again this semester.
None of you are by any means incompetent,
but you fall apart in team battles.
You are fumbling over each other.
Instructor!
What is it, Asagi?
Please change my team.
I cannot fight with these guys.
Submit a report analyzing the reasoning and basis
for why you cannot fight.
You have 30 minutes.
That goes for everyone!
You just had to say that!
You're dragging us down with you.
Don't take it out on me.
We are the Fail Five...
Don't call us that.
I've gotta run!
I'm sorry, but I have a girlfriend.
SALTED SQUID GUTS
I got turned down again.
No kidding!
All he did was treat you kindly once.
I felt fate!
It's still way popular amongst gun enthusiasts.
Its velvety texture is just like your skin!
And this slide-
Be sure to put your tray up
when you finish eating.
Huh?
Hey, Suruga!
Hurry up on your report.
And what are you drawing?
The theme is "Love and Justice".
I didn't ask.
What'll happen? I mean, if Undina falls?
Wouldn't that be pretty bad?
Do you think the enemy really looks like aliens?
Dunno. They haven't been able to
confirm even that much.
We probably won't be sent hunting
for a good while yet.
I wonder if my love will bear fruit first...?
Isn't your bosom the only thing growing?
That's not true. I'm sure it'll work out...
...someday.
When'll that be?! Is it soon or a long ways off?
Well, I can't say...
A lame attempt to comfort her
will have the opposite effect.
Seriously.
You totally don't get how a girl's heart works.
Instructor Suzukaze, Commander Simon
would like to see you.
I let myself in.
Did you call for me?
We have received a sortie request from GDF.
Is that...?
We are participating in the
Undina Evacuation Plan.
Evacuation?!
Gather Team Rabbits together and have
them prepare to leave immediately.
They aren't ready for this yet!
Hurry.
Yes, sir...
Team Rabbits, report to Gate 0131 ASAP.
Gate 0131? Doesn't that gate
lead to outer space?
Why? Are they gonna exile us?
They wouldn't!
Special training?
And here I was in the groove...
Seriously?
Hurry on board.
Thank you for the candy.
Yes?
If possible, could I have that one?
Scumbag!
Pervert!
You gotta respect that.
Respect what?
That was lost on me.
Izuru, you're also a pervert.
Awesome!
Uh, there are five units...
I can see that!
Don't tell me...
Team Rabbits!
Team Rabbits will hereby depart for Undina.
Uh, isn't Undina currently
under Wulgaru attack...?
You will be briefed about your mission
upon boarding Godinion.
Transport the AHSMB units into the Pit.
I repeat: Transport the AHSMB into the Pit.
Sir, this would be our first time
piloting actual units...
Their basic commands are
the same as the practice units.
In fact, they should prove easier to pilot.
The JURIA-SYSTEM
has been uploaded into them.
Who's Juria again?
The system architect.
By incorporating the pilot's DNA,
this system increases AHSMB's precision.
We have already uploaded your DNA data
into the JURIA-SYSTEM.
Now then, I shall announce your formation.
Gunner: Suruga.
Control Unit: Kei.
Booster Unit: Tamaki.
Forward Unit: Asagi.
And the leader... is Izuru Hitachi.
You will be the leader in this operation.
The leader?
Our leader?
The leader...
For real?
This is Godinion.
Requesting permission for takeoff.
This is control.
Godinion is cleared for takeoff.
Cleared for takeoff. All ranges: Green.
Increasing backup engine output.
Activating turbine activation sequence.
External power has been established.
Disconnect all equipment.
AUP activated.
All hatches closed.
External pressure increasing. Turbines activated.
Main engine military!
Take off!
I will explain the operation.
Undina is the GDF's frontline base,
located at coordinates CR-34.
It is currently under enemy attack.
We are to evacuate and abandon this base.
The operation is simple.
You must buy time while the personnel
evacuate Undina Base.
That is all.
They will finish evacuating in three hours.
We expect the base to fall in 2.5 hours.
All you have to do is throw the enemy into disarray and
upset their plans for thirty minutes.
Okay?
Yes, ma'am!
Don't respond without thinking!
Do you realize how hard this is gonna be?
But we have to pull this off...
Why the sigh of relief?
Today, this is the first time
no one snapped at me.
This is our leader...?
Our leader...
Our leader?
That's what we want to nitpick over the most.
That is all I have to say.
Commander!
As you heard, Undina Base is in a dire situation.
But we can still change the tide of war if we swiftly evacuate
as many people as possible.
What are your dreams at present?
Our dreams?
That's right.
My dream has already come true!
It was my dream to fight piloting
a cutting-edge unit as a member of the GDF.
And you?
I-I guess that goes for me, too.
I never put any thought into what my dream is.
M-my dweam ish...
Uh, well, I...
I want to become a hero!
A hero?
What the heck?
What a moron...
Huh? Why's that?
Silence!
You are the GDF's dream.
We shall hereby commence Operation Sarvar.
Everyone, prepare for sortie!
The forward unit dogfights in the vanguard.
It is a versatile midrange battle unit.
It's set to prioritize bursts of
near-instant acceleration.
Go easy on the throttle.
Okay!
The control unit uses a
wide-range battle alert system,
which will be your eyes and ears
on the battlefield.
A single order from your control unit
can determine whether your team lives or dies.
You got that?
I certainly do.
Don't be shocked by the boosters' speed.
This puppy can fly faster than
a high-speed planetary cruiser.
Make sure to never stop.
Constantly move as you
throw the enemy into confusion.
The gunner uses...
Long-ranged attacks with a
high-energy charged particle cannon
and radiation-guided photon resonance
antiaircraft artillery, right?
At least you're knowledgeable.
After a full-power volley, the time lag
and acceleration will be a beat off, so watch yourself.
Your unit is meant for the leader.
Like the forward unit, it is versatile.
But it is capable of handling even
higher-level command transmissions.
Keep constant tab on all incoming information on each unit
and issue the appropriate commands.
Are you done with the explanations?
Yes, Boss!
Bunnies, hang in there!
We will be deploying in the Pit.
Let us know if you need any weapons.
We'll send them over.
Also let us know if you need any
emergency maintenance.
You see, AHSMB break easily in exchange
for their high-energy output.
What?!
Don't worry! We've got your backs.
Prepare for battle.
Godinion, enter Combat Formation I.
Main control: Move CIC.
Navi bridge: Closed.
Bulkhead: Locked.
Whole control room: Move complete.
Completed.
What was that just now?
You connected with your AHSMB.
We connected...?
You are linked together with your AHSMB.
That activates the JURIA-SYSTEM.
Ready for standby?
All vessels enter detachment mode.
Detachment mode: Ready.
Open the bolts.
Pits, take off!
Ignite thrusters.
All vessels are ready.
All vessels, activate thrusters.
All Pit vessels have reached
their designated positions.
Verification checks are complete.
Output is increasing normally.
Blast off!
All AHSMB units have taken off.
<"Don't let them escape! Crush them all!">
At this rate, they'll kill everyone!
Flying aircrafts not in the codebook
are approaching from behind.
No, this is a GDF code...
The MJP?
It's them?
Wow, we've come to quite the hot spot.
Think we'll make it back alive?
I am John Smith, Operations Commander
at GDF Headquarters.
I am Lt. Commander Suzukaze of the MJP.
Lt. Commander Suzukaze, please have
units 1-5 commence battle at Secret Code Delta Zulu-41.
Roger. Commence battle at Delta Zulu-41.
All AHSMB units have turned
on the emergency brakes.
What are you doing?! Get into your positions!
What?! Now it's moving on its own!
AHSMB has a mind of its own!
Your survival instinct is moving it.
Unless you decide to fight,
the JURIA-SYSTEM's
defensive instincts will remain active.
Defensive instincts...?
You have no choice but to fight!
She's right.
If we don't fight, we'll die!
We'll die!
The AHSMB units have reached their positions.
The enemy is split into three waves.
First attack the one in the 2 o'clock direction.
Roger!
What's with this acceleration?!
It's too sensitive!
Rose 3, activate your shield.
Red 5, Blue 1, activate your shields!
Hurry! Retreat while they're buying us some time!
Rose 3, launch your missiles.
Roger!
Undina Base's Third Mobile Infantry Regiment
and the Outer Planetary Army's
21st Regiment have finished evacuating.
The evacuation is complete.
Return promptly!
People are still down there?
Allow me to confirm.
You're right...
This is Purple 2. Godinion, please respond.
GDF Headquarters, there are still people
in the Civilian Residential District.
It's too late.
But-!
Please pull back.
There aren't any ships left for them!
Units 1-5, return.
Izuru?
What's keeping you?
She said to go back...
What're you doing?
People are still down there.
And there are so many...
There aren't any ships left for them.
Come back.
Wasn't it our mission to make sure
that everyone escaped?
Several enemy ships are approaching.
If there aren't any vessels,
the only way to save those
people is to defeat all of the enemy ships here.
Could we pull that off?
It's impossible!
You can't become a hero
if you don't do the impossible!
That's so not you.
That doesn't match you.
Why're you actin' so fired up?
Were you serious about becoming a hero?
They're coming.
Thanks to you, we're stuck fighting!
Why aren't you retreating?
Do you seriously intend to face
the enemy's main fleet head on?
They have no choice but to fight now...
How can we win this...?
We really should be running.
Run away? Fight!
Run away. Fight!
Run away...
Fight!
<"Destroy that red one!">
Red 5, you're over-exerting it!
Izuru, to your right!
Why'd it move on its own?!
HEP Cannon: Set.
Fire at maximum power!
Red 5 is fully storming the enemy.
<"Lord Rada, we won't be able to escape if we stay">
<"Enough! I grow weary of this battle. This hunt is over">
The enemy fleet has retreated.
Confirming that all AHSMB units are intact.
The enemy fleet is pulling away from Undina.
They are headed toward Jupiter.
They protected a base
that we were going to abandon?
We did it...
"Heroes are Born"