Notice to Akane!
I think I have a crush on Azumi-kun
4 Days Until
the Meet
That's it.
That's right, that's right.
And...
There.
Stop.
Good. Okay, next.
Dazai once said, "People exist
for love and for revolution."
No littering!
The road is part of your yard
Your time was good today, Chinatsu.
Well, the race is next week.
Maybe you'll make prefecturals.
No way!
You never know.
Seriously?
You saw your time today.
Can I have a bite?
This again?
It's so good!
What flavor is yours, Akane?
Kinako mochi soda.
Let me taste!
It actually tastes like kinako and soda.
Literally?
No, really, try it.
Can you actually tell?
Your language arts grade
was good, wasn't it?
Yeah.
I'm not saying you shouldn't
go to the festival.
I'm just worried about your exams.
It's an important time for you, Kotarou.
You need to...
Hello, Azumi speaking.
This is Kitamura of Kadoyama Publishing.
Thank you for your submission
for the newcomer award.
Kadoyama Publishing?
Yes.
Can you give me a minute?
Yes, sorry.
No, it's all right.
So hungry...
Here, dig in.
You made way too much, Mom.
Really?
Oh, that looks delicious!
Let's eat.
Eat up, Akane.
You're competing on Sunday, aren't you?
Let's eat.
We'll be there to cheer for you.
Y-You don't have to.
Let's eat.
Why not?
Akane is a third-year now.
So what?
Maybe she's got a boyfriend now?
Right, Akane?
Oh?
Is that true?
Want to meet in the school
library sometime tomorrow morning?
I think I have a crush on Azumi-kun
crush
I have something to discuss with you, too.
Let's talk tomorrow.
Open
Morning.
Hey.
Really? Wow!
Yeah, the publisher called me and
said they wanted to meet with me.
That's awesome!
I don't know.
Wow...
I still don't know what they want to say.
You might be winning that award.
Dunno...
Good for you.
Yeah.
It really is amazing.
Your dream might come true.
Yeah.
Oh, but it's this Sunday.
The same day?
Sorry I can't come cheer for you.
It's totally fine.
The same day, huh?
Yeah.
Let's both do our best.
Yeah, let's.
What about you?
You said you wanted to talk.
Oh, um...
No, never mind.
It's okay. Next time.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Where are you going?
The library.
To study? What about lunch?
No, thanks.
I'll be fine.
Bye.
Be safe.
Let's see...
So expensive...
Azumi-kun
Here goes
Pinky promise
Today's the big day, huh?
Kumagaya Sports and Cultural Center
Oh, over here.
Hi.
Good morning.
Hey...
About that LINE message the other day...
S-Sorry.
For what?
I'm, uh...
in... a relationship.
W-With Azumi-kun.
I know.
It's obvious.
We're friends, after all.
Uh...
Thanks for letting me know.
Set!
Wow, Mizuno's next to Sasaki
from Nishi Middle School.
She's super fast.
Focus, Mizuno!
Go!
Set!
Mizuno, slow down!
My name is Kitamura.
Nice to meet you.
Sorry to bring you out here.
It's fine.
Kitamura Takeshi
So, getting right to business...
I'm an editor for ABC Publishing.
We're searching for young writers right now.
Right.
You're in middle school, aren't you?
Yes.
Lucky you, being so young.
Well, to be honest, I don't think you're
cut out for serious literature.
You don't have talent.
You should give up on it.
Honestly, though, serious literature
doesn't make any money.
I don't recommend it anyway.
Why don't you try
light novel-type stuff instead?
I have a feeling you could do it, Azumi-san.
I think it'd be a better way to spend your
time than chasing after literature awards.
You could get your name out there easily.
There are tons of people who end up in their
thirties, still trying to become writers.
You should give it a shot while you
still have youth on your side.
Kumagaya Sports and Cultural Center
So it's just Nishio going on
to the semi-finals, huh?
Yup.
Nishio-senpai set a new personal best, too.
Is that so?
Mizuno.
What happened today?
You weren't focused at all, were you?
I was sure you could make it to prefecturals.
Your time was actually worse than last year.
Come on, Mizuno...
You can do better.
I like watching you.
You really look like you're
having fun when you're running.
I'm home.
Kotarou.
Your father told me what happened.
A publisher called you?
Don't be like that.
Like I said, you ought to
hear him out a little more.
He doesn't realize the urgency of his
situation because you talk like that!
The festival is one thing, but
nothing good can come of writing.
Stop that.
Yeah, huh...
Well, there are plenty of races left.
Right?
Yeah, yeah. That's right.
"Yeah" is all you've been saying.
Oh, yeah?
Er...
I'm going back to my room.
You got this.
Aye.
This sucks.
My time was terrible.
Because of your relationship?
You know what they say.
You can't keep up both at once,
and you end up losing both.
No.
I just couldn't focus on the race.
Yeah?
Actually, my best friend told me...
Uh-huh.
That she likes the same guy.
What?!
What should I do?
Nope, nope, nope!
You have to ditch her, duh!
No way.
Why not?
Because... my friends are important, too.
I seriously don't get it.
Are you sure you can stay friends with her?
I miss you
Me too
Yeah?
Yeah.
I didn't make it.
What about you?
Me neither.
I see...
I want to focus on track.
You are.
More.
I'm going to do more.
I love it.
I'm going to do it seriously.
Me, too.
I'm going to go further.
We promised.
Yeah.
Schoolgirl
Dazai Osamu
I wanted to talk to you properly.
Yeah.
Sorry I didn't tell you we were dating.
And I'm sorry I fell for him.
Are you angry, Akane?
No.
Thank goodness.
The truth is...
Yeah.
I don't know what to do.
But... we're friends.
Thanks, Akane.
Can I confess to him?
I want proper closure.
Run, Melos!
Sakura's Fantasies 1
Tanaka-san!
Please...
Someone you like
Hold it! I'm the one who likes her!
Nope, she's all mine!
She's mine!
Mine!
Stop fighting!
Don't fight over me.
Come on, hurry up.
Glasses
Just give them to me, damn it.
"All mine"? Gross.
Miu and Inaba 3
Hey, what do you like about me?
Everything, I guess.
Ryouko-sensei's so cute, don't you think?
Huh?
No way.
Try to guess what I want for my birthday.
Let me guess... A bear?
But just last week,
she was staring at that stuffed teddy...
That's what it was?
Ryouko-sensei and Roman 4
Not that I have any plans, but...
Hey, Ryouko-sensei.
Oh, uh, I was just...
I think you'd look good in a dress.
I bet you'd look cute.
That'll be 500 yen.
Miu and Inaba 4
Hey, let's get a picture.
Sure.
Okay, here we go.
Wait, sorry. From a little higher.
Like this?
No, I look ugly from that angle.
A little more to the right.
Like this?
That's it.
From that angle, like this,
with a matching pose.
Can you try it?
Okay.
Oh, and the expression is important, too.
Don't take the picture until I say
it's okay, no matter what.
Okay.
Here I go.
Ew! I can't post it on my feed
with me looking like this!
Let's try again, from the beginning.
Maybe the angle's too high.
What a pain...
I might have overdone it.