M-Mankanshoku!
Hey! How come the slacker's
wearing a Goku Uniform?!
What's the meaning of this, Iori?!
Our top priority now
is to bolster our forces.
The person with the greatest
disparity in combat strength
in and out of a Goku Uniform
was Mankanshoku.
A highly logical decision.
Iori, I think you've set
a new speed record for sewing.
Yes, because these will be
my final Goku Uniforms!
I intend to empty out
every last dresser drawer!
Well, we're busy. 'Bye.
Hey!
999-mount Emergency
Rescue Suction Device!
999-MOUNT EMERGENCY
RESCUE SUCTION DEVICE
Vroom, vroom, vroom!
Hey! What are you just
standing there for?!
You've been fighting this war
without your clothes!
And you call yourselves
naked Nudists?!
Hup!
I have no intention of becoming
someone so... colorful.
But we mustn't let Mankanshoku
fight them alone!
So, shall we get to it?
IN HEAVEN'S STEAD, I SMITE CLOTHING!
Don't get cocky just yet...
...you Honnouji Academy trash!
EPISODE 23
IMITATION GOLD
I've discovered the reason why
Nui Harime's arms didn't regenerate.
The Scissor Blade and Bakuzan are
both capable of severing Life Fibers.
But in the case of
tough Life Fibers,
they begin regenerating immediately
after being severed.
However, if they are cut
from both sides simultaneously,
the newly-regenerating Life Fibers
can be severed again.
That is the true power of the
Scissor Blades that Dr. Matoi created.
RENDING SCISSORS
Hey, hang on. If you have
two Bakuzans, that means—
I expect they will have
the same effect.
We should thank Ragyo
for breaking it in two.
No, we owe our thanks to you four,
who reforged it into two blades.
Goodness, when did you become
the sort who doles out compliments?
Ryuko.
Yeah! I see it!
I'm picking up a powerful energy reading
from the center of the Original Life Fiber.
That's where it's absorbed a lot of people
and is using them as a power source.
If we destroy that,
it will cease functioning.
Yeah, but that woman
is waiting for us.
Ragyo! How dare you force me to wear
an outfit I wouldn't be caught dead in?!
This time, I'll rip the
clothes off your back!
Oh, dear. That is hardly any way
for a 17-year-old lady to speak.
What the—?
I'll remake you two, starting
from the dress patterns on up!
That's—
These blades are
ultra-hardened Life Fibers.
The Scissor Blade and Bakuzan
were both created based on this.
The beginning and end of all things can be
found here within the Original Life Fiber.
I won't allow anyone to defile this
sacred place with their filthy shoes.
If you give yourselves over
to clothing body and soul,
you can even do this.
Shippu Senjin!
Senpu Zankan!
She's tough, all right!
Perhaps, but we mustn't
be defeated!
In that case...
...let's hit that
big-ass thing!
Silly girl.
Ryuko!
Your plan is for the rest
of your merry band
to destroy the Honnouji Academy
transmitter, I take it?
It won't be that simple,
I assure you!
Here you are, Mako!
Thanks, Mom!
All-righty! Croquette Power,
charging complete!
FULL AND FINISHED MAKO MANKANSHOKU
IS READY TO FACE THE ENEMY!!
She's eating during a battle?!
Hey, Mom's croquettes
are powerful stuff.
Come at me!
Stand back!
What happened?!
It's coming for us?
It's changed course?
It's going to devour the Naked Sol?
It wants to eat more people?
I told you, did I not?
You cannot stop us!
Nudist Cannons, fire!
Medic!
I'm on it!
A little of this, some of that!
All done!
Honey, you wrapped her in so
many bandages she can't move!
Oh, no!
Sis, are you okay?
I'm fine...
You don't look fine to me!
There's too many of them!
But I have to do this...
You've done all you can!
But I can't be beaten here!
I have to protect this ship!
Ryuko told me so!
This ship is the homeland
of her soul!
She said no such thing!
The Ryuko in my mind said it!
Mako! Mako!
Even now, she's asking me
to come into the light!
You're pretty messed up
in many ways...
Spare me your opinions!
Don't overdo it, Mankanshoku!
I'll give you an A
for effort, Slacker.
But from here on out,
it's our job.
So, shall we unveil Iori's
final Goku Uniforms?
Three-Star Goku Uniforms,
ultimate configuration!
Blade Regalia: Secret Unsealed!
BLADE REGALIA
SECRET UNSEALED
Symphony Regalia: Finale!
SYMPHONY REGALIA
FINALE
Probe Regalia: Truth Unveiled.
PROBE REGALIA
TRUTH UNVEILED
Shackle Regalia: Persona Unleashed!
SHACKLE REGALIA
PERSONA UNLEASHED
Honnouji Academy Elite Four
Ultimate Battle Regalia!
HONNOUJI ACADEMY ELITE FOUR
ULTIMATE BATTLE REGALIA
- Snake!
- Dog!
- Monkey!
- Toad!
Utter Victory, Single Blow!
UTTER VICTORY
SINGLE BLOW
Wow, that was the amazing!
That's the Elite Four for you!
No need for such
a flashy entrance!
Honestly, you girls
are so thick-skulled.
No matter how much they struggle, humanity is
merely a creature meant
to submit to Life fibers.
The hell they are!
Life Fibers spurred on the evolution
of this world's sentient life.
Clothing transformed beasts
into humans.
Just as humans
raise livestock, you see.
Livestock?
Just as humans eat their livestock,
so will Life Fibers feed on humanity.
Is that not appropriate for
the beings who occupy the
top of this world's food chain?
But that does not mean
we must meekly obey!
Humans have a will to live!
You impudent pigs in clothing...
That will to survive
will disappear soon enough.
Your last bastion
is almost within reach.
This is bad, Ryuko!
The ship, it's—
I know.
Satsuki!
I'm gonna show you if we can
do anything about it!
Finishing move!
SEN-I-SOSHITSU!
Die.
Ryuko!
RYUKO!
Damn you!
Ragyo!
You waste your time.
It was only because Ryuko
was fused with Life Fibers
that you could stand against me,
however slightly.
You, in that makeshift Kamui,
cannot so much as slow me down.
Poor girl, who doesn't even know
her own limitations...
All you can do is go keep
your little sister from being lonely.
The one who is
on her way to Hell.
I admit it,
perhaps I am a sham...
But it is you who will suffer
for underestimating this sham!
How pathetic. What could
you possibly do now?
I can buy time.
I'm a decoy!
Shippu Senjin!
Ryuko?!
When I bisected her,
she deflected my blade
and threw herself into the sea before
her fibers could be completely cut!
That's right!
"Pretend to be killed by you,
heal her wounds in the sea,
and deliver the finishing blow
to the Original Life Fiber."
That was all Ryuko's plan.
You have no one to blame but yourself for
wasting precious time on monologing at me,
Ragyo Kiryuin!
I'll wipe that smug look
off your face!
You!
My arms are equally
as strong as Bakuzan.
Know that I am Ira Gamagoori,
Satsuki Kiryuin's living shield!
Look at how much
I've grown, Auntie Ragyo!
No matter how much you've strengthened
those Goku Uniforms,
do you think the blade
of a blind man can strike me?
You aren't an opponent that one
can afford to hold back against, Director.
My eyes are already open!
Hence the name "Secret Unsealed"!
SECRET UNSEALED
Lady Satsuki, take these!
BAKUZAN-GAKO
BAKUZAN-KORYU
Well done, Inumuta!
We can't shake off another!
Is that so?
I have nothing else to take off,
but being a Nudist means flying
by the seat of your pants.
I agree wholeheartedly, sir.
Clear the deck!
Hey, what are you up to?!
Don't tell me you're—
Oh, but I am!
The last ace up
the Naked Sol's sleeve...
...Great Naked Dagger!
Oh, you want to use that blade
to peel that gourd bare, huh?
I like it!
GREAT NAKED DAGGER
We're here, Ryuko!
This is that thing's core!
Let's do it!
Both halves, Decapitation Mode!
DUAL SCISSOR BLADE: DECAPITATION MODE
Finishing Move: SEN-I-SOSHITSU!
Damage report!
Major damage to #1, #3 turbines!
Remaining #2 turbine
is putting out all it can!
Crap! This is as far as we can get
on human power, huh?
This damn thing is
just too hard!
Ryuko!
But I gotta do it anyway!
I promised Mako and the rest!
This ship is the homeland
of Ryuko's soul!
And not just the one
in my head!
I know the one outside my head
feels the same way!
Ryuko has always, always
waited for me!
So this ship is gonna—
Mr. Mikisugi, the turbine
has started turning again!
Or rather, it's spinning
like crazy!
Wait for us, Ryuko!
I'll catch up to you in no time!
Mako? Is that you?!
Ryuko!
- Ryuko!
- Mako! It's you, right?!
- Mako!
- The gang...
The gang's all here!
Ryuko, I can feel it!
Your blood is all fired up!
- Yeah! Let's do it, Senketsu!
- Right!
Impossible...
The Original Life Fiber
can't be destroyed by mere—
You look all dazed and confused, Ragyo.
That ain't surprising.
Cause not making any sense
is kinda our thing!
The girl you mocked as a sham
will thwart you.
Humanity does not live
for clothing!
You waste your time...
Attention, worthless trash
of Honnouji Academy!
The show is not yet over!
That Kamui and those idiotic
Goku Uniforms,
you were all just
the opening act!
The headline act is the ultimately chic
and elegant fashion show
put on by the ultimate Grand Couturier
and her ultimate model!
Prepare yourselves!
Please pardon the delay,
Lady Ragyo
Shinra-Koketsu is complete.
Well done, Nui.
My foolish daughters
have treated you rudely, I see.
Forgive them.
Lady Ragyo...
What are these?
They are no replacement for
the nimble fingers of the Grand Couturier,
but they will allow you
to fight these foolish humans.
This world will be cloaked
in Life Fibers soon.
There is no longer
any need to sew clothing.
This is enough.
So this is your final creation, eh?
I can't wait to find out
how it feels on me.
Magnificent, Iori.
I am amazed you restored
this many Goku Uniforms.
I didn't restore them.
I made them
even more powerful!
I'm not surprised.
We've got ultimate loadouts, too!
We've incapacitated
the Original Life Fiber.
However, Ragyo Kiryuin
is still alive and well.
We will now fight our way
into Honnouji Academy,
destroy its transmitter,
and apprehend Ragyo Kiryuin
and Nui Harime!
Soroi?
That's hot!
So your eyes are open, but you're still
sensitive to hot drinks, huh?
S-Shut up!
Don't break these cups.
We do not go to our deaths.
We will return here alive and
enjoy another cup of this tea.
Right, Soroi?
I will have plenty
of hot water ready.
Hey, you don't have
to come, too!
I've come this far,
so I have to see it through!
Sis...
Don't worry! If anything
happens to you,
I'll squeeze the Kiryuin Conglomerate
for a ton in damages!
Fight hard, but don't
kill yourself.
Here are some croquettes for you!
Don't let your family's
love go to waste.
Be happy enough to make up
for our cursed family.
Don't worry on that score, Satsuki.
When it comes to being incomprehensible,
this family's the best in the world.
Yep!
We're leaving Mako
in your hands.
If anything happens, we'll
sue the Kiryuin Conglomerate
'til they're bankrupt,
so take good care of her.
I'll keep that in mind.
Okay, let's go,
Ryuko, Lady Satsuki!
You got it!
- Life Fiber Synchronize, Kamui Senketsu!
- Life Fiber Override, Kamui Junketsu!
KAMUI SENKETSU KAMUI JUNKETSU
All right, let's take back
our academy!
Yeah!
Welcome to the runway of death,
Ryuko!
This world belongs
to Life Fibers.
You cannot stop the advent of
the Starseed Cocoon Sphere.
STARSEED COCOON SPHERE
We will!
Kiryuin blood flows in our veins,
and for that very reason,
we will alter that fate!
We've already killed
the Original Life Fiber.
Quit being a sore loser!
Be careful, Ryuko.
This woman is dangerous.
She's on a whole different level from before.
Don't wimp out on me, Senketsu.
The Kamui speaks the truth.
Behold!
Life Fiber Domination:
Shinra-Koketsu!
SHINRA-KOKETSU
Time for the finishing
touches, Hououmaru.
I am ready.
Learn what true fear is,
my foolish daughters!
MANKIND FACES ITS GREATEST CRISIS
As mankind faces its greatest crisis,
so does TRIGGER!
SO DOES TRIGGER
FACE THEIR GREATEST CRISIS
FATEFUL MOTHER AND DAUGHTERS
Whether the fateful showdown between
mother and daughters will be concluded
AND
SHOWDOWN
WHETHER IT WILL BE CONCLUDED OR NOT
STAFF
is all up to the
staff's hard work!
AND
UP TO HARD WORK
FIGHT ON
Fight on, TRIGGER!
Don't lose, TRIGGER!
TRIGGER
DON'T LOSE
KILL LA KILL
Kill la Kill, the finale!
"Past the Infinite Darkness"!
FINALE
EPISODE 24
PAST THE INFINITE DARKNESS