Haikyu!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Shiratorizawa            Karasuno
Episode 10: The Battle of Concepts
We've basically used up all our
options for switching out players.
But right now, the setter's on the back line,
Hinata, nice serve!
and there are three attackers in front.
Along with Hinata's super-fast back
attack, there are two attackers.
This rotation is 100% a
super attack-style rotation.
If you guys can find a chance to attack...
With Nishinoya out and Sawamura in front,
receiving is also really
light on this rotation, too.
Everything is riding on the blockers.
Fly
Got it!
Hayato!
It went in.
Hinata, change positions with me!
Time-difference attacks don't
work against Four-Eyes...
Then we'll get through the
center with sheer speed!
They're going for the center
at a time like this?!
Listen up, brat!
Read blocking is a block that consists of
restraint and persistence, but it's also...
The block where you laugh last.
One touch!
Chance ball!
There's no other...
...choice...
...but to...
...attack!
A minus tempo...
Back attack!
Go!
Jump on it, Taichi!
Shirabu!
Right!
A straight!
Ready, and...
Hinata!
Kageyama, get the last!
Hinata, are you okay?
Yeah!
It's in!
Got it!
They returned it to a terrible spot.
There's no time to hesitate!
Ushijima-san!
Follow!
This toss isn't going up for me...
It's so frustrating...
But...
Because I want to see his spikes...
that's also frustrating.
We're going to stop him!
This is their first 3-person block today
Ready, and...
where they're closing in on a straight...
Whenever we do 3-person blocks,
we always closed in on cross spikes,
but on the last one, let's
close on a straight spike.
It'll be a trap we set up
for one whole set or more.
Out of the dozens of three-person
blocks we've jumped today,
we've always made a route for
the ball to escape through.
We can't mess up this timing.
We won't let it go above us.
Ushiwaka knows that this is the one spot
where he can comfortably hit a straight.
Even when his form was crumbling...
He changed it to a cross at the last second!
Damn it, damn it...
He's so damn cool!
Asahi, get the last!
Chance ball!
Their #10 is coming!
Their #10 isn't running up?
He's slowing down his tempo,
from a minus tempo to a first tempo,
and then...
mixing in.
Shit!
Volleyball is sport of height.
It is an absolute that
tall players are strong.
Fly
Strengthening each
player is a strength,
and so is finding a new way to fight.
That's exactly why there are so many
different attacks and defenses today.
There are truly various kinds of strengths.
The great coach Arie Selinger once said,
"There is no reason to believe that
there will be no development or changes
in the future."
Shiratorizawa            Karasuno
What? Seriously?!
That's my little brother!
The one with the glasses!
They did it...
They really did it.
Tsukki!
Farewell, my paradise.
Hey, it's time to line up.
I-I can't stand up...
Fly
Come on, Shoyo!
Hey!
You can do it!
Thank you very much!
Talk about an upset.
Damn it, why doesn't that bastard
Ushiwaka look more upset?
Thank you very much!
Is Karasuno's #10 about as tall as I am?
Huh? Yes, I believe so.
He'll probably continue to grow, though.
The higher his goals get,
the more treacherous his path will be.
Sorry, Hinata. We were trying
to close in on that straight
but we didn't make it in time...
Are you okay?
Totally fine!
It's because the course was so narrow
that he was able to pick that up.
Kageyama does good work.
Did you notice it, too, Iwa-chan?
Apparently when Four-Eyes came back,
he gave them some kind of
directions about blocking.
Like closing in on Ushiwaka's straight.
That's why after the serve,
Tobio suddenly switched places with the
shrimp who was in the path of the cross,
because Nishinoya-kun wasn't there.
And then he returned the
ball at the last moment.
Your student's not bad.
He's not my student!
And on top of everything,
he was able to accommodate the shrimp,
who came here to do something different.
It's painfully obvious.
Well... all of their good work only happened
because of the blocks of that
first-year with the glasses.
But I guess the shrimp is a spiker
you end up wanting to toss to.
No wonder he's got Tobio wrapped
around his little finger.
Come on, let's go home.
I'd rather die than see the awards ceremony.
You really are a crappy guy.
Thank you for all of your support.
Thank you very much!
Well done!
Great job, you guys!
I love you, Ryu!
Shoyo!
Sho-chan!
Sawamura, Sugawara, Azumane!
Congratulations on your victory!
Certain Victory Charm
Be Courageous Warriors
Shiratorizawa Academy Volleyball Team
Thank you very much!
Kenjiro, are you all right?
Yes.
My head's just spinning a little.
I never thought we would lose.
Well...
No one here thought we would lose...
We'll have a meeting when we get back.
Once the awards ceremony
is over, get onto the bus.
Right.
And you'll be hitting a hundred serves later.
Great job, you guys!
I'm...
I'm... sho happwy...
Sawamura!
Great job...
Great job completing that
three-man block in the end.
but even if your thighs were to split open,
I'm counting on you guys
in the mid-air battles.
Well, I made a promise.
Tsukishima!
No matter what anyone says,
you're the MVP today.
I'm always the MVP, so I'll let you have
that title just for today, Tsukishima.
You're definitely the mental MVP.
Wakatoshi-kun, you got pissed
off in the end, didn't you?
Usually, you'd regroup or leave that
to someone else in that situation.
I got chills thinking they
might actually block it.
I wanted to say, "I'm stronger than you."
Is that childish of me?
But I still wanted to say it.
Isn't what drives most
people childish in general?
That was a great straight.
It felt like I got to see a new
side to you, Wakatoshi-kun.
I'm gonna quit volleyball after high school,
but I'll be watching you on TV
and brag that we were best buds,
so do your best.
Yeah.
When Jonetsu Tairiku makes
a documentary about you
you totally have my permission to let
them interview me as an old comrade.
Okay...
Karasuno                    Shiratorizawa
Ushijima-san was so damn cool...
Hinata Shoyo and Kageyama
Tobio of the concrete...
I'll defeat you next time.
I'll make sure I'll be able to
stand on the same level as you!
I'll make you say that I'm
better than Oikawa-san!
Tsukki, the awards ceremony is starting.
Is something wrong?
I said I would stop a handful of his spikes,
but I was only able to stop one...
Even though there were five sets.
Talk about lame—
There's no way that you
were lame! Are you stupid?!
Stupid—
This isn't the time to be down!
We're going to nationals!
But before that, the awards ceremony!
And now, I present this award to the victors. Miyagi Prefectural Karasuno High School.
Concluding the Miyagi Prefecture Qualifiers of the
National High School Spring Volleyball Tournament,
your team has emerged victorious.
I present you this award in acknowledgment
of your commendable performance.
Congratulations!
To praise both teams for their good match,
and to wish the best to Karasuno
High School for their performance
at the Spring High School Volleyball
National Tournament in January,
I'd like to ask the audience to give
them another big round of applause.
Let's go...
...to the Spring Tournament!
Closed
Izakaya
Osuwari
I'm pretty sure I recently saw my relative's
one-year-old do the same thing...
Tanaka, wake/get up!
Kiyoko-san is scolding me!
Yuhi Beer Dry
You guys need to decide if
you're going to eat or sleep!
Ukai-kun, I'm... sho happwy!
Sensei, your face is a mess...
And that's the eighth time you've said that.
I'm so sorry.
Those guys worked hard on this match
like their lives depended on it.
Make sure you guys don't break any plates.
And now, we're the ones that
are gonna have it rough.
It's gonna get real busy, Sensei.
Haikyu!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Congratulations
On Going to the Spring Volleyball Tournament,
Boys' Volleyball Team!
Class 1-1
Hey, so our volleyball team
is going to nationals?
You guys didn't go to the match,
did you? It was awesome!
Our boys' volleyball team was
a powerhouse to begin with.
Really?
There's a really scary third-year
on the volleyball team, isn't there?
There's a second-year that
looks like a punk, isn't there?
Are you really okay, Hinata?
Their manager is so pretty!
Seriously?
Where are they holding nationals?
The Tokyo... Metropolitan Gymnasium!
That's awesome!
I know, right?
Looks like the idiot's got a huge head now.
Are you going, too, Hinata?
Of course!
He's in charge of holding
the players' belongings,
and like running errands
and doing their laundry.
So he's an errand boy for the scary people.
I'm going to be in the match!
Really? Well, good luck.
You don't believe me!
Class 1-5
Hitoka, what are you drawing?
A rough sketch of the
volleyball team's poster.
Huh...
We're moving rooms next.
I'm gonna go ahead.
Got it! I'll be right there.
That seems rough. Is that
the manager's job, too?
Who knows? But she seemed to be having fun.
The Crows Fly to Tokyo
Kozume Kenma
Re: We won!!!
Congrats.
The representative team from Tokyo
is just about to be decided, right?
Yeah.
I think for Tokyo, four schools get
decided in the first qualifier,
and then I think the qualifier to decide
the representative is in November.
I think that Nekoma and
Fukurodani both made it.
It's amazing that they made it
into the top four schools in Tokyo.
It makes me realize we went to a
training camp with some really crazy guys.
We're gonna beat Nekoma!
Right, Kageyama?
That's if they make it
through the qualifiers.
Of course they will!
We're gonna play a match like there'll
never be another match again...
at the Spring Tournament!
Sumida City Gymnasium
Nekoma High School
Fukurodani Academy
Nohebi Academy
Itachiyama Academy
Congrats! Karasuno High School
Boys Volleyball Team
Confirmed to go to Nationals!!
Nice Kill Ramen
Nice Serve Gyoza
Nice Receive
Fried Rice
10% of the proceeds of the
support menu will be donated.
Congratulations! Karasuno High
School is going to nationals!!
Sakanoshita Shop
The Crows Fly to Tokyo Once Again
The Karasuno High School Boys Volleyball Club will be
going to the Spring High School Volleyball National Tournament!!
We are currently asking for donations.
We thank you for your support.
Contact: Karasuno High School Boys Volleyball Club Advisor: Takeda
Faculty Room
Takeda-sensei, you've got
a call. It's on line 2.
Yes, hello, this is Takeda.
Yes...
Oh, yes. Thank you for calling.
Yes... Yes...
Huh?
What are they doing?
They're measuring the highest point
That was 302 centimeters.
they can hit for the
Spring Tournament pamphlet.
Huh... I guess that's what you do
when you're going to nationals.
Next, Kageyama.
Um... 337 centimeters.
Right now, Kageyama's at the top.
And there's only one remaining...
Next, Hinata.
Right!
How many centimeters?
How many centimeters is it?!
Just wait!
Um...
333 centimeters.
Yes!
That's about the same as you, Asahi.
You owe me three curry buns.
Damn it... I'm not gonna lose.
Next, let's battle with
whoever gets the most blocks!
The loser buys the winner
Gungun Yogurt for a week!
You're on!
Is everyone here?
Gather round!
Right!
Thank you all for your hard work.
This is sudden, but I have some big news.
Kageyama-kun,
you've been asked to attend the
National Youth Intensive Training Camp.
The National...
...Youth...