Chiranosuke's Code, number one:
You must not change history
without my permission.
Number two:
You must not tell anyone else the truth.
I'll make it easy to understand.
First, this is the world you're in.
And this train travels down
the rail, toward the future.
If it goes straight, it will arrive here,
at the worst-case scenario,
the New Year's Eve when the asteroid hits.
But I need you to go
toward the New Year's Eve
where the asteroid doesn't strike.
Beyond that is a supremely
happy and peaceful future.
To guide the world to that future is
the ultimate purpose of the
Human Preservation Project.
In any case, you absolutely, unfailingly,
must succeed in this project.
That is your destiny.
But I'll tell you this:
there is no "next" for you.
Not good.
Two days with no progress.
Hey, Ito, open up!
What was that noise just now?
That was, uh... It was me. I screamed.
Huh?
Oh, yeah, I remember this happening.
To Yu-tan.
I found something funny here,
so I'm sending it to you.
They were selling it at a party store.
What do you think? Isn't it hilarious?
By the way, do you remember how
the poem "Ame ni mo makezu" goes?
I think we learned it in school,
but I didn't remember it at all.
So I looked it up online,
and when I read it again, I just loved it.
You should read it, too, Yu-tan.
Losing neither to rain, nor the wind,
losing neither to the snow,
nor to the heat of summer.
Having a strong body, unfettered by desire,
and never offending anyone...
Like I could wear this thing!
Punch Line
Halt!
Super helper-man of justice,
Miyazawa Kenji, is here!
Miyazawa Kenji?
Another freak.
What, aren't you going to attack?
But I know I'm going to lose...
What?
I don't like pain!
Fine, then I'll start—
Wait! I'm not emotionally prepared!
Called a nobody by everyone.
Never praised, never blamed.
That's the kind of person I...
...want to become.
Huh?
I decided I'd become that way,
so I could guide this world to a supremely
happy and peaceful future.
What the hell are you talking about?
Just give me twenty seconds, would you?
What if I do?
Do I get a reward?
Yeah, I'll amply reward you.
Fine.
Nineteen.
Eighteen.
Seventeen.
I knew I'd come here, but...
I don't know who's there,
but can you get this off of me?
Okay, got it!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Wait, time out!
Don't run!
Muhi!
As promised, your reward—
Huh?
That bastard!
Wait up!
He's like...
A totally different person.
Should I be chasing him like this?
Chiranosuke's Code, number one:
You must not change history
without my permission.
So far, six billion, three hundred
seventy-three million,
one hundred fifty-three thousand,
seven hundred forty yous
have broken that code, and went on to fail.
Still, I can't just let him get away.
Hey, that hurt, man.
Does it really matter?
That's not even your body, Tsubouchi Qmay.
Who are you?
It doesn't matter who I am!
Why is Asteroid VR-1 hitting Earth?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Don't play dumb!
We have no intention of
bringing down the asteroid...
for now.
Because W isn't complete yet?
Right. That cub's regenerative ability
is imperative to W's completion.
I heard it belonged to the
Qmay Group to begin with.
Who told you that?
Does it matter?
It's true that we created it.
At Uber Labs.
Uber Labs?
So you have heard of it.
You appear to be a Uberfier too, after all.
Are you saying the lab was
a Qmay Group facility?
I am.
The Uberfication predictions,
the Hercules virus design...
It was all my doing.
What happened to us is all your fault!
I don't think there'd be any
point in hurting this body.
Why did you do it?
You'd never understand
my sublime philosophies.
Humanity must evolve into a perfect form.
That's the only way to
bring about world peace.
That's why I created the Qmay Group.
When I presented the people with the
miraculous power of Uberfication,
the fools followed me with gleaming eyes.
The people want that power.
You're insane!
Indeed, evolution is beyond the ordinary.
You've already taken the first step.
What are you saying?
Why don't you come work for us again?
Like hell!
You'll soon understand.
I'll be waiting for your return.
But to think you were Strange Juice, Mikatan.
Hey, don't scare me like that.
I thought that man was back.
He's probably at the hospital by now.
He was taken in an ambulance.
Narugino, you don't have to hide it.
I know who you are.
How?
Just who are you?
Haven't I told you?
I'm the super helper-man of
justice, Miyazawa Kenji!
No, no, I have nothing to do with him!
Anyway, Meika, can I talk to you?
Me?
And what do you want?
I thought I'd help you with the repairs.
R-Repairs?
Your fusion reactor broke
down after that man hit you.
Right?
Huh? W-Wait—
Let's get started.
Hey, how did you know I was a robot?
In a word, destiny, I guess.
Destiny, huh?
Fair enough.
That's enough?!
I don't mind.
Shouldn't it bother you a little more?
Well, I'd be lying if I
said it didn't bother me.
But I trust you.
You trust me?
Grandpa told me about you,
a long time ago, before he passed away.
Meika,
it seems my time's up.
Grandpa...
Don't cry, Meika.
I'm always by your side.
You remember my three last requests, right?
First, protect a girl named Chiyoko,
and raise her to be a good hero.
Second, create a secret organization,
Justice Punch, with Chiyoko.
And third...
Are you okay, Grandpa?!
Listen, Meika.
Justice Punch will one day save the world.
That's the will of the heavens.
Don't ever...
Grandpa?
Grandpa!
So, what's the third?
Huh?
What's the third request?
"A hero in a creepy costume will
one day appear before you.
Trust him. He's not a bad person."
Creepy?
And apparently, he's a member
of Justice Punch, too.
Me?
Just two more.
The "Punch" in "Justice Punch" comes
from "pan̄ja," meaning "five" in Hindi.
In other words, it's a group
of five heroes of justice.
Then the other two are...
No way.
Okay, repairs done.
Thanks.
Hey, how did Professor Tenga
know about the future?
This is called a Reizoukou.
Underworld Graphic Communicator
rei                          zou   kou
It stands for Underworld
Graphic Communicator.
It's just a fax machine...
I don't know too much about it.
But he said that one day, he got a
fax message about the future.
A fax?
...writing down diagrams and equations,
and instructions on what
to do on certain dates.
And I was sending them to someone by fax.
What's going on?
Damn it, why did you do that?
Do what?
You broke Tomoda's arms and legs.
Chiranosuke's Code, number one...
I must not change history
without your permission.
If you know, then why?!
What was I supposed to do?!
I couldn't just let Tomoda walk away.
If things went like the last time,
he'd have killed two of Ito's classmates.
All for just two people?
Two people who did horrible
things to Ito, no less.
That doesn't mean I can let them die!
A little sacrifice is inevitable
to save seven billion lives.
Where are you going?
Does it matter?
That said, I don't actually
know where I should go.
He was given to me.
From Rabura's little brother, Rando-oniichan.
Oh, I should go ask that Rando guy.
Hey, Ito, there's something I want to ask...
Hey!
Huh? Is she out?
What's that?
What the heck are you doing?
Hang on, I'll get you free.
It's so cold.
Panties!
You pervert!
Soul
I'm telling you, you're misunderstanding.
What am I misunderstanding, you pervert?
I'm not a pervert.
If anything, he's a perbeart.
Pervert
It's the perbeart's fault.
Perbeart
Perbeart?
Muhi was acting weird, making
a racket under the kotatsu.
So I looked inside, and...
How do you know about Muhi?
Um...
I heard from Rabura.
From Rabura?
She's so loose-lipped,
it's like she's leaking helium.
She'll flap her gums about anything.
Oh, yeah, speaking of Rabura,
do you know where her brother is?
Where's this coming from?
Just tell me. You're cousins, aren't you?
We are, but why?
I have business with him.
Just ask Rabura, then.
I don't think she'd tell me.
She's so tight-lipped, it's like trying
to shove barium down her throat.
You just said helium a minute ago.
That's not the point!
Rando-oniichan is coming here this afternoon.
What?
He wants to check on Muhi.
Soul
I see. So you know about the Qmay Group's plans.
I guess there's no point in hiding it, then.
I used to be a Qmay Group devotee.
A fervent one, at that.
Tsubouchi Qmay took a liking to me,
and he put me in charge of caring for Muhi.
I was ordered to take him from
a research facility deep in
the mountains of Nagano
to the Tokyo headquarters.
But I ended up going...
To Korai House.
You came to give Muhi to Ito.
Why did you defy your orders?
To stop the project, of course.
Without Muhi, they can't make W.
But you said you were a fervent devotee.
You know how they say that the day
before the field trip is the most fun?
I was intoxicated by the Qmay Group's
teachings because they were so unrealistic.
Then it became real, and I got turned off.
What did you do after you gave Muhi to Ito?
I headed back to the mountains in
my car, and ran into a guard rail.
In order to make it look like
Muhi got away in an accident.
That's how you got injured?
No, this isn't from the accident.
The Qmay Group people did it to me.
As punishment for letting Muhi get away.
That's how I came to quit the group.
Nee-chan covered the expensive resignation fee.
"Tsugaru Forced-Sightseeing"
Lyrics: Uchikoshi Koutarou
Music: Komuro Tetsuya
The apples of Tsugaru are ripe with nectar...
Even Dracula eats the garlic grown in Tsugaru...
Hey, by the way, is it true that Meika
is Strange Juice's right-hand man?
Code name: Pumpkin Chair.
I'm basically in charge of mechanical engineering.
Then you made that costume, Meika?
Of course.
Speaking of which, Narugino, you're going on
missions without wearing your
short pants, aren't you?
The size isn't quite right.
They are pretty tight, aren't they?
It'll fine. I'll lose weight.
You totally won't, will you?
Harakiri Harrassment
Lyrics: Uchikoshi Koutarou
Music: Komuro Tetsuya
Eager harakiri...
Heart-pounding, gut-wrenching...
Okay, Yuta-kun, you're up next.
Huh? No, that's okay.
You're not getting out of it.
It's your turn.
It's your duty as a resident.
I really don't want to!
Come on.
No! I'm not singing, okay?
No matter what anyone says—
So white and plump...
I want to stack your buns
higher than Burj Khalifa!
I Wanna Stack Your Buns
Lyrics: Uchikoshi Koutarou
Music: Komuro Tetsuya
Korai House is the best!
Yay!
Rabura-san, come on!
Hey, when should we do this next?
A party?
The closest celebration is New Year's Eve.
That's a bit soon, isn't it?
We can do something else, then.
Like, an event that will
get our hearts pumping...
Like...
Fireworks?
That's it!
Fireworks in the middle of winter...
I just love the mismatch!
All right, let's all do
fireworks on New Year's Eve!
Woo-hoo!
What did you want to talk to me about?
Well... I wanted to thank you.
Thank me?
You helped me when the
bus hijacking happened, right?
So...
Thanks.
You don't need to thank me.
There's something I've felt since I first met you.
You give me a really nostalgic feeling, somehow.
Sorry, that was a weird thing to say...
See you.
Narugino!