"Loss"
You're reassigning me as an instructor?
That's right.
You have two weeks to prepare.
You will undergo special training
before taking your post in
Gurantseere Cosmopolitan Academy.
You were an exceptional pilot.
This is the optimum post
for making the most of those skills.
The MJP Project was founded in GC 35
to develop humans suited for space life.
With the Wulgaru invasion,
it was decided that those over
the age of 12 were to become pilots.
They were transferred to
Gurantseere Cosmopolitan Academy.
Open
SPIRITS
Congratulations!
This isn't the sort of
thing you celebrate.
How could you say that?
Aren't you embarking on a new journey?
My job is to train children
who were genetically
altered before birth to fight on the frontline!
It's depressing...
Those children were temporarily left
in the care of foster parents,
but we're going to erase
all of their personal
memories before they start school.
I wonder if that's so they won't regret
leaving their old lives behind.
Dealing with kids that lack both
a past and future...
I don't know if I can take it.
Excuse me! Gimme another
medium-sized beer!
Are you even listening?
Actually, screw that.
Gimme a bottle of premium saké!
But isn't that why they
chose you, Rin-Rin?
True, my piloting and
fighting days are over...
This is the only job left for me.
But didn't you make it back alive?
You were the only survivor
when your unit got destroyed.
Why don't you pass on
those survival skills?
Okay?
Did you get that?
Thanks to the Ioness Theory,
there was a substantial
boost in engine efficiency.
However, the human reaction time
for those piloting the-
What are you doing in
the middle of class?
Uh, well, you see...!
Well?
Ah, umm, well...
S-sorry, I didn't mean it like that.
Sorry, my bad!
Poopy.
Oh, my God!
Your bodyline is like that
of a beautiful Steyr.
You've shot my heart with your
hot loaded armor-piercing bullets,
knocking me down!
How are the students?
Right. On average,
they are brimming with potential.
They follow their orders
and have fast response times
in mock space battles.
However, there is one team
that is highly problematic.
How so?
Sir...
The team is composed
of students who were
originally unsuited for teamwork.
With impressive latent abilities,
they definitely possess hidden potential.
But they are lacking
on the mental front.
They are ill oriented for group work.
I see.
That will be their downfall as pilots.
And the flip side?
Inversely, they could
become mentally strong.
Once they master teamwork,
they will outstrip the other teams.
Uh, on what grounds...?
They have abnormally strong
survival instincts.
That makes them ideal pilots
for AHSMB units equipped
with the JURIA-SYSTEM.
Train them! That is your mission.
Very well.
Tamaki!
Rose 3's first and second thrusters
have taken damage.
Power is down by 40%!
Enemy fighters are
approaching from β34.
Th-they got me!
What should we do?! What should I do?!
Kei, can't we help her?!
Kei? Kei!
Calm down. Think.
I should be able to save her.
If I'm a hero, fight! Fight!
Fight so we can survive!
Harmonic values, increasing.
One through three are increasing!
My armguards?
If Red 5 removed its armguards,
I could use them as shields...?
Thank you, Red 5!
Let's go! You're going
to become a hero with me.
Send a multi-launcher, please!
Izuru!
Are you all right, Tamaki?
Forget about me! Everyone,
get out of here.
Get a grip, Tamaki!
But at this rate, they'll take you and
everyone else down with me!
We're going to make it back alive!
I... I...!
I've always wanted to go on a date!
Even if we make it back,
that may not happen...
What's with that serious answer?!
That's not what you say
at a time like this!
Just tell her she'll find a date!
Scum.
Blue 1, take the right.
Gold 4, take the left.
Purple 2, issue orders.
Roger!
Blue 1, strike Unit 4 in the upper right
portion of Formation A.
Gold 4, fire at the bottom left
portion of Formation B.
Keep them in check and
carve open a path for Rose 3.
Ally units have taken 32.6% damage.
Ammo down to 10%.
They can only fight for
another 12 minutes.
Probability of return: -15%.
They can't possibly continue to fight!
Vice Chief of Staff, please issue
the order for them to retreat.
Sir!
Retreat is not an option!
Don't run! Fight the beasts!
They can't! At this rate,
we're going to lose all of the units.
Why can't they?!
Do you realize how much money
we've put into them?
Blue 1, Gold 4, Red 5, attack!
Uh, right!
D-don't turn and run!
I'm having control issues here!
Vice Chief of Staff, please
order them to retreat!
All units, retreat!
Force Rose 3 to purge.
Roger.
Purple 2, forcibly purge
Rose 3. Copy that?
Yes, Ma'am!
I'm light!
Rose 3, retreat!
Roger!
If we use Rose 3's
boosters as missiles...
They should pack a real wallop!
Blue 1, protect Rose 3 as you retreat.
Gold 4, serve as backup
while you retreat.
Red 5, slow withdrawal.
How's everyone doing?
They'll reach the ship in just a minute.
Kei, you should head back as well!
Roger!
Izuru!
Izuru, are you all right?
Probably.
Red 5's transmission has been damaged.
Primary reactor has ceased functioning.
Energy reserves down by 25%.
Auxiliary power is dropping fast!
Auxiliary thrusters are totally shot.
He can't change its course.
The emergency escape unit is out, too!
We'll have to cut our
losses with the one.
Wha-?!
You aren't the least bit okay!
I'll be fine, so get back, Kei!
Izuru?!
Get back!
Purple 2, come back immediately!
But Izuru-!
I'll head on back after you leave.
How could you say that?!
You can't even move!
Purple 2, did you hear me?!
The hero always makes
it back in one piece.
I can't die in a place like this!
I still want to draw manga and
eat more of your insanely sweet cakes!
Izuru...
Izuru!
Purple 2!
AHSMB units...? Allies?!
That is...Team Doberman!
Who gave them orders to sortie?
Commander!
Team Doberman will hereby retrieve
Red 5 and withdraw.
Thank you, Sir!
If there was another able team,
we should have included them
in the battle to begin with!
How dare he hold out on me!
Izuru!
Purple 2 has returned.
Is he okay?!
Should I get a stretcher?
Better, just in case!
Izuru?!
Are you all right, Izuru?
The Wulgaru army has
started to pull back.
I believe they are
headed toward Jupiter.
Izuru!
Welcome back!
Care for a drink?
Izuru?
I made it back...
You should have...
You should have gotten out of there
with the rest of us.
What?!
You don't need to handle
everything by yourself.
Do you realize what would have
happened if help hadn't come?
Seriously!
Ah, everyone is giving
me a piece of their mind.
Excuse me?!
That's nothing to be happy about!
Remove everything from
Block 3 to Block 5.
Send Rose 3 and Red 5 to Maintenance D.
Well?
Ugh. We're administering
emergency repairs,
but they need a full overhaul in HQ's dock.
That goes double for Rose 3 and Red 5.
Rose 3 currently uses
a navigational shield.
We'll need to give it
a maximum-power shield
that can withstand enemy beams,
just like the ones Blue 1 and Red 5 use.
Really! This is no time for sweets.
It's time for super-premium dry saké!
I figured.
Where is the Vice Chief of Staff?
Resting in his personal room.
I see.
Sir, GDF high command has requested
we send them a copy of our
battle report in all due haste.
You write it! I'll check
over it once it's ready.
I'll send over the battle logs.
Thank you!
I wonder how long this war
is going to drag out...
Who can say?
We don't even know what
the Wulgaru are after
or where they came from.
True enough.
I'm sorry to have
interrupted your work.
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
February 4, 86 GC.
Our units engaged what
we believe to be an
armed Wulgaru recon force near FRB-1011.
That's right. We've been left in
the dark, ever since then...
They came out of nowhere, striking
Earth's frontier development base.
The armies stationed around the outer planets
were dispatched immediately.
Thus began Earth's first
war in outer space.
We believe the Wulgaru armada is
composed of 1 massive mother ship,
5 large carriers, 800 space-faring vessels
and 3,000 mobile fighters.
Our combined global forces
include 15 million soldiers,
3,500 space-faring vessels and
20,000 mobile fighters.
Despite vastly superior numbers,
our results in battle have been dismal
as we gradually pull back.
At this rate, even the most
favorable calculations
show them reaching Earth in...
Isn't this stuff awesome?
It has a rich fragrance
and a refreshing zing.
Not to mention the delicious fruity taste
that explodes in your mouth!
Hey, stop right there!
S-sorry...
I swear, you're putting perfectly
good saké to waste!
Y'know...
So like, what do you think's
gonna happen to us?
In this battle, I mean...
Rin-Rin!
No matter how much we outnumber them,
their technology is far superior to our own...
That may be the case, but...
Even if we sent a bunch
of men after them,
they can easily counter the attack
with a handful of cutting-edge units.
Oh, my, my...
They swoop in and then
swoop right back out,
so they've suffered
surprisingly few losses.
Too many peanuts overwhelm
the persimmon seeds!
This isn't about persimmon seeds!
Then what are you talking about?
Hey! Don't take that attitude with me!
See, I almost gave up...
I almost gave up on Red 5.
Rin-Rin!
I'm not... supposed to give up
on my own students!
I'm not supposed to lose hope!
Aw, jeez...
Damn, you're a crying drunk...
Tamaki, go to your room
if you're gonna sleep.
No! I'm staying here.
More antacids?
Isn't it only natural to get an upset stomach
after a battle like that?
I'm amazed you guys don't have ulcers.
It's just a matter of time before
you form a hole in your gut.
Shut it!
It'd be nice if there was something
we could do to help relax...
She's crashing in three, two, one!
Hey!
Huggie!
T-Tamaki?!
She's just like a baby.
Sometimes, I have dreams.
Of what?
I dream that I'm a baby and
someone is holding me.
When I close my eyes,
someone gently pats me on the back.
But that's just a dream, right?
Yeah, but I'm sure someone cared
for me like that once.
I just don't remember it.
Say, didn't you think we were
going to die back there?
Yeah...
When I die, do you think
they'll inform the people
who used to pat my back?
It's doubtful.
Dang, you're cold!
Gosh darn it!
Naïve dudes like you are insensitive
to another's naïve beliefs!
What was that?!
Knock it off!
Yeah. Let's head back to our own rooms.
Do something about Tamaki before you go.
Hey, Leader. Carry the girl.
He's drawing again?
That's like a tranquilizer for Izuru.
But Izuru tried to protect
Tamaki, all on his own.
How do you feel?
I am fine.
What is that?
Supposedly it is called
a "picture book".
Pictures are drawn to match the story.
I cannot comprehend such books.
How could anything save the truth
hold any value?
I do not understand, myself.
But they may be unable
to understand us just as
we fail to understand them.
Auron Taul has spoken! Open the gate!
Is fighting the only option for those
who cannot understand one another?
Team Rabbits will hereby return to
Gurantseere Cosmopolitan Academy.
Roger!
We're taking the AHSMB units back to HQ,
where we'll fix them right up.
Please take me with you, too!
And one more thing.
Look after Rin-Rin for me.
I-I'm just fine!
You just had a wee bit too much to drink.
Right, Rin-Rin?
Don't say that in front of my students!
I wanna call you Rin-Rin!
Watch it!
Why do you call her Rin-Rin?
We're childhood friends.
Reika!
I've been calling her that since
elementary school.
We went to different schools after that,
but then we met up again at
the military academy, remember?
Childhood friends...
I like that backstory!
This isn't a manga!
I wonder what it must be like
to have a childhood friend.
Quit going on about that!
We'll reach the ground momentarily.
Rin-Rin, see ya later!
Like I said, quit calling me that!
Where is the head mechanic going?
Wasn't she going to GDF's headquarters?
She said she's dropping
by her home in Kyoto.
Her family is always
giving her a hard time.
Believe it or not, she's a rich heiress.
An heiress?!
For Saionji Pharmaceutical.
My sponsor...?
But she became our head mechanic...?
Against her parents' wishes.
They disapproved? How dramatic!
Your lives are just beginning, too.
You have a lot to look forward to,
not just fighting.
Survive this war! That's a must!
Let's go.
Okay!
But dang does my head hurt!
She's drunk...
I haven't introduced them yet, have I?
That is Team Doberman.
They are the team that rescued you
in that last battle.
They're your seniors.
They are second gen MJP students
entering their third term.
Commander Simon kept them a secret
while they were on standby.
The team is composed of
Chandra, Randy and Patrick.
"Operation: Infiltrate a Planetoid Base"