This token buys one meal.
And this slip of paper can
be converted to 100 tokens.
I see...
Rationed meal tickets are the closest
concept in the Galactic Alliance of Humankind.
This is too much.
Conjecture: Tickets may be exchanged
for supplies other than meals.
Oxygen is so plentiful here
that it'll never run out.
What other supplies could be necessary?
Maybe...
Maybe I was accidentally overpaid?
Ledo!
Huh? Ledo, what's wrong?
I don't understand... how to use salary.
I see...
Come to think of it, I think you
told me there's no money in space.
This may be perfect timing. You'll be able
to use money to have all kinds of fun.
See, the festival is about to begin.
Festival?
Uh-huh!
They're going to catch a lot of fish, so
it means we're all going to celebrate.
Oh, that's right! Now there should
be a job opening to catch fish!
You'll use a Yunboro to get fish.
Guild Master, I've got a delivery!
Thanks!
It's the next course from
the chief navigator.
Got it!
Also, manpower!
Oh yeah, I hear you wanna
be part of the fishing crew?
Yeah. I want to try fish-catching work.
So the lazybones is finally
gonna be productive...
So, what happened to that flying Yunboro?
Don't need Chamber. I will do work.
Objection repeated: Inefficient activity.
That's a Swirling Galaxy.
Lightbugs. A type of nanomachine. A
legacy of the former civilization.
Due to the ocean currents when two Sea Galaxies intersect, sometimes a ring can be formed.
That way, the fish can't get out.
It's what you'd call a giant fishing spot.
Well, the festival's about to start!
Festival
You know how to operate this?
Simple operation system. No problem.
Is that right? Just don't break it!
Alright. Try to raise an arm.
I understand operation system. Where
is information support system?
What the hell is that?
Computer analysis of war situation.
We don't got that. Use your
own eyes to make decisions.
Roger.
Okay. Now just like that,
move to the Swirling Galaxy.
But listen, do it quietly. And
don't open up a hole in the ring.
Display current location.
Set coordinate axis.
What's wrong, Chamber?
Hey, what the hell are you
doin'?! Regain your bearings!
Information support!
You need to swim! Let yourself
relax and you'll float.
I cannot swim!
Ledo!
Yeesh! If he doesn't know how to swim,
he should've told me from the get-go!
I thought machines here
would do more what I say.
Well, there's no ocean in space, right?
Good effort. Anyway, what
do you say we have lunch?
Here you are, one Maiden
Meal and one seaweed bread.
Thanks!
Say, Ledo, are you sure
that's enough for you?
There's other food I'm sure you'd like.
No problem.
It must be tough being a soldier, huh?
About the work, you've got
nothing to feel down about.
I screw up on a regular basis myself.
I think you should be more
easygoing about it, Ledo.
How to become easygoing?
Maybe you should just try to have a good
time. The festival does start today.
But before that... Thank you for the food!
Thank you for the food...
Ledo, is it good?
Yeah. Good.
Really? Then you oughta look like it's good!
Look like it's good... How to do?
Amy, you haven't changed yet?!
Oh, no!
If you don't hurry up, all
the good guys will be taken!
But the hottie's already here!
So he is!
Come on, Amy! Are you
keeping him to yourself?!
Sorry! Let's go to the
festival together later!
Yeah...
Hurry up, let's go!
Proposal: If the mission is to capture
fish, it is possible for me to do it alone.
After all, you are back in
standby mode, Ensign Ledo.
Do what you want.
So this time you're here
in your own Yunboro, huh?
Negative 1: This machine is not a Yunboro.
My designation is Machine Caliber-K6821.
I am volunteering for the fishing mission.
Okay!
Negative 2: My pilot, Ensign Ledo,
is currently observing the festival.
The boy ain't in there?
I will now carry out the fishing
mission by capturing marine life.
Hey! Take a net!
Yo, Ledo! You did a great
job sinking, y'know?
No problem. Chamber is doing it for me.
Aw, don't sulk like that.
Hang out with me for a while.
I hear you don't know
how to spend your money?
Alright! Just for today,
I'll pick up the tab.
You can think of this as an example.
Hey, waitress! Over here!
What do you wanna eat?
Seaweed bread.
Waitress, two special dinners!
Got it! Two special dinners.
What, are you homesick? You
wanna go back to space?
But I have no map. I can't go back.
I see. Then there's nothin' you can do.
What do you think about life here?
Not bad. But great distance
between me and everyone.
Well, of course! It looks like
all you eat is seaweed bread.
People do not like seaweed bread?
That's not it. People can't see you.
People can not see me?
Look, isn't there somethin' you wanna do?
I want to return to Alliance battlefront.
No, not that! I mean somethin'
right now, on this ship!
I don't know.
Is a guy to be trusted if he doesn't
even know what he wants?
Good!
Team up with me in the salvage biz.
Salvage... Work?
Yeah! With you and that tin can of yours,
we could search for some big-ass treasures.
If I earn salary, money is too much...
Then when you make money, spend it
on tasty eats, for cryin' out loud!
And when you make more money,
get yourself a nice boat.
There's no point in just
lettin' your money sit there.
Somewhere along the line, you'll
get a grip on your desires.
Get a grip... on desires...
Hold it right there! I'm not
gonna let you steal him away.
Steal him?
If you're teaming up with anyone, make
it me, who does the actual job.
I can train you to be a first-class salvager.
I don't understand "salvage" so much...
It's simple. I'll teach you.
Alright? If there's anything you don't
understand, all you need do is ask.
If you don't know how to do
something, you can just imitate me.
Don't listen to this one. Stick with me and
you'll eat as much delicious grub as you like.
I'll teach you how to read the tides.
You've got aptitude, so it'll be easy.
With me, you'll be able to drink
your fill of quality booze.
You should know how to swim, too.
You can touch as many pretty
ladies' rumps as you want!
Pinion! You're just being vulgar!
Shut up, turtle shell ass!
Who's got a turtle shell ass,
you who can't even swim?!
I can swim, I just can't dive!
Thank you for your patience.
Here's the main dish.
That's what I've been waitin' for!
What?!
Hideauze!
Hey, what's wrong?!
Hideauze... Enemy of human
race! Objective: Destroy!
That's just a regular old
octopus. And it's yummy...
If this little octopus surprises you,
you'll be scared out of your wits if
you ever encounter a whalesquid.
Octopus... You eat?
Yummy?
Requesting support from pilot, Ensign Ledo.
Beginning capture.
Gravity Waver, fire!
Capture complete.
Both you and Ledo, what the
hell are you thinkin'?!
Nutritionally, there are no problems.
That's not the point!
Response status: Unknown.
I will request support from
my pilot, Ensign Ledo.
What, these are all minced?!
Listen, use a net! Watch and
learn from the people around you!
I want as big a net as possible. That
and cooperation from the Yunboros.
Now that's what I'm talkin' about!
I know, right?
What are you acting proud for?!
That was delicious!
I'm stuffed!
Chamber, enemy search!
Measuring energy response in the area.
Danger level: Minimal.
It's okay. See, look at that!
What is that?
Those are veils of light.
They form when the Swirling Galaxy comes undone.
You need to practice the flute more often.
Practice... Amy... Practiced dance?
I want to see... Amy's dance.
Okay, then as thanks for before...
Thanks...
Here, I brought you a present!
Welcome home, Sis.
Hi there.
Doctor, welcome. I'm home! How have you been?
Ledo!
Present...
Thank you, Ledo.
Get money, give money,
everyone eats good food.
The pay you received shows
that you supported someone.
I supported someone?
That is... work...
I was invited to work.
What is it?!
Salvage work with Chamber.
Lucky!
It is good?
Well, yeah, I mean, all kinds of things
are lying at the bottom of the sea, right?
You can find out what was on
this planet a long time ago!
I want to do salvage.
It really helps having you here.
I was convinced you'd go with Pinion.
I want you to teach me something, Bellows.
Although as long as that Yunboro's around,
you'll probably quickly forget anything I teach you.
Not true. I want to learn many things.
Alright. We hit the jackpot
with this one, too.
It's treasure. So be gentle with it.
Sign of the enemy confirmed. Interceptor.
Confirm it again!
Characteristic response analysis
complete. Probability: 99.7%.
Subject identified as Hideauze.
Begin engagement. Annihilate the Hideauze.
Roger.