Rule the Court
Aoba Johsai High School Volleyball Club
What? Again?
That's his fourth aced serve in a row.
Aoba Johsai                            Omisaki
His power goes without saying,
but that control is pretty nasty, too.
But if they can do something
about that serve...
It's true that his serves are scary,
but Oikawa, as a setter,
is completely unknown to us.
One more! Nice serve!
Sorry!
Chance ball!
Got it!
Okay.
You know, setters...
are like orchestra conductors.
Even if you have the same
song and same orchestra,
if the conductor is different,
the sound is different.
Haikyu!!
Episode 19: Conductors
Rule the Court
Aoba Johsai High School Volleyball Club
How do I put this...
They've got a very smooth transition.
Oikawa-san and Iwaizumi-san,
that #4 on the left.
Apparently those two have been on
the same team since grade school.
They're linked, both mentally and physically.
I don't really think the second-year setter's
level was lower in the practice match.
I mean, they're in Seijoh.
Right.
I think it's just that
Oikawa knows everything
there is to know about Seijoh's team,
Oikawa, one more!
Nice serve!
and is helping them bring out their A-game.
The Great King is so awesome!
I want to hurry up and play him!
Yeah! I hope he aims his serves at me!
I totally want to get them!
Noya-san's awesome, too!
Well, isn't that promising...
Hey, look, Shoyo!
A TV crew's here!
TV?! Awesome! I wanna be on TV, too!
Hey, now...
You two junior high—
Maybe you're grade school kids?
Quiet down a little.
Grade...
Sorry...
Aoba Johsai                            Omisaki
It's so quiet.
Everyone's out cold.
Well, they did play two matches.
Plus they won both straight-set wins,
so that's not bad.
If they keep winning starting tomorrow,
not only will they have two matches a day,
but their opponents
will continue to get stronger.
We'll have to bolster
their morale every time.
Right.
All right, we're going to have a meeting.
Takeda-sensei!
The volleyball club is on TV!
TV?!
Please excuse us!
Faculty Room
National High School Volleyball
Miyagi Prefecture Preliminaries
Now, then...
The first and second matches of the
Miyagi Prefecture Preliminaries for
Oh!
It's really on!
TV!
It's just the local news.
the Inter-High School National Sporting
Competition Volleyball Tournament
Shut up!
were held, and heated matches ensued.
TV is TV!
Shiratorizawa Academy
vs. Oginnami High School
First, in the I Block,
we have the ace player, Ushijima Wakatoshi-kun,
leading the reigning champions at
Shiratorizawa Academy in their first game.
They played against Oginnami High School,
winning 25 to 10 in their first set,
Inter-High School National Sporting Competition Volleyball Tournament
Miyagi Prefecture Preliminaries I Block
Shiratorizawa Academy
vs. Oginnami High School
and 25 to 6 in their second set,
not giving their opponents the
slightest chance against them.
They showed everyone why
they're the reigning champions.
25 to 6?
Will they be able to make it
to nationals once again
or will a team appear that can stop them?
It'll be worth seeing.
Inter-High School National Volleyball Tournament
Prefectural Preliminaries A Block
Next, the A Block is also drawing interest.
That's the gym we played at today!
Inter-High School National Volleyball Tournament
Prefectural Preliminaries A Block
A player you should definitely watch out
for is Aoba Johsai High School's
team captain, Oikawa Toru-kun.
His dashing good looks draw in female fans,
so he's a player with both skill
and popularity to spare.
Oikawa-san! So cute!
Inter-High School National Volleyball Tournament
Prefectural Preliminaries A Block
Tomorrow, going up against Aoba Johsai
is a team that sped to an unbelievable
straight-set victory against Date Tech
—who were expected to place
in the tournament's top eight—
the powerhouse, Karasuno High School.
We're gonna be on!
We asked him what he thought about
his opponent, Karasuno High School,
who he'll be facing in the third match.
Q: What do you think of your opponents for the third match?
They're a great team.
I hope...
...they go for broke.
There'll definitely be more
heated matches tomorrow.
We wish them the best.
Next is the weather.
We have Komata-san reporting
from Sendai Station.
Hello, Komata here.
Th-There was a glimpse of your
match at the very beginning!
You all looked very cool!
Sensei, thank you.
Oh, it was nothing...
All right. Well, then...
Let's do this.
Do what?!
A m-meeting!
Today's match against Date Tech
is what you call "the first sip of beer."
The deliciousness of the
first sip of beer is special,
and you only
get it in that first sip.
Ukai-kun, we should phrase that
differenty for the minors here.
Ahem.
Well, the match with Date Tech
was the first time
we used the freak quick against them.
Therefore, we were able to
catch out opponents off guard.
But we've fought Seijoh once in the past,
so they know at least some of our tricks.
Still, I'm certain that your offense
is stronger than theirs.
First, we need to endure Oikawa's serves.
His serves controlling the game's pace
is what we want the least,
but that's most likely that will happen.
So, for right now, we have the basic
"everyone who's not the setter goes after
the ball" formation to receive serves.
(Net)
Hinata or Tsukishima
However, this time, we won't have the
middle blocker, Hinata or Tsukishima,
participate in receiving the serve.
They'll concentrate solely on attacking.
'Kay.
Okay.
Hey, don't get so bummed out.
We're just dividing up the work.
Oh, also, you guys saw Seijoh and thought,
"Oh, crap. They're strong," right?
But...
If you were seeing our match against Date Tech
from the stands, you'd hesitate, saying,
"What's with that blocking?
Talk about scary. We can't win," right?
But you fought them,
and you won.
Tomorrow will be the same.
All right!
All right. Let's clarify the formation a bit.
Right!
Ukai-san.
Oh, Mori.
This is today's match.
Seijoh vs Omisaki
Sweet. Thanks.
Thanks.
This helps out a lot.
The next round's on me.
All right! Yeah!
See ya.
Is that the Aoba Johsai match?
Yeah.
Well, it's not like watching
this will guarantee
Seijoh vs
Omisaki
we'll be able to receive
Oikawa's serves tomorrow.
But I'd feel pretty anxious
if I wasn't doing anything.
The next round's on me, Ukai-kun.
Seriously?!
All right. Make sure
you're not late tomorrow.
Right!
I want to take my dear underclassman
on in an official match,
setter versus setter, and crush him.
Kageyama seems more irritated than usual.
Oh, there he goes.
Kageyama!
You're going to end up with
permanent forehead wrinkles,
even though you're just a teen!
What?!
Tomorrow, we're going to
defeat the Great King....
Defeat... Oikawa-san...
...and end up on TV, so you should
practice looking good for that!
Mind your own business!
We'll win that match.
If we don't, we can't advance.
All right!
I'll be going, now.
'Kay. Bye-bye!
Karasuno
vs. Date Tech
Hey, make sure you don't stay up all night.
Iwa-chan, are you my mom?
What?
Sorry, sorry, sorry!
I promise I won't!
I promise I'll arrive in top condition!
Stop being stupid, Crappy Oikawa.
I'm shutting the club room doors,
so get out of here, Trashykawa.
Don't shorten the insults!
Trashy Oikawa!
You don't have to rephrase it!
Is it possible that this player...
Go, go, go! Go, go, Seijoh!
Push it, push it, push it!
Push it, push it, Seijoh!
Let's play.
Fly
Looks like Karasuno made it
safely through to day two.
I ended up using another paid day off.
I'm not gonna be able to take
another day off for a while.
Same here.
Rule the Court
Date Tech had quite the crowd
cheering for them, too,
but these guys...
Ready, and...
Oikawa-kun! Do your best!
They've got that.
Ain't no way I'm gonna lose! Let's go!
Yeah!
Come on, louder! It's like Seijoh's
the only team on the court!
We're going to be serving first.
Right.
Right!
Ready, and...
Oikawa-senpai! Do your best—
Karasuno!
Fight!
Yeah!
Next, we'll do serves!
They sure are pumped up.
Right!
By the way, did your student
get better at serves?
What do you mean, "student"?
Will you teach me how to do
a jump float serve?
It's only been a week since then.
Here I go!
He may be able to get some lucky hits in,
but he can't really control it yet.
Nice, Makki. Super sharp.
Sorry, Kindaichi.
That one was a little high.
Uh, no... Yes!
Iwa-chan, you sure you're
not trying too hard?
You don't have to try and show off.
None of the girls will
be looking at you, anyway.
Oikawa-kun is apparently watching
the other players very closely.
I-Iwasaki-san! Calm down!
We're right before a match!
Let go of me, Kindachi!
I don't understand all of
the technical stuff yet,
Now's not a good time! See?
Everyone's staring hard!
but I can see that the team
seems to be in good shape.
I don't care. I'm gonna hit him.
Hey! What are you saying?!
Iwaizumi-san, calm down!
You think so?
Aoba Johsai                          Karasuno
Line up!
Best Setter Award
Oikawa Toru
Certain Victory
Kitagawa Daiichi Junior High School Volleyball Club
I'm going up against him in an
official match for the first time.
Let's play!
Hey, it's starting.
The third match, huh?
If they win, they'll be in the top eight!
I wonder who'll win.
It's definitely going to be Aoba Johsai.
Hey, Tobio-chan.
I came here excited to take
down the genius setter,
so do your best, and hold on.
We will win—
We won't lose!
Don't butt in when I'm talking,
Hinata, you jackass!
We won't...
...lose this time, either!
Go, go, go! Go, go, Seijoh!
Rule the Court
Aoba Johsai High School Volleyball Club
Go, go, go! Go, go, Seijoh!
Push it, push it, push it!
Push it, push it, Seijoh!
All of you
Push it, push it, push it!
Push it, push it, Seijoh!
have already defeated Aoba Johsai once.
Even if our opponents were not
at their best at the time,
I believe the fact that we won
is enough reason to have confidence.
Not conceit, but confidence.
Right!
Karasuno... Fight!
Yeah!
All right. Let's do this.
Now then, as usual...
I believe in all of you.
I think...
...the atmosphere around Aoba Johsai
just changed suddenly.
The one line he always says before a match...
When he says it,
it almost sounds like a joke,
and yet it almost sounds like a threat.
However, because everyone knows that,
there is no underlying
meaning behind those words.
They can all trust in him to the utmost.
Let's go!
Yeah!
Tsukishima, nice serve!
Kunimi!
Right!
Nice recieve!
Two of the guys in the front line jumped out!
Who will they use?
All right.
It's been a while since I've seen
Oikawa-san's set up so close.
I...
It was a setter dump!
Rule the Court
Aoba Johsai High School Volleyball Club
Go, go, Toru! Push it,
push it, Toru! One more!
Damn it!
Well, well...
That was a rather bold dump...
Come on. I'll be doing the same thing again.
Don't stand there so out of it.
Pay attention.
H-He said he'd do that again,
but is he telling the truth?
I guess someone wouldn't
usually do that again...
Then again, he could realize
we'd think that and do it again.
I see! Tanaka-san, you're amazing!
Hey, now. There's no point
in dwelling on that.
It's the same as trying to
figure out what your opponent
will throw out in rock-paper-scissors.
Aoba Johsai                             Karasuno
Don't overthink it.
Right!
Nice serve, Matsukawa!
All right!
Daichi-san, nice recieve!
B!
Come to me!
Hey, it's #10.
Is it coming?
There it is! It's so fast!
It's dead-on!
Hey, is the Seijoh setter
going to try a dump again?
He's being even more obvious this time!
Don't underestimate me!
He went from a spike formation straight into
a set?
Rule the Court
Aoba Johsai High School Volleyball Club
Hey, that was a little low.
Really? Sorry about that.
But Iwa-chan,
you usually hit it regardless.
Wow...
That's slightly infuriating, but wow...
So cool!
Oikawa-senpai!
Well, he's an even more troublesome
opponent than I thought...
Indeed.
It's true that we won the
practice match the other day,
but now that this team has
their conductor to lead them,
they're something else entirely.
Damn it...
Hey, hey, hey...
You knew that Oikawa was
amazing to begin with.
Our setter is just as skilled,
and his attacks
are just as flashy.
Right!
Matsukawa, one more nice serve!
Nishinoya!
Right!
Bring it!
Number 5?!
Or so they think...
Pipe?!
H...
He got them back with a dump!
He sure hates losing, doesn't he?
Do it again!
I'll...
...be doing the same thing again.
Pay attention!
You...
...stupid little brat.
Next Episode Preview
You're really not cute at all, Tobio.
It's not very different than
the first dump you did on them.
But everyone's got my back... V!
You are so infuriating.
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"Oikawa Toru is not a Genius."
Episode 20: Oikawa Toru is not a Genius