Damn it.
I'm serious about it.
Will you marry me? I will make you happy!
Please, please, pretty please.
No marriage!
Well then, pretend
we're married just for tonight!
Please, would you please?
I can't hold it in!
Come on, straight to business?
Right, right, no more waiting!
If I wait any longer, I'll go crazy.
Come on.
What?
Why the hell does she always bother me
when I'm about to have a good time?
What's wrong?
Repair parts for a
motor bike, for God's sake!
Don't touch that! Do you want to blow yourself up?
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, Junkshop.
You miscounted again!
All the time with you.
I got everything you requested.
Thanks!
These are almost as good as new.
Full power with this L-type.
Half if you go with S-type.
Yes, my Handy Man! Excellent!
How much are they?
L-type is 1,000 and S-type is 500.
Is it legal for machines to sell machines?
Can you make it 700?
No discount whatsoever!
How about 800?
Absolutely not, idiot.
Well then, 900?
Are you messing with me?
What then how about 950?
I'll kill you!
Okay, you win. I get it. Geez.
I'll take the S-type. Here, 500.
What a cold-blooded business man you are!
It's a deal. Take it.
What's the matter?
I forgot one thing. My client's
machine can only take the L-type.
You idiot!
I'll take the L-type.
It's 1000.
I know, but...
I have this 500 part in my hand.
And with the 500 cash I put on the
table, that makes 1,000 together.
Right?
Together? 1,000?
All right.
Okay! It's a deal! I'll take this!
Wait a sec. I don't know what's going on,
but something's not right.
You conned me!
Conned? That's not a nice way to say it, old man.
Oh, you're not a man.
What have you done?
I told you.
You should have agreed with
500 in the first place.
To be honest,
I'm not your errand boy.
Do you know that?
You can only be turned on
by machine girls, right?
You idiot, who told you that?
I'll hook you up with a hot
machine girl, so get to work.
You hook me up with a
machine girl, huh?
It better be fixed properly.
As good as my fee's worth.
This thing's practically a zombie.
Honestly,
you drive like a maniac.
Whoops, there goes your license!
Hey hey, don't you think
it's time to get a new one?
You can have it cheap!
There is a good one sitting right there
in my factory. Want to come and see?
Looks good!
Right?
Well then,
the deal was that you hook me up once I fixed it.
So where's this machine girl from?
Is she at your home?
Let me guess, you shot her dead
before I had a shot at her heart?
Just kidding!
No worries, I would
fix her if you did.
And then I could have her live at my factory.
Eventually she and I would
get married.
No, I have to check if our bodies fit
well before marrying her and... what?
See you!
Hey, wait!
Weren't you going to hook me up? Hey!
This isn't supposed to be here.
Did I forget to install it?
Whatever, she'll be fine.
Am I in trouble?
You're my only hope, darling!
I'm sorry.
I'm going to get you your parts. Wait here.
I'm here for parts.
Clearly, my body is becoming faster.
My body has started to change.
I feel so good.
Sis...
Touka wants to play too. I want to destroy them!
No.
No fair! Why do you get to?
Touka has her own will now?
Why?
No fair!
You can't take all the fun for yourself.
Lie to me, and I won't forgive you either.
I'm going to play how I want to now,
even when I don't have your command.
Okay, Sis?