It wasn't supposed to be
like this, head in my hands
Struggling to escape from
this saturated world
Time passes like whispering sand
These circumstances, unchanging
gazing out at a dreamless tomorrow
Wanna say goodbye to the
confusion of yesterday
I try reaching out, as if to resist
We cry millions of times
and then get born again
Let's go with these red eyes
to that pictured future
Come here right by me,
I'm clapping my hands
Where are you? Who are you?
Strain my eyes in the darkness
Can't see anything, don't know
anything, but I'll still go
To the place of shining
light in which you wait
Episode Seven
Daydream
Inspired by Ango Sakaguchi's
Meijikaika Ango Torimonochou
(Meiji-era Detective Stories)
"Foolish Apparition" and "The Retard"
There's no fooling the
Defeated Detective...
Or maybe I'd better call
you the "Great Detective".
Calls Himself a Novelist
Prisoner
Why did you do this?
I'm a novelist.
A novelist?
Yuuki Shinjurou
Detective
I write novels.
Not with a pen, but in reality...
Due to the Great Detective's deductions,
all of the mysteries were to be revealed
and Yajima was supposed
to kill his own wife.
And what did you try to set that up for?
Because that's the role
of the Great Detective.
No matter how cruel the
end result will be,
after all of the victims
have been murdered,
the Great Detective wraps everything
up with his brilliant deduction.
No matter how tragic the reason,
the Great Detective exposes
it all to the light of day.
You were chosen by me...
...to be this world's
last great detective!
You chose me?
Yes. You're my own
personal great detective.
What do you want?!
You don't need to worry. I'm a novelist.
The only thing I know how
to do is write stories.
Except I don't write
on manuscript paper...
...but in this reality.
If reality becomes a novel...
Now go, Great Detective.
Unravel the mystery...
Somebody!
The war...?
Okay, we got it!
Yuuki-chan, what are you doing?
Shouldn't you be over there?
Over there...?
Yuuki-san, the director's
calling for you.
What, were you slacking off again?!
Izawa Sayo
Actress?
When you have an actress come to
fetch you, you must be a big shot!
Sorry! I'll be right there!
Shinjurou-kun, we're waiting on you!
This guy was by the planes...
I called it!
What do you mean, "It
figures", Motoko-chan?
All men love special effects!
Even my dad...
Yada Sumie
Actress?
Tanimura Motoko
Dad?
What's wrong, Motoko-chan?
Nothing.
And stop adding "-chan".
I'm not a little girl!
Mitaka Kichitarou
Movie Director?
What are you doing over there?!
Uh-oh. Okay, should we get started?
Is your makeup all right?
I don't need any.
If I'm not cute, you're not good
at your job, Shinjurou-kun.
I'm ready.
Please make me look pretty.
Director, are we ready?
As always, zero enthusiasm.
Then I'll just start shooting.
Sayo-san, you must have
a boyfriend, right?
But Sumie-san, you're more naive.
I bet you've never had a man!
W-Where is this coming from
all of a sudden, Motoko-chan?!
I told you not to use "chan"!
Anyway, I want to know
more about you two!
We all escaped to here
from different places.
We were taken in by the owner of
this room and just settled here.
That man treated us equally, l... l...
Loving us?
Right, that!
But one day, he disappeared...
...and now we just loiter
in this burning town.
But I hear the director hasn't
decided on the last scene!
Who knows if we can be
reunited with the man...
I hope the four of us can live
happily together again...
That's not what I want!
I want him to choose one of
us from the three, like me!
Oh!
W-What are you laughing at?!
Oh, come on!
They really do look happy...
Right, Director?
Solve the mystery...
Mystery...?
It hurts... It hurts!
It's hot... Red...
I'm... hot...
We're gonna die... We're all gonna die!
Okay, got it!
But why do I have to
"solve the mystery"...
when a crime or whatever
hasn't even happened...
If a war really did happen, I don't
think there would be any escaping it.
You're probably right...
Why?
After all, I've never even imagined it.
I wouldn't know what to do if I looked
out the window and saw a bomb dropping.
Yeah... The last war was before
my grandpa's time, even.
A war isn't happening.
No one is losing their loved ones.
Houses aren't burning down.
No one is grieving...
But that's why we can make
a movie about it, right?
Actually, can we do a retake?
Why?
Because Sayo-san showed me up!
I can do better than that!
Director, I have a favor...
Yuuki Shinjurou...
Why are you standing around chatting?!
Director, can we do it one more time?
You know that I'm the
director, don't you?
Don't you dare bother me!
Director, I...
If we can do it for them...
Don't talk to them.
Got it?! I'll kill you.
Good job, everyone.
Good job.
Where am I...?
That's right. I need to
talk to the director.
This movie has a mystery.
Something isn't right...
You understand, don't
you? You're Papillon!
I don't understand!
Wait!
No! Don't let go!
Please! Don't let go!
Let go of me!
Please! Just do what I say!
Tomorrow, right here, got it?!
What are you doing, Yuuki?!
Get back to the room!
What were you doing, Director?
None of your business!
I've been entrusted with a movie camera.
For days now, I've been
on location for a movie.
The silly premise is that modern-day
Japan has become embroiled in a war.
Was the director with
one of the actresses?
There's a mystery here.
The mystery will be solved.
The truth must be revealed...
There was... no war...
JJ... Systems...
Mamori
"Mamori"... "Kaze"?
Kaze
Shinjurou-sama!
Director...
What?
About last night...
Mr. Mitaka?
Rosenberg and Schaffner, this way.
Okay.
The Works of Director Frank Darabont
Is this a mystery too?
Each is responding
completely differently...
Is this what the director wants?
Sure is hot!
I found shade!
Yuuki Shinjurou, are you
looking at women again?
Uh, you mean the actresses?
Tanimura, Yada are
there... and Izawa, too?
Yes...
What's wrong?
Yuuki-san! Actually, we wanted to ask
the director something about the script...
So we said to him, "We know
the script isn't finished,
but are we going somewhere?"
And he said, "You can't go
anywhere. You're criminals."
Is that what you think
too, Shinjurou-kun?
We don't know who we are
or where we've come from,
and we can't even go anywhere!
There is this line...
War is a toy, isn't it?
And it isn't just me.
It's you, too. And you!
We've all made war into a toy!
We should've sucked off war more.
We should've wrapped our legs around
war and ridden it until it was worn out.
Sucked it more, get more
tangled up with it...
Those are the lines we say when
we hear that the war's over.
So, what about it?
We all have different interpretations
of what it means.
Um, I'm thinking it means we're
happy that the war is over,
so now we can get back
to our normal lives...
But it made me so curious that I wanted
to ask the director what it means...
You're totally wrong.
"Normal lives" has no meaning.
I think it's more like there's a
war and we're just running around,
but meanwhile maybe we finally
realize that we're alive?
We've become just like beasts
who only think of survival...
But there's still the one who's
precious to us, whom we l-l...
Love.
Yes, that!
I can understand it, like...
It's that feeling, like you want
to try living on the edge...
Where you get sick of the tedious
days that never change...
I guess my take on it
is a little different.
I think it means that we're all going
to be put on trial by the war...
Put on trial?
Good people, bad people, they
all die the same, right?
Maybe that's what he meant when
he said we were "criminals".
You're all over thinking it.
This is a movie.
What are you saying, Shinjurou-kun?!
If you're right, then why bother
making a movie like this?
In the middle of this nonexistent
war, what are we running for?
We're running because
of our everyday lives...
Because we've realized how
precious those ordinary,
run-of-the-mill days are to us...
That's not it!
Everyone is secretly wishing for it...
Maybe not for a war, but for
something big to happen...
Something that will
change what we are now.
Something that'll let us
find what's really precious!
But think of people who lose their family
or home in a volcanic eruption or fire...
They wish they could have their
everyday life back, right?
But there are people who go to
a volcano or fire just to watch.
Even though we know just
how sad it would be,
we have this desire to mess up
the world... and ourselves...
So I think it means that
has to be put on trial...
I see... The mystery that is a movie...
Shinjurou-san?
You have been listening, right?
Which one of us do you think is right?
If you want, I'll ask the director
about the ending and try writing it myself.
Maybe you'll find some
kind of answer that way.
Really?!
Yeah.
Come on, lunch break's over!
Right!
But Motoko, this is..
There you go.
Thank you!
That's what he said!
Even if that was one of the three...
...they're embracing life.
They're betting on the movie.
Director! What's this about?!
You intend to ruin the whole thing?!
What have you got there?!
What the hell is this?
Hey, what's wrong?
The director is...
It looks like he was run
over by the streetcar.
That's just part of the set.
The streetcar's a fake.
It doesn't even run.
It seems no one saw Mr.
Mitaka after lunch...
Then I'm the last one who talked to him?
But why was he killed?!
Only one person has a motive.
The person who was angry at Director
Mitaka, who was going to wreck the movie
and all the hard work
these women put into it...
Me.
Yuuki-san...?
Did I...?
What are you dreaming about?!
It's all made-up! A lie!
No, it isn't!
Yuuki-san, stop it! Okay?
It won't stop!
Somebody's telling me
to solve the mystery!
If I gather clues and
deduce the answer...
I'm the only possible culprit...
That's a confession, right?
Kaishou Rie
Metropolitan Police Detective?
Have we met somewhere before?
I'm Kaishou, with the
Metro Police Department.
You're under arrest for the murder
of movie director Mitaka Kichitarou!
In the pale morning
mist, a whispered prayer
I'm gonna follow this
twisted landscape with you
Looking for the "truth",
"a 'lie' will do" is it?
Tracing it as if we can see through
Looking for, beyond words
Like a falling feather
Looking for, find it
So we can cuddle close together here
Looking for, unravel it
Like a tattered cloud
Looking for, find it
So we can cuddle close together here
I'm telling you to let me
see Shinjurou! All right?!
Inga
Detective's Assistant
What should we do, Kazamori?
I smell her here...
Hayami Seigen
Director of the Security Bureau
Metropolitan Police Dept.
Hey, that's all the screen
time I get?! What's the idea?!
Do you know what'll happen
if you make me angry?!
Look, part of the next episode was
inspired by "The Election Murder Case",
and if you read the story first,
it gives you all kinds of spoilers!
Should I spill? Should I talk?
Should I give the game away here?!
Okay, actually...
Ah, K-K-Kazamori!
Stop! O-Okay! I won't do it!
Next time on UN-GO:
"The King of Paradise".
S-Stop it, Kazamori!!