Unbeijini nyopurasara,
I'm going to put a spell on you...
Unbeijini nyopurakura,
I'm going to—
What is that?
It's a magic song.
Ishigata-san taught it to me.
He says it cheers you up if you
sing it when you're lonely or hurting.
Chiyoko, want to play?
Okay!
Here I go!
Bring it on.
S-Sorry.
I'll go get it.
Jeez.
Huh?
Hey, Guriko,
let's run away from here.
What are you saying, Pine?
You know we can't do that!
There's an electrified fence all around the lab,
and besides—
So you're okay with how things are, then?!
Trapped here for your whole life?!
F-Fine.
Then let's talk to Ishigata-san.
I'm sure he'd...
Punch Line
Gliese-sama is an alien from
the planet Gliese 832C.
Rabura, are you sane?
Huh?
Possessed by the Stripes
I'm perfectly sane.
So, this Gliese person is coming to your room.
Have you ever met him?
I've seen pictures.
So anyway, can you hold on to this for me?
Huh?
He might think I'm a weirdo if
I have this doll in my room.
Okay, thanks!
Ah, wait—
And what the heck is this, anyway?
Early this morning,
a young woman was found
Shouro Meiko-san (17)
High school student falls from apartment building
collapsed and bleeding at
her apartment premises.
She was soon confirmed dead.
The deceased was identified
as Shouro Meiko-san,
a local high school student.
Shouro Meiko?
Koto Monami (17)
Shouro Meiko (17)
Io Ruka (17)
Hikiotani Ito (17)
Wasn't she in that video?
What was that?
It's a list of all the people they're going to kill.
A notice of premeditated crime.
That means Ito's in danger!
Ito doesn't seem to know about this yet.
We have to tell her, then!
But how?
The quickest way would be
to possess someone's body.
Whoa, wait a second.
I never heard anything about possessing people!
Because I never told you.
You can't possess someone until
you reach a certain level.
Also, there are a few rules
for possessing people.
Just watch this.
What the hell is this?
You don't know?
It's Ba-dum! Girls Everywhere Swim Meet.
And?
Ahem.
Now, I'll explain.
Possession rule number one!
If the owner of the body is lucid
while they are being possessed,
the possessor must have high spirit
power in order to possess them.
So I just need to use cinnamon
to increase my spirit power?
Possession rule number two!
Fundamentally, it's only possible
to possess someone with
a similar spiritual wavelength.
Provided, however, that the owner of
the body has spirit medium potential.
Spirit medium potential?
Does that mean...
Go scatter some cinnamon,
and possess Rabura's body!
Meika, about this email
from that Gliese person...
Huh? What're they doing?
Oh, I got that email, too.
What do we do about this?
We'll just have to ask him directly.
Hm? Well, anyway...
Where's the cinnamon?
Is it in here?
Found it.
Now to figure out how to bring Rabura here.
All right, got it.
Let's go to Rabura's place, then.
Yeah.
Man, that guy sure is thorough.
Seriously. I wouldn't be so
roundabout if I were him.
Now's my chance!
Rabura...
Wh-What's with that outfit?
Shut up, I'm busy right now. Save it for later.
Good evening-ning!
Now!
Shit!
What the heck are you doing?
No, no, I didn't do anything.
Close one.
Damn it, I have to possess her fast.
Forget the excuses. Here.
No, no, I didn't—
Okay, here goes!
Hey, what happened?!
Did it work?
"Work"?
Ito, listen to me!
You're in trouble!
Huh?
It's seriously bad!
What is?
What is?! I'm saying...
Um, Rabura-san, you're acting a little weird.
Huh?
The way you're talking.
You sound different than usual.
Damn, they won't believe me
no matter how I explain it.
In that case...
Oh me, oh my!
A-Are you okay?
Not to worry.
More importantly, there's
something I have to tell you.
See—
Wait up!
First, I want to ask you something.
What now?
Well, I was wondering,
what's your favorite flower?
Why now?
My favorite flower... My favorite flower, huh?
Uh, Rafflesia.
Here! I have a question, too!
Jeez, what now?
What's your favorite song?
My favorite song?
Well...
That song about "your buns," or whatever.
The She's Mei one?
Yeah.
I'm so happy!
You listen to our music!
The last question's from me.
There's more?
What snacks do you like with your beer?
Snacks?
Turtle Feed
Turtle feed.
Turtle feed?
You're done now, right?
It's my turn now.
Okay, listen carefully.
It's about Ito.
Me?
Huh? Again?
What's wrong with you?! Jeez.
Hey, Rabura.
Bewitching Spirit Wave
Damn it, why?
Oh, right, you can only possess
someone for up to seven minutes!
Why didn't you say so?!
That's a unique dress.
It looks great on you.
My, you flatterer.
Well, then, a toast to our meeting.
Cheers.
Oh, I'll go find some snacks.
No need to worry about that.
Wh-What is this?
I believe you'll know once you try it.
I will, then.
What do you think?
I-It tastes rather different...
Different?
Oh, maybe because they just
recently revamped the product.
Turtle Feed
Are you all right?
How could I be—
O-Of course I am!
I think my body was in shock
from how delicious it was.
I'm glad.
Please, have some more.
Oh, no, I'm full now!
I see.
Um, why don't I turn on some music?
Then please, play this.
"I Want to See Your Buns"?
You can have it.
Oh, but I have this already.
Ah, I should have known.
Of course you would.
It's your favorite song, after all.
No, I wouldn't exactly say that...
It is! It's my favorite!
I listen to it so much, I've worn out the disc.
Thank goodness I have another one now!
I have one more very special present for you.
What is it?
One moment.
Wh-What is this?
A rafflesia.
You must know.
Is something wrong?
No, it just has a very... unique scent.
Yes, it's the scent of a dead animal.
Rafflesia attract flies with this scent
so they can spread their pollen.
I-I see. Flies...
Did you not like it?
Enough already!
I can't take it anymore!
You're mocking me, aren't you?!
No, that's not my intent.
Then what is your intent?
I just wanted to make you happy, Rabura-san.
What the...
With this flower?!
With turtle feed?!
Very well.
I'll tell you the truth.
I gave those answers?
At least, that's what it said in
the emails your friends sent.
You must have been set up.
That does bring something to mind, though.
Hm?
I seem to have had a similar
experience when I was little.
I was about five at the time,
so I don't remember too well...
24 Years Ago...
I woke up in the middle of the
night, and did strange things.
Writing down diagrams and equations,
and instructions on what
to do on certain dates.
And I was sending them to someone by fax.
So you think what happened here
was another sleepwalking incident?
Anyway, I apologize for earlier.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm the one who should apologize.
Let's start over, then.
Wait, please.
Rabura-san, I can't stand to lie
to you any more than I have.
I'll tell you the truth.
It's all right, I already know.
You aren't an alien, right?
Yes, exactly.
It's true that I didn't come from space.
I'm from the U.S. Department of
Defense's intelligence bureau,
the National Security Agency.
What the heck just happened?
I trust that you know about the
Qmay Group hostage incident.
Yes, I do.
And their announcement?
Something about an asteroid hitting
Earth on New Year's Eve or something.
But the government and other
experts said that's impossible.
No, unless Operation Intercept is
carried out, it will collide with Earth.
What?
The United States has secretly
launched a military satellite into orbit,
equipped with several dozen nuclear missiles.
The satellite is under the command of the
Air Force Space Command, also known as AFSPC.
The goal of Operation Intercept
is to use these missiles
to destroy the incoming asteroid.
But the Qmay Group uploaded
a virus to the AFSPC servers
and has taken over the entire system.
The Qmay Group did?
Unless something is done, the AFSPC
missiles will not be launched.
Their true objective has always been
the annihilation of the human race.
What's going on?
Didn't the Qmay Group cause
that incident to tell people
that the asteroid was coming?
But why are you telling me this?
The Qmay Group virus is very sophisticated.
An ordinary person could not remove it.
But there is someone with genius
hacking skills who could do it.
You mean...
Daihatsu Meika-san.
There is no one else on Earth
who could remove the virus.
Thus, we've attempted to establish
contact with her many times,
but—
I see. So that's what this is.
You tried to use me.
You thought you could get to
Meika by getting close to me!
Is that right?!
Rabura-san, please don't misunderstand.
It's true that I was attracted to you—
Don't lie to me!
You wanted to make me happy, my ass!
Don't give me that crap!
He certainly is full of it.
Wh-Who are you?
I have a little something to say to you.
To me?
Is there atmosphere in space?
Lose Not to Rain
I'd love to hear your thoughts on that matter.
You're not getting away!
Special attack, Clam Bomber!
What do you think you're
doing to my Gliese-sama?!
Are you all right?
Please, get away while you can!
But—
He's really powerful when he wants to be.
So please, hurry!
I understand.
I'll repay this debt, I promise.
Damn it, stop!
You pig!
Pig!
Rabura!
What the hell are you doing?!
What was that for?!
This is Miya-Ken! We can trust him!
Meika...
Now go. You need to chase
him down, don't you?
Thanks, I owe you.
Wh-What? Wanna fight?
I was hoping you'd ask.
Meika!
Rabura!
Stop, you two!
What are you doing?
Th-This is totally Ba-dum!
Girls Everywhere Swim Meet!
I want to see your buns
Take this!
Don't!
Those plump, white buns
And this!
A peek at your buns
Damn you!
Don't look, don't look!
Takes me higher than Burj Khalifa
Come on!
Why did you get into a fight?
Meika was defending that guy.
Miya-Ken, was it?
What's with that nickname?
Why are you so mad?
You're a robot. You wouldn't
understand how people feel.
Come on, Rabura-san.
What, did it not work out with that old dude?
You stop it, too, Meika.
Let's all get along, okay?
Don't you agree, Muhi?
Bare Legs
Could it be that he's the
actual cause of all this?
Because you brought that thing home.
I didn't just bring him home.
He was given to me.
From Rabura's little brother, Rando-oniichan.
Wh-Why are you bringing that up?
He came to my room all of
a sudden about a month ago.
He said he wanted me to take
care of this cub for a while.
Jeez...
This kid can be such a pathological liar.
Pathological liar?
Who are you calling a liar?
Spirit mediums are all full of shit.
You're so wimpy, you can't even
go to school. You're one to talk!
Fraud.
Come on, stop it already!
What's gotten into you guys?!
You were such good friends until yesterday!
Rabura-san...
Sorry. I can't put up with you.
I have to think some things over.
It's about a guy, isn't it?
I wish I were as carefree as you.
What happens to humanity doesn't
mean a thing to you, after all.
Huh?
What the hell is she on about?
I don't care anymore.
I'm going home, too.
Ito-chan, please forgive her.
Rabura-san and Meika both really—
What are you playing the nice girl for?
Are you trying to be a hero?
You make me laugh.
I-Ito-chan...
Why?
Don't make me spell it out!
You're a hero, aren't you?!
Ito-chan...
Hey, what's wrong?
Unbeijini nyopurasara...
I'm going to put a spell on you...
Narugino, you're...
No...
This isn't happening...
Ito.
Ito!
Next Time: Punch Line Episode 5
Ito Dies