It's getting lonelier and lonelier.
Does she really live in a place like this?
The lesser spirits said they saw someone who
looked like Felt coming in this direction...
Hey, bro!
Does a girl named Felt live up this way?
Huh? Felt?
Nothing that way but
Old Man Rom's loot house.
Did Felt steal something from you guys?
Well, go try and negotiate to get it back.
Live strong.
Why do I have to pay money to get
back something stolen from me?
Well, at any rate, leave this one to me.
I'll negotiate with him.
Okay. I'll leave it to you.
You agreed to that awfully easily...
The way you've been acting,
I thought you'd say,
"Leave this to a useless boy like you?
That's so ridiculous,
I'm laughing my head off!"
And I'd be hurt, but still make up
my mind to help you all over again.
I wouldn't say something that mean.
Of course, I'd be lying if I said
you haven't been holding me back...
It'd be a lie?!
But...
I'll try believing in you.
If it actually goes well,
I'll consider it a bonus.
If you'd look up at me and say,
"Do your best for me!"
I'd feel a lot more motivated.
I can't force myself to
say something like that.
But... do your best.
Yeah. I will.
I'll go in first. You stay
outside and keep watch.
I won't be back too late,
but you can have dinner without me.
Don't say dumb things like that.
Be careful.
Sure, sure.
Don't come in until I
say it's okay, Satella.
What?
N-Nothing. Never mind.
If you can get my insignia
back, I'll apologize.
Excuse me...
Now, am I walking into a
demon nest or a snake pit?
In a fantasy world,
either one is totally plausible...
This is all stolen loot?
And why isn't there anyone here?
A place that handles stolen goods
can only afford to be so careless.
Oh, dear, you found that?
Well, I have no choice, then.
Yes, I have no choice...
Ow, that burns...
Oh, crap... Is all of this my blood?
This is bad... Very bad...
Subaru? What's wrong?
Subaru?
No... Run! Hurry!
Wait there...
I'm...
going to...
save you...
What's the matter, boy?
You look like you saw a ghost.
What?
I asked you about the appa. The appa!
Do you even have money?
What?
Don't "what" me! The appa!
Are you buying it or not?
Oh... No, like I said,
I'm broke beyond compare...
The hell? If you're just
browsing, then move along.
I run a business here. I don't
have time for window-shoppers
What's going on?
Wasn't it just nighttime a minute ago?
The wound on my belly is gone...
Oh, right! Satella!
Damn it, didn't Puck ask
me to take care of her?
I have to get back to that shop!
Hey, why do you look so spooked?
If you don't wanna get hurt,
cough up whatever you've got!
You guys... Did you see I was
alone and decide to get revenge?
Huh? What're you talking about?
Are you nuts?
Don't worry about it.
Just leave everything you've got
on the ground and we'll let you go.
Okay, fine. Everything I've got, huh?
I'm in a hurry, so I don't even care.
Now act like a dog.
Get on all fours like a
dog and howl, "Help me!"
Don't get cocky, bastard!
Whoa, there.
Don't underestimate a truant
kid with too much free time.
After swinging a wooden sword around
all the time for no reason,
my grip strength is over 70 kilograms!
I'm in a hurry! Don't get in my way again!
Don't freak out...
Don't freak out, don't freak out!
Am I stupid?
After coming this far, I can't
just leave without answers!
Is anyone there?
Someone... Someone's in there, right?
Please, answer me! Please!
Shut yer trap!
You tryin' to bust my
door down when you don't
even know the signal or password?!
You're...
What're you all fidgety for?
Are your balls chafin' ya that much?
I'm not worried about the
position of my privates!
Don't start the conversation
with potty humor!
You're already interrupting
my evening booze.
You'll kill me if you start
talkin' about boring stuff now.
Don't drink while the sun's
still up. You'll die young.
Actually, this is a dumb question, but...
Have you died recently?
Well, I admit I'm an old
man at death's door,
but I ain't really died yet.
Okay, then have you seen
a girl with silver hair?
Silver hair?
I ain't seen anyone that conspicuous.
Was it all a dream?
Then exactly how much of it was a dream,
and why am I in this world?
So what are you doin' here, anyway?
Oh... I'm looking for an insignia.
It belongs to a silver-haired
girl who helped me out.
I don't know why, but it's important to her.
I think she said it had
a jewel in the center.
An insignia with a jewel...
Sorry, but I ain't got anything like that.
Are you sure? Try to think!
Maybe you're just old and senile?
If I can't remember when I'm
at my best, with booze in me,
the only explanation is
that I don't know it.
But...
I've got someone bringing
in some goods later.
I'm told it's some fine loot.
There's a good chance it could
be what you're lookin' for.
Is the one bringing it in a girl named Felt?
What, you even know who swiped it?
Of course, whether you'll be able
to afford it is another matter.
Ha! It's no use trying to size me up.
I'm as broke as they come, after all.
Ain't no use talkin' about it, then.
No, there is the option of trading.
Now that you mention it,
you've got some unusual stuff there.
That's right. For example,
this is a corn potage snack.
It's super tasty!
That's food?
I see! What an odd flavor!
These would go great with booze!
Right? Right?
Hey! Don't just start eating them!
Well, I dunno what you plan to trade,
but you'll have to come
back after Felt gets here.
Mm, that's good!
I guess in any world, there are people
with money, and people without.
It sure is easy to see the difference here.
Hey, what're you doing there?
You're in my way.
Felt!
You know me?
Of course I do! I've been waiting for you!
What for?
Wait, are you saying you don't remember me?
Have we met?
You know, I'm a busy woman,
so I don't remember most people
I meet unless they leave a huge impression.
I'd say that was a pretty huge impression...
Well, forget that.
I want to negotiate for
the insignia you have.
Oh, so that's it, huh?
All right, I'll hear you out.
For a rat...
Poison.
For a white whale...
A harpoon.
To the noble dragon lord, we are...
Shitbags.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Old Man Rom.
My target was more persistent
than I thought.
It took a while to shake them.
Hey, Old Man Rom, did you
water down this milk?
It's nasty.
Hey, I give you something outta the goodness
of my heart, and you call it gross?
You two are closer than I had
either hoped or expected.
I'm feeling left out over here.
Don't talk like a wuss when you've got a
face almost as scary as Old Man Rom's.
People have said many things to me,
but you tell me I can
compete with this old guy?!
Okay, I went too far that time. Sorry, Bro.
You two aren't in some conspiracy
to try to piss me off, are you?
Okay, well, why don't we
get down to business?
How much will you pay for it?
You don't waste time...
Before I answer that, you do
have the insignia, right?
Of course I do.
See?
This one's got a jewel in it,
so I had to work pretty hard to get it.
If you can pay enough to match
my effort, we'll both be happy.
I have no money.
Then we have nothing to discuss!
Tsk, tsk, tsk. I don't have money,
but I have things worth money.
What I have here is a
magical device that can stop
time for everyone, everywhere:
a "cell phone"!
What's that?
Never seen one of those before.
Take this! Nine shots per
second: Continuous Shot!
Whoa! Hey! What's that sound?!
And that was too bright!
Are you tryin' to kill me?!
Don't you go makin' light of this old
man with dodgy tricks like that!
Now, hold on.
Is this...
Them's me and Felt's faces.
What sort of magic is that?
I told you, it's a mystical item
that can freeze a moment in time.
With this, you can capture moments
in time and store them in here.
I see! That is amazing!
Never seen the like.
Is that one of the "metia" I've
been hearing about lately?
"Metia"?
It's the name for devices
that lets people who haven't
opened the gate use magic,
like real magic users.
I'm more concerned with the price.
What can I get out of this metia?
Well, it's my first time using a metia, too.
But I'd say there's no doubt it'll
fetch more than that insignia.
Then that settles it!
This cell phone for the insignia!
Negotiations complete!
Hey!
Nope. Not yet.
Why not?!
You're not the only one I'm
negotiating with for this.
Huh?
Besides, I nabbed this insignia
because I was asked to.
My client told me I could
get ten holy coins for it.
You already had a deal with
the one you stole it for?
I don't know what ten holy
coins would be worth, but...
That metia you've got would be worth
at least twenty holy coins...
No, there are probably fanciers out there
who'd pay more for a thing like that.
Really?! That means I can get
away with overcharging for it!
So, when and where are
you meeting your client?
Don't worry. Negotiations will be held here.
If a little thing like
me dealt with them alone,
I'd be sunk if a client
decided to bilk on me.
But I don't have to worry
with Old Man Rom here.
Do they know the password?
Oh, I didn't mention it.
That's probably for me. I'll go check.
You're okay with letting
her use you like that?
Well, it ain't like we're total strangers.
I've known her a long time,
so I'll help her out.
You know, even I have to give
a wry chuckle at the sight
of someone looking like such a barbarian.
Well, look at where we are.
Everyone around here is
desperate just to survive.
It's common for youngsters
to join forces with others
in similar situations to
keep themselves alive.
But Felt ain't cut out for that.
That's why I gotta look out for her.
I was right. It was for me.
Over here. Care to sit down?
There seem to be several outsiders here.
Well, I'd be in trouble if you bilked on me.
We weaklings have our own brand of smarts.
I know this older fellow,
but who's the young man?
This guy's your rival.
He's the other person negotiating with me.
I see.
I understand the situation now.
So that means you two will be
bidding against each other.
I don't really care who gets the insignia,
so I'll sell it to the highest bidder.
I think I like that personality of yours.
So how much did this young man bid?
I'm putting up this metia.
It's a rare item, probably the only
one of its kind in this world.
That muscleman tells me it's worth
no less than twenty holy coins.
A metia...
As it happens, the client sent
me with some extra funds.
Just so I'd be prepared to sweeten the deal.
The client... So you were
asked to fetch it, too?
That's right. The client
is the one who wants it.
Would you happen to be in the same business?
Being in the same business as me
would mean they're unemployed!
So, this unemployed guy has named a
price that puts him far in the lead.
What price is your master putting on it?
Twenty exactly.
These are all the holy coins
my employer sent with me.
Is it not quite enough?
You're a man! Don't make that pathetic face!
I told you, your metia is
worth no less than twenty...
As I see it, victory in this
deal is leaning toward the boy.
Sorry for you and your employer, but you'd
better bag up those coins and leave.
Yes!
Wh-What? What's wrong with a little
victory pose? I'm psyched!
No one said anything.
Go as crazy as you want. I don't
care, as long as I get my profit.
Uh, sorry, Elsa-san.
You'll probably get in trouble, huh?
It can't be helped.
It was my employer's fault
for trying to underpay.
Well, this deal ended in
disappointment for me,
but I'll be taking my leave now.
By the way, what do you intend
to do with that insignia?
Oh, I'm going to find its
owner and return it to her.
Oh... You're with them, then.
Wh-What?
Do you want to die?!
Oh, my. You dodged my strike.
This is my first battle to
the death with a giant!
Quiet, little girl! I'll grind
you up and feed you to the rats!
This is bad!
Don't worry. There's no way
Old Man Rom will lose.
Take this!
Old Man Rom!
Damn it!
I forgot to say...
I can at least take you with me!
Thank you for the milk.
I'll return this.
You bitch... How dare you?
Oh? It seems you have more
courage than your friend there.
But if you resist,
you might very well get hurt.
I'll kill you, even if you don't
fight back, you psychopath!
If you move around, my hands might slip.
I'm quite rough at handling blades, you see.
Sorry you got caught up in this.
I-I...
Blessing of the Wind.
How wonderful. I can see you
are loved by this world.
I envy you!
The old man and the girl have
fallen, yet you aren't moving.
Have you given up?
D-Damn it...
Ah, you finally stood up.
It's less fun since you took
so long, but still, not bad.
It's no use, though. I can see you're a
novice, and your movements are rough.
You have no blessings or techniques.
I'd hoped I could squeeze wisdom out
of you, but you lack that, too.
Shut up! I do have my pride!
After you put me through all this...
I do acknowledge that you have
extraordinary determination.
If only you could've done that sooner,
things might have gone
differently for these two.
I think it's time to end this.
I'll send you to meet the angels.
Ah... I certainly felt that one.
Are you surprised?
I opened up your belly when
we passed by one another.
This is the one thing I excel at.
As I thought...
Your guts have such a lovely color!
It hurts... It hurts...
Does it hurt? Are you suffering?
It... doesn't hurt?
In pain? Sad? Do you want to die?
Die?
Am I dead? Am I still alive?
When will I die? When will I die?
Slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly...
I'm scared... I'm scared...
I'm scared! I'm scared! I'm scared!
I'm gonna die! I'm gonna
die! I'm gonna die!
Yes, you're slowly losing body heat...
You're slowly growing cold...
Oh... I'm dead.
What's the matter, boy?
You look like you saw a ghost.
Boy? You okay?
I have no idea what's going on anymore...
Are you okay, boy?
Here, forget about the money.
Just take these.
Hey... Wait...
Wait! Please, wait!
Wait! Satella!
Please don't ignore me!
My dying and not doing what
you said were my fault!
But I was desperate!
I went back to the loot house after
that, but I couldn't find you...
I'm sorry for only thinking of myself.
But I'm glad you're all right, Satella.
What are you thinking?
I don't know who you are,
but don't call me by the
name of the Jealous Witch!
What are you thinking?!
The End of the Beginning and
the Beginning of the End