All right!
Boys' Bathroom
You've got a lumpy face, Tadashi.
Why are you so puny?
You've got to bulk up, so you
get to carry all of our bags.
Seriously? You're crying?
He cries about everything!
You crybaby.
What're you looking at?
Hey, isn't he a sixth grader?
No, he's just from class 3.
Lame.
What'd you mean?!
Hey, wait a sec!
What?
Y-You're lame, four-eyes!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
H-Hey, wait a sec.
"Lame."
At the time, Tsukki might have actually
been talking about me, too.
But more importantly,
the fact that he was able to say that
to the bullies who threatened me...
That made him look really cool,
and I was envious.
I wanted to be like that.
What about you, Yamaguchi?
What would you say to Tsukishima?
Haikyu!!
Episode 08: Illusionary Hero
I'm heading out.
Okay.
Good work!
Hey, Tsukishima!
We're gonna practice the synchronized
attack, so help us out for a sec.
I can still go, too.
There'll be three wing spikers,
but that's okay, isn't it?
I wanna get the timing down.
Wait... You aren't trying to
become a regular, are you?
Don't think I'm gonna be
warming that bench forever.
Bring it on!
Daichi-san, let's hurry up and do this.
Let me rest for a bit.
Good job!
Daichi-san!
I can't afford to take this so lightly.
It's just a club.
Miyagi Prefecture Junior High All-Around Sports Tournament
Volleyball
Left! Left!
#4!
Oh, my! It's Tsukishima-kun again!
Nothing less from the ace!
Hey!
Tsukishima, nice kill!
All right!
Amemaru Junior High School
Volleyball Club
Where you gonna go to high school, Ni-chan?
Karasuno.
They're a powerhouse school that
rivals Shiratorizawa right now.
I'm gonna go to nationals
when I get to high school!
Karasuno High School
Volleyball Club
I'm home.
Welcome back!
Were you stay late doing
extra practice again?
Everyone's really skilled,
so I can't afford to slack off.
Not to mention, Coach Ukai is really strict.
But...
I'm totally going to try to get
a regular spot in my first year!
There're a lot of club members, right?
That'd be awesome if could make regular.
Right?
Mom!
Welcome home.
I need three lunches tomorrow, too!
For morning practice, lunch time,
and then right before club.
Got it. High in protein and low-fat, right?
Yep! Thanks!
The lady at the butcher shop today said,
"It's amazing that your brother's
on the Karasuno volleyball team."
Ni-chan, you have a match tomorrow, right?
Can I come watch?
Hmm...
I'll get nervous if you watch, so nope!
Aw...
Hey, what's your position right now?
The same as junior high?
Yeah.
So you're the ace!
Yup!
What about you, Kei?
You just joined a youth team, right?
I hate receiving.
At first, it doesn't go the way
you want it to at all, right?
Here, get into position.
Here we go.
Kei, don't try to raise it with your arms.
See, you lower your hips
and then do it like you're sending
it off with your whole body.
Throw it to me a sec.
Wow!
Receiving is where everything
begins in volleyball.
Connections mean everything in volleyball.
Are you getting along
with the other kids okay?
Yeah...
Liar!
It's written all over your face!
Karasuno General Sports Park
Indoor Gymnasium
Hi.
Ah! Um...
Thank you for the other day.
Have we met?
The... other day... a-at the park...
Oh. So, what are you doing here?
The park...
Oh, um...
I wanted to play some kind of sport...
There are a lot of scary guys
in baseball and soccer,
but this seemed safe.
Ah!
Those shoes are awesome!
I still only have the
school-issued gym shoes.
Mine are hand-me-downs.
These were my older brother's, and I'm
using them until I get my own next week.
Your brother plays volleyball, too?
He plays at a really strong
high school called Karasuno.
He's like the ace.
H-He's the ace of a powerhouse school?!
Th-That's awesome!
N-Nah... It's not that big of a deal.
He's been one ever since junior high.
Wow!
How long has he been playing?
Did he play on this team?
Aces are totally cool!
I'm home.
How was your practice match today?
Yeah, it went great!
I got a lot of spikes in!
That's cool.
Let's practice passing.
After we're done eating.
Yamaguchi.
What's the next class?
Japanese!
I'm gonna go to Karasuno's match
tomorrow, but do you wanna come?
My brother told me not to come
because it'll make him nervous,
but since my brother's a third-year,
this is his final match in the prefecture.
I'll go! I've never seen Akiteru-kun play.
Tsukishima, your brother's in
Karausno's volleyball club, too?
So's mine.
Friendship
What position does your brother play?
Wing spiker.
Hey! So does mine.
That team practically has
a caste system, so it's rough.
If you can't even play in matches,
you really have to wonder if going
to a powerhouse school is worth it.
Tsukki's brother plays in the matches.
Wha? No way.
I saw a match recently,
and none of the regulars
were named Tsukishima.
That can't be true.
I hear about the matches all the time.
It's gotta be some kind of mistake.
You can see for yourself at the match.
Yeah, I can.
South
Miyagi Prefecture
High School
General Sports Tournament
Volleyball
<Boys'>
One more!
Nice receive!
They're going left! Left!
That's awesome! #10 did it again!
He's only around 170cm, too!
And he's only a second-year, right?
See?
The one of the left is
the third-year, Kawada-kun,
and on the other side is the second-year
ace who they call the Little Giant.
For about a year now!
We get it!
We can see that...
My brother's also a third-year
and hasn't been in any matches.
Slice.
It wasn't like a movie or drama, where there's spurts of blood and heads go flying.
This was far more shocking.
My brother wasn't on the court.
One more!
Nice serve!
Fly
How lame.
It was only a club,
but it was everything to my brother.
In the end, it made
my brother tell pointless lies.
So you're the ace!
Yup!
But my brother probably believed...
...that he could be the ace if he tried hard.
But so what if he did?
Would it be worth all of that trouble?
Tsukki!
What?
Tsukki, you were always able to do
anything while being cool and smart,
so I've always been jealous.
And?
But you're being lame lately, Tsukki!
Hinata might become the
Little Giant some day.
That just means you have to beat him, Tsukki!
You just need to become an
even better player than Hinata
and prove your skills!
You have the height, brains, and instinct,
so why do you decide that
getting any better is impossible?
Even if...
I worked really hard and became the
best player on Karasuno's team,
what would happen after that?
Even if there's a tiny chance
we might make it to nationals,
what happens after that?
No matter how high you climb,
there's always someone better.
Even if you are able to show
some results somewhere,
you'll never actually be number one!
You're gonna lose somewhere!
You all know that, so how
can you keep going?!
What else do we need besides pride?!
To think this day would come...
When did you become so cool?
You're actually cool.
T-Tsukki? What's wrong?
If anything...
It's at least better than my
worn-out train of thought.
But I can't accept that.
Huh?
I'm gonna go ask something.
Tsukki?!
Hey, Daichi.
Yeah?
You sure it's okay to leave Tsukishima alone?
If you force someone to do it,
it's not actually free practice.
I know, but...
Ever since we had our first 3-on-3,
I haven't been that worried.
But if there's even the slightest chance
that Tsukishima says he's gonna quit,
I'll do whatever I have to to stop him,
so I might need you to help me out then.
I don't understand how Tsukishima thinks.
We're basically developing at this point,
and we don't know the
limits of our potential.
Even if we felt those limits,
we would still keep aiming higher.
I can't see any logic or reason in his behavior.
True...
Haikyu!!
Gymnasium #1
Yamaguchi-kun said something
in a weird voice as he ran off,
but I wonder if he's okay.
Weird voice?
"Tsukki!"
Like that.
Oh, so he went to see Tsukishima.
Did something happen?
Yeah... He seemed a bit
worried about Tsukishima.
I see.
Tsukishima never does anything that's lame.
He never fails at tests.
He always does things like whoosh!
And swish!
Yeah...
What exactly is the difference
between "whoosh" and "swish"?
So I think he'll be okay.
Being good in volleyball or sucking at it,
I think it's obvious which one's cooler.
Gymnasium #3
Oh?
What's this?
What's this? What's this?
There's something I'd like to ask you. May I?
Sure!
Thank you very much.
Both of your schools
are sometimes considered
powerhouse schools, right?
Well, yeah.
Even if you were able
to make it to nationals,
actually winning there
would be difficult, right?
But not impossible!
Now, now, let's hear him out.
This is just a what-if.
I seriously can't figure out how
everyone can be so determined.
Volleyball is just a club,
and maybe you'll get to write,
"I worked really hard in my club in high school,"
on your resume, right?
"Just a club"?
That almost sounds like someone's name.
Ooh, like Mary Club?
No wait, I guess it was "just some club."
Aw, man! So it doesn't
sound like someone's name.
Man, I was so close!
Damn it!
Are you basically asking me to retort?
Nah. There'll be no end to it.
Say, four-eyes.
It's Tsukishima.
Say, Tsukishima-kun...
Is volleyball fun?
No, not really...
Maybe that's because you suck.
I'm a third-year and I've been to nationals,
and I'm better than you. Like way better.
You don't have to tell me that.
But I only recently starting thinking
that volleyball was fun.
Ever since my straight
became usable in matches.
Straight
Because my cross hits that I was
really good at kept getting blocked,
Cross
I got frustrated and practiced
the hell out of straights.
And...
At the next tournament, the
same blockers couldn't touch it.
I got right past them.
Just that one shot made me feel
like my time had finally come.
It all depends on if you
have that moment or not.
It doesn't really matter
what happens in the future,
or if you can win your next match.
The joy you feel beating
the guy in front of you,
and when you're able to pull out 120%
of your potential, is everything.
Well, at least that's how it is for me,
and it doesn't mean that
applies to everyone.
I don't really understand why
you say it's "just a club,"
but I don't think you're wrong.
But once that moment arrives for you,
that's the moment you'll
be hooked on volleyball.
All right. I answered your question,
now help with blocking.
All right, now.
Come on, hurry it up.
Wait, what...
Ah, Yamaguchi-kun came back.
Yamaguchi, where's Tsukishima?
It looks like he got caught by the
Nekoma and Fukurodani captains.
What?! I'm so jealous.
Maybe I'll go, too.
Hinata, do you think of Tsukki as your rival?
Huh?
Of course I do!
We play the same position,
and he has everything I don't.
But I'm not gonna lose to him!
I've gotta practice!
Captain! I'm coming in!
If Hinata and Tsukishima-kun are rivals,
Sure.
it's like the sun versus the moon.
"Hi" means "sun" and "tsuki" means "moon."
Yeah, you're right!
Yeah!
I hope that happens...
#4!
Eek...
All right!
That #4 is really intense again today.
Sensei.
Fukurodani                 Karasuno
All right!
Even if you're not able
to stop #4's spikes,
at least try to touch it.
Right!
I see... So even if they
aren't able to stop it,
if they're able to touch the ball,
it reduces the momentum?
Right. There are usually
two goals in blocking.
There's the soft block that's used in
order to make the ball easier to receive,
and the kill block that's used
to completely shut the ball out.
Kill... as in, killing something?
Yes.
Eek!
We don't have to stop it?
Well...
If you're able to actually shut the
ball out, there's nothing better.
All right!
Fukurodani            Karasuno
Nice receive!
Give it to me!
Left! #4, #4!
First, you need to visualize it.
Concentrate your strength to your fingertips,
so you're not blown back.
And put your hands in front of you,
instead of over your head.
In front.
And then, make this annoying owl shut up!
Just try it!
Um... a soft block that reduces
the ball's momentum, and...
The one who kills the spike...
Feint!
Damn it!
Wow, I totally thought they were going
to come with a full-on attack there.
To think it was actually a feint...
I guess that's what you get with
an ace that went to nationals.
Daichi-san, that was...
Yeah.
Bokuto-san just ran away.
I did not! I just got around it!
And really well! I got around their block!
You let your guard down.
Ugh! Yeah, yeah, I'm sorry!
Well, now...
Perhaps the troublesome little baby bird
is starting to come out of his shell.
Oh...
The sun versus the moon?
Tsukki! Jump some blocks for us!
Could you please not call me that?
Then... How about Glasses-kun?
All right, let's do this thing, Akaasshi!
Now somehow I'm involved.
Episode 08: "VS "Umbrella""
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"VS "Umbrella"."