So we meet at last, Ayato Amagiri!
I have been looking forward to this day!
As I'm always hearing
about you from my master,
I expect great things of you!
Please trigger more exhilaration
in me than Kirin Toudou did!
Unfortunately,
I can't guarantee that I will.
But this match...
Victory will be ours!
No matter what!
Fine.
All I have to do now is pray
that you two are worthy of my respect.
You good-for-nothing.
Your body is inefficient enough as it is,
so ease up on the inane chatter.
Otherwise, I'll make sure you never
open that mouth of yours again.
But clearly, you're speaking
far more than me.
And besides, I don't have
the type of mouth that opens.
I told you to stop trying
to get in the last word, right?
How bizarre are those two puppets?
But you know, I'm a little glad
that we're facing them in the finals.
Because now we can attack them
without holding back.
Well, as far as being worthy opponents,
I suppose you're right!
Whoa! Looks like Amagiri's not going to
use the Ser=Versta in this match, either!
I think the phrase
you're looking for here is "can't use it."
According to one rumor, he's applied
for an emergency freezing process.
Well, everyone knows
how difficult the Ser=Versta can be.
There might have been some trouble
we don't know about.
During the semifinal,
all I thought was that he'd sent it in
for maintenance.
I have a souvenir for you to take home.
You can decide after seeing it.
But really...
What a tacky souvenir!
The Phoenix Showdown
All right, everybody!
Like it or not, this is the very last match
of the Phoenix Festa!
Now, who will be the ones
to reach the top?
Phoenix Festa Final Match!
Battle...
...start!
- Let's go, Julis!
- Right!
Oh, my! What's up with this move
by the Amagiri/Riessfeld team?
Looks like they're joining forces
to crush AR-D together, right at the outset.
Amagiri Shinmei Style,
Second Sword...
Nine-fanged Sword!
Too bad, but I already have
the data on that move!
Thought you would!
Primrose!
Amagiri Shinmei Style...
You must be quite confident
to leave me by the wayside.
Don't worry...
We're keeping an eye on you!
So assuming we're gonna
go after AR-D together...
what are we going to do
about RM-C in the meantime?
We're going to use
your state of Vijñāna.
True, if I use that, I can get a good read
on what's going on in the whole arena.
You can grasp RM-C's and my
movements simultaneously, right?
Julis!
We can reduce the risks of fighting
two against one by a lot now!
C-Can you believe that?
Wh-What's the matter?
That evasion just now...
Amagiri was guiding Riessfeld!
I'm just guessing here,
but Amagiri must be predicting
RM-C's every move!
Burst into bloom...
Livingstone Daisy!
Ayato, I'm going to bombard him now!
Roger that!
Go!
Talk about time-consuming...
Amagiri Shinmei Style,
Second Sword...
Ten Linked Thistles!
Got him!
This is the moment
I've been waiting for!
Come out...
Gloriosa!
This is nothing!
I don't believe that armor!
I guess we'll have to regroup for now.
Still, they're not going to fall
for the same trick twice!
Too bad we couldn't take him out
with that attack just now.
If only I had the Ser=Versta...
I see.
Their strategy was to attack me
in order to draw
your protective barrier away?
Unbelievable!
So that whole series of moves
was all part of their strategy?!
But apparently this fool's armor
was more durable than they'd imagined.
That was splendid!
What a splendid combination,
Ayato Amagiri
and Julis-Alexia von Riessfeld!
Yesterday, more than
the day before yesterday...
Today, more than yesterday...
Without question, we've evolved!
But apparently,
you two have surpassed even us.
Then we have to unveil
our secret technique sooner!
There it is, there it is!
AR-D's announcement!
Does this mean that we'll be
seeing that fusion again?
I'd intended to do so from the start,
but as usual, you vetoed me, RM-C.
Of course I did.
After all, our master told us
not to use it lightly.
But in order to defeat you two for sure,
there doesn't seem
to be any other choice.
That fusion thing of yours
takes forever to prepare.
And we're not going to miss our chance!
Do you really think our master wouldn't
have a countermeasure in place?
Ruin-Sharif...
Mode: Wolkenwurf...
Oh, no, you're not!
Maximum...
Julis! Get back!
Let's go, RM-C!
ACM Unit, First External Armor,
purging all Luxes...
Ceding Limit Control.
There they are, there they are,
there they are! Oh, yes, they're here!
Start linking!
Now that it's come to this!
Amagiri just charged in,
risking certain damage!
Well, he's desperate
to stop the fusion, after all.
How unfortunate for you,
Ayato Amagiri.
Camilla Pareto... Badge broken!
Looks like you were a step too late!
Fusion complete!
Oh, my...
All right, I'm leaving the rest to you.
Right! Good work!
All right, why don't we
get Round 2 started?
Saya...
Saya, let me go first.
Flora!
You mustn't come near!
We're going to rescue you now.
First the Shadows
from the first floor, and now this...
It must be someone with the ability
to weaponize Shadows.
Meaning that...
This location is...
...the optimal place for this person
to use those powers to the max, right?
I see.
Kirin Toudou, eh?
So they sent in one of their big guns.
Are you the kidnapper?
Please, that's enough!
If you get in my way,
this girl's life will be in the balance.
It'll only put you at a disadvantage
if you do such a thing!
Then go ahead and give it a shot.
But let me advise you of one thing.
As far as my own welfare is concerned,
that doesn't concern me in the least.
First, toss away your weapon.
Kirin!
This sniper... Saya Sasamiya, huh?
Kirin! Take Flora!
Right!
I won't let you!
Thank you very much, Saya!
Come on, Flora!
Lady Toudou!
Kirin!
I'm all right!
Don't worry about me.
Please take Flora!
L-Lady Toudou...
Hurry, go through that door.
Okay!
So powerful!
It's over.
Kirin!
Don't move another muscle.
That's a vital spot.
If you don't get it treated right away...
you'll die.
I'm not done yet.
What can you do
in the shape you're in?
Would you like to test me?
Is that iai?
Toudou Style Art of Sword-drawing...
FOLDED WING
Folded Wing!
What's this?
Here I come.
Impossible...
a virtual image of a sword?
It's a great skill,
but not great enough.
No, no...
That's good enough.
Kirin,
hang in there!
Lady Toudou! Lady Toudou!
Are you okay? Lady Toudou!
Please stay with us, Lady Toudou!
Oh, right...
Ayato-senpai and Julis-senpai's match...
How did it go, I wonder?
What's the matter with you,
Ayato Amagiri?
Ayato!
Burst into bloom...
Primrose!
Seriously! What's going on here?!
Any way you look at it,
he's gotten way too powerful!
Seriously. I totally agree.
He's on a whole different level
than he was in the semifinals!
Right.
And he didn't throw up
multiple protective walls, either!
I am now able to master the use of this
surging power far better than before!
How do I describe this joy?
How do I describe this thrill?
This is the true power
my master granted me!
True power?
Hey, Julis...
What if this is AR-D at his
normal specs right now... What then?
You mean like your seal?
It's not impossible,
but why would he do such a...
Now, then, let's see you take this hit!
This is my...
Not good!
Wolnir Hammer!
Julis, hang on!
Looks like he's upped
the impact, as well.
Come on, we're not done yet
by a long shot!
And continuous fire, as well?!
Run, Julis!
Then how do you like this method?
Wh-What the...
Oh, crap!
You won't be dodging me
so easily now!
Wolnir Hammer...
Fire!
Burst into bloom...
Anthurium!
Julis...
Are you all right?
Yes, somehow...
So you can stand
even after absorbing that direct hit...
Just what I'd expect of you!
Now that it's come to this,
even if we both go down...
How overwhelming is AR-D's power?
Now then, looks like this
final match has been decided—
H-H-Hold up!
What's going on? What's going on?
Uh... ahem.
Claudia?
Ayato, Julis, can you hear me?
Flora is safe.
Please rest assured.
And also...
Have at it!
What is going on?
All right, then, pardon me.
Th-That was Seidoukan Academy's
student council president just now, right?
Uh, yeah... that was her...
Seriously, that girl...
No matter how you look at it,
that was going too far!
Who knew she'd burst into that place
just to communicate with us?
Since she's gone the extra mile
for us, we can't lose now!
For Saya and Kirin's sake, too, right?
I have no idea what that was all about.
But all I can do is exert
my power to the fullest!
Wolnir Hammer!
All right, let's go, then...
Ser=Versta!
Fire!
What the...
Crap.
Now our counterattack begins!
Seriously, when you are with such a slow,
stupid good-for-nothing,
there's never enough time
to get anything done, is there?
All right, let me present
the preview now while I can.
Episode 21
Clinching Victory
Just a moment, RM-C!
Such an important duty
should be mine to—
All right, next episode—