To grant my wishes?
Yep.
Noel.
From seven years ago.
What?
No, I mean—
Nonoka.
It can't be.
Here, Nonoka.
Thanks, Noel.
Their Promise
Nice weather.
Morning, Dad.
Morning.
Two eggs, right?
Sure.
Saucer management
funds to be increased.
Soft-boiled?
Whatever.
Don't you need to get dressed?
You're not one to talk.
As long as you aren't going to be late.
Late? For what?
School.
Isn't it the opening ceremony today?
No way, it's still August.
It's earlier than in Tokyo.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
I thought you'd know, since it's
the same as in elementary school.
I wouldn't remember that.
Can you toast the bread?
Fine, fine.
Dad, you idiot.
I'm Komiya Nonoka.
Nice to meet you.
You should smile a little more.
The eggs weren't even soft-boiled.
You said whatever.
Be careful.
I'm leaving.
Nonoka.
Noel?!
I'm here to see you.
Sorry, I don't have time, thanks to Dad.
See you later.
See you.
Welcome.
Did you find the lost child?
So you weren't a tourist.
Nope.
I just moved here.
Do you know which class you're in?
No, not yet.
There aren't too many people
going from this town.
Really?
Yeah.
I hope we're in the same class.
Yeah, me, too.
I'm Komiya Nonoka.
Nice to meet you.
Okay, everyone, be good to her.
Komiya-san, your seat is in the
very back of the second row.
Hey...
Hey!
Don't you dare touch me.
You could have said
something if you knew.
Why?
We met by the lake before, right?
So?
I wanted to know why
you said what you did.
Is Nonoka done yet?
Komiya-san, let's go home together.
You can call me Nonoka.
You can call me Koharu, too, then.
Do you live by the lake?
Yeah,
but it's more towards the mountains.
So in the morning—
Hold it!
Um...
Mizusaka Yuzuki.
Is it true what you just said?
Did you really just move here?
Yes...?
Come with me.
What?
H-Hey!
Just come.
Wait, Mizusaka-san.
Did you need something from me?
Tell me straight up what you think.
About what?
Isn't it obvious?
Do you like it?
Do you hate it?
The saucer!
Excuse me, two fresh ginger ales.
That's okay with you, right?
Sure, anything's fine.
So, where were we?
We're continuing this?
Of course, it's important.
Calm down, okay?
You might not know,
but it was a huge mess seven years ago.
I saw it on the news,
so I kind of remember.
Besides, around that time, I—
Some things you just have
to be there to understand.
A saucer just showed up out of
nowhere and parked at the lake.
Yet no one even cares anymore!
Okay, come on.
Our drinks are here, too.
Seriously, that saucer caused—
Here, you can have mine.
But I don't think the townspeople mind it.
They're all being fooled.
By who?
The saucer.
Obviously.
It's just been pretending to
sit there for seven years.
What is it really up to?
The town's safety is more
and more at risk every day.
We have to do something about
it before it's too late.
I think the town's as safe as it could be.
The saucer versus a friend in need,
whose side are you on?
Well, a friend in need, but...
All right then, let's take
back the town's safety.
The two of us will.
What?
No Saucer
Your cooperation, please.
Please.
Let's take back our town.
Saucer Palace
Shiihara Shop
Let's take it back.
Your cooperation, please!
Please!
Come on, Nonoka, you, too.
Please don't say my name.
You have to shout louder.
Otherwise they won't get it.
No, I—
Oh, yeah.
Want to use this?
It's fine, I'll be fine.
Oh?
Your cooperation, please!
Let's drive out the saucer!
We do not need a saucer in our town!
We must stay strong!
Mizusaka-san...
What's wrong?
Oh, sorry.
How long are we doing this?
Until the saucer goes away.
Seriously?
Of course.
I think we can get rid of it,
with everyone's help.
Koharu.
What are you doing, customers?
This is, well...
Something important.
I think you should apologize.
Plan B.
B?
Why are we running?
Because we didn't do anything wrong.
Then we should explain properly.
I can't. We've been friends
since we were little.
I know her really well.
Thanks, Nonoka.
For coming.
It just kind of happened.
I was happy, though.
Thanks.
Let's go to our next plan.
Next?
Saucer Management
Thanks for waiting.
You're here about the saucer?
Yes.
Please fill out this form.
Opinions regarding
saucer management.
No, I want to meet straight with
the person in charge of the saucer.
We need to talk to the leaders—
Sorry, never mind.
Let go, Nonoka.
We need to talk straight to the leaders!
Take me to your leader!
Why did you get in the way?
You can't call for the
leaders at a reception desk.
How would you know?
You used to be able to get to that
island on a tour boat, you know?
And now it's off limits,
because it's dangerous.
That's just not right.
We can't just leave it as it is.
We have to take it back.
It's our town.
No Saucer!
Sorry for causing trouble.
Please don't get mad at Yuzuki.
I know how she feels.
Where did it go?
What are you looking for?
A weapon.
Nonoka.
I found it!
All right, we're set.
What are you doing?
It's none of your business, Souta.
Thanks for having me.
I'm talking about that.
That's none of your business either.
I'm telling you not to cause people trouble.
I bet it's something pointless again.
It's not pointless.
Why are you doing something so stupid?
Why?
I knew it.
Yuzuki?
I knew it!
It's all the saucer and that girl's fault.
What's her problem?
Um, thanks for having me.
Hold it, exchange student.
I think that's enough.
Souta, that idiot.
Stupid Souta.
Stupid, stupid!
What are you doing?
Taking action.
We're going to the island.
No, you can't do that!
We have to.
Or nothing will change.
Get me my backpack.
Let's go, Nonoka.
Fine.
I'll go alone.
I've always been alone anyway.
Mizusaka-san!
You're mad at me, aren't you?
Not really.
I'm sorry.
Can I ask you something?
Yeah.
Why do you want to get rid
of the saucer so much?
Seven years ago, the saucer came,
and things changed.
There are still some things that
haven't gone back to how they were.
They used to launch
fireworks from the lake.
Fireworks?
It wasn't a big deal,
but the fireworks were really
pretty shining on the lake.
But they stopped doing it.
Let's launch it.
This works, doesn't it?
Let's launch this rocket.
Three, two, one!
Go!
It didn't even get close.
Yuzuki,
I'll help you.
Let's get rid of the saucer.
Are you sure?
Yeah. But nothing dangerous.
Really?
Yeah.
We'll have to find more
people to help us.
Nonoka.
Thanks.
Yeah.
It's so pretty!
Dad should have come.
You're right.
Nonoka, have you been keeping
your promise to me?
Yep, I have.
That's my girl.
Mom, I—
Nonoka.
What's wrong, Nonoka?
You look down.
Noel.
Is something wrong?
Something I can help with?
Can you help, too?
Sure, leave it to me!
What do I have to do?
We want to make the
saucer leave the city.
Nonoka, do you hate the saucer?
No,
but I want to help my friend somehow.
Sure, just wait a little longer.
I'm glad.
That's three of us.
Next episode of Celestial
Method: "Where Memories Live."
Enjoy.
Where Memories Live