Blue Castle Academy
I was so concerned about the start of school,
but two weeks have already passed.
Teacher...
Roromiya's roasting dried seaweed
on the alcohol lamp.
Teacher...
Roromiya brought a dog to school.
Roromiya is staring off into space.
Teacher...
Roromiya ran away.
I should be more worried
about her than myself...
So if you apply this number here,
Don't Think
this is the result.
And if you plug in this number here...
Oh, it's you.
What were you doing?
Hurry and take your seat!
What's she doing?
She vanished, right in the middle of P.E.
Yeah, she just disappeared
during the marathon.
I mean, it's like you can never
guess what she's thinking.
She's really cute but...
What the hell?
Creepy...
Hey!
I'm twice as bad, so why aren't
you talking about...
Watanuki, shut up.
Time to eat.
And now she just starts eating lunch.
She's unbelievable...
I'm leaving now.
Here you go.
You don't have any money?
Then you were quite foolish to
eat your lunch early.
Red Bean Bun
Want this?
My stomach doesn't feel so great right now.
You're giving it to me?
If you'd like, I have some soy milk, too.
I love you.
I've thought you were nice
ever since I met you.
She just said she loves me!
S-Stop lying...
You're just saying that
because I gave you some food.
No...
My sixth sense told me so.
Y-Yeah, right...
Or maybe my five senses?
You're just making this up as you go along.
Well...
You really should interact
more with others.
But I don't know how I'm supposed to that.
That's so funny!
But why are they rabbit ears?
Rabbit ears?
Because life is just one big game!
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm a mysterious sprite, you know.
Hey, Chiyo!
Haven't seen you since this morning.
You know her?
I can't reveal the nature of our relationship...
That sounds shady.
What are you doing?
Whatever do you mean?
All I ever try to do is enjoy life.
That's all...
He's so funny!
I see.
Goodbye.
Wait up, Chiyo...
He was funny, right?
Wait for me.
A white silk base, with an elaborate
and intricate lace trim.
All rounded up with a ribbon!
How—
What I love about lace is how
it really is an art form...
What do you want?
It appears Watanuki got into a fight,
and he's in the nurse's office now.
Could you show me where that is?
Wh-Why didn't you say that
in the first place?!
You're all torn up...
Whatever.
A delinquent's bruises are his medals.
You seem to have a monopoly
on that distinction.
So, what happened?
Chiyo,
do you know when Watanuki stopped
wearing tighty-whities?
It actually wasn't that long...
All right, I'll talk!
They were calling Karuta weird.
Maybe she walks around in her
own world, but so what?
She's still aware of what's
going on around her.
She isn't just thinking...
It's something deeper.
She probably knows
instinctively what's right...
That's it. She's like a jungle hero.
She's like Tarzan.
Stop laughing!
Watanuki.
Karuta...
Shall we leave them alone?
You're right.
Are you all right?
They're really good friends, huh?
Well, they've known each
other since childhood.
More than friends, but not quite lovers.
A truly beautiful tale...
Don't invade people's privacy that way.
Once upon a time, in a land far, far away,
some people mingled with
supernatural creatures.
The families descended from them
were mysteriously prosperous.
Among them were some individuals
in whom the blood of
the creatures ran particularly strong.
They are known as throwbacks.
And that's who we are.
We were born on the exact day,
at the exact same time,
and with the exact same
personalities as our ancestors.
It's like we've also inherited
The Fate
Ancestor
their memories, and are mysteriously
bound to their same fate.
Throwback
These children were regarded as
the second coming of the ancestors,
and were raised by the whole house.
That is to say,
essentially, the parents did not
factor into their upbringing.
The parents were just a womb.
Having never experienced
the concept of family,
it's natural that we should be lonely.
Waa! Waa!
Why remind me again?
Because the story is about two people
needing each other and becoming close.
It doesn't matter if they're good or bad.
You need relationships with
others to survive.
That means you, too, Chiyo!
Let's communicate!
You really are meddlesome...
Don't complicate it like, "I don't know
how to interact with others."
It'll just happen!
Wha— You looked into me again!
Watanuki...
Let's go home.
Just one moment, please.
I told you before, you don't
have to do this for me.
My name is Kagerou Shoukiin.
I am Soushi's old master and
Ririchiyo Shirakiin's fiancé!
He said that Miketsukami
used to serve him.
So,
does that mean he knew I had a fiancé?
Roromiya?
This, too.
And this.
These are good.
That was unnecessary,
but I guess I'll thank you anyway.
However, this might give me a cavity.
You should watch out, as well.
After I said that, she brought me this.
But I...
Don't complicate it like, "I don't know
how to interact with others."
It'll just happen!
Blue Castle Academy
Home Economics
I'd like you to split into groups
and get to work!
I'm looking forward to working with you.
To think that I'd have to be on your team...
Working in a group...
I need to be sure not to
alienate my classmates.
R-Roromiya...
I have to keep an eye out,
and cover for her, as well.
15 grams of garam masala...
10 grams of coriander.
That was 0.2 grams too much.
This isn't an experiment.
Sh-She criticized me!
There is no manual for cooking.
Today's spices aren't fresh.
They've lost some flavor.
We must consider various factors,
and then improvise.
Cooking is about seeing the
possibilities clearly.
Th-The color of her eyes has changed!
Th-This is good...
Cooking is about seeing the
possibilities clearly.
Ah, she said it again!
Let's eat!
Did you get those injuries
during P.E. yesterday?
There was this cat...
It scratched me when I tried to help it.
When I see a small animal,
I can't help thinking of Watanuki,
and I can't just leave them.
It's hard to understand her,
but everything she does
is actually for a reason.
Maybe she's in her own world,
but she's aware of what's going on.
I see.
Do you
like Miketsukami?
Why do you ask?
I just met him.
We aren't like you two...
Wait.
Now that I think about it,
my irregular heartbeat only
happens when I see him,
or when touches me!
Could this be what's meant by lo...
N-No... We just met, so it's
too early for that!
I know.
It's that part of puberty when you can't
help but think about the opposite sex...
Then, it's just a natural reaction,
stemming from my body's changes.
In fact, it's rather late for it to happen now!
I see!
I was sexually attracted to him
because he saved me!
Bye-bye!
Karuta, let's go home.
I should probably hurry home.
Water?
Why is there water here?
I knew it...
A nure-onna.
The nure-onna, or wet woman,
is a creature with the
head of a woman and the body of a snake.
She has long black hair.
She is called a nure-onna because
her hair is always wet.
Some theories claim that she
is a water snake's avatar.
It's been said that she appears by water,
and devours people.
But in terms of appearance and personality,
too many different rumors exist for certainty.
Hold it!
Facing danger is a man's job.
Women and children should stand back—
Watanuki!
Are you okay?
I-I won't let her run wild on my turf...
Take it easy, and stay back!
You want me to take it easy?
You must be kidding!
Tanuki are on the same level as foxes,
when it comes to transformation!
Did you get her?
I never expected that they'd come here.
I just hope no one saw this.
Don't worry.
She'll be gone by tomorrow morning.
Probably to reappear elsewhere,
but whatever.
This time, I guess I won't refuse to thank you.
That spell wasn't half bad.
Stop petting me!
Did you just hear something?
Like what?
Chiyo... Watanuki.
You're falling.
R-Roromiya...
Watanuki...
You recognized me...
Yes.
Of course.
With my sixth sense.
No, with my fifth sense?
No...
With my organs?
I don't think so...
Did you hear the rumor?
I heard, I heard!
You mean the story about the big skeleton,
the tanuki, and the cosplay girl?
You're saying Roromiya
turned into a skeleton?
Don't you mean she was eaten
by a big skeleton?
See, in the version I heard,
Roromiya ate a tanuki.
I knew something about her was weird...
Whew...
Looks like no one took a picture or anything.
That's fortunate.
We'd have had to erase any evidence.
You're so scary...
Young people, in the spring of youth...
That's happiness.
Roromiya did?
Really? But I can see it.
Roromiya does eat everything...
Though she has such a cute face.
Karuta doesn't care, so you're
just stressing for nothing.
If you're still mad, I'll knock 'em out.
Just make sure you aren't
knocked out yourself.
What? Stop mocking me!
You're good friends.
No, we're not!
Are you blind or something?
It's nice when everything's lively.
I'm bad. I won't be friendly!
Huh?
Just like that, we were hanging out.
So, listen...
What is it?
I just thought...
We are a man and woman, you know?
So?
It's already quite late.
Usually, when you're together until morning,
doesn't that make your heart kind of race?
I'll slice you up, and turn you into a duster.
I'm sorry.
Next time, on Inu X Boku Secret Service:
Their Night Alone.
Finally! My Ririchiyo will be
attacked by tentacles!
Their Night Alone
Your nose is bleeding.
Cooking is about seeing
the possibilities clearly.
Look forward to next time!