Sis, it'll be all right.
Thank you.
I'm going to hang in there.
Thank you, Sis.
Excuse me.
Oh, Mr. Kokubu.
Miss, how are you feeling?
I’m really sorry.
Um, I feel better now, so—
No, no, stay right there.
Uh, Mr. Kokubu,
I was being quite rude earlier...
Um...
Miss, you have nothing at all to be sorry about.
It's okay.
More importantly...
Why don't we talk about what to do next?
Small Palm
Hey, Mr. Kokubu...
How long are you
going to keep calling me here?
I mean...
didn't I already apologize?
Right?
Yes. With your words.
I'm sorry for what I did.
I apologized and I'm keeping
my mouth shut in class.
Isn't that enough?
Part of the work
is becoming aware of what you did.
What'll happen if I become aware of it?
Will something change?
If something changes,
will I get something good out of it?
Tell me, Mr. Kokubu,
will something good happen if we keep living?
My parents and everyone around me
say do your best and study hard
so you can get into a good high school,
but even if I got into a good school,
who's to say I'll get a job at all,
let alone one at a good company?
"If you do your best, you'll get good results,"
but there's no guarantee of that,
and still people say, "Do your best!"
Isn't that crazy?
It's like, if I worked as hard as I could,
but it didn't work out,
nobody's going to take responsibility.
I see.
So you're nervous about the future
because of that.
And your parents don't understand you.
Hm, hmm.
So?
What part of that has anything to do
with Kawamoto and Sakura?
Absolutely nothing, right?
Stop talking like you've come to the conclusion
that it's all society's fault.
Keep it up and I'll start talking about life
in Japan when I was a kid.
The postwar period!
It was still postwar times!
If I did that, you'd be like,
"That has nothing to do with this." Sheesh!
You wouldn't understand how I feel.
That's why I'm asking now!
Let's talk!
All right. The perilla plant is set.
We can put the basil next to it.
And let's put the mint somewhere else.
It grows too much.
Right.
Now let's give them plenty of water.
Okay.
Last week in homeroom, Mr. Kokubu said
something to the class with a clear voice.
Okay, today there are several things
I want to ask you.
First, Arai, Takashi, Kimura,
Mochizuki, Takagi, and Wakabayashi.
There are individual questions for you six,
so you'll each go with a teacher
to another classroom.
That's when everyone in the class realized.
The school had gotten serious
about intervening in the darkness in our class.
Now we knew this teacher wasn't just
going through the motions of doing something.
Okay.
I guess we'll get started here.
So...
Tell me what's really going on.
The unwritten rules that had spread in our class
wouldn't work anymore from now on.
Everyone realized that
maybe the days of living in fear
of becoming the next target may now be over.
And so, the curtain came down.
Um, I apologize.
- I'm sorry.
- I apologize.
With words that made it hard to tell
if it was really over at all.
There wasn't one bit of sincerity in that.
It seems we've still got a long way to go.
Mr. Kokubu, is it okay if I don't forgive them?
Just, "apologize and you'll be forgiven,"
with no punishment given.
When I think about
how Chiho had to change schools...
It's too much to forgive.
"Compassion"?
Hmm, I'm kind of drawing a blank.
Is that like "hypocrisy"?
It's like something you need, or what?
"Education" huh?
If only it were as easy as it sounds.
Our job is to "teach" and "raise" students.
Take "raise" out of the equation,
and I would never have gotten involved...
in this whole issue.
Snore snore...
Wheeze...
Hina!
MS. HINATA KAWAMOTO
FROM CHIHO SAKURA
It's from Chiho!
Hina, I'm sorry it's taken me so long
to get back to you.
Right now, I'm studying with a teacher
in a place called a "Heart Care Center."
It's a quiet, pretty area
surrounded by mountains and forests.
There's a ranch and farm next to the center.
They let me help out there sometimes.
This is a baby goat that was born on the ranch.
Her name is Mei.
The dog to my left is Hana.
They always come running over
to see me when I go to the ranch.
They're the first friends I made here.
All of the people on the farm and ranch
are very friendly.
The people in the neighborhood, too.
The other day, we made plum wine,
plum syrup, and plum jam together.
My mom helped too,
and we had a good time.
My dad's office isn't too far from the center,
so he drops me off and picks me up every day.
I'm really happy to have more chances
to talk to him now.
When I first came here, I couldn't get used to
this new place, so I was really lonely.
But then Ms. Satou, my teacher at the center,
taught me the "three steps to making a friend."
You start by making friends with animals.
After you do that, the next step is making friends
with people who are older than you.
And today...
TO MS. SATOU
Ms. Satou said,
"Why don't we move on to the third step?"
The third step is making friends with someone
who's close to your own age.
When I heard that...
I thought about you, Hina.
I really miss you.
When the plum syrup is just right,
I'd like to drink some with you.
I planted corn too.
It'll be ready to pick by August.
I'd like to eat the corn with you.
Will you come and visit me
during summer vacation?
Can I look forward to seeing you?
From Chiho
Small Palm
In the Sun
TSUKUDAKO BRIDGE
Hello!
Pardon me.
She's sleeping.
Wants to go in, but can't.
Unsure if it's okay to enter
a house where a girl's sleeping
Ooph...
Sat down for now...
I wonder why.
For the first time in a while,
it's like she has a soft aura around her.
Like she's faintly glowing...
Feels like I could look at her like this forever.
Rei...
Rei.
Rei!
Apparently nodded off
Summer tangerines!
And so many of them!
My workshop mentor gave them to me.
He picked a ton, so told me to take them.
I can't believe I fell asleep on her doorstep.
Oh, wow!
So many...
Wait, all of them?
What about you, Mr. Shimada?
It grew on your property,
but you won't eat any?
Nah, I have a feeling the acid in the tangerines
would melt through my stomach lining.
There are no pesticides on them,
so you can make jam and stuff.
I can't, though.
HAHAHA...
Jam?
JAM?
OH
Akari.
You're saving me money on groceries again!
I'll make jam!
It smells good.
This'll be great.
Sis's marmalade is delicious.
Just as I thought, she's faintly glowing...
I wonder why.
Kiriyama, actually...
It seems like it's over.
I think it's over.
Probably...
I see. That must be why...
she's glowing.
Cute, aren't they?
We baked them yesterday
at my classmate Kawashima's house.
We're in the same group.
It was me, Kawashima, Kiuchi,
Kobayashi and Kudou, so five of us.
Kawamoto.
So we're going to make cookies today
at Kawashima's house.
Want to join us?
Um...
I'm sorry!
I-I was scared.
That's why I couldn't do anything.
Even if we apologize, we thought that...
you might not forgive us.
But I really wanted to apologize to you.
After that, I changed clothes,
then met up with the girls
at Kawashima's house.
We baked a lot of cookies together.
The cookies turned out hard and misshapen...
What is this? It's awful!
After I said that, we couldn't stop laughing.
While we were laughing, we said,
"Still, cookies right out of the oven are good,"
and we kept on eating them.
I wonder why.
Store-bought cookies taste much better,
but I had such a good time
and was so happy that they were delicious.
Kiriyama, did you know?
When you put a cookie fresh from the oven
to your mouth, it sizzles?
I burned the inside of my mouth.
Look!
Saying that, she innocently
opened her mouth wide.
When I saw the sunlight
on her teeth and tongue,
for some reason
various feelings welled up inside.
I had a tightening sensation in my chest
and felt like I was going to cry.
Hina, I'm sorry.
I...
In the end, I couldn't do anything.
That's right. Even though I promised right here
that I would protect you that day.
Nothing?
Kiriyama...
Even though...
Even though you listened...
to me...
all those times?
Even though you went to Kyoto
to search for me?
Even though you made me so happy?
After all, I wasn't able to...
Ow!
Don't give me, "After all!"
EHHH
B-But I...
No buts!
Kiriyama, you're an idiot!
Ouch!
CHOMP
Oh, that's right! Guess what!
I got a letter from Chiho!
From Chiho? Really?
And then, and then!
During summer vacation,
I'm going to visit her, for sure!
While telling me that, she pulled me
by the hand as if we were dancing,
and started walking at a steady pace.
And to this small heroine who never gave in,
no matter how much she cried or suffered,
I made another promise,
and a little oath of loyalty in my head.
In the Sun
Next Episode Preview
Episode 36
What is this?
What is this poster?
The design is really cool.
It's my fault?!
Yes.
But for some reason,
it doesn't feel real.
Did you tell her that?
It's easy to figure out.
Because you've been listening
to her all this time.
ILLUSTRATION:
AKIO WATANABE
Maybe I'll have Sis tell me
how to make marmalade
so I can make it, too!