I told you not to piss me off!!
This way?
No!
Damn machines!
An electromagnetic field?
So I was caught...
Eat this!
I better get going.
Someone is coming...
Damn!
You...
The butcher?
You're beaten up bad.
I came to rescue you.
Are you all right?
Are you a member of Eleven?
Indeed.
Here they come.
Let's get out of here quick.
I'll stop them here. Go!
Right now!
I am invincible! Don't worry!
Butcher!
My name is Sebastian!
Sebastian!
I am immortal! Oopsy-daisy.
Are they all gone? Okay!
I am a support unit for Eleven.
This one?
My next body will be... Oopsy-daisy.
Okay!
This body's in pretty good shape.
Hey, Old Chap!!
Yes?
What?
Where is that old chap?
The old man is out for other business.
I am new here. Nice to be at your service.
Then you don't know my usual.
Cut me a kilogram of sirloin for steak.
Yes, right away.
You are much friendlier than the old chap.
Thank you for your waiting.
That's the idea.
You don't mess with us.
That's the secret of a long life.
Yes, sir.
I take out the trash for the humans' sake.
In order to build a beautiful,
harmonious society:
something the humans were
not able to accomplish.
Seek, until when do you intend to
neglect the humans in the reserve area?
Humans also evolve just like plants.
They need to be beaten up for that purpose.
Do you know how many other species
the humans have pushed to extinction?
18,392 spiecies to be exact.
We just add Humans to that number.
Is that not perfect victory?
You were born from me.
Just follow my orders.
We'll manage the humans'
numbers and awaken them.
We don't need them.
We machines are enough!
We machines do not understand love.
We need to know what love is.
Without love, no beautiful
society can be built.
Look, even if they are unwise,
Humans have love.
It drives them to evolve better.
Someday, machines and humans will work
together and build an ideal society.
We work for humans.
I don't understand why you
are soft on that girl!
Soft on her? Does it look that way to you?
All right. I'll kill her.
Humans, if not wise, have love.
But the true meaning of love is unknown.
If we find the meaning of love, a
beautiful world will surely emerge.
And for that, we have to
encourage humans to evolve.
I heard you repair guns here.
Oh, boy.
Let's see.
Ah ha. A Wizard Gun, isn't it?
Quite an old one.
How soon can you fix it?
Let's see...
I'll pay any premium. You call it.
Really? That's cool.
You can have it the day
after tomorrow, little lady.
A bounty hunter.
Don't let her go! Out there!