Some villagers lost their
lives in the attack.
We're at war with a raccoon dog.
Thanks to you, Saizo, we kept Isanami
from falling into Ieyasu's hands.
Which is why...
I have a favor to ask of you.
I don't like the sound of that.
I want you to take Isanami
and go to Izumo.
Then what was the point
of keeping her here?
Old man, are you sure you're not crazy?
How dare you call Yukimura-sama crazy?!
Apologize immediately!
Who the hell is he?
How dare you?!
Don't mind him, Kakei.
Yes, sir.
I am Kakei Juzo,
one of Yukimura-sama's men.
Who are you who dares to
speak so rudely to his superiors?
Cut it out, you two.
Kakei has been investigating
why Izumo was attacked.
According to my sources,
Tokugawa stayed in Izumo long after he burned it to the ground.
He destroyed everything,
from the shrine to the treasury
and the priestess' quarters.
What was he so desperate to find?
So that's why he's after
the sole survivor, Isanami.
What was he looking for?
If they haven't found it yet,
it may still be at Izumo.
We'll have to send Isanami to Izumo
because of her familiarity with the area.
She'll never agree to—
I'll go.
Isanami!
I'll get to travel with Saizo, right?
It'll be fun.
Do you understand how
dangerous this will be?
I'll be fine as long as I'm with you.
You heard her. Look after her, Saizo.
The power to destroy all living things...
The Valley of Whirlwinds
H-He's so cute.
Akeha, son of Aoba.
He'll help us keep in touch.
I can take him with me?
Yes.
Thank you, Sasuke.
Sasuke, you're quite good with women.
He's such a shy kid.
You're late!
This is why I hate traveling with women!
Don't tell me he's coming with us.
Kakei has become very familiar with
many regions during his travels.
I've asked him to help
you protect Isanami.
What?!
But I was looking forward
to my trip with Saizo!
I was so excited thinking about it
last night that I couldn't sleep!
We cannot waste any time!
Hurry up!
Go by yourself!
This was supposed to
be my trip with Saizo!
I don't believe this.
I can't believe I'm going back to Izumo.
You never know where life will take you.
You're over it already?
I wouldn't want to ruin our
trip by sulking the whole time.
Get off of me.
Why? What's wrong with it?
What are you doing? Hurry up, Kakei-san.
I refuse to walk with such a slut!
Slut?
That's right!
Young women shouldn't show
off their skin for anyone to see.
Why not?
It's easy to move in these clothes.
That's not the issue!
Ana doesn't cover her chest or legs.
That's also unacceptable!
However, Ana's job as a ninja
requires her to wear those clothes.
Besides, how can you behave so flippantly
on such an important mission?
If it weren't for Yukimura-sama's orders
I would never travel with you.
Look, a candy shop.
Listen to me!
But I wanna sleep in a
bed and take a bath.
Enough whining.
The road to Izumo is long.
We must conserve our resources.
Kakei-san, let's each keep
watch for half the night.
I'll sleep first.
Very well.
I'll sleep with you.
It's so crowded.
Scoot closer, Saizo.
Why are you always like this?
It's so warm.
Shut up and get off me.
Oh, come on.
Stop, stop, stop!
Saizo, come here.
What?
What do you want, Kakei-san?
A-Are you...
Are you and Isanami married?
Huh?
If you are, I apologize for
calling your wife a slut.
Of course we're not!
She just doesn't know
the meaning of shame.
What?
She had a real comfortable
upbringing in Izumo.
She doesn't know the ways of the world.
Saizo, hurry up.
I'll never sleep with you.
Meanie!
Meanie?
Why did Yukimura-sama make
her one of his braves?
Huh?
He didn't tell you?
I need one brave warrior for each
finger on these two hands.
Ten brave warriors.
Sasuke, Rokuro, Anastasia and
me, plus you and Isanami.
You may be disrespectful,
but I can see why
Yukimura-sama chose you.
However, Isanami is just an ordinary girl.
What's wrong?
What are you thinking about?
Who're you calling a brave?
He can't make me be one.
This is ridiculous.
Those snacks were delicious.
I want some soba next.
Okay, okay.
Something's not right.
What is it?
We haven't passed anyone for a while.
You're right.
That person...
Isanami.
Are you all right? Are you hungry?
No.
I sprained my ankle.
That's terrible.
I can't do anything with
this worthless foot.
We cannot leave a woman
here by herself.
Why don't we take her to
the foot of the mountain?
Why me?
Saizo, we can't abandon someone in need.
Can you stand?
Yes, thank you.
Sorry.
You'd die if you fell from here.
It's a long way down, look.
Shut up, I can see it.
Kakei-san?
Are you afraid of heights?
Leave me alone!
What is this wind?
What's wrong, Isanami?
I won't hurt you.
I, Yuri Kamanosuke-sama, will simply take
everything you have of value.
Impersonating a woman is exhausting.
My hips hurt.
A thief.
This woman's got some jade on her.
You're pretty well off, aren't you?
Isanami!
Saizo!
You can't escape from my wind.
Shut up and sit tight.
I noticed you're hiding
weapons all over your body.
You reek of blood, too.
As long as I keep you bound,
this'll be easy, ninja.
Bastard.
Take everything she has.
Do whatever you want with
her when you're done.
Thanks, boss. You're so generous.
A Tanegashima rifle?
Say your prayers.
He's a good shot.
That bastard.
I'll kill him.
What is this wind?
Now, hand over your wealth.
Don't get ahead of yourself, thief.
I'll kill you.
Oh?
Is this girl that important to you?
What're you talking about?
Sorry you won't be able to save her.
Saizo!
Saizo, are you all right?
You don't know what you're talking about.
I'd never make it as a ninja,
if I died to something like this.
Let's get Isanami.
Ow, ow, ow.
Untie me, you jerk!
Quiet, woman.
If you don't shut up,
I'll cut your legs off.
Why are you doing this?
Do you want money?
Money?
I'm looking for a fun
new toy to play with.
A toy? What do you mean?
That ninja was awfully protective of you.
Isn't that just damn peachy?
I'm sure he'll come to rescue you.
I wonder what face he'll make...
...when he watches me
kill you before his eyes?
I've killed lots of people before,
but I think this'll be the most fun I've had.
What's wrong with you?
What are you thinking?
You're crazy!
I get that a lot.
But you shouldn't judge the
hobbies of others so harshly.
Taking from others is my only pleasure.
Hobby? Pleasure?
What do you think people are?
You're a person, too.
Why don't you stop doing this and—
You're so annoying.
Didn't I tell you not to
criticize my hobbies?
Saizo will defeat you.
I just can't deal with
worthless women like you.
You can't do anything for yourself,
but you never shut up.
Girls like you, who rely
on men for everything,
are the least deserving of life.
Now, come quickly...
...ninja.
I don't believe it.
He seems to be making an example of her.
He's probably trying to lure us in.
We need to find a path.
There's already a path.
The shortest route's right in front of us.
Saizo...
What am I doing? I must look stupid.
First she gets kidnapped,
and now I'm climbing a cliff.
A lookout can't let his guard down.
Ana.
Are you really that worried about them?
I hate Iga ninja, but he is strong.
He will become stronger and return.
What, you like men?
No!
I have faith.
Faith, huh?
That's a nice word.
It's a funny word, though.
When that trust is betrayed...
He's here.
Yo.
You chose quite the
location for your castle.
What are you, king of the mountain?
You look ridiculous.
Hurry on up here before
something terrible happens.
See?
You bastard!
Moron.
Saizo...
What's a ninja doing charging in head on?
How far did you fall?
Did you die?
I get it.
You're an absolutely terrible guy.
Two can play that game!
I like that look.
Yes, that's it.
That's the sort of man you are.
The smell of blood, those eyes...
Those eyes have seen deep darkness.
You've killed as many...
No, more than me, haven't you?
Are you out of gas?
Your back's wide open!
That hurt!
Bring it on.
A bloodthirsty man like you...
...isn't meant to escort a
woman on her little trip.
Don't you enjoy the sight of blood?
Don't you enjoy stealing?
Don't you enjoy killing?!
Let's have some fun together.
Shut up and die.
That sounds like fun.
Om Marici Yeh Svaha!
Shunko!
Otsumuji!
You're not done yet, are you?
Huh?
What?
Isanami!
Impossible.
You're too fast. I didn't even see it.
What is this?
I'm dripping something warm.
It's just as I thought.
I can't get enough of those eyes.
They don't waver at the sight of blood.
You're completely emotionless.
All you do is kill.
It's amazing, amazing,
unbelievably amazing!
I'm almost there, you bastard.
My body's getting cold.
This euphoria...
Give it to me.
Plunge that sword into me
and send me over the edge.
No!
He can't fight any more.
Don't do this.
But the things he did to you...
I'm fine, see?
And you came here to
save me, didn't you?
Saizo!
Are you shitting me?!
It was just getting good.
Hurry up and kill me!
Killing women leaves a
bad taste in my mouth.
What? Who are you calling a woman?
Live and turn yourself
over to the officials.
You idiot! I'll never
do something like that!
Kill me now. Kill me right now!
Hey! Hey, you!
Damn it!
You are quite reckless.
One mistake and Saizo would
have cut you instead.
I trust Saizo.
What a woman.
She's more trouble than she's worth.
But she saved you.
I'm the one who was rescued.
Is that so?
He can't take any more, huh?
Ieyasu's tyranny is quite extreme.
He won't let this one go.
Will Ishida-dono move?
He must be at his limit
if he's sending me this.
This information cannot get out.
Copy it, Rokuro.
As you wish.
How useful.
Either way,
we'll have to take care of
the business at Izumo first.
...ran to hide in the tea jar, crash!
As it broke, away he ran.
The little mouse stole our rice, squeak!
All that action made me hungry.
Let's get something to eat.
Our funds aren't endless. Suck it up.
What?
Oh, I know.
I'll send Akeha to get more
money from Yukimura-sama—
Shut up. Kakei-san will hear you.
No! Absolutely not!
This is not a sightseeing trip.
Just ignore your growling stomach.
You require more training, Saizo.
What? Me?
The next episode of Brave 10 is
"The Souls of the Gods."
Bring it on!
The Souls of the Gods