Your newbie hasn't quit yet?
Nope, he's hanging in there.
Oh?
I'm a good judge of character,
regardless of what you may think.
Yeah, right.
Everyone younger than Sakaki-kun quit.
Oh, it's here. Right here.
Is this a crime?
I don't know.
Is it in our jurisdiction?
Yeah, probably.
Yeah...
But my request to investigate
the scene keeps getting rejected.
And if you get us involved,
that problem will go away?
Yeah, that's about right.
June 13th
Nocturnal Community Relations Section
You want us to investigate the north
and south elevators at City Hall?
We got official permission.
#5 "The Parallel World Elevator of
the City Hall Observation Deck"
Finally, huh?
What's going on?
It's an urban legend that's been going around!
The Parallel World Elevator.
You've at least heard of it, right?
Um... No.
Listen, when you're in this line of work,
you've gotta keep an ear to the ground!
Search for it online. You'll find it right away.
Sorry...
Someone posted to our occult message board
saying that somebody went up
to the City Hall observation deck,
and ended up in another world.
"Our"?
Yeah. I made it.
I went up the observation deck in City Hall and ended up in another world lololol
Anonymous, Lost in a Parallel Dimension
Oh shit. No idea where I am.
I went up to the observation deck and everybody disappeared. It's just me.
Anonymous, Lost in a Parallel Dimension
>>0002 Which observation deck?
>>0003 City Hall. Tokyo.
Anonymous, Lost in a Parallel Dimension
The poster kept a running
account of what was going on,
before they simply stopped posting.
The rumors say he probably went missing.
Ever since then, small numbers
of other people have appeared,
saying the same thing happened to them.
Some were clearly trolling,
but for the others, it's not so clear...
The number of rumors is increasing.
The police are looking for the missing people.
But why are we sticking our noses in it, then?
Well, there's been something else happening...
She disappeared!
At first I thought she was a victim
of the Parallel World Elevator, too...
She's back?
With no visible injuries.
She simply lost her memories
of her time in the observatory.
And there's several other similar reports.
Missing persons and missing memories, huh?
Which means there're
two Anothers at City Hall?
Maybe.
I don't want to think about it, but...
Sakaki-kun's just gone to meet
with the girl and hear her story.
June 13th
It seems they're acquainted.
So, I remember getting to
the south observation deck,
but the next thing I knew, I was at
the north deck for some reason!
I was so shocked!
Anything else unusual?
You're kidding!
Kyo-chan, you're not scared
of the occult at all, huh?
Has anyone you know
experienced anything similar?
A friend of mine once told me that
she'd gotten into the north elevator
and ended up in some weird
place where she saw a woman.
Like in that urban legend.
And your friend remembered this?
Besides the fact that you lost your memories,
nothing else happened, right, Aoi?
I can't think of anything.
Listen, Aoi.
What is it? You look so serious...
Did you make up with him?
Your boyfriend.
No, I didn't.
Oh, that's right.
There's a new girl at work
who I think is a good match for you.
How about I throw a mixer?
June 13th
So, learn anything from Aoi-chan?
Aoi-chan?
A customer from when I was a host.
I see.
I didn't get much in the way of clues.
There's one thing that bothered me, though.
Let's break up...
She had a boyfriend
she was thinking of marrying.
But just the other day, he broke up with her.
However, when I met her, she didn't
seem at all bothered by it.
You don't think she just got over it?
No...
It was more like she'd forgotten it.
So she lost her memories of being engaged?
She remembered her boyfriend, and the breakup.
But it was like she'd lost the memories
of being depressed or the sadness she'd felt.
That's how it felt to me.
Either way, first, we need to examine the scene.
June 13th
Tokyo City Hall Building 1, First Floor
Well, Theo?
No sign of any crests or spells...
So it's not likely artificial, then.
Artificial?
Like incorporating magic into the elevator
itself into make into some kind of device.
What does that mean?
For example, if a believer in
a god, or what we call an Another,
created a magical gate
to offer their deity sacrifices.
The victims would have no idea what happened
as they passed through the gate
and right to the Another's presence.
The data we have made it seem like it happens
when you leave the elevator
to go into the observation deck.
So, we should go up?
Theo, head up to the south
deck and take a look.
Miyako and I will take
a look at the north deck.
Roger.
Pray for me, so I don't
end up in a parallel world.
That's not funny...
Nothing.
Nope.
Up it is, then.
Right.
June 14th
Um,
the missing persons and missing
memories cases are occurring at random
in both the north and south elevators, right?
Yeah. We don't know what makes them happen.
Why would someone do that?
No idea.
The goals of the Anothers
are beyond our comprehension.
June 14th
Okay, let's go.
So this is the Parallel World?
I'm looking for something.
Give what you have to me.
Shinjuku Ward
Nope, nothing.
The hell?
Okay, Arata, then.
Did they end up going to that other world?
Nah, no way.
June 14th
No, no, no.
Kyoichi! Arata!
Maybe...
They did?
Give them to me.
Hey, do you know what she's saying?
"Give them to me."
Give what?
No idea.
Oh?
What you have...
That's not it!
Oh, no! Did I make a mistake?
A mistake?
What about you?
You have nothing.
You've got nothing to do with this!
You made contact with
this human at the entrance
and came with him, it feels like.
Contact at the entrance?
Was it then?
How many times has this happened?
Maybe when you prioritize efficiency,
you become less accurate.
Efficiency? Accurate?
You're human, aren't you?
But you understand what I'm saying?
Uh... yeah.
I'm talking with a human! How wonderful!
Since you're here, I'd like to talk to you.
Huh? Talk to me?
Come on. This way.
Huh? Wait...
Hey, Miyako!
I don't need you anymore.
No—
S-Sakaki-san!
Kyoichi! Kyoichi!
Kyoichi!
What happened?
Where's Arata?
She got him.
She controls that space.
We went to another world, and I was sent back.
I made a mistake...
Sakaki-san? No...
He was in the way, so I got rid of him.
Is he okay?
I just sent him back outside.
Now we can talk, can't we?
What are you doing?
Looking for something.
Looking for something?
Yes.
I'm gathering the things
that escaped from this box.
So she has nothing to do with the
disappearances and the missing memories?
I use that device to tell me who has
what I'm looking for and who doesn't.
Only those who have it are sent to me.
But when I set it to send me more
people, it started making mistakes.
It started sending people who
only had something similar.
Similar?
Similar to what you're looking for?
Yes. The man you were with held a tremendous
sense of loss, and that tripped the device.
I'm looking for a sense of loss, too.
But of a slightly different sort.
A sense of loss? Sakaki-san?
Any luck, Theo?
I kept trying,
which means there needs to be some
condition met that we don't have.
Shit!
We're stuck.
Hey, where are you going?
Hey!
This box once contained many things.
Bad things. Sad feelings. Diseases and crimes.
All sorts of things.
So I was told not to open it...
But when I cracked it open
just a bit, they all flew off.
It was my mistake.
Some of the box's contents,
feelings of loss in love,
fell here in Asia.
Why are you collecting lost
loves in a City Hall elevator?
City Hall?
I don't know anything about human buildings.
I make paths to this place in all
the places that meet my needs.
Then there are other elevators
in Asia that lead here, too?
Here, just wait a minute.
I hope this one isn't a mistake.
Good. This one is right.
I'm taking your feelings of lost love.
Thank you.
Now, you may return.
You're just going home.
Just as you came.
When you wake up,
you'll be where you wish to be.
That girl had a pretty big stock.
It may be time to go.
I've almost recovered enough lost love,
so next I'm going to Europe
to recover jealousy.
Does that mean you're leaving City Hall?
I told you, it triggers when
you leave the elevator.
Calm down.
You're our leader.
I need to bring back Miyako...
Let's call Reiji-kun and come up with a plan.
We won't get anywhere at this rate.
Oh, Reiji-kun?
We've got problems...
Hey!
Kyoichi! Wait!
It's really so much more
wonderful when it's filled.
But this box was essentially my dowry!
Izumi
When are you turning on your phone?!
Izumi?
So it's weird that they'd
tell me not to open it, right?
I can send messages!
How does it make any sense for me
to not open my own dowry?
Can't take... any more...
I'm calling Reiji-kun
regardless of what you say.
Maybe I can call him.
No way. The barrier probably blocks out voice.
Theo
I'm hungry
Miyako Arata
Sakaki-san, are you okay?
What's going on?
I couldn't get through on the phone!
The posts from the other world!
That's right!
That guy was posting on his
phone from another world!
What's your status?
Miyako Arata
Talking with the Another.
I don't seem to be in danger.
You probably caught a glimpse of it,
but the bad things in the box are...
"She has nothing to do with the missing
people or missing memories."
What's your situation?
Nocturnal Community Relations Section (4)
Talking with the Another.
I don't seem to be in danger.
She has nothing to do with the missing
people or missing memories.
She's just collecting feelings of lost love.
Feelings of lost love?
What the hell?
The lost memories are her doing.
The weird thing I felt when I talked to Aoi...
Her feelings of lost love were stolen.
An Another that steals emotions.
If they fly out of the box again,
I have to gather them up...
Um...
When you take their feelings of lost
love, do you take their memories?
Memories?
She says she doesn't know...
She probably really doesn't know.
She's not doing it deliberately.
She doesn't care if someone
finds her or sees her face.
That's why she left my memories.
But if she's responsible
for the missing memories,
then is there another Another somewhere else?
No, wait.
There are no missing people?
We were able to ID that message
board poster and get a hold of him.
There was no missing
person report filed on them.
They said they remembered going to City Hall,
but had no memory of making the posts.
I see where this case is going...
The person was believed to have gone missing
because they stopped posting after that.
But if, like the ones who lost their memories,
he forgot what happened in the other world,
he wouldn't be able to keep posting.
Nobody went missing at all, then...
So the missing people and missing
memories were all your fault.
Is it possible for you to stop?
Stop what?
Looking for what you want with that elevator!
Why?
People want to use that elevator to go places!
Well, it's not a problem for me.
No, not you. Other people!
Why do I have to stop looking for what I want
because it's causing a problem for people?
There's no reason.
What will you do if they
demand your life in exchange?
You should learn more about
the scary parts of Anothers.
Just because I can talk to them doesn't
mean we understand each other.
Anothers and humans can't...
Um...
I'm leaving.
I see. What a shame.
Come back again.
I'll make it so you can come
here any time you like.
Um... One last thing.
What's your name?
Name?
Humans call me, "Pandora."
Pandora? Box...
Pandora's Box?
There's nothing more coming.
She's just collecting feelings of lost love.
She says she doesn't know...
I'm coming back.
Miyako!
Arata!
I'm back...
Hey, are you okay? Are you hurt?
You didn't make any promises with the
Another, or take anything from them, right?
N-No, nothing like that...
Miyako.
I'm sorry.
I should've been more careful.
No, that's not true...
Well, Arata's okay. So it all worked out.
We're packing up for the day.
Let's write our report and go.
Yeah, you're right.
I'm going right to sleep when I get home.
We should eat first.
Where's Miyako?
He'll be here soon.
Oh, hello there.
Hey.
Oh, right.
I read the report.
One Another was responsible
for both cases, huh?
Sounds like a long night.
What good are the Ears of Sand?
Even if I can talk to the Anothers,
I couldn't resolve anything...
Our job isn't to find the big solutions.
You came back safe, and the Another
at City Hall is going to leave.
The case is over.
Oh, Yokoyama-san?
The matter at City Hall's been resolved.
Oh, sure. I can pay you back
by taking you out to eat...
There's one thing I couldn't put in the report.
That Sakaki-san's sense of loss
is what brought us to Pandora.
Sakaki-san's sense of tremendous loss...
Unsolved Missing Girl Cases in Tokyo
What could it be?
#6 "Devil and Sense of Loss"