Everybody on the continent,
we have emergency news!
The tri-country alliance has launched
an emergency attack in response
to the news that demons have appeared
to the south, in the "Dragon's Forest".
Right now, air and land forces from
Biscotti, Galette, and Pastillage
are heading to attack the demons.
This is not a game.
It's a tri-country alliance
attack on the demons!
The tri-country broadcasting federation
will keep you as up to date as we can!
Decisive Battle! The Dragon's Forest!
Biscotti forces are in place.
Pastillage forces are, as well.
Galette forces, too.
Okay, I'll go over where we are right now.
The demon we're attacking
is known as the "Dragon Eater".
It invades the land, the
plants and the creatures,
and makes copies of itself.
It's a dangerous parasite-type demon.
Any animals it eats become part of it,
and become branches that send
nutrients to the main dragon eater.
It's bad enough that
many animals are being attacked, but...
The True Dragons which control
the power of nature live here.
If they're attacked and controlled,
it could cause a huge disaster.
Not just for this forest
or the surrounding areas,
but potentially the whole continent.
So we and the Dragon Priestess
will work together
to protect the true dragons
and destroy the dangerous demon.
Don't worry.
The rulers of the Three
Countries and their Heroes
all have their treasure swords.
Once again it's time
for the three countries to come together!
Today it's not a war game
to entertain everyone.
It's a war to protect everyone.
Everybody!
Let's all do our best!
We will protect the True Dragons.
Galette will protect the
Fire Dragon at the Volcano.
Biscotti will protect the
Thunder Dragon at the Spring.
Pastillage will protect the
Harvest Dragon in the forest!
And the Heroes will use their high speed
to hunt down the demon along
with the Dragon Priestess.
Yeah!
Priestess...
Forgive us for allowing humans to run free
in the Dragon's Forest.
It's to keep this forest
and the continent safe.
Please allow it for a short time.
All right.
It's here.
Okay!
No!
Take this! Seven Tale!
Are you two okay?
I guess.
These tentacles are slimy and nasty...
There they are.
Demons sighted. There's an
incredible number of them.
We'll attack first!
Archers, ready!
Pastillage Sky Knights Squad Two is
beginning combat with the flyers!
Biscotti's main force has
deployed their defenses.
The Pastillage Air Force is in combat
with approximately 800 demons!
An army of demons has appeared
in front of the Galette camp!
1500 more!
More and more keep appearing.
There are about 10,000 in the allied armies,
so we still have the advantage, but...
If the number of demons goes above that...
It's okay.
We'll find the main demon before that!
Maintain defensive formation!
Only attack the demons that charge!
Yes, sir!
Hero Crystal... activate!
Here I go!
I'll crush you all!
Yukikaze-style Ninjutsu!
Senka Reppuu!
Eclair, are you okay?
Yukki!
I'm sorry I'm late!
Sorry about this.
You're taking something
to the Heroes, right?
Fire support, second round, go!
Fire!
All right!
The chief's opened a path!
Oh no!
The True Dragons are crying!
True Dragon-san.
The True Dragons are starting
to turn into demons.
Stopping that from happening is our job.
It's okay.
I won't let you turn into Demons!
I'm sorry.
Please don't blame me for this.
Princess.
Lightning Dragon-san, I'll save you soon.
So hang in there.
You must be suffering,
but hang in just a little while longer.
Just stay there!
Lion King Exploding Thunder Slash!
Hurry, Heroes!
Can you see this?
The battle is already getting fierce!
The light you just saw near the volcano
was probably Leo's...
The flyers have a wide range.
Squad Eight, lead the
reporters down to a safe altitude!
Okay!
Wow.
The humans are standing up to Dragons...
Those are our rulers,
and we're very proud of them!
It's the ruler's job to protect the country.
And it's the Hero's job to save the country
when it's in danger and bring
smiles and happiness to everyone.
I want everybody to smile,
so I'll do my best!
We found the Dragon Eater.
Hero Rebecca, climb!
Right!
If I can finish him...
They just keep coming...
There's no end to them.
I hope the Heroes can do something soon.
I agree.
We need to help her.
You go in from above, Shinku!
I'll kill those roots from below!
Got it!
There's no end to this!
I'm sorry.
Are you okay, Priestess?
Yeah.
They won't hit anymore.
So focus on aiming.
If everybody's in trouble...
I have to do it!
This is Shinku's...
Hero Crystal...
Activate!
Hero Time!
Flame King Sword!
Shinku!
Yukki!
I'm so glad you're safe!
Yukki... I can't breathe!
Oh, sorry.
Did you bring me that Hero Crystal?
I carried it part of the way,
but it just flew off on its own.
The Hero Crystal must've
wanted to see its master.
Yeah.
Everybody's in trouble.
We have to go help them.
Yeah.
We'll bring these crystals to
Rebecca and Nanami.
I'll get closer!
Shinku!
Becky!
Take this!
A Demon God Crystal...
As long as I have this...
Demon God Crystal, Activate!
This is my Hero Crystal?
It's a little different than the others.
Adel-sama prepared it for you.
She says its a Spirit Crystal!
Okay, here I go then!
Spirit Crystal, activate!
The transformation's complete?
It's the power of water and ice,
to let you walk with the flames
and thunder of Leo-sama.
Right!
Fierce battles are still being
reported all around the area!
Meanwhile, the demon itself seems
to be getting bigger and bigger.
Couver-sama?
It's probably absorbing the power
of the Dragons and the land.
At this rate, it will absorb
the power of the land.
It's okay. Don't worry.
Our Heroes will stop it!
It's okay!
The Heroes will finish this soon!
Bullet card: full open!
Go!
Sharl!
It's beautiful...
What is this light?
The power of the land and the dragons
that the Dragon Eater absorbed.
It's coming down from the sky
and going back to the land.
A light of purification and renewal.
It's the phenomenon known
as the Dragon's Tears.
I've heard of this.
Joy and blessings come to the land
where the Dragon's Tears fall.
Yeah...
But
this rain of light is
a little bit odd.
Any equipment or clothes
enchanted with guardian power
that it touches will react, well...
Like that.
That's a big problem!
I'm sure chaos is breaking
out everywhere, but...
Well, it's not going to hurt you.
Actually, it's good for you, so don't worry.
You heard her.
Let's go to Flan-san in the sky.
Yes, I'm here in the sky!
The demon has completely shut down,
and the black clouds above the
forest are gradually clearing up!
The war against the demons seems to be
ending with a victory for
the tri-country alliance!
I caused you a lot of trouble.
Not at all.
Are the dragons okay?
No need to worry.
Eventually they'll wake up and
everything will go back to normal.
The forest should be even
more bountiful than before.
I'm glad.
Hero Shinku...
I...
Looks like it's over.
Just like I thought,
there was nothing for us to do.
It's a sign that the new
generation is growing up right.
But we need to seal it properly,
so that it doesn't revive as a sad demon...
Eventually I'll teach
that to Yukikaze and Noir
and the others.
Thanks to the Dragon Priestess Sharl,
and the heroes of the tri-country alliance,
the forest was saved.
All knights and soldiers who fought,
well done!
The response team is going to
seal the demon we defeated.
We'll be leaving now.
Once we get back, we'll have a detailed report
for the citizens and other countries.
Okay, let's get ready to go!
You're leaving already, aren't you?
Yeah.
If you like...
Can we come back to play?
You shouldn't.
You'll get lost.
Once I'm sure the forest has calmed down...
I'll go see you.
Let's meet again,
Hero Shinku.
The summoning accident surprised me,
but I guess it worked out for the best.
It was a huge mess involving
all three countries,
but you could say we discovered
the problem fast.
Well, now it's finally back to
our peaceful, everyday lives.
I've got places for us to
go eat, and things to see.
I've got a whole plan laid out.
Okay!
It's going to be busy today,
but starting tomorrow,
we can go back to our original
plan of relaxing with everybody!
Yeah!
Princess...
Once again, I'm back.
I was so worried.
I'm truly glad that you're safe.
Once we get back, let's relax, okay?
I want to go on a walk.
Of course! Every day!
Let's all have a baked sweet potato
party to celebrate our victory!
We'll cook meat, too!
Chomp, chomp!
It's so good!
What's Passed On
See you next time!