Flower of Light
Yuzuki!
Please, hear me out.
Wait.
I promise.
A week from now, we'll launch
fireworks from the lake.
Yuzuki!
You need help, right?
Here are some phone books.
Wow!
I thought you might need more
than just Kiriyako City.
Feel free to use the phone, too.
Thanks.
No,
I have to thank you.
I thought there was nothing
that I could do about Yuzuki.
Koharu.
So I have to say thank you.
Fireworks
Hello?
I'd like to ask...
Yes.
Hokkaido pyrotechnicians
Could you please make an exception?
Yes.
I see.
No.
Sorry for bothering you.
Hanazawa Chamber of Commerce
Kumano City Community Union
Yamagishi Corporation
Minami-machi Ltd.
Sawamura Fireworks Group
Kabato-ya
What are you doing here while
you're making others do your job?
I'm thankful.
Sure, but...
Firework technicians
* Budget
* Labor
City permission
* Contact City Hall
* Ask Tourism Union for assistance
Closed
Sorry to keep you so late.
Don't worry about it.
I don't want to give
up partway anymore.
Koharu.
I hope we get permission
for the fireworks.
Yeah.
Yuzuki, the bath's free.
Damn, she's not here.
No Saucer
Fireworks Set
That kid.
Can we talk?
Yuzuki!
Listen to me!
Sou—
What?
Be quick if you want to say something.
I'm busy, unlike you.
Enough already.
You're never going to
get rid of the saucer.
Komiya was desperate.
What?
Trying to launch fireworks
even though it's futile...
She even has Koharu involved.
I bet you—
It has nothing to do with me.
Sorry.
I apologize.
You've been angry at me, haven't you?
Because I didn't listen to you back then.
Why?
Sorry.
Because—
Why are you apologizing?
Stupid Souta!
Hey!
Yuzuki.
I guess it'll be tough while
the saucer is still here.
We still have time.
Let's come ask again.
Yeah, you're right.
Nonoka!
Noel.
Nonoka.
Salisbury steak.
Okay.
Fireworks?
We get to see fireworks?
If we get permission.
Fireworks! Fireworks!
Hey, Nonoka.
What're fireworks?
Time to eat!
It's so good!
Fireworks go up high in
the sky, and go like this.
Like this?
Pssh!
Boom!
Those are fireworks?
Yeah, from the festival
seven years ago.
They had fireworks at the lake.
They're so sparkly.
Pretty!
Pssh! Boom! Crackle, crackle, crackle.
Like that?
Yup.
Noel,
if you want, I'll lend you my album.
Really?
Just this once.
Thanks.
Noel, be careful!
What are you doing, Koharu?
Hurry up and eat.
Storage
Okay.
Found it.
I still had it.
Hey, Yuzuki.
See you tomorrow.
Stop it already.
You can't make fireworks
happen in a week.
I won't stop.
Why?
The saucer's still there.
You can't do it.
Because it was a promise.
Y-You just made that up.
So what about fireworks?
Did you think I would be happy if
you could launch fireworks?
No.
At first, I wanted you to see them.
But now it's different.
I want to see fireworks.
With the same people as back then.
Together.
Why?
Stop being selfish.
Yuzuki!
Yuzuki, let's go.
We made a promise.
Yeah.
Yuzuki!
Where are you, Yuzuki?
Souta!
Souta, where are you?
It's tomorrow, isn't it?
Are you coming, too, Togawa-san?
I'll go.
If the fireworks are happening.
Make sure you come.
Yuzuki.
I want to talk.
You're...
Noel?
I didn't think you'd
ever talk to me again.
Is that why you're hanging
out with Nonoka now?
No, all of us have been
together since way back.
No!
Nonoka doesn't know what
happened seven years ago.
Yet she wants to launch fireworks.
What an idiot!
I don't think Nonoka thought
what you were doing was stupid.
What did you actually
want to talk about?
I...
This is delicious.
I wish Nonoka would make me some.
I've been wanting to ask.
What's your relationship with Nonoka?
Relationship?
I'm asking you where
and when you met her.
She taught me a song on a snowy day.
What?
Want me to sing?
Please don't.
Don't dodge my questions.
Besides, it hasn't snowed since
Nonoka came back to this town.
You know a lot about Nonoka.
You're good friends.
Of course not.
Why aren't you friends anymore?
Because Nonoka is a liar.
A huge liar.
Let's eat together.
You'll smile if you eat delicious things.
Hey—
I...
Why did you go off without telling
anyone in the middle of the night?
No reason, really.
I just got myself hurt.
No.
That's not it.
That's not true.
It was because of...
Because of...
Yuzuki?
It's nothing.
Yuzuki!
Are you okay, Nonoka?
Sorry I'm acting this way,
even though you're helping me out.
I trust you.
I think you should finish
doing what you believe in.
Thanks, Koharu.
Oh, it's you.
Sorry, about that...
I'm here with a different request today.
Oh, I have to go now.
What's wrong?
I made a promise to my friends
to meet my them at the pier
when the fireworks start.
I can go, right, Mom?
All right, but...
Thank you.
I'm going.
Okay, be careful.
Koharu, the shop's
going to be busy today.
Don't go off to the
festival by yourself.
Okay.
Koharu.
Sorry I'm late.
Koharu!
Huh?
Switch spots.
You came.
Just so you know,
I don't know about Yuzuki.
It's up to her.
Okay.
Thanks, Souta.
So, what are we doing?
I knew it.
Liar.
I wanted to go.
Aren't you going?
The fireworks aren't even happening.
Sorry, it has nothing to do with you.
That's not true.
I'm happy when you're all smiling.
Aren't you?
See!
Nonoka's smiling lots!
That's...
I see.
She hasn't forgotten.
What's wrong, Yuzuki?
Hey, Noel?
Am I smiling?
Yeah.
Thanks.
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan.
Fall Festival
This poster's from way back.
You're late.
I... I...
Sorry, Yuzuki, we couldn't do fireworks.
No, you shouldn't be apologizing.
It's because of—
Yuzuki!
I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry!
I've always wanted to apologize.
To you, to Koharu, and to Onii-chan.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry...
So all we have are these
sparklers that I brought.
Shut up.
Mine soaked up a ton of
moisture over the past seven years.
What could I do?
Too bad Togawa-san isn't here.
Sparklers are cute.
Pssh.
I know.
Boom.
Look, look.
I'm really, really...
Next episode of Celestial
Method: "True Friends."
Enjoy.
True Friends