Again, huh?
Episode 10
Slight Fever
I hear Ohana's been
getting up really early
these past few days.
Yeah, when I arrive in the morning,
the entrance is already clean.
She's taking the initiative to
clean early every day, huh...
Yes.
Even the duckboards, the window
frames, and the wooden floors.
By herself?!
Oh, and she cleans the front desk, too.
And you didn't stop her?
I didn't want to take
the fight out of her.
So, why was she collapsed
on the hallway...?
No idea.
Umm...
Anyway, let's let her rest for a while.
Yeah.
Okay.
How was she?
She was asleep.
Has her fever gone down?
The doctor said that her fever
might stay a bit for
the rest of the day.
Oh...
But apparently, after she
rests for the entire day,
she should be able to work tomorrow.
Oh...
She was just overworked, he says.
She's been working really hard lately.
Perhaps I should cook
something for her.
Minko, have Tohru teach
you more about broiling.
Okay!
Rice porridge, maybe?
Here.
Give it back!
Try and get it back.
How about something like this?
What?!
First, the Madam Manager, and
now, one of the waitresses?!
What's wrong with this inn?!
Listen, Saturday is an important
day for the Kissuiso!
Taking care of your own body is
a part of being a professional!
Well, umm...
Yes?
Ohana was working hard for
the sake of Kissuiso...
What?
Even though this inn is small,
you need to put effort
into risk management-
Right, risk management.
Risk management is a
very important skill.
Thankfully, the Madam Manager
was ill the other day,
which led to a good experi-
I mean, a very unfortunate event.
So even you have something
good to say every once in
a while, Miss Kawajiri.
So you were listening, Mom?
"Madam Manager."
I have no hidden agenda.
That's right.
We shouldn't let what we learned the
other day go to waste.
What we learned the other day?
To do your job accurately.
Oh.
Yup.
Serial TV Drama
The Hotel King
That's for the Moon Room, right?
Could you bring two bottles
of oolong tea and two
cups to the Wave Room?
Even though it's your first
time doing it yourself,
you've watched me broil
fish before, right?
Yes.
Then go for it.
Yo.
The customers in the
Camellia Room don't need chicken, right?
Yup, that's right.
Hey, we don't need that much fire!
I'm sorry.
This is how it's done.
Demon Disturbance?
What?
Nothing.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
Anyway, I'm sorry to ask you of this
when you're still a bit sick,
but I was hoping you might be
willing to listen to my new work.
Did you know that there's a theory that
hearing sexual words
invigorates your brain
and makes you livelier?
Okay, here we go.
"The Wet Madam Manager
at the Gambling Den."
This is how it begins, but...
Is this supposed to
be a "get-well visit"
to a sick person's room, Mr. Jiromaru?
The red lanterns reflect
upon the lustrous canal.
On the back of the woman who held
two dice and a jar in her hand
were two more dice. Snake eyes.
The shades and stray hair that go
from those pink shoulders to her nape.
The portion between the
bottom of her kimono
and her white socks caught
the attention of the men.
Excuse me...
Is the Madam Manager supposed
to be the model for this?
Crane Room... sandwich... with ham...
Yes...?
Oh, you can get up now?
Making me cook food for sick people...
It might still be hot, so be careful.
It's delicious...
Of course it is.
There's no other sick person food in
the world with such good broth.
Yeah.
Wow, strawberries...
Oh, those are from Minko.
You've still got a fever, right?
Let me feel your forehead.
I-I'm not really sure.
Maybe I'm also a bit feverish.
I added ham for the sandwiches
for the Crane Room.
That's what you'd asked for, right?
Oh well.
You're okay now, Ohana?!
Nakochi.
Well, I need to be getting to work.
Sick people don't need
to think of such things!
What?
What do you mean, "what"?
See?
You're still not well enough to work.
You need to sleep.
It's cold and good.
Right?
This is what we always feed my brothers
whenever they have a fever.
The younger one
catches colds on purpose
just to eat this.
Nakochi.
You're like an older sister.
I really am an older sister.
I...
I need to be working, too.
It's fine.
We're doing fine without you.
Tomoe and I ran everything together
before you came here, remember?
Get well soon, okay?
I'll stop by later to check up on you.
The Kissuiso can run without me?
How many times have
I been escorted back to my bed today...
You should get
the hint that we want you to rest, then.
Her nape...
her stray hair...
What was the other one?
The portion between her
skirt and her socks?
Ko...
Come home, Ohana.
The Kissuiso will be fine without you.
Ko...
Send Text
To: Ko
Ko.
Ko, I think I'm going to
Rice porridge with broth, huh?
Minko, you still have the fish
bones you separated this morning?
Yes.
She looked like she was really
enjoying the rice porridge,
so I figured we might be able
to serve it to the customers.
Oh yeah,
Minko.
I think she liked your
strawberries... too...?
It needs some minor adjustments.
Let's do this.
Right.
To: Ko
I can't really move my body very well.
Your body was glowing.
Kissuiso has good staff,
and it's not like an ordinary person
like me can just take a position here.
Could you bring this fruit
medley and guide map
to the Wisteria Room?
Okay.
Nako.
Yes?
Are you okay?
I don't want you to
overwork yourself too.
I'm fine.
I need to pick up Ohana's slack, too.
Because, remember? Before she got here,
us two were doing everything.
So you're saying you don't
need Ohana anymore, huh?
You've grown up, Nako.
Th-That's not what I...
Please enjoy your stay.
Say...
Y..Yes?
What happened to the
waitress from yesterday?
I haven't been seeing her around.
Oh, Ohana isn't feeling
very well right now.
Oh, so her name is Ohana.
She just has a slight fever.
You shouldn't worry too much.
You two make such a good team.
You seem to like each other so much.
And you're both so lively,
that it makes breakfast
taste even better.
Thank you!
That was a good bath.
Yeah, I feel refreshed!
Look, I'm all wrinkly!
Wow!
What are you being so scared for?!
I-I'm sorry!
You touch the fish too much.
You need to minimize that.
I'm sorry.
Minchi!
It's too early in the
morning to be yelling.
I-I'm sorry!
What's up, Nako?
Ohana collapsed!
What?!
Minchi...
You looked like you were
really enjoying your sleep.
I feel a bit more relieved.
You were worried about me?
Don't worry, the inn is running okay.
What? What's wrong?!
I'm glad...
The Kissuiso can run without me, right?
No-
No.
That's not true.
Huh?
It's not true.
You tried to get rid
of the bat in the hall
to the bath by yourself, didn't you?
Madam Manager told "you
girls" to get rid of it.
"You girls" refers to you, Nako, and I.
Nako can't stand bats,
so it's up to us.
You can't do everything by yourself!
But I can't do it by myself, either.
I need your help.
Okay?!
Once you're better,
we need to think of a plan
to get rid of the bat!
O-Okay.
Ohana? I'm coming in.
You're here, Minchi.
Don't turn the TV on.
Huh?
But isn't it lonely when you wake up
and you don't hear any voices?
I've got a large family,
so it's really lonely for me.
Hey, the customers in the
Wisteria Room said
that breakfast served
by you is really good.
Come on!
You shouldn't be playing with your
phone when you've got a fever.
To: Ko
I can't really move my body very well.
Your body was glowing.
Kissuiso has good staff,
and it's not like an ordinary person
like me can just take a position here.
This place should be fine without
Huh?
What's...
No!
That's not true, Ohana!
There are times I honestly feel like
we can't afford to lose anyone!
But today, you were out, and
for some miraculous reason,
things weren't  hectic
and our jobs were done.
I hope this isn't the end
of the world or something.
But, but, it doesn't mean
that we don't need that person!
It means that since that person
is so important to us,
we work harder to fill in her gap!
So we really want that person back!
N...Nako
Sorry.
Geez...
Looks like she didn't hear you.
Huh?
W-What?
Have you decided?
I love this place.
I love the Kissuiso.
I see.
I love everyone here.
Okay.
What ya doin'?
Ohana went looking for a fight?!
Ohana!
Help me...
Help me, Ko!
Episode 11
Bark at the Night