Let's create beautiful
harmonies together, Wakana.
Wakana!
Wakana?
Hey, Wakana!
Dad?
You all right?
Are you hurt?
Should I call an ambulance?
I'm fine. I think it's just a cold.
Have you taken medicine?
You didn't have to come back.
Of course I did.
Stay right there. I'll
make up a bed downstairs.
Hey, be careful!
I'm here with you.
Tell me if you're in any pain at all.
Okay.
Dora...
Episode 6
Laughing and Remembering
The commencement of a new school year
means the all-too-short summer
is once again coming to an end.
However, you are still in the
springtime of your lives.
Ahead of you, hot summ—
Wakana isn't here.
The teacher said she has a cold.
You really think that's it?
She's been down for a while now.
Why don't you text her,
if you're so worried?
And what if she doesn't respond?
Then it's probably because you annoy—
Because she wants some time alone.
Really? He says he's happy, too.
Shouldn't you be sleeping?
I'm feeling better.
My fever's gone.
I was sweating, so I'm gonna change.
Take it easy.
You can stay home from
school until next week.
Okay.
Are you sure about this?
Yeah.
Step one says that good vocalization
comes from correct posture.
Now use your glutes to
slowly lower yourself down.
Where's Miyamoto?
I'm here...
Exact change.
Thank you very much.
Wakana?
Wakana, no!
Wakana, don't!
Konatsu!
What are you doing?
How are you feeling?
It's nothing exciting, but here.
Sawa paid for half of it.
Thank you.
Your room's pretty empty, huh?
Tatami's so great.
Reminds me of my grandpa's house.
Did I tell you how much he
loved the Condor Queens?
We sang their songs all the time!
Whenever he drank, he'd always
talk about the concerts he went to.
Then I'd whine about how
much I wish I could've been there.
And then, he'd promise
to take me to the next one!
Unfortunately, it never happened.
Promises should always be
kept, don't you think?
Huh?
I made a promise with my mom.
She tried so hard to keep it...
But I didn't. I was too
busy thinking about myself.
I don't know why she didn't
tell me she was sick.
If only she'd told me...
You now, I'm actually glad it never happened.
Once a promise is fulfilled, that's it.
But since it's still out there,
it makes me think of my grandpa.
Like, "Rats! We never did it!"
It's another precious memory of him.
What song's that?
It's my song.
What's my song?
You don't have one.
How come?
You have to make your own song.
But I don't know how!
Why don't we create your song together?
Sure!
Promise?
Yeah!
I'll wash these clothes
and get them back to you.
No rush.
Think people'll know I'm
not wearing a bra?
Come visit us again.
I will!
Thanks for having me.
I'll treat you to rice
flour dumplings next time.
That sounds great!
Inbox
047 Okita Sawa
The Cake >_<
That Konatsu! "After I took the picture,
Wakana enjoyed the cake, I think," she wrote!
She's not one bit sorry.
I'll make sure she gets it tomorrow at school.
Get well soon!
Can't wait to see you! <3 Cya!
Oh yeah.
My mom wants you to know,
"that thing is done, so you
can come pick it up anytime."
That make sense?
"That thing"?
Cut it in the shape of a penguin.
Like I could!
I'm off.
All right, have a good day!
What about a heart?
I can't!
Hello.
Wakana!
You made it.
Here's the photo.
Let me see.
You can have this, too.
Shirahamazaka Choir Competition
Free Choice Piece
A cassette tape?
We recorded it before going to nationals.
You can hear your mother's voice.
Wow, you were such a cutie,
back in the day.
It's so sad. I hardly recognized you!
Zip it.
Hey, Wakana, are you free now?
Hold the reins, grip the saddle,
and put your foot here.
Your other foot,
or you'll end up backwards.
Oh, okay.
And, up.
It's so high!
Like seeing a different world, yeah?
Definitely.
Okay, here we go.
Slowl—
Try to maintain your balance by squeezing
Sabure's sides with your thighs.
Okay.
Is Sabure your horse?
Nah, he's my dad's.
But I'm riding him this year
in the mounted archery competition.
Your dad was the person
on the moped, right?
Yeah.
He doesn't approve of me
becoming an equestrian.
He says if I won't inherit
the temple business,
I should be a government worker,
so I'm not talking to him.
But if, for some reason,
you could never see him again,
your last conversation would be that fight...
Want to try jogging a bit?
Here we go!
Keep your back straight.
Feel his rhythm!
Don't pull on the reins;
relax your arms.
Like this?
He's going too fast!
Wow, that really works your muscles, huh?
My poor thighs...
Sabure just told me that he likes you.
Really?
You should come ride him again.
Okay.
Morning.
Huh?
Dora, where's Wakana?
I have to get some things
done, so I'm leaving early.
Food's in the microwave.
See you.
YumFluff Toast
Sakai.
Start From Scratch
Vocal Training
<Beginner Edition>
Improve within moments!
I guess "Operation Secret Morning
Practice to Surprise the Group" failed.
You surprised me.
I want to get better, so I
can be useful to you guys.
Wakana, what do you
think we need most?
Common sense?
I told you there's no way
we can improve on our own.
Are you angry?
Huh?
You're making a scary face
and going "Ah-ah!"
No, I'm trying to stay on pitch.
You have to treat voice exercises
like they're a song.
Relax your shoulders, and look!
Sing as if you're trying
to tell someone you love,
who's far away, that you're
doing well and having fun.
Okay.
I get it.
Emotion is important.
I guess a book can't teach you everything.
Thank you, thank you.
I've gotta go.
Okay.
By the way, Ms. Takahashi had her baby.
Oh, she did?
It's a girl.
Wow.
Tanaka-kun, sorry I couldn't
stay and cheer for you
at your last badminton competition.
No worries.
He lost, anyway.
Quiet, you.
Wait, what was she even doing here?
Good question...
Compose
Congrats on your new baby!
Please take good care of yourself.
From Sakai Wakana
Send Mail
046 Ms. Takahashi
Sub: To Ms. Takahashi
Congrats on your new baby!
Please take good care of yourself.
From Sakai Wakana
Sending message
Your message has been sent.
Sakai? Thanks for your message.
School's over, right?
On your way home?
Yes.
Perfect timing!
Want to come over and see the baby?
I also have a favor to ask you.
You know that gelato shop by the train station?
The one next to the Japanese candy store.
Their gelato is fantastic...
Welcome!
Here you go.
Thank you!
I haven't had a chance
to go myself lately.
Come in, come in.
Thank you for having me.
So adorable.
Here you go.
Milk time.
Babies are a lot of work.
She's cute now,
but it pains me to think
of how fast she'll grow
into one of my loud-mouthed students.
Should a teacher be saying that?
Hey, I'm off the clock right now.
Anyway, she doesn't have
to be perfectly-behaved,
so long as she's happy and healthy.
Want to hold her?
Huh?
No, that's okay! I can't!
You'll be fine.
Just put your right arm close to your
side, and your left arm like so.
Like so?
Wakana, dinner!
What's all this?
This here is what you call food.
I'm hoping eating this will
make you mend your lazy
shoving-bread-in-a-microwave-
and-calling-it-breakfast ways.
Today's your wedding anniversary!
You remembered that?
Yeah. Mom said that because
it's close to my birthday,
you just celebrated them
together after a while.
Did she?
Let's eat.
How did you propose to her?
I didn't.
She proposed to me.
Liar.
I should've asked mom.
It's true!
It is the honest truth.
I don't want to brag and say
I was a ladies' man, but...
What?
Too salty?
Why didn't Mom tell me she was sick?
If she had, maybe we
could've kept our promise.
I would've been nicer to her...
Your mom didn't want
you to be nice to her.
Can I say something selfish?
I don't want you to tell Wakana
about my illness just yet.
She may be mature,
but she gets sad too easily.
And her entrance exams are coming up.
But she's not a child anymore.
Yes, it might actually hurt her not to know...
Then why?
Because we made a promise
to write a song together.
She'll understand...
Just explain it to her,
then you can write—
A sad song about saying goodbye?
By writing a song together,
I feel like I can leave
part of me in her heart.
I don't want it to be full of
sadness, but kindness and strength.
Long after I'm gone,
that song will be there for her.
She can think of me whenever she hears it.
Remember how you rushed to the hospital,
without even closing the store,
when Wakana was born?
Sure.
She was still faster.
She's always been impatient.
Do you remember what you said
when you first saw her?
You can never tell her...
I'm so glad she grew up loving music.
My precious little girl...
I'll never leave her alone.
Hey!
She loved me so much, and I...
I didn't understand... I threw it all away...
The memories... The
piano... The music...
Wakana, can I come in?
Sure.
Here.
She'd taken some notes for the song
she wanted to write with
you once exams were over.
But then she was gone so fast...
I've been holding on to these,
waiting for you to
come to terms with things.
I don't know anything
about music, but...
Maybe you could continue it, somehow.
I'd also like the hear the
song you wrote together.
There's this, too.
If you don't want it, I'll take it.
That's...
I couldn't throw away
such an important keepsake.
And the piano?
How could I get rid of it?
Your mom used it to propose to me.
Liar...
Think I could leave it in here?
Might be a bit cramped.
Come on, let's eat.
Do you mind if I take a look at this first?
Not at all.
I'll start eating without you.
Thank you, Mom.
Recording, now!
We will now commence singing—
Too awkward, Nao!
Mahiru...
We'll now sing a song
born between Nao and me,
and nurtured by our choir.
It's Mom!
A fresh wind races through
the grass and leaves.
The view is clear,
as far as the eye can see.
And now, a graceful light is flooding,
softly illuminating everything.
Even if you can't see the stars
because of the rain,
the future you're dreaming of
is still right there.
When you muster your courage
to take a step forward,
I want you to remember
the days we spent with sparkling eyes.
Let's sing every day
with all our hearts,
our song echoing to the skies,
and beyond.
And if it should ever
reach you again somewhere,
I want you to remember
the days we spent with sparkling eyes,
the days we spent with beaming smiles.
You probably don't understand
because you lack experience.
It's not love!
Girls are scary.
Episode 7
Spinning in Circles and Losing Sight
Sai, are you coming, too?
Is liking it not enough?