Seriously, I was about to lose it.
Who would ruin a school trip like that?
It's so hot.
He's really not thinking about how I feel.
He's not thinking about anything.
It's unbelievable.
What's up?
Huh? N-Nothing.
No one else knows, but Azumi-kun
and I have started dating.
Are you taking this seriously?
Your proficiency test scores will determine
your future after middle school.
Pardon me.
You know...
I believe in you, Azumi-kun.
But you might not get into the high school
of your choice if you get a late start.
His hair's not curling up.
Excuse me.
Your hair's not curly today.
Is something wrong?
Just kidding.
Aren't you in the literature club?
Yeah.
I'm in trouble with language arts.
Do you know of any good cram schools?
The one I go to isn't too bad.
Really?
One, two, three, four...
Five, six, seven, eight...
Two, two, three, four...
Chinatsu?
What's up?
Nothing.
Huh...
Mizuno, Nishio. Here.
What's that?
The sprint training plan.
We're going with this until the meet.
Jeez, that's rough.
All right!
You sure are pumped up.
It's our last summer.
Let's do this, Akane.
Yeah.
Thank you very much.
Good work.
The adults are up next.
Hey...
Yeah?
I'm thinking about the next story.
How are things going?
What things?
Studying for entrance exams and stuff.
Dunno.
So?
There's something I wanted to ask you.
What's that?
What are you supposed to do
when you're in a relationship?
For my novel!
Really?
Jeez...
Sorry.
Middle School Dating
Things you shouldn't do
in a relationship
1. Don't text or LINE too much
— Boys hate needy girls
2. Think about how often you reply
— Don't reply right away,
but don't wait too long, either
3. Don't text or LINE during a date
— Do you have a habit of reacting
as soon as you get a message
from your friends?
Dating is so hard.
Oh, stop it.
Goodnight.
Nee-chan.
What are you supposed to
do when you're dating?
What?
You got a boyfriend, huh?
Good for you!
D-Don't tell Mom yet.
I know.
Middle schoolers go on dates,
walk home together,
hang out at each other's homes...
At home?
Why not bring him over?
N-No way.
Yahho! Answers
Question
I'm in middle school. How can I spend time
alone with my girlfriend at school?
Best Answer
Master of Love
I used to meet mine in the library.
There was no one there. It was awesome.
I'm coming in.
You'd better study.
I know.
You're banned from the festival and your
writing if you do poorly on your finals.
Understand?
Goodnight
Are you asleep already?
No, I'm good
We didn't get to talk today again
Keep it cool. Keep it cool.
But I'm just happy I get to see you at school
Me too
I'm going to the library
during lunch break tomorrow
I'll go with you!
I'm all sweaty.
Let's eat outside.
Kota, what about lunch?
Sorry.
I'm starving.
I almost forgot to bring my lunch today.
Wow, that's bad.
I know.
I was freaking out.
What the?
Restroom, probably.
Dude, Daichi, you eat too much.
I ran back home so fast.
No, I don't.
It was scary.
Akanecchi, let's eat.
Fatty.
I'm not fat! This is muscle!
What's wrong?
Muscle. Muscle!
Nothing.
Let's eat.
See? It's all muscle.
There you are, Curly-kun!
I guess you don't have the curl anymore.
Pardon me.
I'll ask, then.
Thank goodness.
You saved me.
Akane?
Huh?
Were you two...
What? No!
That's not it!
Sorry, I kind of...
It's fine.
Right?
Azumi-kun goes to the
cram school by the station.
Oh... Yeah.
I'm thinking of going, too.
Right?
Yeah.
Want to go visit it with me?
Our club takes up so much time.
Yeah.
And my grades suck.
That's not true.
Thanks for everything.
Sure.
Okay, see you, Akane.
Man, I don't know.
Uh, so, do you want to come to the cram—
No.
Off-leash dogs are causing problems.
Please keep your dog on a leash.
Here we go!
Go!
Sorry, Sensei.
Well, it's exam season.
You're doing the best you can.
Here we go!
Go!
Mizuno.
Your time was pretty bad.
Sorry.
I'm not doing too well.
Is something wrong?
Want to talk on our way home?
All right, let's get back to practice.
Okay.
Is something going on?
Well, all right.
Hang in there.
We don't have much longer...
to run together.
Later.
Kokoro is a novel by Natsume Souseki.
Put simply, it's a story about a
love triangle during the Meiji era.
Does that grab your interest,
at least a little?
Not many people from
Daisan Middle, huh?
Yeah.
Might be easier not knowing
too many people there.
That's true.
I'm going to go to that cram school.
Yeah?
Tell me your LINE ID?
Okay.
Whoops...
Sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Man, I'm stuffed.
I'm thinking of breaking up with him.
What?! It's happening?
Why?
I mean, I'm not even enjoying dating him.
I guess things don't really
work out how you expect.
Like, as a girl, I want to talk lots
and date lots and cuddle and stuff.
I know.
He doesn't do any of that.
Straight to the hotel?
What is he, a monkey?
Dating is tough, huh?
It is.
Is it tough for you, too, Akane?
Wh-Why?
No reason.
I think it's over.
I found a painful pressure point!
Ow!
No, I can handle it.
Seriously, he's unbelievable.
Hey, Mizuno-senpai.
Are you dating Hira-senpai?
Huh?
Someone saw you walking home with him.
Not at all.
Oh, okay!
Thank goodness.
Thanks for your time.
So they aren't dating.
Told you so.
I just can't...
What is it?
It's nothing.
Are you stuck on your novel?
Were you asking about
relationships for story ideas?
So what happened after that?
It's not working too well.
We can't find a place to meet.
Are you keeping it a secret?
Yeah.
I see.
You can't go on dates when
you don't have money, either.
Of course it's hard, huh?
Hey, Kotarou...
Thank goodness.
Did you find the place okay?
I used Maps.
Where are we?
My friend's shop.
Uh...
Yeah?
I wanted to talk to you alone.
We don't get to at school.
Yeah.
We're finally going out, so...
No one comes here.
Oh, really?
He said he'll be back at seven.
You know...
Yeah?
I can't really talk when I'm at school.
Me neither.
Sorry about the library.
Y-Yeah.
Is Chinatsu going to your cram school?
She said she's going to.
Oh.
How did the exam go?
Decent.
Lucky.
I did awful.
Really?
I'm not studying.
Your novel?
Yeah.
That's okay, then.
I mean, I think it's okay.
Me too, actually.
The preliminary for the
prefectural meet is coming up.
Yeah?
I can't improve my time at all.
Watching you run...
is really...
I guess I really...
like it.
Thanks.
I think I'll go watch.
To cheer for you.
I, u-uh...
If you don't want—
No.
It's not that I don't want you to.
Dazai once said, "One thing that humans
have, that other creatures don't:
We have secrets."
Sorry.
Chinatsu
Notice to Akane!
I think I have a crush on Azumi-kun
Kokoro
Story of a Man!! Ogasawara Daichi 1
You've gained weight, haven't you, Roman?
Can you tell?
About two kilos.
Damn, spot on!
I can usually guess a person's
weight just by looking.
Ack!
What kind of superpower is that?
Talk about unwanted.
Miu and Inaba 1
Hey, hey. Which one's better?
Cheerleader Costumes
This one.
I'll go with this one.
Why'd you ask in the first place?
Miu and Inaba 2
Hey, hey, which one's better?
Whichever one you like.
You're so useless.
What am I supposed to do?!
Ayane's Boyfriend 1
What a noisy car.
Probably some hooligan.
Hey, Dad, Mom!
Ayane...
My boyfriend gave me a ride.
Hello, I'm Ayane-san's boyfriend.
My name is Kasai Riki.
Nice to meet you.
He's surprisingly proper.
Well, I don't approve.
Are you in college?
Yes.
I'm apprenticing as a
carpenter with my boss.
I hope to be a good craftsman someday.
He's surprisingly proper.
I don't approve!
Bye!
He said he had enough to share.
Come say hi again!
He's a good kid.