Alarm
My Friend and I
There are things I don't know about Suna,
even though I've known him more than ten years.
Even though I know his birthday,
what kind of underwear he wears,
and a secret place only the two of us know,
there's still a lot I don't know.
Why won't you get it?
Even if you scrap the birthday plan you've been
looking forward to, and come to the surgery,
it won't make me feel any better.
Today is Yamato's birthday
and the day Suna's dad undergoes surgery.
I thought you were a gatekeeper.
Suna, when does the surgery start?
Two o'clock.
Well, I'm off.
Give Yamato-san my regards.
Suna...
I know I've been really critical about your plans,
but I think she'll be happy, no matter
what you guys end up doing.
Well, good luck.
Suna, we spent so much time
perfecting the plan for today.
I'll make sure it's a success.
Takeo-kun!
Sorry, did you wait long?
I love her!
When did you arrive?
Just now.
Really?
Whew...
I woke up super early today,
We were supposed to
meet at 10, right?
like at 4 AM.
I tried going back to sleep, but then I dreamed I was running late.
I woke up in a panic,
only to find that it was still 5 AM...
Yamato, happy birthday.
Yeah...
Yeah!
Thanks.
Thank you!
I love you, Yamato.
Today, you can leave everything to me.
Okay.
Where are we going?
It's a secret.
Since we have time, let's walk there.
Okay.
Suna helped me come up with this plan.
Sounds fun!
I'm glad it's sunny today.
It makes me really happy.
Suna...
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
Wow!
This place is really fun!
What should we do?
Bowling...
We spoke at the same time!
We sure did.
Bowl!
You're amazing, Takeo-kun!
blush blush blush
Wow, your ball is so heavy.
You hold it like it's nothing,
but I'm not sure I can lift it...
Wow, Takeo-kun, your hand's so big!
Wow, Takeo-kun, you're so strong!
Wow!
Wow, what?
Sorry, Takeo-kun...
But it's from Nanako.
Hmm?
Oh, sorry.
No, you can look.
Takeo-kun, can I take a selfie with you?
Sure.
I wonder if this is going too far.
Compose Message
To: Nanako
Subject: Re: Happy Birthday, Rinko!
Thanks! I'm with Takeo-kun.
Bowling's super fun!
Maybe it's like I'm bragging.
I'm blushing.
Okay...
Oops, the pins are split.
Those are hard.
Yamato's been laughing the whole time.
She looks like she's having fun.
Suna said you'd have fun,
no matter where I took you.
Huh?
Really?
I'm not that easygoing.
I'm just really having fun.
Okay.
I am, too.
I'm glad I can celebrate my birthday with you.
Me, too.
I'm having lots of fun. I'm glad.
I'm a happy man, Yamato.
Hey, I know this place!
I saw it in a book.
I've wanted to try coming here,
but it's expensive, so it isn't
somewhere you can go often.
I got a job, so it's fine.
Wow! So cute!
Cakes are so sparkly.
Just looking at them is fun.
Yeah.
I think your smile's really sparkly.
Just seeing you smile is fun.
Suna said that if you like making sweets,
you must like eating them, too.
Yeah, I do!
I see!
Suna really gets it.
He's amazing!
Yeah, he is.
Sunakawa-kun's good-looking, and I'd
think he'd be popular with girls.
I wonder why he doesn't have a girlfriend.
I'm not sure...
He said it was too much trouble.
Suna...
Huh?
I'm glad you didn't have a girlfriend, either,
even though you're cool, too.
I'm so lucky I can go out with you.
I'm the one who's lucky.
Happy birthday!
What?
Huh?
Wh-Wh-What?
Please make a wish before
you blow out the candle.
Huh?
Oh, uh, um, okay...
Um, uh...
I wish to spend my next birthday,
and the one after that, and the
one after that with Takeo-kun!
You don't have to say it out loud!
Huh?
You're the first customer
who's said their wish aloud.
Oh, I'm so embarrassed!
I can't believe I did that!
Yamato...
Your wish is my wish.
Suna, I'm spending time with
Yamato and being happy,
just like you told me to.
Takeo-kun?
Hmm?
C-Can I hold hands with you?
Sure!
Huh?
What?
I'm so nervous!
Did you tell the restaurant
that it was my birthday?
Yeah.
Suna told me to.
Sunakawa-kun did?
Wow, I'm so grateful!
I see...
Sunakawa-kun tried really hard for Takeo-kun.
Good friends are nice to have.
What's Sunakawa-kun doing today?
Suna's...
Suna is...
Suna, when does the surgery start?
Two o'clock.
Well, good luck.
Takeo-kun?
10 AM: Meet in front of station
12 PM: Lunch
2 PM: Park if sunny, café if rain
3 PM: Planetarium
Yamato, Suna and I came up with
today's schedule together.
There are tickets in that envelope, too.
Please go with a friend, if you'd like.
I'm going to see Suna.
His father is undergoing surgery today.
What?
It started at 2 PM, at a municipal hospital.
Suna told me not to come,
but I still want to go!
I'm glad.
Congratulations.
Suna, I'm sorry!
Why did you keep quiet about
something this important?
The hospital's toward the station, right?
You should get going!
Yamato...
I'll look at this schedule and go to the planetarium.
I'll make sure I enjoy the plan you guys devised.
You should go be with Sunakawa-kun now!
If you're there, I'm sure he'll feel better!
Yamato...
You have to hurry.
You have to run, Takeo-kun.
Yamato, this is your present.
Please accept it.
Thank you, Yamato!
Thank you for being born.
Thank you for showing up in my life.
Thank you.
Life
Death
Where's the operating room?!
The delivery room is on the third floor!
The operating room!
Huh?
I thought your wife was in labor.
Surgery in Progress
Well, I did think you might
ultimately end up here.
You're an idiot, you know.
You were so excited about your
first girlfriend's birthday...
Where's the relative who's supposed to be here?
He went to work.
Oh.
Surgery in Progress
How long do surgeries usually take?
No idea.
I have no idea what you really want,
what you're really thinking,
or what the right thing to do really is.
But I'm your friend.
Let me stay.
Dad's always had a weak heart.
You?
No, Dad.
That's why, when my sister and
I were about to be born,
he was really worried.
Mom told us that, once he
found out we were fine,
he was so happy, he cried.
I see.
Given all that, he spoiled us rotten.
We could do no wrong.
I've never seen him get angry.
I get it.
Actually, this is his second surgery.
To be honest, it isn't looking good.
The day he collapsed,
Mom and Sis were away on a trip,
and it was just the two of us at home.
I'd stopped by the bookstore and music
store on my way home from school.
I found him on the floor when
I got home, all alone.
I have no idea when it happened.
If only...
I'd gone home earlier.
If I hadn't been out and about,
it might not have come to this.
It's my fault...
You're the only one who thinks that.
Am I?
Definitely.
Your sister, mom, and dad don't think that.
I don't think that, either.
It isn't that Suna didn't tell me before.
Maybe he just couldn't tell me.
Surgery in Progress
So, this surgery was a valvuloplasty
to repair your father's valves.
If he takes anticoagulants,
and no arrhythmia occurs—
What was the result?
Did it work?
It worked, didn't it?!
I-It worked...
Puke.
You came on a little strong there...
Honey!
Makoto!
I'm sorry we're late!
Sorry to make you go through all that alone!
No, I'm fine.
Sorry, Makoto!
It must've been so hard!
No, not at all.
Liar
Can you calm down?
Dad's fine.
Thank g—
Oh, Takeo was with you?
Thanks!
Hey.
Mom and I can handle the rest.
You guys can go home.
How's my husband?
The operation worked, didn't it?
It did, right?!
Please let me see him!
Hey, Doctor...
Where is my father's room?
I believe it's on the second floor...
Puke.
Let's go home.
Yeah.
We ask all visitors to please
make their way to the lobby.
Yamato!
Takeo-kun, Sunakawa-kun...
Oh, I didn't have time,
so there aren't nearly enough cranes, but...
Thanks.
The surgery was a success, so...
Thanks
Really?
Thank goodness.
I'm glad, Sunakawa-kun!
I went to the planetarium,
but I couldn't stop thinking about
you guys, so I came here.
I'm sorry about today, Yamato.
Don't be.
Looking at this schedule,
I could see that you changed things many times.
I could tell that you spent a lot of time on this.
That made me so happy...
Thank you.
Thank you!
Today was my best birthday ever.
Yamato... I love you.
I love you so much.
Thanks, Takeo-kun.
Sorry, but these are happy tears...
This is nice.
Er, don't get me wrong.
Do you want a girlfriend?
No.
Sunakawa-kun, I could introduce
you to someone from my school!
No, please don't do anything.
You know, someone you've been
friends with for a long time
is the kind of person you'd get along with best.
I see!
Bingo!!
I think you'd like a girl like Takeo-kun.
Right!
A girl like me!
What kind of girl would that be?
I'll look for a girl like Takeo-kun!
Suna's a good guy, so I bet she'd like him, too!
Then we could go on a double dates and stuff!
Oh, that sounds great.
Please stop...
It's great when every day's full of romance, Suna.
All right, let's go!
Go where?
To the butt-pine!
Wow.
Yeah.
You should have brought Yamato-san here, too.
You're right.
I'd like to show this to her someday.
When I was little,
before we moved here...
I didn't really like sunsets.
Why?
They kind of make you feel uneasy.
Yeah...
It's right around when you get hungry, too.
Suna! Suna!
The sky! Look!
It looks super yummy...
You can't eat the sky.
Suna!
Suna, did you know this?
Once the sun sets behind the
mountains, it gets real cold!
You're right.
Suna!
Crap, it's night!
We had to be home by 4:30
because of school rules!
The sun set, and night was
here before I knew it!
Suna, crap!
Crap!
I didn't notice...
Well, ever since we moved here,
I haven't felt that way.
It's still cold after the sun sets.
Yeah.
Let's go home.
My Mountain
Next time: My Mountain.