Whenever I counted on someone, I ended up getting hurt.
You can count on me, Ohana!
Okay, who has the answer?
I'll go to your next Parents' Day, I promise!
Me!
All right, Koyanagi?
Okay!
The answer is 45 degrees!
Correct. Well done.
Thank you. Please have a seat.
So, it's best not to rely on anyone, ever.
It's true that I don't know a thing about working,
but...
This is a basic principle.
If you can't accept that,
you shouldn't be here.
Do you understand the concept of "work"?
I'll show them.
Something my mother, that useless woman, taught me is...
You promised! Why didn't you come?
Ohana!
Mark my words: people can't be trusted.
Not even family.
Never rely on someone else.
Believe only in yourself.
That's not even what—
What you need to do,
is get them before they get you.
Gouge them. Cut them down.
Cut them down?
Yes. Cut.
Cut them down!
Yikes, almost got some wild rocamboles.
Huh? Good morning!
Hard at work at five in the morning?
Yep!
What a diligent girl.
Nah...
She's not accomplishing nearly as much as she thinks.
You're not cutting them short enough.
They'll just grow right back.
Careless effort does nothing but harm.
Harsh.
I'm not too fond of Grandma.
I mean, "Madam Manager."
But that's why I'll...
Cut them down!
Come with me.
M-Me?
A new waitress should learn from one more experienced.
Tomoe instructed you, did she not?
Y-Yes, ma'am, but...
I'm going to be a waitress?
That sounds awesome!
Although, I'm not old enough to drink alcohol.
You will not be required to attend banquets.
However, all other duties must be performed perfectly.
As of today, Ohana will be under your wing.
Have I made myself clear?
Y-Yes.
Huh?
I wish I could wear it like you.
You look dazzling!
C-Come on...
Not a single wasted motion.
Your gestures are so elegant!
Plus, you're tall, so I bet you're great at sports!
You've gotta be!
Huh?
Paulownia Room
Even I should be able to do a decent job at cleaning.
Oh, you're not supposed to step there.
Why not?
B-Because.
Okay then, I won't step on it!
W-We need to remove the sheets first.
Oh, we do?
There.
Which room's next on the list?
Th-The Wave Room, but...
But what?
Hey, I need you!
C-Coming!
I-I'll be right back.
O...kay...?
"Never rely on someone else.
Believe only in yourself."
That's what my mother taught me.
Wave Room
I suppose I should go ahead and clean this room.
Housekeeping!
Good grief.
So this must be...
He stays in the Wave Room.
Rumor has it he's a famous author.
I'm not much of a reader,
so I don't know his name,
but I hear he's something else!
Yeah, he's something else, all right.
He must have a lot on his mind.
Famous people have troubles, too.
My problems are pretty small in comparison.
I just want to work hard,
and show everyone what I'm capable of.
Nako!
I finished cleaning.
Y-You did?
What should I do next?
Next? Nothing.
We're done for the morning.
You did well, thank you.
Don't lose heart, Ohana!
Relying on others will only cause you pain.
There's nothing you can't handle.
For crying out loud, get it together!
Y-Yes, sir!
What good is a kitchen hand
if she just makes things worse?!
Look, it's burned to a crisp!
I'm sorry.
We can't serve this garbage to our c–
Tohru.
Stop. What's done is done.
Make salt grilled greenlings instead.
The rape blossoms were to be tonight's entrée,
but we'll use them as a side dish.
Yes, sir!
Umm, and the staff's breakfast?
Not this morning!
There's no time to cook for them.
Get to work!
Yes, sir!
Hmm...
Ahh, I can finally take a break.
Huh?
We're very sorry.
Sorry? For what?
Due to an unforeseen error,
breakfast this morning is—
Wow!
This looks incredible!
I didn't have anything to do, so...
Wow, I didn't know you could cook!
Tasty!
You're amazing, Ohana!
My mom's kind of crazy...
She's had me cooking meals since preschool.
Preschool?!
Boy, you've had a pretty tough life, huh?
What a good girl.
I think she might be better at this than you.
I'm going to do inventory.
What's with her?
Minko!
That was crossing the line, don't you think?
What do you mean?
Wait up!
Minko!
Back off!
Huh?
Did you make that meal just to spite me?
No, of course not!
It's just, I wanted to make up
for the trouble I caused you with the whole futon thing.
So, you repay me by giving me more trouble?
M-More trouble?
Thanks for nothing.
Seriously, what's with y–
Die.
Here we go again...
Why does she hate me so much?
I'm just trying to get used to my job.
And that's when I heard...
Manager!
Get me the manager!
...a phrase that was somehow familiar.
The draft I've been working on non-stop
since coming here has vanished!
You hear me?
It's the work of the century!
It might very well win the Naoki Prize!
Do you understand?!
What's all this about?
That's the girl who cleaned my room, isn't it?
You!
You! You! You! You!
New girl!
Was this your doing?!
Huh?
Office
You're absolutely positive that all you did was clean?
Y-Yes.
I did throw out the papers
that were in the trash, but that's all.
Unbelievable.
Shall we call the police?
No, that's all right.
There's no need for that.
But...
I want to compete with the quality of my work.
If it's made famous simply because of this scandal,
it won't receive a fair evaluation.
I understand.
My entire staff will search for the draft in question.
I'll be holding you responsible if it's not found.
Meaning, my stay here will be free of charge.
Yes, of course.
Mother, that jerk's been here at least a month—
Madam Manager.
What shall we do, Madam Manager?
We are not to clean the Wave Room
without the customer's supervision.
Did Nako not tell you this?
She did, I'm sorry.
It's commendable that you're taking initiative.
But I warned you.
Careless effort does nothing but harm.
Ma'am, that's—
How was I careless?
What do you want from me?
You told me I don't understand what it means to work,
so I was trying my hardest to learn.
I'm doing my best...
But after all that...
I'm going to look for the draft.
No, don't.
I can't have you making another mistake.
Return to your regular duties.
She's acting so strangely today.
She'd usually stop at nothing
to fulfill a customer's request.
I've thought about rebelling,
but I don't even know how to.
Maybe I should be like Mom,
and start flirting with boys.
Hey, kid.
If you've got nothing to do, come with me.
"Kid"? Are you talking to me?
I don't see anyone else here.
Don't you think it's rude
to address someone that way?
Just hop in.
There's going to be a ton of stuff to carry.
But you've got big biceps,
and you look pretty strong,
so you'll be perfect for the job.
I-I highly doubt you can see
my biceps through these sleeves.
Once you're prepared to deal with the pain of loss...
I'm not too fond of this guy.
Say...
Yes?
You don't have any friends, do you?
What?!
How rude! I do so!
I've always liked you, Ohana Matsumae!
Yeah, sure. Doesn't look that way.
You don't seem very considerate, is all.
Right back at you.
Well, you're pretty uncooperative.
It's like you're blind to what's going on around you.
I decided a long time ago not to rely on other people.
Oh, but you can rely on yourself?
Are you so amazing you can do everything by yourself?
Let me rephrase that. I seriously dislike this guy.
What's the best word to hurt
someone in situations like these?
Die.
Huh?
J-Just kidding! You didn't hear that!
I was joking!
What the heck is your problem?!
You trying to kill me?!
Dying is bad.
Don't die! That'd be awful!
I have to go.
Please drive carefully, Tohru.
Come home safe!
H-Hey!
What am I gonna do about the luggage?!
You'll figure something out!
What's wrong with me?
Why do I feel so mixed-up inside?
I thought I just wanted to work.
But is that really all?
I didn't actually come here to work...
But now... I want to prove myself to them.
What is it that I really want to do?
Oh, but you can rely on yourself?
Rely...
On that day, I decided to stop relying on others.
I hate you Mommy
So why am I so confused?
Dinner's ready.
Thanks, Ohana!
I hate you Mommy
Since broccoli was my mom's least favorite food,
I made a ton of it for dinner that night.
Somehow, it made me feel a bit better.
Yeah.
I expect to see crab on the menu tonight.
Do you realize how much trouble you've all caused me?!
Yes, sir.
Sheesh...
Huh?
U-Um...
Minko–
This is your fault.
Die.
Stop telling me to die!
Huh?
What if I actually did end up dying?
You would feel bad afterwards, right?
Choose your words a bit more wisely!
What are you...
And you!
Stop running away all the time!
What is with you?
Why are you bossing us around?
I'll change, too!
I'll learn to be more considerate!
You sure don't seem very considerate right now.
I'll also learn to count on others!
Beg your pardon?
I'll count on you! I'll rely on you!
So teach me more about work,
and the things I shouldn't do!
But not just that!
I want to know more about you two!
Like, tell me your least favorite foods!
What?
I'll make a meal for the staff again tomorrow!
But I'm really mad at you two right now,
so you'll be seeing what you
hate most on your plates!
Excuse me?
You're insane.
Let's go, Nako.
M-Minchi...
Tell me!
Spinach.
Taro, I guess?
Got it!
What's her deal?
Ohana didn't tell the manager.
She didn't tell her it was my fault.
I deserve to face her wrath.
Nako.
What am I doing?
But...
At least this is a start.
I want them to eat this.
I'm counting on them to.
I've gotta face the fact that
I can't do everything myself.
Morning, Ohana!
Good morning to you, too!
That's not where you dump the trash, you know.
Oh?
That's where we put things we don't often use.
Trash goes over there.
Oh man...
Something wrong?
This is where I dumped the trash yesterday,
after I cleaned out that room.
You mean, Nako didn't tell you?
She's gonna be the death of me...
Oh, well, umm...
Just put it where it belongs, okay?
Okay!
I think this is yesterday's trash.
Bingo.
So this is the so-called "work of the century"?
Let's see...
"And that's when Ohana..."
Wow, same name as me!
"Ohana's tender, special spot..."
Her what spot?
Reading on...
Th-Th-Th-Th-This–
It's not my fault.
I swear.
Not my fault!
It's...
Episode 2: Vengeance is a Staff Meal
She betrayed me!
I guess it makes sense for there to be
No, don't say it!
low-class waitresses at a low-class hot spring inn.
Want me to teach you?
You mean, there's a criminal living here?!
I want to sparkle!
Balut!
Episode 3: Balut