Daichi!
Time to get up.
Right...
Why do I feel like I was just having
a really important dream?
It's no use. I can't remember.
Now it's going to bother me all day.
A Midsummer Night's Dream
And summer break starts tomorrow...
I thought he quit the track team
to focus on his studies...
Has he picked up any bad habits,
like staying out late?
No, nothing like that.
I think there has to be some reason
why his grades have fallen so much.
I was going to say that I spent the
whole time playing in my room,
but I didn't.
I didn't think it would help.
I felt like I'd said it before.
Wait... But when did I say that?
You have to start thinking about
what you'll do after high school.
Do you have any dreams or anything?
Like following in your father's footsteps?
Sir...
Yes?
His father has nothing to do with his future plans.
Sometimes...
I think there's something wrong
with me, with the way I am.
But most likely, I'm only imagining it,
and I'm actually just trying to escape
because I don't feel like studying
the stuff they assign at school.
Wow, Daichi.
Huh? Amara!
You're working?
My family owns this place.
Is it okay for me to come unannounced?
Don't worry. My parents aren't home.
Come in.
Oh, it's Daichi-kun.
I found him at the arcade.
Oh? Moco and Ai?
You're good at piloting robots, Daichi-kun!
R-Really?
Huh?
Piloting robots...
What was it?
Hey, let's invite Daichi-kun, too.
If we do, I'm sure Ai will come.
Having lots of people will be more fun!
You're right.
Hey, we're going to a villa in Izu.
You guys want to come with us?
A villa?
Will the old guy with the glasses complain?
He isn't really your father, right?
How did you know?
Daichi's father was an astronaut.
I'm amazed you know that.
I killed him!
What's wrong, Daichi-kun?
N-Nothing!
An astronaut?
He died.
This footage was taken by a local resident.
Hey, Daichi-kun...
Come to Izu with me.
Aren't you interested in this avatar's body?
You'll come, won't you, Daichi-kun?
I'll call you once the schedule's worked out.
Let's enjoy summer vacation together.
Okay, Daichi?
Why, I wonder.
The wind in this town feels strange.
And the dream I had before I woke
up this morning really bothers me.
But I just can't remember it.
And now, an update on the strange light
that appeared over Tanegashima.
Last night, at 11:20 PM, a strange light
was seen shining above Tanegashima.
The weather bureau says it might
have been either a moonbow,
Hey, Daichi.
a rainbow formed from lunar light,
Are you going home?
Yeah.
or a meteorological phenomenon
known as a circumhorizontal arc.
Um...
Oh, Baku...
Are you really quitting the track team?
Yeah.
I already submitted the paperwork.
That's a waste.
Why are you quitting?
Why?
I don't know.
Weren't you a candidate for the next captain?
Why me?
I see...
So that's what you didn't like.
Hey, have you ever had a dream
you couldn't remember,
one that really bothered you?
A dream?
No, never mind.
It's nothing.
Dreams disappear the minute you wake up.
Don't worry about it.
Yeah, you're right.
Life is no different.
Once you're dead, everything's over.
It's been so long since we've
gone to a festival together.
Festival?
Festival? What are they like?
Festival...
A festival, huh?
What am I doing?
Comprehensive Japanese
— Modern —
You're going out?
I'm going to the shrine.
There's a festival today.
Don't you have to study for your make-up tests?
I promised someone.
Promised?
Actually, I didn't promise anyone.
I just felt like I had to go.
Don't stay out too late.
Your teachers said to make sure you didn't
get into the habit of staying out late.
By the way, Uncle...
Have I eaten any watermelon this year?
Do you want to?
No, that isn't it.
I don't think you've had any yet this year.
I guess not.
I'll be back.
What are these...
These memories I've been
recalling in flashes all day?
Festival? What are they like?
What kind of dream was it?
Excuse me...
Do you have some time now?
What is it?
I'm a photographer for a men's fashion magazine.
Are you interested in being a model?
Huh?
I'm so lucky to have run into someone like you!
You'll make a great model!
How about it?
Want to try it?
Um... I can't do that!
Why not?
You won't know unless you try, right?
A future you don't choose doesn't exist.
Being a model's great...
The whole world becomes so much fun.
I'm sorry.
I've got somewhere to be today,
and I'm in a hurry.
Really?
That's a shame.
Um, if you'd like, you can use this.
That's a very kind thing to do
for a girl you've never met.
Is something wrong?
I'm on my way to a funeral.
For someone who was like family to me.
Like family to you?
I was raised by someone who wasn't my parent.
What a coincidence.
But she wasn't really interested in me.
She was only interested in my inheritance.
She raised me to get her hands on it.
And when I realized that,
I got mad and ran away.
But she died in an accident.
I still haven't forgiven her.
But I'm still sad.
You loved her.
I don't know.
But I use people to survive, as well.
In that sense, I'm the same as she was.
Don't people live by helping one another?
My way of life can't be masked
by such beautiful words.
In the end, I'm living in a way I hate.
And that makes my heart heavy.
Then why not start by changing the way you live?
If nothing else, that will make your heart lighter.
Am I wrong?
I don't think that's possible.
You see, I'm the same as you.
The same as me?
I'm terribly sorry.
The bus has been involved in a minor collision.
I apologize, but all passengers
are asked to disembark here.
Maybe I was in too much of a rush.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
After that, I'm amazed you're fine!
Real people don't die.
Right, real princess?
Let's go.
You should go to a hospital, just in case.
Oh, well... I guess I'll take
a taxi or something.
If you're going the same way, want to share?
No, I don't think I'm going
the same way as you yet.
Goodbye.
U-Um, my handkerchief...
The shrine on Third Street, please.
There was a bus accident, wasn't there?
You found out about that fast...
Do you get that kind of news on the taxi radio?
No, this was something different.
I had a feeling there'd be a bus
accident in this area tonight.
Like, intuition...
No, isn't that like a like psychic power?
You've heard of déjà vu, haven't you?
When you visit a place for the first time,
but you feel you've been there before.
I've had a really strong sense of that all day.
Another coincidence...
And now, I even ended up predicting a bus accident.
That's basically psychic power!
Do you live in a country where
they believe in things like that?
A country?
I'm surprised myself.
What do you mean by "a country
where they believe"?
I think it would be interesting
if you could relive a day with perfect
memories of what had happened.
Would that be interesting?
If you knew what would happen,
you could do whatever you wanted.
I think it would be boring to
just repeat the same thing...
I think it's more exciting not
knowing what will happen.
Exciting, huh?
You don't feel frustrated, then?
Thank you.
Make sure you haven't forgotten anything,
Captain.
Why did I decide I had to come here?
I still feel like I've forgotten something important.
Please let the mission go well...
What's the mission?
What have I forgotten?
I love the view of space
from this planet most of all.
So do I.
What am I doing?
Thanks.
I have to go back.
But how do I get back, exactly?
How about a candy apple, sir?
Those look good!
But I'm sorry.
I promised someone I'd eat one with them,
so not now.
Oh?
Your girlfriend?
Yeah.
Now, then...
What do I do?
I have to try that.
Want to try it, sir?
How much for one go?
Three shots for two hundred yen! It's a bargain!
One go, then.
So close!
But you have natural talent.
Found you, Daichi-kun!
There you are, Daichi.
The plan's changed.
We're leaving for that villa tonight.
Let's go, Daichi.
Another close one!
I've figured out the trick.
Real people don't die.
You guys keep saying that. What's a real person?
Once you're dead, everything's over!
Is it?
The hopes my father left are still within me.
A future you don't choose doesn't exist.
That's why I'm going to choose one,
of my own free will.
Don't aim.
Feel.
Like the way you don't look at your right hand
and think, "This is my right hand."
Your right hand is a part of you,
so it's natural for it to be there.
It isn't like it's me and the gun.
It's like both of us comprise "me."
There's no time.
Let's go, Daichi!
This shooting game doesn't matter!
Let's go to that villa and do something more fun.
Sorry.
I can't go to the villa.
There's something I have to do, no matter what.
I don't think I'm going
the same way as you yet.
I'm going.
I'm following the path I believe in.
Aim carefully!
Huh?
What was I just...
He's back.
The captain is back.
Good work, Captain.
You, too, Akari.
Are you okay, Captain?
I'm fine.
No problem.
I'm so glad...
Okay, everyone...
Let's go!
The hyperspace transport Entangle Link
carries our ship, Blume, away from Earth,
to a world unexplored by man.
But we landed somewhere other than our goal.
And the Kiltgang appears there to destroy us.
The Earth Engine is in terrible danger!
Next time, on episode 24 of Captain Earth:
Auberon
Auberon.
Earth Engine, expand!