Exams suck!
I'm so sick of this.
Picked your first-choice school yet?
Not yet.
Have you, Daichi?
More or less, I guess.
I'll take what I can, with my grades.
I already know what I'm gonna do.
Really? What?
Amateur model.
That's not a high school.
What's wrong with that?
Post-Middle School Plans Questionnaire
Dude, stop it.
What the heck?!
Ah! S-Sorry!
Ow, ow! Sorry! Mercy! Mercy!
High school, huh?
Are your parents coming to the fall meet?
I think so.
Your parents always come, Akanecchi.
Mine are too, since it's my last one.
Isn't it embarrassing?
Totally.
Right? I'd hate that.
Maybe I should buy new shoes.
Sounds good.
I should, right?
Yeah.
Wait, wait, you're still going to
do track in high school, right?
I don't know.
I think I will.
Yeah?
Oh, but I guess we still have exams first.
Sorry I'm late.
It's fine.
Have you chosen a high school?
No.
Me, neither.
Private? Public?
Probably public.
Yeah?
My sister's in a private school.
Girls' school?
Yeah.
You, too?
I don't know yet.
The same school, maybe...
If we can.
Yeah.
I don't know if I can, though.
Why not?
You have really good grades.
Not at all.
We live close, though, even if
we're at different high schools.
Yeah.
Hey, Akane-chan.
Welcome.
Thanks for having me.
Thanks for watching the shop, Kotarou-kun.
Here, a gift.
Thanks.
Did you find the record you wanted?
Yup, found it.
Honestly, thanks for watching the shop.
When do you want to do the
parent-teacher meeting?
Whenever you want.
Where should I go for high school?
Have you decided?
I'm still thinking.
Can you clear off the table for me?
Sure.
Okay, your attention, please.
Dad has an announcement to make.
What?
I—
I'm home.
Welcome home.
I'm so hungry.
I'm probably going to be transferred
in the next reshuffle.
I'll be at the head office.
Huh? We're moving?
Again?
I won't know until they tell me.
Is it already that time again?
The head office in Chiba?
Yeah.
This is too sudden.
Hey, let's move to Tokyo, then.
Maybe.
It's dinner time. Put your
stuff away and get changed.
Okay.
Where are we going, if we go to Chiba?
Around Ichikawa, maybe.
Nice! That's closer to my school.
It's been so far for you, huh?
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
You don't know any
schools in Chiba, do you?
Come to think of it, I hear Koumei
High School is a good one in that area.
Koumei?
I heard about it in yoga class.
The instructor's second daughter goes there.
They love it.
It's big on clubs, too.
Koumei High School, right?
Koumei Private High School
This one, I think.
Literature
Miss Kobayashi's
Kitchen Nightmares
You don't have talent.
Well, to be honest, I don't think you're
cut out for serious literature.
Why don't you try
light novel-type stuff instead?
Dinner's ready, Kotarou.
Did you have practice again today?
Yeah.
Kotarou, have you chosen a school yet?
I hate to say this, but are you
really thinking about your future?
You hardly studied outside of cram
school during the summer, either.
Are you listening?
Yeah.
Honestly...
Say something to him, dear.
Not right now. We're eating.
He has to start taking his exam
studies more seriously.
He hasn't even chosen his high school yet.
It's getting way too late.
I'm sure he's thinking about it, too.
He's just putting his problems off.
This is an important time.
He has to choose his future.
What's up?
You seem out of it.
No, nothing.
Hey...
Yeah?
Have you heard of light novels?
I run a bookstore.
Have you read any?
Sure.
Were they any good?
Some of them.
They're the same as regular novels.
Some of them are good, and some of them suck.
It depends on your taste, too.
Huh...
Why?
Someone recommended them to me.
Why don't you read one, if you're curious?
I have plenty, too.
Yeah...
Daisuke!
Coming.
Chiba
Chiba high schools
Are you up?
Yeah, I'm still awake
What's up?
Studying
I lied...
I was going to study,
but I ended up reading... ^^;
lol x_x
GG
About tomorrow...
Yeah?
I think my club will run late,
so go home without me >_<
Okay
Yes
sir!
The track meet is coming up
I'm gonna practice hard
Me too
Kawagoe Festival's coming up,
so I'm practicing hard!
Woo!
Let's do this
Let's do this!!
Is it your last track meet?
Yup
I think I'm going to be super nervous
Can I
come watch the track meet?
Eeeeek!
Just Say No
Sorry
Aww lol
Well...
I'd be embarrassed...
All right ^_^
I'll be cheering for you from afar
Thanks
I'll do good!
Push with a
mother's touch
All right.
Take care.
I'll come to cheer for you later.
Okay.
See you.
It's time.
Yeah.
Track and Field Stadium
She told me to upload it.
Together?
I think so.
Man, my turn's in the afternoon.
That's a problem?
Well, not really.
Programs
500 yen each
2016 Fall
Saitama First Middle School Track Meet
I'd like one, please.
Mizuno Akane
I'm running soon.
My last track meet (omg)
Run like mad
Have fun
Push with a
mother's touch
All right.
They're going to call for the
third-year 100-meter soon.
Let's go, Akane.
Okay.
Go, Senpai!
You've got this.
Go!
Cheer for us, okay?
Yup!
There she is!
Akane!
Go, Akane!
The eight competitors of group 1 in
the girls' 100-meter dash will now enter.
On your marks...
Set...
The eight competitors of
group 2 will now enter.
On your marks...
Set...
Mizuno!
Go!
Yes!
A new personal best!
Akane!
Man, my nerves...
The boys start at noon, right?
Yeah, 400.
Good job. Personal best.
Thanks.
Three Years
Good Job
Jeez, Mom.
What's up?
Nothing.
It's over.
Yeah.
This is our last lunch together.
Hey, don't say that.
But...
Don't!
We ran so much.
Seriously, don't. I'll cry.
It was so exhausting.
Chinatsu!
She's crying.
Well...
Akane.
Thanks for the past three years.
You, too.
I would've given up without you two.
Chinatsu...
Thanks.
Don't laugh.
Well, your nose is really red.
He's right.
Bright red.
You're awful!
Girls'
Mizuno Akane
New personal best!!
Congrats
Are you continuing?
Track.
In high school.
Are you?
I am.
I think I want to.
I like running.
You should go to a competitive
school, if you're serious about it.
The equipment and environment are way better.
That's what last year's third-years told me.
Which school's competitive?
Tokorozawa Sakae, or Saitama Academy...
I can't go if I move, though.
It's not decided or anything yet.
Don't tell anyone, okay?
Where to?
Chiba?
I think they said Ichikawa.
Chiba...
I think Koumei's good in Chiba.
I think you could make it
in on a recommendation.
I've heard of it.
My mom said it's good, too.
Okay.
You're moving, huh?
I told you, I don't know.
Mizuno-senpai, Sensei's calling.
Okay.
And then?
She just randomly started talking to me.
Seriously?
I'm pretty sure we met at some track meet...
You remembered her?
Vaguely.
That's amazing.
Sounds like she'll make for a good rival.
Hey...
Yeah?
Why don't we all go to the
Kawagoe Festival together next month?
Sounds good.
The local train bound for Kawagoe will
be arriving momentarily on track 21.
It'll be the last thing the
track club does together.
Yeah, I'll go.
Are you sure, Akane?
For your safety, please
stand behind the white line.
What about Azumi-kun?
Oh, yeah.
He's going to be in the hayashi.
All right, I'll message
everyone on LINE later.
Okay.
Where should we go?
This is unusual.
Huh?
You, inviting everyone to go together.
I'm the club captain, after all.
Yeah.
Hey, Hira...
Have you not given up?
On what?
I haven't even taken a shot yet.
I don't blame you.
You can't change how you feel.
Can I come in?
Yeah.
Listen,
about high school...
You don't have to get into a good school.
Go wherever you need to
go to do what you love.
Take it easy.
Well, goodnight.
Koumei High School
Azumi-kun: Are you awake?
Are you awake?
Yeah
There's something I need
to apologize for...
Huh? What?
I went to watch the track meet
No!
No what?
Uh, nothing.
Sorry I didn't tell you
Nah
That's a surprise though
You were awesome
Actually
There's something I need
to tell you, too
Huh? What?
I might be moving to Chiba
The Wind Rises
Ayane's Boyfriend 2
You should go out with a guy with high specs.
Smart, kind, good-looking, rich, and...
Truck coming through!
Sorry for the inconvenience.
Pardon.
He's the one!
And that's how I met my boyfriend.
You should go out with a
guy with a trade skill.
Guys' Girl Talk, Girls' Guy Talk
We went in Kyoto, too.
Seriously?
Damn!
You had the money?
Her parents are loaded.
Holy crap.
You're a god.
I know, right?
We went in Kyoto, too.
Ew!
Gross.
Who paid?
I did. All of it.
That sucks!
What a parasite.
I know, right?