Episode 7   Umaru's Onii-chan
Onii-chan, could you get me a drink?
Quick! Hup! Whoa!
You could at least get your own drink.
Thanks... Hup! Whee!
I know she's off today,
but she's really lazing around to the fullest.
She should at least get the
stuff she wants herself.
Onii-chan.
What?
Could you bring me my potato chips?
The Ridges
are
Delicious!
Sour Cream and Onion
Potato Chips
Thanks! Ooh, right there!
Hey, Umaru.
Is it okay to throw away this
box that's on the floor?
Huh? I don't need any boxes
that are lying on the floor.
Onii-chan.
Now what?
I just wanted to call you.
It's already nine.
You should stop lazing around and get up now.
'Kay.
Are you going somewhere, Onii-chan?
I'm taking out the trash.
Oh, could you pick up Young Jumpu at
the convenience store while you're out?
That's enough already!
O-Onii-chan, have you seen the
box that was on the bookshelf?
Hmm?
This Hatsune Migu figure's box.
There were...
"Various Expressions" Parts Included!
various facial expression parts in that box.
Uh, I threw that away this morning.
No way!
Wh-Why did you throw it away?!
Well, you said I could throw it away.
Huh?
Huh? I don't need any boxes
that are lying on the floor.
Yeah, I did say that.
Well, I didn't really like the parts that
figure had, so it doesn't really matter.
I-Is that something it won't work without?
Come on, Umaru! Tell me!
Onii-chan, you idiot!
How could you throw it away?!
Why didn't you look in the box first?!
That was really important to me!
Onii-chan's troubled.
Maybe now I can laze around
and not get yelled at.
All right! I'm gonna let
him have it some more.
Ugh, screw you, Onii-chan!
I'm going to sleep.
Huh? Onii-chan?
Onii-chan?
Onii-chan?!
Ugh, screw you, Onii-chan!
I'm home.
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan! Where were you?!
Well, I went to look for the doll I threw away,
but they didn't have Hatsune whatever.
They recommended this instead.
Is this not good enough?
Onii-chan, they don't sell figures
at a Japanese doll store.
What? Really?!
The Next Day
Come on, Onii-chan.
You're going to be late to work.
R-Right.
Come on, already.
Umaru...
Hm? What is it?
Are you sure that doll is okay?
It's totally different from the
one I threw away, right?
It's fine.
I didn't even care that you threw it away.
What?! Then why were you crying?!
Onii-chan.
Hm? What is it?
I just wanted to call you.
Hatsune
Coming.
Oh, Ebina-chan. Welcome.
U-U-Um...
Umaruun
This is the first time you've invited
us out to eat, Ebina-chan.
I got some gift certificates,
so I thought I'd repay you for
the restaurant the other day.
Ramen, huh?
How exciting.
Thank goodness.
Umaru seems pretty happy about this.
Probably because I've prohibited
instant ramen at home.
Sankakutou Ramen
Welc'm!
The workers sure are lively.
Yeah.
The whole store is oily.
Does that mean their ramen is pretty heavy?
If possible, I'd prefer something lighter...
Onii-chan, Onii-chan.
What is it?
Could you order either this or this,
and just share a little with me?
Hm? Okay, sure.
Thanks f'r waitin'!
Two double garlic ramen, "Arashi,"
and one red hot death ramen!
So good!
It's really heavy, not to mention really oily.
And the garlic makes the soup extremely rich.
The pork back fat and garlic
run around in my mouth.
But that's why it's great!
This is no longer ramen...
It's junk food!
I would pair this ramen
with cola!
There we go. Tiny ramen.
Umaru-chan even eats ramen
in such a pretty way.
But I've never seen her
eat something like this.
I wonder if she's just putting up with it.
I really want to eat this with cola...
Hey, Umaru.
This is really spicy.
How pathetic, Onii-chan.
Then we can trade.
You can't eat wasabi, but you're
okay with chili peppers?
I'm fine, Onii-chan.
Is something wrong, Ebina-chan?
No... Nothing at all.
Sankakutou Ramen
Thanks!
Thanks, Ebina-chan. That was really good.
Thank you for the meal.
Oh, no problem. It was my pleasure.
You can't eat spicy stuff, Onii-chan?
No, that was just especially spicy.
I'm fine, Onii-chan.
I'd love for the three of us to go again.
Yeah, sure.
Huh?! The same place?!
So we worked hard making nothing but ramen,
and the shop just got covered in oil.
This is the true...
"Oilamen"!
Oden
Sankaku
Taihei... Don't you think it's messed up?
For someone to come to a mixer
when she has a boyfriend...
I-I dunno...
Well, it is! It's totally against the rules!
Hey, could I get another draft?!
Sure thing.
Look, is that what you wanted to talk about?
Then I'd like to go ho—
There's something I want to ask you, Taihei.
Wh-What?
You...
Here's your draft.
Oh, thanks.
You...
And your croquettes.
Thanks.
Yo—
And your octopus with wasabi.
Th-Thanks...
You're totally living with
your girlfriend, aren't you?
No, I'm not. What the hell?
You liar! I always thought it was weird.
You go straight home after work,
you don't go to mixers or hostess clubs...
You don't even go to girls' bars!
What the hell is a girls' bar?
And!
People in our office have seen you
walking with a hot young girl!
Wha...
They're probably talking about my sister.
There it is again, "sister."
No one goes shopping with their sister!
Th-They don't?
I was dumped yesterday!
I can't go on knowing that you have a woman!
Can I come over after this?
Nope.
Man... It's always exciting
going over to a friend's house.
I didn't tell him he could follow me...
Well, I guess it's better than
having weird rumors going around.
I should text Umaru.
"My coworker is coming over."
I'm sure once he meets her at the door,
he'll be convinced and go home.
Sh-She's asleep...
She's so cute!
What is this adorable creature?!
Hey, you're being too loud.
I feel like the wound on
my heart has been soothed.
You get it now? This is my sister.
So go home already.
Don't be so stingy. I'm just gonna look.
C'mon, give me healing.
You're being creepy! Go home!
Just for a little bit!
It's not like you lose anything
from it, so come on!
Onii-chan?
Hair Growth
Formula
Onii-chan's head exploded and got huge!
What's with this creature?!
I have to pull it out! I have to pull it out!
Oh, boy...
See ya!
Hey, Onii-chan. Who was that, anyway?
He's my coworker, Bomber.
Bomber?
Motoba
I'm home.
No Trespassing
I'm home!
Wh-Wha—
Kirie!
It's been a while...
Your Onii-chan will give
you a piggyback ride.
Don't come in here without permission!
Ow! What's with you, Kirie?!
Stop! Hey!
Can't you even read "no trespassing,"
you exploded gorilla?!
I...
want to go to an old-timey candy store!
Candy store?
Stop
Ramune
Candy Toys
Matsuribayashi
Ice Cream
This is truly
a good old-fashioned candy store!
A ten-yen game covered in rust!
Out of Order
A Monkey Kong machine with a sunshade!
The capsule machines are broken
and the sides are coming apart!
And there are still things inside!
This is a true candy store!
Shuba
Nothing less from UMR-san. I commend
you for knowing about this shop.
I found it about six months ago.
The place is open, but I'm not sure
if they're actually in business.
Oh, you're right. I don't see anyone working.
But if the door's open, it must
mean they're open for business.
Let's pick out some candy.
Right. I'm sure someone will come out.
Cola Drinko
This is that Cola Drinko that calls itself
cola despite not having any carbonation!
Also, cola ramune,
Cola Gummies
and cola gummies!
They're totally different,
but the word "cola" is tempting me!
Cola
Obsessed?
Though it's an old-fashioned candy store,
I've see many of these at convenience stores.
Carrot
Please yell "Obaa-chan"
as loud as you can.
(There is a chance
I might be sleeping.)
What on earth is this?!
Gungare
I can get all of these,
and it won't cost me 500 yen.
Candy stores are the best.
Oh, UMR-san?
What?
Did you see any of those little yogurts
shaped like this anywhere?
They come with a wooden spoon.
Oh, Yogure?
They weren't up at the front?
I think I saw a stock of them under here.
Morocco Fruit Yogure
Sylphyn.
Here, eat this.
It's really good.
It's Japanese candy.
Well, then... Maybe the owner's in the back.
They haven't come out at all.
Excuse me!
Please come help us.
Please yell "Obaa-chan"
as loud as you can.
(There is a chance
I might be sleeping.)
Obaa-chan!
Sh-She's not coming out...
Let's yell it at the same time,
so it'll be even louder.
Ready, and...
Obaa-chan!
I haven't had one in a while,
but Yogure is great.
Of course it is!
Umaru, don't eat potato chips
first thing in the morning.
Here's your lunch.
Go get ready for school.
Jeez. You sound like a mom, Onii-chan.
Well, be careful, you two.
Bye, Onii-chan.
U-Um, uh, have a good day.
I'm sorry!
Bomber, we just got to the office.
Yeah, I usually get a boost in the afternoon.
Taihei-senpai, my PC froze.
Could I ask for your assistance?
Huh? Again?
2-D Love
Channel
Suck
You two really need to stop.
Today was really tiring again.
Well, I finished up earlier than usual,
so maybe I'll go to the supermarket,
then make dinner...
Where am I?
This is a residential area,
so it's hard to tell...
Do I go back the way I came,
or keep moving forward?
Nyankoro
Cannery
Nyanderful
It says "Nyanderful!"
That's right! I remember
seeing this sign with Umaru.
I've been down this road before...
Which means it'll lead to a road that I know.
I guess I'll keep going.
But I can't remember at all.
If I came here with Umaru...
I don't go out with her much, though.
Actually, she doesn't come
outside much in general.
When did I come here?
In junior high?
Wait, was it high school?
If it was after I became a salaryman...
I'd definitely remember.
It's been about five years
since I started working...
I keep doing the same thing every day,
so it's no wonder I forget things from the past.
It must be around dinner time.
I think the last time I went this way,
it was around the same time of day.
I was hungry, so I wanted to hurry home.
But Umaru always throws
a tantrum at times like that.
Taihei-kun, are you hungry?
What was that just now?
Why did Umaru just call me "Taihei-kun"?
Huh? Something's wrong here...
I guess I'll go home and ask Umaru.
First, I need to get to the main street.
Then I'll get a better idea of where I am.
You're the cat from earlier, aren't you?
Are you here because the cannery's nearby?
That's right. It's not Umaru.
What's the matter, Taihei-kun?
Oh, a cat.
Mommy loves them, too.
Aren't they adorable?
Yeah.
The school's the other way,
so home is this way.
See ya. Watch out for cars.
Onii-chan, dinner nao!
All right. When I get home,
I'll make Umaru something
better than potato chips.
Next Time
Episode 8       Umaru and Christmas and New Year's
Gosh, anime's truly amazing, isn't it?
Uh... Who are you?
I'm Alex.
I should be meeting you soon, Umaru-san.
Those who can't wait, please read volume 4.
Oh, you're just here to advertise.