Chance ball!
Left!
The final set...
Win! Then win some more!
If we lose this...
It'll be over.
Haikyu!!
Episode 23: The Point that Changes the Momentum
Nice receive!
#10!
They've probably changed to different
signs for their god-like quicks.
Because they're such simple signs,
it would be pretty easy to change them.
Still, there's got to be a
way to tell them apart.
Maybe when they keep their eye on
the ball longer, it's a normal quick,
and when they just go for it,
it'll be the god-like quick?
In general, it's probably best
if we keep our eyes on #10.
Right.
#10...
But, in the end, the shrimp
is just efficient decoy.
Don't forget that. Okay?
Right!
All right!
We can't get the shot that will end this.
This rally is going on forever.
Overall, Seijoh's better
at everything, but...
A feint!
...their libero has far
better defensive skills.
All right!
Asahi-san!
The setter received that?!
Now he can't toss!
He'll have to attack now.
Probably to the left.
Watacchi!
Right!
Karasuno                            Aoba Johsai
All right!
I've been wondering this, but...
Hm?
I think Seijoh's libero
was formerly a setter.
What do you mean?
Thanks!
If the libero lifts the ball
from in front of the attack line,
it's illegal to do an overhand
spike from behind the line.
Just now, that libero jumped
up at the very edge of the line
and set while in midair.
Which means, a spike was totally fine.
They can use high-level attacks.
This is why they call
Aoba Johsai a powerhouse.
All right!
Daichi-san, nice receive!
Asahi-san!
The ball's going back!
I'll push it over!
All right!
He did a toss that close to the edge...
Awesome.
All right! You're all fighting well!
Keep cool!
Right!
It looks like they're getting used
to attacks that cut into the middle,
so use the sides of the
court as much as you can!
Right!
What's with the lack of
holes in Seijoh's attacks?
No matter what situation they're put in,
they're able to counter with powerful
attacks, like it's nothing.
Let's go!
Right!
Because Sugawara went in once,
Karasuno was definitely able
to pick itself back up.
Now they're not nervous or overly aggressive.
Right now, everyone's probably using
their current strength to the fullest.
That might be exactly why
we're seeing the difference
in their strength as a team.
Aoba Johsai                  Karasuno
Damn it...
Nice, Tsukishima!
You keep showing up with that annoying
feint when everyone's forgotten about it.
Phrasing...
With every player performing
at 100% of their ability,
Come on! Talk more!
Keep it up!
Seijoh is probably the stronger team.
But sometimes they'll only use 70%
and then bounce up to 120% of their ability.
That's how things can play out
during a match, right?
And Karasuno has the ultimate decoy
who can let everyone attack at 120% of their ability.
Awesome. Awesome. Seijoh's awesome!
Out. Out! I want to hurry and get out.
I want to hurry and go out. Out! Out!
Hinata.
Yes?
Do you remember what Ukai-san said?
About attacking both sides of the
court as much as possible?
Right. That's the best attack.
We haven't used that much this time around.
Yes!
This sucks.
Aoba Johsai                      Karasuno
Our team is settling into a rhythm, and yet
if that little sucky guy
enters the court...
I can't help but be uneasy about that.
A small beast that's gathered its
frustrations while in the warm up zone.
Karasuno is fighting back in the final set,
One more!
Go! One more!
Go, Shoyo!
yet we don't stand a chance against Seijoh.
If we're going to get even
one step ahead of them,
it'll be up to them.
Give Karasuno that one step!
Nice receive!
Left! Left!
Two blocks!
Kageyama, nice one-touch!
Chance ball!
"The sides of the court
as much as possible."
Here it is!
The attack that seems to
rip through the air:
that broad cross!
Rule the Court
Nice shot, Hinata!
Crap.
We can't let those two stay
on the court too long
after they've gotten fired up.
Makki, nice!
All right!
Bring it around, bring it around!
Hurry and bring the rotation around.
Bring the shrimp
one step closer to the back line!
Got it!
The ball's not coming down. So amazing.
Nice cover, Makki!
It's coming back!
Chance ball!
Fly
Again?!
"The sides of the court
as much as possible."
Aoba Johsai                          Karasuno
All right!
That little guy's amazing.
Volleyball, more than anything,
is a sport where you keep
jumping continuously,
so I believe it's also a battle with gravity.
Jumping as decoy,
jumping to block,
and jumping to spike.
Nishinoya, nice cover!
As the rally keeps going,
Go back! Go back!
One more! One more!
fatigue sets in and your mental faculties decline.
Left, left!
We're gonna stop them one more time!
To be honest, you want
to skip the blocking,
and I've had times where I hoped
someone else would spike it.
When long rallies continue and I get
deprived of oxygen, I think,
"Hurry up and drop, ball...
Preferably on the other side."
Bring it!
If I slow down even for a moment,
it'll delay everyone else.
At my height, if I ease off
on my jumps even a little,
I'll be shot down in an instant.
Run! Run!
Jump! Jump!
If you want to stay here!
Like hell
am I going to let you spike freely!
Right now, the sides of the court...
And then...
Break through the middle!
Pipe penetration!
Nice point!
Hinata!
Damn it!
Sorry. I totally got lured out.
I knew that this would be the
perfect timing for a pipe,
and yet... just now...
I was about to toss to Hinata.
I was about to have my toss taken.
Nice determination, Hinata!
Thanks!
The ultimate... decoy.
Aoba Johsai                  Karasuno
Karasuno caught up.
They're tied.
I'll go get the towels.
Thanks.
The rallies are lasting a lot longer
than the first and second set.
That's got to be tiring.
But...
I'm jealous.
What are we going to do
about #10's broad cross?
Let's get rid
of that broad cross.
Aoba Johsai                         Karasuno
Tanaka, nice point!
In the next rotation,
Hinata will be in the back line.
Hey! Are you all right?
I-I'm fine...
Make sure you cash in all you've got
before moving into the back line.
I know that!
Kunimi, nice receive!
Kindachi!
#12! #12!
Nishinoya, nice receive!
Chance!
Is he going to do another
broad... or wait... Huh?
No mark?
Did they give up on the block?
All right! Go free, Hinata!
I can see really well.
Nice receive!
Was there no mark on purpose?!
In this short amount of time...
Just how fast at
switching gears are they?
Now a dump?!
A dump attack taking advantage
of our moment of hesitation.
Let's get rid of that broad.
Get rid of it? How?
That shrimp's broad is god-like.
It's really fast, but his
body will go with the momentum,
so he won't be able to redirect the ball.
Yeah.
Instead of blocking that
broad cross, we'll use a dig.
Right!
An unstoppable block is just going to
get in the way of receiving the ball.
No matter how difficult things get,
don't forget to think and communicate!
Nice receive!
We can't even bring Seijoh
down with that!
Damn. Right when we don't
want them to get ahead,
his turn to serve comes up.
We'll end this in one!
Right!
Rule the Court
Net in! All right! Lucky!
There's nothing you could have
done about that. Move on.
Damn it. We're two points behind again.
Stay calm.
Sorry! Cover!
All right!
Got it!
Kageyama!
Asahi, last!
That was close!
Calm down! Don't lose your cool!
This isn't ending any time soon...
When you make it through a long rally,
you can shift the game's momentum.
With this rally, getting that one
point will be crucial.
Cover!
I'm not going to let you have it...
the point, or our momentum!
It connected!
But who'll get the last hit?
Center!
Shoyo, we're counting on you!
Break through!
Stop him!
All right!
Aoba Johsai                 Karasuno
Damn. They've used up their two timeouts.
It can't be helped.
They've got to physically break
that momentum with a timeout,
or Seijoh's going to take control.
A-At times like this,
your voice is important!
Something... Isn't there something?
Make sure you're using your voice!
Something to change the momentum?
Go, go, Karasuno!
Push it, push it, Karasuno!
It doesn't have to be a trump card.
Just something...
Hey, first it's "go, go."
Anything to give us a change.
Match me!
Seijoh touched net. Thank goodness!
I'm sorry.
Don't mind.
But...
The shrimp's on the back line!
We're counting on you.
Right.
If they miss here, Seijoh will
have the advantage at 20 points.
Hinata, relax!
Right!
If they take the momentum,
we won't be able to catch up.
Hey, Shimada, look at that.
T-Tadashi's the pinch server?!
What is Keishin thinking?!
He's an idiot!
I told him that it's still mostly pure luck!
I think he wants even that pure luck.
You don't know what's going
to change the momentum.
Karasuno's got a pinch server?
Are they good at serves?
Or are they just simply trying
to change the atmosphere?
Either way, we're not giving you this flow.
Yamaguchi, nice serve!
But I'm not gonna lose!
He doesn't want to be pulled
out, even for a moment.
Yamaguchi.
Go and change the momentum.
R-Right!
This line...
Everything beyond this
line is a different world.
It feels like the temperature
on this side... is different.
You got a great spot, Yamaguchi!
Right!
Blast them one, Yamaguchi!
Nice serve!
N-Nice serve. Take it easy.
Asahi, do you understand the
meaning of "take it easy"?
Anyone would be scared at this timing.
This is his first serve at his
first high school match!
Is the coach a super sadist?!
I'm nervous, too.
Crap, Yamaguchi will feel that.
Stay calm...
I think the back of my head is a little
safer than if Hinata was serving.
Is that all right?
He already has enough reason to be nervous,
but won't there be more pressure
from playing with his seniors?
Oh, right.
Hey, Yamaguchi!
Hit a nice serve!
Aoba Johsai                          Karasuno
Dang... He's so stiff.
It can't be helped.
Relying on your team is most of volleyball.
Serving is the only time you're alone.
Everyone will be looking at you,
and you've got all the pressure.
I'm scared... but...
But when you're standing in the serve
position, you're the center of attention,
no matter who you are.
Show them...
That you can fight, too!
Jump floater?!
Go in!
Rule the Court
Aoba Johsai                     Karasuno
Go, go, Seijoh!
Push it, push it, Seijoh!
All right. Lucky!
I-I'm sorry...
Don't mind!
D-Don't worry about it.
I'm sorry...
Nope.
Don't mind, Yamaguchi-kun.
Don't worry about it.
Shake it off.
Yamaguchi!
S-Sorry!
Make sure you make it next time.
Next...
Right!
Karasuno's mood changed?
The captain's amazing.
I'm still no match for him.
Man, but I feel relieved,
like most of the pressure's gone.
Same here.
Eh? So he got brought out
here because of a pinch,
but if he fails, he'll be pulled out?
That's sort of sad.
That's the job of a pinch server.
That one shot
has both the game's momentum
and their pride riding on it.
And Tadashi messed up.
But this chance to feel this
regret and his own helplessness
will definitely make him stronger.
Did the black team cheer up of a sudden?
It's just like Tattsun says...
You don't know
what's going to change the momentum.
Next...
The chance to fight next...
Grab it!
Daichi-san, nice receive!
All right. Don't let them break the streak!
Though it looks so close,
Seijoh's back is so far.
If they can't get any points now, Karasuno
will just have to wait and lose.
Cover! Cover!
Is he spiking from lower because he's tired?
Kunimi-chan!
They're so high-level...
Nice cover!
This is the third game?
It's coming back. Chance ball!
Out, huh?
I'm sorry!
Aoba Johsai                   Karasuno
All right!
Come on... break! Break!
Out!
Nice call!
Aoba Johsai                 Karasuno
Good! Good!
Ryu, last!
Get one more point!
Yeah!
The ball in front of me... Everything!
His foot! He kicked it!
All right!
Looks painful.
Nice, Hinata!
Break!
One more point!
Aoba Johsai                 Karasuno
Kageyama, nice serve!
One more...
Daichi-san!
I'm not going to lose!
I'm not going to...
All right!
They all feel the same.
Now Seijoh's at
Aoba Johsai                          Karasuno
match point.
One more point!
Guys, don't freak out!
If we fall, fall forward!
All right!
Asahi-san, nice shot!
One more point!
Tanaka, nice serve!
One more!
Nice serve!
If I miss this serve, the game will be over.
Even if they are able to receive
it, and do a decent attack,
it'll all be over.
A quick is coming!
Make sure you don't drop it!
At least...
Touch it!
Crap! It's going past the net!
They're going to hit it head on!
One-hand toss!
All right!
Next Episode Preview
You guys are doing a great
job of pushing forward.
Thanks!
24 vs 24... A deuce.
The one who gets two points first, wins.
Of course, we'll be the ones to win.
Yeah!
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"Removing The Solitary King."
Episode 24: "Removing The Solitary King"