You're such a slowpoke, Rita.
Alright, everyone, stay where you are and listen.
We have some new workers
joining us here at the laundry mill today.
Now, ladies, if you'd introduce yourselves...
I'm Bea...
Becky!
Dorothea.
I'm Chieko.
My name is Priscilla.
Quit staring at me, would ya?!
It's Alice.
Anyone disrespects me...
And I knock 'em to Kingdom Come!
Hey!
What kind of a cover is that?
I'm a former delinquent who decided to
turn over a new leaf when her mother fell ill,
So I went to work, but I can't hide my bad attitude.
That's an elaborate backstory.
It's the optimal cover for this mission.
Right. The mission.
Poison Gas Jack.
An elusive phantom killer who's been making
a name for himself in the tabloids.
He's been assassinating important people
who've shown support for the Commonwealth.
But we haven't identified any backers.
We believe he's working alone.
Then we have but to exterminate him.
I will handle it.
A man who uses poison gas will be an easy opponent.
We'll have to find him first.
I wonder what he's trying to accomplish.
Look at this.
This is nerve gas, isn't it?
I thought production of nerve gas
was banned by the Geneva Convention.
Precisely.
So where did he get his illegal poison?
Getting the ingredients would be difficult, too.
Which means he's in the Army?
Control had the same idea.
Gas produced before the Convention
is lying unused in military storehouses.
You mean inside the London Wall?
Yes.
The storehouses were built
before the second round of construction,
So you'd have to go through
the military barracks to get to them.
The odds are good that our poisoner
lives in those barracks.
How many are housed there?
About 1200.
That many?!
How will we find him?
Disguise ourselves as soldiers?
No, the Army is a boys' club.
Women would draw too much attention.
And living in the barracks alongside them,
it would be difficult to maintain a manly facade.
Then what do we do?
Men don't do laundry.
What?
That's true.
None of the boys in class-
Of course!
Nerve gas would adhere to his clothes.
And the barracks send all of the men's uniforms
to a laundry mill for washing.
So we infiltrate the laundry mill
and find the uniform that reacts to a pyridine test.
This is going to take some time.
Um, Miss Alice, you can't just
move the desk around without-
I don't like being ordered around!
Go away!
Y-yes, ma'am!
So that's what she meant by "optimal cover."
It does keep people from asking questions.
By the way, Your Highness, why did you come along?
I'm a part of the team, too!
Listen to you talk.
You just wanted to see what it was like, didn't you?
Yes, I did!
This may be a foolish question, but...
Who is the master laundress of this establishment?
Master?
That would have to be Marilla.
Many pardons.
I've heard that you have the greatest skill with the iron.
I request your guidance.
Stand next to me.
First, watch.
Then if you have any questions, just ask.
You have my thanks.
Japanese people are odd.
I guess I can't expect to find it that soon.
Still...
Someone turn it off!
I think that's all for this one.
Guess it's time for a break.
But we haven't been working an hour.
Hooray! Break time!
Let's have some lunch!
Really!
Let's go!
In two days, we've tested
a total of 150 articles of clothing.
But we couldn't confirm a single reaction
to our chemical test.
At this rate, it's gonna take us a month.
Those women are all too lazy!
If they would work harder, they could earn more!
You're very strict, aren't you, Miss Chise?
Heave-ho.
Huh?
Guess it's about time for a break.
Whew!
So much work today.
Put down the iron, Japan Girl.
No, thank you. I am not tired.
You may all rest without me.
Take a break! That's the rule!
You have but one life to live!
Why would you not give everything your best effort?
Hey! I'm trying-
Rita!
Are you alright?
Yes.
Thank you for your help.
These scars...
This is why I told you to take a break!
The machinery here is junk!
If we don't give it a rest every so often, people get hurt.
We get paid by the day.
If we get hurt, we can't earn any money.
We may not like it, but we do what we can to get on.
Is the foreman in?
Pwah.
You rabble. I don't care who,
but one of you get the foreman.
Tell him Franky is here. He'll understand.
Surely you are aware, Foreman,
that your payment is due.
Y-yes, of course.
So what will it be?
If you can't pay, then I'll run
your sorry little mill into the ground.
Are you ready for that?
No, I need a little...
Is he going to close the mill?
He can't!
Are we bankrupt?
I always said that foreman was useless as a manager!
What do we do?
I don't know.
That's going to put a damper on our plans.
Are we even going to be paid this month?
I didn't know this place was in debt.
What do we do?
Mother's surgery is at the end of the month.
Chise, don't.
Why not?
If you can't pay now, when can you?
H-hey!
Pardon me.
What do you want?
How do you do, everyone?
What? Who are you?
We're in the middle of an important discussion!
I know. And I've come with an important proposal.
I'm going to buy this laundry mill.
Huh?
What...
And I will pay off the debt.
That should resolve all the problems, shouldn't it?
Stay out of this, little girl!
We're not playing a game here!
Y-you would really buy the mill, debt and all?
Yes. I would.
Stop making up stories! A woman, buying the mill!
Who do you think you-
Ow! Oww!
That hurts!
Don't you dare raise your hand against a lady,
you piece of garbage!
Boss!
Don't be such a pigheaded jackass!
No, stop!
She says she's gonna buy the mill,
so shut up and sell it to her, dammit!
Come on, what are you even doing?
What were you thinking,
buying a mill that's losing money?
If the laundry mill were to close,
that would be the end of our mission, wouldn't it?
We just need two more weeks
to check all of the soldiers' uniforms.
And we need to keep the mill
in business until then, is that it?
But Princess...
You don't have that much money
at your disposal, do you?
I'm surprised you knew that.
But I don't intend to let the laundry mill
be a poor investment.
You intend to make a profit from it?
Yes!
Impossible! Not from that place!
That isn't like you, Miss Chise.
I thought we could do anything
with hard work and practice, right?
But...
What about you, Ange? Do you think it's impossible?
Nothing is impossible for a spy.
Don't you lie to us.
The machines here have always made
such terrible noises.
I don't think they've ever seen proper maintenance.
I'd believe that from that stingy foreman.
I think if we just fix them up right,
they'll be able to work that much harder for us.
And the accidents will cease?
Yes!
All we have to do is replace the old parts,
and it will be fine!
We should rearrange them, too.
The workpath is too convoluted.
If we line the machines up according to work sequence,
we can save ourselves a lot of running around.
I imagine they placed them
in order of when they were purchased.
They do look heavy.
I can change that weight to zero.
Then I order you as foreman.
Rearrange the machinery to create
the optimal work path.
Right, and we'll get all the tools
organized while we're at it.
Some of the girls can't read,
so let's have pictures on the signs.
Let's repair these pipes, too.
Princess, may we try the method used in my country?
Sounds fascinating! Tell me about it!
What happened here?
It's so organized.
The belts have stopped squeaking.
It's like a new machine!
We serviced them!
Some dust got mixed in with the old grease,
and clogged it up.
We cleaned it, so it won't stop anymore.
Wait, YOU girls did all this?
Yes.
In one night?
Yes, in one night.
And so, everyone.
Today we'll have a fresh start, and work our hardest!
This is easy!
So fast!
Ugh!
May I have a word?
We know an excellent way to do laundry.
Miss Chieko.
When we're sad, we'll all laugh
We want to go see our mothers and fathers
What's that song?
It's coming from the laundry mill.
We want to go see our mothers and fathers
When we want to cry, we'll all laugh
It's an odd song.
So we can cry tears of joy
So we can
We're done.
For the whole week.
We did it!
I don't believe it!
We finished so fast!
Ahem.
Ladies of the laundry mill!
Now that we've improved our efficiency,
I don't suppose you'd like to improve
our revenue, as well?
What? You mean earn more money?
If we wash more, we earn more.
But there's nothing left to wash,
And the Army won't bring more 'round til the weekend.
Then we'll just have to get some from other sources.
Some of you girls could really shine with a little polish.
What?
Hey! Keep lollygagging
and it'll be dark before we're through!
Hello!
I'm here with a business proposal.
What kind of proposal?
We would like to wash all of your work clothes.
"We"?
We look forward to working with you!
With you!
Me, too!
You sure are cute!
Oh, bother.
We already have a launderer.
But you can change that!
Boss!
Let's let them wash our clothes!
Weren't you just complaining about their sloppy work?
You boys...
I suppose we could see how you do.
Hooray!
That's an awful lot of clothes.
We had a lot of success,
thanks to our excellent saleslady.
What? Rita?
Yoohoo!
What happened?
You're all so pretty, I hardly recognize you!
Miss Dorothea taught us how to wear makeup.
What! Lucky!
No fair!
Do me, too!
Me, too!
Alright, save the chatter.
Let's get these clothes in the machines.
Yes, ma'am!
Thanks for doing sales, Rita.
Yeah!
What's this report?
It's the income and expense report
for the laundry mill Princess purchased.
They've increased revenue 231% since last year.
Ho ho, how interesting.
What the hell are they doing?
I thought their job was to find Poison Gas Jack!
Wasting their time on these frivolities!
What does D say about it?
That it was a necessary measure
in continuing the mission.
Where's my uniform?
I left it on my bed.
Oh, is that all? They came around collecting laundry,
so I gave it to them for you.
It's just, this guy always does his own laundry!
He didn't want your help, Mate.
What? Have to do it the way Mummy taught you?
Turn one more round
Let's do our best to earn a living
To eat delicious food
When we're tired, we'll all sing
So we can stop our sighing
You can use this if you wish.
Uh, thanks.
When we're sad, we'll all laugh
A bandage?
You wear it like this.
When we're sad, we'll all laugh
We want to go see our mothers and fathers
It's called a hachimaki.
When we want to cry, we'll all laugh
In my country, we use them to rouse our fighting spirit.
I see.
When we want to cry, we'll all laugh
So we can cry tears of joy.
Miss Dorothy!
What's up?
Look.
That's our Princess.
You have a way of attracting things.
Private William Ricard, Platoon 2.
His unit's barracks is right above the storehouse.
Then he's the one?
Yeah. I'll go get the car.
Put the evidence in this bag.
All right.
You.
What are you doing here?
None who work here feel the need
to walk with such cat-like tread.
And...
Scoundrel.
Hello? Chieko!
Marilla!
Long live the Kingdom!
NO!
I was...
Um...
Miss Chieko and the others
haven't come to work in days.
You don't think they have tummyaches, do you?
Ladies, would you all come here, please?
What is it? Why are we having a meeting?
Are our wages going up again?
I've decided to step down as foreman.
What?!
Why? We need you!
Tell us why!
What happened to Chieko?
Are ALL of you quitting?
No!
I still have so much to learn! Don't go!
They didn't even say goodbye!
Stay with us forever, Priscilla!
All of you, be quiet!
We've had people quit before, remember?
I'm sure they have their reasons.
Thank you, Marilla.
It's nothing. Forcing you to stay
would only make us all uncomfortable.
And so, about your new foreman...
I was hoping I could ask you, Marilla.
What?!
Really?
Marilla? Our foreman?
Then we've nothing to worry about!
No, no, no! Wait a minute! Just hold on!
No! I can't be foreman!
Then who else could I ask to do it?
If Marilla won't do it, I will!
And I'll give everyone three lunch breaks!
Then I volunteer!
I'll double our wages!
I'll turn the mill into a flower garden!
Fine! I'll do it!
Hooray!
We're counting on you, Marilla!
Foreman Marilla!
But I won't be as forgiving as Priscilla!
Get ready to work!
Yes, ma'am!
Priscilla!
Would you tell Chieko something for me?
I don't really know what's going on in her life...
But, um...
Tell her, "Don't let it beat you."
I will.
You think the girls at the laundry mill
will get on without us?
I do.
They are now strong enough.
I'm certain they'll be fine.
Let's go.
Yes, ma'am.