Amagiri Shinmei Style
Um...
A-Amagiri Shinmei Style First Sword,
Twin Dragons!
Let's call it a day.
Thank you very much.
Big Sis Haru sure is powerful, huh?
Saya-chan?
You were watching?
Yeah.
Hey, listen...
About that favor...
- Can't we just forget about—
- Nope.
But see, yelling out the name
of the move is kind of embarrassing.
No, it's not.
It's totally cool, so don't worry!
You think so?
You'll be fine.
You'll get used to it soon.
Okay, then, about the favor
I'm gonna ask you...
FAVOR TICKET
I want to beat my sister once,
no matter what.
Do you think you can help me out?
Burst into bloom,
Amaryllis!
Go!
We're in training now,
so what's with the daydreaming?
S-Sorry.
Breaking the Memory Barrier
The Eclipse Festa.
Haruka Amagiri lost.
Well, I hear that she didn't actually die.
Ayato...
Hey, Ayato!
Oh. Julis...
Wh-What's up?
Just as I thought,
your mind is on your sister...
No, that's...
You said before that you wouldn't go
out of your way to search for your sister.
Ayato... You...
Could it be that you're afraid?
Afraid?
Why your sister sealed your powers...
Why she vanished without a word...
When you're reunited with her,
the reason will become clear.
But precisely because you love her,
the fear must be real, as well.
The fear that your sister might
actually have abandoned you...
I see.
Yeah, that just might be the case.
It's painful to be rejected
by someone you cherish.
I know that all too well.
But it's also a fact that you can
never move on at this rate.
You need to think long and hard
about searching for your sister.
Afraid, huh?
Boo!
Help me get down from here!
Whoops-a-daisy.
Saya, I told you before.
Try not to scare me so much, will you?
But I couldn't get through to you
on your cell phone.
Come on, Ayato.
Have a seat.
So what was it
you wanted to see me about?
Wh-What's going on?
That's what I should be asking you.
Ayato!
Just what is it that's bothering you?
I see.
So you heard about it from Julis?
Riessfeld's really worried
about you, Ayato.
Otherwise, she'd never turn to me.
Ayato, do you really believe
that Big Sis Haru abandoned you?
Well...
Dummy!
I assure you!
There's absolutely no way
Big Sis Haru would ever abandon you!
Saya...
And besides, if Big Sis Haru
really did lose to someone...
not that I can believe it,
but if that really is the truth,
then it might be that she just has
no way of contacting you.
In which case, you can't afford
to sit around here, brooding.
Yeah, you're absolutely right, Saya.
All right.
Now that sounds more like my Ayato!
Saya...
Ayato, do you remember this?
A Favor Ticket, huh?
What a blast from the past...
You and I were always competing
with those tickets on the line.
Using this ticket to call in a favor,
you and I took on Big Sis Haru together.
Yeah, of course I remember.
Looks like your swordsmanship's
a lot better now.
All that basic training paid off, huh?
Well, but...
that's all... you ever...
let me do...
Right?
Saya-chan!
Leave it to me!
Now this is actually...
Ayato!
I think I panicked just a little.
I guess it would be insulting
if I didn't go all-out in return, right?
What was that?
The first of the Amagiri Shinmei Style
Hidden Techniques...
Banish Evil Spirits.
Banish Evil Spirits...
In the end, we never did manage
to beat Big Sis Haru even once.
Well, my sister was totally unstoppable.
Even though she was always
so laid-back.
Well, that's also true of you, Ayato.
We've got to find Big Sis Haru
and get the best of her next time.
You and me both, Ayato.
Yeah, I agree.
Although I'm pretty sure
we still can't beat her.
Well, when that day comes,
all we have to do is join forces.
So Ayato...
When you're in trouble,
you should lean on someone else.
Aside from me,
I'm sure there are other people
who'd help you out.
Though I kind of hate to admit it.
As you can see from their
previous matches,
these twins focus on attacking
only their opponents' weak points.
They create a situation where they have
an insurmountable advantage,
and only then do they
go on the offensive.
They sound like trouble.
That said, for this match only,
there is one thing in our favor.
In our favor?
If it's true that these twins only
attack their opponents' flaws,
then this time around,
that flaw couldn't be more obvious.
My seal, huh?
In which case, we should be able to gauge
what kind of tactics they'll go for.
Buying time...
So with that in mind,
how should we counter them?
This is the only strategy
I could come up with, but...
All right, now!
At last, the final match
of the quarterfinals is upon us!
SAYA SASAMIYA
KIRIN TOUDOU
DOROTEO LEMUS
ELLIOT FORSTER
ERNESTA KUHNE
CAMILLA PARETO
And since all the other matches played
at other venues have concluded,
three of the berths for the semifinals
have been locked up!
Which team will claim
that last semifinal spot?
First, here's the duo
from Seidoukan,
Ayato Amagiri
and Julis-Alexia von Riessfeld!
And their opponents... the team
from Jie Long Seventh Institute,
Shenyun Li and Shenhua Li!
This is the match to watch!
Both teams have taken the field!
Such an epic weak point unmasked,
yet you didn't run away.
Either you've got nerves of steel,
or you're just stupid.
Or else, do you actually
have some kind of strategy?
Who knows?
Only thing is,
we don't plan to lose to you.
I don't know what you've got up your
sleeve, but I'm looking forward to it.
Though we're going to win
in the end anyway!
All we need to do
is what we should do.
That's right.
With the sword inside me,
I shall break out of this starry prison
and release my savage force!
There it is, there it is!
Amagiri's performance!
No, wait, it's not a performance, is it?
The majority view seems to be
that it's a necessary step
for releasing his sealed powers.
I see, I see...
Oh, wait, wouldn't you know,
it's time for the match to begin!
Phoenix Festa, Match #4
of the quarterfinals...
Battle start!
You're fast.
But not so fast that I can't dodge it
if I can see it coming.
Burst into bloom, Primrose!
Make it happen at once, Edict!
EDICT
What's this?
Whoa! Already a smoke screen
this early in the match!
Are they planning to fight
hidden by the smoke?
Who knew they'd go for that?
Julis...
This smoke... it's probably fake.
I see, a mirage, eh?
Hey, we can't see a thing!
Show us the match!
Really,
audiences these days
are so impatient.
Well, I guess that was enough
for our purposes.
All right, one minute has passed
since the match began!
For Amagiri, who can only manifest
his powers up to five minutes,
this one minute is significant.
Talk about twisted personalities!
Hey, those two are pretty impatient, too!
All right, then, shall I?
Now, then, it looks
like we're ready to go,
but waiting for you to make a move
would be a bit dull, no?
Yes, and it would probably
bore the audience, as well.
We need to get everyone pumped up,
or we might get booed again.
Therefore...
Why don't we make a big splash here?
Ayato, watch your back.
But there's only one
who's real among them, right?
Well, that's true, but...
So that was an illusion?
Too bad! Wrong one!
Explode!
Ayato! Are you all right?
Have you forgotten about me?
That just won't do!
Julis!
I'm fine.
But the thing is, we're out of time.
I'll cover you,
so you take out Shenyun first.
All right.
Burst into bloom...
Livingstone Daisy!
So they're coming after me, after all?
You really should be careful.
Since you can't see
the talismans Shenhua released.
Released?
While that smoke screen was up, huh?
If that's the case, all we have to do
is burn them all away!
I told you...
I'm in this battle, too, you know.
Summoning Thunder!
Julis!
Ayato!
Don't worry about me!
You take out Shenyun!
All right!
Not bad.
It'll be the same
if I slash all five of them!
Too bad. You guessed wrong again.
Two more to go...
Which is the real one?
Amagiri Shinmei Style First Sword...
Twin Dragons!
Another one?!
Oh, my, have you reached your limit?
Ayato!
Feels so good!
I don't know the reason for it,
but it's certainly inconvenient, that seal.
So how are you feeling right now?
What's so funny?
Oh, it's nothing.
It's just that... this match
hasn't been decided yet!
Can you believe it?!
The seemingly drained Amagiri
has pulled off a comeback victory!
I see.
So he pretended he'd fallen
for their stalling tactics,
then lured them
into letting down their guard.
No way!
Hey, that was close, that was close.
Just like they say,
"He who understands destiny
does not stand under a wall
on the verge of collapse," eh?
Was I really only
taking on the clones the whole time,
after the smoke screen?
You think I merely used those clones
to get within striking distance of you?
Of course I'd never do
such an idiotic thing!
Now then, in your current state,
even these won't be easy
for you to evade, will they?
All right, how will you dodge them?
Not yet...
Not yet, I said!
I can't let myself lose
in a place like this yet!
So even you get that look
on your face sometimes.
Yeah, that really stirs me up.
I like that struggling...
I find it so thrilling!
Now, then, it is a shame,
but I think I'm going to end this now.
Ayato!
Stretch out your hand!
Damn!
Th-Thanks, Julis.
No...
I owe you an apology.
I had some trouble
getting away from Shenhua.
Don't act reckless!
You and I are partners.
We each have a wish, and we're both
out to do what we can for each other.
Julis...
The trouble with you is, you're always
trying to take everything on alone.
What you said to me once...
Let me fire back
those exact same words.
Well, then,
who's going to protect you?
What was that?
Are you done chatting?
In that case...
How about we resume this battle?
Most likely, they have
some invisible talismans ready.
We've got to do something
about that, or...
Julis...
Thanks.
Wh-What's that all of a sudden?
No... thanks to you, I've awakened.
This time for sure, see.
So now I have a favor
to ask of my partner.
Do you mind?
At last... at last,
the time has come!
Looking back, it was a long
and grueling road.
But from now on,
it will be my time, all the time!
Episode 16
Never Back Down
The whole universe revolves
around Ayato and me!
Don't miss it!