That girl still believes in the future.
How's the audience tonight, X22?
Jam-packed.
Good to know.
No surprise. Your songs are the best, Eleanor.
You are always on my side.
Forever...
Only we could use that word.
Forever.
Desertion is unacceptable!
Let me go, please, Jay!
I cannot.
You're an old model, but you are the
best captain in our troop.
I cannot simply let you go
and defect to the enemy.
I admit. You are good team mate.
You never look down on an old model like me.
You treated me as your equal.
For that I thank you.
If so, you understand my situation.
I am sorry.
X22!
Come back! X22!
What is going on,
calling me out to a place like this?
Don't tell me you were a spy.
Say something!
X22,
Captain of Mechanized
Corp, General Office,
murdered 2000 soldiers at
the battle of Zelbia,
4500 in Grogia,
and 9800 in Gene Delta.
You know a lot.
Such a war hero ended up as a
traitor with a price on your head.
How much is that price on your head?
Tell me how it feels to be a wanted
by both humans and machines.
Be sure to get your 10 million.
Thanks, but I am not interested
in nickels and dimes.
What I am interested in is...
The reason you have
not killed me so far.
Is that all?
Yeah.
I know I can't kill you with
a gun like this.
Killing us is just as easy
for you as killing a fly.
How many men can you bring down in a minute?
Ten? A hundred?
My high score is 375.
I may not be gunned down
by you quite quietly.
Eleanor told me to come meet you here.
If you do not have any business
with me, I'd like to leave.
It was you who called me out here!
No, I did not.
I do not trust you yet.
You are a machine.
Yes, but I am a friend of Eleanor.
Don't tell me you're broken.
Broken? I might well be.
I know it now.
You are in love with Eleanor?
Don't tell me it's true!
Hey, this is a trap!
You sold me out?!
You are such a dumb nut!
I've got a pair of Super Chip 11s in my head.
Truly unexpected.
Would you like to join Eleven?
This head cannot be broken down!
Transformation!
Are you Xiaogang?
Hey! Are you dead?
What? What happened?
You don't remember?
No.
Look at that.
It can't be, are you Xiaogang?
Such devastating violence.
Oh hell...
Admission procedure?
What's going on?
What the hell was that?
I can give you details
after you join.
What's wrong?
I feel sick.
No more... Just no more.
Who are you?
My name is Jay...
This place shall be your grave, today.
Yeah?
Sorry you went through the effort.
I won't be needing it.
Fast!
The bullet turned.
That's what he meant!
He has a special gun, I heard.
Special? How?
You cannot run away!
Touka!
Yes!
What the hell?
It can't be.
Non-quantifiable energy system.
What the hell is it?
Here I come!
Hup!
Heck of good reflexes.
Tell me why a machine like
you is siding with humans.
I don't know.
What do you mean you don't know?
Machines are never ambiugous about anything, are they?
That's the thing, I don't know.
I don't know what's happening inside my head.
What??
I am a friend of Eleanor.
so Eleanor's friends are my friends.