I've been waiting for you.
Is she for sale?
This is my daughter.
My apologies.
But, Boss...
You shouldn't be bringing your
daughter to a place like this.
Someday, she'll be running my gang.
It's a learning experience for her.
Then will you also choose one, Miss?
Choose one?
Yes...
I hope you find one you like.
Oh? I didn't expect you
to actually select one.
What is it, Kumiko?
Do you want him?
That dream again...
I've been doing what I can to track
down the designer children...
But I couldn't learn their current locations.
I guess we'll have to rely on your power, after all.
She says we'll have to rely on you.
During the last battle, the Machine
Goodfellow didn't activate.
Teppei, you're still awake?
But Amarok and Malkin appeared...
I think one of the two remaining
designer children was there.
Hana predicted the flow of Orgone energy,
but the Machine Goodfellow didn't activate.
Does that mean something there
other than Machine Goodfellows
uses Orgone energy?
Something felt different than usual...
Pitz says.
That's interesting.
What do you think, Captain?
The captain is asleep.
He really is asleep.
The captain's asleep?
Why not give him a goodnight kiss?
Is he really asleep?
Yeah, he's out cold.
Is that okay?
I guess so?
Goodnight, Captain.
Is this really what the Japanese
independent attack force should be?
The wait is over.
This is tonight's main event!
The challenger:
Asia's one surviving carnivorous dinosaur...
Devil Zynus!
And...
How long will his win streak continue?
The undefeated emperor,
the champion of this arena...
Baku!
That's it!
That's the match!
Fast... That was so fast!
The massive Devil Zynus fell
in a mere ten seconds.
Ten seconds, and he's lying
on the floor of the ring!
The giant impact of the champion's right fist
has slain the last living dinosaur!
Baku! Baku! Baku! Baku!
Baku! Baku! Baku! Baku! Baku! Baku!
Boys' Battlefield
Baku, you don't have to keep doing this.
Those are your father's orders.
You don't need to do as he says...
I'll talk to him!
It's fine.
These fights are nothing.
Please stop it.
I'm all sweaty.
And...
You have a fiancé, Miss.
You smell good.
Like the sun...
Here.
They say this mascot will help you sleep at night.
It matches mine.
Thank you.
Do you think
holding on to it can really keep bad dreams away?
I hope so...
I guess it's a little childish, though.
Miss...
You were wonderful out there tonight, Baku!
With you around, we make
lots of money in one night.
But the money you earn, and you,
both belong to the Asanoda Yakuza.
Don't forget that.
I'm told that your grades are good, too.
Be grateful to the lady...
She's allowing you to go to school.
That's none of your business.
It's time to go home, Miss.
I'll go alone. Leave me.
I can't do that.
Your father's orders.
You guys are always eating something...
It's important!
This is good.
I wonder if there's a pool around here...
Want to go swimming again?
We aren't here to play.
It's important to pace yourself!
Pace yourself?
That's nice...
Hey, Captain...
Keep looking ahead.
Have you ever kissed anyone?
What?
Is that important?
It's important.
N-Not yet... Why?
I see.
Roger, Captain.
Hey, what was that about?
They look so happy...
But if the Kiltgangs come to
Earth, everyone's gonna die.
We won't let that happen. No matter what!
Yes? This is Manatsu.
How is the town looking?
We haven't found anything yet.
I found something interesting.
I'm sending the information now.
There's an illegal underground arena in this city.
An underground arena?
They hold unauthorized fighting tournaments,
and the audience bets on the winners.
That sounds suspicious...
Tonight, I'll send agents from
another team there—
No, the Midsummer's Knights will go!
We need to handle stuff like that ourselves!
Right, Captain?
So it seems...
All right!
By the way, Miss...
Did it work?
What are you talking about?
That little mascot charm
you gave Baku last night.
Is it true that it brings deep
sleep with no nightmares?
I'd love to have a mascot
that matches yours, too.
Um, Sir...
Is there really a mascot that prevents
you from having nightmares?
If there is, I'd like one...
Idiot.
Of course there's no such thing.
I'm sorry... Do you have an invitation?
Will this do?
Minors are not permitted here.
U-Um...
Will this suffice to change your mind?
We're here for... educational purposes.
Go in, then... I hope you learn something.
This has happened before, hasn't it?
The wait is over.
This is tonight's main event!
Tonight's challenger:
The Northern Hemisphere's
ultimate murder weapon,
Gimerock Bomber!
And facing him is the man you all know.
The fighting prince of the arena,
the champion, Baku!
I've never seen you here...
Who're you betting on?
What are the odds on the champion tonight?
1.2 to 1.
All right... I'm in for 2,000,000 yen!
You have guts, little girl.
Okay!
All right! Come on, champion!
Is this the real reason you wanted to come?
He opens up with a knife!
But any non-ranged weapon is allowed.
The murder weapon's blade slices back and forth!
Will it strike his prey?
Baku...
All right!
That was amazing.
No contest!
Once more, Baku's fists explode into the enemy!
The Northern Hemisphere's
ultimate murder weapon
was no match for the invincible champion.
Oh! This is a surprise...
Our arena always welcomes surprise challengers,
but this is the first night we've actually had one!
So, tell us your name, hero!
I'm Amara.
Amarok...
Teppei,
not here.
Ranged weapons are against the rules, huh?
That's...
Our brave challenger's name is Amara!
Amara and the champion, Baku,
are staring each other down.
The tension is immense...
What?
This brings back memories, Bugbear...
I remember when we used to play like this.
What...
are you?
Stay away from me!
Whoa! Is this an earthquake?
Bugbear's heart is causing space itself to shake.
Turn on the emergency lights.
Hurry!
Baku, are you okay?
Amarok...
Who's there?
Come out.
What? It isn't Bugbear?
Do you remember me, kid?
I don't think so...
Who are you?
I think his name was Kariya Haruhiko...
He was at the casino where I worked.
Are you Zin?
I knew you were working with him.
Those iron pipes leaning against
that wall over there...
They're dangerous.
You know you have to pay for what you did.
I warned you that they're dangerous.
Sir! Sir!
You bastards...
Oh, you aren't very friendly, mister...
A girl's standing here alone,
and you just walk by?
Are you with him?
With him? It's more like...
We're bound by fate.
Who are you guys?
You could say we're scouts.
I don't like hitting women.
Get lost.
Don't destroy who I am now.
That's exactly what we're here to do!
I thought you didn't hit women.
Ranged weapons are against the rules.
Wait, Bugbear!
He's gone.
And I was going to show him a good time.
Sir... Sir... Sir!
His pupils are dilated.
He isn't breathing, and we can't get a pulse...
We'll have to wait for a doctor
to say for sure, but he's...
S-Sir...
What?
His heart stopped!
What's going on?
Are you really okay?
I am immortal.
If Amarok and Malkin were there,
then the one we're looking for was, as well.
Let's go back tomorrow.
Yeah.
This time without Akari.
Want my chips?
I knew something was wrong...
What is it?
I looked into the Asanoda Yakuza when
I checked out the underground arena...
The Magus incident.
You're sweating terribly.
Did you have a bad dream?
Hey, am I really the one you...
No, never mind.
Don't destroy who I am now...
We were right.
The new member of the Planetary Gears
is Baku, the boy from the arena.
But Baku instinctively fears contact
with Amarok and the others.
Will he pilot his Machine Goodfellow?
Next time, on episode 13 of Captain Earth:
My Town.
My Town
Earth Engine, scramble!