I, Asseylum Vers Allusia,
will take Count Slaine Saazbaum
Troyard as my husband,
and proclaim that I shall create
a new kingdom here in Earthspace.
At this time, in spite of the best efforts
of you daring and resolute knights,
this war is giving every indication
that it will become protracted.
With matters having come to this,
what should our course of action be?
Is this a time for Orbital Knights
to squabble among themselves?
Is it a time to compete
for one's own glory?
The time has come for us to gather under one
flag and fight together for the future of Vers.
I have delegated all of my authority to the
lord of this newly empowered castle,
and my future consort, Count Troyard.
This includes the right to decide upon whom
to bestow the power to awaken Aldnoah.
Until the day comes
when we achieve victory in this war,
it is my heartfelt wish that you think of
Count Troyard's words as my own
and rally to his side.
All that we do, we do for Vers!
The battle against Earth
continues to prove difficult, I see.
Yes, Milord. But to those knights
who are anxious regarding this situation,
Her Highness's words must have
been akin to divine revelation.
Divine revelation?
Everyone knows that she was only able to
issue that proclamation because of you.
To the knights who are unhappy
about the present state of affairs,
they were words from on high.
Surely they must feel that someone
has appeared who will lead them.
You exaggerate.
But on the other hand, rebel factions
are also certain to appear.
There is something that I wish
you to do on that front.
Make a display of power?
Is that what you mean, Milord?
No, if we continue to engage with such ilk,
we will never see the end of it.
Start by rooting out the
dangerous elements.
We can let the proper authorities
take it from there.
Milord?
Princess Asseylum's name
will be motivation enough.
And it should be simple enough
to strip them of their knighthood
with some random accusation or other.
You do not approve?
You think it too underhanded?
No, Milord. Quite the opposite.
It is only natural that you would stop
at nothing to achieve your goal.
Ever since the announcement, I...
If I may be so bold,
you seem to have firmed your resolve.
My wish was to be close to Her Highness.
My wish was to be worthy of her.
And to be of some service to her...
But I...
If power is the only thing
that I can achieve, then...
Is that you, Harklight? Enter.
M-Milord Slaine...
Miss Eddelrittuo?
We are quite satisfied with
your ship's current actions.
For the time being, we want you to continue
providing unit support as a commando squad.
I have no objections to that.
But with regard to the proclamation
by Princess Asseylum...
That nonsense about founding
a new dynasty in Earthspace?
It's nothing but big talk meant
to stir up the Mars Knights.
We doubt it's anything more.
That might be the case.
But perhaps we should consider
the possibility that the enemy's attacks
may escalate.
We're sitting on our thumbs, doing nothing?
Is that what you are implying?
No, sir. I meant nothing of the sort.
As far as new operations go, we are currently
coordinating with our primary units.
Once that has been finalized,
you will be contacted.
You may be unhappy with your
status as a commando unit,
but there is no telling how much faith we can
put in a ship that runs on enemy technology.
Not to put too fine a point on it,
but that's just how it is.
I'm amazed that you sat through
that without any outbursts.
Did you want me to?
Remember, I'm only here as your escort.
Anyway, I'm not that naive.
They just don't understand.
They probably just don't know what they've got.
They're doing the best they can.
No. I'm not griping about
how they're treating the Deucalion.
But they're being overconfident.
About us?
No, about the Martians.
The war may have tilted
ever so slightly in our favor,
but it does not justify
their possibly misguided optimism.
I find the prospect terrifying.
I will drain the therapeutic fluid and
bring Princess Asseylum to my castle.
Tell no one of this.
Not even Princess Lemrina, of course.
But why not—
Do as I say!
Forgive me. I did not mean to startle you.
No visitors allowed?!
My sister's condition is that serious?
She... Perhaps it was a miracle
that she held on for this long.
How much time does she have?
Today? Tomorrow?
They say that they still do not know.
It is just as possible that she will remain
in this condition indefinitely.
I see...
I can guess what you are feeling.
You may have mixed feelings, but she
is your only sibling by blood.
It is you who are truly sad,
aren't you, Slaine?
I must go.
Slaine...
I forgive you, Slaine.
Even if you cry in front of me today.
Even if you shed tears over her.
Because I...
...am already yours.
Could that have triggered it?
No... It couldn't be.
I always looked up to you.
You had everything that I did not.
So I hated you.
Still, do not worry, sister.
From now on, I will officially
take your place.
I will be Slaine's support!
Why...?
Huh? What's up with that?
Does that mean she got ditched here?
"The captain left me in charge
because she trusts me."
That's what she said, but Cdr. Mizusaki
has got to be devastated.
Why did she pick Lt. Marito of all people
as her traveling companion?
Companion? Escort, more like.
What's this about Lt. Marito?
No, um... It's just that he accompanied
the captain to the conference,
so I thought it might be serious.
Ah. With that Martian proclamation and all,
the situation is definitely in flux.
I can't believe that the princess
is getting married...
That's what you're interested in?
No, but look...
Isn't it possible that her change of heart was
because of someone she developed feelings for?
Like, she was seduced by him or something?
Sorry.
But we're still not 100% sure that
the Princess Asseylum who said that
was the princess who
spent time with us, right?
I honestly can't say.
Inaho insists that she is an impostor,
but there's no telling
just how much even he can see.
Have you eaten?
In a bit. Let me find
a good place to leave off.
You've been this way since we were little.
When you're into something,
everything else fades away.
Here.
Thanks, Yuki.
You've heard, right? About Asseylum's, uh...
Yeah.
That proclamation seemed to prove
everything you've been saying.
It all seems a little too convenient, and if that
really were the genuine Princess Asseylum,
would she think of a founding
a kingdom in Earthspace?
Slaine Troyard.
That douchebag who shot
my dear little brother?
Thanks. But watch your language, Yuki.
It doesn't matter if she's
real or not anymore.
I don't think anyone would listen to her.
Even if she tried to broker a peace
between Earth and Mars again.
About the attack on Earth, Milord,
if there are no problems,
I will get preparations underway.
Milord Slaine?
I'm listening. Proceed as planned.
Yes, Milord. Her Highness has yet to—
She will wake up soon. I know it.
I eagerly await that day, Milord.
As do I.
But... the thought also terrifies me.
Milord?
It's nothing.
Has there been any change?
No. They believe that she might remain
in this condition for some time.
We will wait as long as it takes.
We are used to waiting.
She will surely be surprised, waking up
to find that everything has changed.
Will I...
Will I seem different to her, as well?
She will think that you have grown
into a fine man, I'm sure of it.
I shall return.
Milord Slaine!
...rittuo...
Eddelrittuo...
Milady...
I...
She... She is awake...
Your Highness! It is me! It is Slaine!
Do you recognize me?
It's Slaine, Slaine Troyard!
I am Slaine Troyard...
Your Highness...
Slaine... Slaine... Slaine...
Your Highness!
I've been waiting so long to hear you
say my name once again!
Let me begin by saying that I am glad
to see you safe, Count Mazuurek.
My apologies for causing you
to worry, Count Barouhcruz.
So, what are your plans?
I have none as yet. I have lost
my Kataphrakt, as well.
If you wish to ally yourself with Count
Troyard, I can act as intermediary.
I have heard what happened
with Count Marylcian.
It must have been most galling.
No, both sides fought fairly,
and that was the result.
There is nothing to hold a grudge over.
Count Barouhcruz,
Troyard is dangerous.
He not only killed Marylcian,
there are even suspicions that
he also killed Count Saazbaum—
Who spoke of such accusations?
I merely... But you—
Hold your tongue. How could you let yourself
be misled by such unfounded rumors?
You heard Princess Asseylum's
proclamation, I take it?
No one can stop Count Troyard's rise.
Not when he holds all the cards,
even Aldnoah activation privileges.
As they say, "Do not try to fight
an Olympian sandstorm."
If you wish to make a comeback,
I suggest you choose wisely.
Count Barouhcruz pledges his full
and unconditional cooperation.
Counts Sebring and Raffia have have
yet to make their allegiances clear,
but they appear to be amenable to
acknowledging the new kingdom.
Morale is also on the increase
within the base.
We have almost finished compiling
the list of knights who
seem likely to oppose you.
We are ready to take the necessary
steps by force at any time.
Milord Slaine?
Is something the matter?
Begging your pardon, Milord, but is it
about Princess Asseylum's recovery?
You want me to give her time off? Eddelrittuo?
Yes. If only a little while.
Princess Asseylum's sudden turn
came as quite a shock to her.
Yes, I shouldn't wonder. And how are
you taking it, Slaine? I've been worried.
Thank you for your concern.
You are the only person
that I can count on now.
I will make Vers mine.
For Her Highness.
Dales Platoon and Orlov Platoon currently
marching towards enemy Landing Castle.
Clydesdale and Mustang commando platoons,
be on alert for enemy Kataphrakts,
and once one's spotted, go on the offensive
immediately and destroy it.
They're lovely.
Yes, Lord Slaine had this garden
made for you, Milady.
Oh, he did?
It looks just like Earth.
It does. Are your memories of Earth returning?
Birds...
I was watching birds... with that boy.
Inaho Kaizuka, Milady?
Kaizuka...?
Is something the matter?
Er, no... Look, aren't those flowers lovely, too?
This is Dales Platoon.
Currently closing on enemy
Landing Castle with Orlov Platoon.
Clydesdale Platoon?
The arrowheads are equipped with
a powerful explosive charge! Be careful!
Bastard!
Don't waste your ammunition!
The enemy is cloaked and fast!
The bow seems to be its weapon,
which is probably to...
Right, muzzle flashes would make
it easy to pinpoint its location.
This must be to avoid that.
Optical camouflage?
They have cloaking technology?
The device's based on that, but...
It's more ingenious than just that.
There's nothing on my thermograph,
and it's not casting a shadow. But...
It's definitely out there.
Yeah.
You are giving this
to me, Milord?
Customize it however you like.
I've already discussed the matters
of your peerage title and activation
factor with Princess Lemrina.
Milord Slaine...
The arrow has been loosed.
There is no turning back now.
Yes, Milord!
Inform Count Sebring,
Count Raffia, and Count Orga
that they are to prove their fealty to me.
Smoke grenades, loading complete.
Ready here, too.
Fire!
He's right. It's definitely out there.
And if it is...
...it will have an effect on air currents!
Target located.
Right! Open fire!
Lieutenant!
What is it?
At our 3 o'clock! New enemy!
New enemy closing in from dead ahead!
They're attacking as a team?
From overhead, too! Incoming!
A Landing Castle...
All units, brace for impact!
Multiple Landing Castles...
Multiple Kataphrakts...
Simultaneously!
He's making his move!
It's him!
That's right. It's too late for doubts now.
There is no returning from
this place I have come to.
Flaw in Paradise