When we started living in
the same dorm together,
I figured trouble would come of it.
We started talking to each other
about cats he had taken in,
and we even ended up in the
same class in our second year.
Composing Message
To: Former Freeloader
Sakura Hall, a congregation of the
school's problem students.
But being in such close proximity...
makes some things even harder to say.
Expressing these feelings out loud
has gotten a lot more difficult.
Could you leave the dorm...
just for the night on Christmas Eve?
Why?
You really want to know?
No, I'm not that interested.
What did he say?
He said he'd see what he could do.
Is this really going to work?
What about Mashiron?
#14 The Windows and Lights of Christmas Eve
Oh, right.
Her publisher's throwing a party on the 24th...
So, that just leaves Chihiro-sensei?
You two are going on a date, so...
It might just work!
It's not a date.
Please Knock
Mashiron's Room
Get out from inside of me!
Since then, I haven't
really talked to Shiina.
Baumkuchen: For Sorata
What are you doing?
I'm cold.
Of course you're cold.
Just eat it.
Is it good?
Do you want some?
What is this little skit all about?
It's not a skit. I'm eating baumkuchen.
I know that. I'm talking about...
Sorata, you're angry...
What makes you say that?
I'm sorry.
For what?
Don't apologize if you don't understand.
Anyway, what about your manuscript?
Don't you have a lot to do
before the end of the year?
Sorata, you're angry...
I just told you, I'm not angry!
Sorata
Were you listening?
I heard everything.
How did I seem to you?
Will you be satisfied if I tell
you that you're a bad person?
That's your chance!
You've got to confess your
feelings to him on the night...
of Christmas Eve!
Wh-Why do I have to do that?
Why?
Kanda-kun and Shiina-san's relationship...
is on the rocks, isn't it?
And you've got a date with
Kanda-kun on Christmas Eve, right?
Hold your horses. It's not a date.
Kanda-kun is taking Mashiro to a party...
and he's picking her up afterwards.
While he's waiting for her, we're just
going to watch a play and get dinner.
So, basically, a date, right?
No, it's not.
What is it, then?
A date?
See? What are you going to wear?
I haven't really decided yet...
You've got to wear a skirt!
Don't get careless and wear
denim or something like that!
What?
A skirt, huh?
Rumi-san
Would you like to delete this entry?
If you study too hard,
you'll get accepted into
an art school in Osaka.
Is that something you
should say to a friend...
who's working hard to get into
the school of his choice?
Who are you calling your friend?
Sorry. I meant, my best friend.
So, did you need something,
Student Council President?
It's "former" now.
Are you serious about going to Osaka?
You heard from Hau-hau?
You two are rather close...
Our relationship isn't important.
You sure you can cope with the distance?
Yes, it'll be fine.
For you, maybe.
I'm sure you'll have no trouble...
finding girls to mess around with
as soon as you get there.
But, Kamiigusa...
I don't intend to.
I already broke up with
all the women...
I've been messing around with.
Besides, Misaki isn't alone anymore.
She has Sakura Hall?
Yeah.
Is there something else bothering you?
What do you want to do?
What do you mean?
What do you want? Tell me.
I want her to look at me.
What are you talking about?
She's already looking right at you.
That's because she loves me.
That's not what I mean.
I don't just want her to love me,
I want to make her love me.
Why?
Because I really do love her.
Sakura Hall
Well? How about this?
It's not really me...
That's not true! It's cute!
It makes me want to marry you, Nanamin!
You're taking it off?
You can borrow this, too!
Battle underwear.
Kouhai-kun will love it!
Why did you mention Kanda-kun?!
I'm not letting him see my underwear!
You've got to fight!
Yes, but... Kamiigusa-senpai,
are you going to be okay?
What do you mean?
What do I mean?
Your confession on Christmas Eve.
Aren't you afraid to
tell him how you feel?
What are you talking about, Nanamin?
Of course I'm scared.
After all, I've liked Jin
since elementary school.
Though, I didn't realize how
I felt until middle school.
Of course I'm nervous.
But if I think about that
even a little, it's all over.
Fear takes hold and propels
me around the circle again!
Circle?
I start by thinking,
"I need to tell Jin how I feel! I can't
live like this anymore!" You understand?
"But I'm scared. What if he rejects me?"
"Well, I guess it's not so
bad the way things are now.
I get to be with Jin..."
"But I want to be closer to Jin!"
"Jin's dating other girls.
What am I going to do
if he goes away?"
Which brings me right back here.
I think I understand.
I've probably gone through it a
hundred times since middle school.
A hundred?
Yeah, and I'm starting to get sick of
watching the same scenery go by.
So...
I'm going to close my eyes and leap!
To where?
Space, maybe?
That sounds painful.
What?
Nanamin, you're the worst!
Oh, that's not what I meant. Um...
The stars...
I'm sure the stars are beautiful.
Kanda Sorata-sama
Results of the Screening Process
Baumkuchen: For Sorata
What's with her?
I'm sure she had something in mind.
Chihiro-sensei.
Not that I don't understand
how you feel.
Anyone who's working
hard would get angry...
when they see someone else slacking off.
You're a teacher.
There are certain lines you
shouldn't cross with your students.
You don't want me to go there
because you understand, right?
You know Mashiro isn't slacking off.
She just doesn't know how to face...
an emotion she's never felt before.
Mashiro doesn't know how
to reconcile with someone.
What good will facing her with
your own half-baked feelings do?
Are you telling me to apologize to her?
You idiot. You're such a little kid.
How so?
Because if something isn't white,
you reckon it must be black.
The world isn't that simple.
Most things aren't that clear.
They're neither white nor
black. They're gray.
Do you understand?
What am I supposed to do, then?
How should I know?
All I know is, if you become...
someone who can only accept
his own ideal scenario,
you'll make yourself and
everyone around you unhappy.
Huh? What is that supposed to—
Do something about Mashiro.
That's all.
Because I'm on Mashiro Duty?
Because you're a man.
Oh, right.
I'm locking up Sakura Hall
at the end of this year.
What?
I'm going to go have
some fun in Australia.
You'll all have to go home.
But that's so sudden...
And so, the day approaches.
Baumkuchen: For Sorata
Feelings I don't know how to handle.
Feelings I don't know if I should convey.
Feelings I've decided not to convey yet.
They intersect, overlap, collide,
and pass by each other...
Handmade Cakes Tirol
Make sure you bring a cake.
She said to come by after 5pm.
Sure.
Don't forget.
You're a sight for sore eyes!
How do I look, kouhai-kun?
Oh, um...
I'm so cute, you're at a loss for words?
I see, I see.
You look like you're pretty
comfortable wearing that.
I've worn dresses to award ceremonies.
Here, wear a coat.
The rest is up to you, Jin-san.
You don't have to run.
Misaki.
What?
Are you going to the Sakura Hall party?
Of course I am.
We'll be exchanging gifts, so don't
forget to bring something.
This isn't good...
Mashiro doesn't know how
to reconcile with someone.
What good will facing her with
your own half-baked feelings do?
Sorata.
That letter...
It's the results of the audition.
You're not going to look?
I'll look later.
Thank you, Kanda-kun.
Don't mention it.
I'll take the princess from here.
I'll be back by 9:30.
Okay.
Let me take your coat.
Sorata.
What's wrong?
Say something.
Talk to me.
Did something happen?
No, nothing... I'll leave her to you now.
Shiina, don't forget to
greet people properly.
Talk to me.
Hey, what are you doing?
Aoyama?!
There's no need to act so surprised!
S-Sorry. I just didn't expect this.
Does it look weird?
That's not what I meant.
You just look different.
Different how?
Let's see...
I think this side of you isn't so bad.
Really?
Yeah, I was pretty taken aback.
It's a huge success!
It's snowing.
Hey, stupid couples,
go blow yourselves up!
Don't hang up on me!
Let me talk to Ryunosuke!
Request denied.
For a country bumpkin like
you to try to set a flag...
by sending something like
this is inconceivable!
Just let me talk to Ryunosuke!
I refuse.
Snow.
Sora
It's coming down pretty hard.
I wonder if any will stick.
I guess it's okay if snow falls on me...
Here.
You want me to hold it?
I'm letting you use my umbrella,
so the least you can do is hold it.
Okay, okay.
What'd you think of the play?
It was interesting, but the
actors also surprised me...
and made me frustrated.
Yeah, I feel the same
way when I play games.
Professionals are on a
completely different level than us,
from their oratory skills
to their acting talents...
We've got to work harder.
But, I guess that isn't
something I should say...
to someone who's already
working really hard.
You think I'm working hard?
You're working really hard.
Still not confident?
Do I look that way?
Kinda.
There's an audition for
an agency in February.
Really?
My parents told me to
come back to Osaka...
if an agency doesn't hire me.
What?
Hold up. What does that mean?
Exactly how it sounds.
If I fail the audition, I'll transfer
schools and go back to Osaka.
If I pass, I'll work for an agency
while attending Suimei High.
You mean...
Kanda-kun.
Would you be sad if I left?
Don't ask me that.
I know you'll pass.
Actually, there's one more thing.
If I pass my audition...
I want you...
to hear what I have to say.
What do you want to tell me?
I'll tell you then, not now!
Once I say it, things will change!
Are you sure?
Okay. I promise I'll listen.
Anyway...
I-If... If the time comes
and I'm hesitating,
I want you to tell me...
To leap into space!
Say what?
Who cares what it means? Just say it!
I'm not sure I understand, but sure.
Hello?
Kanda-kun?
It's Ayano. Is Shiina-san with you?
What? Shiina?
I'm sorry. Shiina-san
has disappeared...
The hotel staff said they
saw her go outside.
Do you have any idea
where she might have gone?
Is something wrong?
Aoyama, take this.
Kanda-kun?
Misaki...
Answer me.
I love you.
Really?
Yes, I've always loved you.
The snow stopped.
Shiina!
You...
Sorata.
You idiot, what are you doing?
Where are your shoes?
They disappeared somewhere
while I was walking.
Somewhere...
You can have this.
It's good. I wanted you to eat it.
That's why you left?
What were you thinking?
You've been angry a lot recently.
There's a lot I want
to talk to you about,
but you always look so unhappy.
I don't like it, so I tried to
think of what I could do to help.
How could I make you happy?
How could I make you have fun?
But I don't know.
This is all I can do.
Is it good?
It's hard.
You're mad.
That's right, I'm mad.
Sorata.
I'll worry about you if you disappear
without saying anything.
They said you suddenly vanished
and they couldn't find you.
I thought you might have been
involved in an accident.
I thought my heart was going to stop.
Sorata.
You need more self-awareness.
Walking around here barefoot,
cutting your finger...
You're a professional manga artist.
I think about you a lot.
It made me want to make lunch for you.
I didn't think of you like this before.
I don't understand it myself.
I've never felt this way before.
Watching you draw manga
gave me goosebumps.
It shocked me.
You put all you had into drawing,
never thinking about...
compromising or consequences.
You put everything on
the line so naturally.
Since then, I haven't been
able to take my eyes off you.
Since then, I've liked that about you.
So don't let me down.
I have my eyes on you.
I'm watching you, so...
Sorata...
How long are you two going
to stand there like that?
How long are we...
How long have you been watching?
If you knew, it'd make you want to die.
Don't tell me, then!
"Let's Make a Game!" Screening Committee Member
Here.
It's important, isn't it?
You dropped it.
Aoyama.
What?
Will you help me prepare
for my presentation again?
Of course!
I'll help, too.
You're heavy...
That's not nice.
What are we going to do?
It's pitch black.
Maybe they're getting it on.
D-Don't say it like that!
Anyway, I'm going in...
What?!
I can't take it anymore...
Huh? It's not locked...
Misaki-senpai?
I tried really hard
so we could be lovers,
but...
I can't treat you right
the way I am now.
That's fine.
That's not fine at all.
What am I supposed to do, then?
You don't have to do anything.
You're fine the way you are.
I don't understand.
I don't understand what you're saying.
Stay the way you are.
Be the girl I love.
It doesn't make sense.
Jin was so nice, but...
This isn't right.
I wanted Jin to hurt me today!
He's bringing three girls home with him.
#15 Where is My Usual Self?
It takes only the slightest stimulus
for sons to grow up quickly.
So very true...