It's the start of fall.
Things got a little hectic
in central Flognarde,
but now it's all back to normal.
The demon incident that occurred in
the south at the Dragon's Forest
was safely resolved by the Heroes,
who'd happened to be there at the time, and
an expedition by the three-country alliance.
Peace returned to the forest
and the hero Shinku was able to
come back with the rest of us.
The folks at Galette went
back with Hero Nanami.
Leo-sama and Prince Gaul
were worried about Nanami-san,
so now they're relieved.
The folks at Pastillage are flying home.
Cou-sama and Rebecca-san are
both happy they can relax.
They've got plans for
their vacation, they say.
What's Passed On
Princess...
Good morning, Princess.
It's time for our morning walk.
Princess!
I'm all ready for our walk!
You scared me, Princess!
I'm sorry.
I got up early because I was looking
forward to our walk so much, so...
Okay, let's head out on our walk.
Yes!
Is Nanami already...
Yes, she's already in.
She's all set.
Okay!
So this is it?
Yeah.
Wow!
It's the new walk spot I found!
Okay, let's play then!
Yeah!
It's warm.
And it smells so good.
It's called Rose Daydream.
It's a massage oil popular in London.
Your shoulders... aren't that stiff.
It feels so good, though.
Your hips and legs are stiff, though.
I didn't get to rest on
the expedition yesterday.
You came at top speed from
Galette for me, didn't you?
Thank you, Leo-sama.
Oh, it wasn't just me.
I'm glad that you and Shinku and the
creatures in the Dragon's Forest were all safe.
You've got a national broadcast
after this, right?
Yeah, I'm going to share the details of
what happened in the Dragon's Forest.
Large expeditions put stress
and worry on the people.
I have a duty to explain
to them what happened,
and what the results were.
It's tough being a ruler.
Well, only a very few think of it that way.
Our activities are of
great interest to the people,
so I have to share
everything with the whole continent.
I see.
So I have to make your skin and
hair sparkle so people can
tell on the broadcast!
Yeah!
Go!
Nice catch!
I got it!
Wow, Princess!
Let's play more!
Okay! As much as you want!
I just have this feeling that the
Hero is being rude to the princess.
I'm sure they're having fun together.
I can't wait to play with the Hero, too!
Well, I'm sure it'll be your turn
to play with him once he gets back.
Yup!
Who's going to be on the
broadcast besides you?
It'll be Violet, from our side,
and several military pundits
from Biscotti and Pastillage.
I see.
Oh, right.
I didn't get a chance to thank Adel-sama for
the Spirit Crystal she gave me.
That's right,
you missed her.
Then why not go see her today?
Is it okay?
The three Genoise are heading
to Pastillage on an errand.
You can go with them.
All right, Noir, Jaune, Vert,
take Nanami with you!
Understood...
Leo-sama is so sparkly.
You look more wonderful than usual!
I'll give you a treatment later, too.
Yay!
Couver, the hall seems
very lively today.
That's right.
There's some kind of fall merchant's event.
They're announcing the new weapons
and armor for the war games.
I see.
Here you are!
Okay.
What's this?
It's called a florentine.
It's a cookie from France!
France is an Earth country, right?
That's...
Thank you, Rebecca.
There weren't any cute cookies
like this when I was on Earth,
but it still reminds me of home.
It's thanks to these cute cookies
and this cute Hero
that I can touch the memories
of the place I was born.
If you like, I'll bring more.
Okay!
As a new Hero,
there's things I'd like to
learn from the original Hero.
Oh, my.
The first Hero in modern Flognarde,
and the Hero King who saved the world!
You're so amazing!
Oh my, you flatter me.
My ancestor is the pride of Pastillage!
Oh, you guys are making
too big a deal out of it.
We just helped
the continent recover a little.
The name and position of Hero King
were something they gave me, after all.
Excuse me, everyone.
Oh, Callaway.
The Hero Nanami is coming from Galette.
Really?
She wants to thank Adel-sama
for yesterday, she says.
Oh?
So where's she now?
Well...
Adel-sama! Cou-sama!
Hello!
We're coming over!
They're almost here.
Ancestor!
It's okay. Let them in.
Adel-sama,
I wanted to thank you once
again for the Spirit Crystal.
No, if you can use it
that makes me happy.
That crystal borrows the
power of the spirits.
It's the same type as one used by
someone very dear to me:
the princess who brought me here,
the last ruler of the Kingdom of Pastillage.
I remembered the one she had,
and recreated it.
You looked very pretty
after transforming, right?
Yes!
I was taller and my hair changed color...
I gave my Hero Crystal to Shinku and Gaul.
I gave the Demon Crystal
Valerie had to Rebecca.
And you get her Spirit Crystal.
I've heard of that:
the story of the first Hero.
The princess and the Hero
and the Demon King combined
their three powers to
defeat the demons and bring peace!
It's a story of Heroes
told all over the world.
I see.
In the past, that was a job a Hero did.
The world is really peaceful now,
but the most important part of being a Hero
is still the same.
It's to bring smiles to everybody.
So I hope you'll all...
Why am I getting this service
so early in the morning?
Huh?
Those are...
This weird squishy thing
jumped on me all of sudden.
Squishy?
This way, everybody.
Valerie!
Adel!
What is this?
Snap!
I knew it.
You were raising Muni-Muni, weren't you?
Muni-Muni?
Muni-Muni are a quickly multiplying
monster that attack people.
They're dangerous.
Wait, Adel!
That's not a fair way to say it!
What other way am I supposed to say it?
Those things don't hurt people!
They just eat cloth and metal!
Cloth and metal?
Yes!
They especially like things soaked
with human sweat and bodily fluids.
That means...
When I was Demon King,
I'd put them right near
the entrance to dungeons.
They're very convenient!
They'd melt and eat the weapons and clothes
of the people who were
so eager to attack me,
and make them lose their will
to fight and drive them off!
I agree that's convenient, but...
You don't need them anymore,
so you promised to put them
in the sealed box, right?
Well, yeah...
Lately that idiot Leasha and her friends
have been getting one over on me a lot.
And so I thought I'd use them
to get back at them a little...
Pathetic.
You're really pathetic.
If they're after armor and clothes,
is the knights barracks in danger?
The event hall!
It's not knights participating
in the event, it's models!
That's bad!
Let's go!
Yeah!
This is the Knight Squad!
The demons appeared here,
but the ones that showed up
at the barracks we defeated!
Nice, Leasha!
We're heading for the hall!
No!
Look at that!
They're multiplying!
And really fast!
If they keep multiplying
and head out into town...
Oh no!
Let's stop them!
Get ready, everyone!
Yeah!
We'll help, too!
Valerie.
Can't you control them?
I can try,
but it's not like they're that smart.
Snap!
We can't cause problems for other people.
We need to resolve this quickly!
Right!
No way!
No!
Oh no! He's tough!
How awful!
Seven Tail!
Oh no!
It got me.
This is such a shock...
The Genoise were defeated?
I can't hear Cou-sama's
gunfire anymore, either.
The speed at which they multiply is fast.
At this rate...
This is really bad.
Valerie! Do something!
That's...
That's right.
The power of the Spirit, the Demon,
and the Hero...
If we combine the three of them,
it may just work!
Rebecca! Nanami!
I want your help.
Demon Crystal...
Spirit Crystal!
Activate!
Demon King Crest!
Spirit Barrier!
Hero Crystal!
Shine, purifying light!
No, wait... seriously?
Even if those were low-rank demons,
they turned them into spirits in an instant.
I haven't seen anybody pull off a
stunt like that since my sister did.
The show was given extra time
and was back on.
Nobody was hurt and the building wasn't
as badly damaged as we thought.
Callaway-san had a
hard time dealing with it all,
but I'm taking him something later.
We've really caused problems for you all.
Not at all.
Actually, we're sorry for not being useful.
We're useless.
That's not true!
I guess I did something amazing,
but I don't remember it.
You'll understand eventually.
But it's thanks to the Spirit Crystal
and Demon Crystal, isn't it?
Yeah.
It was a dangerous situation,
but because the power of
the Hero, Spirit, and Demon
worked together,
it all worked out.
It kind of reminds me
of old times...
By the way, where's Valerie-san?
You're right.
I haven't seen him since this evening.
Adel.
Hey, Adel!
I'm sorry! I feel really bad!
I'm really sorry!
No playing tricks, okay?
Jeez, what is wrong with you?
I said I'm sorry!
I hope you'll play with us next time, too!
Exploration at
the Crystal Mines!
I'll do my best.