Shuichi
Are we there yet?
Almost.
You keep saying that.
This time it's true.
You said that a lot, too.
This place.
Do you remember?
Not really.
You were tiny.
No wonder.
The city's different from
how it was back then, right?
You'll be surprised.
I can't believe it.
Welcome to Lake Kiriya City
Nonoka.
Saucer City
Furumiya      Shuichi
Kaori
Nonoka
Wait, wait.
I got it! Be quiet.
No—
Where?
Where are you?
I should have pulled out the batteries.
Umm...
Found it!
Hey, this is Dad's stuff.
Nonoka.
Seven years, huh?
Morning, Dad.
Morning.
Did you sleep well?
Not really.
I fell asleep while I was unpacking.
It was a long trip. I don't blame you.
You haven't had breakfast, have you?
I'll make some.
I should have bought
something yesterday.
This'll do.
Dad.
About today.
Geez.
Huh?
You're stuck, Koharu.
Welcome.
You grew another hand.
And I'm not a customer.
Too bad.
Don't you have any employees?
You know I'm the banner girl, right?
This is part of my job.
Banner girl doesn't mean you're
in charge of the banners.
Did you say something?
Switch over.
Thanks, Souta.
These saucer buns:
how are they any different from
the buns we were eating before?
How they look, I guess.
Man, that thing's giving
you a ton of trouble, huh?
Shiihara Shop
Not really.
It brought in a lot of customers.
It's fun talking to all kinds of customers.
So much for your summer break.
I've always been helping with the store.
It's true that things have
changed since then, though.
Dad, I'm almost done washing.
Let's clean up together after.
Sorry!
Now?
Sorry,
they really want me to take over today.
I should be back by night.
But what about cleaning and shopping?
Thanks.
I'm not doing it alone.
There's no way!
Now...
Nonoka.
Nonoka!
Ow.
Wait.
Hey, wait.
Nonoka! Nonoka!
Who are you?
Noel.
Noel?
Come.
This'll keep me in the fight for a while.
Wait, bus!
Hey, driver!
Hey!
What the heck? You cheapo!
That's such an insult.
Your name's Noel?
Yep.
There's lots I want to ask you.
I want to talk to you lots, too.
Um, why were you in my room?
Because I wanted to see you.
I was at that spot forever,
but I got tired of waiting.
That spot?
Where we met.
I don't know what you're talking about.
But I get the sense that I know you.
Why?
Because we were together.
Together?
Yep, a long time ago.
A long time ago, huh?
Nonoka?
Aren't you hungry?
I'll go shopping.
I'll go with you.
I'll be back right away, wait here.
I'll be waiting.
Why is it?
Maybe Nonoka can't talk because she's busy.
Wait there, I'll be back right away.
I'll be waiting.
Why did you bother coming back now?
Huh?
Hey—
Me?
Ta-da!
I've got this.
Here we go.
That scared me.
See, it didn't work.
It was fun, but I got nervous.
Wait.
Aren't we going now?
Just once more.
It's getting late.
We have to get home before it gets deep.
Next time.
Let's go.
Pretty soon, I'm...
What's wrong?
Next time.
Yeah.
I'm...
moving.
Huh?
I'm home.
Maybe he's back.
What is this?
Noel.
Nonoka.
Welcome back, Nonoka.
Why did you do such a thing?
What thing?
I thought you'd like it.
Get out.
What about dinner?
I don't know who you are,
but never show up in front of me again.
Noel.
But still...
I'm home.
Welcome home.
I feel bad, running off today.
Dad...
What's wrong?
Sorry, I was being careless.
Oh, you found it.
I did that by accident while
we were packing in Tokyo.
I bought one on my way home from work
to fix it before you'd noticed.
Noel.
Please.
What's going on?
I'm going out.
It's almost dark.
I have to apologize.
I have to apologize lots to Noel.
Motor boats
Noel.
Noel!
Lake Kiriya Shore
Shiihara
Excuse me.
Welcome.
Sorry, it's just that
I'm looking for someone.
A small girl.
Is she lost?
No, not exactly.
Do you know a girl named Noel?
She's dressed weird.
Is she from abroad?
I guess it was hopeless to look for her.
Never show up in front of me again.
Why did I say something like that?
The observatory.
You're so good, Nonoka.
Mom is even better.
'Cause Mom taught me.
She's even better than you?
Yup.
I want to hear your mom sing, too.
Both me and Mom are leaving town today.
We're moving to Tokyo.
Are you going far away?
I know, I'll bring Mom.
I'll tell her about you.
She'd be glad to come.
Really?
Wait here, I'll be right back.
I'll be waiting.
Nonoka, where were you?
We're leaving right away.
What's wrong?
Noel's waiting.
And I haven't said bye to everyone yet.
We have to catch the ferry.
Don't give Mom so much trouble.
Are we coming back here right away?
Yeah, of course.
All three of us will be back.
Noel, I—
Hey.
I believed you.
I believed you'd come back for me.
I'm sorry.
I—
Noel.
I'm sorry.
Welcome back, Nonoka.
I'm back.
I'm back, Noel.
This time...
This time, it's my turn
to fulfill my promise.
Your promise?
Yep, that's what I'm here for.
To grant your wishes.
Next episode of Celestial Method:
"Their Promise."
Enjoy.
Their Promise