Everyone, over here!
Is anyone hurt?
Kaname!
Hurry and ready some towels and a fire!
Akari-san!
Did anyone call the doctor yet?
Where's Hikari and the others?
I'm going to go again!
Wait, I'll go, too!
Manaka! Manaka!
Manaka!
Miuna-chan held me...
and then all of my lost feelings
came back to me like breathing...
That's because my Ena is
shouting that it loves Hikari.
Yes...
Just like breathing,
not only my feelings, but all sorts
of feelings came into my heart.
Miuna-chan's mom loved Miuna-chan's
dad and left for the surface.
Akari-san, Tsumugu-kun's grandpa,
Satsuki-san from the candy
store, Kouji-niisan...
And other people who I don't know,
all left for the surface for
the ones they loved.
And among them was Ojoshi-sama.
Ojoshi-sama was crying.
What I was feeling in the shining sea
was the story that melted into the sea.
The story of the Sea God.
The Sea God came to love Ojoshi-sama,
even though she was a sacrifice,
and things became painful.
The fact that before Ojoshi-sama
became a sacrifice,
she was in love with
someone on the surface.
The fact that he was the one
who ripped them apart.
But Ojoshi-sama never
blamed him for that.
However...
The more the Sea God
fell in love with her,
the more pain he felt.
Seeing her cry in secret
because she was unable
to forget the one she loved,
he decided to return
her to the surface...
But the Sea God knew...
The one that the Ojoshi-sama
left behind on the surface
couldn't bear the pain of
losing the one he loved
and was not of this world anymore.
So, the Sea God took away the
her ability to love anyone.
If she had those feelings,
she may follow in her love's foot steps,
unable to bear with the
despair of losing him.
The calmed sea is
the Ojoshi-sama's heart.
A peaceful heart that lost its love,
and will never storm again.
Manaka!
Chisaki! How's Manaka?!
Look, Chisaki!
Ena.
Manaka!
Chii-chan.
Manaka! Thank goodness...
The sea is... pretty.
"Miuna"...
the beautiful sea...
It's so beautiful...
What on earth is going on?
The sea is speaking.
Miuna!
Hikari, wait!
Stop.
If we force her out now,
she'll end up just like Mukaido.
So you want me to just
sit here and watch?!
Just helplessly...
I...
Miuna was always looking at the sea.
What's up?
I'm waiting for Hikari.
I see.
There has to be a way to save her.
It's better not to do anything rash.
I'll see if there is any
change in the village.
Looks like quite the ruckus
has happened again.
Uroko-sama...
what are you doing here?
The Sea God asked me
to take him to Shishio.
For Manaka to fall in love with me...
I've always wished for that.
I always wanted to be laughing
the closest to her...
I wanted to protect Manaka's smile.
But the one who was
the closest to me,
and protected me when
I came to the surface and felt
like I was going to be
crushed by anxiety was...
And yet I...
couldn't even realize your feelings.
I'm in love with Manaka.
More!
I love Manaka!
More...
More!
I hurt you really badly...
I...
What's with you?
You're an idiot, aren't you?
Why the heck would you fall
in love with a guy like me?
Even if Manaka feels the
same way about me...
Miuna...
If you're gonna end up
like this, it's no good!
Because you were able to love Akari,
this happiness exists.
That's why I want her to remember...
That was wrong.
You were right after all.
If I didn't love, I wouldn't be sad...
If you have feelings for someone,
someone else will cry.
Someone will be
sacrificed and get hurt.
If that's what love means...
Then it's horrible
to fall in love with someone.
Come on, take it, Sea God!
My ability to fall in
love with someone...
Take the whole damn thing!
And save Miuna in return!
Manaka...
It's okay, Hii-kun.
Huh?
Miuna-chan's feelings are...
He's crying...
Aw...
Hikari's an idiot.
The Sea God is an idiot, too.
Sea God, why did you steal
away Ojoshi-sama's heart?
I mean, the Ojoshi-sama...
I wish I could tell the Sea God...
And Hikari...
Miuna...
The ability to fall in
love with someone...
The sacred fire...
No!
The Sea God's will!
I want to tell Hikari.
Shioshishio...
The fact that I fell in love
with someone that cares so
much for me and can cry for me...
It makes me very happy.
Miuna!
You taught me this, Hikari.
I don't want to think that it's hopeless
or useless to love someone.
Yeah, it's not wrong.
Falling in love with someone...
is not wrong.
Miuna! Miuna!
This is...
The Ojoshi-samas?
Sea God!
Why did you...
Sea... God...
Miuna!
Ojoshi-sama's feelings...
into the sea...
I don't want to forget...
They're going into the sea...
I didn't want to forget him...
However, more than anything,
I didn't want to lose
the children and my days with you.
My loving heart that is within me...
How foolish!
How unbelievable as a god...
Sea God!
You stole Ojoshi's feelings of love...
yet you didn't even know who
those feelings were directed to?
And...
you just now found out the truth behind
Ojoshi's feelings that melted into the sea?
The sacred fire...
It's responding to the Ojoshi-sama's heart.
Getting a hold of Manaka
in place of Ojoshi-sama...
The Sea God's frank feelings that
melted into the sea have calmed down,
and the sea is now at a lull.
As long as they are not hurt,
there will be no waves.
However, though there is no sadness there,
there is no happiness either.
The sacred fire is the Sea
God's consciousness, right?
Indeed.
The sacred fire threw
away its own identity
and carried out the duties as the god...
But it must have remembered because of
Ojoshi-sama's heart that melted into the sea.
Uroko-sama...
Yes.
I am a scale.
The scale of the Sea God.
However...
Just like the Sea God, Ojoshi-sama...
I will love you forever.
Dad?
Huh?
D-Dad?!
Wh-Why are you awake?
You scared the hell out of me!
What happened to your hibernation?
Miuna, you've gotten big.
Grandpa...
A child born between a person from the
surface and the sea will lose their Ena.
That is why with the impending
danger coming to the surface,
the people of the sea had to hibernate.
To make sure that there were
descendants to leave behind,
and that there was
a chance at a future.
However, there is Miuna.
Miuna has Ena.
Therefore, there is hope for the future.
I-Is that okay, Uroko-sama?!
It won't do any good to ask me...
I'm not the one who woke him up.
I'd like to go meet Akira.
Huh?
How do you know about Akira...
Or rather, hey!
How do you even know
about Miuna's Ena?
Did you forget?
You're the one who told me about them.
About Miuna having Ena now,
and about Akira being born.
Your voice reached me.
Your feelings also reached me.
Dad...
The heart that doesn't
change for eternity.
The heart that changes with the times...
None of them are a mistake...
Welcome back.
Sea!
The calmed sea begins to move.
Why?
It had been calm this whole time...
Look over there.
Bring out the boats!
Hey!
Hey! Hikari!
Love is born from the sea.
Hikari!
Hey, Hikari!
Hikari, thank goodness.
We believed in you, our beloved friend!
The gentle and kind...
There we go.
The rough and painful...
And yet, the sea is forever kind...
Manaka.
Love is like the sea.
Manaka...
Miuna-chan!
Thank goodness!
Thank goodness, Miuna-chan!
Hey... what about worrying about me?
You're sturdy, Hii-kun...
"Sturdy"?
Sturdy as a rock!
Manaka-san is...
What's that supposed to mean?
Huh?
Manaka-san is...
It's the Manaka-san that
I knew since I was little.
Welcome back, Manaka-san!
Saying welcome back is
my line, Miuna-chan!
Welcome back!
Welcome back! Welcome back!
Everything is born from the sea.
Oshiooshi Fishing Cooperative
Giant squid!
Akira, wait!
Whale shark!
Did you sleep well?
Nah, still didn't get enough sleep...
Here, food.
So Old Man Hayakawa
still hasn't woken up?
He was always a worrywort.
He probably plans to
continue hibernating.
I see.
So we probably won't be able
to see him for a while.
Yeah, when everyone wakes up is their own choice.
I see...
What the hell? Manaka's still not here?
Yeah.
She said she forgot something,
so we should head up without her.
Jeez...
All right, let's wait up top.
Things same as usual
with you and Manaka?
Where'd that come from all of a sudden?
You guys should go on a date.
You found out you feel the
same way about each other after all.
Isn't it a problem that
there's been no progress?
That stuff doesn't matter...
Are you being like Chisaki
from a little while ago?
The whole "I don't
want to change" thing?
No, things can change.
Huh?
But things don't have to change.
Whatever is fine.
Yeah, you're right.
I wonder if Hii-kun is mad...
Namaka!
Akira-kun?
You came to the sea again?
Akari-san was getting angry that you
kept coming since you were able to dive in.
One spin!
The sea's gotten pretty warm...
But even then, if you come in
too often, you'll catch a cold.
You still aren't used to it.
Let's go together.
Tsumugu-kun, good morning!
Morning.
Want a lift?
Yeah!
You're leaving today, aren't you?
Forest Animals Juice
Tangerine
Full of Vitamins
I thought I'd come see the sea before
heading back to the university.
Won't Chii-chan be lonely?
I'll be back on breaks.
I see.
I love the sea that you
can see from the surface.
Why don't you tell Hikari
that instead of me?
Th-That wasn't about
Hii-kun or anything!
See you later!
See you later.
Ee you later.
When Manaka and Tsumugu first met,
I thought it was a fateful meeting.
Hii-kun!
Hey!
But...
Hurry up!
We're going to be late!
Tsumugu!
You can go to the city or whatever...
But hurry up and come back!
Nothing is actually fated.
We're able to change
everything ourselves.
Hey, does this look okay?
It looks good on you.
I wonder if this makes me
look a little more mature...
I think if you don't
stand on your tip-toes,
the more Kaname-san will
understand how great you are.
Good morning!
Even though I lived on the surface,
Morning!
I fell in love with
someone from the sea.
Good morning.
O-Oh, good morning.
Heyo!
I think Shiodome's gotten
prettier lately...
You still haven't given up?
And the tears I shed over my first love
melted into the kind sea.
Oh, there they are.
Hey!
The sea that melted everything...
Don't rush, Manaka-san!
Manaka!
Thank you, Miuna-chan!
Even now, it will bring new
life and new feelings.
I'm going to stop by my home
in the sea on the way back,
so I'll be a little late.
You can go back to the sea if you want.
Well, the miso soup you make is salty.
I'm worried about your blood pressure.
My mom said she'd teach me how to make
dishes that would be healthy for you.
I see...
Tsumugu, were you ready?
Come to the station with me.
Yeah.
See you later.
I'll be back at the end
of the month to visit.
Yeah.
The end of the surface world
that will come some day...
We don't know exactly what'll happen,
Oshiooshi Fishing Cooperative
Shishio and Oshishi's
Cooperative Development
Side Dishes from
the Sea and Mountains
but I feel that our feelings
will be able to change it.
Sea God,
humans are quite interesting,
are they not?
Even after being hurt,
and having no answers...
They still struggle
and continue to dream.
And those feelings may change
the great flow...
Oh?
So the saltflake snow has stopped.
Final Episode:
The Color of the Sea. The Color of the Earth. The Color of the Wind. The Color of Your Heart. Your Color.
Hey, Hii-kun. Do you remember?
Five years ago at the Ofunehiki...
About you wanting to tell me
something after it was over, right?
So you did remember.
You're the one who forgot.
But even if I don't say it...
I already know what you wanted to say.
Melted into the sea,
melted into the air...
Going beyond time...
The feelings are passed down.
This world is filled
with so many shining feelings.