The tool I discarded became Gilbert's pet.
But after losing both of her arms,
her master,
and everything else in the world,
there she was,
standing there.
Thank you very much.
You're so naive.
You're out of time.
You might have made it
if you killed me quickly.
A bomb?
Pull the emergency brake! Now!
It's not working!
Try the brake in the guest car!
Pull the emergency brakes!
What was that?
Violet!
-Get the other bomb!
-I'm on it!
I got it!
Violet!
GARDARIK EMPIRE
CAPITAL CITY OF HORMGARD
LEIDENSCHAFTLICH
INTERIM EMBASSY
The two nations of Gardarik
and Leidenschaftlich
hereby recognize each other
as equal sovereigns
in order to maintain
global peace and safety.
To that end,
both nations will resume fair trade,
and Leidenschaftlich shall provide
one year of emergency aid
as a show of goodwill.
We vow to honor this peace treaty
between our nations.
-The war is over.
-Yes.
What's wrong?
Even though it's over...
Even though the war is over,
my son hasn't returned home.
I've told my wife
that we should give up already.
But...
I understand.
I understand very well.
Can you write this in the letter?
"Thank you for being born our son."
Yes.
An air show.
We couldn't have any during the war.
Everyone is looking forward
to our first one in five years.
Tomorrow is the deadline.
So, it's one more day of hard work.
Yes, I will do my best.
You know, I've been thinking
about writing a letter myself.
I was a dancer before I became a Doll.
Many soldiers came to where I worked.
So many of them lost their lives.
I thought I'd write a letter to them.
Why don't you write one, too, Violet?
I...
I still have never written a letter
of my own.
Then it will be your very first one!
Just write how you feel.
Follow your heart.
My heart.
Major.
What is it?
Am I no longer needed?
What are you talking about?
After I am dismissed,
will I be transferred under
Lieutenant Colonel Hodgins' command?
Will I no longer receive any orders
from you again, Major?
Do you really want my orders that badly?
Orders are my everything.
You no longer need to follow my orders
after this battle.
In fact, you won't have to follow
anyone's orders.
Live free.
Is that an order?
Why? What makes you think it's an order?
Do you...
Do you really believe
that I think of you as a tool?
If that's the case,
then I wouldn't have taken you in.
I wouldn't have kept you by my side
all this time!
You should realize this.
The reason I'm upset...
This pain is because I--!
Major?
You have feelings.
You have a heart, just like me!
If you don't,
then why are you reacting that way?
You're capable of expressions!
You're scared of me right now, aren't you?
You don't like being yelled at, right?
I don't know.
You're angry that I'm being unfair to you,
aren't you?
-I don't know!
-Stop lying!
I am not lying.
I don't understand it myself.
I...
I only want to keep getting orders
from you.
If I have your orders, I can go anywhere.
That is all.
I'm sorry.
But it's painful for me
to see that you view yourself as a tool.
Because I'm the one
that made you this way.
But you still...
You still put your trust in me.
You've done nothing wrong.
We'll be battling in a few hours.
Let's talk about this next time.
You couldn't write it?
I have feelings.
I had them, even back then.
But... I don't know what...
You don't know what you want
to say to the major?
Violet.
The deadline is tonight,
but if you write it by tomorrow morning,
I'll take it to the office myself.
You should write one.
Even if it's something short.
Even if it's just one sentence.
Yes?
Excuse me.
There is a Mr. Bougainvillea
here to see Violet.
Thank you very much.
Over here.
You must have been busy writing
all of those letters for the air show.
Sorry to be the one
to drag you away on your day off.
Not at all.
I don't think you've been
to our mansion in Leiden.
I'll just mention this
so you won't be surprised,
but her memory is a little fuzzy.
This is my mother.
Who are you?
This is Violet.
The one you wanted to meet.
Oh, that's right.
The one he wanted us to take in.
You finally came.
Yes.
Is Gilbert not with you?
Mother, Gilbert is...
He is with me.
That's the same color as his eyes.
It is the same color as your eyes.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Yes.
I did not know the word,
so, I never said it before.
But your eyes were beautiful
from the moment we met.
It is beautiful.
And, so, what was your
relationship with Gilbert?
The major took me in,
raised me,
and employed me.
But...
I know.
He passed away at the Battle of Intense.
That's right. That is why you had her
come here, isn't it, Mother?
It was, wasn't it?
It wasn't your fault.
You do not have to carry that burden.
Diethard told me
to give up on Gilbert already.
Even though he can't do it himself.
The two of them were very close
since they were young.
My son is alive.
Inside our hearts.
That is why I will never forget him.
Even though it may be painful,
I will always carry him in my heart.
Because even now...
I still love him.
Yes.
Violet!
You must live to honor his memory.
Live.
Live a long life.
And then die.
This is my final order.
I...
no longer need orders.
Gilbert didn't treat her
like a tool like I did.
That's why even though she lost
both arms and her master,
she will never lose
all the important things he has given her.
I'm glad the weather turned out nice.
It's been a long time
since it last snowed in Leiden.
Violet!
Luculia.
I'm so glad you made it.
You must have been busy
scribing for the air show.
No.
But I wrote many letters.
A letter of my own for the first time.
I see.
I wrote one, too. To my parents.
I am sure it will reach them.
Thank you.
I wrote one, too!
To my future self! I'll be
the number one Doll in Leiden then.
No, the number one Doll on the continent!
-That's some dream.
-What about you, Erica?
What did you write?
I've recently started liking someone,
-so, I've--
-What!?
-Who? Who is it!?
-Hey!
Do you want to know
what I wrote in my letter?
Yes.
Oh.
I actually wrote one to Hodgins.
What?
I wrote that I'd be the future boss.
Hey! Are you coming after my job?
How could you write that!?
You're one to talk.
You want to share what you wrote?
-"To Daddy's future daughter."
-How did you get that!?
Please stop!
Your trash can was filled
with your rough drafts, Daddy.
Don't call me Daddy!
Daddy.
Knock it off!
"Daddy is waiting for you to be born.
And I pray that you grow up healthy.
That you find happiness.
That you fall in love with someone
who loves you in return.
And that the world of your future
and of your future children...
is one without conflict,
filled with happiness."
All of these people's feelings
are falling from the sky.
Violet.
Major.
"To my beloved Major Gilbert.
How are you?
I hope all is well with you.
Where are you right now?
I hope you are not stressed out.
Spring, summer, autumn, and winter.
Many seasons have passed,
but I am still waiting for your return.
At first, I did not understand.
I did not understand any of your feelings.
But I started learning about emotions,
from this new life you have provided me.
Through writing letters for others.
Through the people I have met.
I still believe that you are still alive
out there somewhere.
That is why
I will continue to live my life.
I may not know what lies ahead,
but I will simply live.
And if we should ever meet again,
this is what I would tell you.
I now understand what the words...
'I love you' mean."
Violet! You have a new request!
They say it's urgent!
-Benedict, go make some tea.
-What? Why do I have to get the tea?
Violet, you have a client waiting.
I will be right there.
THE AUTO MEMORY DOLL
AND "I LOVE YOU"
It is a pleasure to meet you.
I will travel anywhere
to meet your request.
Auto Memory Doll...
Violet Evergarden at your service.
Subtitle translation by
Zensho Yamamoto