Okay!
My lord, do you want some jam?
No, this is a hot dog.
I see.
Naotsugu, how about some mustard?
I'm eating pancakes.
I did that on purpose.
So, it's the second day of the Scale Festival.
What will you be doing, Minori?
I do have some plans.
It's a festival, so you've gotta
make the most of it. Right, Minori?
Yeah.
I'll be taking the dog for a walk.
Who are you talking about, Miss Isuzu?
Will you be spending the day fighting
hordes of paperwork again, Shiroe?
Yes, I think so.
I'd love to help you...
But I have a mission.
A mission?
Food safety inspections.
Food safety inspections?
Student of the Mage
Student of the Mage.
Scale Festival
This spicy sauce is delicious!
Now, what do I eat next?
You just want to eat.
That's what you call a "safety inspection"?
No, you see...
Okay, at least tell me the recipe!
Julius Ripsky/ Person of the Land
Marriage Shiyo/ Adventurer
Then I'll pay for it!
You want to steal my unique flavor?
I won't tell you anything.
Now, now, you two.
They say a festival always has fights,
but let's settle this peacefully.
A hamburger feast after a good deed!
Learn some moderation.
You're in a good mood this morning, shrimp.
You're imagining it.
And don't call me shrimp.
Did something good happen with Shiro?
D-Don't be stupid!
I'll cut you!
Now, now...
Here's yours.
This goes way beyond oversized, but...
Mustard and avocado and tomatoes...
Oh, it's Shiro!
Just kidding!
Nice reaction!
Why, you...
Prepare to die!
Oh, right.
Here.
What is this?
A stamp card.
Each stand you visit will give you one stamp.
By the way,
I only have one more to go.
What?
Stamp Rally
"Get all the stamps, and win a wonderful prize"?
I wonder what the prize is.
Maybe it's a pair of pure white...
Pure white?
Lacy pant—
Y-You didn't have to hit me so hard, you—
Huh? She's gone!
Damn you, Stupid-tsugu!
Okay, Minori... I'm off to
go help Crescent Moon.
See you later, Tohya!
An assassin with Japanese
accessories would look great!
For Display
An invitation?
Yes, for the Twilight Banquet
with Princess Lenessia...
You want to go see Karashin, then.
All right.
Thank you.
No problem.
By the way, why are you inside those boxes?
Well... It's good for the skin.
Oh, Minori!
Hello, there.
Have you seen Marielle?
This whole thing was her idea,
and now she's gone...
For Display
No, I'm sorry.
My lord.
Naotsugu just wanted to eat, after all.
I'm sure.
With that iron stomach of his, he'd never
even know if something were poisoned.
You're right.
Hmm. I don't understand at all.
Um...
You're in the way.
Oh, right.
Henrietta wanted me to send you over.
Think you could go see what she needs?
Understood.
My lord!
What is this?
Your wonderful prize.
All right! That's all of them!
The wonderful prize is mine!
Huh? Only one stamp?
It couldn't be...
Did she switch them out?
Curse you, shrimp!
Actually, I guess I can just go eat more!
Gonna try to eat until I drop!
Crafting Guild
Council Office
Knock First!!
That can come later.
Can you send some people over here at once?
What? You're all booked, too?
Man, what a problem...
I can't talk to him now...
Karashin!
I brought the reports on the
south block sales figur—
I'm sorry.
Oh, you're the girl from Shiroe's...
Yes, I'm Minori.
Um... Do you want me to help?
Did the cake buffet yesterday go well?
What do you mean?
Minori's trying to restore Shiroe's reputation.
She's working hard.
His reputation, huh?
He should really step out and
show his stuff a little more.
He always just leaves all that to Crusty.
Yes.
People are good at some
things, and bad at others.
I'll simply have to show my stuff in his stead!
That's nonsense!
It's your fault for using a beat-up carriage!
What?
Just get out of the way!
There's a line forming behind you!
How rude.
You're only talking to us that way
because we're People of the Land!
No, I'm not!
I'm just telling you not to block the road!
This won't do.
Rudy!
Come on, now, gentlemen!
Akihabara's a peaceful place, so no fighting—
You don't have time to rest, Marie.
You know I'm not cut out for heavy lifting.
Everyone's busy since we brought
Crescent Moon Burgers back.
We need to carry this stuff ourselves.
No!
I'm all sweaty!
I want to take a bath!
I guess I have no choice.
Yes, it's me.
Sorry to interrupt when you're having fun.
Umeko?
That's right. We don't have enough men
to carry all these boxes for our sale.
Yes, Marie could have just asked you herself,
but she's being all hesitant.
She's so cute!
Wh-Who are you talking to?
I'm on the phone.
Be quiet.
But you're talking about me! I can't be quiet!
Oh, you'll help me,
Naotsugu?
Yes, Marie will be very happy.
See you soon.
Jeez...
Why are you so mean to me?
I'm not being mean.
I'm trying to help you.
I'm going to take a shower.
Right now?
I won't run away, so don't worry.
It'd be rude to see him when I'm this sweaty.
She's always so honest with herself.
I'm jealous.
But I, on the other hand...
Oh, no!
I mean, sure, he's an attractive guy...
But he's only the best of
all the guys I actually know.
Who am I making these excuses to?
Why are you standing there spacing out?
Oh, dear!
Don't surprise me like that!
You're the one who called for me.
Th-That's right.
Maybe I simply act too indifferent...
Is something wrong?
No... Not at all.
This afternoon, we're setting up
a stand to sell winter clothing.
Crescent Moon Shop
In Preparations
I'd love it if you could help out.
Winter clothing?
You aren't planning something again, are you?
You'll just be working in the background.
Then it doesn't need to be me, does it?
Shiroe will be coming later...
Okay, I'll consider it.
What a straightforward personality!
Like a puppy!
Yo!
This is the life I live!
Uh... What's going on here?
God almighty!
I don't know.
Watermaple Mansion
Japan Server
Akihabara
City/ No Monsters
No PVP
Entry Restrictions/ None
Exit Restrictions/ None
What should we do about food?
I don't know anything about adventurers!
Could you put some more flowers over there?
Yes, understood.
I think that'll basically do it...
It comes with three meals and a nap.
He tricked me again. Honestly...
It's that mean monster's fault that I'm so busy.
I should remind him which of us
has the greater power here.
I'm already well aware of that, so there's no need.
H-How did...
Elissa let me through.
What are you doing here?
For once, you're actually doing some work,
so I thought I'd come to give sympathy.
Whose fault do you think this is?
I'm told the Twilight Banquet was your idea.
It's my way of thanking the adventurers.
It was smart to use a number of smaller tables,
rather than a single big one,
where people are ordered by rank.
Adventurers dislike the nobles' useless formalities.
Yes, I think I understand that a little now.
Glad to hear it.
I thought he'd make sarcastic comments as usual.
Why did he come here?
Trying to figure out what that monster's
thinking is a waste of time.
I'll never understand.
Hey, are you sure about this?
Don't you have your own work to do?
I'm free today.
But anyway...
All these forms have completely
different sizes and layouts...
People of the Land have come from all over.
I wonder if each territory has its own forms.
I don't know...
What a pain.
I'll start by organizing them.
Oh?
Minori, I didn't know your subclass was scribe.
No, it's apprentice.
Minori
Race/ Human
Shrine Priest, Lv. 37
Log Horizon
I... I like...
Subclass
Apprentice, Lv. 21
I'd like to ask you about my skills.
You want to change your subclass?
Yes, but I don't know what to pick.
Then what about this?
There's a subclass called "apprentice."
Apprentice?
It's exactly what it sounds like...
It makes you someone's apprentice.
You can become someone's student,
and copy their skills.
That's amazing.
But there are limits on which skills you can learn.
You can only gain the skills for your level.
But you get a bonus, so it levels up quickly.
And when you change classes,
you keep your experience points.
Until you decide what you want to do,
it might not be a bad idea.
I've decided.
I'll become an apprentice!
That was fast!
But you already have your tailoring skill...
No, I didn't pick that because I liked it.
And so...
Shiroe, will you be my teacher?
Me?
I changed my subclass because
I wanted to be useful to Shiroe.
If I can be of use to the people of Akihabara,
it might help my teacher's reputation.
And for that, I must start by doing
what I can, one step at a time!
This is my battlefield!
That's amazing...
You work fast, Minori!
I'm Shiroe's student, after all.
Linguini
This is great!
The tomato sauce here is delicious.
Now I'll have enough energy to go back
to Crescent Moon this afternoon!
There's the smile I wanted to see.
I'll do my best to help.
I'm so sorry!
What's wrong with you?
Look at this stain!
I'll p-pay for it, so please...
You could never afford it! Honestly!
This is why I told you it wasn't worth
coming to a filthy shop like this!
That's awful...
Is he stupid?
He chose to come here.
Get lost.
Which of you just insulted me?!
You three, then?
I'll have to teach you a lesson.
You want to fight?
With us?
Nyanta...
No need to worry.
Meow.
What do you want, cat?
I'm not a cat.
I am a proud member of the cat-people.
Never heard of them.
Then you really ought to learn.
Wh-What are you doing?
Let me go... Let me go!
My lord!
You shouldn't be mean to others.
Akihabara has its own rules
by which you must abide.
How dare you disgrace me?!
My lord, control yourself.
Please!
I'll get you for this, cat!
Nyanta is so cool!
Meow.
You're just playing around,
aren't you?
A conflict with the People of the Land, again?
You might want to beef up security.
To a degree, I expected this.
People of the Land live in a class-based
society, while we're free.
That's true.
All of the People of the Land's traders
at this festival are professionals,
while everyone else running a
shop here is an amateur.
D.D.D. and the Black Swords are available.
And that's why I have Naotsugu running around.
I think we can leave things alone.
Team 3 is back!
Team 2, heading out!
Right. Good work.
Reporting.
We assisted one carriage, stuck on a side road,
halted four arguments,
and dealt with two claims of nonpayment.
All involved People of the Land.
Got it.
You've just got to be tough and draw the line!
Keep at it.
Yes, sir.
But I didn't expect to see so many here.
I'm sure People of the Land
love their festivals, too.
Still...
It's hard to believe that villain was the one
who brought all this business to Akihabara.
I once invited him to join my guild.
This was after the Tea Party disbanded,
when he was a solo player.
I'd seen how he fought while
he was a guest of ours.
And?
He turned me down.
"I don't think I'm worthy of the offer," he said.
And so, I lost interest.
I'm not interested in anyone who isn't
ready to find and slay new enemies.
And after the Apocalypse, he grew up...
Enough to have an influence on the entire city.
That's what I don't get...
Is he a strategist? Or a gambler?
I'm not even sure if he feels dead or alive.
I think Shiroe is at his best when anything goes.
"Anything goes"?
I don't think he's a strategist at all.
When the chips are down,
and you have to do whatever it takes,
and there's nothing in it for him,
he's as strong as anyone you'll ever see.
He's like a cursed sword.
I understand...
But now, that cursed sword
is buried in paperwork.
Who knows when he'll be drawn next?
I guess we still have something to look forward to.
Merchant's Hall
Japan Server
Akihabara
City/ No Monsters
No PVP
Entry Restrictions/ None
Exit Restrictions/ None
Silver Plaza
Japan Server
Merchant's Hall/ Silver Plaza
City/ No Monsters
No PVP
Entry Restrictions/ None
Exit Restrictions/ None
Oh, Akatsuki...
You look great. So cute!
Oh, I can't... I can't even...
You didn't say anything about
being in a fashion show!
Didn't you say I'd be working in the background?
That's right...
The clothing is the star of the show.
I didn't lie to you.
You wear this, Shiro!
This?
I think it'll look good, my lord.
But I'm not laughing.
I haven't seen this many people
in a long time, though...
I told you I'd pay!
Th-The money isn't the issue!
What?
Minori?
Is something wrong?
Cocoa Brown
I've come all the way from
the far west to buy this stuff.
But it's only two items per customer...
Nemimi/ Adventurer
Constantan/ Person of the Land
I can make you famous across the land!
That isn't what we want.
What?
Yes, yes.
I understand your point.
But they feel differently.
Please leave.
I've got nothing to say to a young kid like you!
Move!
You will leave, won't you?
Now I'm mad.
I'm never coming back.
Thank you...
If he'd bought everything, I wouldn't have
the fun of selling them one a time.
You're welcome.
That's strange.
Why would he leave so easily?
Hey, how long do I have to wait?
I'm here to do business, you know!
I'm asking you how many you have!
We really can't do that...
I'm not moving until you say yes.
Please stop...
How much do I have to pay for a whole box?
What's wrong, my lord?
The place is getting rowdy.
Yes, more than I'd anticipated.
The People of the Land are acting strangely.
But I don't understand it.
I can't get a clear enough picture.
I feel like I'm missing something...
It's me, Minori.
I'm going through the paperwork,
and something isn't right.
Some of the paperwork overlaps,
and some of their math is wrong.
There's a huge number of very basic errors.
And...
Most of them come from People of the Land.
I see...
So that's it.
My lord, what will we do about the show?
Minori, keep this line open.
Right.
Akatsuki, find Isaac and get
a report on our security.
It looks like someone is attacking Akihabara.
Attacking?
An enemy?
I'm going to my office in the guild building.
This may be an emergency.
Understood.
Shiroe...
I let down my guard!
All the signs were there.
But I was careless...
Now they have the advantage!
New Spirit Ship
Eagle
We'll be arriving in approximately thirty minutes.
Prepare to disembark, Lord Marves.
The town of Akihabara is under attack.
Shiroe senses the enemy, and takes action.
But his guesswork is off, and his calculations fail.
The Round Table faces grave danger.
What is the enemy really after?
In the hour of greatest peril, the strategist
Shiroe begins his counterattack.
Next time: Chaos.
Chaos
We will change the world.