The Second Plate
Episode 9
43rd Autumn Elections
Finals
What?!
What the hell is that?
A dull blade?
The transfer student guy's
done something weird again.
Did he give up on the fight?
I see.
So that's why you didn't come
to the fish market this morning.
Huh?
You chose aging as a way to compensate
for the difference in ingredient quality.
I could tell what you used
to age the fish just by looking at it.
But that's not enough to reach
the best of what the season has to offer.
You won't know that for sure
until you eat it.
I'll cook enough for you guys to try, too.
Yeah, right.
The outcome's already clear.
Congratulations for finishing third.
That's good enough to be rightfully proud of.
Honored guests, the time for the
Autumn Elections Finals to begin is almost here!
Please look up at the ceiling!
Wow!
The ceiling's splitting open!
Soon.
This is Gatten Hall as it truly is.
The cooking time in the finals
will span approximately two hours.
This is the time it takes from the moment
the moon appears in full,
traverses across the skies,
and becomes hidden once more.
Though it's the same every year,
it's still quite the spectacle.
I fondly remember those days...
That night when I fought
in the Autumn Election finals...
All the chefs who have ever
stood on this stage
has seen the same moon.
Don't lose to anyone else until
you lose to me again next time!
I'm gonna gun for the top seat
among Totsuki's first-years!
Ready!
Let the cooking...
...begin!
A Sword That Signals Autumn
None of the candidates have
touched their Pacific saury.
They'll start by prepping their other
ingredients. Typical, I suppose.
Working the fish more than necessary
will negatively impact its freshness.
They have to maintain the fish's
freshness as much as possible.
I'm becoming excited, yes.
Watching young men...
this is sight for sore eyes.
Oh, Mother, you're being
rather inappropriate.
And your vocabulary is skewed, as usual.
Alice!
Go back to your seat in the audience!
Erina, you should come over here, too!
She can, can't she, Grandfather?
Yes. It doesn't matter.
See, Erina?
What a fun family, Nakiri-kun.
Oh?
Yukihira seems to be
handling his Pacific saury.
Maybe the aging was a success?
Yeah. What kind of dish will he make with it?
Kurokiba Ryo. Hayama Akira.
Can you win against
those two monsters, Yukihira?
Ah!
So many different seafood ingredients
on the young Kurokiba's prep surface!
I also see ripe tomatoes and olive oil.
He probably intends to make acqua pazza.
Acqua pazza—a regional
dish from Southern Italy.
With fish as the main ingredient, many
other ingredients are simmered into a stew.
It's a simple yet dynamic dish.
It's traditional to use olive oil,
tomatoes, and shellfish.
It's also notable that the dish doesn't
use much in the way of seasoning.
Because of its simplicity, the quality
of its ingredients comes to the fore.
It's a great dish to showcase
his ability to judge his ingredients.
But each and every ingredient
is strong enough to be the main player.
Wouldn't blindly
boiling them down together
actually eclipse the
Pacific saury's strengths?
True, and the Pacific saury's
in season, too...
In season!
That's it.
Because it's in season,
the Pacific saury won't be eclipsed.
Rather, it has the potential to become
a solid foundation for the entire dish.
He was able to select that dish
precisely because
he has such confidence
in his ability to judge ingredients.
Above all, he's very calm.
I don't sense any nerves or eagerness
toward the match in him.
Very impressive.
Of course you wouldn't, Chef Dojima.
Ryo-kun has faced me in cooking battles
for a very long time now!
Very nostalgic.
You were both so young. Very cute, it was.
You knew him back when he was still
in Scandinavia, Leonora-obasama.
Obaa-sama?!
How rude!
Showing off your youth!
Selfish, Erina-chan!
That's not what I said!
"Oba-sama" and "Obaa-sama"
are two different words!
So this is the boy, Alice?
Yes, Mother!
I want to make him my aide!
Let go.
I'm prepping.
Erina has a secretary now!
I want an aide around my own age, too!
Well, we should ask your father.
Don't act like I'm not even here!
I'm already the head chef of this restaurant!
I'm not gonna serve you—
I believe I told you to call me "miss."
Go home.
Then let's do a cooking battle.
Huh?
If you lose, become my loyal dog.
Woof, woof!
That little girl's dish was better...
Come on. Say "woof" for me.
Battle me one more time!
Two years after our first match,
the moment's finally come!
I've won!
His first victory!
Good job, Ryo!
We'll face off again tomorrow!
Okay, Ryo-kun?!
Fine... miss.
I'll fight you any time.
Then you'll be polite to me
when I win next time?
No way!
Heat-resistant film?
What, it's not cling wrap?
It's capable of withstanding heat
of higher than 200 C, and cold up to -40 C.
Food can be wrapped in it and cooked.
He's gained an arsenal of
molecular gastronomy techniques
that he absorbed through
his battles with Alice.
His cooking now is not
something he'd think up just
from cooking in a port town pub.
This is indicative of their whole
history working hard together.
Ryo-kun, don't lose, okay?
No need to remind me... miss.
This film is the key to my dish!
Hayama!
I'll get you for sure this time!
The one who will stand at the
top of these elections... will be me!
The moon's halfway across the sky...
Less than an hour left now.
Oh, look.
I'm done.
So first up is Kurokiba.
But...
Is that... really his dish?
In a rush, huh?
Let's hope you didn't overlook
anything in your dish.
Run your mouth while you still can.
My dish will crush your weapon.
What's Kurokiba trying to do
with that flimsy film?
Something you're very familiar with, I bet.
Candidate Kurokiba will serve first!
The moon serves to illuminate
the candidate who is
advancing toward the judges
like a stage light.
It's as though the light is purifying
the chef and his dish!
Wow!
Still simmering inside the pouch!
Very piping hot!
He's going to make the judges open the dish?
Now, have a taste!
Shrimp!
Mussels!
Clams!
And Pacific saury!
I'm getting dragged into a
torrent of different aromas!
It's so good, my face is going slack!
Director!
He's usually so stern, yet he's grinning!
It's The Grin!
Who knew we'd see The Grin here?!
The ingredients are about the same
as those in an acqua pazza,
but wrapping them in a heat-resistant
film changes the dish's name.
It's a cartoccio!
My dish is Autumn Pacific Saury Cartoccio!
He served an umami detonator
in the semi-finals.
He followed that up with
an aroma detonator, I guess.
I see.
Go on! Taste it!
So fresh! The Pacific saury's fat
is meltingly sweet!
The seafood ingredients
are all extraordinarily fresh!
There's more than enough umami here!
Such power, sealing such dynamic umami
into this dish through sheer force...
This is Kurokiba Ryo's true worth!
The Pacific saury may be in season,
but how could he craft such richness in flavor
without much seasoning to speak of?
Hm?
What is this refreshing aroma?
It's not from seafood. It's...
It's from herbs.
That's right!
I added them to the packet when
I wrapped the ingredient with the film.
I used this herb butter!
After softening butter at room temperature,
he kneaded in finely chopped
herbs, spices, and garlic.
The herb butter is complete
after resting it overnight in the fridge.
It melted gradually from
the heat in the oven,
and its richness and flavor
gradually seeped into the
Pacific saury and other ingredients!
It gave an incredible boost
to the flavors and the fragrance!
It's a violence of flavor that is absolute!
It seems we'll see my mother's "baring."
What?!
In somewhere this public?
Seriously?!
Th-Th-That'd be really bad!
Huh?
What a wonderful Pacific saury dish.
First, it had immediate visual impact
upon arriving at the table.
You have a firm grasp
of the modern cooking trend
that acknowledges the importance
of a dish's aesthetics.
Given that the entire audience
had leaned forward to look at the dish,
your plan can be said to be a success.
Anchovies are often used in acqua pazza,
When Mother eats something delicious,
she sheds her broken Japanese
but not in this dish,
since herb butter was used.
That was wise.
and "bares" a fluent command of the language.
Adding both would have led
to a clash of flavors.
Right, I remember.
The herb butter plays a critical role
in establishing this dish.
"Shedding" broken Japanese? How's that work?!
The mellow butter serves to meld
the flavors from each ingredient.
Its herbs impart a flavor that is strong,
yet light and not overwhelming...
Flavors only made possible with
Pacific saury in season, and no other fish!
That further enhances
the Pacific saury's aroma.
The heat-resistant film
and herb butter both serve
to take full advantage of the
Pacific saury's flavors.
This is a culmination
of his culinary techniques!
His singular focus in doing so
is what made
this dish's flavors possible!
Body...
...soul...
...and ocean!
All as one!
Kurokiba, that's amazing!
The director went bare-chested, too!
Well?!
Sear my dish's power
into your eyes, Hayama...
Next, Candidate Hayama will serve his dish!
The hell, asshole?!
You think you can win against me
with that kind of dish?!
Are you even being serious about this match?!
Forget it—
You don't know that aroma can recreate
even the philosophy behind a dish.
It can't be...
A carpaccio?!
An antipasto?!
No way!
These are the finals!
How can he win with an antipasto dish?
The antipasto is a dish intended to pique
the diners' appetite at the start of a course.
It is, by necessity,
a lighter dish than others.
Why did he choose that?
Hayama!
Your ability to judge ingredients
is equal to mine.
I bet you tried to take advantage
of the best Pacific saury's
fresh flavor in the raw,
but there's no way your dish
can contend with my cartoccio.
Not after it crushed the judges with
its heavy umami and aroma impact!
Well, let us taste—
Please wait a moment.
There's one last step.
He's searing the surface with a torch.
But that'd hardly enough to counter
the Kurokiba boy's aroma detonator.
Done.
My dish is Seared Pacific Saury Carpaccio!
Delicious...
Delicious!
It's delicious without even
having a single taste!
I can tell just how juicy it is!
It goes above and beyond what curing can do.
Wow!
The dish became completely different
after the fish was seared.
Sizzle!
It's as though the dish is seducing
everyone who is about to taste it!
Oh!
I can't wait... another... second!
The dressing consists of
extra virgin olive oil, wine vinegar,
and Pacific saury innards!
The rich flavor of the innards
floods the tongue,
and emphasizes the sweetness
of the Pacific saury's fat!
I'm drowning in the overflowing
aromas and flavors!
How many spices did you add to this dish?!
Nay!
He has only used allspice!
What?!
He only used one spice?
I thought Hayama's special weapon
was to weave various spices
into the best aroma possible...
No.
His ability to manipulate fragrance
is not just additive.
He was able to highlight the seasonal flavor
of Pacific saury with vivid clarity
by intentionally subtracting
spices from the dish.
And yet, how did he manage
such richness of fragrance?
It's on par with the aromatic force
of Ryo-kun's cartoccio.
Yes, and it's not possible to achieve
through searing alone!
It's the kaeshi sauce.
I brushed it over the fish,
right before serving.
The kaeshi?
Is that Tsubame Gaeshi?
Kojiro Sasaki?
I'm surprised you know that word.
But that's different.
Kaeshi is a seasoning made by
a mixture of soy sauce with mirin, sake,
and other ingredients.
You can make soba dipping sauce
by diluting kaeshi with stock.
It's considered an all-purpose seasoning
for most Japanese dishes.
No wonder.
Fish is hard to sear, even
with high heat from the torch.
Kaeshi contains sugar, which makes
the fish much easier to sear!
So he prevented the loss of flavor
that would have resulted from
a more prolonged exposure to heat.
The surface fat of the fish
and the sugars in the kaeshi
sizzle and bubble from the heat.
In other words, I managed to demonstrate
two theoretically opposing principles—
the subtraction of aroma and its emphasis—
in unison with this single dish.
Kurokiba Ryo and Hayama Akira...
They both evolved because
of their previous match.
Kurokiba Ryo wields a massive sword.
He further improved the explosive,
appetizing power of his dish at the finals.
In contrast, the duck dish that
Hayama Akira served at the semi-finals
was a brilliant feast of spices.
It was like a finely crafted, ornate sword.
But look at Hayama tonight.
Refinement through
differentiation and selection
has produced a blade that is as sharp
and fine as a well-honed rapier!
What did you call me before?
A one-trick pony with spices?
This is what it means to have
absolute mastery over aroma.
So this is the master of fragrance,
Hayama Akira's, true worth!
This Pacific saury is such a pure force!
It unleashes its flavor... with no pretense!
A well-aimed arrow is true!
Bravo!
The director's gone bare-chested again!
Oh!
The moon's starting to set!
Hurry, Soma-kun!
Yukihira, you're running out of time!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
This will be the finish!
This is irresistible to anyone
who eats rice on a daily basis.
It's enough to make you smile
purely from reflex
from the sight of it,
and the destructive aroma!
It's Salted Rice Bran Pacific Saury Rice.
Salted rice bran?!
Pickled with salted rice bran?!
So he didn't give up.
It looks delicious!
Well, I was thinking it would be
the worst case scenario
when I saw that dull-looking Pacific saury.
Yeah, I guess it looked dull because
it'd been pickled in salted rice bran.
I can't bear the piping hot fragrance!
Yes, yes.
I'll serve you right away.
Please wait. Just a moment.
Oh, Yukihira-kun!
What a tease! Hurry!
The other two were also creative
about heightening our expectations,
but Yukihira Soma is not
taking a back seat to them!
He knows how to make his guests
eager for his dish!
Here it comes!
Finally!
Now, let's taste!
The happiness of Pacific saury
brought by autumn
is spreading throughout my body!
What gentle flavor!
He grilled the fish on a
clay cooking stove first—
He grilled it first,
then cooked it with the rice!
Such meticulous prep work allowed
this much of the Pacific saury's aroma
to transfer to the rice!
And the Pacific saury itself
is marvelous, too!
With every bite,
the deep umami and fragrant aroma bursts
forth from the saltiness into your mouth!
This is on par with the Pacific saury
in the other two's dishes!
Is this deep flavor
due to the salted rice bran?!
Indeed. It's a traditional favorite
from Hokkaido.
The salted rice bran
draws out an ingredient's umami,
removes any bad smells,
and improves the nutritional value.
Some insist that it is the
best preparation for Pacific saury.
Still, I'm impressed you managed to
improve the flavor to this degree, Yukihira.
I took a big risk.
It was a race against time!
I bought as many high-quality Pacific saury
from the fish market as I could,
and kept testing aging methods.
Of course, I tried and improved other
aging methods than salted rice bran, too.
It was hard to make something that could
compete with top-quality Pacific saury in season,
but I finally found one that was
satisfactory right before the match.
That was this fish,
aged using salted rice bran!
Hints from Fumio-san's words,
the salted rice bran pickles at the dorm...
All the tips and tricks about aging
I learned from my friends...
All of it contributed to my inspiration!
He discovered that aging
method on his own?!
Though we thought it was a worthless blade,
it has shown itself to be a fine sword!
Just like a swordsmith who
forges steel into a fine blade,
he has created that sword
of autumn on his own!
Soma-kun's amazing!
Yeah! No complaints here!
I bet he'll get high marks for that!
Oh!
The director hasn't gone bare-chested!
H-Hey.
Yeah.
Right.
Chef Dojima and Ms. Leonora have also
already rested their chopsticks!
That means...
Hmm...
Did the Yukihira boy spend too much time
trying to close the ingredient quality gap?
In terms of creativity, his dish
is not on par with those two!
Of course he couldn't hope
to compete with them...
Yeah.
Like I thought, the match will be between...
...Kurokiba and Hayama!
I'd like you to have seconds, too.
Does no one want more?
It's the end of the line.
Soma-kun!
With this, we conclude the evaluation—
If it means you'd have seconds,
I'd like you to pour this
over the rice and dig in.
Hmm!
My Pacific saury dish...
...is not yet complete.
I'll show you this blade's real edge!
Food
Wars
The Second Plate
Next Episode: A New Genius
Next time, "A New Genius."