Were you on it?
Hey, I'm in Class 3.
I'm Class 2.
There's me!
Nakajima
Kotono
Ninomiya
Hina
Mizuno
Akane
Miyamoto
Aira
Ryuuzaki
Shiho
Class 1.
Hey, at least we can see
each other in the club.
That's true.
You think we'll get some first-years?
I hope we get lots!
Really?
Want me to try it on you?
Sure.
It's curling up...
LINE!
Can you give me your LINE ID?
Looking forward to working with you.
Please and thank you
No one else knows, but Azumi-kun
and I have started dating.
First Half: The Road So Far
Akanecchi's up next.
Go for it, Akanecchi!
I really don't want to.
Go embarrass yourself.
Dazai said, "Be laughed at.
Be laughed at, and become strong."
I don't really want to
get laughed at, though.
Set...
He got passed.
No good.
Hey, have you seen my potato
mascot around here?
Huh?
Potato? You mean that thing?
Yeah.
This is bad, isn't it?
It's bad.
Potato?
Is this yours, Mizuno-san?
How?!
I found it in the storage room.
Thank goodness!
I get so nervous without this.
I even messed up today, you know?
I really don't like being
in front of people.
It's so embarrassing,
but I really like running, so...
I'm hopeless, right?
N-No, you're not...
You don't need to be embarrassed.
I think... you're fine the way you are.
Okay, time's up.
The literature club has a superstition.
Pick out a book at random,
and that book will give you the perfect
life advice for your situation.
At the very least, I don't believe
romance comes down to chance.
I believe it comes down to volition.
Really?
Is your track meet coming up?
Yup, on Sunday
I have practice on Sunday.
I'm going to the shrine on
Sunday, so I'll pray for you
Please and thank you
He should just ask her out.
Hira?
I doubt Akane would turn him down.
Hey, is there a guy that you like?
I want to ask, but...
Wasn't that girl awesome?
Who?
I made up my mind.
I'm gonna train like mad.
Oh?
Starting tomorrow.
But the school trip's coming up.
Are you going to train in Kyoto?
The meet's over
Good idea!
Seriously?
Thank you very much.
Well done.
Mizuno-san.
Oh, um...
Is that...
This is, uh...
For the Kawagoe Festival?
Yeah.
Wow!
Are you in the march?
Awesome!
Nah, it's nothing.
So, um, how was the meet?
I set a new personal best.
Nice!
Congrats.
Thanks.
I was wondering how you did.
My battery died...
I was on my way home,
thinking you might be here...
And I found you.
This is weird.
Who was it that translated "I love you"
as "Isn't the moon beautiful tonight?"
Was it Dazai Osamu or Natsume Souseki?
The moon...
Huh? The moon?
I know. It's so pretty.
Would you go out with me?
Middle School Dating
Curly-kun!
Hey!
We're friends now.
You told me Curly-kun's cool, so...
Akane!
Akane.
Let's pick out gifts for the club members.
Good idea.
Keychains?
Snacks for the boys.
Curly-kun.
Pick one.
Me?
What kind do boys like?
Um...
I think the bigger one.
That's it!
We're choosing gifts for our club.
Oh, really?
Yeah. You know how guys eat a lot.
What do you like?
Me?
Yeah. For reference.
Anything.
Really?
So, who's next?
Akanecchi.
Me?
You have someone, don't you?
If you're curious about
someone, that counts, too.
There is someone I'm curious about.
Who? Who? Who? Who? Who? Who?
Hira?
Did he ask you out?
Hira's cool.
You should go out with him.
Just like that?
No, I...
That was close.
The teacher was right there.
That scared me.
Why are you guys here?
Azumi-kun: What're you up to?
Why not?
What's the problem?
We're going to be the ones to get yelled at.
If you want, tomorrow at 12:00 in front
of Doimaru Department Store
Why so cold?
We don't want you here.
Come on, we're already here.
Stop, idiot! Idiot!
Huh? Say what?
Suspicious.
Uh... Yeah.
No secrets, remember?
I, uh... My parents are
asking about souvenirs.
Yasaka Shrine
What's wrong?
Nothing.
What?
Have to go?
No?
That's enough.
We're torturing her.
Let's split up.
Let's go, Miu.
Huh?
Come on.
Hey, wait...
See you later!
I'm at Doimaru Department Store
Where are you?
He's not answering me.
We aren't dating.
I never even gave him an answer.
He might not come.
Hello, Akane?
Here.
H-Hey...
Who's this?
Azumi.
Why?
Some stuff happened...
I don't get it.
I was waiting for you.
Where are you?
You're so late.
Sorry.
You told me to meet you here,
so I came, but you weren't here.
It's raining, and you aren't
answering your phone.
S-Sorry.
The teacher took my phone.
Why Chinatsu's phone?
You guys are close, huh?
She just happened to...
I...
What?
Nothing.
I don't know.
I don't know, but we can't
even talk at all...
Yeah.
I want...
to talk with you more, Azumi-kun.
Is that...
your answer?
Yeah.
Things you shouldn't do
in a relationship
1. Don't text or LINE too much
— Boys hate needy girls
2. Think about how often you reply
— Don't reply right away,
but don't wait too long, either
3. Don't text or LINE during a date
— Do you have a habit of reacting
as soon as you get a message
from your friends?
Dating is so hard.
I'm going to go to that cram school.
Yeah?
Tell me your LINE ID?
Okay.
Whoops...
Sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Thank goodness.
Did you find the place okay?
I used Maps.
How did the exam go?
Decent.
Lucky.
I did awful.
Really?
I'm not studying.
Your novel?
Yeah.
That's okay, then.
I mean, I think it's okay.
Sorry.
Chinatsu
Notice to Akane!
I think I have a crush on Azumi-kun
Can I have a bite?
This again?
It's so good!
What flavor is yours, Akane?
Kinako mochi soda.
Let me taste!
Really? Wow!
Yeah, the publisher called me and
said they wanted to meet with me.
That's awesome!
I don't know.
Wow...
I still don't know what they want to say.
You might be winning that award.
Dunno...
Good for you.
Yeah.
It really is amazing.
Your dream might come true.
Yeah.
Oh, but it's this Sunday.
The same day?
Sorry I can't come cheer for you.
It's totally fine.
The same day, huh?
Yeah.
Let's both do our best.
Yeah, let's.
What about you?
You said you wanted to talk.
Oh, um...
No, never mind.
It's okay. Next time.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Azumi-kun
Here goes
Pinky promise
Oh, over here.
Hi.
Hey...
About that LINE message the other day...
S-Sorry.
For what?
I'm, uh...
in... a relationship.
W-With Azumi-kun.
I know.
It's obvious.
We're friends, after all.
Uh...
Thanks for letting me know.
Set!
Mizuno, slow down!
We're searching for young writers right now.
Right.
You're in middle school, aren't you?
Yes.
Lucky you, being so young.
Well, to be honest, I don't think you're
cut out for serious literature.
Why don't you try
light novel-type stuff instead?
I have a feeling you could do it, Azumi-san.
Mizuno.
What happened today?
You weren't focused at all, were you?
I was sure you could make it to prefecturals.
Your time was actually worse than last year.
Come on, Mizuno...
Sorry I didn't tell you we were dating.
And I'm sorry I fell for him.
The truth is...
Yeah.
I don't know what to do.
But... we're friends.
Thanks, Akane.
Can I confess to him?
I want proper closure.