Let's go over safety before we hit the pool.
If you have a fever, haven't slept,
I feel like my eyes meet
with my classmate's, Sugawara-kun's,
or if haven't had breakfast, let me know.
a lot during swimming class.
Is it just a coincidence?
Gaze
Was he looking at me?
Nah, there's no way
he would be looking at me.
I can't help but glance at Takano
in her swimsuit during swimming class.
Our eyes even met just now.
I need to stop, or she'll get creeped—
Let's do warm-up exercises.
All right.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight...
But why do Sugawara-kun's and my eyes meet?
I wonder if he was looking at someone else.
Crap, our eyes keep meeting.
She knows I'm looking.
I guess I should say hi rather than
pretend nothing happened.
I wonder who he just waved to.
It doesn't look like anyone reacted.
Could it be me?
That was embarrassing.
What do I do?
Should I apologize?
But then I should do it during break
It's not like he's looking at me.
I feel bad for reacting as if he was.
It's going to get more awkward
as time passes.
I should be casual about it.
I think I'll ask him who he's looking at.
All right, jump in in order, on my mark.
Hey, sorry about what's been happening.
Huh? W-Why?
I mean, it's not on purpose,
but I kept glancing at you.
Nah.
I'm sorry for interrupting, too.
Interrupting what?
You were looking at
someone else, weren't you?
Huh?
Who was it?
The girl beside me?
You, Takano.
Huh?
What did Sugawara-kun...
What's wrong, Takano?
Hurry up.
O-Okay.
Sugawara-kun was watching me this whole time?
Why?
I don't have that nice of a body.
There's nothing to look at.
Why?
Why is my heart racing?
S-Sugawara-kun.
I think I was looking at you, too.
I'm Goda, though.
I told her.
Should I pass that on to Sugawara?
No.
Forget what I said.
The End
Things have been awkward ever since
I confessed to the guy I like.
I can give up dating him, but I want
to at least go back to being friends.
Square One
No, I want to date him if I can, but...
It's been a month since Kanda confessed
to me. I haven't been able to reply.
She avoids me when I try to talk to her.
It hasn't bothered me.
Don't worry about it.
This is her only reply to my message.
Would I just be annoying if I kept trying
to talk when she doesn't want me to?
Is it too late for me to confess again?
I'll apologize to Takase.
I'll apologize and make things normal again.
Okay.
Ah, that's mine.
Oh, here.
Th-Thanks.
H-Hi.
This is weird.
How did I talk to Takase before?
Huh?
Something's different again today.
Maybe it's nothing.
Cras—
Huh?
Class is starting.
I misspoke! Crap, that was embarrassing!
K-Kanda?
What's up with you today?
No, uh, sorry!
No, I'm sorry, too.
No, it was my fault.
Nah, it was me.
No, I'm so sorry!
I'm really sorry!
I've been meaning to apologize,
but I couldn't find the right time.
Nah, I've been meaning to say something, too.
I can talk to him.
I can tell him honestly.
I-I don't really care anymore.
Huh?
Wait, that sounded like
I don't like him anymore.
But maybe it's easier to make up if I act
like I don't have feelings for him anymore?
Y-You really don't care anymore?
Is he asking because he's relieved?
Or because he's disappointed?
If there's still a chance...
U-Uh...
I-If it's okay with you...
Yeah, let's be friends again.
Y-Yeah?
Sure, that's...
Yeah.
I'm glad.
I wanted to be friends, too.
I-I'm so glad!
I'm saved!
I was too late!
I should have confessed!
I guess I was being friend-zoned all along.
I'm glad we made up,
but now I have mixed feelings.
Y-You can stop avoiding me, all right?
S-Sorry.
My boyfriend and I kissed for the first time.
But it was so sudden, I choked.
Once More
Who chokes on their first kiss?
I want to try again.
I want to try again!
Kamine's been weird lately.
She looks like she wants to say something.
Is it about that kiss?
Is she pissed that I did it out of the blue?
Was it too soon?
I wonder if Goda-kun
isn't going to do it today.
Maybe I should ask him.
Of course.
I never had her permission.
It must have bothered her.
I don't want to be the one to ask, though.
I hope he'll do it again.
I'll quit doing that kind of thing
from now on.
Hey, Goda-kun, there's no one
at the park today.
There isn't.
It's just us two.
It is.
Doesn't that make you think of that kiss?
Want to go somewhere else, then?
Wh-Why?
I mean, if it bothers you...
I-It doesn't bother me.
But what about you?
Don't you want to try again?
I'm fine.
I have no regrets.
O-Oh, really?
Uh-huh...
Wow.
It doesn't look like he's going to do it.
Maybe the mood's not right.
She's pretty wary of me.
I need to be careful
so she doesn't think I'm a player.
M-Man, I'm getting sleepy.
Want to go home?
Nah.
Can I sleep here?
Sure.
There.
"There"?
I-I'm sleeping in his lap!
My heart's going to explode.
But maybe this will get him in the mood.
Zzz...
He's sleeping!
He's actually sleeping!
He must have been tired from club work.
I guess it's not going to happen.
Whoops, sorry.
I was dozing off.
I was about to touch your face.
Are you all right, Kamine?
Kamine?
What's wrong?
The End
Minagawa-san, the student president,
says she likes me.
Like
I like you.
Minagawa-san, are you being serious?
No.
"No"? So you were kidding?
Please, I wasn't kidding.
It's true that I like you,
but I'm not serious.
I don't get it.
I haven't shown you serious power.
Guys like this sort of thing, don't you?
Th-Then what's your usual "like"?
My usual is "like" as in,
"You're so cute, Furuya-kun."
So you are messing with me.
I like you.
That was "like" as in,
"You're so cute when you're angry."
How am I supposed to answer
when you act like that?
Oh?
You were going to give me an answer?
Well, yeah, I don't like
letting it drag on forever.
Then I'll listen seriously.
But I can't give an answer
if you aren't serious about liking me.
Can you handle my serious "like"?
All right, I'll let you hear it.
Wait, you're already making a joke out of it!
I'm not.
I'm embarrassed, too.
Then... Here I go.
I like you.
I-I like you, too.
Sorry, I take that back.
That was an "I like your serious face, too"
kind of "like."
It's hard to be serious.
Y-Yeah?
I thought so, too, actually.
I like you.
I like you!
None of them really clicks.
Maybe I can't express
my serious "like" in words.
Huh? Say what?
Close your eyes.
What? Why?
Just do it.
I can't do it with your eyes open.
Are they closed?
Don't open them until I say so.
Not yet.
Don't open them yet.
Wait, what?
Is this okay?
We aren't even dating yet.
No, so why don't I just go out with her?
Okay.
Well?
Did you feel my serious "like"?
What part of that was serious?!
Y-You used your fingers
to pretend you were kissing me!
I never said that was my fingers.
You can tell if that was my fingers
or if I was serious, can't you?
Which do you think it was?
Well?
Next episode: Lovers.
Lovers