As always, I can't make any sense of you.
Whatever.
You better get ready,
Rin.
And you're as icy as ever.
Yeah...
You really piss me off.
Makoto.
Give us the start signal.
Okay.
We'll race 100 meters,
freestyle.
Ready,
go!
Wow! Rin-chan has a stronger kick!
But...
Haru's stroke is faster!
Gou?
Damn it!
From: Matsuoka Gou
Subject:
Did you get to see Nanase-san and the other guys?
Does this mean that
I can't ever beat him?
Memories in the Distance!
Idiots!
Do you actually feel bad
about what you've done?!
Sorry.
First you trespass in
an abandoned building,
now you trespass in
another school's pool?!
Honestly, we're fortunate that
they've agreed not to
make a big deal of this.
Now, now. I think that's enough.
There's a famous saying that
applies to this situation.
In Ancient China during the Shang Dynasty,
Duke Tai of Qi would fish without any bait...
I hate fish.
Excuse me.
Miss Ama-chan wasn't much help.
I wonder how that fish saying goes...
Haru, do you know...?
Huh?
Haru-chan's over there.
When did that happen?
Ah, Gou-chan!
I told you to call me Kou!
Does it really matter?
It matters! I'm Kou!
Gou.
Kou!
Kou.
Gou!
Damn you!
So were you able to see my brother?
Yeah, about that...
Rin-chan's so mean!
We haven't seen each
other in four years!
And the first thing he does is
challenge Haru-chan to a race.
He completely ignored me and Makoto.
We didn't get a chance
to talk about anything.
Have you heard anything
from Rin, Kou-chan?
I've sent him e-mails and called
his cell without any luck.
I even called his dorm number
and nobody picked up.
How come Rin-chan's changed so much?
Did something happen in Australia?
I don't know.
I was hoping that he'd open
up after meeting you guys.
Are you responsible for Rin
showing up at the swimming club?
I wouldn't say that I was responsible...
I was just trying to help.
I happened to overhear your conversation,
I just heard that they're tearing down
the swimming club you used to go to
so I sent him a message.
But he never replied.
That's why you went to
Haru's place yesterday?
Yes, I was hoping he
might have some answers.
Hey, I have a great idea!
Let's start a swim club!
Then we can see Rin-chan at tournaments.
Uh, I'm not sure Haru will
be on board with that.
Whatever. Knock yourself out.
Huh?
Really?
Yay!
We're good to go then!
I'm so excited!
Are you sure about this?
We won't be doing this by ourselves.
You're expected to join the club.
I know.
No! Don't look!
Girls my age shouldn't ogle naked men!
Must... not...
look...
What...
incredible triceps!
Oh, yeah. Haru-chan wasn't
with us the other day.
This is Rin-chan's sister.
H-Hello. It's been a long time.
Matsuoka
Kou.
Yes!
I'm sorry about what my
brother did yesterday.
Don't sweat it.
Oh, if you're making tea, I
have some squid to go with it.
What? Wouldn't chocolate be better?
We'll compromise and have mackerel.
That's not a compromise.
I'll give you a hand!
Is this okay?
Isn't this...
Ah, right.
That's the trophy the
four of us won as kids.
Rin told us that he no longer needed it.
Everyone's smiling.
Actually, Haru's the sole
exception in this photo.
Haru-chan is always smiling on the inside.
You make him sound like a bad person!
Oh, so is this the first time Rin's
come back to Japan since he left?
Huh?
He came back every year for New Year's.
Really?!
And he never told us?!
That's mean.
Haru?
Since everyone's on board,
I picked up a new club application form.
You move fast.
It's important to get the ball rolling.
Let's see, the purpose of this club is
to train our minds and
bodies through swimming
and improve the school experience.
And you know what you're doing.
There will be three members initially.
Mako-chan, you can be the captain.
Uh, shouldn't it be Haru?
He's the fastest swimmer.
This isn't about speed.
Different people are better
at different things.
Okay!
First-years are on cleanup duty!
Second-years are in
charge of the chlorine!
Third-years have a meeting once
they've finished stretching!
Got it, Captain Haruka!
I don't think so.
That means Mako-chan is the captain,
and Haru-chan can be the vice-captain.
Hey, don't just volunteer me.
Now, now, now.
Vice-captain is just an empty title
with no actual responsibilities,
so don't worry.
You just offended every
vice-captain on this planet.
I'll be the treasurer,
which means we just need a faculty advisor.
Any ideas?
I was thinking about asking Ama-chan.
Miss Ama-chan?
I heard a crazy story from
one of our classmates.
Faculty Office
What?
I can't do it.
Sports aren't my thing.
I mean, I teach classical literature.
But I heard that
until last year, you had a job in
Tokyo that involved swimsuits.
Hey!
Not so loud!
Who'd you hear that from?
It was Nashimoto-kun, from our class.
Did you work for a swimsuit designer?
What?
Y-Yes, you could say that...
In that case,
we would be thrilled to have you
advise us about the technology
that goes into competitive swimwear!
Advise us!
Please!
If you really need me...
Thank you very much!
Yay!
Samezuka Academy
I'm Matsuoka Rin's sister.
I'm here to see my brother.
Oh, looks like Matsuoka-kun isn't back yet.
Really.
Excuse me...
Incredible...
Totally a prestigious school's swimming club.
Traps and pecs everywhere!
They're gorgeous!
Hey, so it's you?
The one who's looking for her big brother?
Oh, yes.
Hold on.
You know...
You're pretty cute.
Thank you. I'm looking for
Matsuoka Rin, my brother.
Matsuoka?
There's nobody named
Matsuoka on the swim team.
Huh?
Now,
in regard to the swim club
charter that you submitted...
After strict review by the faculty,
it was approved!
Really?
Awesome! I knew we could count on
a former swimwear company employee!
Th-That's right...
This is what I can do when
I put my mind to it.
However, a school organization is
required to have four members,
so you'll have to find one more person.
And there's one more condition.
No problem!
I'm willing to do anything!
Wow, so much nature.
Are you saying that...
Yes, you must restore this
pool to a usable state.
You're not allowed to run away.
You said you were willing to do anything.
Let's swim together
Iwatobi Swim Club
Haru?
Huh? He's not here.
It's cleaned up rather nicely.
Can't you get out of that
chair and give us a hand?
Do you realize what you're saying?
The UV rays this time of year are brutal.
You're still young,
so it's not an issue.
This is pretty fun.
Feels like we're back in grade school.
Grade schoolers wouldn't
be asked to fix a pool.
True.
Wow, it's all cleaned up!
Ah! Are you here to help, Gou-chan?
I told you to call me Kou!
Otherwise, you don't get any of this.
What? You can't be serious!
Hey, there!
Interested in joining the swim club?
I've already decided to
join the track team.
Hey, guys!
Let's have fun swimming together!
Why would you want to swim in a pool
when the ocean's right over there?
If you join now, you'll receive
a year's supply of Iwatobi's
mascot character, Iwatobi-chan!
No, thanks.
No luck!
Nobody wants to join.
It's starting to look like we
fixed the pool for nothing.
Don't say that!
It's time to use our last resort...
We have Ama-chan give the
shirt off her back for us!
How so?
Advertise the fact that
Ama-chan is our advisor,
and tell everyone they'll get
to see her in a swimsuit if they join!
I see. That's giving up her shirt, all right.
Excuse me...
If you do that, I'll quit immediately.
I swore to myself that I'd
never put on a swimsuit again!
Understood?
Are we clear?
Crystal.
I'll leave the juice here.
Thanks.
I don't quite get it, though.
Get what?
Why didn't you try to start a swim
club when you were first-years?
Haru wasn't interested.
But he's such a good swimmer.
Haru joined the swim
club in middle school,
but he quit at the end of our first year.
Did something happen?
No idea.
He didn't want to talk about it.
Our old swimming club was shut
down around the same time,
and Haru hasn't done any
competitive swimming since.
So he wanted to quit swimming.
Probably.
I wonder if my brother's the same way.
Huh?
I was looking for my brother the other day,
and found out he's not on the swim team.
He transferred to Samezuka Academy,
but he didn't join the swim team.
No way!
I mean, he just raced Haru and...
He must have lost.
That's why he's given up on swimming.
No, that can't be it.
I mean, when they raced that night...
Haru's so good.
Yep.
He lost ground to Rin-chan on every turn,
but he's nearly caught up now!
Damn! I can't shake him!
They're making the final turn!
Who hit first?!
Too close to tell!
They're neck and neck!
No, Rin's legs put him
ahead after the turn!
Haru...
I've seen this before.
This sensation...
I get it now.
This is what I wanted.
No need to rely on or
work with other people.
I just want to drift through
the water alone in silence.
Haru-chan!
Haru!
Yes!
What?!
My brother won?!
Yeah, didn't Rin tell you?
He didn't respond, so I thought
he was upset about losing.
He didn't seem very happy about winning.
In fact, I'd say that Haru was more...
You win.
That's great, Rin.
That's great?
That was when
we were found by a teacher
who heard all the noise.
I don't get why he'd say that after losing.
Haru just wanted to swim.
He's back to his old self.
Haru was never one to care about
winning or improving his time.
Will my brother also go
back to his old self?
You still need one more member, right?
That's right.
Please let me join!
You're the only ones who
can change my brother.
If you're willing to have me,
I can serve as your
manager and help you out!
Ooh, ooh. What's going on?
Kou-chan offered to join the swim club!
What? Really?!
That means the swim club is
officially open for business!
Yay!
Oh, that's wonderful news.
You'll get to swim with everyone again.
Yeah, we still have a
lot of prep work to do.
That's mine!
Don't take it!
You never finish your food.
I eat my ham!
Come on.
Stop fighting.
You can have some of mine.
Big brother, I want some too!
There you go.
Speaking of which,
I believe the swimming
club you used to go to
is finally being torn down.
Hurts, right?
It's not easy to watch as
your memories are destroyed.
Were you a part of this club?
Well, you can't go against the times.
It's sad.
Wait, are you...
Coach Sasabe?!
It's Makoto!
Tachibana Makoto!
You got real big, Makoto!
It's been too long!
Well, I work part-time as
a pizza deliveryman now.
Did you come here for one last glimpse?
Is that why you're here?
I thought I'd drop by on my
way back from a delivery.
Are the other boys doing well?
Yes. I go to the same
school as Haru and Nagisa.
Are you still friends with Rin?
Yes...
He goes to a different school though.
Rin's back from Australia, right?
He looked pretty glum when I last
saw him, so I was a little worried.
Glum?
Haruka didn't mention it?
I think it was during the winter of
your first year of middle school.
I was closing down the place for the
end of the year when
Haruka and Rin showed up.
Apparently, they ran into each
other while Rin was back home.
Did they have a race?
That's right. And Haruka won easily.
Rin was pretty upset about it.
Can't blame him.
He went to a swimming school abroad,
and it didn't make a difference.
Is something wrong?
No...
I see.
So that's why Haru quit
swimming competitively.
It's because he hurt Rin.
The customer you have called
is currently unable to answer.
Please leave your name and
message after the tone.
Rin?
It's me, Makoto.
We're starting up a swim club.
So you should join the swim team.
We might get to swim
together at a tournament.
Don't need you to tell me that.
I already decided to join the swim team.
However...
I'm not doing this for a chance
to swim with you guys.
Okay.
Here's to the establishment
of the new swim club!
Cheers!
It's not warm enough to start swimming,
but we filled the pool as a test run.
All that's left is to toss these in together.
There!
The swim club is finally ready to go.
Well, we can't get in the pool yet...
Wait, Haru!
You were wearing your swimsuit again?!
I can't get enough of those triceps!
What? Triceps?!
Haru, it's still too cold right now!
Oh, dear.
I don't see a problem.
He looks comfortable enough.
That's true...
Wait! His lips are turning purple!
Get out of the water
before you catch a cold!
Go, Haru-chan!
No! He can't!
I'll go find a net!
Huh? A net?
So what's this Iwatobi-chan
I've been hearing about?
It's the mascot character for our town
that was chosen from 987 entries last year.
I submitted an entry for that.
What?! You did?!
So 1 of the 987 entries
was from Haruka-senpai?
What was your entry?
Let me see!
Here. Tobimaru-kun.
It's not cute.
Next time: Theoretical Dolphin Kick.
Theoretical Dolphin Kick!
The swim club's about to get
an awesome new member!
Hooked by Iwatobi-chan?!