Okikura here.
Hi, it's Fukami, from school.
Oh, it's me.
Oh, Okikura-kun, hey,
I want to see the future.
I want to see the future, too.
That thing just now—
Episode 3
"Utility Tank"
Yeah, is that now?
Yeah, now.
Let's meet up to talk.
I'll go to your place.
Eh?
It'll get late if we meet now.
No, don't worry about it. I'll be fine.
I'm going to finish up some things first.
I have a really important guest—
Piece! Yeah, piece—that I'm going to work on.
So don't come into the workshop.
Sure, but be done by dinner.
I will.
You're a hard worker, Touko.
It wasn't Yana-chan that Yuki-kun liked...
And Okikura-kun is coming over...
Okay.
Yuki-kun and Yana-chan are
such precious friends to me.
They always have been,
and they always will be.
But even if my feelings don't change,
our friendships might.
Yana-chan's crying.
Try glassware
single-flower cups
I'm going to make Yana-chan cry.
You saw the future?
Yeah.
Makes sense.
Hm?
This is why glass is your medium.
Maybe.
A guest?
Good evening.
We're busy.
Thanks for taking care of my sister.
I'll bring tea—
It's fine, Okikura-kun was just about to leave.
D-Don't tell Mom and Dad, okay?
We're having pork cutlets tonight.
See you.
Sorry you came only to
have me kick you out.
Don't worry about it.
I wanted to see Yana-chan
and Yuki-kun's future.
Did Yukinari Imi confess
to you or something?
H-How did you—
Yana-chan realized there was
someone Yuki-kun liked,
so she came to talk to me.
You must have been the only
one who hadn't noticed.
What would you have done,
having seen their future?
I wanted to think of a way to make
sure we wouldn't get torn apart.
I don't know if that can be granted,
but I like that you put
effort into everything.
I'll be fine from here. Thanks.
We're going to the mountain tomorrow.
Would you like to come, too?
Why?
I was thinking maybe you haven't made
many new friends here yet.
I make a point to go hiking by myself.
See you soon.
I was the only one who didn't notice.
No way.
There's still time.
Did you have trouble sleeping?
A bit.
But I need another way...
That doesn't make any sense.
I'm telling you, it's important for girls.
Why do you need to bring
a dryer on a hiking trip?
What if my hair gets messed up?
Where are we even going
to find wall sockets?
Rechargeable, duh.
Morning.
We were waiting for you.
All right, let's do this.
I'm here.
You're late, Nee-chan.
Sorry.
I took the wrong road. Tee hee.
You're really, really going to be okay?
It'll be fine.
Trust me. I care about you.
Call me right away if you get worried.
See you at the meet-up spot!
Back up, everyone!
I've seen you a few times before, Sacchan.
Can I call you "Sacchan"?
Yes.
Everyone around here goes
to the central hospital, right?
Shoot.
Oh, that's a cute pendant.
Where did you buy it?
It was a gift.
Good taste.
From who, your boyfriend?
No, but it's someone I love.
Oh man, he's good!
Whoops.
So yeah,
my kid brother's out-of-touch
when it comes to girls,
and he worries about silly
things like his height,
but he's a good guy at heart.
Right...
Be good to him, yeah?
Thanks.
Were you too pumped about today to sleep?
Okikura-kun came over yesterday.
Okikura-kun is that new student, right?
He seemed like he'd like mountains.
Maybe we should have invited him.
I did, but he said he likes hiking alone.
A lone wolf, huh?
I like hiking with my friends.
Let's go, another half-hour!
Over here!
How are you feeling?
Thanks, it was fun in the car.
It was fun?
I've never been on one,
but I imagine it's what roller coasters are like.
Roller...
Okay, I'll come pick you up when it's time.
Yeah, thanks.
You be careful, too—
She's like the wind.
Living with her, she's more like a typhoon.
We're here!
Look, mountains!
And the ocean!
We just came up a mountain, too, you know.
What?
It feels awesome.
There's still snow over there.
Isn't that Hinode Mountain?
How can I help?
Can you get some water in here?
Roger!
Where can we go for water, again?
I'll go with you.
You shouldn't, Sachi.
Yeah. You're probably the weakest one here.
I'll go.
Then I'll go, too.
You're in charge of the tents, Yukinari.
I am?
Let's go, Yana-chan.
Imagine if we look all over,
and it turns out there's water right there.
Hey, Yana-chan.
There's something I wanted
to ask you, Touko.
Oh hey, a creek.
It's so pretty.
Are you going to go out with Yuki?
What?
What are you doing?
Sorry.
Hey...
I set up sheets. You can sit down and read.
Good luck, dude.
Where are you going?
I'm going to find those two.
Yeah, they're late.
Maybe they couldn't figure
out where to get water.
There's a tap just over there.
He's pretty thoughtful, too.
Do you like yakisoba?
With a lot of pickled red ginger.
Got it.
We should be okay here.
You're so bold.
Whose fault is that?
I'm sorry.
Well, I just have bad timing.
Yana-chan.
Touko, what did you think about Yuki?
Honestly,
I'm surprised. I don't know.
Seems like it.
You wouldn't normally say "thanks"
after being confessed to.
I said that?
Wait, how did you know?
I saw,
by accident.
Touko, are you going to go out with him?
No.
Yuki-kun's really cool
but my romance sensor didn't go off.
Your what?
I doubt you have such a thing installed.
Too bad I can't show you.
You're not going to, huh?
You'd be a bit more obvious if
you liked him, I guess.
Besides, I decided to support you.
I
won't give up.
No service
You couldn't get lost here
even if you tried, but...
What the hell are you doing?
Why are you the one screaming?
Get lost!
And damn yourself to an
eternity of fetching water!
You're so beautiful,
the way you're so invested in reading.
You're like
a doll to me.
Pretty. A poem or something?
No.
Where're the noodles?
Here.
Thanks.
Hot!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Water.
I'm back. What's the water for?
For Hiro-kun.
Do I dump it on his head?
How about I dump it on your head?
Seriously, that freaked me out.
Time to eat!
It's good.
Right? Dig in!
A token of our friendship.
I'll have it, then.
Good.
Token.
That sounds good.
I'll have some if it gets
on the menu. Good luck.
Yeah.
I'm looking forward to it.
You were like a doll to me.
But I realized...
Sacchan.
How's your hand?
Yeah, it's not burnt or anything.
Here.
For taking care of me.
Not at all, thanks to you, t—
You can read it now, if you want.
Sacchan, I,
well—
I—Sachi!
I like your name.
There's something I need to tell you.
I think there's someone
that's more suited for you.
Is there someone you like?
No.
Then—
I can't.
Why?
Because you're a precious friend.
I see.
Sorry to be such a bother.
No problem.
Wait inside.
Okay.
Oh yeah, I saw a boar on my way here.
It looked pretty vicious,
so if you run into one,
don't pretend to be asleep.
Isn't that for bears?
Sorry.
Oh, really?
Sorry I didn't help.
It didn't take long to pack up, no worries.
We're done, Nee-chan.
You're getting a ride home, right?
Yes.
Café next time, then, maybe?
Thanks for everything today, Touko-chan.
We're heading out.
Be careful, Nee-chan.
Yeah, yeah.
Sacchan, are you doing okay?
Okay, let's go, before we run into boars.
Did you know there are more
accidents going down mountains
Okay, whatever, let's go.
than going up?
Let's go, Touko.
Okay, thanks.
I'll lead the way.
Don't get lost.
Roger.
Yeah, yeah.
Hinode
Bridge
Sacchan
Text Message
To Touko-chan,
Thanks for everything today.
I'll contact you soon.
Welcome home.
I'm home.
Hey, Hina-chan,
what would you do if your best friend
got confessed to by someone you like?
You got confessed to?
Jeez, stop it.
Well?
What could I do?
It'd depend on whether I liked
the person back or not.
What else could I say?
That's my Hina-chan.
Stop it!
So that guy from the other day—
did he go hiking with you?
No, he didn't!
Kakeru is a weird name.
Yanagi—nice name.
Kind of awesome, isn't it?
Really?
Do you like him?
Episode 4:
"Steep Road"
You're showing off a bit, aren't you?