Wow! We can actually use the CROWDS!
Stop!
Calm down, people!
Platoon, engage!
Move! Out of my way!
Please calm down!
Please return to the evacuation point!
To all G-team members!
Be careful with your attacks!
Do not attack unless
the CROWDS attack first!
Humans are so foolish.
Berg-Katze.
I await you at the Spiritual Precipice.
Ah, ha! There you are, Gay-chan.
Do you really think I'll fly
right into such an obvious trap?
Well, I bet you won't come, anyway.
You can't do anything unless you're
pretending to be someone else.
You're a fragile chicken-chan!
Oh?
Hey, you!
Just who do you think
you're picking a fight with?
Now, I'm mad!
So, Rui-kun...
This is too much for us
to handle by ourselves, anymore!
What?!
I'm sure it will come.
JJ, this planet is
surprisingly immature.
Outta the way!
Why?
Why is this happening?
To all CROWDS!
Stop the violence immediately!
Stay out of this, JSDF!
It's not like you guys can even
fight without permission, right?
Give us some respect!
We will not let you pass!
Everyone's carrying on with their lives
Damn it!
without knowing what's right.
Quit screwing around!
Stop!
I can't do this alone.
We can't do this alone.
A fragmented world where you
can't get anything you want.
They continue to move forward...
Stop!
That won't change the world!
Violence will never change the world!
...while making multiple mistakes.
Papa!
People are trying to find
something that'll make today
different than the day before.
This is...
They're so precious.
That's why I can't let
anything harm this planet...
Oh, man...
Katze-san, where are you?
Hajime-tan, Hajime-tan!
Do you remember the riddle?
What everyone loves.
The sweet, sweet taste of—
Other people's misfortunes?
Yep, yep, yep!
Everyone on this planet's
probably really excited right now!
Do you think so?
Well, of course they are!
They all love other people
having a tough time!
I mean, who can listen
to people going on
and on about how happy they are?
You can listen to them
sobbing for hours, though!
I wonder if that's how it really is...
What? Are you crying?
You're always smiling!
Hajime-tan, are you teary-eyed?
I'm not.
Hajime-tan, what I like about
you is that you're honest.
Try being honest.
Aren't you super annoyed right now?
Wouldn't you love it if I died?
Katze-san, I won't kill you.
I promise!
L-I-E-S!
It's not a lie.
Man, you seriously make me puke.
Die!
I won't die.
And I won't kill you.
Right. LOL, LOL.
Katze-san!
LOL, LOL.
Once things settle down,
will you go out with me?
Boyfriend!
It might take a while,
LOL
but please wait for me
at Tachikawa Station's concourse.
Katze-san!
What makes a hero?
What, what, what?
And let me thank you
one last time, JJ.
What, what, what?
What's a hero?
Can you become one?
What makes a hero?
Thanks for turning
Hajime-chan into a Gatchaman!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
I'd like to make a report
to dear JJ-dono,
who watches over this foolish planet!
Tachikawa is totally finished!
This shitty planet's annihilation
has begun with this city!
Don't celebrate too soon, Berg-Katze.
Are you sure about this?
When you spread your wings,
everything will disappear, right?
Just like back then,
with your daddy's planet...
I'll finish you in an instant.
No blinking allowed.
Are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready.
I am the last line of defense,
the final wings protecting this planet!
I will vanquish you for eternity
with these arrows of annihilation!
Go, Bird!
I'm actually scared out of my mind.
I mean, if I destroy everything,
I won't be able to see my friends anymore.
OD...
Gay-chan, finished.
OD, I'll make dinner tonight.
Thank you for always taking care of me!
If you don't come back, I'll be gloomy!
Utsutsu, when'd you learn to talk smack?
Quit screwing around, asshole!
Aw, damn.
Oh, crap!
I'm gonna disappear!
Listen, Berg-Katze.
I'm not scared.
I just want to continue watching this world,
because a future far greater
than your imagination awaits it!
A f-f-future?!
Boring!
Take this!
OD!
I have faith in everyone.
The NOTE.
I need the NOTE to do it.
OD-san...
Here I am!
I made you wait way too long!
OD-san!
Rui-kun, the rest is up to you.
Spread your wings to your
heart's content.
Nice catch!
Thank you!
By now, the world has gone
up in a big, red blaze.
What fun!
Mayor, Prime Minister.
I'd like to try something.
Thank you...
X, I was not wrong.
Everyone was my partner.
That was the truth.
Gatcha
Gatchannel
Please Wait a Moment
Here we go with another
installment of the Gatchannel!
I am Ninomiya Rui.
Gatcha!
I'd like to start a game in Tachikawa.
The name of the game is
the Tachikawa CROWDS Game!
All participants...
will receive the CROWDS ability!
What?!
No way!
Gimme a break!
Update!
Did you see that?
Isn't it amazing?
I'd like everyone to use
their own CROWDS ability, too.
Will you join the Tachikawa CROWDS Game?
I'll let you decide how you will use it,
because I'm not you.
It's easy.
Just download the app I'll send you now.
You can always stop whenever things get bad.
I won't be stingy and tell you
it's only for Tachikawa users.
I'm going to send this app
to GALAX users worldwide.
Then you can come here from
anywhere, just with one click!
You'll be able to see the Gatchaman
fight super up close and personal!
Why limit yourself to just watching the fight?
Let's all become heroes while we're at it!
Will you join the Tachikawa CROWDS Game?
Aren't you getting excited?
You can do anything you want.
Find your own, personal game!
If you can't join,
just send us your update points...
Update.
...by clicking on the Update button
while we're playing our own game!
Let's go for one billion
update points before dawn!
Now, are you ready?
Let's go, everyone!
Play the CROWDS!
Do you think this will work, X?
Why do you ask that, Rui?
I can tell
that you are feeling more
excitement than anyone else.
X,
I'm really, really happy
that I could meet you.
Will you join the Tachikawa CROWDS Game?
Join.
"Will you join the Tachikawa CROWDS Game?"
Well, I guess I can give it a try.
Join.
I wish I knew what that brainiac was thinking...
Whoa! So light!
Hey, is this really a good idea?
They're squabbling!
Ow!
Should we deal with it?
There are too many of you guys!
Hey! Hands off!
Rui, the evacuees don't have enough food.
Okay, how about this for a game?
Fast and Furious Rice Balls Game
Fast and Furious Rice Balls Game?
It says, "Right now, there are many
people in Tachikawa who need food.
"Your skills as a
housewife are needed."
"Skills as a housewife"?
Nice one, GALAX!
Want to give our skills a try?
Let's make a team!
Let's earn points!
There is ongoing conflict among
the CROWDS throughout the nation—
Maybe we should set up
a CROWDS pushback game.
One has already been
set up by GALAX users.
The game is called Neo100 Hunter.
Thanks to the participants,
violence by the Neo Hundred
CROWDS is dying down.
Maybe I'll play it, too.
He's amazing.
Who is it?!
He's special.
Hey, don't be reckless. Stop!
No way!
My ranking's on the line!
Ranking?!
1, 2, 3!
Yeah!
Oh my goodness!
Grandma, you rock!
Ah, that felt great.
X, how many more Neo
Hundred CROWDS are there?
There are 23 remaining.
ZAKUZAKU Rubble Collection
Ooh, I'm now at number 40 for
the Shinjuku area in this game!
Yeah!
Nice!
I get this piece, then!
Hey, if you're just
here to gawk, go home!
Scram!
Paiman-san, you've been a ton of help.
Because of the CROWDS,
this area's been cleaned up, too.
Got the gramps and the kid!
Tachikawa Detective Millennium Rankings
Hey! What do you think you're doing?!
I'll sic the Gatchaman on you!
Dad!
Kousuke!
I've been looking for them.
Thank you!
Bye!
Yay!
A grandfather and his grandson!
Should be major points for that!
This is fun.
Please, Mayor.
You have to be kidding!
She's right!
We're trying our best here.
What's up with them?!
Why not?
It's nice to see some smiles around here,
no matter what the reason.
I was worried about you.
We should focus on doing things
only we can do as public servants.
Let them have fun helping us!
Tachikawa CROWDS Game
X, this has become something amazing.
Rui, it is all due to your courageous decision.
No, it's gone far beyond my imagination.
Everyone's off doing their own thing.
How many people came to Tachikawa?
A total of one million two
hundred thousand users.
The number of participants
are increasing.
Wonderful!
I wish they'd participate in elections like that.
You never know.
You can get a pretty good idea
of what people are thinking.
Hajime-chan...
What happens next?
I have no idea!
Wouldn't most people say, "it'll be fine"?
Well, that's just like you, though.
Messy!
All right.
Time to get to work!
Hi, everyone. All the Neo Hundred
CROWDS have been dealt with!
The Tachikawa CROWDS game is now finished.
Thank you for all of your hard work!
You've cleared the game!
Uh, wow. Really?
Suga-yan,
you might just want
to leave the rest up to them.
Right, Rui-kun?
What's wrong, Rui-kun?
It's not really over yet, is it?
You're right.
It's not that easy.
Sorry about that.
I've taken due notice of your opinion.
The game will continue
for the time being!
It'll be okay.
We're all heroes. Every one of us!
What makes a hero?
What, what, what?
I relaxed too much!
Katze-san's here!
Huh?
Hrrr
There!
Will win!
Give housewives respect!
Wh-Wh-What?
What are you all doing?
Creepy!
You can do it,
Mom
Hey, the CROWDS are super dangerous!
Crush them now!
Huh?
Katze-san's here!
Super awesome technique!
Tachikawa Live Updates
Looks like the Neo Hundred has been neutralized.
Good riddance. They were clueless, getting ahead of themselves and making a huge mess.
Just luddites.
Neo Crowds should just all die.
Morons!
Y'all have poor taste!
Oh, Mom?
How are you?
Oh, I'm fine.
I just wanted to hear your voice.
Oh, I wanted to say one thing.
No matter what happens, I'm just me.
That's all.
Bye!
Okay!
Summer 2016
Tachikawa
Prime Minister,
the CROWDS crime rate
is increasing once more.
Some believe the CROWDS ability
should become licensed.
What do you have to say to that?
X, did you hear that?
Please summarize everyone's
opinion and put it on GALAX.
Understood, Suga-yan.
I am personally against licensing.
The CROWDS is valuable precisely
because it is available to everyone.
But, I am willing to hear people out first.
You see, I am not the sole
leader of this nation.
Okay, I'll be out for a bit!
Okay.
Take care, Hajime.
Take care.
Wow! It's a great day.
Can you see?
I can't, moron!
We'll go see the ocean tomorrow.
It'll be great!
You sicken me, damn bitch!
Let's swim and crack some watermelons!
No way!
You're pissing me off!
All right, let's take on the day!
Gatcha!
The End