Cou-sama, are you awake?
I am... but it's not time to get up!
Yeah.
Today's the last day of Union Fest.
The town will be quite
lively again, I'm sure.
Yeah, I bet it'll be quite a party.
I'm sad that the festivities are ending.
I wish the fun times would
just continue forever!
Me, too...
The three Heroes' return home is scheduled
for two days after the end of Union Fest.
The day on which we have to
part is already looming...
We're really grateful that
you're taking us, Rebecca.
Final Stage
Thank you!
Don't mention it.
So today, Nanami's going to
Biscotti with the Princess.
Sink's going to Pastillage with Couverte.
And I'm going to Galette.
It's kind of like a Hero trade.
Indeed.
We've prepared something pretty fun.
Nanami and Millihi have
given their consent, but...
Rebecca, won't you play along, too?
Now, broadcast live,
the Union Fest special!
Our guest at the studio
is the ruler of the Republic of Biscotti,
Princess Millihiore!
Hello.
Representing the Galette Lion Army,
we have the ladies from Genoise!
Yeah!
And right here, we have Biscotti's...
Hiya!
I'm Biscotti's hero, Takatsuki Nanami!
What?!
Um, this hero seems to be a
little different than usual...
Oh, really?
I am the hero!
Actually, we have a little project going
and Nanami-san is my Hero for today.
A "One Day Hero", so to speak.
Lady Leo!
Today's the final day of the Union Fest.
How do you feel about the event so far?
So far I have nothing to complain about.  It's been perfect.
Prince Gaul, a word about the Hero?
Why not use this opportunity
to talk to her directly?
Then come, my Hero!
Yes!
H-Hello.
I'm Galette's hero, Rebecca.
Today Rebecca is Galette's Hero.
Well, the Ex Machina is a replica.
But her cuteness is quite real!
Thank you.
Rebecca-sama is really cute.
Nanami-dono and Rebecca-dono
do look good in those outfits.
That means our Hero
is Pastillage's Hero for the day, right?
Indeed.
That means that he'll have
to wear the costume, right?
Indeed...
Magical Beam!
That's not good!
No, actually it's not bad.
Indeed.
It's borderline in many respects!
Sorry for the wait.
Huh? What's wrong?
Oh, that suits you quite well.
I'm glad... really glad...
If you think about it,
this was the only thing that makes sense.
You look good, Sink!
Huh? Thanks...
I guess the Heroes are all
going to go home soon.
Well, I heard they're
coming back very soon.
Earth, that brings back memories...
Couldn't I go with them
while they're over there?
Why do you want to go?
Isn't that obvious?
To check out the body types and
underwear of the girls over there.
I couldn't quite hear you.
What did you say?
Nothing.
I thought so.
That's that, so please enjoy
tonight's Final Stage!
Everybody, great work!
Yup.
Great work!
Huh? Noir?
Rico, Noir, and I are going out for a bit.
Should I bring you somewhere?
No, we're fine.
The Skyer can handle us three just fine.
All right. We'll be back before
Millihi-nee's live performance.
Be careful.
Skyer, go!
Bye bye!
Okay, should we go to the stage, too?
Yeah.
Agreed.
Biometric data confirmed for
the rightful heir to Pastillage
and the Heavenly Spear Crimaris is present.
Opening doors.
This is the legendary treasure vault
under Castle Eschenbach,
the pride of Pastillage that's both
an ancient place and a giant maze.
I have heard stories,
but this is the first time
I've ever been inside!
You both mentioned before that you
wanted to explore this place.
That was when we were quite young.
You remembered?!
It's my motto to never
forget or break promises,
but you'll have to be careful.
This vault is filled with
traps to catch intruders.
But those are only on lower floors.
The ones on the first
floor are all deactivated.
Oh, Cou-sama!
Don't scare me like that!
But you have some business
down here as well, right?
Yes. I wanted to fetch an item
that I wanted to give Rebecca
for the return ritual.
I've stored some mementos down here.
I see.
And Rico, Noir,
you both have experienced
the return ritual.
I wanted to ask you to tell
me a little about that.
Oh, there it is!
That jewel case.
Let's take this first and....
Cou-sama!
Skyer!
Bright Power Release!
Seven Tails!
Just in time...
Nicely done, Noir!
You saved us.
That trap was active.
Well, this place is quite old,
so it's bound to have some issues...
Where are we?
I guess about ten levels lower.
We only fell straight down.
If I use Skyer, it's easy to...
It closed.
That means...
We're trapped!
There's a map!
If we check that, I'm sure
we'll find the way out!
A trap...
You two, be careful where you step.
Sorry, I should've kept my mouth shut.
This maze is horrible.
We have to get out of here.
This chair is perfect.
This sound...
Could it be...
I knew it!
Rebecca, is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Really?
Yes.
I wonder why I have this
really bad feeling...
A side path! We need a side path!
There are no intersections in sight,
no matter how far we run!
It's catching up to us!
Are you all okay?
I'm alive...
Is that Becky?
Hey, Sink,
did Cou-sama and the
others get there already?
Not yet...
That's weird.
It shouldn't take that long...
What?
Under the castle?
Yes, she was going to the
treasure vault under the castle.
Treasure vault?
That's the maze I used when
I was still doing my Demon King thing.
It's a dark and intense final dungeon
that's filled with brutal traps.
What?!
Of course the traps are all deactivated.
But that place is really old, so...
Becky!
Yes!
Is this a dead end?
Let's take a breather, I'm a bit tired.
I agree.
Rico, Noir, I'm really sorry.
This happened because I invited you here.
Cou-sama, that's not true.
We're the ones who wanted
to come here, anyway.
But if I had been more careful,
if I had properly maintained this place...
Well, then I could have also
caught you two with my Seven
Tails before you fell.
And I should have noticed
the trap on the floor.
But...
We're fine.
We're below the castle,
so someone's bound to come save us soon.
Right!
Anyway, let's take a rest.
Oh that reminds me, Cou-sama.
What did you want to know
about the return ritual?
Oh, yes... Did you feel sad when
you had to say good bye to your Hero?
Or... did you maybe feel worried...
and stuff like that...
Of course I felt sad and lonely,
and I cried and cried.
The last return was
difficult on many levels.
I heard a bit about that.
But when I heard that we would meet again,
all my lonely feelings just flew away!
I'm also sad that Nanami
and Sink are leaving,
but we really can meet
again whenever we want.
Even knowing that, I'm still worried.
Rebecca lives in a far away world.
There are many fun things
in her home world,
a lot of people who are important to her...
I worry that she'll forget
about me after a while.
Cou-sama...
I know. Rebecca is a kind girl.
I know that won't happen.
But I still feel really sad about
having to part with her.
I don't have enough faith...
Just laugh at me for being
a feeble fledgling ruler.
We'd never laugh at you.
There's nobody in the world
who wouldn't feel sad
when they have to part
with someone they love.
Okay, Rico. The break's over.
Right!
We need to make sure that you
can spend as much time as possible
with Rebecca before she has to leave!
So we're getting out of here.
Rico... Noir...
Now...
That's not fair!
Just when I was being cool!
First, we have to esc-
We can't...
You two, up there!
I am going to do something about this.
I am not going to let my
best friends get hurt!
I've located the Crimaris.
The trap's been temporarily stopped,
but it won't last long.
Sink, Rebecca, please get them out!
Right!
Hey, take this!
What is this?
A Demon God Crystal.
Simply put, it's the Demon King's version
of the Hero Crystal.
I'm sure you'll be able to use it well.
I'll do my best!
Hero Teleport!
It's falling again!
If only I could open this door...
Sorry for the wait, guys!
Hero "Just in Time" Sink...
...and Hero Rebecca have arrived!
Sink... Rebecca...
Hang on, we're going to
push this thing back right now!
What the... this thing is really heavy.
I'll do it.
Sink, can I ask you to
hold it for just a moment?
Got it!
Demon God Crystal, activate!
Demon King Seal!
Witch Cannon! Ultra Demon King Mode!
Everybody, get down!
Go!
Thanks Sink.  I managed somehow.
Hero!
Sink!
Rebecca!
Cou-sama!
Rebecca... I'm so happy...
Jeez. I told you that you have
to always take me or the knights
when you go somewhere dangerous.
I'm so sorry.
But I'm really relieved that you're safe.
I am a knight...
Noir, shhh.
Now let's get out of here.
The Princess's performance is starting soon!
You're right!
We're on schedule for the show.
Five minutes!
Princess!
Everybody just now got to their seats!
That's great...
Oh, but are they all okay? Is anybody hurt?
All is well.
They're all laughing and smiling.
Then I'm relieved.
I'm going to my seat, as well.
Princess, good luck!
Thank you!
Princess!  Princess!
My dreams will come true, I'm sure of it.
My wishes are overflowing.
I will catch them now, in the light.
I want to show them, tell them
to you, these important feelings!
These feelings of love
tucked away in my heart...
Right now, a summer-colored
flower opens in the blue wind.
The chance for love is right here.
My heart waves when I think you may not love me too.
But it's okay, I'll just start walking
and move forward step by step.
My dreams will come true, I'm sure of it.
My wishes are overflowing.
If you can share smiles,
that's the beginning.
I'm sure your love will blossom.
I'm so excited that my heart
is pounding when we touch.
My heart sparkles in the light.
Listen to the season of love,
and don't forget to smile.
The costume for Pastillage's
One Day Hero...
Wait, this is Becky's!
Once again, I'm grateful to everybody.
This elasticity is quite something.