Chance ball.
All right.
Nice kill.
Dateko                         Karasuno
Tsukishima, one more. Nice serve!
If this give-and-take continues,
Nice receive.
#7's coming.
Right.
Karasuno could win the first set.
But to totally get ahead...
That's it!
Nice one-touch!
Counter!
Chance ball.
C quick!
Don't underestimate us!
That's the first time two blockers
went up against Hinata-kun's quick.
Karasuno                        Dateko
Amazing.
It's our set point against Dateko.
Haikyu!!
Episode 18: Guarding Your Back
Nice receive.
Karasuno's on a roll.
Give me a toss!
All right.
Karasuno                        Dateko
Wow. Karasuno won it, for real.
As expected, Karasuno's scary
when they get on a roll.
They might take the second set
if they keep it up.
Kunimi, you dolt!
Move your feet, or you can sit out!
But I doubt we'll see
a repeat of that first set.
Because Dateko's giant, #7, will no longer
be surprised by those quicks.
Bummer, Aone.
We'll take the next one. We will.
That tall #7 and lastly that #6
managed to touch Hinata-kun's quick.
Yeah. Amazing.
The cornerstone of our offense
is that freak quick.
We can't let them start
blocking it, like Nekoma did.
Tanaka               Kageyama            Tsukishima
Hinata                 Sawamura              Azumane
So, we're going to start the second set
with our second rotation.
The first rotation
directly matched up Hinata
and no-eyebrows #7,
so we'll shift that over
two places to start.
I see. That means Hinata-kun
won't get marked by #7
like he was in the first set.
But we can't completely avoid that.
All we're doing is shifting players around.
While Hinata won't get marked,
but other players will get marked instead.
We can't let Hinata
shoulder all of our burden.
When Hinata's at his best,
we're at our best.
I'll do my part as the ace.
Asahi-san, you're awesome!
You've grown, Asahi.
What are you, my relative?
Me too!
I can't back attack like you, Asahi-san.
So I'll score as many points
as I can while I'm up front.
I'll be the best decoy ever!
Yeah, I'm counting on you.
And you can count on me, too.
Yes.
Go! Go! Let's go! Let's go, Dateko!
Iron Wall of Date
The second set is about to start.
I don't envy you, Tsukishima.
You'll be facing #7 a lot more
than in the first set.
Nah. No one expects me
to beat their #7 head-on.
It's Hinata's job to steal the spotlight.
It's my job to keep trouble from happening
while Hinata's rotated into the rear guard.
It's the usual situation, isn't it?
Besides, that blocker has already
locked on to you, Azumane-san.
Tanaka, nice serve.
Nice receive.
Karasuno made a double rotation.
Left.
I wonder if they're trying to avoid
a match-up between their #10 and Aone?
It doesn't matter what the match-up is.
The spiker in front must be blocked.
That's all there is to it.
We're usually cocky problem children...
So at least during the tournament,
we should act like good underclassmen.
Kageyama.
All right.
He was lured in for a moment by Hinata's move,
but he's already on the left...
Dateko                        Karasuno
Nice, Tanaka.
Nice receive.
Open.
Here comes #3.
The long-haired guy had the
target area covered on that one.
Our shrimp is the only
player who can do a quick
when the receive goes awry.
Nice, Aone.
Okay, let's block the next one, too.
Nice, Sawamura.
Dateko                        Karasuno
All right.
Karasuno's #10 is vanguard now.
Bring it.
It's up, nice.
Kageyama, cover.
Bring it here.
He's so damned fast when he's in front.
Nice, Hinata, Kageyama.
What a monster.
All right.
Dateko                        Karasuno
Even after Karasuno
shifted their rotation,
their quicks are still surprising,
don't you think?
But as time goes on,
they'll begin to lose effectiveness.
If Dateko wins this set
and takes it to the third set,
Karasuno will find themselves
at a disadvantage.
Karasuno must find ways to battle Dateko's #7
while their #10 is in the rear guard.
The deciding factor will be
how they deal
with the iron wall
without #10 to act as decoy.
Hinata, nice serve.
I heard Karasuno's #10's quicks are amazing.
Nice receive.
Open.
Where?
Oh, he's rear guard right now.
Dateko                        Karasuno
Hey, Tsukishima.
You said it's your job to keep trouble
from happening while Hinata's
rotated into the rear guard.
You're doing that against Dateko.
I say that's quite awesome.
It's true that our offense relies on
Hinata and Kageyama,
but it's also essential
to augment their attacks.
Just as spikers can't score
without strong receivers to help,
playing our parts now
will let us win the match.
Sorry. Kageyama, cover.
All right.
The balls come to the ace
when the going gets rough.
Open.
Azumane-san.
Coming from the left.
So what if it's an iron wall...
I'll blast through it.
Iron Wall of Date
All right.
Dateko's blocking is awesome.
Asahi-san, one more.
Although he's only middle blocker,
it's like #10 is their real ace.
Don't worry, don't worry.
#7 is the best blocker in the iron wall.
Things will get rough for his team
if he doesn't rotate to the rear soon.
Let's do another one.
Will Karasuno's ace hold up?
Dateko                        Karasuno
Daichi-san, nice receive.
All right.
#3, #3!
I won't let them break me again.
One touch!
Counter!
Karasuno...
...has a wall, too!
All right.
Whoa! They blocked the quick.
After all, Karasuno's #3 and #11
are their two tallest players.
Nice block, Tsukishima.
Thanks.
All right! Block point!
Good. If Dateko scores,
their huge #7 rotates to the rear.
Next, next.
One more!
Okay.
Keep gaining on them!
Dateko                      Karasuno
Whoa, he's up. Karasuno's #10.
All right.
Only six more points to go.
Get 'em while you can, shrimpy.
#12, #12!
It's up. Kageyama, cover.
Yes.
Bring it.
He's awesome.
Usually they'd let the left handle
that one, but he used a quick instead.
Take that.
We're going to stall them.
Nice, Kamachi!
Iron Wall of Date
Dateko                        Karasuno
We just can't seem to pull ahead.
Persevere. Go at it carefully.
Nice, Asahi-san.
Chance ball.
Give me a toss!
Crap...
All right.
Nice keep.
One more!
One more to match point.
Go! One more point!
Nice receive.
Dateko's big guy is in the rear,
and shrimpy's still vanguard.
Nice receive, Noya-san.
Chance ball.
This is our chance to gain on them.
Kamasaki-san, you're
hiding in Aone's shadow.
Are you intimidated or something?
Huh?
Cut the crap. All of us are...
The iron wall!
All right.
Damn it.
We'll score the next one.
Sorry.
And now it's #7's turn as vanguard...
We're counting on you.
Don't worry.
The freak quick will still work.
But...
Nishinoya.
Nice receive.
Bring it.
All right.
That was too close for comfort!
It barely got sucked in.
At least it's match point now.
Dateko                        Karasuno
Go! One point!
All right.
You can block the next one. I know it!
We've only just begun.
It's Karasuno's match point,
but #10's in the rear guard now.
And Dateko's strongest
blockers are up front...
Nice serve.
S-Sorry!
Nice judge.
I'm sorry.
Lucky, lucky!
Don't mind. Don't worry about it.
Hinata, you lousy airhead!
You know what you did wrong,
so don't beat yourself up.
Don't, you idiot.
Yes.
Dateko                        Karasuno
It's deuce if Dateko scores two more points.
That's a very possible,
given their current rotation.
If it's deuce while #10's in the back,
Karasuno will be in trouble.
We'll get the next one. Don't worry.
Dateko's #7 is amazing.
Yeah. I thought he had me
blocked that last time.
But at least we have
Asahi-san playing vanguard.
Bring it, one point!
Asahi.
Azumane.
The ace is there. We'll be okay.
Tsukishima.
Nice receive.
Here comes a quick.
We're doing well, but they're wising up.
#7! #7!
Cover! Cover!
Azumane-san.
Yeah.
What kind of ace am I,
if I can't score this last point?
We've defeated this spiker once already.
We're no Iron Wall if we can't do it again!
Moniwa-san, nice block.
Crap, the rear is wide open.
He saved it.
Cover for me!
Spike it. Keep spiking as
long as tosses keep coming.
Left! One more!
Azumane-san.
That toss is too close to the net.
A joust.
Get 'em, long-haired guy.
It's too far...
So close!
Awesome.
He's incredible.
One more!
Nishinoya, nice follow!
Get back! Get back in position!
I need enough distance to get up to speed.
I must jump with all my might.
As many times as it takes!
Don't lose concentration.
Don't stop running.
If I lose momentum, the ball will drop.
Kageyama, cover.
Yes.
One more!
I won't stop 'til I score.
Asahi spikes best when
he's slightly away from the net...
...and has a high toss.
Kageyama-kun's tossing to him again?
It's fine.
Huh?
That was the best he could've done, Sensei.
Go, Asahi!
Blast through, Asahi!
Go!
Dateko                        Karasuno
All right!
We did it!
All right.
They did it! They did it!
Let's line up.
Thank you very much.
Karasuno
You did it, Asahi-san.
Asahi-san. You went,
"Boom!" past Dateko's blockers.
And they went like, "Argh!"
And I was like, "Ka-blam!"
Speak Japanese.
I'm the ace,
but you guys are heroes.
Heroes!
I like that.
You did great against
their freakish quicks.
Spring tournament!
That's right, Moniwa-san.
We'll get our revenge in the
spring tournament preliminaries.
The preliminaries are in September.
We'll go back and start
strategizing right away.
We'll beat Karasuno if we play
them in the spring preliminaries!
The third-years will be gone
by the spring tournament.
Why? Because they can't be bothered with us?
What are you talking about?
I've told you this over and over.
The third-years' season ends
after the Inter-High.
But...
You guys are strong.
Iron Wall of Date
They say we're a powerhouse,
but they've also said our
third-years are duds.
They said we're a bad crop.
We were able to maintain our reputation
as the Iron Wall because of you guys.
That's why, by the time
you guys are third-years,
you have to make it
to the spring tournament.
You'll have a new team and a new strategy.
We lost in the preliminaries
this year, but next year...
Aoba Johsai, Shiratorizawa, and Karasuno...
You'll conquer them all,
and go on to nationals!
But...
Understood?
Yeah.
We can't hear you, Futakuchi.
Sawamura! Sugawara! Azumane!
Congrats on winning your second match.
Michimiya! I knew I heard
the girls' voices behind us.
You didn't notice them?
Aya-senpai.
You got your revenge.
Yeah.
And we're gonna keep on winning.
Um, Ukai-kun.
That last toss.
What did you mean when you said
it was "the best he could've done"?
When a receive goes awry and
we can't make an offensive play,
the last ball always goes left,
to the ace's position.
I wanted him to know what it feels like
to be the last resort
Thank you very much.
and to wrestle a point away from that wall.
I see.
That'll boost his confidence
for our next match.
From what I've heard, Azumane
got beaten pretty badly by them before.
But I'm sure he's fine now.
He fought tenaciously against them,
even without our decoy.
It's also a matter of pride when
the ball gets tossed to the spiker.
Because it means he's earned
the setter's trust.
He's had two setters put their trust in him.
That's got to give him confidence.
I must admit,
Dateko's blocking was downright scary.
Right?
I wonder how they decided when
it was appropriate to use
the first-year duo's crazy quicks.
Come to think of it, they didn't
use any signals during the rally.
They didn't notice our signals, huh?
Yeah. They should be effective for a while.
Your brains are made of muscle,
so I'm amazed you thought them up.
It wasn't us that thought them up.
Oh, no wonder. Who did the thinking for you?
Sugawara-san.
We did it. We got our revenge.
Yeah.
But then again...
I do wish my tosses could've
played a part in the victory.
Sorry about that.
Please don't repeat that.
I'm glad.
I'm glad you still want to fight.
Tomorrow's another match. We'll win again.
Yeah.
Oikawa-san.
Omisaki
Aoba Johsai
It's Aoba Johsai's...
...first match.
Who will devour
the king and the dark horse?
Aoba Johsai
Who will devour them all
and go to the nationals?
We will.
Next Episode Preview
That guy think's he's hot stuff because
girls throw themselves at him.
Yeah, but we have Kiyoko-san.
Oikawa-san!
What? Kiyoko-san?
Just kidding.
Really?
Please don't do that to us.
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"Coaches."
Episode 19: Coaches