Episode 10   Umaru and Now and Once Upon a Time
I keep telling her she needs to sleep in her bed,
but she fell asleep playing a game again.
You've got a cold.
My head hurts, Onii-chan.
Stay home from school today.
I actually don't feel that bad.
I'll just have Onii-chan dote on me
for a while, and laze around.
Aah
Well, I'm heading to the office.
Huh? Why?! You're not taking the day off?
Onii-chan, you're actually going to leave
your sick sister home alone, and go to work?
No one stays home from work because
their little sister has a cold.
Not to mention, this time,
you got what you deserved.
This happened because you fell asleep
playing a game and left the AC on.
I'll be home early, so stay in bed
and think about what you've done.
I'll let Ebina-chan know.
Hmph!
I hate you, Onii-chan!
I'll just make myself sicker,
and make you worry more.
The Next Day
Umaru is back!
Of course, my virus is totally lazy.
What do you guys wanna do?
So tired.
Let's not bother this time.
Yeah.
They died in a day! Viva health!
The morning after you get
over a cold feels so good!
I'll do some radio calisthenics
that I vaguely remember!
Oh, Onii-chan, good mor—
My head hurts.
Wh-What the...
It's a cold! You totally caught a cold, Onii-chan!
Ow...
Stop yelling! The sound is rattling my brain.
Yep. Fever.
Umaruun
Oh, hello. Thank you for everything you do.
This is Doma Taihei's sister.
Yes. You see, my brother has a fever.
Yes, I'm terribly sorry...
Are you calling my office?!
Well, you have a cold, so you need to rest.
You're going to start weird rumors again.
I'll talk to them myself. Give me the phone!
"Again"?
Lucky for you, I have today off,
since it's my school's anniversary.
Don't worry. I'll take good care of you.
Well, I'm gonna go shopping.
H-Hey...
Make sure you stay in bed, Onii-chan.
What is she plotting?
Don't worry, Onii-chan.
I'll take very good care of you.
And I'll do that using...
the Sparta method, of course!
You will pay deeply for leaving
me home with a cold alone.
I hear it's good to sweat
when you have a cold,
so first, I'll give Onii-chan a spicy
soup filled with plenty of Tabasco.
Green onions!
I've heard that green onions work
well when stabbed up the butt.
I'll do that for Onii-chan, too.
Just you wait, Onii-chan!
O-O...
Onii-chan!
O-Oh, no! What is this?!
This totally isn't funny!
It's the Umaru Virus.
Because I gave it to him...
Onii-chan is... Onii-chan is...
Get a fever, get a fever,
get a fever, fever, fever.
Suffer and writhe, Onii-chan, one, two!
I must defeat them.
Get a fever, get a fever,
get a fever, fever, fever.
Shiver and get dizzy, Onii-chan.
Hi-yah!
I'm going to protect Onii-chan!
Stop, damn it!
L-Let's all defeat her together!
Onii-chan!
A green onion?
Why?! You're not taking the day off?
Umaru.
Thanks for taking care of me.
You reek of green onions, Onii-chan.
But it seems like this took care of the cold.
Green Pepper Stir-fry
Potato Salad
Stewed Seaweed
Mackerel Roasted with Salt
Let's eat.
Wait, what's with this dinner?
That's pretty rude, after I made this for you.
But I wanted Hamburg steak.
You shouldn't expect to get what
you want to eat every time.
Come on. Let's eat.
Hey, Umaru.
Why haven't you touched your green peppers?
Because they're bitter!
You don't eat vegetables,
so I chop them up finely,
change the seasoning...
I put a lot of work into making it for you.
Well, that seems like a lot of trouble,
so you don't have to make it anymore.
You idiot!
At least eat your green peppers.
I don't care if you make those dramatic
reactions, as long as you eat them.
Umaru, wake up.
Good morning, Onii-chan.
Here's your lunch.
Onii-chan, you didn't put green
peppers in my lunch, did you?
Nope...
Stop sniffing it, and go!
You always bring a lunch, Ebina-chan.
Y-Yes.
I finished my lunch first!
It's so hard to make them in the morning...
Oh, but I guess it's the
same for you, Umaru-chan.
Oh, well, in my case, Onii-chan...
Don't be a picky eater.
Onii-chan's such a picky eater,
it's difficult to make his lunches.
Wow. You make your brother's lunches, too?
It's not a big deal.
No, it's amazing.
It's hard enough for me just to make my own.
Making two really isn't that much
more work than making one.
Really?
Y-Yeah...
Lunch break's almost over, so let's hurry and eat.
Okay.
Hamburg steak!
There are green peppers in it!
Ah, Hamburg steak with green peppers.
Huh? Y-Yeah. Onii-chan hates green peppers.
Huh? He does?
But you're amazing, Umaru-chan.
Hamburg steak with green peppers is
a lot of work to do in the morning.
You don't eat vegetables,
so I chop them up finely,
change the seasoning...
I put a lot of work into making it for you.
I'm sure Onii-san is very happy
that you add them in a
way that he can eat them.
Yeah.
I'm home.
So tired.
Umaru Dive!
Hey! You really need to stop that!
What're you going to do if my glasses break?
There were green peppers in my lunch today.
I guess even Hamburg steak didn't work.
It was a lot of work to make that.
I know.
Huh?
So from now on, just green
pepper stir-fry is fine.
Umaru?
Are you all right?
Did you eat something weird?
Umaru Dive!
I said stop that!
[Crazy Dance] Nassuu's Weird Dance Moves [Tried Dancing It]
Nassuu's always so funny.
I never get tired of his face or his moves.
But the Internet is really amazing,
since it lets me watch
all this amusing stuff for free.
I'm connected to the world right now!
It's going to spill!
Make it in time!
Umaruun
Such a waste.
It got under the desk, too.
What's this contraption?
What's it doing under the desk?
It's got a lot of glowing lights...
Unable to connect to the Internet
Details
O-Oh, no! That contraption was
for connecting to the Internet!
Wh-Wh-What am I going to do?!
I can't use the Internet!
Oh, I know. I'll look it up on Yapoo Answers!
Unable to connect to the Internet
Details
I can't connect to the Internet,
so I can't look it up!
I know. I'll use my tablet...
MogPad is not
connected to
the Internet.
This is a Wi-Fi model...
The Internet...
Without the Internet,
I can't connect to the world.
I never thought something
this awful would happen.
I'll just play a game to calm my nerves.
Unable to connect to the Internet
Details
I've been isolated from the world!
Unable to connect to the Internet
I'm home.
I came to visit!
Oh, so you broke it.
Since it got wet, it's too
dangerous to turn on the power,
so it'll have to be fixed.
Tanukichi.
Nassuu!
Taihei... Your turn.
What's so funny?
Where'd you get this?
I got it playing pachinko.
You've got such a nice face,
and that totally kills it!
Sequence revolution with a joker!
What? Seriously?!
Wait. What happens with a
joker revolution, Tanukichi?
Threes are the strongest!
We don't have a rule like that where I'm from!
By the way, is "Tanukichi" supposed to be me?
Yeah. That hood is a tanuki, right?
It's a hamster.
Nassuu!
Manga Café
Counter
Please help us
achieve 0
drink waste
CONBU
My first time at a manga café!
Since our Internet is out, I threw a
tantrum, and Onii-chan gave me money.
Then go to a manga café or something.
Price Guide
Basic Charges
Entrance Fee: 300 yen
First 30 Minutes: 200 yen
Additional 10 Minute Increments: 80 yen
3 Hour Pack: 680 yen
5 Hour Pack: 1000 yen
7 Hour Pack: 1400 yen
Long Night Pack: 1580 yen
How long would you like to stay?
Three? No...
What should I do?
I ended up renting this space for seven hours.
It's so tiny.
I guess it's not just this one.
All of the rooms are small.
But because it's so tiny...
It feels like I've got my own secret base!
And I can use the Internet all I want!
I can read all the manga I want!
I can drink all the drinks I want!
It's not every day you find
such a comfortable base.
They even have ice cream!
I'm going to conquer at least three
long-running manga titles today.
And since it's a private room,
I can look like this, even
though I'm out of the house!
This always relaxes me the most.
I wonder what this is.
Off  On
Body  Fingers
Neck|Shoulders  Clapping
Back  Rolling
Speed  High|Low  Knead
10 Min  30 Min  60 Min
Repeat  Random  Special
I-Is this...
Wh-What in the world?!
Massages! Who knew they'd
have a massage chair, too?!
This isn't a base! This is better than my house!
I could live here. I could do it.
I could totally live here.
Remaining Time
I still have six hours left, so I need to
have even more fun than I usually do.
Remaining Time
Miss, you still have more than
four hours remaining.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I'm home! Onii-chan!
10 Years Ago
Doma, you got a 100.
Come on. Doma got another 100?
He's just like a computer.
His head's as pointy as ever, though.
You got a 100 again? That's amazing!
Shut up, Bomber.
What? There's some trick or
something, right, Taihei?
You knew the test questions
early, or something.
No... The math was actually
really easy this time.
But I got a 15.
I studied, and all I got was a 15!
Which means a score of 15
is apparently your limit.
H-How dare you say that, woman?!
More importantly, Taihei.
Since the test is over,
why don't we go out somewhere?
Huh? Well... I'm not sure.
Oh! Then let's go to the arcade
that opened up by the station.
I'll show you my awesome
crane game techniques.
You need to go home and study
so you can shoot for a 20.
What? I could get a 30 if I tried!
Taihei, let's leave this idiot and go.
No way! Our friendship is real, isn't it?!
Let's all go, then.
I've never been to an arcade before.
What a noisy place.
This is the prize?
What a shallow attempt to get people to play.
A cat! What a cute plushie!
Let's get it.
For plushies like this, you aim for the neck.
Make your winning pose after you win something.
Head is Heavy
Dolls have a heavy head, which puts
their center of balance higher.
In other words, if you go for the neck,
it'll be stable, and you can lift it up.
What the hell's with this crane?!
The arm is super weak!
*Please Do Not Hit the Machine
You're a total failure.
I figured it out.
You don't lift things up in this. You push them.
After watching Bomber play just now,
I saw that there was no
limit to the arm's descent.
Which means you use the arm to push
a plushie that's near the hole down.
What's with this thing?!
I pushed it, but it didn't move at all!
*Please Do Not Shake the Machine
Pathetic!
What did you say?!
What the hell was that for,
you violent woman?!
Shut up, you shitty afro!
What did you say?
But I look so awesome!
Do you know what decade
this is, you idiot?!
That's a hairstyle from half a century ago!
No way...
Why can't you see the
awesomeness of this hair?!
Like I'd want to know!
People lack originality!
In a time where people lack originality,
my hair shines gloriously...
Now that I look, the plushies'
legs are tangled together.
What?! No wonder it didn't move!
What's up?
Yeah, there's no way we could get these.
What if we aimed for the tag on this plushie?
Huh? No way.
You'd be wasting a hundred yen, Taihei.
No way!
There are three, so let's
divide them between us.
Taihei!
I love you.
I'm home, Umaru.
Welcome home, Onii-chan.
Have you been a good girl?
Yep. Hey, what's that?
Oh, I got something cool for you, Umaru.
Cool?
Here.
A kitty cat!
Thank you, Onii-chan.
10 Years Later
Welcome home, Onii-chan!
I got even more plushies at the arcade!
That's way too many!
Next Time
Episode 11         Umaru's Day
Hello.
People mistakenly call me "Kanou," but I'm Kanau.
Someone I haven't met in the
anime came to the preview again.
Don't you worry.
I'm not even sure when we'll meet
in the original story, either.
This is awkward in so many ways...