High School National Ogura Hundred Poets Karuta Championship
We will begin now.
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
Here comes spring, now
the flower blooms
This is our grand finale!
As this trip takes me away in haste,
I have only autumn leaves as an offering
for the gods watching over me
While
I sigh and lament how the one
I love does not feel the same,
Wh-What is this?
She's different.
Completely different.
Her reflexes...
Her sense...
Rion, the reader is your grandmother,
Yamashiro Kyoko, grade 7.
You should be able to play well.
By the time the other players
have also taken five cards,
Mizusawa
will realize their imminent defeat.
Chihaya Furu
Gust
of
wind
Episode 17
Today is a day for teams.
Why, Arata?
This match looks boring.
only tears can bring relief
in this cruel life
The sound of people pitying...
H-His stance is so low!
His spider-like form is solid as a rock.
This guy acts sort of feminine,
but he plays like a man!
He's strong!
I'm not in love with Rion!
Not Rion!
H-He's weird!
Weird!
Secret Technique: Thunder Fall!
Very weird!
descends from Mount Yoshino
upon my long-forgotten home
Though I prayed to the god of mercy
that the one I love not shun me,
He covered on a two-syllable card?
It's possible to move
and stop so quickly?
They're physically strong.
Especially their upper bodies...
Coach Sakurazawa.
I've been playing competitive
karuta since I was six,
and the harder I played, the harder
it was for my knees and back.
So my goal is for all of you
to be able to play karuta
for a very long time
without injuring yourself.
For that, the first thing you need is stamina.
Before and after practice, you
must stretch for thirty minutes.
Throw in thirty minutes of running
and three reps of weight training.
Groan
Whenever you play full matches as part
of practice, include the full regimen.
Whenever Coach Sakurazawa
said that word,
Stamina.
I was motivated to endure
whatever she put us through.
There's nothing erotic about that word!
Damn you, Eromu!
With 50 club members, Fujisaki
is famous for always winning.
The karuta club made it
to the nationals again.
That's amazing.
There are no students in our school
who would belittle karuta.
First-years will work
on their memorization.
Second-years will work
on card placement.
Third-years will work on sending cards.
Take it one step at a time.
Coach Sakurazawa has been
karuta advisor for 12 years,
and the legacy she has built...
is the pride of the Fujisaki karuta club.
Are our opponents really that good?
We're already losing...
Oe-senpa—
Chihaya-chan...
I never asked to be treated colder
than the winds of Mount Hatsuse
I wish I could show the
people how my sleeves
Stupid.
Coach Sakurazawa, why did you send
Rion out in the final match?
There are plenty of third-year
players who worked
far harder than she did.
We don't need her hearing
and talent to win.
We can defend Fujisaki's
legacy without her.
Wh-Why?
Why did she move after hearing "I"?
I've lost a bunch of two-syllable
cards on the first syllable.
Twenty-eight one-syllable cards.
Is she a Suo-san type?
But she's reacting too fast.
What can she hear?
What is it?
Rion's matched against the Mizusawa
player with good game sense.
That's why she's going all out.
She wants to put this game away early.
Can you keep it up, Rion?
I'm so bored...
But...
have been soaked red
with tears of blood
The reader is Yamashiro, grade 7.
Since the dew atop the blades of grass
has been scattered by the winds,
Dead card.
it is as though pearls have been
strung across the autumn plain
While autumn leaves crunch
under deer footsteps,
Dead card.
the stag cries longingly for the doe
My favorite reader, Yamashiro-san,
has a multicolor voice.
Her voice, its resonance...
Multicolor...
The "Impassionate" card looks
bright red to you.
I also have cards
whose images are so strong in
my mind, they appear in color.
But...
Can a reading also have color?
Can she hear colors?
There's too much information
communicated when Yamashiro-san reads.
I can beat Suo-san in most situations,
but if Yamashiro-san is the
reader, he can be a pain.
This girl could also be a pain.
She's in Class B?
Why?
Rion...
When she came to my karuta society
to practice as a little girl,
even setting aside my bias
toward her as family,
I had great hopes for her as
she was clearly a genius.
But...
Why do you stop trying
during a match, Rion?
The same thing happened
at the last tournament.
You have to keep trying
until the match is over.
The reading
wasn't pretty.
It was difficult to understand.
I like your reading better.
If there is such a thing as
perfect pitch in karuta,
that's what Rion seeks.
In tournaments, there are many
readers with unique styles.
If you lose a single match,
you can't win the tournament.
Rion has never won a tournament.
She cannot become the Queen.
So you should be grateful, Rion.
Victory for Fujisaki
Your team has given you
a chance to be a winning player.
Damn!
He's good!
He's weird!
I-I'm already down six cards.
Stay calm.
I can't let her get any further ahead.
As the game progresses,
when there are more one-syllable
cards on the field,
then I can...
Chihaya-chan.
Listen to the poems.
Listen
to the poetry being read.
The rain has stopped.
The sun has set.
I smell sweat.
I smell tatami.
I smell the cards.
I hear the air conditioner.
as short-lived as the reeds of Naniwa Bay
Summer.
to set the Tatsuta River ablaze
Storm.
but instead you see a pale moon in the dawn sky
Sound.
Echo.
though autumn is not mine alone
Loneliness.
for there is no one else out here
Cherry blossoms.
Takasogo pines can never replace them
Friend.
as my concern this morning is as tangled as my black hair
Black.
burning brightly by night, yet extinguished by day
Torch.
as short-lived as the reeds of Naniwa Bay
The desire to be together...
May the
time spent...
"May the scarlet," "May the time we,"
and "May it" are all in play,
yet she covered on the
first syllable and
took the card on the second syllable?
Is her game sense just as good?
Kana-chan...
"May the time we" is a dull green,
like that of withered grass in winter.
"May the time spent" is more of a young
green, like that of budding reeds.
I don't have many cards with a
color to connect to their sound.
This is a risky way to play,
so I can't depend on it.
But...
This is how I can build
momentum, Dr. Harada.
bring a life of everlasting love
My only thought as
I don't think so!
I am put out to sea is
to ask the fishermen
Chihaya?!
Chihaya?
No way!
Is she hurt?
Chihaya, too?!
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
That scared me.
I'm fine.
That's good.
Excuse me.
Multi-syllable cards require
experience and technique.
Rion relies on her hearing,
so her motion is sloppy.
She panicked.
I really wanted "My only thought as I."
Especially after I got
"May the time spent."
I'll have to change the momentum again.
One card...
One card at a time.
One card.
May the scarlet kadsuras...
Crap!
A fault.
I was remembering the
placement from my last match.
Damn!
Be careful.
Emuro Ryoga doesn't commit faults.
Damn...
He looks so relaxed after
playing five matches.
Doesn't he get tired?
He doesn't make any mistakes?
That's because I'm in
Class A, unlike you.
I think I can hear my inner voice
This is bad.
Nobody can find their rhythm.
A mountain stream dips
Not even Chihaya!
I should have gotten that one.
What was I doing? It was sitting at the
opponent's lower right, ripe for picking.
What's wrong?
Why does it hurt like this?
Didn't I just jam it?
What is this?
What's wrong?
Ayase...
Okay, we can still do this!
We should consider ourselves lucky!
It wasn't our ace who got hurt.
Luck is on our side.
I can't stop!
I can't break the luck that
started with Kana-chan!
Fujisaki is leading every game.
They're on a completely different level.
It looks like they'll dominate this match.
Excuse me.
I should probably leave.
Ugh...
Wakamiya-san, you came to watch?
You shouldn't stand back here.
Please come to the front.
What?
No, it's really not necessary.
Everyone will play harder
if the Queen is watching.
Huh?
They keep saying the same thing...
Your presence will encourage
some of the players.
Everyone will play harder
if the Queen is watching.
It's the Queen.
That's absurd.
She looks familiar?
As the first frost...
Must be my imagination.
Nobody
in this room is interested in playing me.
The sight of the lonely
moon in the early morning
Her reactions were quicker before...
Was she injured?
When I hit her?
reminds me of the lonely
dawns after we parted
As I wait...
Good, I was able to defend it.
When winds send waves...
"As I" and "When winds send" are easy cards
for players with good game sense.
Injuries are very bad.
Avoid them at all cost.
However, they can also
provide an opportunity.
Injury affects the one who caused
it more than the one injured.
What am I doing?
Listen carefully.
I have to win.
That's why I'm here.
Yamashiro-san, you only try
when we're playing off a CD.
It's obvious that you don't like it
when the older players read.
You're so stuck-up, it gets us in trouble, too.
Such a pain.
I don't fit in anywhere...
except here.
I have to win here!
I'm sending a card.
are joined at river's end
She sent the only one-syllable
card in the match.
It's risky to hope to attack it.
Is she giving it up?
My right index finger is
the one that's hurting.
However, I've been practicing to hit the
green edge of the card with
my right middle finger.
I recall how my own
efforts were in vain
When the misty bridge...
The storm will soon carry me...
Ow!
Focus!
Focus harder!
Become a player who has
nothing but her right middle
finger and her ears!
so I wish for a memory
of you to take with me
...waters parted
That was fast!
I didn't think anyone besides
the Queen could be that fast!
I remember now!
She's the one who took a one-syllable
card from my lower left.
If I remember right,
it's Chihaya!
Yama...
Yamashiro...
Can't
remember
her first name
Yama-chan.
Gave up
This injury means nothing.
We're playing to the sound
of a certified reader.
We're competing to grasp
every little sound.
If you don't focus, you'll fall behind.
Stupid.
The bob cut girl is a fool.
It was a mistake to place the
one-syllable card that was
sent at her lower right.
That makes it easier to target.
You're supposed to move it
over a little to be safe.
I wouldn't be that stupid.
If I were playing...
You're too far forward.
Ayase is on a roll!
Four cards in a row!  Awesome!
She's still down 6 cards,
but look at her face.
That face...
Ayase, you can't hide it from me.
I'm right next to you.
Two girls have gotten injured
playing their hearts out.
I keep losing when it counts,
and I'm behind Mr. Excavator right now.
When am I going to come through?!
It has to be now!
Excuse me.
The passion...
The passion always
comes from Chihaya,
but this feels different.
I can feel something burning
in my chest like magma.
I know what this is.
This is how it feels
when five people refuse to give up!