48 Days Until the Prefectural Tournament!
Gou-chan, you're still doing those?
Can you stop that?
49 Days Until the Prefectural Tournament!
50 Days Until the Prefectural Tournament!
Pressure is what pushes
people to the next level.
50 Days Until the Prefectural Tournament!
52 Days Until the Prefectural Tournament!
51 Days Until the Prefectural Tournament!
Pressure can also ruin some people.
Are you talking about Rei-chan?
I'm not that weak!
Wait, why are you wearing a hakama?
Stop talking and start practicing!
Get going!
Honestly...
Man!
This is such a pain.
What's this?
This is...
Look at this!
Trial in Open Water!
Our new tracksuits arrived!
The jackets are nice,
Iwatobi Swim Club
but what is that thing on the T-shirt?
That's the secret Iwatobi-chan version.
Since you were against putting
Iwatobi-chan on our tracksuits.
What, so there's a secret version?
Well, let's get started.
Before we begin practice,
let's review the events we'll
be entering at prefecturals.
I'll be swimming the 100 m
and 200 m backstroke.
What are you doing, Nagisa?
I'm swimming breast.
I'm thinking both the 100 and 200.
And Haru?
I only swim free.
Shouldn't have bothered to ask.
Rei?
I can only swim butterfly.
That's right!
Anyway, it's been a while
since we've competed,
so stamina will be an issue.
I recommend sticking to short distances.
So we have our lineup for individual events.
That leaves the relay.
I guess we can wait to make that decision.
Keep that in mind while we're practicing—
You won't believe this!
I found something amazing!
Iwatobi High School Swim Club
Summer Training Camp from Hell
on a Deserted Island
Iwatobi High School Swim Club
Summer Training Camp from
Hell on a Deserted Island...
Hell?
Deserted island?
Sounds fun!
This took place several decades ago,
when Iwatobi still had a swim club!
So what's your point?
We should steal their training regimen and hold
a summer training camp on a deserted island!
To prepare for prefecturals!
Too much effort.
This is no time for complaining!
Look at the training regimen they used!
They swam long distances in the ocean.
From one deserted island to the next.
Don't you think this training is
perfect for building stamina?
The ocean...
Yep, the ocean!
We should participate in the same
training regimen that our
storied swim club used!
Our swim club was storied?
Yep, look what I found.
Sixth place in the Iwatobi Junior Tournament.
Weak.
Anyway!
Right now, the Iwatobi
Swim Club needs stamina!
And summer is the perfect time
to hold a training camp!
In the ocean! On deserted islands!
Wait, I don't see how deserted
islands are relevant here.
But it's more exciting when
you add deserted islands.
I know, right?
So let's hold a training camp!
Your decision, Captain?
Huh?
Oh...
I guess it's a good idea
to hold a training camp to
prepare for prefecturals.
Hurray! It's settled, then!
Yippee!
Faculty Office
The club doesn't have the money for that.
Then we could ask our
generous advisor to pay for it!
I'm not that generous!
Besides, people only get that
lucky in TV shows and manga.
The Irish playwright, George
Bernard Shaw, said it best.
"The book that has had
the most influence on my life
is my checkbook."
But I really want to go to a
deserted island with everyone.
If the school won't pay for it, we
can try to pay for it ourselves.
I can't afford it.
We had to pay for the tracksuits ourselves,
and I bought a non-speedo swimsuit.
I also bought a swimsuit.
Same here.
Rei-kun needed a swimsuit,
but the rest of you didn't need to buy one.
Especially not Haruka-senpai.
All of your swimsuits look the same.
They fit differently.
We could all find part-time jobs.
It's too late for that.
Unfortunately, it looks like this plan's a bust.
Wait.
I'll think of something.
There should be a way to hold
a camp without needing money.
Mako-chan's getting serious!
We can count on our captain!
Whatcha doing, big brother?
Are you going camping? I wanna come!
I've got a training camp with
Haru and everyone else.
Maybe some other time.
What? That's no fair!
His idea is to literally camp outside?
And what do we do about
the boat fare to the island?
Are we going to hitchhike?
There aren't any cars
or trucks in the ocean.
What's this?
A grave for a goldfish.
It was Makoto's pet.
Oh, yeah. He had a pet
goldfish in grade school.
So this is still here.
This is some serious equipment.
Our family always goes
camping during the summer.
Who gave you permission to
use my place for storage?
But there's so much room here.
Are these all deserted islands?
We could camp on a deserted island!
That's a bad idea.
Let's have a barbeque
on a deserted island!
Barbeque!
Can you drop the deserted
island business?
Now we just need money
for transportation.
Do you think Ama-chan has a boat?
I seriously doubt it.
I know someone with one!
Yes, I have the squid fishing
boat left by my grandpa.
And I have a boating license.
However...
You buy me one pizza and expect
me to do you a favor like that?
Please help us out!
We'll also give you this!
I don't want that!
Oh, fine.
I can't participate in your camp,
but I can take you there and back.
Really?!
Yeah.
Yay!
I could use a little cruise.
A cruise in a squid fishing boat?
Thank you so much!
Sure.
You can have this!
I told you, I don't want that!
Iwatobi Station
Bye!
See you tomorrow!
Yeah!
Let's go.
Yeah.
Looks like this camp
is going to work out.
We just need permission
from Miss Ama-chan now.
Yeah.
A training camp with everyone, huh?
I'm looking forward to this.
Oh. Rei's a beginner, so we
need to watch out for him.
Is he going to be able to handle this?
I'm not much of a long
distance swimmer myself.
What's wrong?
Are you really okay with this?
The ocean.
I'll be fine.
It was a long time ago.
Have fun.
Buy souvenirs.
Be good now.
Morning, Haru.
Haru-chan! Mako-chan!
Over here!
Good morning!
Good morning.
Morning.
Is everyone here?
We're still missing Miss Amakata.
Huh?
Sorry to keep you all waiting.
You must be Sasabe-san.
Thank you for your help.
Please take this.
It's just a token, but...
Oh, thank you.
Is something wrong?
Oh, uh...
Have we met before?
No, we haven't!
This is the first time I've met you.
Is he trying to hit on her?
Okay, let's set sail!
Big Catch
Sasa
I'll fly our flag with a prayer for
your training camp's success!
Off we go to the deserted island!
Full steam ahead!
We're not going to a deserted island!
Now, now. Don't be so picky!
I'm not being picky!
This place is gorgeous!
I'm so glad I came!
Absolutely!
Are you okay, Rei?
I'm okay...
I need to go to the restroom.
And here's a gift from me.
Good luck!
I'll be back for you on your last day!
Thank you very much!
Is Rei-chan okay?
It seems there's a sports facility over there.
It has a 50 meter pool.
We could swim there...
We don't have the money to go there.
I'll go look for a good camping site.
Okay.
So what was his gift?
Pizza?
And this is...
Mackerel.
You like mackerel way too much.
Hey!
Come over here!
Inoue!
Yamanaka!
You're falling behind!
Why is Samezuka's swim team here?
Pick up the pace!
Oh, Rin-chan's here.
Did you do something again, Gou-chan?
Huh? I didn't know anything this time.
Really?
I mean, it's obvious that my brother
won't listen to anything I say.
Plus...
Plus?
No, it's nothing.
So it's just a coincidence.
We should go say hello then.
Don't.
Huh? Why not?
I promised him
that we would meet at prefecturals.
What? Really?
When did that happen?
What is it, Senpai?
Oh, I thought I smelled something.
Smelled something?
Smelled like mackerel.
Oh, Matsuoka! You've got a sharp nose!
We're having mackerel curry for lunch!
Now practice hard!
Yes!
I wanna swim in a 50 meter pool.
I guess powerhouse schools
do get special treatment.
They're clearly in a different class.
Doesn't matter.
Haru's right.
Our goal for this training
camp is to build stamina.
Right! We still have our deserted islands!
Are you comparing 50 meter
pools to deserted islands?
Aren't they similar?
How are they similar?!
Okay, then.
Let's go check in at the lodge.
Yes.
Lodge?
What do you mean?
We booked lodging for ourselves.
Over there!
What?!
You can't expect a couple
of girls to sleep outside.
Right, Gou-chan?
Right?
Class difference again...
We're the bottom 1%?
This is a lovely place.
They offer rock bathing nearby.
And this says they offer a seasonal
facial treatment in summer.
Samezuka Academy
If we go now, we can get free
coupons for extra hyaluronan!
If you look at the map, you'll see that
there are a number of
smaller islands in the area.
Deserted islands!
What is it with you
and deserted islands?
We'll be swimming between
Sukishima, Oshima, and
Mizushima for our training.
The distance between each island
is about one kilometer.
Mizushima
Oshima
Sukishima
We're looking at 4 kilometers of swimming
and 1 kilometer of running each circuit.
Our goal is to complete three
circuits on the first day.
That sounds hard.
Can you handle that, Rei-chan?
Rei's a beginner, so we have
a different regimen for him.
No, I'll do what everyone is doing.
I studied up on the concepts
of long distance swimming.
You may know the concepts perfectly,
but the ocean is a dangerous place.
If you want to do the same regimen,
you should use a kickboard or inflatables.
Take your pick.
It's not beautiful!
Just go with a kickboard.
With that...
Let's start training!
Ah, hold on!
We're supposed to start at
the same time, Nagisa-kun!
Hurry up!
Wait for me!
Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
Let's get going.
Yeah...
I didn't realize long distance
swimming was so taxing.
You did well for a first-timer.
Good work.
It really feels like we're training.
We'll be a lot stronger
when this camp is over!
If we win prefecturals
and do well at regionals,
we'll be headed to nationals!
Yep.
It all sounds like a dream,
but I want to see how far we can go.
If we place, we'll get a bigger budget!
Then we'll be able to swim
indoors during winter!
I hope so.
You'll get to swim all the time!
Good work!
Thanks.
Was the training regimen
from hell too hard after all?
You guys only completed half of it.
Well, it's only the first day.
I-I'll do better tomorrow!
You'll do fine, Rei-chan.
I'll catch up in no time!
That's the spirit.
Hey!
That's enough performance reviews for now.
Let's eat before it gets dark.
I'm starving!
Oh, no.
I forgot to bring seasoning.
What?!
I'll go borrow some from the lodge.
Thank you.
Sorry!
You're Matsuoka-senpai's...
What's wrong?
Big brother.
Gou?
Nitori, you head back first.
It's not what you're thinking.
It's not?
Haru and the rest of them are here, right?
They are.
But it's purely coincidence.
We happen to be here for a training camp.
Training camp?
We're using the pool.
Where are they swimming?
The ocean.
Makoto's okay with that?
Huh?
Forget it. Never mind.
Are they completing their regimen?
Uh-huh...
Well, they only finished half of it today.
What?
Nothing.
Sounds like you're still worried about them.
I'm not.
But you promised to meet
them at prefecturals?
I didn't do it to see them.
I'm going to beat Haru.
That's all I care about.
Gou, where are you staying?
Oh, the lodge over there.
I'll walk you back.
What's that smile for?
No reason.
Mackerel and hokke!
Mackerel and pineapple!
What?
Pineapple's the one topping
I'll never put on pizza.
I hate green peas in shumai!
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
What? I'm not sure about that one.
Really?
Why would you say that?!
Rei, you don't need to worry
about not finishing the regimen.
Just take it slow.
I'm just glad we're able to practice
and camp here together.
It's important to improve our times,
but what makes me happiest is
that we can all swim together.
Yes.
Then Haru and I will be in this tent.
What? I wanna sleep with Haru-chan.
You don't want to be in a tent with me?
Well, you probably grind
your teeth when you sleep.
I don't do that!
We can use amida to decide.
I'm in!
We can draw in the sand.
Okay.
Let's head back to the lodge.
I'm on the far right!
Oh, yes.
Ah! That's the one I wanted!
Now, now.
Which one are you taking, Haru?
The one on the end.
Why isn't big brother with them?
Amida!
I have to work harder.
Beautiful...
Okay, I think I'm getting the hang of this.
Shoot!
Huh?
Rei?
It's raining hard.
H-Help!
Rei!
There's trouble, Haru-chan!
Rei-chan's gone!
Makoto's missing, too.
Are they swimming out there?!
Ah! Stop, Haru-chan!
Wait! It's not safe to go alone!
Next time: Shocking No Breathing!
Shocking No Breathing!
Rei-chan!
Mako-chan!
Hold on!
I'll save you!