It's so cold, I can't sleep.
Maybe I'll drink some warm milk...
Huh?
There's a nice smell
coming from the kitchen...
Aki-chan, Aki-chan, Aki-chan, Aki-chan...
The Place We Longed to Reach
M-Mayu-chan, what are you making?
Hina-chan?
I'm prepping for tomorrow.
A-At this hour?
Also, you're acting kind of strange.
You were muttering the landlady's name...
I-I was not!
Hina-chan, you must be half-asleep
and hearing things!
Hurry up and get to bed!
Come on, right now! Hurry!
Sh-She's hiding something!
I'm suspicious!
Show me what you're making.
Huh?!
N-No! It's a secret until tomorrow!
You can't look! You can't look!
She's so cute, I can't pursue it any further!
Huh?
I'll go talk to Kuu-chan!
Oh, my...
Kuu-chan, are you still awake?
I sure am.
What brings you here at this hour?
W-Well, Mayu-chan was muttering
the landlady's name
while dressed like a witch
and stirring a big pot!
C-Calm down! What on Earth happened?!
Mayu-chan was muttering the landlady's name
while making something in a big pot!
It must have been the kind of
creepy potion that witches make!
A creepy potion?
Like a paralyzing potion...
Huh?!
C-Creepy potion...
I'll go sneak a taste of it!
You can't!
Come to think of it,
isn't tomorrow Valentine's Day?
Will the landlady be okay?
What if there's some kind of incident?
What if we wake up in the morning
to find the landlady unconscious?!
That sounds like the premise
of a mystery novel!
Let's say, for example, the landlady
doesn't wake up in the morning.
So we go to her room to check on her, and...
And?
And we find her in the middle of changing,
in a very immodest position!
Hitotose
I was so worried about the landlady,
I couldn't get any sleep.
Oh, Hina-chan. Good morning.
M-Miss Landlady!
You look a bit pale. Are you okay?
Um, I...
What now? Where should I even start?
P-Please take extra good care of yourself!
Huh? Th-Thanks.
Same to you.
Aki-chan! Good morning!
Here, this is for you!
Thanks for doing this every year.
Miss Landlady!
I'll check it for poison first!
Poison?
I've got some for you, too, Hina-chan.
Did I do something to make you hate me?
Th-They're just Valentine's
chocolates, Hina-chan!
What are you so afraid of?
Aki-chan and I were making chocolates
to serve at the coffee shop.
Huh? But why were you dressed like that?
It was really cold last night.
Dressed
Warmly
It made cooking so uncomfortable.
And why were you muttering
the landlady's name?
Because...
I heard if you chant the name of the person
you're making chocolate for,
it'll taste better.
I saw it written in a book of spells.
So that's it!
I was sure you were making
some kind of potion to paralyze the landlady!
Hina-chan, you come up with
some of the most outlandish insults...
I made this chocolate for Chiaki-senpai,
but will I be able to give it to her?
Chiaki-senpai...
I've always been watching you.
I really admire you!
Please accept this!
Okay!
I've got it all planned out!
Chiaki-senpai!
Thank you.
R-Reality is harsh!
I appreciate it. Thank you.
If I hesitate too long, I'll miss my chance!
Thank you.
Well, bye.
Chiaki-senpai!
Oh, Yua-chan.
Um...
U-Um...
Well...
What do I do?
Now that she's right in front of me,
I'm so nervous...
But I have to give it to her!
Miss Landlady! Happy Valentine's Day!
I bought this at the school store!
Thank you, Hina-chan.
Wow, you've got lots of them!
Yeah.
Why are you so mentally strong
only at times like this?
Yua-chan? What's wrong?
Hinako...
Come with me.
I want your help with something.
What is it?
I want to give chocolate to Chiaki-senpai,
but when I try to be honest about
how I feel, I get embarrassed.
I thought her behavior
made it obvious enough...
Oh, Mayu-chan.
Mayu-senpai...
Oh? Yua-chan, have you not been able to
give your chocolate to Aki-chan yet?
Huh?!
H-How did you know I'm giving it to her?!
Do you have ESP?!
It's pretty obvious just from watching you.
Please accept this.
Thank you.
Your hair accessory is crooked.
Th-Thank you!
Aki-chan's pretty, and really nice to boot.
Even the girls love her.
I see... That's very true.
A long time ago,
she saved me when I was
surrounded by older students.
Huh?
Well, aren't you cute?
Super cute.
Hold it right there!
Huh?
Wh-Wh-Who the heck are you?!
Aki-chan! You came for me?
Beat it!
In spite of how she looks, is the landlady
actually a delinquent at heart?
I-It wasn't like that...
It was my first day of school.
You're so tiny and cute!
Are you new?
What's your class?
U-Um...
You look like a doll!
Come here and I'll give you some candy!
Look, she's blushing!
Um, you're making Mayu-chan uncomfortable.
Are you new, too?
You're really pretty!
Your hair's so smooth!
And your figure's perfect!
Look at that waist!
U-Um, excuse me... I don't...
So that's how Aki-chan helped me.
I guess it's not easy being beautiful...
I get nervous whenever I see Senpai's face,
so I'd like you to give her this for me...
I can't!
You put all your heart into making it,
so you have to give it to her yourself!
I'm sure she'll understand your feelings.
Hinako...
You're right. I chanted
her name while I made it.
Chiaki-senpai, Chiaki-senpai, Chiaki-senpai...
I'm sure she'll accept it.
Y-Yeah...
I guess she read
the same book Mayu-chan did.
I'm going!
Good luck!
Chiaki-senpai!
Please accept this!
Um, I've always watched you, and...
Yep, I know.
I always thought we seemed
to make eye contact a lot.
I-I'm so embarrassed!
Thank you for the chocolate.
I'd like to give you something in return.
Can you come to the shop after school?
Huh? I really can?
Your expressions change at the
drop of the hat. It's so neat.
Coffee Shop
I wonder what Senpai wants
to give me in return...
I'm here... Huh?
Have some chocolate.
Thanks.
Yua-chan!
Yua-chan, welcome.
We're giving chocolate
to all our customers today.
Mayu-chan made them!
Come in and have some!
Chiaki-senpai in a maid outfit...
What a feast for the eyes!
Sh-She was so happy, it made her cry?!
We sure had lots of customers
yesterday, huh?
Yeah. We gave away almost
all the chocolate I made.
You're right!
As the landlady, the boost in sales
yesterday makes me very happy.
It must be because of
your chocolate, Mayu-chan.
You think so?
I think it had more to do with how you and
Hina-chan looked in the maid outfits.
By the way, Mayu-chan...
Hm?
Are you free this afternoon?
Huh? I don't have anything
planned for today...
I can't call it thanking you
for the Valentine's chocolate,
but if you like, why don't we...
Is Aki-chan asking me...
Sure!
Chocolate Rhapsody No. 8
Old Town Factory
Shimokita Theater
Wow! Tickets to a play?
I got a bunch of them from a friend,
so I wanted to invite all of you
as thanks for the Valentine's chocolate.
Um, I'd be happy to, but...
Mayu-chan seems to be
pouting about something.
Did something happen?
I'm not really sure...
Mayu-chan, here.
I'm not really into plays.
Hey, isn't this...
What is it, Hina-chan?
The theater where this is
being held... is it...
Shimokita Theater
Hmm... It says "Shimokita Theater."
Isn't this the place where
we want to perform, Suzuran, is?
It's near there.
So when we go to see the play,
can we also take a look at Suzuran?
Sure, if we leave a bit early.
Great! I'm so happy!
I'm excited, too!
I bet there's a lot of great food
around there, too!
That's what you're excited for?
Mayu-chan, here.
Suzuran...
Closed Today
Sorry!
Hina-chan, hurry up!
Just a second!
I'm glad you decided to
come along, Mayu-chan.
Yeah.
Well, I was the one who told
Hina-chan about Suzuran.
That's true.
That was when we found our goal.
Sorry for the wait!
Well, we're going to check out
Suzuran before the play, right?
So let's hurry!
Aki-chan, you didn't forget
the tickets, did you?
Nope. All set.
Kuu-chan, you didn't forget to
lock up the bookstore, did you?
Nope! All set!
Okay, then! Let's go!
Mayu-chan!
Did you lock the coffee shop?
Looks like there's no place to sit.
Let's head more toward the middle.
You could just grab that rail...
I'm fine! I can reach it on my tiptoes!
Would you like to have my seat, dear?
Please don't worry about me...
That's just like Mayu-chan.
So cute!
The train arriving now is the
express train bound for Shibuya.
This way. Follow me.
This sure is a complicated route.
It's like a maze.
This station has been under
construction for a long time.
This way.
It's easy to get the exits
mixed up in this station.
South Exit
South Exit This Way
Welcome to
Shimokitazawa!
You're right.
I'd get lost here in a heartbeat.
Um...
Hina-chan isn't behind us.
Hina-chan!
Wh-Where is everyone?
Hello?
Hina-chan? Where are you?
U-Um... I'm...
I'm not sure where I am!
W-Wait just a second, Hina-chan.
We'll just have to look for her ourselves.
According to the map...
She came downstairs with us,
so she's probably at the north exit.
A-Aki-chan...
Yeah.
This is a shortcut.
She's not here...
Yeah, I don't see her.
Hina-chan? Where are you now?
I'm not sure where I am!
Why did you move?!
I went looking for you!
We finally found each other!
Jeez, why'd you move
when you were the one who got lost?
I'm sorry...
No, Hina-chan, you did well!
Eh? Kuu-chan?
Thanks to you, I got to buy up all the best food
from the shops around the station!
Kuu-chan, that's amazing!
When did you...
Honma Theater
"Seki" Mini Theater
What's up, Hina-chan?
I feel like we're seeing theaters everywhere
just by walking through here.
This town is known as the "town of theater."
Honma Theater, The Suzuran, Train Station Mini Theater,
"Seki" Mini Theater, Rakuen Mini Theater, Theater 717
Wow!
And the one that started it all
is right over there.
Suzuran Alley
The Suzuran
So that's...
Suzuran!
Suzuran Alley
The Suzuran
This is my first time seeing it, too.
It's a very classical-looking building.
Are you surprised?
Yeah! I'd love to take a look inside
if we ever have a chance!
Suzuran Alley
The Suzuran
It feels so historical, somehow.
Yeah, it does.
I hope I can stand on the stage
here someday...
Thank you all for coming today!
Did you enjoy the play?
It was great!
I think I could learn a lot from that script.
I cried a little.
I still feel really moved...
It moved you that much?
It was a comedy. What part made you cry?
No way! The last part was really emotional!
See? There's someone crying over there, too!
Huh?
Yua-chan!
H-Hinako?
Chiaki-senpai!
What a coincidence!
Everyone...
This really is quite a coincidence.
Ruri-chan!
Sensei?
Since we're all here,
why don't we all go back to
the coffee shop for dinner?
Would it be all right if I joined you?
Of course!
It'll be fun to talk about
the play over dinner.
Yes, I'm sure it'll be a
productive conversation.
Come with us, Yua-chan!
That aside, why are you all
here with Chiaki-senpai?
I'm sorry, Yua-chan.
I invited them all to
thank them for Valentine's Day.
I should have told you about it, too.
N-No, I didn't mean...
I've been theater-hopping
since this morning, so...
So you were moved to tears too,
huh, Yua-chan?
I-I just had something
in my eyes, that's all.
But it was a great play, wasn't it?
Y-Yeah...
You two might actually
be pretty similar, huh?
Maybe!
We are not!
Anyway... I wish I could've gone
to Suzuran with everyone, too.
You've seen it before, haven't you?
I have, but I wanted to see it together!
Let's go again sometime!
Huh? F-Fine.