Coffee Shop Hitotose
I'm back.
Oh, Hina-chan.
I'm back, Miss Landlady.
This letter came for you, from your mom.
Really?
180-3003
1-7-5 Kichijoji Minami,
Higashi Musashimurano, Tokyo
Sakuragi Hinako-sama
Let's see...
Hinako, are you doing well?
Nothing's changed here.
When I think of a girl like you who
can't speak becoming an actress,
it worries me so...
Mom...
So, to see you acting,
I'll be coming to visit you soon!
Coming to... visit soon?
Visit?
Hina-chan?
What?!
We'll Have a Training Camp
I can't believe it... Mom is coming here?
Hina-chan, what's wrong?
N-N-Nothing!
Wh-What do I do?
Mom's coming to see me act?
I'll get nervous and turn into
a scarecrow for sure!
I haven't even been in any real
performances since the culture festival...
Oh, I know!
I'll just have to let her see me
working in the coffee shop
W-W-Welcome.
to give her peace of mind...
My, what a stylish costume!
Look this way!
No way! That'd be even more embarrassing!
Hina-chan?
When I looked at the flowerbed at school today, there were some flowers that weren't there yesterday. I wondered if someone had planted them.
I wonder if it looked like this. Or this.
The next time I have a sketch assignment in class, I think I'll sketch some flowers from the flowerbed. I wonder if there will be different flowers then. How exciting.
I hope there are sunflowers in the summer.
You're working?
Yeah, a bit.
Oh, right... See this?
Yokomichi Street Shopping District Stamp Rally Event to Be Held
Our annual Yokomichi Street shopping district stamp rally event will be
held again this year. We are recruiting local businesses to participate.
We welcome new businesses, as well as those who participated
in previous years! We're awaiting your applications!
The Yokonyans Are Rooting for You!
Yokomichi Street Shopping District Restoration Association
There's going to be a stamp rally event
in the shopping district soon.
Stamp rally?
Yeah.
Bakery
Excuse me!
Customers visit all the
participating stores in turn
Greengrocer
I'd like a stamp, please!
and get a card stamped at each store.
Butcher
Thank you!
Then at the end, prizes are awarded.
Yay!
And our shop is going to be
participating this year.
So I was thinking,
what can we do to bring in lots of customers?
I-In that case, why don't we
do a performance?
Huh?
I've been wanting the Hitotose Troupe
to have its first performance!
And it would give my mom
a chance to see me acting, too!
Hina-chan, you've been thinking
of our troupe that much?
Huh? Ah, no, I...
This month's class goals!
Sleep earlier than usual!
Wake up earlier than usual!
I see...
If that's what you're planning,
I'll write a script for us.
And I'll help with the props and wardrobe.
Thank you, Kuu-chan, Mayu-chan!
Mayu-chan, you should be in the play, too.
N-No way! I don't like
being in the spotlight,
and I can't memorize lines!
But you did so well
at the culture festival...
Th-That was out of desperation
to help Hina-chan!
I thought you'd be perfect
for an angel or child role.
I'm not a child!
Then how about a doll role?
I'm not that small!
What kind of play should it be?
I think it should be one both
adults and children can enjoy.
How about an adventure story, then?
The main character is a treasure hunter
who's traveling the world.
That's an awfully large scale...
There it is!
Cave
She wanders into a dungeon,
and enemies try to kill her...
Monster
Monsters attack her...
...and in the end, the enemy's lair blows up.
Script
You want to blow up the shop?!
Let's play it safe and
do our take on a fairy tale.
Isn't that...
I can't wait— whoops!
Hinako?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Where will we practice?
In the usual park.
She's being all friendly
with Chiaki-senpai again!
What are they talking about?
But the park will be
really crowded on the weekend.
That's true...
Then why don't we practice in my room?
There's not much furniture, so it's roomy.
Yeah, your room is always so tidy.
And you have lots of
stuffed animals in yours.
After coming to Tokyo, I got into
the habit of collecting stuffed animals...
They're all very cute.
No fair, Hinako!
I want to talk about that stuff, too!
Merchandise for the new mascot comes out today!
Some of it is seasonal exclusives,
so I'll have to go straight over after school.
It's only available during this season, after all!
What's the matter, Yua-chan?
The Hitotose Troupe's first performance?
You should have told me sooner.
I'm a member of the troupe, you know!
I'm sorry.
We actually just decided to do it yesterday.
Can't we practice in
the school's empty classroom?
If we say it's for a theater assignment,
we can get permission.
You think it'll be that easy?
Just leave it to me!
The teachers trust me a lot!
Wow!
I should've known!
You really do have your act together!
Well, it's more like my stock naturally went up
as I kept covering for Hinako...
I've been curious about the cake shop that opened in front of the station, so I'll buy a cake from there.
I think I'll buy a cake for Mom, too! I wonder what kind of cake she likes...
I worked really hard today, so my mom gave me an allowance!
Yay!
The cast will be you, me, Kuina,
and Chiaki-senpai,
and Mayu-senpai is making
the props and wardrobe, right?
Yeah!
Maybe I'll take care of the makeup.
And the landlady's going to make flyers.
She likes to draw, she says.
Then maybe she'll do our
backdrops and scenery, too.
I'm writing the script...
And I'll also take care of picking
a venue for our after-party.
We want a restaurant
with good, cheap food, right?
Do you guys prefer Japanese or Western food?
You should put more effort into writing
the script than picking a restaurant...
I-I think I'd like to
play a tree or a statue.
That way, if I turn into a scarecrow,
Mom won't notice.
Aren't you the principal?!
So for that reason,
we'd like to borrow the empty
classroom after school.
Play practice, huh?
This isn't for the theater club?
No, it's private.
All right.
I know it's safe to let
you use it, Nakajima-san.
It really was easy to get permission!
That's our Yua-chan!
What did I tell you?
Hello?
It sounds like you're planning
something interesting.
Ruri-chan!
Sensei!
I didn't know you had a desk
in the faculty office, Ruri-chan.
Well, despite my appearance,
I am a club advisor.
Anyway, what is it you're planning to do?
Oh, actually, we'll be putting on
a theater performance at Hitotose.
I see. So that's why you'll be practicing.
That's right.
I can't just sit idly by knowing
you're practicing theater.
Would it be all right if I joined you?
What? You will?
As the theater club's advisor,
it's just part of my job.
Wow! Thank you!
On that note,
let's hold a training camp
here at school this weekend!
Huh? Training camp?
Um, Sensei, a training camp
on such short notice?
I can't wait!
I guess you like that sort
of event, huh, Ruri-chan?
Sorry!
Packing my things took longer than I expected!
Wow, you brought a pretty big bag.
Yeah.
Let's see... I brought my pajamas,
a change of clothes, and...
Well, I brought lots of things.
Kuu-chan and Mayu-chan,
you have big bags, too.
Mine is...
...all books!
Wow! You brought all these
as references to write a script?
Huh?
Oh, right! They're all for reference!
Sh-She plans to eat them all...
Hey, look at this!
I brought my favorite stuffed animal!
Oh, I did, too!
This is going to be fun!
Yeah!
This is shaping up to be
just a slumber party...
Jeez, you guys are too hyped up
for just an overnight training camp.
All you need is the bare minimum:
face wash, toner, moisturizer, and aroma oils.
I'd say those are the things
we'll need the least.
What do you think is
most important to bring, then?
Questions like that are common, huh?
Like, what would you take
to a deserted island?
I'd take a field guide of edible plants.
It's both useful and edible!
It won't be useful anymore if you eat it!
I'd take a water filter.
What about you, Hina-chan?
Huh? Well...
Maybe food for all the animals
that would come to see me?
Eat up.
Worry about getting food for yourself!
Oh, here it is!
This classroom is where we'll be
training all night!
Oh?
Good morning, everyone.
Ruri-chan, you're already here?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Don't worry about it.
I laid out the futons while I waited.
Huh?! Wh-Why?!
My parents told me the best part of
a training camp is the pillow fight.
Huh?
R-Really?
This really is shaping up to be
just a slumber party...
Well, shall we begin practice?
I'll make dinner while
you're all practicing.
Thank you!
She isn't an actress in the Hitotose Troupe?
Oh... no, she gets embarrassed easily,
so she doesn't want to be on the stage.
Maybe I'll change
into a maid outfit later...
What a shame.
She's such a cute girl.
She's a very good dancer, too.
In that case, why don't
we debut her as an idol?
Everyone! Are you having a good time?
I think she'd be even more
embarrassed to do that.
There we go.
Okay! Time to polish my acting skills
so I can impress Mom!
Hina-chan seems even more driven than usual.
Miss Landlady, is the shopping
district event very large in scale?
No, it's not that large.
But the shop that draws the most customers
will receive a bale of rice.
Ah, I see!
You really love to eat, huh, Hina-chan?
Huh?
Oh, no, I fully understand
where you're coming from!
Well, shall we end our practice for now?
Yes... So tired...
Since it's a training camp,
I got a bit overzealous.
Can't go on...
You two are pathetic, passing out from that!
You're still very energetic, Yua-chan.
Y-Yes! Um, I-I can still
keep going... I mean, um...
Oh, right! I'm going to go wash my face!
It's raining...
I-It's kind of creepy in here...
The lights keep flickering.
F-Feels almost like a ghost might pop out...
I'll wash up fast and hurry back.
Dinner time...
Y-Yua-chan?!
What's wrong?
A ghost! A French doll ghost!
Huh?! A French doll ghost?!
Wh-Where?! Where?!
This month's goal: Only 1 cake per day!
Work:
Tues:
Thurs:
Sat:
Buy the ticket by next Thursday!
Diet = Having to exercise somewhat. In order to continue things you don't like doing, it's important to do what you can every day.
Let's eat!
Mayu-chan, your vegetable curry is so good!
You're right! It's really good!
My, it is delicious.
What's your favorite food, Hina-chan?
I like all vegetables!
The ones we could pick back home
were the best, though!
Fresh-picked is always better, isn't it?
What's your favorite, Mayu-chan?
I like shortcake and Hamburg steaks.
I like nanbu senbei, salt-grilled saury...
Oh, and plum-and-kelp tea.
Most of the foods I like are the things
that you like the least, huh?
Yeah.
You two really are opposite extremes...
The school is kind of creepy
at night, isn't it?
By the way, have you heard of
this school's seven mysteries?
Huh? It has those?
Your school didn't have anything
like that, Hina-chan?
I'm quite interested, too.
Hmm... Did we?
Oh, yeah!
I think there was a walking
Ninomiya Kinjirou,
a Ninomiya Kinjirou
that suddenly grew heavy,
a dancing Ninomiya Kinjirou,
I don't want them to think I,
Yua-sama, was scared by a ghost!
the Ninomiya Kinjirou in the mirror,
I'm not leaving this classroom again
for the rest of the night!
a stain on the wall that
was Ninomiya Kinjirou,
a Ninomiya Kinjirou with shining eyes, and...
There.
Hina-chan, could you go get a washrag
from the home ec classroom?
Ah...
I'll go!
Crap! I just said that out of habit!
Okay, you can both go together.
Sure!
I'm not scared... I'm not scared!
Um, the home ec room is this way, right?
Ah, so that's why Mayu-chan gave me this.
Hey... W-Wait for me!
I knew I shouldn't have
left the classroom...
I'm so scared, I feel like I'll pass out!
Yua-chan, do you not like dark places?
That's not... not... not true...
Aren't you scared, Hinako?
Well, a little...
But you always help me out,
so I thought I should be
there for you this time.
Y-You're just Hinako...
Oh, fine. I guess I'll hold your hand.
Be grateful!
Well, this is still a lot brighter
than the countryside at night.
Hey! Why'd you stop?
Something's there.
Huh?
Wh-Where?
See? Right there.
Th-There's nothing there!
H-Hey, Hinako! Wait for me!
H-Hinako?
Hinako, come on!
Yua-chan, look! It was a kitty!
I guess it wandered in here and got lost.
Yua-chan?!
Easy, Kuu-chan.
Aren't training camps fun?
I wish we could stay over at
school every weekend.
I've had enough.
After spending the day with all of you,
I've got some ideas for my script!
It's a horror story, though...
Yua-chan?!
Are you okay?
Everyone's having fun, and all is well.
Open your eyes!
I guess this kind of training camp
could be nice once in a while.
By the way...
When do we get to have the pillow fight?
You're really stuck on that, huh, Sensei?
Goodnight.
Hinako, are you awake?
I mean, it's fine if you're not.
Um... Thanks for earlier.
It was really reassuring having you ther—
Yua-chan?! Yua-chan?
What happened?
What?
Is something wrong?
A burglar?! Is there a burglar?!
The training camp was so much fun.
Last night was awful for me, though.
I'm sorry. I can't sleep
without that mask on...
I-It's not like I was scared or anything!
It just startled me!
"It just startled me."
Kuu-chan, are you writing the script?
Yep! I think it'll be done
by the end of this week!
Wait, you didn't...
Don't worry. It's not a horror story.
I'm not scared of that stuff, okay?!
The script and our practices
are coming along well.
If we keep this up,
I think I can be confident on the stage!
I'll make sure Mom sees me at my best!
I can't wait until the day of the event.
Yeah!
Let's make the Hitotose Troupe's
first performance a success!
Hinako...
Hina-chan, is a bale of rice
that appealing to you?
Huh? Bale of rice?
Pa-Pa-Parade
Kuu-chan finally finished the script for
the Hitotose Troupe's first performance!
Which means it's my time to shine!
Everyone, try on these costumes right away!
Next time, "Pa-Pa-Parade."