She's been gazing at them a lot lately,
but do you think she might want to go?
Who, Kanna? I think so.
Every dragon's had those
thoughts at some point.
How young, how young.
Huh? What are you talking about?
A journey to eliminate humanity, right?
No, I'm talking about school.
Oh, school.
I see that come up on the Internet often.
The Internet? You've gotten used to it, huh.
Kanna-chan.
What, Kobayashi?
Oh, well...
Want to go to school?
Oborozuka Shopping District
Kobayashi!
Hurry! Hurry!
Hey, Kanna, don't make
trouble for Miss Kobayashi!
You need all this just to go to school?
Textbooks and storage boxes will be provided on the first day.
Pencil case | Pencils | Erasers
Crayons (16 colors) | Colored pencils (12 colors)
Scissors | Glue | Pencil board
Ruler | Unruled notebooks
Indoor slippers | Slipper case | Gym clothes
Gym cap | Gym clothes case
Handkerchief | Safety buzzer
You said it.
I sense some collusion between
schools and the manufacturers.
It's a conspiracy.
I don't think that's true.
The Internet said it is!
It's a bad influence on dragons, too, huh...
Shop at your local shopping district!
Save with your point card!
Well, let's pick up
all the stationery first.
Noyama Stationery
Welcome!
Yeah, this is it.
I see stationery stores haven't
changed at all since long ago.
What's that look for?!
They're not cute.
Huh?!
Jeez, you don't get it, Miss Kobayashi.
Leave it to me!
What's this place?
The feathers plucked from live birds
around this season make good pens!
Scary! Scary!
Seems like this is wrong, too.
That's strange.
When I was in the other world
everyone used quill pens.
I want a cute one. A cute one.
So she says.
Oh, I heard a new store opened
outside the shopping district recently.
What is this?
Everything's sparkling in my eyes.
Kobayashi!
What's this?
How do you use it?
Kanna
You use this to write characters.
You'll be using a pencil though, Kanna-chan.
Miss Kobayashi!
How's this?!
I <3 Miss Kobayashi
Scary!
Hey, Kobayashi,
what's this thing that looks
like a dragon's mouth?
You use it like this.
What a torture device.
How did you jump to that?
Then what about this?
That's a tool for branding slaves.
You use it to mark your property.
Come on, Miss Kobayashi! Brand me as yours!
No.
Popular! Unicorn Pencil Box
Look, Lady Tohru, a unicorn.
I think that unicorn would
be happy knowing this.
Part of me wants to ask,
and part of me doesn't.
*Miss Kobayashi paid for it after this.
Total
Cash
Change
Thank you very much!
Now we've got most of it.
Then on to the next stop!
Does it really have to be this place?
This is the only place in the
area that sells backpacks.
I understand that,
but I still don't like it.
I can't help but remember...
Well, let's go.
The two of us.
Please wait!
Kanna-chan, which one do you like?
This.
She chose a surprisingly normal one.
Figures, Kanna.
I can see why you'd choose a cursed
item that's absorbed human blood.
Uh-huh.
That's your reason?!
That'll be 38,000 yen.
It costs that much?
Is this all right?
Oh, yeah. It's fine.
I'm sorry, I'll be paying with card.
Sure. Thank you very much.
Ohyama Clothing Store
Student Uniform Specialty Shop
Welcome!
Miss Kobayashi, Kanna's going to pout again
if we go in another store like this.
This is the store designated by the school,
so we have no choice.
It's collusion.
You're persistent about that.
Are these the ones designated by the school?
They all seem the same.
That's fine.
Everyone should be wearing the same thing.
Why's that?
To reduce differences.
Men, women, Japanese,
and foreigners are all the same.
That's important.
What happens when you're
different from everyone else?
Sometimes you're eliminated.
It might not be like that for dragons,
but humans don't like things
different from themselves.
That's foolish.
Yeah, I agree it is.
But everyone's afraid...
of things that are different.
I kind of understand.
Sorry.
This wasn't my intent.
Thanks for your concern.
Kanna-chan, are you looking
forward to school?
Yeah.
All right then. Once we get home,
we prepare for tomorrow!
Miss Kobayashi, that's not fair!
Please hold my hand, too!
Yes, yes.
Kobayashi!
Look, look!
You look good!
Yeah, cute.
Lady Tohru.
Look, look.
Kanna.
Please lend that to me.
Miss Kobayashi!
Please look! What do you think?
Too many different themes to tell.
Huh?!
In the end, she wore that
backpack all day long.
She must really be looking forward to it.
Is it something to go that far over?
Even though she's a dragon, she's still a child.
In the way.
What's Kanna-chan doing?
She's practicing her writing.
Well, think you'll remember them?
500,000 loan,
no co-signer needed!
We'll teach you how to
earn money in your sleep!
Becoming a billionaire isn't a dream!
Bring in business and good fortune!!
Increase your fortune just by
learning these tips! Guaranteed results
or your money back!
How to score a boyfriend!
Recommended for friends, family,
and coworkers!
No co-signer needed
Same-day financing
Earn
Fortune
Money
Boyfriend
Cosigner
Repay
Let's forget all this for now.
Episode 4
Kanna Goes to School! (Not That She Needs To)
Good morning!
Oborozuka Elementary
Give a
bright smile
every day
Yes, good morning.
Today we have a new friend to
introduce to everyone here.
This is Kobayashi Kanna-chan.
Kobayashi Kanna.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Cute!
Where'd you come from?
Ushishir Island.
From abroad?! Wow!
It looks like her introduction went well.
Watch over Kanna-chan, okay?
Leave it to me, Miss Kobayashi!
Yes. Now, for this problem,
can you solve it, Kobayashi-san?
What a boring problem.
Kanna wanted to do things like that?
Yes, that's correct.
Such an inefficient way to learn.
Putting them in different classes based on their
abilities would help them grow faster.
Cram School Approach
It seems to be some game of
hitting each other with a ball.
A fitting game for barbaric humans.
Yes, that's it!
No mercy, huh?
Kobayashi-san, you're incredible!
You can do anything, can't you?
Can I call you Kanna-chan?
Oh, can I call you that, too?
But everyone's afraid...
of things that are different.
But they do take clear steps to
ally themselves with the strong.
Even young, they're still human, huh?
Farewell, Sensei!
Dream
Yes, farewell!
Hey, Kobayashi Kanna-san!
Don't you think you've been
standing out too much?
Saikawa Riko
It's Saikawa, the one who acts like a queen!
Thanks for the clear explanation.
But no! Shut up!
I stood out?
You did! You're so cute, it ticks
me off and I want to hug you!
Wants to hug me, stood out, transfer
student, cute and talented, too cute, eliminated
"That's wicked"
I challenge you, Kobayashi Kanna-san!
I'll prove I'm better than you!
Kanna-chan, don't do it.
Saikawa-san plays dirty and cheats,
and she's a hopeless person
who won't admit defeat!
Hey, you, be quiet!
Now, care to try arm wrestling me?
Despite how I look,
I've won at karate tournaments...
I'd like to be friends.
I-I'm sorry, I didn't mean to!
I-I, um, I wanted to be
friends with you, too!
Oh, shoot, what do I do?!
She's too blundering.
Don't cry.
Here, I'll give you some candy.
Ah! You can't bring that to school.
Be quiet!
Still, fake crying? What a roundabout
way to settle things, Kanna.
I would've just blasted them away.
Yeah.
Why did you decide you
wanted to go to school?
Because it was fun watching them.
Was it fun?
Yeah.
I think there will be some
aspects that aren't fun, as well.
Yeah.
There's no real need for us
to be the same as humans.
Living among them doesn't
mean living with them.
But they're close by,
and we share time together, so...
Maybe that's why I want to be with them.
Be with them...
I've seen plenty of my comrades
destroy themselves,
unable to be satisfied with that.
But, well...
For now, I'll affirm that choice, too.
How was school?
Fun.
Good to hear.
Miss Kobayashi!
I fulfilled my mission, too.
Please praise me.
Yeah, thanks.
Oh, right.
Here you go.
This is...
Congratulations on entering school.
You can hang it on your backpack.
Miss Kobayashi!
What about me?
Hey, Miss Kobayashi, what about me?
Here.
Yay!
Simple-gon.
What are you doing?
Putting on name tags.
They said to put them on my things.
This is today's special product!
Tohru
There we go!
A drill perfect for woodwork!
Why?
How
How...
did things get like this?
The story starts one day ago.
So good!
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Sorry I keep dropping by all the time.
You're checking up on Tohru, right?
Oh, you knew?
Well, he's here, too.
I'm bored with this already.
I'm going to play some other game.
To be honest, you're here to
check on Tohru, too, right?
I'm home.
Oh, welcome home, Kanna-chan.
What's happened?
A duel.
A duel?!
I'll aid you!
I'll kill them.
Wait, wait, you delinquents!
Today, on the way home...
Kanna-san.
I'm going home with you today,
so consider it an honor.
Yeah. You're kind, Saikawa.
I like you.
Today I'll show you a good place to play!
Okay.
Well?
Despite how big this place is,
it's a hidden spot people rarely come to.
That's the thing you fly with!
F-Fly?
Yeah, in the clouds.
W-Well, let's play on the seesaw together!
Sorry, sorry.
Hey, watch it, you guys!
What? You're frightened by
a ball coming your way?
Stop that.
Sorry, we were playing dodgeball.
L-Little children come here often, too,
so you should stop that.
There's nowhere else.
Whatever, we're taking over this place.
Go on home, squirts.
I told you to stop that.
I challenge you.
What?
I challenge you to dodgeball tomorrow!
If you lose, then give
up on using this place!
You hear that?
S-She's going to play with us!
Sorry. We don't have time to play with you.
My, running away?
Are you afraid I'll
discipline you all myself?
You American gorilla!
Wh-What'd you say?!
Don't listen to her.
You there, black-haired mama's boy!
Huh?
You're actually scared without your
beloved mama around, aren't you?
You should say so.
"Mama, help me!"
You brat!
Oh?
I thought you weren't going
to take a child seriously?
Children.
Bring it on! We'll face you!
You better get ready to lose!
What do I do?
So you picked a fight
and they bought it, huh?
So, did you gather enough people?
We couldn't.
Saikawa's not popular.
Sorry about that!
Well, what to do, then?
I think you can still negotiate with them.
No, I assure you, they should fight!
We can't have them taking us
noble, proud dragons lightly!
Do you know the rules?
Yes!
I know them, too.
I've played a lot of Explosive Dodgeball.
Explosive Dodgeball
This isn't that kind of game.
All right, let's do this!
Don't worry, it'll work out.
Hmm...
- The Following Day -
What's this, squirt?!
You called in friends?
We won't go easy on you.
Tohru.
Don't kill them.
Yes!
I could see how it would
end when it started.
From the beginning their abilities... well,
their species... were on different levels.
Sorry!
The game was beyond one-sided.
They destroyed them.
Damn it!
That's not fair, jerk! You'll regret this!
He's beat up...
Kanna-san, your friends are incredible!
Yeah, they're the worst scum ever.
That phrasing may be accurate,
but it's cruel.
I still haven't had enough.
Oh? What a coincidence. Me neither.
Me neither.
That reminds me...
I've yet to win against you two, haven't I?
Are you going to surpass us today?
Bring it on.
Huh? Isn't this turning bad?
Me, too.
From that point on,
the playground became a battlefield.
There're even more dragons.
Where did my peaceful, daily life run off to?
Well, whatever.
And that brings us to now.
Oh, I'll restore the playground to normal.
I'll tweak the memories
of those who saw us, too.
You're useful to have around.
- Several Days Later -
After that, they took to
playing dodgeball regularly.
Pay more attention to your lower back!
Oh, like this?
More like you're an old lady
about to be abandoned!
That's at my standards.
Kanna-chan, look, look.
Isn't this cute?
Oh, that's wicked.
Hey, Kobayashi, this is super interesting.
Hey, Kanna-san.
Saikawa, you're wicked.
Okay, time to start class.
That's wicked!
What is this? It's wicked!
Next Episode
Kanna-san, aren't you glad
we won the dodgeball game?
Yeah.
We nearly lost our ability
to play at the playground.
That's okay.
I'll be happy anywhere
if I'm with you, Saikawa.
Episode 5
Tohru's Real World Lessons! (She Thinks She Understands It Already)