I wonder if I'll get to
see the fall next year.
The sun is the light for the early sleepers.
The moon and stars are
light for the night owls.
Complete all the rituals by night.
The night of Yule comes!
Hey, beloved child of the night.
Human child.
Do you think you'll be
done preparing for Yule?
Yule?
We're preparing for Yule soon.
Elias.
You sleepy-head, the night will
be here before you know it.
Set the Yule Log ablaze in your hearth...
Before the Horned God and
his Dark Lady walk the earth.
Thank you.
Take care.
Good morning, Elias.
Who were they?
Yule.
I call them the Yule twins because they
always come on the day of the winter solstice,
but I don't really know their names.
We're going to be busy today.
Okay.
You have to tell me if you get tired.
I'll tell you, I promise.
I'm a failure of a familiar.
I can't help Chise when she's in trouble.
He's been like this ever since that day.
What's even the point?
I'm done for.
You understand Chise far
better than I do, don't you?
It may be tough for you to say anything
because Chise tends to hide things,
but you can tell me sooner.
I'll take care of it.
This is painfully awkward.
She's a bit cold right now.
Chise.
It's because we just came inside.
All right.
Let's prepare for Yule.
It's so pretty.
Is this "pretty"?
I think it is.
There we go.
They say that traditionally, it's okay
to kiss under the mistletoe.
I see...
Want to try it?
He looks like he wants to.
Um...
Could you crouch for me?
Okay.
And back to you.
How was it?
Hmm...
How to phrase it...
My back? My waist? They feel tingly.
Why?
Dunno.
One for you too, Ruth.
All right, let's have dinner.
Okay.
Okay, sir, I'll be sure to deliver this.
Sorry it's always so last-minute.
It's no problem at all.
Now's my chance.
It'll be okay, I left a note.
Bye.
So many people.
Chise, I'll be inside.
Okay.
Sorry to drag you all the way out to London.
So, um...
A Christmas present, right?
For Renfred-san.
Yeah.
You really don't know what to get for him?
What did you get him before?
Before, well...
He was the one giving me gifts, so I thought
this year, I'd get him something.
They're eating.
They're really digging in.
Aren't you getting that bonehead anything?
Me?
I'd never even thought about it.
Let's go look for a present together, then.
Wait...
She's not giving me a choice, is she?
Did you find anything good?
Nope.
There's the question of taste, too.
What about you?
I don't even know what his tastes are.
Sorry.
I've never given anyone a gift before.
I don't... well, I don't know too many people.
M-Me, neither.
I don't know anyone like that, either.
We're in the same boat, then.
In the same boat?
You're a mage and I'm a sorcerer,
but we both live our lives
studying with our masters.
So we're in the same boat.
Oh.
You're right.
Hey, it's the lady from
Mr. Ainsworth's place.
Hazel-san. Hello.
Who are you talking to, Chise?
Oh, is your friend...
Unlike mages, sorcerers don't notice
people like us, who've disguised ourselves.
Nice to meet you, my lady.
Christmas presents, huh?
Yeah...
What about something that
you can picture them using?
Think really carefully about them.
Imagine something that makes sense.
Want to take another lap around?
Okay.
Something he uses all the time, huh?
I think I have an idea.
No fair! Tell me.
You can't copy me, though.
Hey, it's Alice.
Let's go, Chise.
What?
Let's hang out, like old times.
I'm not doing drugs anymore.
Yo!
You...
Wh-Where the hell did you...
Go!
Sorry about that.
They're just stragglers from my past.
Alice-san...
Do drugs taste good?
Not at all.
They're not my thing.
I didn't start by choice, either.
It's still like a dream.
This isn't fun to talk about.
Let's not.
It's okay.
I want to hear.
My shitty parents got me into drugs.
I had nothing going for me outside of selling
that crap, when Master took me in.
Hey, have you seen the blonde brat?
We need to teach her a lesson.
What the hell are you looking at?
What are you...
Do you want to stay here forever?
No!
I haven't introduced myself yet.
I'm Mikhail Renfred.
Call me what you want.
Hey, asshole...
Take a bath first.
Wait...
I didn't trust him in
the slightest at the time.
Before that, I'd grown up in a trash pit.
There was no way I could trust people.
But, one day...
What a pain.
I can't read the title.
I told you not to open them!
Ow!
No, that was my fault, too.
I should have told you more clearly.
Why?
Your face...
You're hurt.
It's fine.
I'm glad, though.
You're finally getting better.
You shouldn't be getting yourself hurt again.
This way.
I'm used to treating wounds.
I can do it.
I'm self-taught, though.
I'm sorry.
I'll be more careful.
I'll protect you, as your bodyguard.
I'm counting on you next time.
Thinking about that makes me feel like shit.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to say.
You don't need to think anything about it.
I'll decide for myself whether
I'm happy or miserable.
Thanks for hearing me out.
All right, let's get back.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, is my servant bird at your place?
It's this tiny thing.
Oh, never mind.
I'll write you a letter again.
Thanks for coming out at the last minute.
No, thank you, too.
I hope it works out for both of us.
You have a friend now. I'm happy for you.
As my big brother, do you approve?
She's not a bad person.
Jeez, Ethan!
I'm sorry!
Stella! Ethan!
Let's head home, then.
Welcome home, Chise.
You're late.
Thanks, Elias.
What did you want all the way out in London?
And you even met with
Renfred's apprentice.
Y-You were watching?
Do you know how many times
you've put yourself in danger?
You can't sneak out like that.
I thought you'd say no.
Of course I would.
I was with her.
Don't be too angry, Elias.
Angry?
This is angry? I am?
I think so.
I'm sorry.
Um...
I went to buy this.
I know it's a day early, but...
Merry Christmas.
Elias?
Oh, right.
I didn't think you'd get me anything.
I didn't think I'd get you anything.
I'm sorry, Elias.
Uh...
You're always wearing the same one,
so I thought maybe it relaxes you.
I-If you don't like it...
Thanks, Chise.
One for you, too, then.
It's big.
I've only made them for
Angelica and her family.
I thought I'd make one for you, too.
You made this?
You did?
Yeah.
Angelica told me a long time ago that
she wanted a teddy bear as a gift.
I think this year's is my best one yet.
You've been doing it ever since?
Yeah.
I don't really know what else to do.
Thank you.
It has a bit of a trick, too.
Also...
Those are all gifts for you.
Angelica, Simon, and Lindel
have gotten you gifts, too.
Gifts are meant to be
opened on Christmas Day,
so these are for tomorrow.
Okay.
All right, let's have dinner first.
I'll scold you after.
I was hoping he'd forgotten.
You should have told me.
I would have gone with you.
And I could have gotten some shopping done.
I wouldn't agree to that.
I had a secret talk with another
girl about girl stuff.
Is this what Christmas
is supposed to be like?
I can't believe I'm looking
forward to waking up.
Oh?
I see a pitiful child.
An ancient being, Ashen Eye.
Siblings that are at the
mercy of his eternal life.
The mage and the girl
lend them a hand, but...
Give him back! He's my brother!