Wow.
It looks delicious.
Oh, Miuna-chan.
Oh, I-I'm going to take a bath now.
It's no use...
Huh?
Episode Twenty-Two:
Something Lost
Uroko-sama!
Uroko-sama, where are you?
Is Uroko-sama really on the surface?
Tsumugu hasn't been in the sea,
and yet he got cursed
and the fish appeared.
That means he should be
somewhere in Oshiooshi.
But where?
I don't know.
Uroko-sama!
Hey!
Come on... it's not like
he's a dog or a cat...
Ugh, so gross!
You don't have to look at it.
Will this really work?
Sayu?
Manaka-san?
Can we really catch him with this?
Yeah, probably.
What are you two doing?!
We're planting a porn magazine
we found on the shore.
Uroko-sama likes perverted
things, and...
Ooh!
You made that for Uroko-sama?
Yeah.
It has bamboo shoots,
carrots, and chicken.
I prepared them all separately.
Let me taste it!
Wow, so good!
My grandma's is better, but...
I'll take one more.
Yay, it turned out good.
I wonder if Uroko-sama will
come out if we leave this as well.
Yeah, totally.
But he's not a dog or a cat...
But he totally eats things that
have fallen on the floor.
Wow, that's awful!
What am I going to do if he has super
hairy fingers and emits a pervy aura...
He doesn't have hairy fingers,
but he has scales on
his chest and his arms.
Well, I guess they don't call
him Uroko-sama for nothing.
The thing you said you'd tell
me after the Ofunehiki...
I'll hear it now.
What did you want to say?
Is it about Tsumugu?
Huh?
Isn't it about Tsumugu?
What are you talking about?
What are you staring at so blankly?
Nothing.
It's snowing...
Lately, the salt-flake snow has
been falling more frequently.
And according to the news,
it's now falling in towns
and cities far from the sea as well.
I wonder where Uroko-sama is...
I guess searching aimlessly won't work.
Is there somewhere on the surface
that's connected to the Sea God?
Huh? Um...
No idea.
Do you know anywhere, Miuna?
What?
Oh...
I know there's some old shrine, but...
You're going back to
the university, right?
Where is that?
Are you sure you're okay doing this?
South of the beach.
But it's sort of barren...
Finding Uroko-sama is part
of our research, too.
Is that place even related
to the Sea God, though?
It sounds like a fart.
Yours was like that too.
You totally hated it when
it was on your knee.
That's true.
I wonder if it's hungry.
I'm gonna give it some food.
Food? It eats?
It does. Wanna watch?
Gross!
I wanna see!
Oh, Sayu?
Why don't we take a break?
I'll go prepare some tea.
I'll help.
Whoa, it's really coming down!
I wonder if Uroko-sama ate some of the stew.
Um, you had a fish appear
on you, too, Manaka-san?
Yeah, I was totally surprised!
After it was gone, you lied
and still said it was there.
It's so funny!
Whoa! It totally ate it!
Gross!
It's like a frog! Here!
I got those bean pastries
from a patient.
This is so cool!
Huh. From a guy?
Oh, stop. What are you saying?
You're so popular.
Stupid. He's an old man.
I'm kinda jealous.
Maybe I should ask you out again.
Kidding.
Some time passed,
and Mihashi-sensei had to go back to
the university earlier than expected.
Because of the bad weather,
the investigations were delayed,
and since there were dangers,
he was called back to the university.
Sorry about this.
This is from Chisaki.
To eat on your trip.
That's great!
Thanks.
I kept telling them that this is exactly
why we need to continue
our investigations, but...
Is there that much
salt-flake snow falling?
It was on the news, wasn't it?
Even cities far inlands
are getting heavy snow,
causing problems with the traffic
network and power outages.
Are you going back, too, Tsumugu-kun?
No, I'm staying for a little longer.
I see.
Well, there's still some
time before the sun sets,
so I'm going to go look for
that bastard, Uroko.
Oh, I'll go, too.
Sayu, let's go, too.
Yeah.
Are you staying behind for Chisaki?
And I thought you were going to say that
you're staying behind for the investigation.
What's the point in that?
I want an answer, too.
Unsweetened Coffee
Zero Sweetness,
Bitter and Black
Coffee
Yeah...
Don't Hikari and Manaka-san
seem a bit weird to you?
Sayu?
Shiodome, what are you doing?
Well, you know...
I see.
They say it's going to snow again.
It's probably better
if you get home soon.
Right. Thanks.
See ya.
Miuna...
Minegishi asked you out, right?
Huh?
Wh-What are you talking
about all of a sudden?
Asking out, huh...
Wow!
Hii-kun, Hii-kun, the tupper
and the porn magazine are gone!
It has to be Uroko-sama!
You don't know for sure.
Some random old perv
could have taken them.
No, it's gotta be Uroko-sama!
So he really is on the surface!
Let's find him.
Uroko-sama, where are you?
Uroko-sama's not around, huh?
When Tsumugu and I raced...
Huh?
And I messed up and got hurt...
Ready...
Ow...
Hii-kun!
You were the first one to dive
into the pool, weren't you?
Uh...
You don't remember that either, do you?
What else don't you remember?
Do you even remember the fish
coming out of your knee...
Oh, I do remember that!
Really.
But...
What?
I don't remember telling a lie
about it still being there.
I-I'm sorry!
I didn't want to worry all of you.
You don't remember?
Oh, but I remember making the
Ojoshi-sama with everyone!
It's okay.
I think I'm just a little sleepy still.
When...
When we were told not to go to the
surface because it was dangerous...
The fact that I...
The fact that I ended up holding you...
Before everyone was about to hibernate,
when we went to Nami
Junior High and I...
...said I loved you...
I don't understand any of that!
You don't...
You don't remember any of that?
Um...
Hii-kun?
Hey, you octopus!
You pushed a lady and you're
just going to leave her?!
Hikari?
Hey, Miuna?
Miuna!
Where are you going, Hikari?
Hey, Hikari!
Go away!
What?
I said, go away!
Hikari!
Ow...
Man, what are you doing?
Sorry...
Th-Thanks.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Fish
I didn't know there was
a small shrine here...
What's this?
Oh, S-Sayu said that was for Uroko-sama.
For goodness sake,
you actually thought
you could catch me with that?
Apparently I'm rather underestimated.
Uroko-sama!
Tell Mukaido's granddaughter, Manaka...
That hers is still pales in
comparison to the old woman's.
When did you come to the surface?
My job is to watch over
the people of the sea.
However, everyone's asleep now,
so I was rather bored.
So you were keeping an eye
on us since we were awake?
Then you should have come out sooner!
I am the scale of the Sea God.
The more I'm in the sea,
the more I'm bound...
Hm?
What a wonderful smell.
You have a womanly scent.
Wha—
What the hell are you talking about?!
I didn't notice this
the other day, but...
Oh, and your Ena's
developed quite nicely.
R-Really?
Stop it, you perverted scale!
So, what did you want?
Weren't you looking for me because
you wanted to ask me something?
Er, yeah!
Uroko-sama, what's going
to happen to the surface?
Is it going to keep getting
even more messed up?
And what about everyone in Shishio?
When are they going to wake up?
Is that all you want to ask?
Manaka...
What happened to Manaka?
Is she never going to be
able to go back to the sea?
And she's forgotten a lot of stuff
from before she fell asleep...
What?
What the hell is happening to her?!
Manaka had become the Ojoshi-sama...
The Ojoshi-sama?!
The girl who became the
Sea God's sacrifice
and had his child...
She came while leaving someone
she loved on the surface.
Seeing that she was never
able to forget those feelings
and started to shut everything out,
the Sea God returned her to the surface...
Taking something in return.
I know that story.
The Sea God took her Ena, right?
What does that have
to do with anything?
The Ojoshi-sama returned to the surface,
and many years passed.
The Sea God lost his life,
and his body melted into the sea,
becoming one with it.
And one of the scales that
fell off at that time is me.
Even now, some of the fragments
of the Sea God's emotions
that had melted into
the sea still remain.
Fragments of his emotions?
Neither good nor evil.
Rage, sadness, happiness, envy.
All raw emotions.
The sacred fire is also
a part of the Sea God,
but it's a bit more structured...
Well, it's something like his consciousness.
It wishes to stop whatever is about
to befall the sea and the surface.
However, the fragments of his
emotions that remain in the sea
felt the air of the world of humans.
And at times, they become the menace
of the sea, acting on their own.
At that time,
Manaka was dragged in by
the Sea God's feelings,
and became the sacrifice.
Apparently the feelings when the Sea God
was longing for the Ojoshi-sama had remained.
At the graveyard of Ojoshi-samas,
Manaka was wrapped up in even thicker
Ena and became the sacrifice.
Because of that, the
sea had calmed itself,
and the end of the surface was halted.
The fragments of emotions that were left
in the sea and the sacred fire became one,
and an equilibrium was reached.
However...
a certain sentiment within Manaka did
not accept that she was the sacrifice,
and tried to free itself.
That sentiment destroyed her Ena,
and started flowing little by little,
creating a small current.
The current that led to Shioshishio?
The tiny grains of Ena that flowed
from Manaka bumped into each other,
making a sound,
and that is what the girl
from the surface heard.
Then that was...
So that sound was Manaka-san's Ena...
No, Manaka-san's emotions...
Where are Miuna and Hikari-kun?
Not back yet.
I wonder if they're okay...
They're not little kids anymore.
There's nothing to worry about.
When you went to look for Manaka,
the Sea God's fragments of emotions thought
that Ojoshi-sama would be taken away,
took something away from Manaka,
just as it had done before.
Namaka, rawr!
That is when the Ena protecting
Manaka came off all at once.
Rawr!
Because Manaka was the
sacrifice, the sea was calm.
Because it lost Manaka,
the end of the surface
may come even sooner.
What the hell does that mean?
You're saying that the
surface got all messed up
because of Manaka?
So you're saying it was better if
Manaka had stayed asleep in the sea forever?!
What the hell?!
What the hell is that supposed to mean?!
Calm down.
Even though I said it
may come even sooner,
we're talking about after you die as
well as long after your children die.
U-Um...
You said that something was taken,
and that's when her Ena came off...
Then the thing stolen from
Manaka-san wasn't her Ena?
Oh, yeah...
Then what...
Hikari, you are in love
with Manaka, are you not?
Wh—
That doesn't have to do
with anything right now!
Your feelings for her may
never... reach Manaka.
Actually, no one's may ever reach her.
God damn it!
Hikari?!
The thing that Manaka lost...
is...
Rawr! Boom!
Is...
the heart to fall in love with someone.
All right, how about this?!
I'm not gonna lose!
Take that!
Manaka is now unable to love anyone.
Oh no, you got me!
Oh, welcome home.
Miuna-chan, Hii-kun.
Are you doubting Manaka's feelings?!
It's selfish to say that it's better
to not be able to love someone!
Well, Manaka looks
like she's having fun.
If you lose the ability
to love someone...
I won't lose it!
Episode Twenty-Three:
Who Do These
Feelings Belong To?
I won't lose it...