Yo, pay your rent, dumbass! Scum!
Korai House Landlord Daihatsu Meika
Mom, another hot sake, please.
The hell are you doing?
And what are you here for?
Don't play dumb! I'm here to collect!
You need to pay this rent you owe!
Penis rent?
Pay. This. Rent!
What's the matter with you?
Did something happen?
Yesterday's exorcism didn't go so well.
Fake Exorcist Chichibu Rabura
They called me a scammer and a fraud.
Necromancy
So you're drowning your sorrows?
I know I don't have spirit powers!
My family has been priestesses for generations.
I'm the only one with tan skin.
What's that got to do with anything?
Besides, there's no such thing as spirits.
You don't believe in spirits?
Of course not.
Who's that, then?
C-Cut that out.
I'm kidding.
What?
It came from downstairs!
Punch Line
Hey, Ito, open up!
What was that noise just now?
That was, uh... It was me. I screamed.
Huh?
You know how the air's been really dry lately?
That's why you screamed like that?
Yeah, it's refreshing to scream.
That's why...
Huh, it sounded like a beast's roar.
Of course not!
We can't have pets in Korai House, right?
Hey! What was it that time?
Man, I'm itchy!
I'm so itchy...
Wait, you're telling me that sound
was you scratching yourself?
I have dry skin.
Hold up!
You're scratching way too much!
I just picked a scab.
That's a huge scab.
There's an "ahem bug" caught in my throat.
Are you seriously okay?
Um, yeah, I'm fine. I'm good now.
I don't know what's going on,
but you should go to the hospital.
Later.
The Lace of Compassion
Right now, you're like a
baby sucking on a breast.
No one knows when you'll wake
up to suck on the breast,
and no one knows when you'll
finish sucking on the breast
and go back to sleep.
You just want an excuse
to say "breast," don't you?
The point is, a newly disembodied spirit's
moment of awakening is erratic.
The bus hijacking was on the 21st,
and today's the 23rd.
Is that why I missed a day?
Yes.
Then I could go back in time like before—
No, you can't.
At your current level,
you can only land at the bottom
of the Space-Time Valley.
What the heck is a Space-Time Valley?
The valley between the countless
breasts spread across space-time.
You can call it the Boobies Valley if you want.
No way.
With a low spirit power level,
even if you land near a nipple,
you'll slip towards the bottom of the valley.
Do you have to use boob analogies
to explain everything?!
Just look at this.
Dude, seriously, what's up with that?!
You let me see those on purpose, don't you?
Streaming:
What the hell is he doing?
There must be something
suspicious in that box.
But who took my body, anyway?
It's definitely a spirit entity.
Otherwise, it couldn't possess you.
For now, I'll have to focus on
finding the Nandala Gandala.
Then I can get a grip on all my problems.
Like a pair of boobies.
Enough!
Oh, what's wrong,
Miyako-chan? You look upset.
Doctor, my friend's had her heart broken.
She's really depressed.
Then you need Cheermancy.
Cheermancy
Make him
smile again!
Cheermancy?
Written with "happiness"
and "cheer." Cheermancy.
With this technique developed by NASA,
you can be rid of all your
woes in the blink of an eye!
My, how wonderful!
Now, let's have the doctor
teach us how it works.
* Please prepare the included "Mask 1."
Turtle, turtle.
Are you an exorcist, Rabura-san?
Gliese
Yes, sort of...
What a great occupation!
It's mysterious and charming!
I'd like to speak with you sometime.
Please meet with me in person.
What should I do?
He might hate me if he finds
out I'm a fake exorcist.
Oh, man.
An IT venture CEO, my ass.
He's so full of himself.
Rejected again?
Don't say "again"!
Besides, it's not like I got rejected.
What was it, then?
I saw him walking with a girl.
That's it?
They were holding hands.
Not like this, but like this.
Rabura, are you a virgin?
H-Huh?!
I'm not a v-virgin!
I heard from my sister.
You've never dated anyone before?
She's one to talk. She used to run a
24-hour live feed of her private life.
That's true.
But I wonder why she decided
to study abroad in the US.
Who's left to hear me vent?
Yu-tan, hear me out!
That IT venture pervert...
Rabura-san, I made apple pie.
Idol Group "She's Mei" Member
Narugino Mikatan
Would you like—
Huh?! What happened?!
Your Tsugaru accent is back.
Your profile says you're from Tokyo.
That might not bode well for She's Mei.
Uh, have some apple pie.
If there's not enough cinnamon, you can use this.
Strange Juice-san, please
comment on the incident.
Theater hostage situation safely resolved
I—
Hey, why'd you turn it off?!
Huh? Oh, I thought you weren't watching.
I'm glad, though.
About what?
The bus hijacking.
You said you were on that bus, right?
Oh, yeah.
One wrong move and I would've been dead.
Thanks to Akina.
Yuta-kun's sister?
Yeah.
Akina was visiting home, but she
said she had to go back right away,
so Yuta and I saw her off at the airport.
And on the way home...
You got caught up in that incident.
I hate turtles!
I see nothing! I see nothing!
Rabura's Pet Kamenishi-kun
What the heck is this smell?
Cinnamon?
What do you want this time?
The rent is—
A pigeon?!
What do you think?
What should I think?
Why are you dressed like that?
I actually learned it.
Learned what?
Cheermancy
Cheermancy.
Necromancy?
Necromancy
Just watch this.
General liberal, deflation spiral,
natural mineral, come on!
That's Cheermancy?
Yup.
Yeah?
So you can do necromancy just by
wearing that mask and singing?
Don't make me laugh!
You aren't laughing.
What are you pissed about?
Of course I'm pissed!
I'm working through some serious problems!
That's why I'm here!
If necromancy were that easy,
I'd have no problems.
Maybe you just lack the sense for it.
My sense has nothing to do with it!
Of course it does!
You doofus!
Damn it, what the hell was that?!
Incoming Call
Yuta-sensei
Yes?
You finally answered.
MMO Vegetable Hikiotani Ito
I went to your place yesterday.
What? Why?
I wanted to let you know something.
And I wanted to hear what you
thought about that script.
Hey, why don't you come to school already?
If you're nervous about it, I'll...
Sorry, someone's here.
Bye.
Hey, wait—
Good evening.
General liberal, deflation spiral,
natural mineral, come on!
Spirit-san, spirit-san, if you're here, uh...
Move this bottle!
Now!
Why don't you respond?
The bottle talked!
It's me.
Oh, it's you.
Respond?
But at my spirit power level,
the best I can do is roll a pencil.
Cinnamon.
There are cinnamon particles
scattered throughout the room.
Cinnamon has a strange effect
that increases your spirit power.
That's such a random premise.
Just give it a try.
How is this gonna cut it?!
Don't mess with necromancy!
What the hell am I doing?
Move. Move!
No way.
Advanced Spirit Power User
Well, let's eat.
W-Wait, didn't you promise you'd
leave once you gave me the pie?
Oh, this is fine.
No, it's not!
Is there something you don't want me to see?
N-No, nothing at all!
Okay, let's eat, then...
We don't have forks.
The forks are in the kitchen.
Okay.
What was that?
That was me.
You just screamed?
See?
Um, are you all right?
What?
You're hiding in your room
all the time these days.
You need to get some sun, or...
You'll get weird.
Psychologically, mentally...
I'm fine, really.
I go outside sometimes.
You don't look like it.
Your hair's a mess.
I know, I'll brush it for you.
Where's your hairbrush?
Found it!
Oh, that's...
Wow, your hair's redder than it looks.
D-Don't be so rude.
Sorry.
Hey, what's this?
C-Can't you tell? It's a salmon.
Why is it on the floor?
Wait, Ito-chan!
What?
That's not how you're supposed to eat it.
This is normal in my family.
Normal?
And what's that?
That's, uh, where I scratch my back.
Would it end up like that just
from scratching your back?
Shut up already!
I have spines starting to grow out of my back!
Like a stegosaurus.
That's definitely an illness.
Just leave me alone!
I-Ito-chan, what are you doing?
Okay, I get it, Ito-chan! Calm down!
Someone! Someone, come quick!
Monthly
Handstands for Beginners
Ito-chan's in trouble!
Salmon's so delicious!
It's filled with roe! So delicious!
Wh-What are you doing?
Are you possessed by a fox?
No, listen to this!
Ito-chan's back...
has spines growing out of it,
like a stegosaurus!
Isn't that bad?
She'd be better off being possessed by a fox.
I think she's about to evolve into
some other kind of creature.
Isn't that even worse?
Meika-emon!
Don't you have anything to stop an evolution?!
Do I look like I have a pocket on my belly?!
Psych!
A bear?!
What the heck?! Why is that creature here?!
Is it legal to keep bears?
This is my brother, Muhi.
Hikiotani Muhi.
He's a second grader and just
learned the times table for eight.
Now, Muhi, let's go back home.
That's such a lame lie!
Didn't I tell you? No pets in Korai House!
Rabura has one, though!
Turtles are okay.
They don't make noise or cause trouble,
and they don't damage the room.
But why is there a baby bear here?
I picked him up on a rainy day.
I found him crying in a box, and...
I told you not to lie.
It's true!
We have to report it to
the public health center.
Wait!
Move.
I won't.
I'm not letting anyone have Muhi.
He's the only one that understands me.
Hey, Meika, could you wait a bit?
Isn't it odd that a bear would
be abandoned in the rain?
That's true. It's not exactly a cat or a dog.
I think we should investigate first,
to find out why that baby bear was abandoned.
Fine.
However, if you can't find any
leads by the end of the year,
I won't hesitate to report him.
Got it?
Yeah!
I'm going to protect you, Muhi.
Hey, stop it, Muhi.
That tickles!
There you are!
Need something?
Yeah, kind of.
I was thinking about what
Ito-chan said earlier.
I wonder why Ito-chan
stopped going to school.
Who knows?
I've asked, but she won't tell me.
It's coming!
Quit wussing out, you K/D ratio freak!
Seriously?
Man, I can't believe the legendary
Torahachiro with the 4.85
K/D ratio lived next door.
You've been skipping
school to play, haven't you?
No wonder you got so good.
You're in a private girls' school, aren't you?
Why did you stop going?
You're insensitive.
Don't you think it's rude
to ask questions like that?
Sorry.
Oh!
How pretty...
I never knew there was such a place.
Something crappy happened at school.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Because you'd call me insensitive again.
Is that why you stopped going to school?
Insensitive.
It's why I started living here.
I got disowned.
Disowned?
Ito's dad is a board member
or something, on the metropolitan
assembly education committee.
It'd be bad if it got out that his
daughter refuses to go to school.
It might affect the next election.
So her cousin, Rabura-san,
introduced her to Korai House?
Yeah.
Ito-chan must be lonely.
I know!
Let's have a party!
A party?
Yeah, it's Christmas Eve
tomorrow night, right?
So...
We're going to invite Ito, too?
Of course! Everyone in Korai House!
Me, too?
Guys, listen to this.
There's something I forgot to tell you earlier.
Natural mineral, come on!
Now, mister spirit, do that thing again!
Wait, I have to do it here?!
Go!
I can't.
I guess I need the cinnamon to do it.
Hey, Rabura...
What?!
"Cheermancy"? As in, "happiness" and "cheer"?!
Of course.
There's no such thing as spirits.
Even if there were, I don't have spirit power.
But how'd that happen before, then?!
I'm, uh, sorry.
I've always admired my grandma and my mom.
But I don't have that kind of power.
I wanted to be able to do necromancy, too.
And...
General liberal, deflation spiral,
natural mineral, come on!
What are you guys doing?!
Who would've imagined this
"Cheermancy" would actually work?
Do you feel better?
Yeah.
Okay, I'll show you lesson two.
That's so random.
I'm up next, then.
You idiot.
Tomoda Chihaya
Hikiotani Ito
Subject: Video
Do you know about this video?
It's all over the internet right now.
[Viewer beware] This Year's Victims
List of this year's victims. Happy New Year, everybody.
Tags: horror, urban legends, Niconico danger zone, trauma
[Live Broadcast] "Harakiri Harassment"
Episodes 11-13 One-Time Broadcast
Shujo Manoto (17)
Koto Monami (17)
Iji Meiko (17)
Io Ruka (17)
Hikiotani Ito (17)
No...
Those are this year's victims.
Happy New Year...