Let’s have a White Festival!
Yeah, let's do it.
Just the five of us?
How would we do that?
We’ll figure it out.
We'll find a way somehow...
...because we've just gotta sing!
Music Practice Room Two
Choir Club Culture Fair | Beauties and the Frogs
Script - Miyamoto | - Wakana to coach everyone on their song parts
What’s the best case scenario?
Choreography - Sawa | Set - Tanaka | Props - Wien
Costumes - Wein? | Stage Crew - Everyone
(17 days to go)
That we get the school's permission.
And that people from
other clubs join us.
Basically, a regular culture fair
where loads of people come.
Then, worst case would be that
the school doesn't allow it?
And that we sing, alone,
in an empty gym?
The worst would be if
we can't sing at all!
That won't happen.
But I’d still prefer to
have a large audience.
If we can sing this song together,
we’ll think of each other
whenever we hear it,
no matter how far we’re
scattered after graduation.
We'll remember being invited,
and arguing, and...
Getting mad, and laughing, and...
Fighting, and losing, and...
Saying weird things, and...
Meeting great friends!
If a whole crowd of people
share that fun memory
with us by listening to our song,
remembering that would be
an encouragement to me, always.
Yeah!
All right, then we’ve
gotta make this happen.
Yeah, let's make it a
performance to remember!
Let's pour everything into this song
and step out into the future!
So cool!
Why was I the only one?
Episode 12
Piling Up and Rippling
We're collecting the trash from
the culture fair as well,
so please deposit it by the parking lot.
Okay.
Defective Metronomes | Culture
Fair Props (Made by Maeda)
Okita!
You scared me. What's up?
Could I, um,
take your picture?
What?
Um, yeah, I was just...
Why?
Hamachi... I mean,
I owe this guy a picture of you,
for helping me paint the sets.
But you know what, never mind.
Sorry for even mentioning it.
I don't mind.
What?
But make sure it’s flattering.
S-Sure.
You'll have to take it from above.
Does it make a difference?
Just do it.
Hurry up.
Okay, that looks good.
Tell the guy I'll have
a horse stomp on him
if the quality of his work is too low.
Sure, thanks.
Tanaka, I’m impressed!
Thanks, I guess.
Oh, what a goddess!
Look at this line... It's perfect.
She said she'd have a horse stomp
on you if the quality sucks.
I wouldn’t mind being
stomped on by her!
Okay, leave the rest to me!
I think this part flows nicely,
but it needs a bit more “oomph.”
Got it.
Okay, from the top.
Hey, where’d Wien's props go?
They’re gone?
Would Konatsu have them?
Where is she?
In a meeting, so she
shouldn't have them.
So I was right...
I thought I saw someone
with them earlier.
There they are!
I'll go to the dump!
Me, too!
As the White Festival’s been canceled,
any leftover budget
funds should be returned
to the school and—
Objection!
Pardon me?
I propose a cancellation of the
cancellation of the White Festival!
The cancellation's already happened.
And you’re okay with that?
We can't do anything about the school,
but don't you find it questionable
that they canceled
the fair just because
of some construction?
We all put a lot of effort
into getting ready!
So many people were
looking forward to it!
Maybe this isn't a big deal for those
who'll be in big competitions
or pursuing professional careers,
but some of us don’t have
any other stage to stand on!
Personally, I don’t want to become
the kind of sad adult who blindly
follows wrong directions
just because they came from above!
At least let the student council
propose to keep the fair.
There wouldn’t be enough time
for our club to prepare a song.
And you call us amateurs?!
If you're so great, put your money
where your mouth is!
Order, please.
We'll take a vote.
Those in favor of the
choir club's suggestion,
please raise your hand.
It can’t hurt to ask, right?
Your proposal is denied.
Fine! But we’re still gonna sing!
Did you find them?
Tanaka, why didn't you
stop them right away?
Now it's my fault?
You're the club president! You
should’ve taken better care of them!
Why didn't anybody notice?
But you saw it happen!
Not clearly!
Whether you get mad.
Whether you laugh.
The sun will set,
morning will come.
Each and every time.
I’ll just start over.
I might not be able to
finish them all, but...
Thanks for looking for them.
Yeah.
Sorry the student council
angle didn't work.
Not your fault.
We’ll just keep at it tomorrow.
Right.
Yeah! Now let’s go home.
Time to go.
Here you are. Will that be all?
I'm about to leave.
Okay. I left the flowers by the door.
Sorry I can't make it.
It's fine.
I'll tell Mom that
you're hard at work.
See you later!
Bye. Have a good day.
Excuse me.
Oh, sorry.
I haven’t been
able to create a single
lasting thing on my own.
The song we wrote together...
The choir club we created...
Nothing I've done compares.
That school was the only
tie to music I had left,
and now even that’s...
I guess,
in the end, you were the
only one the music loved.
Pardon my intrusion.
Vice principal!
Sakai Family
Would you mind listening to this?
It's the song I wrote with my mother.
The phrase you used for the
refrain is a bit unconventional.
But I can sense Mahiru in it.
I was able to finish it thanks
to the advice you gave me,
that music should be fun.
That’s what Mahiru said.
She was constantly telling
me to have fun.
I’ve got no right to give advice.
But for me, enjoying it wasn’t enough.
The support of my friends
was equally important.
They encouraged me
through my struggles.
They're all so different from me,
but they’re honest and determined.
We fought, but we also worked together.
I know my mother had a
friend like that, too.
Someone to have fun with.
Someone to share her worries.
Mom, I finished the song
we promised to write.
Sorry it took so long.
I’m glad I could create this
song with you and my friends.
I'll treasure it always, for
bringing us all together.
Thank you, Mom.
Konatsu's not here yet?
Haven't had a morning
meeting in a while.
Was he here all night?
Oh, morning, guys.
Good morning.
You're gonna wear yourself out.
I'm fine.
I wanted to do the costumes after
I finished the props, but...
Leave that to me.
You know how to make costumes?
I'll figure it out. I want to help.
You're kinda clumsy, so be careful.
Let's all try to come
up with a solution.
I know!
If it comes down to it,
draping these over us
might look pretty cool.
So, Wakana, I was practicing
yesterday and...
Have a little faith in me.
I have faith in you.
And?
Could you teach me how to make these?
You? Have you ever sewn before?
No, but I know how to thread a needle!
The sewing machine is backwards.
Why are you guys so set on
having the White Festival?
Um, well, Miyamoto and
Sakai have their reasons,
but for me it's just
that I like singing
and I want to finish what I started.
Whoa! What was that?!
All right, enough.
You'll break the machine.
No, please! I can't give up!
That's why I'm offering
to do it for you.
You're amazing.
What can I do to help?
You can't make five
costumes by yourself.
Can you guys give me a hand over here?
Sure!
Oh, and get Kuwata from
class 2 and Hara from class 3.
They'd be good to have on board.
Okay.
And get bean buns from the canteen!
Got it!
For everyone!
What?!
We'd very much like to
grant your request,
since you seem to have
your heart set on it.
But if the board,
I mean the school, decided
to cancel the fair,
we're not sure we should be
advertising it without their okay.
It could cause serious problems.
What did the board say to you?
Oh, nothing...
It's just, with what they're
planning to build...
We can't go against them.
The region desperately needs the money.
I'm begging you!
I want as many people as
possible hear our song,
even if it's just one more!
We have to do more than
advertising at school.
If they're not interested in our song,
they don't have to come.
But maybe some of them would want to
be there to show their
support for our futures!
I know there are some
things I just have to let go,
but I don't think the culture
fair is one of them!
It means so much to us!
Please!
Putting up posters in our
shops should be fine.
Quite a few graduates from
Shiro High live around here,
so I'm sure they'd want
to stop by one last time,
before it's shut down.
I'm actually one of them.
Oh? Were you a music major?
No, no, I was just a regular student.
Here's the music for
Sakai-san's song and a recording.
It's still pretty rough,
but you'll at least be
able to hear us sing.
Okay.
You know, I like the
way you play piano.
It's gentle, yet strong.
Thank you.
If you can't do it, we'll
just record Wakana.
But we'd prefer to have
your accompaniment.
No.
Don't drag others into
your personal whims,
when the school's facing a crisis.
Shouldn't we be singing
because there's a crisis?
Hirohata-san, why do you sing?
You're not planning to make
a career of it, right?
I may not like you,
but I know you love singing.
We did used to be in the same club.
Let's sing together!
What's wrong with you?
Come on, sing with us!
Cut it out!
As club president, I can't go off and do
whatever I want, like some people.
Go preach your childish "I love
singing!" to someone else.
I'm way more serious
about music than that!
You think I'm doing this on a whim?
Quiet in the halls.
Is everyone inside?
Ah, yes!
Begin practice.
Yes, ma'am!
Ueno-san, you too.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm sorry.
A Brighter Future For You
This might not be a big deal
for students participating
in big competitions
or pursuing professional careers,
but some of them don't have
any other stage to stand on.
Do those students really need a stage?
Huh?
Of course they do.
I don't want to become
the sad kind of adult
who tramples my students' dreams.
I'm sure this has been hard on you.
Once it all blows over,
you should celebrate with this.
Why would you want to
stir up trouble now,
when everything's been settled?
I spotted this in town.
The Final White Festival of Shirohamazaka High
Shirohamazaka High Choir
and Sometimes Badminton Club
I don't want any unnecessary discord
with the locals over this.
Construction is already
behind schedule.
Students are not to be on school grounds
past 5 P.M. on school days,
and not at all on Sundays and holidays.
Violators will be suspended from school.
Isn't that a bit harsh?
All you need to worry about
are the construction delays,
and your retirement.
White Festival
Finally Tomorrow!!
The props and costumes are done.
He said he'd finish the backdrops
by pulling an all-nighter.
Please, sun! Please, sun! Please!
Anyone who comes to see
us in this downpour is
worth their weight in gold.
What are you, a rain whisperer, Konatsu?
All right! We've done all we could!
It will soon be 5 P.M.
All students must return
to their homes immediately.
Tomorrow's the big day.
Even if nobody comes...
My dad will be there, for sure.
After all we've done,
if only one person shows...
...it'd look pretty pathetic.
Who cares.
A lot of things were
out of our control.
But it was still fun, right?
Think it'll stop if we wait?
Nope.
You expected too much.
But Konatsu's a rain whisperer...
There's no rain that won't end.
Okay, let's sing.
Right here?
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit!
Final Episode
Sunny Days and Crying and Sometimes Singing.
What will you do, Sawa?
We'll do it, even if you
won't acknowledge it.