Hajime-chan, you were already
my favorite the moment I met you.
I felt you accepted me
for who I was right away,
and that made me so happy.
You're always like that, aren't you?
You don't care at all about
appearances or labels.
You look right at the person in front of you.
You bypass conventions that
everyone's going along with,
with such careless ease.
Well, like...
There's no point in cutting them down.
Oh, more importantly,
it's like, I haven't really met them!
Yeah, that's it!
That's why even Utsutsu,
who never opened up to anyone before...
Whoa!
Are you trying to reject
the basic premise of Gatchaman?
I've been alive for three centuries,
but I've never met anyone like you.
I have a feeling that you'll
change us lonely caged birds
like you fold origami shapes.
I've never felt this way
in the G-team before!
Senpai!
Huh?
What would you think if I died?
What?
O-Of course I'd be sad.
That's right, girl.
You're like the sun that
shines brightly on us,
no, everyone on this planet.
You're way too bright!
You're the G-team's shining sun!
Hajime, you know... back then...
Every single day, I wanted
to vanish and disappear.
I'm gloomy...
You can't.
I can because my body is weird.
Wow. That's great.
It's not great.
I felt that way because I didn't
know why I had been born.
That's why I used to hate you because you
were always so full of energy.
I thought you'd take OD away from me.
But I began to notice
who you were as a person.
I'm gloomy...
Utsutsu-chan, you're fine
just the way you are.
I wondered why you would care
to look at me when I was such a failure.
And I used to hate you so much.
I guess things like this really happen.
I found myself starting
to want to be noticed by you,
Okay, go!
A present to Utsutsu-chan
for a good deed!
What?
and be with you.
We had a lot of fun
today, Utsutsu-chan!
What?
Let's play hide-and-seek together again!
I was so happy...
What's the matter?
O-Origami.
I'm happy now that I was born,
because I was able to meet you.
But I'm still just me.
Go, Bird!
That's okay, right?
You told me it was...
I'm the leader, Paiman.
Hey, Newbie.
You were trouble from the very beginning.
I was always scolding you.
I thought that you didn't take
Gatchaman duties seriously enough.
I thought you were a disappointment.
But...
you had already noticed from early on
that I was always running.
You knew that I was clinging
to the god-like JJ-sama,
because he was insurance
against my own fear
and pathetic indecisiveness.
I was caving in under
the pressure of being the leader.
I knew I must not run.
I knew I must make a decision.
But, I just couldn't muster the confidence...
I was a failure as the leader.
But you said...
That's not true!
If you need to run,
you should run the best you can!
Then you can just take your time to think.
I was shocked.
Pai-Pai.
Most things in life are unexpected.
You were totally right.
I began to think for myself.
I began to face who I was:
a pathetic loser.
That was when I finally realized
what you had been asking of me...
what I really wanted to do.
I found myself repeating
the words you'd said to me.
Do you love this country?
Hey, Newbie.
Listen up.
I'll only say it once.
You're the first human to understand how I felt.
I...
I am the leader...
of the Gatchaman,
protectors of this planet!
Berg-Katze is nothing to fear!
Bow down before my courageous wings!
Go, Bird!
Bite and Build!
Transform!
You're so cool, Panda Man!
Run, kids!
Okay!
All right, I'm heading out.
Miss, when I met you,
I thought of myself as a little shit.
After meeting JJ and many other aliens,
I felt we had such a small existence.
I thought of you as a useless newbie, too.
I thought there was nothing for
us to reach an understanding on.
But...
you weren't an average Jane.
I wondered if you might
be someone extraordinary.
But I didn't want to accept that.
Achieving world peace?
I had started to give up
on my goal as being too naive.
Oh, it's MESSY-chan!
All right!
Okay!
But you continued to believe and pressed on.
Utsutsu?
Doing that will kill you!
I want to save them!
You know that, right?
But I want to save them!
You set all of our hearts on fire,
in a big red blaze.
I'm gloomy...
Hey, give us a hand here, too!
This is how it should be...
I am no one special...
I'm just...
Thank you, Jou-san...
And now, I...
I can tell you this now.
Way too...
lame!
You're amazing!
Do you have any idea what
crazy shit you just pulled?
Humans are still worth saving!
Go, Bird!
Could you be...
the new team member?
I'm Ichinose Hajime!
I think I somehow became
a Gatchaman today.
At the time, I...
It's Senpai and me!
...thought that we'd gotten
ourselves a troublemaker newbie.
I was totally confused by
everything you said and did.
Someone might feel awful,
but can't skip work.
Someone might be sick, too.
Maybe it's not what I thought.
We had a huge fight afterwards.
Wh-What the...
You idiot!
I just didn't understand you back then.
I could only butt heads with you.
But, one day, it occurred to me that...
Newbie, you should just follow
Sugane's orders, for now!
Boo!
Hey, it's not bad.
I'm not cut out for this, after all.
It's fine.
Everyone's is different.
Hey!
What are you doing?
You have to be kidding me...
MESS-chan!
Good morning!
Nice to meet you!
I think we've now met!
Hey, it's not safe.
Stop.
You...
...you're not just some weirdo.
Senpai, aren't there times
when you find yourself taking
action without even thinking about it?
I think you've taught me...
Hey!
The time is now!
That's what heroes do!
...that if you see the world in front of
you from a different perspective...
We don't need your prophecies anymore.
This is our planet.
So, we'll do as we wish.
That is all I have to say.
...you will find a new answer to your questions
that belongs only to you.
Reveal your names!
If you will not, then listen!
We are...
the wings that protect this planet!
We're the Gatchaman!
I wasn't the only one who had that insight.
I think everyone did.
That's why we
could take flight from the cramped bird cage.
All right!
Let's all work together to protect Tachikawa.
Three, two...
Gatcha!
X!
Can you see me?
Rui...?
X!
Rui-kun?
Hmm? X, my friend?
Oh, well.
I don't need any friends.
As long as I have this NOTE, I'm invincible!
Tachikawa Live Updates Thread
But I want to know if I'm truly invincible.
And the truth is...
It's show time!
X!
Are you watching this city?!
This wasn't what we were trying to do, is it?
I...
I don't want to see any more bloodshed!
X!
Answer me!
Rui?
X!
Rui,
did you see the sunset yesterday?
I did.
It was beautiful.
I thought so, too.
How joyous...
What's up, Rui-kun?
Hajime-chan, my friend came back.
Great!
Let's connect the Tachikawa team
with everyone through GALAX, then!
Hey, everyone. X came back!
Please look to GALAX to figure
out your next course of action!
Understood!
I've got this!
Phoenix Dive!
Rending Gale Blade!
Sugane, isn't this nostalgic?
Yes!
X, what's the GALAX penetration
rate among Tachikawa citizens?
Approximately sixty percent.
108,234 out of 180,000
are registered users.
That's less than I expected.
Huh?
The Gatchannel?
Yeah, I want you to tell the people
something as their Prime Minister.
Oh, no way.
No one will listen to me.
They all look down
on the Prime Minister, anyway.
Then why don't you quit being one?
Huh?
Try to imagine that you've
resigned, in your heart.
I'm sure you'll feel a lot better!
Oh, by the way, the show's already on.
Huh? You're kidding.
Please Wait
I wrote everything down here.
I'm counting on you, Suga-yan!
Su...
Suga-yan?!
You want me to handle it, right?
You can count on me.
X is back!
X, we need intel on the
injured and the disaster!
Understood.
Injured people requesting assistance
are marked by a human icon.
Fires are marked by a flame icon.
Okay.
Uh, I'm Sugayama.
Gatcha....
Uh... So Tachikawa citizens...
Please register on GALAX as soon as possible.
Use GALAX to figure out
what you can do... Huh?
What's this?
Lame-o Prime Minister
Who are you calling "lame"?!
Bite and Build!
To all G members!
I will keep the CROWDS
coming from Hino at bay!
Jou, cover the train station!
Sugane, defend the school!
Understood!
Utsutsu, protect the river!
Roger!
Go, my fragments!
Understood!
I'm gloomy...
Hajime, cover the park!
Sure thing, Pai-Pai!
"Die"?
How can you even say that
to someone you've never met?
I have a family, too!
They'd be heartbroken
if they were watching right now!
Have you ever thought of that? Huh?
Wow.
Don't give me that crap!
I'm just me!
Keep going, Suga-yan!
Sugayama respect
Each location of the CROWDS is marked by an X,
and the Gatchaman's combat
locations are marked by stars.
Please split up and protect
the citizens from the CROWDS.
Roger!
Everyone, don't worry!
There are no CROWDS
in this area, at the  moment.
Even if they attack,
we, with the help of the Gatchaman,
will hold them off with everything we've got!
Thank goodness...
Thanks.
We're counting on you!
Stay strong!
GALAX users, please keep an eye on updates
and relay information to non-GALAX users!
You fix it, bastard!
Negligence
"You fix it, bastard"?
You're the leader,
aren't you?
You're living life
off our taxes!
The country's in danger!
So you think someone else will
always figure it out, don't you?!
GALAX is too scary to use!
Now you're pissed at us?
He's pissed lol
and you're the PM? lol
Pissed
True colors showing!
True self's showing, SG
And when they don't, you'll bitch and moan.
He's hopeless
Dude, he's scary
Is he srsly yelling at us?
Talk about holier than thou
Don't put it on us--
But what did you do?!
Why are we getting blamed?
Dude, calm down
Don't make it sound so easy!
Have you ever done anything
for this nation, even once?
Don't look at me
You've been found out
Srsly, a lecture?
Well...
You're telling us that?
Nope
Sry, dude
You don't even go to elections!
If I had to pick, nope
Sry, bout that, dude
Touché
If you've got complaints,
try a hand at being the Prime Minister!
The Prime Minister's lost it.
I'm starting to like him!
And go change the nation!
Er... Please excuse me
for what I just said.
I have felt utterly isolated ever
since I became the Prime Minister.
Huh? Seriously?
What's wrong?
Freezing up?
Hey lolll
The heck?
Hellooo
Tech difficulty lolll
Say something
I... I am declaring a state
of emergency for Tachikawa City!
Looking at his
planner again
Nervous
Actually, that
planner's super cute!
Wait, wut?
Srsly?
State of Emergency-----
Suga went all out
We will now distribute smart phones
free of charge to all Tachikawa citizens!
What does that mean?
??????
He seems weak
Wut? lolll
You can do it if you try
What now?
Wut? How? lol
The hell?
Someone explain in 3 lines
Wut...?
Srsly?!
We ask that everyone register on GALAX!
Gimme
Gimme all
Why lolll
Gimme!
Where?
What about
Hino residents?
Do we have to
give them back?
Registering sux
Just take 'em all!
Hurry!
Everyone, please register on GALAX, now!
Who doesn't have a smart phone?
Who's having trouble registering?
Prime Minister Sugayama.
Y-Yes? You talking to me?
There is chaos on Itsukaichi-Kaido
Avenue due to citizens
trying to flee the city.
Your abilities as Prime
Minister are needed.
Me? Needed?
Go, Suga-yan
Go handle it
You're the PM
Hurry up!
You're the only one
who can handle it
Go forth, final Hero!
Thy name is Sugayan!
All right!
I'm gonna do this!
Rui, eighty-two percent
of the citizens have safely evacuated.
Good! We're almost there.
Abandon your vehicles and
head to the evacuation zone!
Many of the citizens
attempting to leave the city
do not like the riot
police's announcements.
Okay!
Give me that for a sec!
Yes, Ma'am.
We understand your desire to leave the city.
However, doing so en masse will cause chaos.
Leaving the city does not necessarily
guarantee your safety.
All of us want to reach safety!
Please help us keep you safe!
Huh? How can we trust cops?!
I'm not gonna put up with this!
Prime Minister!
Citizens!
Please follow evacuation orders
and remain in the city!
It's the Prime Minister!
Why's he here?
I'm not running anymore!
I will fight with Tachikawa
citizens and the Gatchaman!
Please believe in us, and do what we ask!
Citizens!
Have you finished registering on GALAX?
Please look at the icon next to the X button!
What?
What's going on?
If you click that icon,
you will obtain the ability of CROWDS!
To overcome this unprecedented crisis,
all of us need the ability of CROWDS!
They will be the CROWDS of Justice!
Defeat the malicious CROWDS
and restore peace to Tachikawa!
No!
That's not me!
I'm here!
I am Sugayama!
It's Katze.
No!
Stop!