Come at me from any direction!
Yuta...
Yuta?
Wait!
What are you doing?
C'mon, we have a contract.
Yuta, fulfill the contract.
Even I realize that this has to be a dream.
But the fact that I am having this dream...
means I may be harboring expectations.
In other words, well...
What?!
Ow!
I thought so.
What is that you're doing?
Wicked Lord Shingan is generating
a Zero-G magnetic field.
The gravity within this room
is now under my control.
Y-Yuta, are you okay?
Hey, what was that noise?
It's an emergency! Yuta!
Why you little...
Emergency...
Knock that off!
Yuta, that hurts!
My current mobility is too limited
to evade attack.
Magical Devil Girl in Pursuit
Life function critical.
Your roller shoes are banned
for the foreseeable future!
That is what you get for
putting a hole in my ceiling!
That can't be right! I obtained
a permit from the Committee!
What committee?
Gasp! Did they have a hand in this?!
If so, I must hurry before
the situation becomes dire.
Either her chunibyo is getting worse,
or she's having a relapse.
We may fulfill our contract as we see fit!
Maybe if I hadn't said all that to her,
by now we'd be...
Yuta?
No, no, no, no! Not, not, not, not!
Rikka and I aren't like that!
I said what I said because
I thought it was the right solution.
Mobility confirmed!
Well, don't!
What is it now?
Wicked One gale force heroic blast!
It's working!
No, not at all.
So what? Am I the enemy now?
No.
I will summon the Dark Flame Dragon within you.
Dark Flame Dragon?
Yes.
The Dark Flame Dragon
is a mutation of the Black Flame Dragon having gained dark powers.
It is the source of the
Dark Flame Master's powers...
...and it is your dragon soulmate.
And why do you need it right this moment?
The Enemy approaches.
I believe her to be a powerful magic user.
A magic user? Do you mean Toka?
No. I have already imprisoned
the Priestess within the Vatican...
...with the might of my dark powers.
Don't make her mad.
The magic user is even more powerful.
I fear this person is one of the demon elite...
...and so I must summon the Dark Flame Dragon.
That's my T-shirt!
The magical injection is completed.
I order you, on the name of
Wicked Lord Shingan...
...Dark Flame Dragon sleeping
within this man! Appear before me!
Stop that! Don't draw
summoning circles on my stuff.
Which actually looks pretty damned good.
Yuta, suit up!
I refuse!
Or at least I'd like to refuse...
...but I appreciate the effort this took.
Really?
But I can't just put it on either.
All right, I will put it on if you get
better marks than me on the next test.
If you get worse marks, the Dark Flame Dragon
will be confined. Deal?
Cheh!
Don't give me that 'cheh'!
Oh, no. I let my guard down.
Foolish Dark Flame Master!
I will show you the might of
Wicked Lord Shingan...
...in a way you will not soon forget!
YUTA TOGASHI
RIKKA TAKANASHI
They're nearly identical!
Be quiet! Now you are servant to a servant!
Master, you are awesome! My fervor is renewed!
Rikka, you really worked hard.
Naturally!
Now, Dark Flame Master!
You must now produce the Dark Flame Dragon
that resides within you for my master!
Who are you supposed to be?
Therefore, you will wear this.
And what is this?
As you can see, it is a magical girl costume.
I thought I had to wear a T-shirt!
You're awfully picky for a man.
How did a magical girl costume
enter the equation?!
The Dark Flame Dragon
responds powerfully to magic.
Therefore, the act of wrapping
your entire body in magic...
...will prompt it to appear.
I designed it to flatter you.
Dekomori and I co-produced it.
It is a true tour de force!
Don't worry. Through the all-seeing
Wicked Lord Shingan...
...I have measured your waist, hips and bust.
Are you aware that I'm a guy?
Due to the unfortunate fact that
there are no male magical girls...
...its production was fraught with difficulty.
So, I have prepared this.
Twin tails?!
Incidentally, your transformation call
is personalized just for you: "Brave Up!"
Enough!
Now, transform at once!
Yuta!
Kumin-senpai?
Understood! A deal is a deal!
Why are you removing your clothing?!
You must transform!
Like how?!
How did this happen? Let's see here.
Hey, it isn't bad at all...
...yeah, right.
Everyone, come wish with me!
Magical...
Whew, a flawless parabola.
I'll say!
How could you do that to my phone?!
Holy moley! Nibutani putting the moves
on Togashi in drag!
Erase it!
Move it.
Ooh, have you finished your transformation?
It looks really good on you. I am relieved.
I am not.
Yuta, speak the incantation!
I will not!
You look so cute, Togashi!
Wait, have you joined them, Kumin?!
Deko just happened to have this prototype.
Would you like to try it on?
No, thanks, I'm good.
Far-East Magical Napping
Society Summer Thereof
Hey, you! The angel! I'm here to make war!
Come on out, you...
It appears I am summoned.
How can you tell from that announcement?
I know, for I am an angel.
A deep black fallen angel to be precise.
Does that mean I have been
servant to a fallen angel?
That is a good development! Very smart!
I take my leave. Please exercise caution, Yuta.
We'll show you what kind of angels we can be!
Wicked Lord Shingan detection mode activated!
Location: the vicinity of the intercom room!
What's angelic about that?
And who was that on the intercom?
INTERCOM ROOM
I will look in this direction!
It's all yours.
Spatial breakaway!
She must be in the area.
It is you!
I knew you were the angel.
Now, are you a surviving angel,
or are you a new kind of angel?
Either way, you have perfect timing!
I am Sophia Ring SP Saturn VII!
I am the magical devil girl Sophia
the whole town is talking about.
I am otherwise known as "she who rules
the devilish magical seven holy lands!"
You'd do well to remember that!
I am the Wicked Lord Shingan,
the deep black fallen angel...
...Rikka Takanashi!
So, you are the Wicked Lord Shingan?
I could not ask for a better opponent.
Very well, let us commence the war!
Fine. Wicked Lord Shingan, activate!
Field, deploy!
Imprisoned King Containment Ring!
Devil Lord, recognized.
Magical power, released.
Be destroyed, real.
Cherubim aria.
Blow up, synapses!
Seraphim, descend!
Banishment This World!
Cyndrilical metaphysical!
That was an impressive display of ability.
You are definitely the angel I took you to be.
I sense an unpleasant premonition
from you. So you must die.
Split open, Door of Darkness!
Release the darkness within.
Utilize the power of the King of Demise
to scatter the fictitious ...
The ultimate magic so soon?!
...and conduct me to the finale!
Schwarz Aschenputtel!
Vulcanus Shield!
The shield was improvised,
but that was real power!
Very clever, fallen angel Wicked Lord Shingan.
Sophia just may have to take off
the kid gloves with you.
Don't waste your time.
I'm so sorry, but I am a magical devil girl...
...quite unlike your typical
powder-puff magical girl.
How many of my Thousand Phoenix
do you think you can dodge?
Maximum shield!
Firebird Flame Flash!
Overconfidence is your own worst enemy!
A marionette?!
Infinity system, activate!
Crimson Vermillion Flame.
Entwine the darkness and become dark flame.
Aria magic?!
Be entombed in the abyss!
Onyx Flame Cannon!
Suppressive defense!
Shichimiya.
Hey, Shichimiya!
It's Hero.
What?!
STAFF ROOM
You know better than that.
You can't enter a school
you don't attend without permission.
I'm sorry.
Allow me to explain!
Satone Shichimiya is a girl I hung out with
in Year One of middle school.
As a matter of fact, she is the Patient Zero
who caused my chunibyo outbreak.
I heard the way she spoke,
saw her in invisible combat...
...decided it was awesome, and imitated her.
Incidentally, both the Dark Flame Master...
...and "Be enveloped in the flames
of darkness and disappear!"
...both sort of came from her.
Wow, this is great. Is this your hideout, Hero?
Yuta, that one is dangerous. Stand back.
Do you want to resume our battle,
Deep Black Fallen Angel?
Apparently Shichimiya, in her chunibyo way,
decided that Rikka is a fallen angel,
I'll make you regret ever picking a fight with Sophia!
then deduced from her uniform which school
she attends, and came to see her.
I'll show you the power of a magical devil girl!
I never knew she had taken a turn for the worse.
Do not push your luck!
I will take you out next time.
Don't.
Sorry, but I have to go home early.
What?!
Nana told me to walk Shichimiya home.
Very well, we will celebrate our
reunion by raising a glass to the posthumous world!
Too close!
Yes, yes, but only with juice.
Later! You really haven't
changed a bit, have you?
I'm surprised trackers from the
Organization were still around.
You should exercise caution.
Here.
Now, let us drink!
I have to be straight with you.
I'm through with all that.
Through?
Yes.
Do you mean you're moving up from
Level 7 to a Level 8 hero?
No! It's over, finished, done!
No more fires of darkness
and no more Dark Flame Master!
I'm having a distinctive feeling of deja vu.
Hero, did you look into the angel's eye?
No! I am not a hero anymore.
I am an average Year Two high school student!
You, Hero?
Yeah. Actually, I haven't been called "hero"
in more than three years.
I see. That sounds boring.
Boring? How?
It's boring because it's boring.
The world is such a big, interesting place!
What's with you? We're going.
So, how do you get home?
Well, let's see...
You take this train?
Yeah.
And get off here?
And cross this bridge?
Yeah!
But this is...
You live right above me.
Huh? So the Togashi nameplate is yours, Hero?
Don't call me that.
Are you living with Wicked Lord Shingan?!
How do you know that?!
Crimson Vermillion Flame.
Entwine the darkness and become dark flame.
Be entombed in the abyss!
Onyx Flame Cannon!
Wicked Lord Shingan ultimate magic.
Purgatorial Fascination!
Um, what should I do?
Purgatorial fascination...
...is one of Wicked Lord Shingan's
eight deep secrets.
It is his most powerful attack.
A provisional magical devil girl such as
yourself could not possibly resist it.
O-oh, I get it. Okay...
Ooh, Master! That is incredible!
It is not!
Honestly. How is that a magical girl?
That's just a commando girl.
Go away.
In the first place, magic is used
to make people happy.
The spirits who manipulate magic...
...were always thoroughly pure of heart.
They never resorted to brute force...
Wait, what?!
Memo, memo.
Morisummer, you're very knowledgeable.
This will help to know thy enemy.
I need to write this down.
Hey, stop taking notes!
What's with the magical girl stuff anyway?
That is the secret organization's hideout.
A huge factory.
It's suspicious. Very suspicious.
Shichimiya?
Yes.
Shichimiya... Shichimiya who?
Apparently she and Togashi used to be friends.
She and Rikka suddenly
started fighting each other.
An old friend?
Could she be his ex?
It's nothing like that.
No, you never can tell.
She goes to another school
but stormed into our school...
...and then went home with Togashi, right?
There's something to it.
Like what?
It's the scene of the crime! A love triangle!
Morisummer, you're very bloodthirsty.
I'm not, really.
And stop calling me Morisummer!
I don't really know anything...
...but I really don't think it will come to that.
I swear on Wicked Lord Shingan
that I will never give in to the devil!
Yes!
Satone?
Who goes there?
It's Kuzuha. Have you forgotten about her?
What? Oh, it's you, Kuzuha!
Kuzuha!
No way! How did you get so tall?
It's been three years.
You haven't changed much at all.
I'm shocked.
At this rate, you'll be the size
of a demonic non-articulated-foot worm!
Non-articulated?
Yuta! I have returned to base!
I urgently require supplies...
I did not anticipate she would infiltrate this easily!
Did you actually believe I would be
stopped by such a weak barrier?
Do not underestimate
the power of Sophia's magic.
Settle down.
Hey, no fair! Why only me?
Rikka, go put your bag away.
Shichimiya's folks are going to be
late home from work...
...so she'll be eating supper with us.
All right?
If you don't like it, we can settle here and now
who is the superior magical girl.
Just knock it off.
Ow. That's very effective, Hero.
Honestly, you.
Satone, you used to always hang out
with Yuta back then.
I required a Hero's abilities
to locate the samsara corridor.
I never would have thought
I would find his base here.
Shichimiya, I forget.
You didn't know where I lived?
I knew that even though we were allies, you could
never trust me with that information.
I made several attempts to shadow you.
Oh, yeah. I remember that.
You would always warn me
when we left for school in the morning.
You told me to be extra cautious
because we might be followed.
So, why is Wicked Lord Shingan living here?
I feel no need to disclose that to my foe.
Hey.
Rikka originally lived in the apartment above us.
But she found herself homeless by mistake.
What? So you are a wanderer
without a base in the mundane world?
That's amazing!
N-no, all dark beings are this way.
After all, I frequently spend time of
non-existence in this world.
I only took up residence here
due to my contract with Yuta.
It is merely transitory.
You're one haughty freeloader.
Contract?
A contract through Wicked Lord Shingan.
We have been joined for many moons.
Really?
Well, it's not really a contract...
These two are going out.
What?
Kuzuha!
It... It is merely a contract.
It... It is not as commonplace as
merely "going out."
Yeah. And besides, Kuzuha is here!
Way to go, Hero.
That's too close!
You found a travelling partner!
And she's the all-powerful Wicked Lord Shingan!
I got it. I get it, so back off.
Wicked Lord Shingan!
W-what?
What is your goal with Hero?
What is your objective?
My original goal was to discover
the invisible boundary line.
We have already achieved that objective
with our combined strength.
Therefore, my current objective is to awaken
the Dark Flame Dragon sleeping within him.
Dark Flame Dragon?
I don't recall needing any such thing.
You do. Your spirit-soul demands it.
Hey.
The Dark Flame Dragon? I see.
I'm rooting for you, Wicked Lord Shingan.
Hero, I should head home.
What? Already?
Yeah. Sophia needs to prepare herself
for battle with the angel.
What the heck?
Hero?
Huh?
H-hey, Shichimiya!
Hey, wait a second!
That was delicious, thank you.
Tell Kuzuha I said so.
Listen.
You're in high school now,
so stop being so clingy!
How come? We always used to touch noses.
Well, it's banned! Later.
I forgot.
Huh?
I never did say goodbye to you
when I left, did I?
Yeah.
I never did say anything to you...
...when I transferred schools. I just left.
That's because that would be goodbye.
Once you say your farewells,
that becomes goodbye.
Is that how it works?
As long as you lived somewhere in the world...
...it was never goodbye.
It is never goodbye until you say farewell.
That is the logic of the world,
and one of the natural laws.
You never change.
I will remain unchanged for all eternity!
And that is how I was reunited
with Satone Shichimiya.
She always had that habit.
It's like a greeting to her.
The nose?
Yes, the nose.
The nose...
All right, I'll enter into a contract with you.
I will never go near any girl but you.
Really?
Yeah.
And so, safe in my anxious certainty
that new trouble had yet to come...
I was filled with careless joy...
...that I was one step closer to Rikka.
To Be Continued