My only thought as
I don't think so!
I am put out to sea is
to ask the fishermen
Is she hurt?
Chihaya, too?!
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
What's wrong?
Why does it hurt like this?
Didn't I just jam it?
What is this?
What's wrong?
Ayase...
Ayase, you can't hide it from me.
I'm right next to you.
Two girls have gotten injured
playing their hearts out.
I keep losing when it counts,
and I'm behind Mr. Excavator right now.
When am I going to come through?!
It has to be now!
Excuse me.
The passion...
The passion always
comes from Chihaya,
but this feels different.
I can feel something burning
in my chest like magma.
I know what this is.
This is how it feels
when five people refuse to give up!
Chihaya Furu
Episode 18
My
fear
is
that
you
will
forget
Chihaya-chan is down six cards.
Porky is down three cards.
President Mashima is down four cards.
Tsukuba-kun and Desktomu-kun
are both down seven cards.
Everyone's losing,
but I can feel
their refusal to give up!
It's time for you to learn
that there are times when spirit
isn't enough to cut it.
A mountain village grows...
He's good,
but he's not as good as Arata.
Why do I feel that way?
What's with
his hands...
Arata's definitely better than he is!
Arata...
I'm happy when I forget you,
but then I feel encouraged
when I remember you.
I'm no good.
I'm a bad forgetter.
Coach Sakurazawa's F-cup boobies...
Excuse me.
Again?
17 cards to 12 cards.
I'm down by five.
Let's get started.
You've improved, Eyebrows.
I'll spot you a 5 card handicap starting today.
Dr. Harada started with
five more cards than I did
on the first practice match of the day.
The memorization left over from
the prior four matches today
and the card movements during this match
will go away!
Excuse me.
I'll spot you...
when people and grass grow scarce
...a 5 card handicap!
That's the best swing I've seen
from the Prez this match!
Now...
Let's get started.
H-He's good.
I can't do anything against him.
I doubt I'll be able to win my game.
It won't be that easy.
I want to overcome...
I want to overcome my own analysis.
"So spring nights," "So spring ends."
"So the flower has," "So the flower petals."
Plenty of similar cards remaining.
Extend and retract.
"Feel sorrow."
"Feel love" is a dead card,
so I want to be careful.
If I hear "sorrow," I have to attack.
I have to take it.
Repeatedly check the card so my
body remembers the path to take.
Take it.
Take the card, Tsukuba.
The Zodiac series is magnificent.
If that card's read, I'll go Virgo.
If it's that card, I'll go Libra.
He's weird.
He's weird and he's not
taking me seriously.
He's using those pointless
poses to scare me
while taking my cards!
I can't become a hero like this!
There are two cards you
absolutely have to be good at.
"Feel love deepen" and "Feel sorrow wash"?
I'm good at both of those.
Same here.
Ditto.
I won't lose those cards, either.
"Feel sorrow" was a poem by Oe no
Chisato about pale moonlight.
When looking at the moon, you
will be overcome by sorrow,
as you realize that autumn belongs to...
I don't really understand how you can
get sentimental about
looking at the moon,
but...
Feel sorrow wash...
When I see a card that I've practiced
constantly on the tatami,
I get a confidence boost!
He got it!
He did it!
Now things are going our way!
Chihaya-chan.
Seven cards in a row!
She's cut the deficit down to three!
Amazing...
Lacking experience playing under pressure.
Rion...
She's getting faster.
What about her injury?
Is she not really hurt?
It's not often that you get to play an
opponent with such amazing game sense.
Yama-chan, give me the best you've got.
That's what I'm doing.
My fear is that you will forget...
What is Rion doing?!
She guaranteed that she
would win her game!
Uh, have you chosen a card to send?
Doesn't matter!
Take this one!
I love everything that is beautiful.
No to outdoors
That's why I chose not to participate
in sports that would get me dirty.
No to getting sweaty
Stretching?
I didn't know that karuta was
just as intense until after
Jogging?
It'll help
keep you
beautiful
I was already hooked.
But...
While most players slap
away at the cards,
Rion was special.
She was beautiful.
Win, Rion!
If you can't win in such
favorable circumstances,
you'll get picked on again!
By me!
Thank you very much.
One win for Fujisaki!
Focus, Rion!
He doesn't blow at his bangs
when he's in trouble.
It's a signal that he's about to get serious.
My analysis was incomplete.
I wasn't up to the task...
This is the strength of a Fujisaki third-year!
You're very fortunate, Rion.
I was worried that it would be unfair
for me to participate as a reader,
but your opponent's game sense rivals yours.
I thought he was the only one
out there capable of that.
Kyo...
Yamashiro Kyoko-san...
Please allow me to record your reading.
but instead you see a pale
moon in the dawn sky
Said world...
Chihaya-chan, "Said
world grants no escape"
and "Said world grants no change" are
the same up to the fourth syllable,
but they have completely different meanings.
You could say they're different
as light and dark.
Said world grants no escape,
I hide in the mountains,
only to hear the haunting cry of a deer
It invokes the image of a dead end.
Said world grants no change, I pray,
when the fisherman who casts
his nets can seem dear
You can feel a longing for the eternal.
Said world
grants no change, I pray,
No way!
They both moved before the
unique syllable was read!
"Said world grants no escape" is still in play!
Were they gambling?
That's the only possible explanation.
Same time.
So close.
It was on Yama-chan's side, so she gets it.
There's something very
wrong about this pain.
Ignore it!
But it hurts!
It hurts...
Ignore it!
Why...
Why do I think it was Arata who
brought Shinobu-chan here?
I'm not interested in team tournaments.
I'm focused on winning the
individual tournament.
I might not be able to play in
the individual tournament.
I might not get to play
Arata or Shinobu-chan.
But!
We all feel the same way.
In this team match,
we're only focused on winning!
Like I was saying!
We lost because we didn't
have enough members.
Adult tournaments are
dominated by Fukui,
so there should be plenty
of experienced players.
I guess.
Can I go to the restroom?
Yeah, sure.
Go ahead.
How many experienced players
are in our high school?
I'll do some research
when next term starts.
I can feel the air grow thinner
as the number of cards on the
tatami dwindles towards the end.
Who will it be?
Who will be the next to win
and take a breath?
The championship match is intense,
but all five games in the third-place
match are within three cards.
This is big!
They aren't backing down.
Both schools came here
to win the tournament.
They can no longer accomplish that goal,
yet their spirits haven't broken?
Feels the presence of a serpent
It's the same with everything.
The main reason people continue
to fight after losing...
After I determined to abandon...
is because other people
are still watching.
Defended!
Same here!
Nice job, Megumu!
Take the next one, team!
I feel sick.
I took one!
Keep attacking, Shiroyama!
Stay focused!
Hokuo will win!
Yeah!
I feel sick.
I should have left...
I won another close game.
Shinobu-chan, that makes us rivals.
Shinobu-chan, play against
Ryuusei-kun next.
We should keep Shinobu-chan
away from children her age.
She'll learn to go easy on her opponents.
The more alone she is,
the stronger she'll become.
Why am I remembering this now?
I should have left.
But...
is that I have no way
to tell you in person
While it may be beyond...
Who won that one?
Was it the Fujisaki player?
I'm standing right next to
them and it's still hard...
I will make the call on that last play.
Thank you very much.
Neither of them are contesting the card,
so this isn't the typical time
for a referee to step in,
but I want to let them focus.
It's rare for two players
with such amazing game sense
to play one another.
You need to move back.
Rion's having a hard time!
I should have played instead.
The coach made the wrong decision!
The match started off with plenty of
three-syllable cards and
very few one-syllable cards.
Rion had the advantage,
given her familiarity with the
voice of Yamashiro, rank 7.
At least in the early game.
She should have pressed that advantage
to seal the game away early.
What will you do now, Rion?
There are one-syllable cards everywhere.
So the flower has wilted...
I've never lost a match with
Grandma as the reader.
I was convinced
that I could defeat the Queen
if Grandma was reading.
You'll have a lot to answer for if
you lose in the number one seat.
No...
I don't want to lose!
Shinobu-chan...
We don't belong to teams,
so we can only focus on
making ourselves stronger.
Our love for karuta is real,
but think about it:
Our beloved world of karuta can only grow
through the recruiting,
teaching,
and encouraging of new players.
It's team players who keep this game alive.
Doesn't matter.
It's got nothing to do with me.
Nobody will ever take me seriously.
Nobody...
Please wait!
Ayase-san,
Nishida-kun, and Tsukuba-kun
are all doing their best...
against Fujisaki!
Mashima-kun is still down by 5 cards!
He can't catch up!
That early mistake is making a difference.
He stabilized midway through the
game and made some good plays,
but his luck is still terrible!
He wants to attack, but the last five
cards have all been on his side!
I can see why this guy is their captain.
He doesn't over-memorize.
It's something I'm too scared to try.
He wasn't targeting the
two cards I just lost.
He moved his body halfway
across the field before making his move,
and I still lost.
He covers on two-syllable cards.
If I press the issue,
he manages to block me.
He doesn't commit faults.
He's got confidence and the
stamina to back it up.
Damn...
We're both on our fifth match.
The last five cards
have been on my side.
Should I focus on defending
the seven cards on my side
instead of attacking the
two on the opponent's side?
Living Ghost
I don't need you, Dr. Harada.
What?!
When in trouble...
As the years pass...
Go lower right!
Yes!
He got it!
He wasn't blindly attacking
the lower right!
"As my" is still in play, so he
covered before taking it!
He was able to block his opponent!
Amazing!
Tsukuba-kun...
Thank you very much.
Damn it.  Damn it.
So you know how to use proper technique.
Shining Rainbow
You were just toying with me.
You're pretty good.
You forced me to use
my Gear Second!
Not happy
Tsukuba-kun, please win for me.
Two wins for Fujisaki!
Good!
One more win!
One more win for the championship!
Yeah!
Mizusawa's down 0 to 2.
This is tough.
Fujisaki's got this in the bag.
It's impressive that they
came out of nowhere to
make the grand finale.
They're strong.
That makes it a five-peat for Fujisaki.
I'm sending a card.
the cresting waves almost look like clouds in the skies
A multi-syllable card?
"My only thought as I" was already read,
so this is now a two-syllable card.
You won't be able to surprise me.
I'm sticking to my usual playing style.
This is painful.
It would be most gratifying
if Mizusawa was able
to secure a single win from
the dominating Fujisaki.
Three wins.
We're getting three wins, guys.