Mitaka Jin
Letter of Exam Success
Misaki-sama cannot come
to the phone right now.
Please leave a message.
Well...
What should I do now?
This is the place, right?
#18 First Love with an Alien
Thanks for meeting me here.
I'm taking the afternoon
flight to San Francisco.
For work?
Yes, I'm supposed to give a
presentation at a game conference.
So, shall we get started?
Yes, please.
I see.
Let's move forward with
your idea for the battles.
Okay, thank you very much.
Now, we just have to write up a
pitch for the title review board.
I'll do my best.
Oh, right.
Could we ask the girl...
who drew this to do some
additional illustrations for us?
It has such presence.
I think including more drawings would
help us with the review board.
You're right...
Is there a problem?
No, I'll ask Shiina about it.
Then, let's call it a day.
Okay.
Planning to go on a date after this?
The results of my sister's
exam come out this afternoon.
I see.
I'm home.
Huh? Sensei, you're
working again today?
I have a meeting I don't want to go to.
What's going on?
Usually she says something like,
"Why don't you go in my place?"
Kanda-kun, you're back.
Yeah, I'm home...
But I'm changing and heading
straight back out again.
For Yuko-chan's test results, right?
Can I go with you?
Sure.
Wait right here. I'll go get changed.
So...
Why did you tag along, Shiina?
Whether Yuko passes or not is important.
How so?
It's related to my plans for the future.
What happens if she passes?
Plan C.
You really like that plan, don't you?
Do you prefer Plan B?
That's the one where we go out!
G-Go out?
N-No, it's not...
I love you!
A-Aoyama...
Sorata, Nanami...
Your faces are red. Are you sick?
N-No, we're not!
Come on, let's hurry.
B-By the way, Aoyama, when do the
results of your audition come out?
B-Between the end of February
and the middle of March.
I see.
Sorata, you seem happy.
How do I look happy?!
Nanami, you seem happy, too.
Th-That's not true!
Not that I care.
Then, don't act like you're angry.
I'm not angry.
She sounds it, doesn't she, Aoyama?
Yeah.
You're being friendly with Nanami again.
N-No, I'm not!
N-No, he's not!
See? Friendly.
I-It's green.
Come on, let's go.
O-Oh, I forgot...
Shiina, I have a favor to ask you.
What?
Would you draw more illustrations for—
I'll do it.
But if it'll get in the way of your manga—
I-I see. In that case, thanks.
Sorata, you're not happy?
No, that's not it. It's a huge help.
Then, I'll do my best.
What's Yuko-chan's number?
Ninety-nine.
Let's see...
Well, not much we can do.
How did it go, Onii-chan?!
You failed.
That's impossible! Check again!
No matter how many times I
check, you still failed.
All the other numbers in the nineties
passed, but 99 isn't up there.
Why only me?
You must not have scored
very well on the test.
Why can't you be nicer
to me when I'm in pain?
When can I crack open my ball with the
"congratulations on passing" banner?
How should I know? And what
the heck is that, anyway?
I pulled three all-nighters making it!
I'm breaking it open now!
My ball failed, too!
Do your best on the
prefectural school exam.
Kanda-kun.
What are you doing here?
My younger brother, Iori,
applied to the music department.
Your brother?
That's amazing.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Looks like Misaki isn't with you?
What?
Mitaka's here at the school.
Huh? Jin-san?
He came to tell his homeroom
teacher that he passed his exam.
Mitaka really intends to leave
Misaki behind and go to Osaka.
She didn't even get to see
him on Valentine's Day.
There are only two weeks
left before graduation.
Two weeks...
I can't believe the two of
them will graduate like this.
They can't.
Aoyama! Misaki-senpai—
I'll go back and get her!
Thanks! I'll keep Jin-san from leaving!
Do you think it'll be all right?
Who knows? I can't look
after them all the time.
If you'll excuse me...
Jin-san!
What's wrong?
Mashiro-chan, that's some
face you're pulling.
Could you come with us for a bit?
It's forbidden love.
Fine, fine. Do whatever
you want with me.
Why did you bring me here?
You're not actually confessing
your love to me, are you?
It's about Misaki-senpai.
How has she been lately?
She's making an animation.
That's what she should be doing.
She'll forget about me soon enough.
Are you serious?
Would it be better if
I said I was joking?
Of course not.
I'm going to Osaka.
Please talk to Misaki-senpai!
I can't date Misaki.
Jin-san!
What else am I supposed to say?
You're not acting like your usual self.
And what's my usual self?
Always cool, always smart,
capable of anything,
mature, dependable,
and always gives me advice.
That's the person I expect you to be!
You're mistaken. Give it up.
I can't give up!
How can you think I'd give
up on you and Misaki-senpai?
Don't be ridiculous!
What if someone takes
Misaki-senpai away from you?
Let go.
What if they start dating?
I'm asking you whether you'd mind...
if Misaki-senpai gave all of
her being to another man!
Do you understand?
Don't think you can say
whatever you like!
You're the one making me say it!
That hurt!
Smart, mature, and dependable?
Who are you talking about?
I couldn't take any more!
I didn't even know if
I'd get into college!
I couldn't focus on anything
because of Misaki!
It's not easy for me to confess
my feelings to Misaki!
I need to be prepared to spend
the rest of my life with her!
How can you say that when
you've always been ready?
Sorata, are you alive?
I feel like I'm dying.
Listen, Shiina...
What?
I can almost see your panties.
Don't look.
You've grown up a bit if you're
shamelessly looking up girls' skirts now.
Jin-san.
What?
Why don't you stop this
if you like her so much?
Please go out with Misaki-senpai.
Haven't you been listening to me?
Misaki will be here soon.
Aoyama went to get her. So, please...
She won't come.
What?
Kamiigusa-senpai!
You're full of energy, Nanamin.
Mitaka-senpai's at school right now!
Come with me!
I'm not going.
What? Senpai...
Why not?
Because I'm finishing this right now.
Let's do it! I'm gonna do it!
Are you sure, Kamiigusa-senpai?
I'm sure.
You're lying.
You're the one who taught me
not to hold my feelings in!
That's why I did my best.
Senpai, are you going to do another...
hundred laps around that same circle?
I don't want to either,
but...
Misaki-chan, you're amazing!
Jin, look!
I was always with Jin.
It's snow! It's a fight!
It's a snowball fight!
Let's see who wants to play!
I don't want to play if you're playing.
What? Why not?
Because we can't win.
Yeah.
We'll beat Misaki today!
Our pride depends on it!
I thought Jin would
always be by my side.
Jin, it's morning! Wake up!
If you don't get up, I'm giving
you a good morning kiss!
Okay, okay. Good morning.
Hey, how do I look?
Don't do that outside.
Why not?
Because he doesn't want
other people to see you.
Fuuka.
Misaki, let's take a picture.
Come here.
Got it.
Our parents get so excited
over everything Misaki does.
And as her older sister,
you're not happy about it.
They even bought a new camera.
Anyway, aren't you going to change?
I was waiting for you to leave.
How cheeky of you to worry about me.
What are you talking about?
Jin, hurry.
I wonder whether...
it would have been better if
I'd realized how I felt sooner.
We've finished our first semester!
Yahoo!
Look. How embarrassing.
I can't get my head around
the fact she's a brainiac.
Exam Results
1. Kamiigusa Misaki
Mitaka-kun, are you going home already?
We're off to sing karaoke.
Do you want to join us?
Some other girls from
our class are coming.
Is there anyone cuter than her?
What?
I said I've got something
I have to do today.
You're no fun.
Next time, then. Promise?
She's kinda sexy, isn't she?
Her personality's beyond belief, though.
I wonder if she'd let me—
What do you think you're doing?
Don't mess with me!
Yay! All done!
Impressive.
Kamiigusa again? There's
nothing we can do about her.
You have your work
cut out with that one.
Ow.
What am I doing?
Did you get in a fight again?
How many times is this now?
Ow!
What are you doing, Fuuka?
Your heart's pounding.
So is yours.
I can't watch this anymore.
Watch what?
I can't watch Misaki hurt you anymore.
I'm not...
Your heart just leaped, didn't it?
I won't hurt you.
Maybe I wouldn't have been running
in circles if I'd noticed sooner.
Jin! Fuuka-chan! Welcome...
See you tomorrow.
Time for dinner.
Misaki, we made your favorite! Crab!
Come and get it.
Your parents are calling you.
Yeah.
Let's eat.
Misaki won't show.
She's been avoiding me lately.
Huh? Avoiding... What?!
But Misaki-senpai's feeling better now...
Why?
She won't answer her phone
and she doesn't answer my texts.
Misaki won't show.
I'm too afraid to go see Jin.
I feel like I'd say
something mean if I did.
What?
I thought I might be able to see
him after I finished this scene,
but I just can't finish it.
I don't want to finish it!
Senpai...
Misaki will still come.
Nanami will bring her.
I'm really glad I came to Suimei High.
Do you want this?
Thanks!
There you are, Kamiigusa.
Sensei.
Oopsy-daisy.
Did you come to deliver
your last words, Master?
I'm not dying yet.
You're going soft, Master.
What's that?
Suimei University of
the Arts High School?
Listen, Kamiigusa:
There are no aliens like
you in this tiny town.
But if you go to that school,
you might find others like you...
who have found their
way onto this planet.
Why don't you try applying here?
Like me...
That's when I realized
Misaki knew she was alone.
Why did you apply to Suimei High?
I...
I'm thinking of applying to Suimei, too.
That's not funny.
Leaving home and living in a dorm
sounds like fun, doesn't it?
I'm kind of interested in
attending an art school, too.
So you do prefer Misaki.
You're always so worried about Misaki.
Misaki's the only one you see.
I thought you'd at least look at me.
I'm nothing more than a
Misaki substitute to you.
That's not—
You're afraid you'll hurt Misaki.
You want to keep her pure and
untouched by your side forever.
Isn't that why you're with me instead?
At least make an excuse.
I probably just couldn't ignore Misaki.
Oh, that's it! I'm out of patience!
Nanamin?
Mitaka-senpai's going
far away this time!
Is that okay with you?
Leap into space!
Hey, Nanamin!
Under Construction
I'm really glad I came to Suimei High.
I'm glad I met you guys.
Knowing Misaki has people around her
who will get angry for her sake...
makes me extremely happy.
Jin-san.
She's definitely not going to show now.
Thanks for waiting, Senpai.
Aoyama!
What?
Hey!
We heard there was a fight...
What are you doing on a
test announcement day?
There's an explanation for all of this!
I don't care!
I'm sure you don't!
Open this door, Kanda!
Jin-san!
Please wait!
I'm telling you to open this door!
Shiina, help us!
Okay.
Run, then!
Are you pushing me?
Tickling me? Massaging me?!
Which is it?
Which do you want?
Push!
Kamiigusa-senpai!
Harder!
What a bunch of meddling
underclassmen.
Well, I guess it's not
so bad once in a while.
Misaki.
Jin.
I passed. I'm going to Osaka in April.
Congratulations.
So, Misaki, don't worry about me.
Do what you really want to do.
You must have realized it
when we all worked on Nyapollon.
You had fun, didn't you?
Yeah. Mashiron's work was amazing,
and every day was exciting.
The Dragon did everything
I asked him to do, too.
I had so much fun.
Then, you know my scripts
aren't good enough.
At least you're honest.
I'm sorry. Your scripts
aren't good enough.
They don't excite me.
You were disappointed every
time I finished one.
I'm sorry.
Four years.
Four years from now,
I'll come back and write scripts...
good enough to be
hired by Kamiigusa Misaki.
So, well...
Wh-What—
It'll keep men away.
If you don't want it, pitch it.
Jin.
I'll never take it off.
That's great.
Come and join us in
the faculty office for a while!
Does "a while" mean five minutes?
You're really going to get it today!
Prepare yourselves!
Okay, okay.
Thanks for the last three years.
Hey! Mitaka, open the door!
You'll get in even more trouble later.
Sorata's the one who
will get in trouble.
Why me?
Third years can come
and go as we please,
and I won't be coming
to school tomorrow.
You had all of that worked out?!
Come on, let's go home.
Home?
To Sakura Hall, of course.
What?
Yeah!
Open this door!
Please open this door! Please!
There are people on the roof.
Please look out for them while doing your rounds!
Nanamin! Mashiron! Look! Ta-da!
That's great, Senpai.
It suits you perfectly.
She really does seem happy.
It took a long time to get here.
What are you two talking about?
You scared me.
We were wondering how far we can go.
You can go anywhere.
Kouhai-kun, that's some statement.
Living in Sakura Hall
makes you think like that.
Sakura Hall
We're home.
Mitaka's here, too? Perfect.
The board of trustees have decided
to demolish Sakura Hall...
at the end of the year.
Hikari...
What was Sakura Hall like
before I showed up?
#19 There's No Place Like Sakura Hall
"Our biscuits were soggy."
"And Sorata was slouched over
like a soggy biscuit." I see.