It won't take long.
Be patient.
How did I get here?
Elias was telling me
about the dragons, and...
Dragons?
Yes, dragons.
They've been on the move lately.
I've been asked to check it out.
Here, in Iceland, is the dragons' nest.
They're on the verge of
extinction, just like us mages.
The handful of surviving breeds have been
rounded up here to be taken care of.
It's remote and scarcely inhabited here,
which makes it a perfect hiding space.
Are they vicious?
The majority of them were
weeded out long ago.
There are more docile ones now.
I see.
Chise!
Elias!
His half-baked talent makes him cocky.
He hasn't changed much.
See, look over there.
The last land of the dragons.
Hey, let her go.
Hey!
Does she plan to just keep sinking?
My body feels heavy.
Chise.
Well.
What an unusual guest.
You smell like a mage...
albeit a young one.
A sapling.
And you smell of plants, flowers,
and rocks from another place.
It's a nice scent.
His eyes...
His whole body is like a forest of moss, too.
He's a breed of dragon called an uil.
He's both father and the mother to the forest,
bearing vegetation on his decaying body.
Apologies for the rough handling.
Welcome to the land of
dragons, Daughter of Thorn.
Why me?
There was commotion among the ariels.
They said that Thorn had
finally taken an apprentice.
For them, rumors spread
literally like the wind.
You arrived quite quickly this time around.
When are you going to stop hiding
in your apprentice's shadows, Thorn?
Or rather, Ainsworth?
When the old fogey finishes his bumbling.
It's been 300 years, and you still haven't
stopped toying with people, have you, Echos?
Do you want your apprentice
to freeze to death, Ainsworth?
I'm... I'm fine.
You're absolutely soaked.
Nettles in the shadow...
Ring of holly...
I'm dry.
Th-Thank you.
What are you grinning at?
At this little brat acting
like he's all grown up.
Shut it.
Chise, that's Lindel.
He's a mage, like me, and
caretaker of this dragon's nest.
Caretaker?
His duty is to keep the land of dragons
hidden from the sight of ordinary humans.
Hence, "caretaker."
Despite his appearance, he's a mischievous
senior, even more ancient than I am,
so be careful around him.
How dare you...
Hey, hey!
Are you done talking?
Let's play.
Let's play! Let's play!
Come on.
Those are dragon hatchlings.
Let's play.
Let's play!
Please?
The one with wings is a gwee.
Come on!
The one by your feet is a beana.
Come on, let's play!
The slow-moving one is an uil.
Granted, that's just what
I call them personally.
Let's play!
Come on!
Hey, are you listening?
Lindel.
Let's play!
Tell me, has there been any trouble lately?
They're making a fuss again, are they?
Food has been scarce this year.
A number of the dragons
have been traveling far.
Chise, would you mind
playing with them for me?
What should we do?
Over there.
Let's jump off and practice
gliding toward the pond.
Humans can fly these days, right?
Er, that might be hard without having my bones
and muscles modified at the genetic level.
Yay!
And now I'm wet again.
Hey, can we try that?
That was awesome!
He has wings, so I guess
he must be able to fly.
He's all tattered, though.
Have you never seen a dragon before?
S-Sorry, I didn't mean to...
I didn't mean it like that.
Uncle Nevin's awake.
It's won't be long before I return home.
I'd supposed you would prefer to watch
over the rollicking young instead.
It's almost his time.
His time?
Uncle Nevin's turning into a tree soon.
Yup.
All the uils do.
They turn into excellent trees and pasture.
When you say "return"...
What do you mean?
We're going to turn into trees and
moss and boulders when we die, too.
Right?
When you die?
We don't fear death the way you humans do.
We live our lives to the fullest, so
that we're never left with regrets.
Doesn't it hurt?
You're a kind-hearted child.
We understand that what
is given to us is the same
as what is given to all
who live on this planet.
Whether that's the joy or the pain of
living, or the sadness or loneliness of dying.
Besides, I've lived for
more than enough time.
For a long, long time, even for a dragon.
Life will be handed down
to the next generation.
You have no reason to grieve.
No.
I'm not grieving.
I can't.
It's really...
The living shouldn't envy the dead.
You cannot fly, so it's
fortunate that you didn't.
He wouldn't have known who to take as
his apprentice if he hadn't met you.
Were you going through my memories?
That was a disrespectful
thing to do to a human.
I'm sorry.
I believe I ought to let you experience the
joy of true flight, as you cannot fly yourself.
I don't have the strength to fly anymore,
but I can show you the sky I see in my mind.
Behold.
Looks like Nevin is having his
final dream, along with Chise.
A lot of dragons are passing the torch lately.
I suppose he's the last of the old dragons.
It's the same for dragons as
it is for magic, isn't it?
We're being pushed aside by the changing
times and the growing number of humans.
If Chise becomes a mage, she may
very well be of the last generation.
Does that bother you?
Chise's power is flowing into Nevin.
She'll be a great help to Nevin,
but a Sleigh Beggy's overwhelming
power, at times, hurts its wielder.
She doesn't know how to hold back yet.
Isn't it your job to teach her?
She won't last three years
unless you stop her.
I know.
Don't let her out of your sight.
There are countless people
who want a Sleigh Beggy.
The rumors these days aren't encouraging.
She wasn't easy to obtain.
I won't let her go that easily.
I hope she grows up safely...
That Sleigh Beggy.
Our kind abandoned the skies.
But it was always our fate
to dwell beneath it.
Your name has the character
for "bird" within it.
You must also fly beneath
this sky, in order to live.
In order to live?
Fly?
In order to live...
It's a tree.
Thank you.
Because you were here, I spent
my last moments in flight.
I didn't do anything.
A little while ago, Lindel
planted a small seed in my body.
It'll produce beautiful
white flowers, I'm told.
You're a mage, are you not?
You'll need a wand, someday.
Make one out of my branches.
Good night, little mage.
Uncle was awesome.
Wasn't he?
I hope I can become a huge tree, too.
Welcome back, Chise.
Was it beautiful in Nevin's sky?
It was very beautiful.
That was a rare thing you got to witness.
Not many get to witness
a dragon return to the earth.
Lindenbaum.
Its beautiful white flowers are in bloom.
There's not a single reason to be sad, Chise.
This is the work of nature.
The dragons all spend enormous
time strengthening their minds,
and in the end, are at peace with
becoming seedbeds for other life.
Okay.
Like Nevin said,
we'll return for a branch to use for your wand,
once it's time for you to have one.
Our business here is done for now.
Let's head home.
What? Leaving so soon?
This isn't the only matter
I've had shoved at me.
You could just bail on it.
You're surprisingly proper, aren't you?
Shut up.
This is nature...
Let's go, Chise.
I'm not sad.
He was just like a stranger who happened
to show me some kindness.
My head's spinning.
Is it because of the flight?
But still,
I can't help but be a little envious
of the peaceful way he passed.
Past the tunnel was
a nation of cats.
There, in a land drowning in sadness,
the girl learns of her own cruel duty.
Please, help us. Help me.