Let's find some shade.
You're a cute couple.
What was—
Are you okay, Touko?
You scared me. What happened?
What? Sorry,
I don't really know.
Seems like you're okay for now.
Yeah.
I'll take you home.
Please.
I'd like you to.
I'm going to ask for a proper explanation.
You're going to help Touko-chan, right?
He's not coming.
No fun.
Why aren't you coming, 5:30 guy?
Episode 8
"Snow"
Hinode-hama High School
Track Club Summer Camp
Hey, Yukinari.
The hero returns, huh?
Thanks.
We were waiting for you. How're you doing?
Still taking it slow.
Let's get going.
Bring it in!
Hinode Dance School
No! No!
Did you hear me? We're not
doing the beach trip today.
Looks like he's here.
Coming.
Yanagi-chan!
Long time no see, Auntie.
It's a day late, but she's being
discharged this afternoon.
I came in time, then.
Thank you, Yanagi-chan.
You're welcome.
We're just going to the rooftop.
We'll be back in about twenty minutes.
Oh!
I heard from Hiro. You're in for tests?
Yes.
I brought steamed sake buns for you today.
Be good to Hiro for me.
Sure.
You've been with Hiro
a lot lately, haven't you?
Yeah.
Hiro made it so obvious.
Did something happen with Hiro?
Yeah.
I won't ask, then.
The beach trip got canceled last-minute,
but it's kinda for the best since
your hospital stay was extended.
But I was looking forward to it,
and I had my bathing suit ready
and everything, so I went.
Oh. With Yukinari-kun, then?
About that,
Yuki went off to a summer camp for track club.
Way late.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, and he didn't even tell me.
I think I won't ask.
I came to the hospital because
there was something I wanted to ask you.
Since I was visiting anyway.
Yeah.
Touko and David are kind of strange.
Touko and David seem to have
feelings for each other.
Did you know?
I did.
Seems like they have a secret.
I thought you might know.
Would you tell me?
Or did you promise Touko not to?
I didn't promise Touko anything,
but I don't really know much.
Mr. Boyfriend isn't coming today.
Yeah.
I want cookies.
I'll make some tea.
I think I'll join you, too.
Sure.
Touko, are you awake?
I'm awake.
Mom said to bring this.
Thanks.
Can I stay for a bit?
Sure.
Fine, fine.
How was it?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
What was that?
Sorry, I don't really know either.
Let's meet up.
Are you afraid you might see
something like that again?
Where should we meet?
Let's see...
I think I want to see Jonathan.
All right, good idea.
See you in an hour.
Yeah.
Touko said you'd be fine when
you were being hospitalized.
Like she knew about the future.
Yeah?
Oh yeah, and when David
first came to Kazemichi,
he said something about "seeing
the same thing as you."
"I saw what you saw," was it?
You know something, don't you?
Like I said, I don't know too much.
I should tell you
everything I know, shouldn't I?
I think Touko-chan and David
have a special relationship.
Sachi,
about Touko, do you—
Not bad.
Thanks.
The other day...
Huh?
Sorry, I said something
stupid at the track meet.
We're even, aren't we?
Imi!
Yes?
I saw Yana-chan at the hospital.
Yeah?
Huh, aren't you going today?
Nope.
But I told the girl with the
glasses to be good to you.
You have to do your part.
Sure.
So something did happen.
Kakeru, are you having fun, living here?
Sure, I think.
Okay.
I'm going to school.
Hey, Onee-chan.
Yeah?
Sorry about earlier.
No,
about Yukinari-san.
I mean, I wasn't
like this before.
So I did something unlike
me, and I got worked up
and chased him on my bike,
and I told him to stay attractive.
You talked to him?
Yeah, I guess.
But...
But what?
He wasn't running yesterday.
Everyone was making a fuss, because they
look forward to seeing him every day.
Really?
I have practice soon, too, so I'll go check.
Oh,
he's not running.
Let's watch them next time.
When they're making stuff?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Oh,
nothing.
There!
Who's that?
Are we not going to be able to
sit next to each other anymore?
We can.
What do you think it was?
I'm a little afraid to be next to you now.
I'm terrible, huh?
I don't know what it was either.
But yeah, I'm a little wary of coming
close to you right now.
From: Hina
No subject
Yanagi-san's running
instead of Yukinari-san
Oh, it's from my sister.
Yuki-kun's turned into Yana-chan.
Hina-chan, the other day...
Oh, my sister's name is Hina.
Hina-chan's swim club...
Oh, do you mind if I talk about Yuki-kun?
What about her swim club?
Yeah, he's popular at the swim club.
I called Yana-chan, but
she wouldn't pick up.
From what I heard, it doesn't
sound like Takayama is panicking,
so I think it'll be okay.
I wonder. I hope so.
Are you
worried about me, Kakeru-kun?
Yeah.
I don't think there's a reason
to worry about Yukinari Imi,
but if it's bothering you,
we could go to his place together.
Sure.
I was sketching here
a while ago, just like this,
and I saw Yuki-kun.
So we went to the art class prep room
to pick up Conté crayons, and...
And there, he...
Touko,
are you thinking about that Kakeru guy?
What now?
Do you like him?
I see.
You do.
No, it's not that.
So I was surprised, too.
I'm talking about Yuki-kun again.
I see. So that happened.
Oh, no, that's really all it was.
Nothing more.
But then you hesitated quite a bit, didn't you?
We might learn something new about
the fragments of the future if we
go to the art-class prep room.
Really?
How about you go there with me this time?
But—
What?
Right, maybe...
What—
Where is it?
Through the front door, and to the right.
This way.
Here it is.
All contacts     Details     Edit
Hiro Shirosaki
Cell
080 552 1068
The customer you have dialed
is out of the service area, or—
We should probably tell
Yukinari Imi or Takayama.
Huh, why?
Why should we tell everyone?
What do you think Takayama thought
when she saw us at the beach?
Well,
I'm sure she was surprised.
But is that it?
Takayama will surely ask
you about what happened.
But how am I supposed to explain?
She would never believe me.
If that kind of thing is
going to keep happening...
It will?
Again?
Kakeru-kun, is this...
What—
W-Was that a fragment of the future?
Hey, what's wrong?
No!
Touko!
What happened? What did you see?
It can't be.
Touko!
From: Sacchan
Subject: Untitled
I'm home. Please come see me again.
I have a book I want to lend you.
The place we promised...
I want to go to that art room.
I'm going to become a new me.
Yeah, right.
For tomorrow.
And those were my lines.
Episode 9
"Moon"