Deep in the woods, there was a training facility.
Amazing...
To us, it was known simply as "the Farm."
It served one purpose:
To train first-class spies.
This is why, if they determined
that a girl did not meet their standards,
we'd wake up one day and find she was gone.
Saying goodbye was never part of the program.
Finished.
What? You're kidding!
Already?
Finished!
Whoa! Her, too?!
How?!
Come on, girls.
You don't have to be THAT fast.
I understand you were classmates?
Yes, Sir.
She was an extremely good student.
An honor student whose grades
never fell below second place.
We still have her records.
You two will be well-suited for this mission.
You think so, sir?
What have you said to her?
We've told her what she needs to know.
Now I want you to meet her on-site
and determine how to proceed.
Yes, Sir.
Our mission is to retrieve top secret documents
from the estate of the First Lord of the Admiralty.
The operation will take place on the 25th.
Christmas.
That's today!
We can't! We haven't done anything to prepare!
That's alright. We have an ally on the inside.
She'll be our guide when we get there.
She's good at what she does. Don't worry.
You know her?
We were classmates.
Back at the training facility.
The sea charts of all Europe are about to change.
With the marked increase in military power,
if we are to resist the navies of the World Powers,
we must disband the Channel Fleet defending
Albion proper, and move forward with our plans
to join it with the Atlantic Fleet, combining all of
the Kingdom's forces into the new Grand Fleet.
Well, it's Christmas. That should do for tonight.
Yes, Your Lordship.
Will you be spending the evening
with anyone, Miss Eleanor?
No one.
I don't much care for Christmas.
And why might that be?
It reminds me of an old acquaintance.
Oh?
She was...
the woman I always wished I could be.
They said it was the third window from the right?
Yes. That window, there.
And your classmate left it unlocked for us?
Yeah.
Let's go.
You think so, too, right?
You do have a point.
Your posture is all wrong.
The way you shift your weight
makes your footsteps louder.
Strict as ever, I see.
Give her some slack.
She wasn't trained at the Farm like we were.
You can't expect the enemy to give you slack.
Are YOU...
Miss Ange's classmate?
I can't believe they sent the two of you.
Control has its moments.
And now we can have a class reunion.
We're not going to do that.
Agreed.
Could you at least TRY to get along?
We ARE the only three left from our class, after all.
Really? You are?
Do you have any idea what you're actually doing?
I struggle to understand.
Why in the world did Control send us this amateur?
Those two are simply amazing.
They've hardly said a word to each other,
but they work perfectly together.
They were by far the best in our class.
Over there.
The secret documents are in a cellar
under the gamekeeper's cabin.
But there's a problem.
Those annoying guards.
Dogs? And so many of them!
We can't win them over with bribes or flattery.
What's your plan?
This is why we're here.
Beatrice.
Yes, I can take care of this.
Not even the Farm's top of the class could
pull off a trick like that, right?
You two keep a lookout.
Wh-what...
As expected, she's good.
So are you, Prefect.
I've heard about your exploits since we graduated.
I was desperate, that's all.
Do you think Ange and the others are alright?
Worry not.
You are aware of their degree of skill.
True, but...
Miss Chise, what is that?
It is a shishi odoshi.
A proper one should be made of bamboo,
but unfortunately, I could not obtain any.
What do you use it for?
What do I...?
Hmm.
Cheers!
You just did a toast a little while ago.
That was number 17.
You were counting?
Our Prefect's always been obsessed with details.
You make it sound like a bad thing.
It was a compliment!
Because I'm just the opposite.
Um, they have prefects at spy school?
"Prefect" is a nickname.
Because she's responsible and gets good grades.
And took charge of our class.
I was just a nag, that's all.
Besides, my grades were eternally second-best.
That's not your fault.
Number one was a space alien.
That's "Black Lizard Planet native."
So has Miss Ange always been like this?
She was odd for as long as I've known her.
And you were normal.
Are you calling me average?
It's not an insult.
Of course.
You don't care about people enough to insult them.
So they don't get along?
Well, they were rivals.
Please excuse me.
Aww, you're leaving?
I'm going to the powder room. Don't make me say it.
Have fun!
You never change, do you?
Oh?
Where are the others?
I sent the children home.
But the night's still young.
Drink with me.
Alright.
A double agent?
There's a possibility.
Our real mission is to find out
whether or not she's betrayed us.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because we wanted to avoid raising
her suspicions as much as possible.
You would have acted differently.
That may be true, but...
This is it.
Where are we?
Prefect's boarding house.
Cheers!
That's 21.
You're still counting?
Do you remember?
The Christmas exam.
Exam?
Oh yeah, I remember.
You, Ange, and I were all on a team together.
You lost sight of the target?
I'm so sorry!
We'll never pass the exam now.
All because I failed!
We just have to find them again-
The exam ends tonight!
Finding one person in a city like this...
it's like looking for a leaf in the forest!
Well, I guess that's true.
In that case...
let's go have fun!
What?
They don't let us out of the Farm every day.
And I think the traveling funfair is in town.
What are you thinking? We're in the middle of an exam!
But we've already failed, right?
I thought you were a blithering idiot.
But you did go to the funfair with me.
I was desperate.
I was sure I was going to be expelled.
You really believed them when they said
they'd expel us if we failed the test.
But of course, while we were out fooling around,
Ange went and found our target.
She's a natural, that girl.
That's the first time I've ever heard
you say anything nice about Ange.
Really?
That makes me happy.
But I'm not sure why.
Look at all that snow.
Say, Dorothy.
Have you ever had someone you really looked up to?
I... don't think so.
I have.
Someone I wanted to be like so badly.
But I just couldn't pull it off.
Let's pull out.
I couldn't find any evidence.
Alright!
I'm glad your friend's not a double agent.
Correction.
I...
am not her friend.
I knew it.
They came to spy on me.
She's making a move.
Prefect...
What's going on?
You just said there wasn't any evidence.
I deliberately left footprints on the trap she had set up.
I figured that if she was up to anything,
she would react and make a move.
We're going to apprehend her.
At this time of day, she'd be going to the station.
I'll head her off.
You two go after her.
We'll have her surrounded when she gets to the station.
You're not going to use the C-ball?
I want to save it for a last resort.
Why would you do this, Prefect?
We've caught up to her.
Now we just make sure she doesn't see-
Miss Ange?
I give up.
This whole thing was a setup, and I fell for it.
I won't ask why you betrayed us.
That's not part of the assignment.
And I'm sure you wouldn't let me go
just because I asked nicely.
Don't move!
Put down the gun and your case,
and put your hands in the air.
You've changed.
The old you would have ended it
with one shot to the back of my head.
I don't suppose a certain someone
planted feelings in the black lizard's heart?
But...
Gunfire?
She didn't!
The new you is a sitting duck!
Miss Ange!
Stay back.
You'll get burned.
Ange! Beatrice!
What happened? Did she spot you?
No, er...
We brought the fight to her... you might say...
Ange!
I told you we'd surround her! Why didn't you wait?
I wanted to ensure the mission's success.
Did you think you could beat
our prefect all by yourself?
Or were you trying to prove
which one of you was really the better spy?
Answer me, Ange!
Excuse me, Miss!
Hey!
We can't allow this, Young Lady.
I'm sorry. I don't suppose you have
any vacant compartments?
But of course.
Follow me, Miss.
Thank you.
I would like to get some sleep.
Would you please lend me a blanket?
Right away, Miss.
If we go in a straight line,
we'll catch up to her at the bridge.
There she is!
What took you so long?
Dorothy!
How did you...?
I caught up by car and jumped aboard with the C-ball.
The C-ball... I'd heard the rumors.
So it was issued to your team.
They have high hopes for you.
For Ange, yes.
You can't just ask me to take the wheel!
You're really something.
Giving Ange the slip like that.
It was luck.
I didn't think it would work that well.
It was skill.
You beat Ange, Prefect.
You just don't get it.
The woman I looked up to was never Ange.
The woman I always looked up to...
The woman I wanted so badly to be like...
...but never could.
It was you, Dorothy.
The truth is, I never cared about grades.
I only did everything I could to be a good student,
because I didn't want to disappoint anyone.
But I got tired of it all.
So you took a break, but you weren't careful...
and they got you?
Or...
Both.
If only I could have been more like you.
Prefect...
You know, that Christmas, it was my first time at a funfair.
It was fun.
I still dream about it.
About how we fooled around, and laughed together.
Then let's go again! Come to London!
I'll introduce you to my team, and...
Dorothy.
You were always like the wind.
So light and free.
Stop it, Prefect.
I don't want to shoot a friend.
Thank you.
Because you were kind enough to call me your friend,
I'll give you a Christmas present.
A free pass, to get you out of shooting your friend.
Don't do it... Prefect!
Goodbye, Dorothy.
Thanks, Ange.
For what?
When you jumped the gun back there...
you were trying to make sure
I didn't have to shoot Prefect, weren't you?
I was increasing the odds of our mission's success.
That's all.
For crying out loud, I'm surrounded by liars.
Well, we are spies.
Yeah. We are.
Enter.
Excuse us.
L has been transferred.
I am the General.
From now on, you will be taking orders from me.
Did something happen to L?
That's none of your concern.
You both did well on this last mission.
Since you were so successful, I would like you
to move right on to your next assignment.
Assignment... Sir?
Her.
That's...
You will assassinate Princess.