Hey, so I totally forgot to give this
to your mom on New Year's Day...
Safe Birth Charm
Oh, thanks!
I was so worked up that day...
Me, too.
I love her!
By the way, Yamato...
Why don't you come over?
I think she'd be happy to get
it from you personally.
Okay.
What're you doing?!
Cleaning.
That's too much!
I was like this when I had you, too.
With me, too?!
Oh, hello, Yamato-san.
Welcome back.
Hello!
I'll go buy some rice.
Wait, how much are you going to buy?
Rice?
Ten kilos.
I'll go!
Sale
Oh, really?
This much?
Buy the other stuff, too.
My Mom
The men in this home are such worrywarts.
He's a caring person.
He's overprotective...
Maybe I should show him my
prenatal checkup notes.
I have zero problems.
I'd love to become a strong
mother like you someday.
Right!
Men are such wimps, women have
to be the strong ones.
Eh?
Takeo-kun is plenty strong!
Not at all...
When he was about five,
we were waiting for the kindergarten bus,
and the idiot jumped into the street.
There!
I instinctively got Take out of there,
but I scraped my arm.
The scar
I was bleeding pretty heavily.
Then Take...
Bawling
Don't die, Mom!
And this is the boy who got bruises
and bled from cuts every day,
without making a single fuss.
Huh? Blood? I'm bleeding?
Then, from the start, Takeo-kun was caring!
He's a wimp.
He must care a lot about his mom.
So he's a mommy's boy to boot.
Men can be weak in surprising ways.
Please stick with him.
Okay.
...so when he was finally born,
everyone in the delivery room
clapped and cheered.
Wow!
They seem to be having fun.
When I brought him in for his
one-month checkup,
the nurse raised Takeo over her head and said,
"The yokozuna's here."
Like in the Lion King?
Yep.
What's the Lion King?
Oh, Takeo-kun...
Welcome back.
Thanks.
How much rice did you buy?
I thought we should stock up.
Did you use all the money in my wallet?!
My goodness...
Well, I'll be off to the hospital for my checkup.
Okay, don't trip!
Oh, um...
This is for you.
Safe Birth Charm
Oh, my...
Thank you, Yamato-san.
Hang in there.
Okay!
Off I go
Takeo-kun, when you were born,
you weighed 4,300 grams.
Yeah.
You heard that from Mom?
I was a preemie, so I was fewer than 2,000 grams.
For a long time, I was in this transparent case...
I was so small, I couldn't leave
the hospital with Mom.
I'm healthy now, though!
Okay, that's good.
Yeah!
I'm looking forward to meeting the new baby.
Hello.
Are you due soon?
Yes.
I'm anemic again, so I was asked to come in...
Mom, look!
Hey, stop running.
Is this the baby's brother?
Y-Yes.
We wanted our second child sooner,
but now he's much older...
I'm glad you got your wish.
Your big brother's waiting for you.
Hang in there.
Koshihikari
Don't lift that!
I'll do it!
Koshihikari
How did it go at the hospital?
Easy peasy.
I see.
When Yamato was born, she was half my weight.
She told me she couldn't
go home with her mom.
Oh...
Takeo,
there isn't a guarantee that babies born
into this world will live to grow up.
Honey, I'll clean the bathtub.
What's this?!
An angel!
Yamato Rinko
Subject: Me at 100 Days
Was I tiny?
She was so tiny...
I'm glad she grew up.
I was born larger than most,
and I never really got sick growing up.
I hadn't thought very much about it before.
But I guess that isn't always the case...
Hello.
Let me carry that for you.
Not you, too.
Everyone worries too much.
Oh...
Not as much as Takeo.
Having a caring friend like you
and a cute girlfriend,
Takeo's a lucky boy...
That's because he's a good man.
To me, he's still a little boy.
I hope this one will make good friends, too...
Thanks for the charm.
Mom's really happy with it.
She put it on the bag she takes everywhere.
Oh, really?
That makes me happy...
I hope I can meet the baby soon.
Mochi Waffle
Yeah.
I want to see your 100-day baby pictures, too.
Sure.
I'm back.
What're you doing?!
Oh, welcome back.
This posture is supposed to be good,
for ensuring a safe delivery.
Maybe so, but aren't you doing that too fast?
Mom?
That was a real strong kick.
This one will be really healthy.
I'm home.
Honey, I'll go clean the bath—
Takeo's 100-Day Celebration
I was huge.
To: Yamato
This is me at 100 days.
From: Yamato
So cute, Takeo-kun.
You're so round
Cute
I'm cute, huh?
I'll be off.
Wait, where do you think you're going?
I'm just taking a walk.
It's better to walk around a lot,
so the baby will be healthy.
I'll come, too!
Me, too.
At our ages, if we all take a walk together,
it'd be too embarrassing.
I'm off.
I'm worried.
Takeo, do you know why I married your mom?
No, I don't.
Well, she and I began working at
the company at the same time.
Your mom had this presence,
even as a new employee.
She worked very hard, so her
supervisor looked after her,
and all the other female employees
looked up to her...
I see.
That year, at the end-of-the-year party...
Takenaka-san, please pass that pot around.
Maiden Name
Takenaka Yuriko
Sure.
Be careful. It's hot.
Ow!
Yuriko-chan! Your hand!
I'm fine...
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'll go wash my hand.
I'm wearing a lot of layers, so it's fine.
Would you like me to bring some ice?
Oh... It's fine. Don't worry.
When I see cute girls like her,
I just want to protect them, you know?
That was the first time in my life,
I thought I'd want to ride out the turbulent
waves of life with someone like her!
Would you like to play golf with me?
You have strong core muscles.
Let's go for a drive.
I want to protect you, Takenaka-san.
Although, your mom's so strong,
I've never gotten around to protecting her.
Gouda-san?
Oh!
Gouda-san, you have another checkup
tomorrow, don't you?
I do.
We're both due soon, aren't we?
Yes.
See you tomorrow.
Gouda-san!
Are you okay, Gouda-san?!
I'm fine, I'm fine...
Are you okay?
Yes.
Be careful.
Thank you.
You don't know if it's a boy or a girl yet?
No.
Which one would you guess?
Oh, I have no idea.
I can't really imagine a girl...
guffaw
I can only think of the kid with your face.
Why are you laughing?
A little brother or sister...
You're right, I can only think of one face.
Suna, you're laughing too much!
I'm home.
What's wrong?
Did the baby kick again?
T-Take, get a taxi...
Mom's going to the hospital for a bit.
Taxi!
Where're all the taxis?
Takeo, did something happen?
I heard a really loud noise.
It's Mom...
Life
Fate
I see.
I should have just called one.
Dad's at work.
I have to keep it together.
Where to, sir?
What should I do?
What should I...
Sir?
Please go to Shisuda General Hospital.
I'll come, too.
Shisuda Hospital
Suna...
I'm fine...
Take, I left my wallet at home—
I'll go get it.
I've paid for the taxi.
You have a good head on your
shoulders, Makoto-kun.
Where's the wallet?
On the dresser.
Got it.
My goodness, I wish he'd calm down a little.
That's why he's a good man.
You're too nice to Takeo...
Both you and Yamato-san.
How's Mom?!
The doctor's with her now.
Calm down!
Calm down, Suna!
You calm down.
Sorry.
Yeah.
She's always been healthy, so...
I've never seen her like this.
Yeah.
Sorry...
Oh, Take, did you bring my wallet?
Yeah.
Are you both okay?
I'm going to be hospitalized.
Hospitalized...
I want you to do a couple things,
so write them down.
I'll do it.
In my room, there's a bag I put
together for the hospital stay.
Bring that.
Oh, and don't forget to wash the
dishes and do the laundry.
Tomorrow's flammables, so take out the trash.
I'll call Dad.
Take!
I'm fine, so don't worry.
I'll take you to your room.
Please take care of her!
O-Okay!
Did someone break in?
No, it was me.
I'll go drop this off!
See you
Gouda-san's in room 203.
Thanks.
Oh, the doctor is seeing your wife.
I'll take her bags.
Thanks!
Please look after her!
Suna?
Did he go home?
I have to keep it together.
Takeo-kun!
Sunakawa-kun told me...
your mom's been hospitalized?
Can I use your kitchen?
I'll make curry.
I went and got groceries!
Oh, welcome back, Takeo.
Excuse me!
Takeo-kun, you aren't peeling the vegetables?
Oh, is it like a macrobiotic thing?!
Definitely not.
Your pots are super heavy! Are they iron?!
Really?
Is that detergent?
Takeo, that's bleach.
So good.
Is it too sweet?
I like making curry on the sweet side.
You got your face dirty.
Huh?!
Ha ha, you make
a lot of bubbles
when you wash dishes!
You're using way too much detergent.
Oh, you don't have to walk me home.
Stay here, Takeo-kun.
Okay.
If you need any help, call me.
I'll come right away.
Okay, thanks.
I'm home.
Oh, there's curry.
Did you make it?
No, it was Yamato.
I see, I see...
You went by the hospital, right?
How was Mom?
How was my brother or sister?
Oh, they're fine.
Don't worry.
On your way back from school tomorrow,
stop by the hospital.
Okay.
I'm glad you were here!
I know another mother who's expecting,
due around the same time as I am.
When she tripped and I turned to catch her,
I felt a pain in my stomach.
I just couldn't help myself.
I wonder if our baby's mad at me for that...
It'll be fine.
You wanted to protect them both.
Next, turn to page 53.
Let's have one of you read the page.
I have to keep it together!
Is it the hospital?!
Yamato Rinko
Subject: Still have curry?
Can I come over today, too?
Is there still curry left?
Yamato...
I'm going to the hospital.
Sorry, we ate all the curry.
Can I come, too?
Of course! Mom would be happy to see you.
Shisuda Hospital
Really? I'll come, then.
I have to keep it together!
Don't run.
Sorry!
Hello!
Excuse me!
Oh, Take...
Don't look so worried.
Don't you have to stay lying down?
Hey, I'm not some invalid.
I'm fine.
OBGYN
Gouda Yuriko
Anything you want me to do?
Oh, buy me some water.
But doesn't she look pale?
She was sweating, too.
I don't really know anything about this,
but a human being's going to
pop out of another person.
I still wanna play!        It's time for dinner.
Isn't that a big deal?
Hey, it isn't over yet.             Man, you're so strong, Mom!
Isn't there something I can do?
Takeo-kun!
How's your mom?
Yamato...
It'll be okay!
I'm right here with you!
Her room's on the second floor, right?
Yeah.
I'm being pathetic...
I'm not a kid anymore.
It's Mom and the baby who're
having to tough it out.
Okay!
I'm going to go cheer on my mom a bit!
Mom!
Suna and Yamato have come to see you—
Take, use the intercom to call the nurse...
I've let the contractions go on too long.
I can't walk...
Okay! This one, right?
Takeo, this one.
Yes? What can I help you with?
Please come!
The baby's coming!
Mom, it's going to be okay!
She can't walk, so please bring a wheelchair.
Hey, can you hear me?!
I'm your brother!
Come out healthy!
I'm waiting for you!
What's wrong?
I'm sorry, I need a wheelchair, too...
Gouda-san, here's a wheelchair.
Please take the lady next to me first.
It's her first birth, and she's scared.
Oh, but...
Are you going to be okay?
I'm fine.
I'll carry Mom.
Go.
I'll follow.
Okay!
It's going to be okay.
Your brother will carry you.
Your brother's friend and girlfriend
want to meet you.
They're great people.
Your dad and mom are waiting for you, too.
You can feel safe coming out.
Thanks to Gouda-san,
my baby was born safely yesterday!
Hang in there, Gouda-san.
I will.
I hope our children can become friends.
Your friend's waiting, too.
This way, please.
Oh, wait.
Take, please bring my black bag.
Okay.
So fast!!
This one, right?
Yes, thanks.
Safe Birth Charm
Okay, I'll go push one out now.
Just wait and see.
Thanks...
Let's sit and wait.
Okay.
Gouda-san, your baby was born!
Huh?
It went fine!
That was fast!
She's a beautiful baby girl, at 4,200 grams!
Thank you!
Sir, your wife did really well.
He isn't the father.
Thank you!
I'm happy for you.
Congratulations to the new father.
He isn't the father.
Thank you!
I'm so relieved.
Wow...
You hung in there.
Mother: Gouda Yuriko
4,200 grams... You really worked hard.
She's so cute.
She's so small.
She's almost twice as big as
the other babies, though.
It's my first time seeing a real newborn!
She's pretty.
She's sleeping real peacefully.
I'd be okay with her marrying you.
The age difference is too great..
No, thanks.
I was born healthier than most,
and grew up bigger than most.
Yamato...
Someday, I'd like to have a
job helping other people.
Yeah.
That's really vague.
I never would've thought that Takeo would
carry me like a princess one day.
I've been thinking of him as a little boy,
but he's all grown up...
I see.
Let's raise another one together.
What should we name her?
The baby was really cute.
Super cute.
So tiny!
So warm.
So soft.
Wow, look at her nails...
I love Yamato when she's holding a baby.
So tiny!
So fluffy.
I want to become a kindergarten
teacher or a midwife.
Sounds like a plan.
That'd be two totally different
tracks in college, though.
Those are just details, Suna!
I wonder what your little sister will call you.
Maybe "Onii-chan."
Right!
Or maybe "Nii-san."
I'm sure it'll just be "Takeo."
That's what everyone calls you.
"Takeo"?!
Well, I don't mind.
My Chocolate
Next time: My Chocolate.