You're invading the Empire of Misurugi?
Lizardia sent word that Aura
was found in a secret compartment in the
deepest levels of the Misurugi's underground.
Beneath the Empire?
We will open a singularity at
the hour of Suzaku tomorrow morning.
We will invade Misurugi with
all our forces and take back Aura.
So why are you telling me this?
Are you ordering me to
join your fight or something?
Of course not.
You are free, Ange.
You can live in this world,
or return to that other Earth.
Of course, there would be
nothing more encouraging than
to have you fight alongside us.
I wanted to know how you felt about
this before we move out tomorrow.
Me?
We are indebted to you for saving our people.
I would like to help you in any way I can.
The Black Angel of Destruction
I think fighting alongside
the DRAGONs would be okay.
I'm sure Embryo's world would
be devastated if we rescued Aura.
But is it the right thing to do?
Huh?
I'm feeling doubtful.
About Salamandinay-san?
About everything.
It was a lie that the DRAGONs
were our enemies and attacking us.
It was a lie that Norma were
fighting to protect the world's peace.
It was all lies.
And I'm sick of it.
What if we fight with the DRAGONs,
and that's also a mistake?
Besides, a former princess joining the
DRAGONs to invade the Empire of Misurugi?
That's like a bad joke.
I don't know what's right anymore.
No one knows what's right.
Huh?
It's not what's right that's important.
It's about doing what you want to do, I think.
Just do your best for
what you think is right.
And I'll support you completely.
You're silly.
What'll happen if I do
things for such selfish reasons?
You think?
You're a relief, though,
the way you're so dense.
Thanks for the compliment.
Ange, Ange!
Mom says she wants to thank you!
Oh, my!
You perma-horny!
Thank you so much for
protecting us and our town.
I just helped Salako—
I mean, Salamandinay a little.
Besides...
There were a lot of people we couldn't save.
Say, "Ahh!"
He ate it!
Men are so cute.
Y-You think so?
Looks like you're having fun.
Ow...
Here, say, "Ahh."
What, you don't want it?
No, why?
You can't use your hands, can you?
I went too far.
I'm fine. It's not a big deal.
Ange's knight is invincible!
It's good.
And it's even better when you feed me.
Idiot.
This is a nice place.
Yes, you're popular, aren't you?
That's not what I meant...
But it really is a nice place.
Even though there's suffering,
even though there's no Mana,
everyone lives life to the fullest.
I see.
It's like Arzenal...
I'm going back home.
Momoka's waiting.
Ange...
I see. So you have made your choice.
I may be forced to fight you again.
Salako...
She's dangerous!
She knows too much about us.
Who knows how she'd
threaten us if she returned?
But Ange saved the townspeople!
It's not that long ago we
were trying to kill each other.
We should at least take her
into custody. And immediately.
I don't intend to fight you any longer.
See, she's going to—what?
I won't fight you again.
Then feel free to return to the other side
when the singularity opens in the morning.
I will have Kaname and Naga
escort you, if you require it.
S-Salamandinay-sama!
Why is it a surprise that I trust a friend?
Salako...
Be well, Ange.
Let us finish our competition
when this battle is over.
Next time, it'll be a karaoke competition.
So you're leaving tomorrow morning?
I'd better get ready, then.
I'm worried about the others, too.
But Vivian, you're...
Oh.
Mom...
Vivian.
Quiz time.
What's this?
Huh?
The answer is... your baby clothes.
You've gotten so big since then.
You wouldn't fit in this anymore.
And you've met a lot of people
and made a lot of memories.
Yeah.
So you have to go back, then.
Back to your friends.
Huh?
Don't worry about my injury.
I'm strong.
Mom...
Thanks for coming back, Mii.
I'm so happy I got to meet you again.
I hope you let me say,
"Welcome home," one more time.
Yeah.
I'll be back to say, "I'm home," for sure.
Viebel clan and Sylphis clan are standing by.
What about the Genomus clan?
They need more time to cross the river.
Whoa, it's a full course DRAGON menu!
It's a real spectacle.
Tusk-san...
I was looking forward to doing more
research on your adult male body.
It's a real shame...
Oh, i-it is?
Next time, we must experiment with mating.
Sorry, Doctor.
He's not a rare specimen
for you to experiment on.
He's my knight.
Right.
Get a room!
Let's go, you two.
Proud people of Aura, many moons have
passed since we were robbed
of the light we know as Aura.
The time for retaliation has come.
Now is the time to show
Embryo our anger and might.
Even if we children of Aura fall,
our wings will not break.
Woohoo!
Headquarters, this is
lieutenant guardian Salamandinay.
All units, move out!
See you!
What? You're acting creepy.
I'm just so happy.
You've finally accepted me as your knight.
Hey, if the DRAGONs win, is our fight over, too?
Huh? Yeah, probably.
We'll be bored!
What should we do then?
Huh?
I'm going to invite Salia and the others over!
To my house.
What about you, Tusk?
Me?
I'm going to open a small cafe
in a nice town by the sea.
With Ange.
I'm going to call it Angel's Cafe Ange.
The sea snake soup is going to be popular.
We'll live on the second floor
with our four children.
Vivian, you can kick him off.
Roger.
No, I mean...
I'm just hoping we'll
get to enjoy peace someday.
What about you, Ange?
Me?
Deploying singularity.
It's open!
All units, follow me!
But that sounds nice.
Cafe Ange...
Where are we?
Quiz time!
The answer is...
with our wind, our sea, and our sky!
We're back.
We're back!
We're 48,000 northeast of
our destination coordinates!
What's going on?
I don't know.
The singularity was
supposed to open over Misurugi.
Warning
What is it?!
It's...
What's that?
A black Villkiss...
Princess, what is this?
An ambush.
An ambush?!
Then Lizardia's intel...
Right now, our first priority
is defeating them.
All units, destroy the enemy!
What do you think?
Thanks to the information you provided,
your friends are being massacred...
Riza.
Or should I say Lizardia?
Stop!
Ange!
I'm going to help Salako.
Wait! This is Embryo's doing!
Should I sit here and watch instead?!
Shit.
Hang on tight, Vivian.
Right.
Right flank is down thirty percent.
The left flank's line isn't going to hold!
There're only five of them...
So fast!
That Villkiss...
Is it Ange?
Are you all right, Salako?
Yes.
Retreat while you still can.
I cannot.
Not until we take Aura back from Embryo!
You idiot! You're the
lieutenant guardian, aren't you?
Look around you.
Do you really think you're
going to get Aura back now?
But...
Ange is right.
Retreat for now, and regroup.
So you can win next time!
Aura...
All units, retreat.
All units, collapse the front
and retreat to the singularity.
Ange, take this.
Be safe.
Just go already!
The DRAGONs are retreating.
Irma, Tania, pursue them,
but don't go too far.
Yes, Knight Leader.
But...
I knew it.
You. Why?
Salia.
It's Salia!
But...
What do you think you're doing?
I'll ask the questions here.
It really is you, Ange-chan.
I'm shocked.
Ersha and Chris...
Ange, why are you fighting
alongside the DRAGONs?
Salia here.
Understood, Embryo-sama.
Ange, we're taking you into custody..
We have a lot of questions to ask you.
Got it, you two?
Yes, Knight Leader.
Retreat is successful.
Princess, hurry!
Ange!
No, Princess! The singularity is closing!
Ange...
I never knew you were so weak.
Huh?
No, it's that I've gotten stronger.
I've changed, thanks to Embryo-sama.
Now!
Use formation Shining Rose Triangle!
So lame...
Did you say something?
No, nothing.
Understood.
It's over, Ange.
Vivi-chan!
No way.
Nice catch!
Now!
Out of the way, Vivian!
Ange, I'm taking you to Embryo-sama.
"Embryo-sama," my ass.
Are you sleeping with that
creepy narcissist, or what?
I won't let you disrespect him!
Now!
Again!
Shining Rose Triangle!
Fly, Villkiss!
Ange!
You flew before!
You can fly again!
When are you going to fly, if not now?!
What's she yelling about?
Beats me...
I'll beat the shit out of you if you don't fly!
Fly!
What?
Wh-Where did she go?
No way, isn't this...
We're back at Arzenal.
Where did everyone go?
Do you think...
I'm sure they escaped safely.
Jill wouldn't go down so easily.
Hm?
What is that?
Monsters?
Ghosts?
Umibozu?
No!
An... sama...
No.
Angelise-sama!
No. I...
Momoka.
Angelise-sama!
Whoa, it's them!
Ew, the DRAGON chick!
Is it really you, Ange?
Of course, Hilda.
So you really are a man.
Next Episode
Four episodes ago, I was thrown into the sea.
My last line was, "You fatass!"
Now I'm back as a bad guy?
Maybe the staff hates you.
They hate you more, Ange.
The Sea of Parting
What? What?!