Doctor!  Big news!
What?!  Yamamoto Yumi-san?!
Yes!  My next opponent
is Yamamoto Yumi-san!
You're really playing against
Yamamoto Yumi-san?!
From the Suihoku society?!
Yes!
Yamamoto Yumi-san!
Doctor, what should I do?!
Yamamoto Yumi-san...
You've got bad luck, Chihaya-chan.
Okay, let's try this.
Yamamoto...
Excuse me, who is Yamamoto-san?
Ayase Chihaya
Yamamoto Yumi.
Yamamoto Yumi
The previous Queen.
Chihaya Furu
Verse 22
Just
As
My
Beauty
Has
Faded
G-Good luck!
Ayase Chihaya-san...
She's just as pretty as everyone said.
She's nothing like me,
with my plain looks and name.
I'm already sick of her.
Why are her eyes shining?
That just makes it harder.
We will now proceed with fifteen minutes
of memorization time for the second round.
You have until 11:17 by that clock.
Why did I enter this tournament again?
I'm playing the previous
Queen, Yamamoto Yumi-san.
Th-This is...
Five one-syllable cards on her side?!
Seven three-syllable cards!
Everything else is a two-syllable card!
I can attack like crazy!
Luck is on my side!
I missed the Queen match this year,
but I saw last year's at Dr. Harada's house.
Miss Yamamoto, congratulations
on your first Queen title.
Your moment of glory comes in
your last year of college.
How do you feel right now?
Coach Kitano...
I really hate Kitano, but he
has a model student here!
When you kids become Master or Queen,
make sure you call my name!
I don't really remember
how the match went.
Just that she absolutely
refused to give up.
That she called her teacher's name.
Her tears.
A posture that took years to perfect.
And the calluses to show for it.
She worked hard to make
her dream come true.
The previous Queen is strong,
but you've learned when to
give yourself the go sign.
You can control a match
against the previous queen.
Is that Ayase's opponent?
I've seen her before at
the Suihoku society,
but I've never seen her practice.
She has an office job,
so we're on different schedules.
Nishida, you've been
in the Suihoku society
since you were little,
so you should know.
What's Yamamoto Yuri-san like?
Wait, what?!
102, 103, 104...
I was burned...
Lost by 20 cards...
He hasn't recovered from the shock
of losing to Sudo-san from Hokuo.
Hey, Nishida.  You okay?
This was the first time
I ever met a real sadist.
It's too bad I don't get to eat you
after roasting you in a karuta match,
since it'd be bad for my health.
I can't believe Ayase actually beat him.
I'm scared.  Class A is scary.
There are all these monsters
that I can't beat!
There, there.
By the way, what's Yamamoto
Yuri-san's karuta like?
Yamamoto Yumi!  Yumin!
Huh?  Sorry.
Wait, Yumin?
Yumin's playing style is
persistent and stubborn.
After she became Queen,
she settled down a bit,
but the real Yumin is...
Idiot!
Stop talking with that Shiranami
boy and come over here!
Kana-chan and Komano-kun, too!
You're with us now!
Huh?
Cheer for Yumin!
Watch her reclaim the title of Queen!
Cheer her on!
Coach...
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
Here comes spring, now the flower blooms
It's starting to get warm
now that the sun is out.
We'll need to take a
break to air out the room.
The players won't last much longer.
Here comes spring, now the flower blooms
May the scarlet kadsuras of Mount
Afusaka live up to their name
Her swing is compact and measured.
Her body knows how far away each card is.
I'm impressed.
Even the air feels too warm.
The heat works against
us in this tournament.
You're absolutely right, Doctor!
But... I like it.
Normal people can never join us here.
The players are all in Class A.
Every little sound matters.
We all understand how important sound is.
and allow us this secret rendezvous
Top-class readers are used for
the Master and Queen qualifiers,
The hazy early morning light
comes not from the moon
and I'm playing against the previous Queen!
This is fun!
She got it!
Nice!
Stay on the attack!
My fear is not...
Attack!
After I determined...
Three in a row!
She even managed to win
a three-syllable card!
She hasn't committed any faults today.
She's on a roll!
Huh?
You're still in good shape, Yumin!
You can win!
It's time to get stubborn!
This girl is in high school,
much like the Queen.
Young, beautiful, and talented at karuta.
God is so unfair.
All I have is karuta.
Karuta has been my life
since I was a child.
And yet...
After working ten years to
earn the title of Queen,
I lost that title to Wakamiya
Shinobu a year later.
A fifteen-year-old was able to
prevent me from playing my karuta.
She's probably forgotten
about me already.
That's how strong she was.
If I win here, I still have
to face her in the end...
I can't win...
It's so hot...  I'm dying...
Hey, look at the condensation.
How hot is it inside?
Why does the window have to fog up?!
Yumin won't be able to see us!
You can still stage a comeback, Yumin!
You can win!
is that I have no way
to tell you in person
While I sigh and lament how the one
I love does not feel the same,
Four in a row for Ayase!
You were so close, Yumin!
Huh?
Why did she smile?
She's played karuta all her life,
yet she's leaning back.
She isn't following through on her swing.
The previous Queen...
Someone who achieved her dream...
...is losing her passion?
What's wrong with Yumin?
Will she be okay?
Of course she will!
Yumin's tenacity is about to kick in!
It was an unfortunate ending.
You haven't been practicing as
much because you have a job now.
Yumin, you can avenge yourself
against Wakamiya next year.
Eighth place in the national tournament?
That's a pity.
I know you could have placed higher.
What's wrong, Yumin?
You lost in the second round
of the Kanezawa tournament?
Yumin, it just wasn't your day!
Don't worry.
In terms of skill, you're number one!
Yes, I'll try my best.
She's tired.
Not tired of losing.
She's tired of failing
to meet expectations.
It's so hot in this room,
but her soul is growing colder.
Chihaya-chan, you've learned when
to give yourself the go sign.
Dr. Harada...
I won't let a person who's given
up take a single card off me!
The condensation's so bad
that we can't see inside.
It must be really hot in there.
I wonder if Chihaya-chan is okay.
Hang in there, Chihaya!
Yumin...
I can't see anything!
The window's so fogged up
that I can't see a thing!
Coach Kitano, you have to stay quiet!
Idiot.
Huh?
Long last we meet...
That was a dead card.
When the misty bridge...
Why is she swinging so
hard on a dead card?
Gust of wind...
Five in a row for Ayase!
Yumin!
She's going hard after every card?
Why?
She was being careful before.
It's like she thinks she
can dominate this match.
Dominate?
It's getting hard to see.
Is it really that much hotter inside?
Can we get someone to wipe
the windows from the inside?
Class A matches are incredible.
Yes,
but I'm a little sad.
Huh?
I mean...
Nobody is actually
listening to the poems.
That...
might be true.
But...
The emotions experienced
after a long-awaited reunion
banish any lingering memories of the past
Her voice is so clear!
Like there isn't a glass
window between us.
Because she's reading poetry...
Poetry can transcend any barrier.
Readers are pretty amazing.
They have ranks and exams.
There are less than ten special readers
qualified for the Master match.
Special readers...
How hard is it to become one?
Chihaya-chan...
Listen to the poems.
She thinks that her victory is in sight.
What's with them?
First, Wakamiya Shinobu, now, this girl...
They expect every player to
be oozing with confidence.
I lost my confidence a long time ago!
But that's why I understand now.
You can't let your passion take over.
Impassioned was your...
She went for "Impassionate"
instead of "Impassioned was"!
Did Chihaya hear wrong?
And she touched a card
on the opponent's side
while the correct one was on her own!
It's a double fault!
Chihaya-chan...
I can't see!
I can't see a thing!
What am I doing?
She made a mistake.
Pathetic.
The previous Queen needs her
opponents to make mistakes.
the red that is the Tatsuta River
From a 7 card lead to a 4 card lead.
I've played hundreds
of matches, so I know.
The match will be determined here.
What am I doing?
How could I make a mistake now?
How could I mess up "Impassionate"?
Why?
I still have a chance.
I can do this.
Ki-Kitano-san!
You can't open a window during the match!
Fool!
If it's too hot, they're
going to suffocate!
You have to let some air in
or the players will keep suffering!
You're not supposed to do
anything without permission!
I don't give a damn!
Wipe the windows!
Coach Kitano...
That feels so good.
You just helped my opponent recover.
Come on, Kitano-san!  That's enough!
You're still in good shape!
Play your own karuta!
Enough already!
I'm going to close the window.
If you don't want me to
open the window again,
you better wipe it every ten minutes!
Coach Kitano...
My own karuta...
Yes, my own karuta...
He just helped every simple-minded
player in the room.
My own karuta...
My own karuta.
Next time, you can avenge
yourself against Wakamiya.
You should be excited, Yumin.
You get to be a challenger again!
My own karuta.
My own...
The karuta that comes from all the
practice I've done with everyone.
I'm going to play...
My own karuta!
Alas, another autumn has passed in vain
I know that my heart is all aflutter
Yes!  Got it!
What?  Please wait.
I believe that card is mine.
Huh?
But I'm the one who hit it...
You may have knocked it away,
but my pinky touched it first.
Like this.
Huh?
You just happened to knock it away.
B-But...
Are you sure you touched it first?
I saw everything happen.
My pinky was on the edge of the card.
But, um...
I think I was first...
After that, you knocked
the card away from above.
Watch.
This is what happened.
U-Um...
Then you can take it...
What was that?
Sh-She's back!
The legendary Contest Yumi!
Contest Yumi?
Yeah.
She's known for contesting every close call
with absolute confidence.
I touched it first.
I'm positive!
While she's arguing, everyone
else has to stop playing,
so most people frown upon her habit.
She stopped because it was
unfitting for the Queen.
That doesn't matter anymore.
I'm just a challenger now.
Th-This makes it harder...
Your right hand is on the playing field.
Huh?
Oh, I'm sorry!
She's making it harder.
Focus...  Focus!
It might be harder, but I still have
to focus on taking the cards I can!
There are plenty of my
sweet cards on the field!
and by no fault of mine
Swift waters parted...
Yes!
She did it!
You seem to be confused.
I'm supposed to keep one-syllable
cards on my own side.
"I won't let her take a
single card off me."
Why would I think that?
I'm playing against the previous queen!
No matter where...
For the cold nights...
Karuta is scary...
Chihaya has lost all of her confidence.
She's freezing up and making mistakes.
I didn't realize that mental
strength was so important.
Mental strength.
How badly you want it...
Yes!
Please wait.
I touched that card before you did.
What?
Look, I hit it here.
That pair keeps arguing.
The match will never end.
Don't worry about it, Yumin.
People will remember your
tendency to contest cards,
but your karuta happens to
be that much more refined,
that much more accurate.
Everyone here knows how difficult
it is to get to that point.
I hide in the mountains, only to
hear the haunting cry of a deer
You can do it!
Yumin!
None are left...
You did it, Yumin!
Thank you very much.