I didn't know you were
in a relationship, Akane.
Miu messaged me on LINE.
Why?
She was in my class in first year.
The news is spreading?
No way...
I mean, even I'm getting
messages about it now.
School check-in day could be rough.
You're going to get so much attention.
Isn't it next week?
August 10th?
Oh, yeah, you're right.
School's such a pain.
Open for Prayers
Let's take ten.
I'll do my best
Want to go home together after school?
Sorry
Sorry, I have practice
Dazai once said, "There is such a thing
as love in this world. I'm sure of it.
It's the expression—the etiquette—
of love that is so hard to find."
What? Seriously?
Yeah, Azumi and Mizuno.
No way!
For real?
I know!
Dude, Kota! Holy crap!
You're famous!
Is it sexy? Is it sexy?
You dating? You dating?!
Morning.
Morning!
Akanecchi!
Over here.
B-But...
Just come.
Hey, Akanecchi.
Yeah?
Why Azumi?
Miu, harsh!
But I had no idea.
Sorry.
Hey, what do you like about him?
Well...
What? Nothing?
Nothing?
There's obviously something.
No, it's...
I don't know.
But you like him anyway?
I totally thought it would be Hira.
I know.
Me, too.
No more secrets, okay?
Okay.
Let me know if you guys kiss.
I don't think Azumi can do it.
I don't think he has the guts.
Please submit your summer break
homework if you've finished it.
Summer School
There's less than half of summer break left.
Be sure to keep up the pace.
Aren't you going home together?
She has practice.
So wait for her.
You're the literature club
president, aren't you?
Yeah.
Mizuno-san!
I have club, too.
Okay.
Here we go.
Ready... Go!
It's so hot.
I'm so hungry.
Want to stop by the convenience store?
All-nighter?
Probably
Take care of yourself
Yeah, thanks
I'll be waiting in the library
Let's have lunch together
Yeah, let's go.
What flavor ice cream should I have today?
What flavor...
H-Hey, I...
Gotta go?
Yeah.
Are you going home together?
Okay.
Later.
Lucky Akane.
Boyfriends are just a hassle.
I really don't get it.
Akane-chan.
Akane...
Open
Let's eat.
That hits the spot.
You old fart.
Well, it's so hot.
Is your club keeping you busy?
Very.
It's every day.
Wow.
And the literature club?
We just do whatever.
Plus, I have summer lessons
and festival prep.
Oh, right. Cram school.
Yeah.
I guess I'll start that after I retire from track.
In the fall?
Yeah.
Sorry.
I found the book you were looking for
I'll be there after practice
Got it
Thank you
Can you make it to practice?
There's something I want to work on
What's up?
He's asking if I can come to practice today.
For the hayashi?
Yeah.
I want to see!
Can I come with you?
Sure, I guess.
Yay!
Sorry, would I be bothering you?
No, not at all.
Let's take it from the top.
Okay.
Well, this is unusual.
Who might you be?
Hello.
Kotarou's girlfrie—
Hey!
His girlfriend!
Oh, so this is your girlfriend, huh?
Here.
Man...
If you want...
Thanks.
What did you think?
It was so good.
I've never seen it before. I loved it.
Great.
Sorry to call you out during
your time together.
It's fine.
Oh, yeah, Hikawa Shrine...
They have wind chimes right now.
I've never been there.
It's awesome.
Good work today.
Hang on.
Here.
Just take it.
But...
I'll take care of locking up.
I'm here.
I told my mom I was going to the
festival, and she had me put it on.
What do you think?
Y-You look great.
Thanks.
So much potato stuff.
Kawagoe's known for them.
Yeah.
Yum.
We have them at my place all the time.
Lucky.
I used to hate them.
They're so old-fashioned.
I like them now, though.
I have one of these.
It feels really nice. Try it.
You're right.
I want one, too.
Aw, these are cute!
They're so adorable!
I like Japanese-style stuff.
Yeah?
It suits you.
Fortunes?
When's your birthday?
August 7th.
It's already past!
Why?
Why what?
You should have told me!
I didn't know.
We didn't do anything to celebrate.
It's fine.
Aw, man...
No one's ever celebrated it
since it's during summer break.
I'm going to go call home again.
Home?
Smartphone Covers
Japanese
Patterns
Money...
I'm back.
Done?
Yeah.
Um...
Let's go.
They're so pretty.
I've never been here before.
It's amazing.
Yeah.
Apparently you can write wishes on the chimes.
Relationship Fortune Tags
500 yen each
May you be blessed
with good relationships
I'd like two.
One thousand yen, please.
What did you write?
It's a secret.
It's embarrassing.
Want to keep going?
Yeah, let's go.
Ow.
What's wrong?
Sorry, I...
Can you give me a minute?
Let me.
There.
Thanks.
Let's go.
H-Hang on.
Here.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
Open it.
Sorry, I didn't have time to choose,
so it's the same as mine.
Wow... I love it.
Wait, did you just go buy it earlier?
Yeah.
Wow!
I'm glad you like it.
I didn't know when to give it to
you, or if you'd even like it.
I couldn't stop thinking about it.
The whole time I was thinking,
"Wow, the wind chimes are pretty,"
my heart was pounding.
I'm glad I could give it to you, though.
Th... Thanks, Akane-chan.
Can I call you that?
Yeah.
And I'll call you Kotarou-kun.
Term 2 Opening Ceremony
10:00 - Gymnasium
Don't be late!!
I've never seen Azumi and
Akanecchi talking, have you?
Azumi's pretty plain.
Come on, what do you like about him?
Azumi-kun kind of keeps to himself,
but I feel really safe when I'm with him.
Have you changed, Akanecchi?
They say people change
when they fall in love.
Has anything happened?
Tell us!
No secrets, remember?
I wish for us to be
together forever
Vita Sexualis
Aira and Kaneko 2
Hey, I know her.
Who is she?
She's a new idol.
She's in dramas and stuff lately.
She's so cute, isn't she?
Try doing that pose.
Are you crazy?
I want to see you do it.
Here?
L-Like this?
You actually thought I was serious?
Stupid.
Jeez!
You're cute enough without doing that.
Ryouko-sensei and Roman 5
Summer break is so long.
Miu and Inaba 5
Welcome!
Takoyaki
Okonomiyaki
Jeez, there are so many people.
Hey, I want that.
Buttered Potatoes
Fruit Stand
Two of these, please!
I wish I were here with a boyfriend.
What am I?!
Sakura and Roman
Yo, Kota.
Wait up.
Huh?
Did you switch lip gloss?
Ew, creepy!
How could he tell I changed my lip gloss?
He's totally checking me out!
Gross!
Oh my God...
I mean, I am kinda happy...
Aoi Takizawa: A Girl
One, two, three, four...
How many times do I have to tell you?
Come on, do it right.
Ow, ow, ow!
Yes, sir! Sorry, sir!
Me too, Senpai.
I can't do it either, Senpai.
Do it right!
Aoi's popular.
Boys are so annoying.
Ryouko-sensei and Roman 6
Graduation's so far off.
Kotarou's Parents
Novels?
I was cleaning Kotarou's room,
and I found his half-finished novels.
You read them?
I haven't read them yet.
I can't condone you reading
them, even as his mom.
There must be rules against that.
You think so?
You've got a pretty good
grasp of how women think.
He really doesn't understand how women think.