What a kill count,
and on only her third mission.
Not bad, not bad.
No one could use that machine well,
and then she does it so effortlessly.
The Villkiss must have accepted Ange.
So then she's—
Shall we begin, then?
The Libertus.
Got a problem with that, Salia?
She'll die immediately.
She the villain that killed their captain
and their beloved new recruits.
Of course they hate her.
She...
I could do it.
I'll show you.
I can handle the Villkiss better.
So why?
The right person for the job.
If something happens to the Villkiss—
I'll fix it if it comes to that.
I'll stake my life on it.
That's our duty, after all.
Mei.
Focus on your own duty.
Got it, Salia?
Good girl.
Things are going to get busy now, huh?
Again, don't get cocky.
Especially towards the officer.
"Good girl," huh?
You're a sly woman, aren't you?
I'll use whatever I can.
Feelings, lives.
I'm already in hell.
A Loner's Revolt
Destroyed three Scuna-class,
and an anchor driven into a Galleon-class.
Subtracting ammo,
fuel consumption, and armor wear,
this week you earned 180,000 cash.
That's it?
That's enough. I only earned a single digit.
And you, Hilda?
Five and a half million cash for the week.
Good going, Ange.
She really earned it.
Thank you for your deposit.
What's wrong?
My.
Was it you guys again?
Gee, who knows.
Wh-What's your problem?
Rosalie.
Bitch.
Damn.
You worry too much, Dad.
Don't worry, I've learned how to do my job,
and I'm getting used to the Norma.
So long as I keep my eye on them,
not a single Norma is
going to step out of line.
S-Stop!
You, why are you dressed like that?
It's my uniform.
I will not allow you to dress in a
way that disturbs this base's order.
Fix it or buy a new one, immediately.
That's an order.
Ah.
"Understood, Officer."
Don't forget your salutes.
Really.
Are you not embarrassed
to dress so shamelessly?
Are you embarrassed
when a bug sees you naked?
Excuse me.
Did you hear that?
She seriously pisses me off.
What's her problem?
You're a Norma, too, you skank.
Ow!
Are you going to buy a new one?
I don't have that kind of money.
I'll have to teach that whore properly.
Yeah, until she cries and
begs for forgiveness.
Right, Hilda?
Yeah.
Let's give her space.
She's the most shocked
about Zola-oneesama's death.
We have to be the ones to avenge Onee-sama.
For Hilda, too.
Ow.
Whoopsies.
You little—
Rosalie!
Wh-What was that for, you—
Rosalie.
Holy shit, that was bad.
That whore, I'm going to wreck her.
Dammit, what am I going do
about that wretched whoregoblin?
Sh-She wears that?
She's a total slut!
Let's hang it in the hallways.
I'll shame her to hell and back.
That was a good shower.
This will be awesome.
Huh?
Yeah, that ugly pig hoe's
skanky bitch panties.
Let's expose her.
Yeah, nice, nice.
Say it again.
Ugly pig hoe's skanky bitch panties...
Hello, I'm the ugly pig hoe skank bitch.
Ersha Lariat!
Ersha Special Magnum!
You should stay a little longer, dear.
Air Ersha Wheel!
They have a new one!
Auntie, how much is this?
Call me Onee-san.
Dammit.
The super chrome steel boomerang blade?
Eighteen million cash.
Gladly!
Thank you.
Whoa, sexy.
Looks pretty cool.
Do you have uniforms?
Do I?
I've got everything from bras to
railway guns here at the Jasmine Mall.
How could she have ended up like that?
Bye.
You're going already?
You should buy weapons and stuff, too.
You've made a ton, haven't you?
Hey, how about this one?
I think it'd look awesome on your machine.
A Para-mail is a Norma's casket.
It's because you'll die there
that you're allowed to
customize it to your liking.
Powerful weapons,
thick armor, flashy decorations.
It's one of few freedoms given to Norma.
Pointless.
You can't blame the
others for targeting you,
if you're going to be like that.
But even that is something
that money can save you from.
Safety, peace of mind, and life...
It's not just material objects that you can buy.
Buy them out, huh?
You're indeed a princess.
You're quick to understand.
How about 10,000,000 for handling each?
Such a shameless Norma.
I'm fine by myself.
I've been dismissing it
as just blowing off steam,
but it's becoming intolerable lately.
I know you don't like her, but—
Don't you have a problem with this?
She killed our captain and two
new recruits, but she's still alive!
But she bought all our graves,
and she came back to the battlefield.
She's already redeemed herself.
That's enough?
You're telling us to stop over that?
Maybe a good girl like you could,
but not the rest of us ordinary people.
Hilda.
What the hell is Command thinking?
Her only punishment was
being put in that crappy machine.
Ah, I bet Command likes her, too.
I guess then I can understand why.
Smooth-talking that Commander...
Impressive. Her Majesty the Princess
must be good in bed, too.
That's insubordination.
And if it is?
I won't let you mess with Ange any more.
You're defending her, when she
looks at you like you're a bug?
That's an order.
Fine, Captain.
Let's go, you two.
Dammit, you two need to go all the way.
You could have helped, if you were watching.
I was busy, too.
That key.
I haven't been in this room for a while.
Captain.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't even avenge you right.
Quit crying.
Just leave everything to me from now on.
I bought up all of it.
Everything Zola left.
It's mine now.
Hilda.
This room, the two of you...
You're all mine.
Got it?
Y-Yes.
High-speed armor piercing shells,
high-output variable gears,
composite armor, and potato chips.
There are so many things I want!
It must suck not wanting anything, too.
And now for a quiz.
What is Salia reading?
Training instructions.
It's tough, being in charge and
readying and managing troops.
So do you think you can do it?
I wouldn't be struggling if it were so easy.
No fun.
You promised, Jill,
that you'd give me that machine.
You look scary again.
Hey.
You have a better expression
when you're reading the usual stuff.
The usual stuff?
You know, that one in your second drawer,
the one with the boy and girl kissing.
Now show me your everything!
Stop it!
Go through my things again,
and I'll really stab you.
Sorry.
Time to eat.
Let's go, Salia.
I'm—
I'm going to study some more.
Yeah? Okay.
Readying and managing troops?
So complicated.
Oh, yeah.
It's good, isn't it?
Ersha's on cooking duty today.
Lucky us.
Hi, there!
Ersha's curry is the best curry.
Time to eat.
It's so good.
Oh, yeah.
I'll give you this.
Quiz time.
What could this be?
The correct answer is, it's a set!
With me, Hilda, and you in a forward,
I think we can form an even stronger team.
This is so we have proof.
I told you, I'm fine by myself.
Ange.
Ange-chan.
I liked you, Zola.
All assemble.
That's it for today.
Dismissed.
I'm going to work hard.
For you, too, Onee.
Type 1 contact warning.
Para-mail First Troop, prepare for sortie.
I repeat, Type 1 contact warning.
All right, bring it to the deck.
Para-mail First Troop, prepare for sortie.
Signal received from Observation Post 21.
Planck signal above threshold detected at
Partial breaking of chiral symmetry.
Singular point opening.
altitude 2,400, bearing 83 degrees, 50 minutes.
T plus 280 from estimated opening.
Estimated fifteen Scuna-class.
Classes and numbers undetermined
due to absence of signal.
Respond as appropriate upon contact.
All soldiers, man your machines.
Reactor temperature rising
to 2 million degrees Kelvin.
Igniting plenum chambers.
Ow.
Air traffic controller evacuation confirmed.
Open blast doors immediately.
Brainless insects.
Ange, your final checks!
PMA exterior armor normal.
How are the interiors?
Dammit! No issues.
All units, release safety.
Open force gates, raise landing gear.
Runway clear. Ready for lift-off.
All units ready for lift-off.
Salia Squadron, sortie!
Salia Squadron, Ange lifting off.
Distance to Singular: 12,000
Roger. All units disable safety.
The door's opening.
Fire!
Ange, don't charge in by yourself!
Whoa, Ange!
What are you doing?
Get your machine under control.
Want some help?
Piss off, cockroach!
Villkiss!
Where are you going, Salia-chan?
A big one's coming.
Destroying them is our
top priority right now.
Target the Brig-class ahead.
All units, attack!
Shit.
Next Episode Preview
See? All I ever do is scream and shout.
The staff is so repetitive.
Can't they make me say something cute?
Like "mweeheehee" or "teehee" or "nyan, nyan"?
Ange, Lost
What? Next week? Really?