All right, first-years, introduce yourselves.
Right!
I-I'm Suga Koshi from Nagamushi Junior High.
I played setter.
Thank you for having me.
I-I'm Azumane Asahi from Sekodai Junior High.
I played left. Thank you for hafing mwe!
I messed up…
I'm Sawamura Daichi from
Izumitate Junior High!
I played left.  After seeing
Karasuno's match at nationals,
I decided I would come to Karasuno!
Thank you for having me!
Oh, I see. That's great.
Let's strive to win at nationals!
Right!
Oh, I'm Tashiro.
I guess you could call me
the captain of this club.
All right. I'll stop by again
once you guys are done.
Right!
All right, let's start practice!
Um...
That teacher was the advisor, right?
Is there someone else that's
more like a coach?
Nope.
That was Kurokawa-kun from
Hisa Junior High, right?
Do you know him?
Our schools played each other,
and I remember his offense and
defense both being really good.
Seriously? That's awesome.
We finally made it to the Karasuno!
Haikyu!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Episode 06: The Chemical Change of Encounters
Hey, Kurokawa. Tell me the
secret behind receiving serves.
I'm the type that goes right for the
ball once the other team hits it.
I see...
Clean up!
Right!
Say, even though there's a tournament coming up,
we haven't had many practice matches...
They were saying that ever
since Coach Ukai's been gone,
we've lost connections with other schools.
Apparently, even the school we
regularly had practice matches with
declined the offer for the most recent match.
Why?
It means that we're not
worth their precious time.
I knew that Karasuno was
different than before...
But I thought that if we kept practicing,
we could bring things up again.
It's not like there were big troubles,
or any hopeless situations...
Yet...
There was a fear that felt like we
were gradually getting lost...
Um...
Could I stay behind and
practice a little more?
I'll make sure to lock up!
M-Me, too!
Me, too! We'll let Sensei know, too!
S-Sure...
We can't go on like this!
It may seem like there's time,
but there really isn't!
You totally sound like a teacher!
Are you really the same
age as us, Sawamura-kun?
Even if we just pick up the balls,
there's still something we can do!
Read the ball's course
from the form of the spike!
Hey! Why did you catch that?
I-I'm sorry!
We'll think and act on our own.
We'll do everything that
we possibly can right now.
Starting tomorrow, we have
the Inter-High qualifiers.
Let's do our best so that
we don't have any regrets.
Right!
Let's strive to win at nationals!
Hey, I've been thinking this for a while,
but why don't we strive for
something more attainable?
What?
They say that aiming for goals that are too
high is connected to losing confidence,
and not good.
Wh-What the heck?
Every time I would mention
winning at nationals,
you would just scoff and ignore me...
Now you want to argue with me?
What the heck? Why the heck am
I sort of happy about this, damn it?!
Wha? Like I would know!
I don't feel like we were
able to share our goals,
but I feel like we're definitely
doing better than before!
And we all share the desire
to win the upcoming match.
We're gonna win this thing!
Yeah!
And so, the Miyagi qualifiers
of the Inter-High...
Karasuno                   Araigawa
Karasuno lost in the second round,
and the third-years retired.
Karasuno's fallen back down to earth...
We started working together way too late.
You know how they say,
"Chance favors the prepared mind," right?
There's a chance that Karasuno may
never get stronger...
Even if they do, it might
be years from now.
Even so, if the chance appears,
you'd better grab it!
Now. We have to go now.
This is that chance!
Hinata's block that the opponent
hadn't been ready for
will definitely shake them up.
That itself is a subtle crack
and the wind's definitely
blowing in our favor right now.
Karasuno              Shiratorizawa
Chance ball!
Damn it!
Guard that desperately stolen half-step
lead with everything you've got!
Goshiki!
I moved a moment late!
Hinata's block that suddenly
enters the field of view...
They can't just ignore it.
It's definitely going to be a straight.
Leave it to me!
All right!
Nice kill, Asahi!
I can't lose to Hinata and Tanaka.
Kageyama, you got a great receive, too.
Thanks.
Karasuno            Shiratorizawa
Their serve is strong!
We're going to cut it off at one!
Right!
Nishinoya!
Sorry! It's long!
Hold it, Tsutomu!
Karasuno's setter has his back to the net.
There won't be a dump. Watch carefully...
He's already there!
All right!
Damn it!
We've gotten this far, and their
moves are as sharp as ever.
They must be stamina monsters.
Man...
That move's gotta be hard to repeat.
Shiratorizawa!
We're counting on you!
That #10 finally went back.
Shiratorizawa!
Tsukki! Don't lose to Hinata!
Huh?!
Shiratorizawa!
It's not like we're competing.
Hey.
Huh?
We're counting on you!
Right!
Shiratorizawa!
I can do it, but can you?
Well... I practiced with Akaashi-san, so...
This guy's practicing
with Fukurodani's setter?
I'm super jealous!
Hinata!
Shiratorizawa!
Sit! From here on out, it's going
to be a battle of stamina.
Rest while you can.
Shiratorizawa!
Okay.
I don't want to lose to Hinata, either.
This time, I'm going to
make my chance for sure!
Yamaguchi-kun, nice serve!
Huh? Looks like he's going to hit
really close to the edge this time.
Your serve will become a weapon.
Straight. Just concentrate
on hitting straight.
Right where Ushiwaka is!
Yes! We broke through!
And...
Goshiki!
Right!
Ushiwaka will follow...
Three blockers!
Don't underestimate me.
I'm going to break through!
One touch!
Why, you...
Nice cover!
One person time difference...
You're not the only one
that was preparing a new move
at the training camp, Hinata.
All right!
Karasuno              Shiratorizawa
Karasuno broke through!
That first-year is pretty ballsy.
Damn it, Tsukishima! Damn it...
Nice kill, Tsukki!
You're lowering your elbows!
You're not going to be able to hit anything
even if it's perfectly hittable like that!
You've got those huge bodies of yours!
So you need to be more...
Dynamic?
Yeah!
Shiratorizawa!
It's true that Karasuno's defense
is evolving throughout the match,
Shiratorizawa!
even if it's just a thin veneer.
But...
A defense with no holes doesn't exist.
Shiratorizawa!
Yamaguchi, one more!
It's in! Towards the front!
Got it!
Damn it...
Ushiwaka's hits aren't easing up.
But since he's hit so much, he must
be feeling it in his legs by now.
Yeah. If Ushiwaka keeps going like this,
he'll eventually reach
the end of his stamina.
Karasuno               Shiratorizawa
Go, Asahi-san!
Got it!
It didn't line up!
All right! Lucky!
My heart felt so tight!
But it all worked out!
They're at set point!
Their first five-set match,
and their opponents have been to
nationals more than once.
The fourth set on is unknown
territory for Karasuno.
He's able to make sense out of
their #10's ridiculous attacks,
and has been doing it ever since
the match started like it was easy.
Precision may be expected of him,
probably more than anyone else...
And as he faces more pressure from the
opponent's blockers than anyone else,
he touches the ball more than
anyone else in the match.
Looks like that one might have
reached his limits first.
Sorry.
You apologizing is creepy, so please don't.
What?!
See? You're fine.
Daichi-san, nice serve!
Front!
Ushijima-san!
All right!
Damn it!
Could that be their second pinch server?
Since it's Shiratorizawa, I'm sure
they've got a deep team.
Please just don't bring this into a deuce...
Let's go!
A jump float serve!
Sorry!
Azumane-san!
He picked it up!
It's Ushiwaka!
Wakatoshi!
Here we go. Ready, and...
Damn!
When you defend a part of the court,
you are always sacrificing
another part of the court.
If you brace for a powerful hit
and move back, of course...
The front will be open.
Nice kill, Ushijima!
Karasuno              Shiratorizawa
Ushijima!
They were totally aiming
for the open space...
Shiratorizawa!
But I thought Kageyama
would be able to get that...
Shiratorizawa!
It must be exhaustion.
Is the exhausted setter going to
have to face the deuce of despair?
Shiratorizawa!
The only time I will ever feel despair
is when I won't be able to
play volleyball anymore.
Shiratorizawa!
All of you guys are monsters.
Haikyu!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Be Courageous Warriors
All right, here we go!
The position of the defense
is fine as it is right now.
You were able to follow up with a one touch.
Right!
Can you go on, Kageyama?
Of course.
If you're exhausted, I can
switch with you at any time.
I won't get exhausted!
Karasuno              Shiratorizawa
Fly
Daichi-san!
It's stretching...
All right!
Yes!
Now they're at set point again.
Karasuno              Shiratorizawa
They're at a deuce again.
It's fine! They'll be able to...
Ugh! Why at a time like this?
Bring it!
Miracle boy, Wakatoshi!
A net in at a time like this?
Now they've got the match point...
If they get another point, it's all over!
Karasuno               Shiratorizawa
One more point! One more point!
Be Courageous Warriors
You can do it... You can do it!
Nishinoya!
Damn demon serve...
Chance ball!
Crap!
God damn it!
Yes!
They stopped it!
They got through the match point!
That's amazing!
Hey, could you not just run into me?
You're not Hinata. Jump up. Up.
What?! This wouldn't be
considered bumping into you!
You just lack training!
You two!
Seriously, give me a break!
I can feel my lifespan shortening.
Hmph. This ain't nothing.
Says the guy who was panicking when
it was Shiratorizawa's chance ball.
It ain't nothing.
Karasuno                 Araigawa
Compared to before they
were a powerhouse school
and didn't gather any attention...
I'm counting on you, Karasuno!
Whoa, what?
Who's that?
N-No idea...
That guy's still coming to our matches?
Then I guess we can't let him down.
Get out there!
For me, the most troublesome person
isn't any kind of opponent blocker,
it's him...
All right!
We're going to win!
Go, go, Karasuno! Push it, push it, Karasuno!
Hey, Tiredyama-kun.
I can hit any kind of toss,
no matter how sucky!
Go, go, Karasuno! Push it, push it, Karasuno!
I never suck!
Right!
If Sugawara is coming in as
a pinch server right now,
that means they're going the rest of
this set with Kageyama as the setter.
Well, nothing good would come out of
suddenly changing them
out at a time like this.
Suga! Get a nice serve in!
Leon, up front!
Nice receive!
Your beautiful form...
is falling apart!
Out!
Karasuno              Shiratorizawa
All right!
I think it'd be okay to rely on
the left a little bit, but...
Kageyama-kun sure is confident.
It's a silent plea.
No matter how tired he is
or how tense things get,
he doesn't plan on backing
down on the attacks.
So he wants the middle blocker
to keep up his guard, too.
Bring it!
That was good!
Front!
Chance ball!
It's short!
Volleyball is a sport where
you can't hold the ball.
You're only allowed to touch
the ball for a few seconds...
You need to control that moment,
as though ball were
a part of your body.
His body's going right, but...
He used his left hand.
Karasuno                     Shiratorizawa
All right!
They're turning misfortune
into fortune, or something...
Do you have glue on your feet, or something?!
You idiots! You could have gotten that ball!
Wow...
They finally caught up!
Seriously?
Nice, Hinata! Good reaction.
Thanks!
This is our ultimate opportunity.
If the chance appears,
you'd better grab it!
We can do this.
Let's go!
Nice cover.
Then at least say it with a nice face!
More importantly, Kageyama...
We get to play one more set!
Yeah.
When we were first-years,
for about six months, I internally
called you "Hafing Mwe," Asahi.
Since you sort of looked
like a foreigner, too.
Actually, you called me that
quite a few times out loud, too.
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"Obsession."
Episode 07: Obsession