Give alien weapons to Earth!
Give them to Earth!
The cries to repel alien forces and
strengthen Earth defenses
have been intensifying.
That would lead to the
path of destruction.
Until now, the masses have
considered this war
someone else's problem.
We will mass produce AHSMB units
on the Rhinos' production line.
Is that why you disclosed information
regarding the Rhinos units?
"Deep Recon"
Dang! So, would defeating
a Lega-whatever in a game
be like vanquishing a midboss?
Wasn't he a "Legatus"?
It's their Military
Commander equivalent.
Is a Military Commander high ranking?
Shouldn't he be?
Then isn't it about time we shed
our title as the Fail Five?
Not if each midboss
trashes all of our units.
Repairs are only 28% done for mine...
Mine is in similar shape.
You two have it good!
They said mine's smashed
like a water flea.
What's a "water flea"?
A crustacean of the Branchiopoda class,
Diplostraca order, Cladocera suborder,
Anomopoda suborder, Daphniidae
family, Daphnia genus.
In layman's terms, it's
a type of plankton.
Oh, okay! But what does that
have to do with your AHSMB?
Beats me.
Didn't you pay attention?!
Anyway, doesn't vanquishing
a midboss unlock
an event that leads to power ups?
No, heroes are supposed to train next!
I don't wanna train.
Here! Thanks for waiting for Meal Set A.
Asagi, I gave you an extra serving.
I can't eat all of this.
Then I'll he-
You can have half of mine.
Nah, I'll pass...
What's wrong?
I'm not feeling terribly hungry.
That's not cool!
A hero must always eat well
and sleep well, remember?
Randy! And Officer Ange, too.
Yep! Mr. Cool is in the house!
I heard you had a rough fight.
I know how to perk ya back up.
Why do we have to watch
this in my room?!
Like it matters!
So whadda ya think of this one?
Where are you going?!
M-man, I've only got eyes for guns...
You won't know until you try.
He's right!
Isn't it nice how girls
are so cute and soft?
I like 'em firm!
I don't see it. You must
have rather unusual taste.
Say, doesn't this actress
kinda resemble Captain Amane?
You really have a thing for your
superior officers, don't you?
Randy is definitely the type
that loves to get stepped on!
Is that what turns you on, Randy?
Yeah! Aren't the kinda strict
"big sister" types awesome?
I quiver with delight each
time they order me around.
Masochistic freak.
Officer... Ange?! How
long have you been here?
From the start.
Crap!
What the hell?! Why'd you turn it off?
Why is he in Violent Mode?
Listen up!
Nothing pisses me off more
than when someone kills
a video when I'm watching it.
You'd better remember that!
Doesn't watching this give
you the same sense of elation
as when we're fighting?
That's because the content
is meant to arouse you.
That's not what I meant.
The realization that I'm alive
gushes up from the bottom of my heart.
It's like someone is
telling me that I must
defeat more foes and survive!
That is precisely why
I watch these videos.
When I watch them, I feel
as though I am truly alive.
By experiencing the ritual related to
the creation and birth of new life,
my resolve to fight to protect
the next generation...
Uh, what was I gonna say?
You were trying to
sound cool and failed!
No surprise coming from
a failure at life.
Who'd you call a "failure"?!
That's your nickname!
I'm a "bummer"!
I can't hear a thing!
I can't see a thing!
Don't call yourself that!
I-I know!
Guys, what do you plan on
doing once the war is over?
To be honest, there is
something I'd like to do.
Huh? Did I say something wrong?
Nah, not really.
Just wonderin', is Patrick an airhead?
That's right.
Then I shouldn't hold it against him.
Oh, yeah! I ordered a new video,
so you can have this one.
Thank you very much!
Don't wind up makin' that girl
cry with all these videos!
Who is "that girl"?
Meh, forget it.
This? I have a fiancée back on Earth.
A fiancée?
Yeah. My parents picked her
out back when I was a kid.
But when I met her, she
was just so cute and kind!
She's also very kind hearted,
domestic and understanding!
I fell in love at first sight.
Aren't you getting married
when the war is over?
Y-yeah.
You're getting married? Congratulations!
We've gotta work hard so that you can!
Do you have a hologram of her?
Sure do! Wanna see?
Well? Isn't she cute?
She really is cute!
I know, right?
That's cute?
She his mom?
The 1st and 2nd Mobile Units'
supplies are down to 30%.
Their warships are burning
through artillery.
It hurts to have lost all of
those skilled pilots, doesn't it?
Indeed. We can always build new
fighters, but not new pilots...
Even if you combined the Bela-Russian
and Great Chinese Alliance's forces
with the Organization
of American States,
Europe Union and Pacific
Rim-India Alliance,
we would not survive a
full-scale invasion the next
time Earth is attacked.
In which case, the only
thing we have in our favor
is the enemy's poor stamina.
OPEN
Couldn't you manage somethin'?
Yakitori     Beer     Simmered Giblets
Those bunnies put up a pretty
good fight in their AHSMBs.
Their units were destroyed during
the Gurantseere Defensive Battle.
Man, and they were my only hope!
No wonder Reika was bent outta shape.
I'm outta gas! I'm gonna
die if I don't drink!
Then we oughta drink on her behalf.
Yep! Keep it comin'!
None of the countries have any military
might left and they're run by morons!
I'm up a river without a paddle!
Same here.
I've got a secretive boss
who's running me ragged
with preparing to launch the new
mass production AHSMB models.
Gimme!
This?
That, too. But gimme those AHSMBs.
Sure, you can have 'em.
Yay! You can't take that back later.
That's nothing if it'll make
life easier on those kids.
A counter-attack combining
all of Earth's forces, huh?
Those kids will lead the vanguard.
We really are horrible, aren't we?
The line extends beyond Uranus'
orbit and in toward Jupiter...
So this is the Wulgaru's
navigation route.
You wish to destroy the gate?
Is that even possible?
I suppose...
If you destroyed the gate's controls,
within a certain period of
time, the gate would close.
Once it did, what would happen
to the Wulgaru's invading army?
If they were cut from
their supply route,
I imagine they would perish before long.
Would they withdraw before that happens?
Knowing my brother...
We have secured enough to sustain you.
I trust you.
I love your planet, Earth.
However, your star of hope
is starting to grow clouded.
Are you referring to Izuru Hitachi?
If you lose his protection,
your planet will probably
fall into my brother's hands.
After he claims your genes,
there will be nothing left.
The Wulgaru truly are interested
in nothing but our genes.
For the Wulgaru, obtaining
them is life's greatest joy.
Do you know where the gate is located?
Even I do not know the
current state of the gate.
In order to locate the enemy's gate,
I need you to conduct a long-range
tactical reconnaissance mission.
What's this about a "gate"?
The gate is a dimensional
hole that can be
created in locations with
gravitic fluctuations.
We believe the Wulgaru
forced the gate open,
which is how they came
to our solar system.
You've heard this before!
I forgot.
The chance of a safe
return is extremely slim.
This is a perilous mission.
You are the only ones
capable of pulling it off.
Wow, that's awesome!
Where is the gate?
It's past Saturn?!
Absurd! Humanity hasn't
even reached Saturn yet.
So it's a one-way ticket, eh?
Look at this.
That's huge! It looks
just like an erected-
What is that?
It's a booster bound to
sublight-speed guided missiles.
But it still won't be fast enough.
We've also attached laser sails.
The laser propulsion will provide your
primary acceleration until
you reach escape velocity.
Is this even possible?
Theoretically, you can accelerate
to 10% the speed of light.
In which case, we'd reach
our target in 50 hours.
It will take 120 hours to
reach maximum acceleration.
What's wrong?
Wow, that startled me!
Venturing uncharted space!
This is every man's dream!
Question, Ma'am!
Couldn't we take the Godinion?
The Godinion is too large
to handle accelerating
on that makeshift booster.
What if you forced it to?
I'm confident it would get torn apart.
Then what about our units?
According to my calculations,
the Rhinos should be fine.
According to your calculations...?
Is there a possibility that
the enemy will find us?
You'll be fine getting there.
But when returning, you'll
decelerate upon making
a gravity turn at Jupiter.
There is a possibility that
they could strike then.
That's right.
Let me reiterate: This mission must
be carried out in absolute secrecy.
Do not let the Wulgaru catch
you searching for their gate.
The future of Earth rests on
this reconnaissance mission!
We're counting on you.
Yes, sir!
Commence Operation: Eagle Landed.
Awesome! I've never seen a
booster like that before.
We're doing a test run for
a new top-secret weapon.
Whatcha think? Pretty cool, right?
It's incredible!
Damn! I wish my unit
wasn't all busted up.
There is no need for you to help.
We can handle this one ourselves!
But-
Give us a chance to show
off every now and then.
Dude, I'll prove to ya that we're
the real heroes around here.
No, I'm not handing over
my role as the hero.
Then let's duke it out to see who
the real hero is when I get back.
I'm holding you to that.
Have I ever broken a promise?
You break them all of the time!
Yeah. It's far rarer
for you to keep them.
Dudes, as my teammates,
you oughta back me up!
Tamaki!
I'd like to tell you
something when I get back.
You would?
Want me to introduce you to Guiliano?
No, that's not it...
It's not? Then were you after Siegfried?
You've got it wrong!
Then was it Master Daneel all along?!
Whatever shall I do?
You haven't eaten since before
that last mission, have you?
I could bake you a cake.
Cut the guy some slack.
What was that?
Everyone!
It's time for your checkups.
Checkups?
Right. You just finished
another big mission,
so we're going to give you checkups.
So? How'd it go, Patrick?
How'd what go?
Don't be so shy!
Didn't you tell Tamaki how
you feel before we left?
N-n-n-not yet!
That's no fun.
But I just found out what
Tamaki's favorite food is.
I'll win her over with that.
Oh, good thinking!
Are you seriously going to be okay?
I had some sent up all
of the way from Earth.
I'll give it to her when I get back.
Best of luck to ya!
Thanks!
Tamaki Irie, please accept this.
I gained more weight!
I knew it!
They seem to be havin' fun over there...
It's grimy over here.
It's stuffy and crowded!
Visual on Neptune.
We've reached the final veering point.
Wow! So that's Neptune!
We're the first humans in
history to make it this far.
I'm going to set our swing-by maneuver.
I'm countin' on ya!
Which will it be: Heavy
G and get there quick
or a slow and easy ride?
I'd prefer the easy-
Obviously we're gonna
take the quicker method!
Yeah, I figured as much.
Man!
Great! Report in via our secure line.
Roger!
Static...?
What's wrong?
I can't get through.
Just a sec. I'll look into it.
Problem found!
A solar storm is emitting
extremely strong electromagnetic
interference.
What range are we lookin' at?
Everywhere between us... and Jupiter.
Well, jeez! It looks like we're stuck
goin' home so we can hand the info over!
And here I thought this was an easy job
where we just transmitted
the data we found.
Well, there's no such
thing as an easy job!
Changing course.
Disconnecting from the sails in
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Disconnect.
We successfully disconnected.
Sweet! Ignite the booster!
Even with a G canceler, this is brutal!
They oughta pay us overtime for this!
It would help cover all
of my upcoming dates!
Just how much are you
gonna spend on her?
We're gonna zoom by!
Set all of your sensors to
auto. We can't miss the gate!
I see it!
Another exam?
Right. I'm concerned about some
of the results that came up.
How is everyone else?
They will reach the rendezvous
point in 10 hours.
Due to a solar storm, we
are unable to reach them.
Can you find them via optical tracking?
It hasn't picked them up yet.
Do you think they're all right?
All we can do is go in
the hopes that they are.
Rate of deceleration
increasing from 60 to 70.
We will reach our target
speed in 30 seconds.
Be sure to keep your eyes peeled!
I'm pulling my radar up.
We're under attack!
Patrick, can you get through?
The solar storm is still interfering!
I see... Leave this to
me and get outta here!
But-
Hurry! Every second counts!
Roger!
There is an emergency transmission!
Requesting reinforcements! Randy
is currently engaging the-
Right now, we are at Jupi-
Did you get the data?
We can't receive it due to the strong
interference from the solar storm!
No matter what the cost,
you must recover that data!
Commander!
I repeat, retrieving that
data takes top priority.
Roger.
Siegfried, open the solar sails!
Guiliano, ask Star Rose for an
emergency laser propulsion shot.
Roger!
Do you think Randy will be all right?
We have to carry on his will.
We must- we must- get
this information back.
It's the same fighter from earlier!
I'll hold him back!
Go, Patrick!
But-!
The fate of Earth rests
on this information! Go!
Okay!
At the very least, I
want you to survive.
First I'll take your right arm!
Then your left arm!
And your legs.
That was far too easy...
It was hardly beautiful.
I've gotta hurry and inform everyone!
Tamaki!
Patrick!
My radar is... not malfunctioning.
And my sensors are operational, too.
For him to have disappeared
before anyone retrieved him...
Damn it!
I have to get back somehow...
If I don't relay this information,
we really will have died like dogs!
I'm so close! Move, dammit!
Is this the end?
Tally-ho!
Randy?! You're still alive?
Don't go killin' me off just yet!
I've gotta let them bunnies
know who the real hero is.
They got Patrick! Please
hurry to the Godinion!
That's your job.
Let me handle things
here. You get goin'!
But my unit-
Don't give me that
bullshit! I said to go!
Outta ammo, huh?
It turned on!
Go!
Sorry!
Randy!
The lives of everyone on Earth are
hangin' on that information...
It's cool; just go...
Randy!
Oh, yeah. Please pick up that
new video I ordered, Chandra...
Randy!
What the hell?
You're a bummer clear up to the end...
What's the situation?
Black 6 has taken off.
I've identified a large explosion
in our target direction.
What does that mean?
There is an enemy battleship!
Offer support fire!
It's too far away!
Please link my unit to
the fire control system!
I will calculate the trajectory.
Authorization granted!
Sensors, linked! Coordinate
axis, transferred!
Roger!
Correcting precision error of 0.3.
Firing all scatter lasers!
There are signs of impact.
I have an 87.5% estimate
of the targets' location,
speed and projected routes.
I'm sending the specifics.
I've got the info!
We have a 250% rate of convergence!
Target: The Wulgaru flagship!
My main cannon is ready to fire!
Fire!
I'm firing everything I've got!
Such tactics lack any form of beauty.
It fails to excite my DNA in the least.
Gate's coordinates... verified...
"Genes of Destiny"