Wow, it's beautiful!
So this is Gallia's capital, Lutis.
This is where Tabitha is from.
Are you really sure we can
ask you to repair the ship?
I think I've used up my
luck as a researcher.
I mean, I get to see another
barbarian country.
If I knew this was going to happen,
I would have insisted on
following Lord Bidalsha.
Don't sigh like that.
Think of it as our
honeymoon and enjoy it.
Where the heck did that Saito go?
Hey!
Oh, Sait—
Wait up, you two!
Tiffa said you'd have
trouble without this.
Right, Tiffa?
Oh, thank you.
What are you so mad about?
What's with all the "Tiffa, Tiffa" stuff?
I was your master first!
I see, so you're Tiffa's rival.
Rival?
I'm surprised you were
able to win with those.
S-Saito prefers them small!
Is that so?
Weren't you happily touching her breasts?
What did you say?
What does that mean?!
Th-That's...
What?!
Lady Charlotte!
I am so relieved you are safe.
Start preparing the coronation
ceremony right away.
So she decided...
Tabitha's Coronation
We need more stuffing here.
That's why I told you to lay eggs.
Charlotte.
Mother...
So you made the decision.
Thank you.
I still can't believe it.
Tabitha is going to be a queen soon.
I bet Miss Tabitha will be quite pretty
at the coronation ceremony.
But we can't let our guard down.
"This is the last chance to lay eggs!"
That's what that rhyme dragon will say,
and try to get in our way.
Tabitha is too busy preparing for that.
You never know.
There might be a hidden room here.
Like here, or here!
Oh no!
Miss Vallière!
What?
She might be more of a
danger than Miss Tabitha.
I mean, Miss Westwood is
also Saito's master now.
The second! I was his master first.
The order doesn't matter.
What matters is what Saito thinks.
O-Of course he's going to choose me...
What?! What is that stupid dog doing?!
Uh, a little higher.
Higher?
Even higher.
But that's...
Now it's lower...
Lower? Okay, now I'll...
Louise?!
Do tell, what are you doing?!
Ow, ow, ow!
What the hell?
I was just trying to get the bug out.
A bug? Please, try to think
of a more plausible lie.
Yes, really. Like a bug would
oh so conveniently get into her clothes.
See, I told you.
I'm glad that's solved, Tiffa.
I-I'm sorry...
It's fine.
This is what I'm here for.
You should depend on me more.
I'm your familiar after all.
Okay.
Then please excuse me.
Oh, you're going to the
guest house, right?
I'll go with you.
Those guys were on my mind, too.
I was thinking that they
might feel a bit lost...
You're so kind, Tiffa.
Wouldn't it be best to make sure
it's clear who the real master is?
Of course.
Explore the palace?
Yes. Don't you want to see
the other buildings now that we're here?
I'll pass.
Seeing more jail-like buildings
would just be depressing.
I knew you'd say that.
Then I'll go by myself.
Oh, you guys are...
I'm captain of the Order
of the Undine Knights,
Guiche de Gramont.
I-I'm Malicorne de Grandple.
This is perfect.
Could I ask you to show
me around the palace?
I'm sorry, but we can't
let you leave this place.
But the girl with the blue hair
said I was free to do what I want.
I don't know what Tabitha said...
But we can't have you cause
any commotion right now.
Commotion?
If anybody found out that
they're hiding elves here,
you can forget about the coronation.
That's what they mean.
I'm glad you understand.
Please stay here quietly then.
With you as our guards, huh?
Come on, just a tiny bit.
I'll be right back.
No, no.
Please go back. I said no!
I'm so sorry!
How dare you touch Lukshana!
I-I thought I was going to die...
What are you doing?
You elves are truly uncivilized.
Uncivilized?
That's the ultimate insult,
coming from a barbarian!
Hey, guys!
Do you need anythi—
Whoa, what are you doing?!
This barbarian manhandled Lukshana.
I-I did not!
You're the one who started it!
C'mon, who cares? Just put that
away and let's get along, okay?
You say get along, but you know...
No way, not with someone who
looks down on others like that.
He's just putting up a tough front
because he's in a totally foreign place.
You can relate, right?
I think they'd understand
if they'd just talk...
Whoa, wh-what's this?
I'm choosing what to wear to the dance.
Tabitha provided me with these.
Now that you mention it,
I guess there is a dance after
the coronation ceremony.
Hey, what about this one?
I think that's more for girls
with a bigger chest, like Tiffa.
No, I mean... Uh, um...
I think this is better for you, Louise.
Then I'll try it on, so help me!
W-Wait...
Louise...
Help me with this.
M-Me?
Are you saying you won't
listen to your master?
Aren't you my familiar?!
A-All right...
Ah, that tickles.
I'm sorry.
Don't forget to tie the ribbon.
G-Got it.
Y-You can touch them if you want.
What? Really?!
If it's just a little bit.
I... I... Louise!
Jeez, I said just a little bit.
That's impossible, Louise.
Saito, can I ask you something?
I'm the only master for you, right?
Of c—
Please help me, Saito!
Tiffa?
What's wrong, Tiffa?
I'm having trouble putting this on.
Is it all right to depend on you
for things like this, too?
U-Uh...
I'll do it! These things
should be done by girls!
Huh? It seems to be a bit tight...
Got it!
D-Don't look!
By tomorrow, Tabitha will be a queen.
It's amazing, she'll be of the
same standing as Lady Henrietta.
Speaking of, I heard she just arrived.
Help! Lukshana is gone!
Gone?
She said she was going to take a bath,
but since she was taking
so long, I went in to check
and she was gone.
Then...
She ran away?!
What are you doing? Go find her already!
This has been irking me since before,
but what's with your tone?
Is that how you ask people for favors?
Can it!
Isn't this what
you were guarding us for?!
We're not standing guard for you,
we're doing it for Tabitha!
What did you say?!
You two, don't start this...
Hey, did you hear?
His Holiness has arrived.
His Holiness? You mean from Romalia?
This is bad. If this gets out...
Let's find Lukshana before it's too late!
What? Lukshana is missing?
She didn't come here, then?
No...
Maybe she got captured by
barbarians and is being abused...
She's got her wits together,
so there's no need to worry.
I want to help look for her,
but the queen summoned me.
Saito, let's go!
I'm coming.
I'm sorry, I'll see you later.
Let's try another place.
I'll find her, no matter what!
It's primitive, but very pretty.
I'd like to congratulate you on
your coronation, Queen Charlotte.
Thank you very much.
Saito and Miss Westwood,
I'm relieved you are safe.
Normally, we should have
come to rescue you, but...
Oh, it was fine.
But I'm surprised you were able to
rescue those two from
those unknown lands.
About that...
When I came to, I was casting a spell...
You can use a World Door...
World Door?
It's a Void spell that can
connect two distant places.
Louise, so you learned a new spell.
I actually almost ran out of energy,
but when I grabbed Saito's hands,
the window got bigger.
Got bigger?
Does that mean the power
of the spell got stronger?
I believe so.
But Gandalfr shouldn't
have that kind of power...
What is it?
I think this has something to do with it.
That's...
Apparently I've become
Tiffa's familiar as well.
Is that even possible?
One body can house multiple
familiar powers, my lord?
I've never heard of it.
But the fact that Lífþrasir is here...
Líf... What?
Lífþrasir is someone who has the
ability to amplify the Void powers.
That's what caused the surge
of power in Miss Vallière.
So that's why...
Joseph's familiar was the
Mind of God, Mioznitnirn.
Then, there's the Left
Hand of God, Gandalfr.
The Right Hand of God, Windalfr.
And the Heart of God, Lífþrasir.
Four familiars to fight alongside
the four Void Mages.
It is said that the four
and four exist to join
their powers in order to
save Halkeginia from danger.
As we have not found Joseph's successor,
the four and four are
currently incomplete.
Even if Halkeginia were to face a crisis,
as long as we have Lífþrasir,
we can amplify our powers many times.
Lífþrasir is wonderful news for us.
I have that kind of power?
So I guess it's basically a booster.
So using this power,
your Explosion would get
much stronger, right?
I suppose...
This is all thanks to Tiffa...
Maybe this means that me binding
the contract with Saito had its use...
Then, perhaps there was a
point to my feelings, too...
Ah, there you are.
We were looking for you.
We were thinking of
going to Tabitha's room.
Tonight's the last night,
we wanted to spend it with her.
That sounds good. I'm in.
Tiffa, you'll come too, right?
Y-Yes.
I'll come, too.
Nope. No boys allowed.
All right, let's go.
Don't get too carried away!
We know!
I bet Tabitha will be surprised
when all of us suddenly show up.
Th-That's...
She's got blond hair like you,
and breasts like you...
Guiche, I can't believe you!
Ow, ow, ow, M-Montmorency!
I let you out of my sight for
one second and this happens!
It's not what you think, Montmorency!
I'm actually looking
for someone. Right now—
I don't want to hear your excuses!
You really never learn!
Wait, Montmorency!
You deserve that.
Why won't you listen to me?
We're the same...
I realized that elves and
barbarians are the same
when it comes to women.
You have it quite rough, too.
What the hell is he thinking?
When he has someone like me?! Jeez!
You guys are just like us.
Lukshana?!
You weren't in the guest house?
I simply had to see the palace.
I didn't think it'd
lead to such a ruckus.
So, what Guiche said back there... Wait,
was he looking for you?!
Looks like it.
Oh no, I thought...
It's his fault for not being clear.
That's often why Ari and I fight as well.
It looks like we'll get along quite well.
What's all this noise?
Did something happen?
I'm not going to look
for Lukshana any more!
She always does what she wants,
but if I dare to voice my opinion,
she immediately threatens
to not marry me!
Of course she knows that
I can't say anything then!
Exactly!
If I even talk to another girl,
she screams that I'm cheating on her!
Women are so annoying!
It looks like those two are
best buddies all of a sudden.
Well, I'm just glad they get along now.
But I wonder where Lukshana is.
Saito! Malicorne!
Huh? Lukshana?
Please tell Ari that Lukshana
will stay over here tonight.
Thanks!
Lukshana and Montmorency, too?
When did that happen?
I told you. They'll understand
if they just talk.
I, Charlotte Helene Orléans,
hereby proclaim that I
will be Queen of Gallia.
My Queen!
A new queen has been born!
Tabitha is queen, huh?
So, about that thing we
discussed the other day...
What was it?
About me being your only master.
That doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter?!
I mean that "master" and
all that doesn't matter.
The only one I love is you, Louise.
Saito...
Hurry up or you'll be late.
But... Wait, Saito!
I haven't finished putting on my dress!
Man, where did he go?
Your Highness, why didn't
you tell Saito about it?
About Lífþrasir?
Yes. Indeed, it amplifies
the power of the Void,
but the energy of his soul can never be
replenished once it's used.
If he keeps using it, Saito will...
Using the power of Lífþrasir is
essentially shaving off
a part of his life.
When he runs out of energy, he will die.
But telling him this would only
strike unnecessary fear into his heart.
When the time comes that
that power is truly needed,
he won't be able to face the
danger threatening the world.
Die?
What do they mean?
The power of Lífþrasir
that Saito has gained...
I never expected that the time
it's truly needed would come so soon.
Next time: The Awakening of Calamity.
Saito, please, you can't die!
The Awakening of Calamity