My name is Glass.
Feel free to consider me your enemy, hero.
She destroyed that Soul Eater in one hit.
How overpowered can you be?
I can't stop trembling.
I'm Naofumi.
Naofumi, is it?
Now, shall we begin
the true battle of the Wave?
The Rising of the Shield Hero
Aren't you going to attack, Hero Naofumi?
The Raven Invader
Why not send those servants of yours at me?
Servants?
Did you just call us...
...Naofumi's servants?
Screw you!
Meteor Slash!
Meteor Thrust!
Meteor Shot!
Is that all you've got?
Zero-Stance Rondo: Reverse Four Seasons.
So you are but mere servants.
Sh-She's strong!
Soul Soothing Potion—Effect: SP Recovery
I hope you'll entertain me a little.
Sorry, but I'm no entertainer.
Shield Prison!
Raphtalia!
Do you really think this feeble
venom could put defeat me?
Filo!
High Quick!
Eight kicks in a single instant?
How very admirable.
But they cannot touch me.
Not even worthy of mention.
Both of you, get behind me!
Shield Prison!
Reverse Four Seasons.
I'm impressed that you're still
standing after that attack.
Now, when exactly do you plan on using
that flaming shield from before?
Naofumi-sama...
Come forth, Rage Shield!
I told you.
You cannot touch me.
Filo!
Raphtalia, take care of Filo.
Your flame is too cold to burn me.
Rupture-Stance Rondo:
Tortoise Shell Cracker.
Naofumi-sama!
Even that isn't enough to bring you down?
If nothing else, I see your defense
lives up to your title of hero.
Aw, you flatter me.
However, your dark flame only activates
with close-quarter attacks.
Not when you attack from range.
You have an ace up your sleeve, do you not?
Don't hold it back. Show it to me.
Very well, if you insist.
Shield Prison!
Change Shield!
Iron Maiden!
It's even less potent than
I thought it would be.
Wha...
Such a disappointment.
Is there... Is there nothing we can do?
The time limit?
I didn't expect to hit it so soon.
When I give the sign, use light magic.
The battle of the Wave
will end in our victory.
I have nothing against you,
but it is what it is.
Now!
Fast Light!
Fast Heal!
Run for it!
Of all the futile...
Naofumi-sama! She's attacking!
Air Strike Shield!
So I can't defeat him at this range.
I shall leave this time,
but you won't survive our next
encounter unless you get stronger.
Remember that we shall be the ones
to emerge triumphant from the Waves.
Is it over?
Did we manage to get away somehow?
That countdown showed up out of nowhere.
It must've been signaling
the end of the Wave.
But what are the Waves, anyway?
Weren't they supposed to be
world-ending calamities?
That Glass woman was fixated
on defeating me, a hero.
...the true battle of the Wave?
All these questions, and no answers.
But one thing's for sure: we must grow
much stronger by the next Wave.
If we don't, we'll die for sure.
Feeding my shield monster fragments
will let me obtain new skills,
Soul Eater Shield
but any concrete improvement will require
Raphtalia and Filo to get class upgrades.
U-Um, Sir Hero...
You are to report to the castle at once.
What?
Shield Prison!
Change Shield!
Iron Maiden!
I saw what happened through
the crystal ball.
You did well to quell the Wave,
as much as I hate to admit it.
Is that really how you thank someone?
Please, Sir Hero!
I know how you feel,
but please go with the Captain!
I have a question for you.
How did you obtain such strength?
You possess power unbecoming
of the Shield Hero.
It is your duty to reveal
the secret behind it.
Now, spit it out.
And don't you dare lie to me.
If you want to know so badly,
kneel before me.
In my world, one grovels before the
person they're asking for something.
And they say, "I beg you.
Please enlighten my ignorant self."
You cur!
As I am now, I could kill you here and
walk out the front door if I wanted.
You're bluffing.
Do any of you here want to fight me,
the man who killed the Wave's boss monster?
I'm willing to cooperate with you until
the Waves die down and I can go home.
So don't ever bother me again.
I'm the king! You cannot
disrespect me this way, Shield!
I know.
I'll have your wretched slaves
pay for your crimes, and...
Use all the dirty,
underhanded tricks you want.
I will protect my party through it all.
You'll never take anything from me again.
I dare you to lay a finger on them.
I'll chase you to the ends of the earth
and make you regret ever being born.
Accursed Shield!
You did splendidly well
this time, I daresay.
Your efforts have become impossible
for anyone to ignore...
Including powers who don't take too
kindly to you, Sir Shield Hero.
Virtuous on the surface,
conniving and conspiring behind the scenes...
You should exercise the utmost
caution going forward,
I daresay.
"Daresay"?
Oh, Melty!
What can I do for you?
I heard that you spoke with
the Shield Hero just now.
And also that your talk ended
in a very hostile manner.
Father, if you remain at
odds with the Shield Hero,
we may lose our means to fight the Waves,
which could threaten our country's safety.
Please try to reconcile.
Reconcile with that swine?!
O-Oh, I'm not angry at you.
Why do you hate the Shield Hero so?
Well...
If I let him and the demi-humans do as
they please, I'll yet again lose my family.
Father?
Your defiance is an affront.
With the queen away,
the king's word is final.
And even we princesses cannot overturn it.
Sister...
Our father is the king.
Whether you understand
his decisions or not,
they're all for the
betterment of our country.
I know you're still at an age
where you want him to baby you,
but you should learn to
hold back a little, Melty.
Just a word of advice as your older sister.
I appreciate your concern,
but this is none of your business.
Just like Mother and Father, I want
the best for our country, too.
And it is my job as
crown princess to see to it.
Melty, you little...
I'll take my leave now, Father.
Melty...
Papa...
I can't believe you actually went
shopping for a fight with the king.
Wrong. He picked a fight with me.
Man, I've got everything ya need.
Do all your shopping here.
Anyway, what are you going
to do about class upgrades?
From what you just said, I doubt they'll
let you use the dragon hourglass here.
I was thinking of going to either
Siltvelt or Shieldfreeden.
I always figured you'd go
to those places someday.
I recommend Shieldfreeden.
The slave merchant recommended it, too.
Said it's very welcoming to humans
for a country of demi-humans.
Yeah.
Over in Siltvelt, they can get pretty
extreme about demi-human supremacy.
But as the Shield Hero...
Master, are we going on another trip?
Yay!
It usually takes a month by wagon,
Trip, trip!
but our fowl lassie here should
get you there sooner.
I can't wait!
I'll get everything ya need
and load it on to your wagon.
Also, I'd like a new sword for Raphtalia.
Oh, I have a spare.
But...
This will be another long journey.
We should save money where we can.
We were able to leave so quickly.
Elhart-san always works fast, doesn't he?
Yeah.
Kid,
I got you some gifts for the road.
Use 'em if ya like.
For the kid, a shield accessory.
It can analyze a shield and
do tons of other useful stuff.
For the missy, a sword.
It's the same make as the one she broke.
Nothing beats a trusty old friend, right?
There's another for the missy.
A mana sword.
Use it on enemies with no physical form.
If, God forbid,
the fowl lassie can't draw the wagon anymore,
this item will help.
Put this on, and gain the
strength of a hundred men!
Even you could draw the wagon, kid!
Hod...
I love traveling.
It makes me free, shackled by no one.
I don't have to deal with royalty
or the other heroes, either.
Found you!
Oh, Mel-chan!
Hey! Long time no see!
Filo!
Naofumi-sama, it may not have been for long,
Hurry up, Mel-chan!
but we traveled together as a party.
Over here, over here!
Master...
Mel-chan's a good girl, y'know?
Sir Shield Hero,
I'd like you to return to the capital
and meet with King Aultcray once more.
I refuse.
I want you to apologize
for your conduct and reconcile.
I refuse!
We need your help to stop the Waves.
Also, you would be lost without
the king's financial support.
Support?
I'm the one graciously working with
you lot until the Waves are gone.
Naofumi-sama...
She's royalty, too.
Why...
Why do both you and my father
have to be like this?!
A hero and the king can't be fighting
among themselves! Absolutely not!
Mel-chan?
Don't you agree, Filo-chan?
Er...
You agree too, don't you, Raphtalia-san?!
W-Well, I am Naofumi-sama's sword.
See? They're agreeing with me!
Uh, they're not.
Look, just apologize to Father!
Otherwise, Mother will yell at him!
The way she throws a tantrum
is just like her dad.
Wait... Her mother will yell at him?
Listen to me when I'm talking to you!
This feeling...
It's the same as back then.
It reeks of a setup!
So return to the capital—
The Devil of the Shield