The one-on-one fights that took
place in the sky and on land:
Nanami-sama and the chief,
and the serious battle between
the Princess and Rebecca-sama!
There were countless exciting things,
like plenty of fanshots,
the appearance of Hero Mask, and so on.
So what was the result after that kind
of opening day of Union Fest?
Change My Heart
The opening battle of
the Union Fest is over!
We will now announce the
battle results on the stage!
This is quite unexpected,
but the Principality of
Pastillage is in first place!
They were slightly behind
in the beginning,
but started to catch up at an
incredible pace in the second half.
In the end, they pulled
through and caused an upset!
Couverte-sama, what would you say
lead to your victory this time?
Well, of course all of our
people did their very best,
but it might have been
that person over there.
People of Pastillage,
I am here to aid you,
the undefeatable Hero Mask!
Did Adel-sama stop caring
about hiding her face?
Looks like she's really let herself go.
Hero Mask!
Next time you'll have to face me, too!
Me, too!
Very well, Leonmichelli and Nanami,
I will meet you in battle!
She's really popular!
Pastillage's savior, Hero Mask!
The spectators already love her!
Let's all do our best again tomorrow!
The second day will be a sea battle!
All the contestants for
the various beach events
have already gathered here
on this beach battlefield!
The intra-country friendship
marine race will be held here, too!
Also, on the field specially
set up for it,
the Princess' project
"Mounted Battle by the
Sea - Water battle"
is about to begin!
Let the water battle by the sea begin!
The sky we both
gazed up at on that day
Galette army! Advance!
I'll never forget it.
I love these events!
All right, let's just keep our
lead all the way to the end!
Wishing that we could all
Indeed!
I'll do my best!
run together someday.
We'll go in as well!
It's not "Goodbye",
it's "we will meet again."
Because I know my wish will come true!
Let's embrace our passionate memories
of those days that we rushed through.
That promise we made
hand in hand.
We will meet again and it'll come true.
As you can see, the second
day of Union Fest
was another huge success.
I'll wait forever.
Obviously, there were many
more events after that and Rico-chan
and Noir-chan even scored
big at a quiz competition.
Yes, Chief Ricotta!
General Godwin!
Correct!
Knights and common
folk mingled on stage
and everybody had fun together.
Next, next.
The level of excitement
stayed high during the
rest of the events...
As of today, all the
war games between our
three countries have been concluded.
The sporting
and art events
are still going on and there's
also the final stage
that'll take place on the last day.
But, for now, we've
concluded this section.
There were no major accidents
or other trouble
during the large scale
events, which is all
thanks to your hard work.
Let's hear a toast
from the representative
of the three countries'
knight orders, Lord Risler.
What? Me?
Please.
Lord Risler!
Um, then I'd like to
toast to the continued peace,
prosperity, and even better
cooperation between the three countries.
Cheers!
Sink.
Good work.
Becky, Cou-sama. Good work.
Sink, you're going on a walk with
the Princess again
tomorrow morning, right?
Yeah, she said there's a
place she wanted to go to.
Yes, so about that...
Oh, Cou-sama, Rebecca-san.
Princess.
Millihi-nee, perfect timing!
Yes?
You're have your on-air performance
in our country tomorrow, right?
Rebecca and I wanted to bring you.
Wow, thank you.
Where will you be going
for your walk tomorrow?
Since we have some time,
I wanted to go to a place
with many memories that
we haven't been to lately.
I haven't been to this
stream in a while.
Sink, you had your training
camp here last time, right?
Yes, with Yukki, Ecle, and Noir.
Princess! Sink!
Yukikaze!
I apologize for wanting
to come over so suddenly.
Please don't apologize,
you're always more than welcome!
Are Lady d'Arquien and
Isuka-san in today?
They left early in the morning
to get some metal for his swordsmithing.
I see.
The only ones at our house
are Kanata and myself,
so please stay as long as you wish.
Here you go, Princess.
Thank you!
Yukikaze's tail pillow!
It's just as fluffy and
soft as I remember!
Sink, want to try it, too?
It's really fluffy!
Uh, I guess I'll try later.
Here you go.
Thank you!
You two really get along well.
She played with me a lot
when I was smaller.
No no, you were the one
who took care of me.
When you were young,
I was a tiny thing, too.
Oh, really?
Right, Kanata-san?
Yes, you're right.
I suspect that it's thanks
to the Princess and
Ecle and the others that Yuki-chan
grew into what she is now.
Normally local gods grow
bigger when their god rank
goes up after they've done
enough virtuous deeds.
From the time the lady picked me up
until very recently,
I was always a tiny thing...
There was even a time
when you were smaller
than Ecle or myself.
Yes, but I guess seeing
you get bigger each day
made me want to be bigger, too.
So I trained really hard
and when I realized what had happened,
I was this big.
It was hard to keep her clothed
because she grew so quickly!
But I really think I won't
get any taller than this.
Thank you for the meal!
Uh, Princess?
Did something happen?
No, I just saw something
on the ground...
See, this.
A jewel? Or egg?
I've never seen that before.
Does it belong to
Isuka-san or Adel-sama?
Princess! Yuki-chan! Hero!
An... animal?
A local god?
Are you all okay?!
What happened?
Uh, Hero?
Yes?
Huh? No, I didn't mean you, Yuki-chan.
No, I'm over here.
Why am I over there?!
This is...
Y-Yukki...
I am over there, this is
the Princess' body...
I am Sink...
And the Princess is me, Yukikaze...
We got switched around...
Could it be?
Princess?
Th-then who's inside the
Hero who just left?
Probably what was in this
little thing before...
We'll have to catch it quickly!
Let's call for help! Brave Connect On!
It won't work...
I see, it makes sense that our moves
won't work with a different body.
Sink, we'll have to
chase the escaped Sink!
All right, Princes- I mean Yukki!
But you can't run around like that.
I'll get my clothes- whoa?!
My legs won't move like
I want them to...
Princ- Yukki!
...move...
All done.
I will hurry and find myself!
Yukki, you keep the
Princess' body safe!
Roger.
I'll make sure to treat
Yukki's body carefully!
But still, we can't just
leave it all to Sink alone.
Don't worry Prince- Yuki-chan.
The Secret Squad's
already on the hunt.
I jumped too far!
I have to remember how
Yukki runs and moves.
That's the sign to meet up!
Princess, Yukki!
Sink!
We found out where your body is.
Really?
It's through the eastern path,
by the the old pine tree.
The Secret Squad's got it surrounded,
but then it climbed up the tree...
Nice work Secret Squad!
Then we can catch it right away!
Can you do it?
Yes! Let's catch it with teamwork!
Yup!
Hero Style Ninja Art
- Lightning Blossom!
Holy Ray!
There!
Hero Kick!
Prince- Yuki-chan!
Why you...
Braze Drive - Hurricane!
Justice is served!
Princess, Yukki, Kanata-san.
Are you all right?
Y-Yes.
Sink, well done!
Don't tell me it's happening again...
Let's confirm.
I'm still Sink in Yukki.
I'm Millihiore. I'm back.
Inside Sink is me indeed.
That means...
The monster and the Princess are back in
their own bodies while Yukki
and myself are switched?
That's all thanks to
your quick judgment.
Nicely done.
It would have been
nice if you two could
have returned to normal as well.
I remembered that Sink was holding
that jewel when we first got switched.
So I thought that this little guy maybe
switches bodies with
the one closest to it.
And when that happens,
those who are close to
it also get switched.
Yes, probably.
But I'm glad that at least the
Princess was able to get her body back.
Let's quickly find a way to get Sink and
Yukikaze back to normal.
Yeah.
Yukki, can you try using
the Brave Connect?
I'll try.
Brave Connect On!
I-I'm sorry!
I forgot that thing there.
That little one isn't a
monster, but a sprite.
I took it there to set it
free far from civilization, but...
But last night you got too
excited and forgot, right?
How do we get back to normal?
You should return to normal
without having to do anything,
but we're on our way there now.
We'll go there at supersonic speeds!
Hey, Sink!
We're coming to pick you up!
We'll arrive at the
Fuugetsu Lodge soon!
We have to explain this, right?
Yes.
Your bodies got switched?
Yes, right now I am Sink.
And I am Yukikaze!
A body switching sprite.
That's like a dream come true!
With this thing the fun possibilities
are nearly endless!
Cou-sama! This is dangerous!
But... but...
We have to return it to Adel-sama. So no!
Sink, Yukikaze, I'm sorry.
This all happened because
I found that jewel.
No, no, no, no.
This is nothing for you to worry about.
We were able to resolve it
through our teamwork anyway.
This will be just another
fun memory from the summer.
Right!
Right, then we'll be
taking Millihi-nee with us!
See you two later!
Call us on the Brave Connect
if anything happens.
Okay!
Have a safe trip!
Let's relax a bit until
Adel-sama arrives.
Sure.
But since we got dirty during the fight,
how about a bath?
That sounds good.
Wait, right now's no good!
Huh? I don't see any problem.
Are we back to normal?
I'm back! Yay!
Hooray!
My own body
fits me the best.
Indeed.
It just feels right.
I really have to thank you
for treating my body with such care
when we were switched.
I'm glad I didn't fall
down or something.
You looked cool in action, too.
That's because it's easy
to move in your body.
If I try hard enough,
I think I can reproduce
the "Body Switching" move.
How about we try switching
bodies and not telling anybody?
Hero Sink is here!
Sounds like fun!
It's good Sink and Yuki-chan
were able to return to normal.
I'm so glad!
Since the Heroes have arrived,
we haven't had a shortage of fun events.
And lots of trouble.
Since it's all fun, it's all good.
For me there've been a lot of firsts...
It's been a wonderful summer
with plenty of great memories.
The Union Fest kind
of went by in a blur.
The time for you Heroes to
return is drawing closer, too.
I don't want to go home...
When you have days off over there,
you're always welcome to come here.
Okay!
Next time, we'll have to summon
you at a more relaxing time,
so you won't have as
much work as this time.
That's fine! I love the Hero work!
Oh, but I'd like to go out with
the three rulers and the three Heroes
before we go home.
True, at Pastillage that
didn't really work out
because of the trouble
with the demon king.
Let's have a nice summer
memory of just being lazy!
It looks like I got too excited.
I've sealed away that mask.
Final Stage
Then let me show you my
Ninja Art - Body Switching!
We're not doing that!