What's going on?
Rinon!
Senpai.
Kirishima-kun.
I'll take care of this.
But!
Listen to your senpai.
I might not look it,
but I'm pretty confident
in my ability to run away.
Remon!
Senpai!
Now then.
The first alien I met...
She's very nice.
She's my best friend.
And if you're going to
try to get in her way...
I'll just have to do
something you won't like.
Remon!
Senpai.
Right!
No, I can't run anymore.
Kanna-chan?
Huh?
Manami-san?!
Why are you here?!
My husband randomly told
me to come out here...
Huh?
Please drive.
A stalker is chasing me!
A stalker?
I'll make quick work of him...
Your stalker's way too big!
Is it still following us?
Yeah!
All right!
I wonder if everyone's okay.
I'm sure they're just about there by now.
Yeah! I'm sure!
Senpai, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Once we get over this mountain,
we'll be at the train station.
Then we can...
No way!
Not again!
Senpai!
Ouch...
Rinna!
No, it's not.
So then... Onee-chan?
There's an anti-field, so this
is about all I can do.
Go, Ichika.
Make sure you have
nothing left to regret.
Thank you.
It's still...
Rinon?
Rinon?!
Let's go, Kaito-kun!
Right!
Rinon!
This will take us to where we're going.
This is my fault...
Because I was so selfish...
Tanigawa-san,
Ishigaki-kun,
Kitahara-san...
Remon...
Rinon, too.
I'm sorry, everyone.
You can't apologize.
Everyone wants to make
your dream a reality.
But...
It's for all of us, too.
We're going to go to that place,
find evidence of aliens,
and then you won't have
to go back to space.
We'll all be able to stay together.
It'll be fine. It'll go fine.
If everything goes according to plan,
maybe I'll be able to go
see your planet someday.
You want to?
Of course.
I want to know where you lived,
and what your family's like.
I want to meet them.
I'd like to introduce you to them.
And who will you tell them I am?
Silly.
I wish I could have introduced
you to my parents, too.
But it's fine. I have my sister.
But sometimes I wish...
...that I could have made some more
memories with everyone, you know?
But that's why I'm leaving lots
of things behind with this.
Even the smallest things,
so at least I won't have any regrets.
You have a lot of
memories in this thing.
I do.
Tetsuro, Tanigawa, Kitahara,
Remon-senpai, even my sister.
Everyone's in here.
Me, too?
Of course. You're the heroine.
Ever since I came to this planet,
I've been thinking...
I'm so glad I got to meet all of you,
hang out together, and make the movie.
All of it's just been so fun.
I want everything to stay this way.
I wish this summer wouldn't end.
That's what I've been thinking.
I fell in love, too.
Before I realized it, you
became my everything.
I feel the same about you.
It wasn't all fun.
There were hard times, too.
I was mad at times, and I cried at times.
There'll be a lot more to come.
We might end up fighting, too.
What will you do if we do?
I'll make up with you.
No matter what.
You can overcome anything
as long as you're in love.
Will you love me forever?
Of course.
I'm in love with you, too.
I'll love you forever.
I promise.
Could you say that one more time?
I...
I will love you forever, Kaito-kun.
So...
So love me forever, okay?
I will.
I swear.
You're pretty tough, as expected.
But I can't give up yet.
Took you long enough.
Tetsuro-kun?
Sorry, Mio.
We're out of gas.
What?!
You okay?
Tetsuro-kun?
That voice...
Is that you, Satoshi-san?!
Huh? Satoshi-san?
You mean Manami-san's...
Save me, Satoshi!
He's going to get me!
What's going on?!
I don't know, but let's keep going!
It...
It really existed.
Then...
Yeah, this is it.
The place in the image I had.
I finally made it here.
I finally found it.
Thank you, Kaito-kun...
Everyone...
Senpai, let's start looking for proof.
Yeah.
What's that?
That's...
That's from the aliens?
But this...
The way it reacted... That means...
But why?
Huh?
S-Senpai...
What is this?
You can see it?!
Yes?
But this is the image in my head.
The cells I used to heal him.
This is... the proof!
Senpai!
No...
Why?
We came all this way!
All this way!
That's...
The place Ichika and the
others were heading to?
Did they break the spacial shielding?
This is bad, Ichika.
Hurry and get out of there.
Kaito-kun!
Senpai!
Stop it!
Don't hurt him!
I won't run anymore!
No, Senpai!
Stop it!
Please...
Please stop.
Senpai!
I'm sorry, Kaito-kun.
I can't do this anymore...
What are you—
This is my fault.
You're in danger! Everyone's
in danger because of me.
This is all because I was being selfish!
No!
No, Senpai.
I already told you.
Everyone... At least I know I...
I don't think that.
If anything, I'm the one being selfish.
I don't want to let you go, Senpai!
Thank you, Kaito-kun.
Senpai!
I...
...almost regretted coming to this planet.
I got everyone caught up in
doing what I wanted to do.
And in the end, I didn't achieve anything.
But now I understand.
We found each other because we
all wanted something to happen.
We were able to find each other.
I will always have this
feeling within me.
It'll never disappear.
I can believe in that.
But...
I love you, Kaito-kun.
I will always... always...
Sen—
I'll come get you!
I swear I'll come get you!
I know. I'll be waiting.
Senpai!
Kai—
I wonder how long it's been.
But thank you for finding this.
I can hear it directly
from the In-Grove...
I made an emergency
landing on this planet,
The data our ancestors passed
down to us has been released.
after my spaceship had trouble,
and was saved by someone here.
Before I knew it, he meant a lot to me.
But this is a remote planet
where contact with
the locals is forbidden.
Help will soon be on the way.
I imagine my memories on this planet
will be sealed to maintain secrecy.
But... I wanted...
...to leave behind the memories
I had with him, no matter what.
Even if my memories faded,
even if I couldn't remember,
I wanted to leave something behind.
Thank you for finding it.
I pray that at least my
memories will live on in you.
Please don't forget.
I won't forget.
I could never forget.
I'll always be waiting.
It was only a few months.
Uminokuchi Station
Something that happened one summer.
Back then we still hadn't done anything.
But we wanted to.
And that's when Ichika-senpai
appeared before us.
And made our summer special for us.
Joy and sorrow.
All of it was there,
in that summer.
We...
Episode 12
Waiting there, in the summer.
...will never forget that summer.
Here, Tetsuro.
Hm?
A girl in the class next door
asked me to give it to you.
Don't take stuff like that.
I couldn't help it.
Make sure you give her an answer.
Actually, get a girlfriend already.
Yeah, but...
Mio's good enough, isn't she?
I'd welcome you.
Well, yeah, but...
Don't laugh, Kai!
Okay, see you later.
Be careful heading back.
Right.
I'll get going, too.
Okay, see you.
Hey.
Let's go home.
Yeah.
Huh?
Did I forget to lock it?
Welcome home.
Nee-san...
I'm back.
How was Bolivia?
It was a lot of work.
But it was fun.
That's good.
Oh, yeah.
Here are your souvenirs.
I question your taste.
Really?
The doll is famous over there for
being able to grant wishes.
And this is for Ichika-chan!
Actually, where is Ichika-chan?
H-Her period for studying abroad ended.
She went back to her homeland.
Really? That's too bad.
Yeah.
Then we can send it to her.
You know her address, right?
Yeah, let's do that.
Wishes...
What?
You're transferring?
Yes, family issues.
But you can't leave, too—
So when are you transferring?
Right now.
Huh?
It's not a farewell gift or anything,
but this is for you guys.
What is it?
This is...
Film?
Why—
Huh?
Remon-senpai?
That was truly a wonderful summer.
But...
...the film is incomplete.
You're the one who has to put the
finishing touches on the last scene.
Sorry about this, Kai.
We came over all of a sudden.
It's fine.
My sister's going to be
home late today, anyway.
But it's been a while since
we've all been here together.
I'm going to turn off the lights, okay?
Yeah.
Kai.
You good?
Here goes.
Remon Yamano
Unfinished Production
People say that when someone
dies, they can go to heaven.
But I don't think that's the case.
When someone dies,
I'm sure that person journeys
into people's hearts.
They live on as a memory.
But that, too, will eventually wane.
That's why people desire to leave
something behind in this world.
So others won't forget them,
so we'll remember them...
I'll keep filming.
Recording the continuation
to what I have on film,
the continuation to that summer...
Special Consultant
Violet Festival
They're playing this
movie again this year.
You mean the one that
the alumni left behind?
I saw it last year. It was pretty good.
There was a spaceship and
a mech. Lots of SFX.
The heroine's a hottie.
That's what you gotta bring up?
You have no place to live?
Th-That's right.
Movie in Session
Annual
"Waiting in the Summer"
Showing
Then how about you come to my place?
I live on my own.
So I have extra rooms.
What happened to your spaceship?
Huh? It broke?
Again?
Thank You Very Much
Thank you all for your support!
Thank you very much!