Why do I have such an eerie feeling?
Huh?
Something is coming near.
I smell Sekigahara.
It's the nauseating smell of a bloody battle.
Find them.
Hunt them down.
Let's go, Gilles de Rais.
I can smell them.
It's them, the Drifters!
Kill them.
Kill those Drifters!
Blight the fig trees...
...before they bear fruit.
What is that?
What is that sound?
I found them... I found them...
I can smell their stench.
Drifters!
Come out now!
I will turn you into ashes and
have you float away on the wind.
That's a fancy trick.
Was that ghost sorcery or something?
Do all of you use the same trick?
Well?!
Here you are!
"Act 7
Chaos Diver"
Shara, gather all the men.
Don't forget bows and arrows.
Let the women flee into the forest.
Yes, sir.
We're going to crush the cavalry.
Are you sure?
You probably don't know about this,
but I am the best in the whole world
when it comes to destroying cavalry.
I will leave it to you, then.
My enemy seems to be...
...that one over there.
Gilles de Rais, kill that girly boy.
I'll take care of this Drifter.
Joan, walk your path well.
He cut the ramparts...
What swordsmanship!
He's just like Musashibo Benkei.
Drifters,
you are the only obstruction to the
Black Lord's eradication of this world!
We will burn all of you Drifters!
So, you are the Ends that
those glasses described to me.
She said you were insane and irrational.
By the way, are you a man or a woman?
He is a quick yellow monkey.
You're trapped now.
Huh? What are you going to do?
What the hell are you
going to do now?! Drifter!
This time, you idiots will be cast down.
Wh... What the hell...?
We are the magician organization, Octobrists.
Our mission is to protect the Drifters!
Wow! You also practice sorcery, huh?!
Well... umm... the only thing I can do
is make the stone wall appear.
Besides, only two charms are...
Grand Master could have done so much better...
I'm an amateur... so... I'm sorry.
No worries! You saved my life.
You have my gratitude.
P-Please stop. Raise your head!
Look! We are surrounded by
enemies and a raging inferno!
Now is not the time for thanking me.
Yeah... but when a man doesn't
express gratitude right away,
he sometimes never gets the chance to later.
That man practices frightening sorcery,
but he seems to have very little or
no experience in battle. He's a rookie.
Wh-What? How come...?
Just intuition. But...
...it seems like he is boasting of his abilities.
In other words, he is bragging about
his powers to someone somewhere.
It's almost like he is saying...
"I possess such power.
Behold. Behold my power."
He is a rookie.
His green head stands out, which means...
...it will be easy for me to take.
This is what makes these
Japanese feudal lords so terrifying.
The same smile indicates
both death and gratitude.
You said you would be able to make
two more stone walls appear, right?
Eh? Umm... yes.
In that case, please do as I tell you.
After that...
...escape to the forest.
Mon... Monster...
That huge knight is a monster, but...
...Yoichi is matching him step for step.
He... is laughing...
That's it. That's how you do it.
It's fun to fight, isn't it, Yoichi?
We humans are born to display our skills.
Your technique is lethal.
You're too good for just practicing
target shooting with fans.
Whoa, well played, Gilles de Rais.
He can't afford to laugh any more, can he?
I shot him so many times...
...mostly in vital spots.
Why? Why is his still alive?!
My journey isn't finished yet.
Thus, I am not finished.
Oh, yeah? You sound...
...just like Benkei.
Super nostalgic!
Hi, everyone. Listen up.
I, Demon King of the Sixth Heaven,
will now begin an easy monkey-level
lecture about how to destroy cavalry.
Listen very carefully, otherwise you could die.
Cavalry can be utterly terrifying,
but there's no need to be afraid of them at all.
You may not understand what I mean here.
They are quite frightening when they make
a sudden attack, galloping towards you.
Yet, when they get carried away and
chase you down to a forest like this one,
unaccompanied by foot soldiers,
they are no longer a threat to us.
Galloping on horses, they think
they have the upper hand.
But as the sound of hooves
is traveling towards trees...
...just like that... we could take them
down with just a small obstacle.
It is suicidal for them to come
into a forest without enough forces.
I had a bad experience with Ise.
Release, now.
If you secure a higher spot, the victory is yours.
This concludes today's lesson.
I-In the blink of an eye...
W-Wow...
This reminds me of Nagashino...
Powerful cavalry shot down by petty soldiers.
Perhaps, the development of firearms will put
an end to knights and warlords in feudalism.
Thus, no matter what...
...we must make a large quantity of firearms.
The issue is that our targets
are those two monsters.
Otherwise, the castle will burn down.
Where are you! Where did you go?!
Where are you hiding?! Get out here!
Get out here now, Drifter!
Or else, or else...
The forest, the castle... I will burn it all!
I can't let you do that.
Even though it's run-down,
it's still our castle.
There you are.
Indeed, here I am.
This time... I won't let you go.
Agreed. I'm not going to escape.
You don't learn, do you?
His escape route...
Fool!
Has he lost his mind?!
Indeed. You won't find a single warrior
from Satsuma who hasn't lost it.
Leave your head...
...with me.
What's with him?! Why?!
He's trapped himself.
I don't get him! Why?! Why?! Why?!
Does he seek death?!
Do it now! Olminu!
This is madness!
Why?! Why?! Why?! Why?!
I can't believe he used the "Stone Wall"
spell to launch his attack...
I meant to use it for his defense.
What is he?!
Grand Master told me that the warriors of
the Sengoku period are more or less insane.
But, in Toyohisa's case, he is willing
to throw away his life and risk it all
as though all he aspires for
is the feat of taking the enemy's head.
But isn't that exactly what the Ends are?!
Every castle has at least a few of these,
and you are standing in front of it...
This is the moment I've been waiting for.
The well!
Wa... Water...
This is water!
What I sought so desperately...
What I yearned for...
What I so keenly desired...
Water!
Witch!
Through flame, be purified!
Behold. The witch is burning!
You dress like a man of the battlefield,
but you're a witch inside... What a joke!
Here it goes. Your crotch will burn through.
Is the bitch a man or woman?
The witch of Orleans! Show us more!
Is it the same down there as a human?!
A witch...
Why me...?
I fought for my people...
For France...
For God!
Come with me...
...you who have been abandoned.
Huh?
What the hell?!
You're a woman?!
Why the hell is a woman wearing
armor and fighting in battle?!
Taking a woman's head is no great feat.
Get out of here. Go home and act like a woman!
You...
What do you people know?
We fought for the people of France!
We fought in the name of Christ!
We fought for our faith!
We fought long and hard...
What do you know about any of that?!
I don't give a damn.
I never heard of a country called "France"!
And what on earth is this "Christ"?!
Argh, you are such a pain in the ass!
You southern barbarians don't talk sense.
Now, I really have to go and
cut the head off that spearman.
If I can't even take one good head,
how can I show my face to my father?
Why?!
Why won't he die?!
Good. Got him.
N-No!
Don't let Yoichi die!
Shoot! Shoot! Shoot!
H-He must be an immortal or a monster...
Wrong!
Unkillable monsters don't exist in this world.
Every life has its end! Everything can be killed!
Shoot! Shoot!
Wow! He is just like Benkei.
The hell is this?!
Hell if I know.
Wh-What the...?!
Do you hate this world, "the End"?!
You are the roaming resentment...
...abandoned by the world!
This is the last magazine!
This is it!
Watch out! Hurry!
She won't last long!
Wh-What the hell?!
Wh-What...?
This has to be a joke!
The Maiden couldn't go to heaven.
She was burned at the stake,
as a heretic and as a witch,
and so slipped into hell.
Since that was the case, I will follow her.
I shall sin enough to get myself damned.
Wait for me in hell, Joan.
Yet, the Maiden didn't go to hell after all...
I found her here in this world...
...but she was no longer the Maiden.
She will certainly go to hell.
Thus, this time, I will arrive first,
and I will wait for her in hell.
Bon voyage, Joan.
As I thought,
he turned into his body's weight in salt...
What is that? What is going on?
Grand Master!
Magician Olminu, you have done a great job.
Th-Thank you!
Who are you? I mean... who are all of you?
I am a man who hates the Ends.
I am Olminu's master and the leader of
the magician organization, the Octobrists.
I am the man tasked
with supporting the Drifters
and wiping out the Ends who
should not exist in this world.
So, you are one of those Drifters?
Your name?
Abe no Haruakira.
"Naming Taboo"
"Rules"
"Onmyoji Temple"
"Act 8
Mystery CALL ME"