The conflict began from a single spark,
and has grown into a massive war.
A multitude of people had myriad
hopes and dreams that were at odds,
resulting in great tragedy.
This is a sad thing indeed.
This war has brought me great sorrow.
I feel both shame and a deep regret
over our use of power
that was not meant for us.
I hereby...
...succeed the previous emperor,
Rayregalia Vers Rayvers,
and name myself Empress
of the Vers Empire.
I also take Count Cruhteo, member of the
Orbital Knights' 37 Clans, to be my husband.
We, the imperial family of the Vers Empire,
wish to make peace with Earth!
In the name of the Empress of Vers,
I command all Orbital Knights who
are listening to this transmission
to cease hostilities immediately!
Impossible!
Wasn't Princess Asseylum going to found
a new dynasty with Lord Troyard?
What about the all-out
offensive on the UFE?
Wait. Do nothing for now.
We'll see which way the wind blows.
I should have known.
Lord Troyard was a lowborn Terran.
His attempts to inveigle his way into
the imperial family are offensive.
What is the meaning of this?!
Sir Harklight, we're returning to base!
Lord Slaine...
Shooting Star of Yesteryear
Why are they still fighting?!
The princess just declared
that they must stop!
The moonbase's forces
are still itching for action.
Stay sharp, everyone!
The battle isn't over!
Did you hear that?
Yeah...
That Princess Asseylum just now...
Um, that Empress Asseylum
was the princess I remember.
Yeah...
So it's just as Lt. Kaizuka predicted.
Then that cease-fire
order was also genuine.
The enemies in front of us don't seem
interested in laying down arms, though.
Any word from HQ?
No instructions, ma'am.
So it's "continue operation."
Neither the moonbase nor Landing Castles
are showing any intent to cease hostilities.
Empress Asseylum's location?
That transmission originated from
Count Mazuurek's Landing Castle.
She's abandoned the Moon?
Or has there been a split?
Count Troyard, what of
Empress Asseylum's order?
Order? What order?
My apologies, Lord.
I'm surprised.
I didn't think her capable of that.
Princess Lemrina.
What is truly important
is the imperial family's blood.
So long as you still have
Aldnoah activation privileges,
can you not still
make your dream come true?
I am not going anywhere.
After all, this is the only place
that I can call home.
So please...
Yes, of course.
Your kindness is touching,
Princess Lemrina.
Let's be off.
Of course.
It's lovely...
Was that a terrible thing to say?
I have seen a great many things
while flying among those lights.
Many things?
The future.
The future...
All of it, both good and bad.
Only the immediate future can be seen.
I thought that I knew everything.
Many things unfolded
exactly as I foresaw.
However...
I failed to see what was truly important.
Rearm it.
Yes, sir!
Lord Troyard!
What is the meaning of this?!
Why would Princess Asseylum
say such a thing?!
Milord Slaine...
Patch this through the command center.
I will address all our forces.
The deployed Stygis Squadron, as well.
Yes, sir!
Hear me! Get clear of the moonbase
in the next 10 minutes!
Surrender to the UFE
along with the Landing Castles!
We will abandon the moonbase!
Have you gone mad?!
Slaine!
Princess Lemrina...
I apologize for the many wrongs...
I have done you.
Slaine?
May you remain in good health.
Harklight, please escort
Princess Lemrina to a shuttle.
As you wish.
No! Slaine!
Highness, please come with me.
I won't go!
Slaine! Slaine!
Multiple new signatures detected
leaving the moonbase.
Reinforcements?
No, they're...
They're leaving the combat zone, ma'am.
The moonbase...
It's fallen?
Did we beat them?
No...
They're making it self-destruct?
Sir Harklight?
See to the shuttle's defense!
Sir Harklight!
Harklight.
What are you doing? Turn back.
I thought I ordered you to surrender.
Harklight!
Stygis Squadron!
Don't act without orders!
Enemy reinforcements closing in.
10 o'clock. Angle of elevation, -10!
Stand by to engage!
Don't! We no longer have
any hope of winning!
Don't throw your lives away!
I made my peace with death
long ago, Lord.
Please allow me this one selfish act.
Surrender, Harklight!
I beg your pardon, Milord Slaine...
But I cannot comply with that order.
Here they come!
All units, scatter!
Come on!
How could they do this?
Damn it all!
What's that?
Those moves...
You're right, Harklight.
We can't let it end like this.
There is still something that I must do!
I've come for you,
Slaine Troyard.
Let's settle this once and for all,
Inaho Kaizuka!
No matter how much you predict my attacks,
there's no point if you can't escape.
You're the one who can't escape!
Opening contact channel.
Decrypting protocols.
I don't think it will do any good,
but I'll ask anyway. Surrender, Slaine Troyard.
You came all this way to say
such a pointless thing to me, Inaho Kaizuka?
No, I have a different objective.
I'm glad to hear that!
Don't disappoint me!
Damn... My monitors are damaged?
I know... You can't do
any more high-load processing.
Cut all predictive imagers.
I no longer...
...have any need for a future!
2 o'clock! Angle of elevation, 5! Incoming!
All ahead, emergency speed!
Come about, 060!
Coming about, 060!
Load canister shot!
Fire once targets are locked!
Wow...
Nao's combat data is stored
in the tactical data link.
All units, refer to that and–
Yuki!
I'm okay!
Barouhcruz, member of the
Orbital Knights 37 Clans!
Do you mind if I cut in?
Count Barouhcruz...
8 o'clock! Angle of elevation, -25! Incoming!
Intercept!
I've got this!
Remaining rounds, 3...
There's nothing to be gained
by continuing to fight.
Agreed. But there's nothing
to be lost by it, either.
Giving in to despair
is a foolish choice.
You just don't get it!
This is the choice I wanted the most!
Slice them up!
Rayet!
Fool!
Radar returns
approaching at high speed!
What?
It's the Tharsis...
and a UFE Kataphrakt!
That's...
Rayet!
Three-direction crossfire!
MRSI, neutralize target, auto fire!
I always...
I always hated that color!
Sir Harklight!
The drones are on autopilot!
Use the boulders!
We can limit the direction of their attack!
Are you all right?
Yes. I only lost an arm.
Sir Harklight.
Battle status?
Including myself,
3 Stygis Masters remain,
as well as some 6 Slaves.
The rest have been downed by the UFE.
I have fired most of my bullets as well.
Count Barouhcruz.
The Octantis' right
arm is nonfunctional.
It must have been damaged
in that last attack.
These Terran warriors
are not without skill.
Yes.
It is Lord Slaine's
birthplace, after all.
"Do not try to fight
an Olympian sandstorm," eh?
We seem to have
misread the winds.
Let's have another go!
I shall join you.
9 o'clock! Angle of elevation, 20!
Enemy formation closing in!
All guns, take aim!
Kataphrakt platoons!
All units, fire at will!
I'll act as a drogue chute.
It will stabilize you.
You intend to die with me?
You'll burn up.
Kataphrakt frames are high density.
They'll work well enough
as ablative shielding.
Impossible... It can't be done.
Really? I guess we'll see.
Sis, look!
A shooting star!
Look at this.
Aldnoah Reactor #1, constructed as a sign
of goodwill between Earth and Vers,
is scheduled to be activated today.
We're told that Empress Asseylum herself
will participate in the activation ceremony.
Research into making activation privileges
universal so that anyone can do it is still ongoing.
When that happens,
industries using Aldnoah will develop
and will help greatly
with Earth's reconstruction.
And as the nation that produces Aldnoah,
it should also prove to be
an effective means for the Vers
Empire to earn foreign capital.
Dr. Troyard's theories have
already been proven,
so we should see them put into
practice in the near future.
It's ironic that Slaine Troyard,
the son of that same Dr. Troyard,
plotted the assassination of Empress Asseylum,
which was the trigger for
Interplanetary War II.
Slaine Troyard's death allowed Earth
and Vers to conclude a friendship treaty.
Yes, but there are still Mars Knights
who occupy territory on Earth.
One goal of Empress Asseylum's visit
is peace negotiations with those knights.
Here's hoping that we'll be seeing
the prompt return of that occupied territory.
In the hope that this light
will be a bridge of peace
between Earth and Vers,
....awaken!
How are you feeling?
You don't seem too bad.
You really should eat your meals, though.
The warden has been complaining.
Your move.
Your eye.
Is that from when I shot you?
An analytical engine.
I had a bio-device implanted
that was neuro-linked to my cranial nerves.
But I had it removed.
I don't need it anymore.
Hasn't it been long enough?
I deceived, I stole, I killed.
I sacrificed many of my own.
Please.
No. You're going to live.
Why?!
Why did you save me?!
I have one more favor to ask of you.
It wasn't me.
It's what Princess Asseylum wants.
Please...
Please, save Slaine.
Save Slaine Troyard.
Save him from the chains of misery.
Please.
Seylum asked me...
...to save you.
My goodness...
The blue sky and sea go on forever!
It's so beautiful...
I'm told that the blue sky is the result
of something called Rayleigh scattering.
You're quite well-informed.
When I visited Earth last time,
a Terran I had befriended
was kind enough to teach me.
It's a lovely memory.