"Hosu General Hospital"
Two days since the Hosu incident,
and five days since
we started our internships...
Since my injuries from Stain were not
fully healed yet, I was in a hospital bed.
"Special Report: Hero Killer!"
On the news, the hero killer
was the talk of the town.
"Near the scene the day after the incident"
When seven pro heroes and three high school
students came across the hero killer,
Endeavor rushed over
and took care of the situation.
That was the official story
released by the police.
Just as the person from the police said,
Iida, Todoroki,
and my names were not made public,
and our injuries were explained away
as accidents that happened
during our internships.
The night Iida got the results of
the examination of his injured arms,
"Tenya Iida - Quirk: Engine"
he went back with his mom
to his parents' house.
"Izuku Midoriya - Quirk: One For All"
As for Todoroki,
who had relatively light injuries...
"Shoto Todoroki - Quirk: Half-Cold, Half-Hot"
I will return to my internship.
To Endeavor's place?
I want to learn what I can from him.
Besides, they said he defeated the
hero killer even though he didn't actually do it.
I want to see his expression.
You become kind of mean when
it comes to Endeavor, huh, Todoroki?
I'm sure everyone else
is working hard right now.
"Everyone's Internships"
It is possible that the villains who were
inspired by the Hosu incident the other day
will become more active.
Even though this is just a patrol,
don't let your guard down.
Right.
This is sudden, but here's a question.
Patrols are meant to deter
villains from committing crimes,
"Katsuki Bakugo - Quirk: Explosion"
but they also have a secondary effect.
What is it?
If we see villains, we
beat them up right away!
"Pro Hero - Best Jeanist"
No.
It's Best Jeanist!
Please do your best at work!
The answer is: to show people who we are.
To give the public peace of mind.
It builds trust between those who
protect and those who are being protected.
What is this, a courtesy visit?
Oh, I've seen him on TV before!
The sports festival again?
He was caught by a villain and
looked like he was about to cry, right?
What did you say?!
Did you already forget what I taught you?
Deal with them properly.
All right already!
You know, I wasn't caught
by the villain back then,
I was thinking about how to defeat him.
It wasn't that I'd lost.
I'm the man who'll become
the number one hero!
There's no reason for kids
like you to worry about me--
He's too proud.
It's fine for those strong feelings
to be aimed at becoming a hero,
but if that is no longer the case...
Now, what shall I do with you?
"Pro Hero - Gunhead"
How would you fight against
an opponent with a knife?
Uravity, can you try attacking me?
You sure?
You don't have to hold back.
"Ochaco Uraraka - Quirk: Zero Gravity"
Then, here I come!
When someone's waving a knife at you,
deal with it by keeping your distance.
If they attack directly,
use one leg as an axis to turn and dodge,
then grab their wrist
and neck and the same time,
and then hold them down
as you pull their wrist.
If you can twist their wrist
to make them drop the knife
and kick the knife far away,
it'll be even more perfect.
He moved so smoothly, without hesitation.
Gunhead Martial Arts...
So amazing!
Even though he acts cute...
This time, I'll hold the knife, 'kay?
We'll keep repeating this
until you can do it!
All right?
Yes, sir!
--Uwabami, can I have your autograph?
--Can I take your picture?
"Pro Hero - Uwabami"
Look this way, please!
Um...
When you work diligently like this,
you can eventually make big blossoms bloom.
"Momo Yaoyorozu - Quirk: Creation"
It's like when an enka singer
goes on provincial tours.
Doesn't "work diligently"...
...mean something different?
"Itsuka Kendo - Quirk: Big Fist"
"Pro Hero - Fourth Kind"
Contributing to the community is
also an essential part of being a hero.
Don't drag your feet doing it!
Do you understand?
Yes, Mr. Fourth Kind...
I can't hear you!
"Tetsutetsu Tetsutetsu - Quirk: Steel"
"Eijiro Kirishima - Quirk: Hardening"
Yes, Mr. Fourth Kind!
"Pro Hero - Death Arms"
How many hostages are there?
From what I can hear, there are two.
"Kyoka Jiro - Quirk: Earphone Jack"
All right. We're breaking in.
Earphone Jack, please tell
the escaping hostages what to do.
R-Right, Death Arms.
Let's go!
This is a pro hero! Do as I say!
I will escort you! Come below with me!
We're saved!
Thank you, hero!
"Oki Mariner"
"Tsuyu Asui - Quirk: Frog"
Ribbit.
Froppy!
Ribbit?
How are things on your end?
I've finished cleaning the deck, Sirius.
It's boring just training and
cleaning the deck every day, isn't it?
Yes, a little.
It was the same when I did my internship.
I was confused by the difference
between the image I had of what a hero
was when I was a kid and
what the reality was.
I imagined something a lot showier,
but in reality, it's a daily grind
of training and patrols and cleaning.
On top of that, I even had
to wash the captain's underwear!
What part of this is being a hero? I thought.
Did you get tired of it?
At first, I did.
But after becoming the
captain's sidekick, I realized
what was really important for a hero.
What's really important? What is it?
You have to find the answer to that yourself.
Right?
Ribbit.
Hey, Froppy!
What're you playing around for?
Just because frogs have big mouths doesn't
mean you can spend all your time gabbing.
And Sirius, I ordered you to supervise her.
Make sure you're doing your job properly!
I've finished cleaning, Captain.
And I'm supervising her properly!
Ribbit.
Oh, is that right?
I guess I jumped to conclusions.
I see, I see! My bad!
I'm sorry!
Was I too cute for words, Froppy?
She's dumbfounded.
I always say this, but you
can't just make your face cute.
Below the neck, you're too macho...
Your face is also too rugged, though...
What did you say?!
When I do this for kids, they love it!
Yeah! They love making fun of it!
Because it's not cute at all.
How cute.
Captain Selkie, there's a message
from the Japan Coast Guard!
All right, I'll be there right away!
Froppy, help me unfasten the ropes.
We'll probably be sailing out.
Ribbit!
It's me.
That's right. You're good at this.
One, two! One, two! One, two!
I see. Got it!
The ropes are unfastened!
Sailors! We're making an emergency departure!
--Aye aye, sir!
--Ribbit!
Full speed ahead!
All right, the Oki Mariner is sailing out!
"Affiliation: U.A. High School Hero Class 1-A"
"Birthday: 8/1" "Height: 154 cm"
"Blood Type: A" "Likes: Rock Music"
"Kyoka Jiro"
"Quirk: Earphone Jack"
"She can insert the plugs on her earlobes into her opponent and channel loud sounds into them."
"Affiliation: U.A. High School Hero Class 1-A"
"Birthday: 2/12" "Height: 150 cm"
"Blood Type: B" "Likes: Jello"
"Tsuyu Asui"
"Quirk: Frog"
"She can do pretty much everything a frog can, like stretch out her tongue really far."
Stowaways?
The Coast Guard got a tip that there
were stowaways on the trade ship, Nysan.
The Coast Guard inspected the Nysan,
\but the stowaways were nowhere to be found.
However, after more careful investigation,
they found cargo missing
from the ship's freight list.
Do you know what this means, Froppy?
Ribbit.
I think it means that
before the Coast Guard arrived,
the stowaways moved the cargo
to another ship and ran away.
The stowaways may have
been smuggling brokers.
That's correct!
That's not cute...
How cute.
The job we've taken on this time
is to secure the stowaways
thought to have escaped on a small boat
and deliver them to the Coast Guard!
Based on the Nysan's position,
this is the area of the ocean where
the smaller boat is predicted to land.
The Coast Guard and other sea rescue
heroes are also searching for the boat.
We will be responsible for...
...this area!
The sun will set soon.
You guys search for the boat with the radar!
I will look for them in the ocean.
That is all!
Now, get to work, sailors!
--Aye aye, sir!
--Ribbit!
"Selkie"
"Quirk: Spotted Seal"
Sea Rescue Hero: Selkie!
Quirk: Spotted Seal.
He can do pretty much
anything a spotted seal can.
He can even make a sonar-like sound
and use the echo to determine
the position of his opponent.
He's also very strong!
They aren't around here.
Guess I'll widen my search a little!
As expected, I can't see
anything in this darkness...
It doesn't look like we've been able
to catch anything on the radar yet, either.
It's fine!
Ribbit?
We've got the captain on our side!
We have a message from the Coast Guard!
A fishing boat thought to belong to
the stowaways shook off
a hero agency patrol boat
and escaped into the direction
of the area we're in charge of!
Ribbit...
Captain!
I've confirmed the location of the fishing
boat thought to belong to the stowaways!
Sailors!
Turn off all the lights and get close
without letting them know where we are!
--Aye aye, sir!
--Ribbit!
Captain, I can see a
fishing boat with my naked eye.
All right, block their
course with a patrol boat
and board their boat while
setting off a flare.
Aye aye, sir!
What should I do?
Stay here.
Ribbit!
Sirius, stay with her.
Yes, sir!
Then I won't be able
to experience the internship.
Just be quiet and do as I say!
Let's go!
Aye aye, sir!
Ribbit...
I know that you want to go with them, Froppy.
But you know, even if we're up against
stowaways, we have to be very careful, right?
So follow the captain's orders.
Let's give them support together.
Ribbit.
Captain, we've arrived
at the fishing boat's course!
All right, leave the rest to me.
Stop the ship! This is a pro hero!
We are here on a job for the
Japan Coast Guard to inspect your ship!
Captain! I didn't find
any of the cargo in question.
There wasn't any here, either.
That's what I told you!
We were just fishing--
Then, you can show us
what's under here, too, right?
There's nothing but fish down there.
Just open it up!
What a pain.
There's nothing but fish...
It's too dark to see clearly...
Can't you turn on any lights--
I did as you said.
So p... please spare my life...
We won't kill ya.
Don't worry!
If we can buy this much time...
...then it'll be easier for Boss Innsmouth
to do what he needs to do.
Our job's done!
See ya!
Captain! Captain, please respond!
It's no good. The radio's
not getting through.
I'll go take a look!
Wait!
"Sirius"
"Quirk: Good Ear"
Sirius! Quirk: Good Ear.
She can hear high frequencies
that humans cannot hear.
"Stowaways"...
"Different boat"!
"We're fine. Find them."
Mick, start the ship!
Yes, ma'am!
If that boat is a decoy, then the stowaways
should be heading toward the shore.
Hurry!
Got it!
We don't have to resuce
the captain and the others?
We're going to follow the captain's orders.
Because we believe what the captain
decided is the best course of action!
Froppy, you believe, too--
In the captain,
and in us.
Ribbit!
I see them!
They're hiding in the shadow of Double Rock!
Damn it, in a place like that...!
Cut the engine and go to
one of the cruiser's blind spots!
Yes, ma'am!
Froppy, you help, too!
Ribbit!
There's someone keeping watch...
Froppy, can you bring the guard over here?
Leave it to me.
Wha... Wha... What?!
Y-You guys--
If you answer our questions,
then we won't get rough with you.
Here I go.
Thanks.
There's only one person on the cruiser.
He's hiding in a cabin.
I'll drag him out!
What?! I can't see!
Mick!
Froppy!
Sirius!
Gotcha.
A villain!
I thought I'd gotten clean away,
but you guys are too persistent!
Ribbit...
Huh? What, you've only got
a woman and a kid left?
Oops, don't move!
I'll give her back once
I'm free of the Coast Guard.
I'll have you help me move the cargo, too.
Sorry.
We're locked up in the fishing boat
and our transmission's been blocked.
The captain went ahead.
--Ribbit...
--How are things on your end?
Tell me your situation. Please respond!
So it's a radio, huh?
Hey, kid!
If you care about this woman's life,
then tell them this:
"We couldn't find the stowaways."
Ribbit...!
Don't do it, Fro--
Sirius!
Hurry up!
You don't care what'll happen to this woman?
Huh? How about it?
Ribbit...
Well?
...what was really important for a hero.
We're going to follow the captain's orders.
Because we believe what the captain
decided is the best course of action!
Froppy, you believe, too--
I know.
The stowaways are at Double Rock!
Tsu...
You little brat...!
I'll kill you!
Stop moving around so much! It's so annoying!
Ribbit!
--Oops! I've got you.
--Ribbit...
Ribbit...
Ri... Ribbit... Rib...
The end!
You're just a brat.
Since you came here uninvited,
you'll have to die!
Boss!
My brothers!
Ribbit!
Captain!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Leave the rest to me!
No way!
Even if I can't see...
I know...
...where you are!
Damn bastard!
Captain!
All right!
The captain's amazing...
Froppy!
Ribbit...
Are you all right? Are you hurt?
I'm fine. What about you, Sirius?
My body's the only thing strong about me.
Good job, you two.
Thanks to you, we were
able to catch the stowaways.
Captain...
Thanks!
You're doing that now?
Sirius, I'm glad I was able
to come to this internship.
Huh?
What's really important for a hero...
I think I understand a little better now!
I see.
Arrest all the stowaways.
We were able to recover all the
illegal drugs they were trying to bring in, too.
By the way, Selkie,
when did you get a new sidekick?
Ribbit?
She's a U.A. student
here for an internship.
Is that right? We made you
go through something scary, huh?
Sorry.
Hey, don't treat her like a kid.
Froppy doesn't have her license yet,
but she's already an excellent hero.
I guarantee it.
Yup, yup.
Then, I'm looking forward to
when we can work together,
Froppy.
Ribbit, ribbit.
"Preview"
All Might! I have returned
from my internship!
You went through a lot
with the Hosu incident, huh?
I'm sorry I couldn't be nearby!
Well, what were you trying to tell me?
The time has come when I must tell you
about me and One For All,
and the mission entrusted to you!
Next time, "Listen Up!!
A Tale from the Past."
It's an important episode,
so you're not allowed to miss it!
Go beyond!
"Next time: Listen Up!! A Tale from the Past"
Plus Ultra!