Go, go!
Wow!
Motoba is fast!
Aah, so close!
In third place, from Arayada High School: Motoba!
And so...
Motoba has just placed third
in the Prefectural Tournament!
Kirie is great, huh?
She's the fastest swimmer in our school!
This is impressive indeed, Kirie!
Okay, both of you take your seats.
Great job, Motoba!
You were faster than the third-years!
Sure enough, you have a future as a pro swimmer!
I don't get it, but maybe talking about
being a pro swimmer is...
Huh? It's a BAD thing?
Maybe it's all the pressure.
As in, using the restroom?
Master!
Please, look! I placed third in a swimming competition!
Great job, Kirie!
It's because you helped hone my skills
through "Wii Wii Sports"!
I wonder if you can use that in real life...
Oh, that's right!
You like the beach and stuff, and now
you're a swimmer in The Game of Life, huh?
Ah! You're right.
Maybe you'll be a pro swimmer and capture the gold!
No...!
I don't get it, but maybe
talking about being a pro swimmer is...
Oh, no! Kirie might not like being told stuff like that!
Oh, no! I've displeased my Master!
I, um, I'm sorry, Master.
Huh?
A storybook?
"Kirinrin."
Kiri...
Say, was it YOU who wrote this?
Y-yes!
I'm sorry. I meant no disrespect.
I-I mean... I...
I want to... to be a... storybook author!
A storybook author?
So, it's a storybook author you've wanted to be.
That's awesome, Kirie!
Huh?!
Hey, can I take a look?
N-no! I-I'm sorry. I'm embarrassed!
Naah, come on!
I wanna see it. What's it about?
P-please forgive me, Master!
Huh? For real?
Shpaaan!
I know, right?
Yes!
Ah, Sylphin.
Huh? A kimono.
Oh, good morning, Kirie.
Everyone, are you aware what day it is today?
March 5th, right?
Yes! And March 5th is Girls' Day,
when girls dress in traditional Japanese clothing!
I'm pretty sure it's on March 3rd...
It may be over, but we can still wear our kimonos, right?
Note: On this day, elaborate dolls are put out on display.
That's right! And it's still okay to keep the dolls out.
Really?
Yup, right up until Insect Awakening Day!
Come to think of it, some areas keep them out
until the 4th... so, we're fine!
Sylphin looks so different in a kimono, doesn't she?
Yup!
She's always wearing the same thing...
Indeed, this year was the first time I've worn a kimono!
The three of us wore kimonos
at the department store one time, didn't we?
Oh, that's right!
I... I have a picture.
Shugaaan!
No! M-me too!
Squaring off against Sylphin makes Kirie rather active...
Leaving me out is unfair indeed! I wish to take a photo as well!
So...
Let's all four of us go take a photo.
We shall, indeed!
Huh? We're not going to Nyaon?
We don't have to go to a department store.
We can take a splendid photo at my house!
After all, my mother is...
Oh, my. Welcome back, Sylph.
Are these your friends?
Mother!
That's her mom?!
She's so young!
Indeed, I am her mother.
Shpa!
You must be Umaru, yes?
Huh? Y-yes.
Such elegance... such an aura!
All your body's numerical values
adhere to the golden ratio!
Truly, it is the Divine Proportion!
Do you have some regimen to accentuate your beauty?
Uh...
No, no, no! I want it, I want it, I want it!
Bl-bleegh!
N-not especially...
Well, Sylph?
Shall we guide them to that room?
My mother has won the
All-Japan Kimono Fitting Championship.
Wow.
So then...
I cannot accept it!
Not unless I... am always the best!
Indeed! Indeed!
Yeah, they're pretty similar...
Shba!
Sylph, your sleeves aren't aligned properly.
W-well, I was moving around at school, so...
Is this not better?
Indeed!
I'm glad they get along.
Yeah.
Oh. Yeah...
Ebina's hometown is in Akita,
so I bet she can't go back that much.
Maybe I'll have my mom teach me
how to put on a kimono too.
Shba!
Ebina, we have to put a little more force into it.
Shba.
Shba!
SHBA!
Shbababa!
Whoa!
Indeed, that's my mother's high-speed
kimono fitting technique.
All done!
Such a tangible feeling of feminine power!
And look, the dolls are still out on display.
Whoa...
Note: Sushi toppings scattered over a bowl of rice.
We have chirashizushi as well! Let's all eat together.
Y-yeah.
Now then...
I'd say this calls for a photo. Come now, sit, sit.
Very well, here goes.
Okay! Say cheese.
Relax and enjoy yourselves.
It's delicious!
Sylphin, your mom is amazing.
Yeah. And so young.
No, that's not true. She just turned-
Sylph.
INDEED!
Whoa!
This is awesome, Kirie!
It's like a book you'd see in the store!
No... the big sellers at Mujimuji Ryohin
are the ones that aren't too hard to make.
Sure enough, I haven't got it.
Huh?
This artwork still isn't enough to capture your grace!
Your cuteness! Your charm!
The feeling of just wanting to hold you tight!
Huh...?
Th-that's why... I-I'd like to have you model for me.
Huh? Un modele?!
M-Master! I'm sorry! That's fine for now!
Huh? I was no good?
Being a model sure is hard, huh?
I'm sorry, Master! Please, just act normal.
I'll take care of the posing on my end.
Huh? Still, I'll be thinking about you being there...
Not to worry!
Removing all trace of my presence is my special skill!
Is that really a "special skill"?
Squeak, squeak. Squeak, squeak.
Master is right here in front of me, and she's so cute,
but I just can't capture her expressions.
Is this a lack of my own abilities?
Still, I'm sure that with more observation, I will...
Yes, I must watch her even more closely!
More closely...
MORE CLOSELY!
Umaruuun!
Umaru?!
Huh?
Wait, what? Kirie?
I-I'm sorry, Master! I didn't mean to wake you!
What was that just now?
Even if Master Komaru is
Umaru's younger sister, that was...!
I'm home.
That was super fast!
It's good to see you, Kirie.
S-sorry for the bother!
Here. I got you a new flavor of potato chips.
Huh? A new flavor?!
But we're about to have dinner,
so you can't eat them today.
Yes, I know, Big Brother.
Oh...
Master's biggest smile is when her older brother is here.
Kirie, you should join...!
Um, join us for dinner.
No! I must go home and start drawing immediately!
Drawing what?
Huh?
Umaru.
This says there's a new Western-style restaurant.
How about we have lunch there while we're shopping?
I'm just gonna... sleep.
Oh... okay...
That Umaru, I swear.
This whole spring break, all she's done is sleep.
I can understand that she's sleepy, but still...
she should dress up a little
and go have fun with her friends.
Ah, Taihei!
Good afternoon!
Hi, Ebina.
That's pretty responsible of you
to always do the shopping yourself.
No, not at all. Also...
Apparently, a new restaurant has opened up!
We live in the same complex,
so I guess we do a lot of the same things.
Also, um...
it might be the restaurant where my big brother works.
Um, Ebina...
Kirie!
Kirie, w-wait!
How are you, Kirie?
H-h-hello, Taihei.
What are you going to do with all those pens?
I-I...!
I want to be a storybook author!
Huh?
U-uh...
Th-that is...
Um!
We use them a lot in art class.
They're always running out.
Ah, they're for school, huh? That sure takes me back.
Huh? But it's spring break.
Well, that is...
Um... I mean...!
So, Big Brother went off to eat alone, did he?!
Ah! There he is. And Kirie and Ebina?
Big Brother!
Umaru.
What's the big idea? How can you go off and eat alone?!
What brings you out with my brother?
W-well, I happened to run into him here...
For me, it was at the supermarket.
Kirie, are you buying those pens?
Huh?! No!
Kirie, I bet you could totally be a storybook author...!
...author...!
I-it may be spring break, but we
use them a lot in art class, don't we?
Huh? Art class?
There's something Kirie doesn't want us to know.
Ebina saw that and has been trying to cover for her.
She's not talking to Umaru and Kirie
about her big brother either...
Maybe she thinks she has to be careful
and not talk about these things.
Ebina...
Y-yes?
You're really kind, aren't you?
Huh?
Huuuuuuuh?!
Ebina, what is it?
Ebina!
Welcome.
It's great, isn't it, Ebina?
Y-yes!
I wanna turn the A/C on! I wanna turn the A/C on!
It's HOT, Big Brother! So hot!
It's still only May, so it's too soon.
I was so hot last night that I couldn't sleep!
And here, this is what YOU looked like!
When did you take that?!
Let's turn it on early this year! It won't cost that much
if we keep it up a little high.
It's not like I'm trying to say we're broke.
If you keep the A/C on all the time,
you'll stop being able to regulate your body heat
and you'll get cooling disorder.
I've got no strength...
I'm tired...
I'm sleepy...
Big Brother! Big Brother! Big Brother...!
That's how Big Brother sees me?
In any case, we're not turning on the A/C till July!
He's turned into some stubborn old man.
Still, stubborn old men are known
for having a soft spot for kids...
You sure do know a lot, Big Brother.
I'd never heard of cooling disorder!
Huh? No, I just saw it on the news.
Don't be modest! You have SO much knowledge
to draw from that I'm jealous!
Why is she acting like some young performer?
And you're always helping me with my studies.
It's such a big help!
R-really?
So turn on the A/C.
What the heck?
I said no, and that means NO!
What?! Big Brother, you're such a scrooge!
Ughhh... it's so hot. Big Brother, I can't sleep...
Huh? What's that?
A fan.
Hm? We had a fan?
Bomba gave it to me last year.
Huh?! Why didn't you bring it out sooner?
Sorry. It was in the closet
and I completely forgot about it.
We'll get a nice breeze if we put it by the window.
It's a lot cooler than you'd think, huh?
Tonight, I can sleep in comfort!
Ah! Big Brother, what are you doing?
Come here and see.
Huh? What?
Are shooting stars gonna shoot?
I don't think we'll be seeing
any meteor showers this time of year.
There, you see those five stars
in a staggered pattern? That's Cassiopeia.
I know that.
You know what that glowing one there is?
Sure don't.
It's Altair. And next to that is Deneb.
And over there, look. That bird-looking one is Cygnus.
The orange one is Arcturus.
The white there is Spica.
And that's... huh?
Haven't I taught you like this before?
Huh? Nope.
Guess I'm imagining things.
Umaru, do you know any other stars?
There was a mosquito, huh?
There was a mosquito.
Your dream is so wonderful, Kirie!
I'm not worthy of such words, Master!
You should let other people know about it!
One day, I would like to ask your older sister about it.
Yup. She'll be waiting.