Bellows!
You've got a delivery!
Hey, thanks.
Good work.
Thank you!
It looks like you've cheered up some.
I can't stay sad forever.
Apparently, Flange and the others
are staying in the Sea of Mist.
The Milky Way winds that direction, so if we
stay on this course, we'll pass close by.
We might find out how they're doing, too.
I just hope Pinion doesn't mess things up.
If everyone's safe, I
don't care about the rest.
See you!
Hey! What is that?!
It's huge! Don't tell me they're pirates?!
Fleet Commander!
Sound the alarm to all ships in the fleet!
However, don't act carelessly.
Order Pinion to...
Never mind, I'll tell him.
Ledo!
Commander Kugel... Commander, is that you?!
Long time no see, Ledo.
It's great to see you alive and well.
You too, Commander...
I picked up your distress signal,
but I was on the other side
of the planet, you see.
If you'd sent out a transmission,
I would have gone to you.
It was necessary to stay radio silent.
Can you come over here?
Yes, sir. Ensign Ledo is setting
out to rejoin your command.
What is that?
Are they pirates?
It's gigantic! We could be in deep shit!
Pinion, wouldn't we be better off just escaping?
Escape? Escape where?!
Come on, we got the cannon
and the tin can on our side.
Let's fire a shot off their
port bow by way of greeting.
Yeah!
Huh...
Angle of elevation set!
Ready to launch!
Fire!
How do you like that? Did
we knock some sense...
Wha...?!
W-What was that?!
It was like lightning...
What the hell do you think
you're doin' to my treasure?!
What's that?
The tin can?
No, it's different...
Hey, Ledo! Where's Ledo?!
This is Ensign Ledo.
I am now returning to the command of the
Galactic Alliance of Humankind army.
Hey! What are you talkin' about?!
Ledo! Tin can!
Supreme Ruler of Terror
Guide signal received. Now landing.
What are they doing?
Unknown. Conjecture: Collective action
to indicate military proficiency.
These people are under military command?
Welcome,
envoy from the sky, clad in lightning giant.
In the name of providence, we wish you
blessings of prosperity and peace.
What's she saying?
Speculation: She used an idiomatic expression
referring to a Machine Caliber or pilot.
Where is Commander Kugel?
This way.
Follow me.
Please wait here.
I beg your pardon for using a holograph.
Commander Kugel!
I can't believe we're meeting on this
planet! You were safe all this time!
Not safe. I have an endemic disease.
To remain in a sterile environment,
I can't leave the cockpit.
Are you okay?
No problem.
I see.
Issuing orders from here
is surprisingly a pain.
I can imagine.
It helps that you're here.
Well? Will you follow me again?
Of course, Commander!
From Chamber K6821 to Striker X3752,
requesting information on
relevant endemic disease.
From Striker X3752 to Chamber K6821,
request granted. Transmitting information.
Hey, we're surrounded.
This doesn't look good.
We've got the treasure.
You sure we're gonna be okay?!
Don't panic. Worse comes to
worst, the tin can will...
Didn't it leave a little while ago?
It's all over...
O-Okay, calm down.
We don't even know what they want yet...
They're obviously after the relics!
How would they know about it?!
Because you announced it to the world!
How are you gonna get us out of this?!
Well, I, uh... Sorry.
Is this any time to be squabbling?
You stay out of it!
Look at what's going on around you.
Then everyone return to your posts!
Thanks for that.
I heard the owner of that
weapon is Ledo's friend...
Yeah...
Then there was more than
one visitor from the sky...
But what in the world does Ledo's
friend intend to do with us?
Emergency!
You've got a message from the fleet!
Flange here. What's wrong?
They're demanding to see a representative.
What do they want?
They didn't say.
They must be after the relics. I'll go.
Wait! I'm the one who
called the bastards over.
I'll talk to them.
Don't be ridiculous. I can't give you the
responsibility of diplomatic negotiations.
Um, actually...
They've designated "Pinion of the
Sea of Mist" as the representative.
See? It's my time to shine.
Don't be stupid...
If you become a hostage,
who's gonna keep the fleet together?
I see your point, but...
Don't worry!
After I brought this fine state of affairs
down upon us, nobody's gonna follow me.
I'm gettin' what I deserve.
Understood. Just be sure to act cautiously.
Sure. Well, see ya later.
Pinion!
They're telling you to wait.
They'll bring a boat over.
Is that right?
"After I brought this fine state of affairs
down upon us, nobody's gonna follow me."
Shut up, would ya?
You're overreacting. People
don't think that way.
Oh yeah?
You've always been a screw-up.
Nobody's gonna wash their hands
of you over something like this.
That's much appreciated.
Here it comes!
Wha...?! Huh?
That's...
...the Surfing Lobster!
Pinion of the Sea of Mist.
That is you, isn't it?
Yeah. I never thought I'd meet
the Great Pirate Lukkage here.
You can just call me "Lukkage".
And one more thing...
For the time being, you'd
best watch your tongue.
Right...
Everybody looks hard up. Aren't they
gettin' enough to eat around here?
The weak serve the strong.
That's divine providence, apparently.
That's their god?
That's a lightning giant.
They're supposed to be envoys of
god that deliver holy judgment.
Even as the humans of this planet
are blessed with this environment,
they're overwhelmed by and live
in terror of the Hideauze.
Our duty is teaching them how to fight
and enlightening them about
the dignity of the human race.
About that, Commander...
The Hideauze...
They're humans!
You mean formerly humans.
Commander, you knew?!
Among the higher-ups, it
was tacitly understood.
But for soldiers like us on the front
line, that's unnecessary information.
Unnecessary?
The Hideauze just live and
reproduce as they desire.
They cannot be called humans.
Yes, sir.
The strong and the weak support
each other through rationality.
They each have their own ways to
contribute and build a society.
That's what humans are.
That may be true, but...
I brought order to this fleet.
As a result of the current system,
there's been a marked improvement in
the level of happiness of fleet members.
Request: Definition of
"happiness" in this context.
According to the philosophy
of the Galactic Alliance,
happiness is the realization
of a circumstance in which the individual
renders service to the entire group
and the cost-benefit performance of
that is at the greatest efficiency.
As such, happiness is commensurate with
the degree of stability of command.
Agreed on the definition and the conclusion.
Really?
Hey, Ledo,
how about trying to change
this planet with me?
Here.
Nobody's here?
What the hell is this?
This is cool!
Like this...
How about that?
That's right...
Pinion of the Sea of Mist, you are
welcome here as a distinguished guest.
What the hell? A communication device?
The remaining humans on Earth require
an improvement in technical proficiency.
This was a test to measure your technical
ability, Pinion of the Sea of Mist.
Conclusion: You have an aptitude for it.
I've heard that fancy pants
way of talking before.
Don't tell me you're a
relative of the tin can?
I am a Pilot Support Enlightenment
Interface System, Striker X3752.
And what does the great Striker want with me?
Your ability to repair weapons that are
brought up from the ocean floor is admirable.
But only emergency measures are taken as
basic operating principles are not understood.
Ain't my fault!
Like I'm supposed to know how machines
were put together way back when?
I am prepared to provide you with
information on their construction.
That's...
With your ability, you need
not stop at repairing weapons.
You may be able to design
and produce new weapons.
You're givin' me way too much credit.
Conclusion: You have the ability
to learn that technology.
My final request is for you to
become an engineering officer.
An officer?!
I ain't no soldier!
More importantly, can you guarantee
the safety of our fleet?
It is valid human resources
that should not be wasted.
Wasted?
Whatever, if you guarantee its safety,
I guess I could help you out.
I have great expectations of your progress.
Please, before you dine...
It will be over soon if
you do as you're told.
Who the hell do you people think you are?
Hold still if you want
to be finished quickly.
This is Pinion of the Sea of
Mist to my fellow human beings.
Commitment and cooperation
are what make humans human.
By joining the Flange fleet
with the Kugel fleet,
we would acquire even more
prosperity and peace.
I seek a wise judgment from my fellow humans.
Is what it says...
It's a nice way of demanding
that we surrender.
Fleet Commander...
Though we have no choice but to accept...
Am I addressing the fleet commander?
Indeed.
You have my respect for making a wise choice.
I would like to believe that it was made
amicably. But what are you trying to do?
They mean to split up the fleet!
What?!
Each ship will be requisitioned
separately, according to their use.
That's a problem. The fleet is like a family.
It only works if we're all together.
From today on, you are all in the
service of an even bigger family.
But...
Those who comply with
providence shall be blessed.
However, those who betray providence
shall be crushed by the hammer of God.
Understood.
Then get on your knees. You
shall receive a benediction.
New servant of Kugel,
in the name of providence,
you shall devote yourself body
and soul to the great cause.
This is totally different
from the area I saw before.
Guys that live here must be makin' bank.
There is no money here.
What do you do without money?
According to your work, you receive the
appropriate amount of rations from the fleet.
It's an extremely fair society.
Fair, huh?
This is your residential area.
I'll show you to your quarters.
What's with them?
Where's everyone from my ship?
Right about now, each part of the
fleet is being requisitioned.
Each part?
Yes.
Did you really think this fleet would allow
the consolidation of a potential insurgency?
It suited you to bring us in
and now you talk insurgency?!
At any rate, you'd be better off avoiding
contact with your friends for the time being.
Fine.
Virus data analysis complete.
Running Ensign Ledo's physical evaluation.
Physical evaluation complete.
Nothing abnormal detected.
All this time, the commander led a
huge fleet from this cramped space?
I can't imitate him.
Conjecture: Commander Kugel
has withdrawn into his cockpit
because he wishes his existence to be a symbol
and to strike the crew members with awe.
Speculation: As a result, strong
leadership will be produced.
So it's scarier if he can't be seen...
But is it good to instill terror?
Dealing with fear is one of the fundamentals
of the behavior of all living things.
A show of strength causes
the enemy to be afraid,
but brings refuge to those who are obedient.
Certainly, that's true, but...
Conclusion: As a countermeasure
against the Hideauze,
a display of force is a valid
means to optimize leadership.
It mobilizes many people
and is connected to the maintenance of a high
degree of community functionality. Plus...
Enough already!
Me too...
Maybe I shouldn't have ever left this cockpit...
Welcome back, Mistress!
Good work!
I'm back, girls.
How was that Pinion guy?
Don't be vulgar.
Oh, my!
Then can we get out?
It's still early for that.
It seems that he is capable in
his own way. On top of that...
...I'm growing weary of
having too much free time.
Awakening process complete.
Communication from Commander Kugel.
How do you feel?
Good.
I'd like to get your help right away.
The Hideauze?
No. It's an awareness program
for the people of this planet.
As you command.
I like that answer.
With your arrival, that
makes two Machine Calibers,
so we're going to carry out a major
awareness strategy I've had in mind for a while.
This is the target.
That's...
...Gargantia!