That's correct, Doma-san.
This formula will show up on the
test, so please remember it.
Umaru-san!
I will not lose to you on
the upcoming midterms!
Shubaphyyn
The one who will get first place
is I, Tachibana Sylphynford!
Tachibana-san, we're in
the middle of class...
Oh, dear. Pardon me.
Menacing
Episode 3   Umaru and Her Student
Maybe it's because of the test next week,
but everyone seems on edge.
Yeah... You're right...
Wh-What's wrong, Ebina-chan?
I'm not feeling very confident
about our next test.
I made so many mistakes on the last one.
I make a lot of mistakes, too.
I even lost my student ID yesterday.
What? Really?
Maybe you just don't do well
under pressure, Ebina-chan.
Just stay calm and you'll do fine.
Y-You think so?
Yeah. So let's both do our best.
Umaru-chan...
If that's what you told her,
you should study, too.
Aw, but that's such a pain.
You sure you should be playing some
war game and not studying for your test?
It's an FPS, Onii-chan!
Well, I guess it's okay.
Even if you don't study,
you always listen in class,
so your grades are good.
Oh, but midterms do have
a lot of trick questions.
It might be hard to get a good
score just by going to class.
But I guess you can't help that if you're
just playing games before the test.
An FPS is not a game!
It's not a game! It's not a game!
This is all your fault, Onii-chan!
The enemy's ridiculously strong!
They're totally going for a headshot!
What? They're not really that strong.
Perhaps you're just weak.
What?!
Umaru-chan...
I'm really not confident about this...
Ebina-chan...
Perhaps you're just weak.
I'm really not confident about this...
You're just weak.
I'm not confident about this.
Onii-chan, help me study!
I-I thought she was a youkai...
Youkai Umaru Nezumi:
A youkai that falls on you in the night and clings.
If you give it snacks, it'll go away.
Umaru
Gimme snacks! Gimme snacks!
I knew this would happen.
Oh, it's fine.
A Few Days Later
Midterm Results
1. Doma Umaru
2. Tachibana Sylphynford
Wow, that's amazing!
Umaru-chan, you're number one again.
Oh, it's just a coincidence.
And the tests were so hard! That's amazing!
Are you going to a good cram school?
More like a home tutor.
Umaru Nezumi
Umaru-chan's so cute...
And she's got a great figure, she's smart...
Midterm Results
1. Doma Umaru
And she's good at sports.
She's pretty much perfect.
Not only that, her family's amazing, too.
Huh?
Apparently, Umaru-chan's dad is the
president of Doma Corporation.
What? That huge company?
Seriously?!
I see...
So that's why she's so graceful.
If she's that perfect,
there can't be anyone who'd hate her.
She's divine, even.
Oh, but there's one person
who seems to hate her.
Huh? Who?
Sylphyn?
Sylphyn just likes attention.
No, I mean... You know,
the other girl in our class.
Oh, yeah. I guess she does stare
at Umaru-chan all the time.
What's wrong?
Menacing
It's Motoba-san.
She's glaring daggers...
Isn't she scary?
Huh?
Motoba-san has such sharp eyes,
and she hardly ever talks.
You never know what she's thinking.
I heard she got in a serious
fight with an older guy, too.
Really?
I wonder if Motoba-san wants
to say something to me.
What? Motoba-san?
You mean Motoba Kirie-chan?
Yeah.
Actually, she seemed
to want to say something
Menacing
right before the test, too.
K-Kirie-chan's been staring at
you for a while, Umaru-chan.
R-Really?
Yeah. Lately, in particular,
she's been doing it every day.
You didn't notice?
No, not at all...
Oh, are you friends with
Motoba-san, Ebina-chan?
No.
But there was one time I invited
her to eat lunch with us.
Kirie-chan.
W-Want to eat lunch together?
With Umaru-san, too?
Y-Yeah. She'll be there, too.
I see...
So after you told her I'd be there...
I don't think that's why.
Huh?
I don't know how to put it,
and everyone's scared of Kirie-chan, but...
I don't think she's scary.
Bye.
See you tomorrow.
I wonder why Motoba-san's been staring at me...
Maybe she's suspicious of me.
If that's the case...
She'd probably be pretty shocked
if she saw me like this.
Derrrp.
Hey! You're not like you are at school!
You tricked me!
Please forgive her!
Now, now. Let's not fight.
Let's get on these and play.
Yahoo!
We're flying!
Oh, crap! There's a new quest out today!
That was close. I almost missed it.
This isn't the time to be
worrying about reality.
The Net! The Net!
You got a giant piece of meat!
Growwwl
I'm hungry.
I wonder when Onii-chan's going to be home.
Oh, that's right. Today's Wednesday,
so he'll be shopping for groceries.
Which means he'll bring home some meat, too.
I wonder if he'll make me steak.
Who's that? A delivery?
Oh, that's right.
Onii-chan went shopping,
so he can't open the door.
Heyo, Onii-chan!
Hey, for dinner tonight...
Oh noes!
S...
So cute.
Huh?
P-Pardon me!
Sh-She hasn't realized it?
I-I ended up letting her in.
I wonder why she came over...
What's up with her?
Um...
I-I'm sorry! I didn't even introduce myself.
M-My name is Motoba Kirie.
Huh? Er, right...
I know that...
U-Um, I apologize in advance
if I'm wrong, but...
A-A-Are you Umaru-san's younger sister?
Younger
sister
I'm her younger sister, Komaru.
I knew it! No wonder you have a
certain elegance, like Umaru-san.
That's not true...
I just created a pretty handy character.
S-So, it appears that Umaru-san
isn't here right now.
Around when will she be home?
Huh? Ah, n-no...
Only Onii-chan and I live here.
Onee-chan doesn't.
I-I see...
Speaking of which, I wonder
how she knew where I lived.
Why did you think Onee-chan
was here, Kirie-chan?
W-Well...
For the past week, I've been
following Umaru-san home.
O-Oh, no! I was supposed
to give you this first,
or I'd seem like some kind of stalker!
Huh? You're not one?
Arayada High School Student ID
Regular Curriculum
Name:       Doma Umaru
Birth date: 9/26
Enrolled:  Heisei Year 27 April 1st
Oh, it's my student ID that I dropped.
U-Um... I picked that up a week ago.
And, um... I couldn't find the
right time to give it back.
Everyone's scared of Kirie-chan, but...
I don't think she's scary.
Kirie-chan.
Thanks!
M...
"M"?
May I call you "Master"?!
M-Master?
Y-Yes! I've just decided that I want
to follow you, Master Komaru!
Master Komaru?
That makes me sound like a comic storyteller.
I'm home.
Oh, Onii-chan.
Is someone over?
Huh? Umaru's wearing her
hood in front of a friend.
Did something happen?
Um... This is Kirie-chan.
We became friends today.
Oh, it's nice to meet you.
Huh?
Sh-She's creepy!
Oh, I get it.
She's so shy, she can only talk to children.
Menacing
That's amazing, Doma. You set a new record.
Kirie-san.
Let us go home together.
Yes.
I shall protect you, Umaru-san.
Huh?
What's the matter, Kirie-chan?
N-N-No, it's nothing, Master.
All right, I'm going to spin a
rare Gatcha, so come watch.
R-Right.
Come on, super ultra rare!
Please! Don't lose to the other users!
I know... Maybe if I talk to Master,
I can be friends with Umaru-san...
Another normal!
U-Um, Master...
U-Um, uh...
W-Well, um...
H-How do I put this...
U-Um, ah...
Never mind...
Huh? Are you sure?
Y-Yes.
It's Motoba-san.
Her eyes are as sharp as ever.
She's so scary, it's hard to approach her.
Oh, there you are.
Motoba-san!
Thank you for always playing
with my little sister!
Motoba-san, want to walk home together?
Y... Y... Yes!
What's the matter, Kirie-chan?
Oh, I always walk home with Ebina-chan.
We're good friends.
Ebina-chan.
Always together.
Friends.
Ebina-chan.
Always together.
U-Um... We've talked to
each other before, right?
Kirie-chan?
Are you all right?
I-I'm this way.
Kirie-chan!
A Later Day
Master.
A... rival I must defeat has appeared.
I wonder what went wrong.
Hey, dinner's ready.
Thanks for dinner!
Thank you very much.
The 100th
Win 1 Million Yen
Guess the Pork Cutlet Sauce!!
What?
Huh? It broke?
Ugh. A power outage?
It was just getting good, too.
The second floor?
What's that noise?
It's coming from the roof.
Wait. What are you going to do?
We're going to check it out, of course.
That scared me.
Don't scare me like tha—
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Umaru, you sure you don't
want to turn on the lights?
Are you scared, Onii-chan?
Ju-Oun
No. My eyes hurt.
Hey!
This totally ruins the feel of the movie!
Well, I guess that's fine.
It's not that scary.
Huh? Were you always okay with scary movies?
Yeah! I'm not scared of ghosts at all!
Even if a ghost did appear,
I'd take care of them with
my footwork, like that!
Like that!
Footwork?
End
See? It wasn't that scary.
But I heard the sequel's really
good, so let's watch it.
Actually, I've got to go shopping.
You can watch it by yourself.
By myself?!
I guess it can't be helped.
I'll wait until you get back.
Onii-chan?
I guess it can't be him. He just left...
What's that noise?
I-It's my imagination. Just my imagination.
I know!
I'll watch some funny video, or something.
A p-power outage?
Umaru!
Onii-chan!
I knew it! It's soaked!
Umaru!
At least bring in the
laundry at times like this.
It can't be... Someone is...
The only person who could
do this is Yashichi-san...
I thought you weren't scared.
I-I'm not!
Next Time
Episode 4       Umaru and Her Rival
Kirie, well done. You've surpassed me.
I've nothing more to teach you. Flump.
Master! Please open your eyes! Master!
Um, was that all right?
Yeah! Playing master and student is fun!