There is nothing to debate!
I merely punished them for their folly!
You wolf in sheep's clothing!
Go back to hell!
And now, having killed me,
you and I are the same.
May you burn
with the rest of the criminals.
I must live with my sin now.
For the rest of my life!
Yesterday's play was so good.
You should have come, Violet.
If you mean Red Devil,
I am reading the play now.
I'm so jealous.
I would have loved to scribe
for Oscar Webster.
It means you get to read
his new work first, doesn't it?
It'll be his first new work in a while
when he finishes.
"Ah, I must live with my sin now.
For the rest of my life."
Here are the letter requests.
This many?
There have been more requests for Violet
since the published love letters.
Hey.
Did you talk to her about her major?
No.
I only ask because she seems
to be lost in her thoughts lately.
GENETRIX
ROSWELL REGION
Who is it?
The Auto Memory Doll service.
What's that?
It is a pleasure to meet you.
I will travel anywhere
to meet your request.
Auto Memory Doll
Violet Evergarden at your service.
There was a girl standing there.
She had the same hair color
as the girl I wanted to see again.
I can't even say her name
because it makes me so sad.
What a surprise.
I wasn't expecting such a child.
If I am not to your liking,
I can arrange for another Doll.
No, as long as you can type.
My health hasn't been the best.
I am terribly sorry,
but I ask that you refrain from alcohol
while we work.
I can't write unless I drink!
I will be the one writing.
Then let's start working tomorrow.
You're being a little difficult.
-Will we be writing in this room?
-Either here or the terrace.
There is a study,
but it's a little too cramped.
In that case...
-What happened to your hand?
-I lost it in the war.
However, it will not affect my work.
Sir.
I have cleaned the area
for a better writing environment.
I brought my own typewriter.
Do you have any typing paper?
No. They sell it at the store by the port.
Go buy some.
And dinner, too, while you're at it.
I want carbonara.
Sir.
I am a scribe, not a maid.
You're being difficult.
I've got all the ingredients
you need here.
Thank you very much.
What's wrong? Is there something on it?
No, I was just wondering
how I am supposed to cook this.
You crack the egg and separate the yolk.
Yolk?
What are you doing?
I am trying my hand at cooking.
Well, it's pretty good for your first try.
-Are you not having any?
-I will have some later.
I see.
What are you doing?
Where's the alcohol that was here?
I hid it.
They will hinder the writing process.
And also, it is not good for your health.
I will keep them in my possession for now.
Next is Olive's line.
"We must cross this valley of fire
in order to get the sword
to slay the monster."
Stage direction. "Enter a water spirit."
The spirit's line.
"I will extinguish this fire for you.
Then you will be able
to cross this valley."
So, they will be able to cross it?
Thank goodness.
Stage directions.
"The burning fire is extinguished."
How will it be extinguished?
If they pull in the red cloth
that is waving around on the stage,
it will look like it's been put out.
I see. Understood.
So, what do you think?
Is it good?
How do I put this?
Yes?
I feel like I'm going through
the experience
even though it never really happened.
I find myself feeling
much like this girl, Olive.
Feeling happy, and feeling sad.
Feeling uncertain.
Why is that?
That's because you are feeling
what the protagonist Olive is feeling.
You feel empathy towards Olive.
I'm relieved that you feel that way.
This is my first time
writing a children's play.
Will Olive be able
to cross the valley of fire,
find the sword,
and slay the monster after this?
Yes, but in the process, she loses
her power to speak with the spirits.
Oh, no.
Then how will she return home?
She already lost her boat.
I haven't come up with that yet.
You must.
You have to,
or she can't return to her father
who is waiting for her.
Have you come up with an idea?
The weather is nice today.
No, it's too good.
Sir.
What is this?
Oh, it's just a parasol.
Why do you ask?
It's a really beautiful parasol.
I need...
a little break.
One day...
I promise to show you one day.
Stop!
Please, stop!
I apologize.
-I shouldn't have...
-That's enough!
That's enough.
Go home.
Then the play will not be completed.
Olive's story will never be completed.
Sir, is there something
you're hiding from me?
I don't have the ability
to sense those emotions.
I apologize.
I can't write anything anymore.
But I can't let it end like this.
So, that's why
I thought I would finish
the story I told Olivia.
Olivia?
Yes.
My daughter.
I moved here with my daughter
after I lost my wife to an illness.
This used to be our summer home.
I think she was sad not having a mother.
But...
But she never showed it.
Rather, she always helped me
so I could focus on my work.
My daughter's favorite things
were a frilled parasol
and water birds.
Wow.
I'm so jealous.
I want to try crossing this lake, too.
Do you think I could walk on those leaves?
Maybe if you let the wind carry you
with your parasol.
Olivia!
I'm okay.
I'm going to walk across this lake.
I promise to show you one day.
Okay, Dad?
And then...
after arguing with the doctors,
I decided to bring her back here
to spend what time she had left.
It was good to see her smile again.
Our days were quiet and warm.
But...
my only hope...
Why does God continue to take away
what's most precious to me?
Parting with someone
who is important to you...
Never being able to see them again...
I never knew it was so sad...
and painful.
I'm sorry for earlier.
No, you are the one in pain.
I apologize for being the one
to lose composure.
I will finish it.
Olive's story.
The girl will reach her home
and reunite with her father.
No matter how difficult the adventure,
she will get a happy ending.
Both the protagonist and audience
will be happy.
I will make it happen.
The monster falls.
Olive.
"We finally slayed the monster."
Water spirit.
"You did well."
Wind spirit.
"We must return to the spirit realm."
Fire spirit. "This is goodbye."
Olive stands frozen.
Now, how do we get Olive home
from here?
Since her boat sank,
will she take a plane?
Something a little more imaginative.
She could fly home if she were a bird.
-What about flying with a parasol?
-You cannot fly with a parasol.
But you can!
The wind spirit appears before her
one last time and says,
"Olive, open your parasol."
Could you try opening the parasol for me?
"That parasol is your wings.
You'll be carried away
if you fly too high.
So, step on the ocean's waves,
the river's rocks,
and the fallen leaves on the lake."
That's a wonderful idea.
Right? After returning home,
Olive reunites with her father.
And the first thing she says when they're
reunited after crossing the ocean is...
What should it be?
"I'm home."
No, "Father?"
Do you have writer's block again?
Could you walk towards me from over there?
I'd like to visualize it.
I can do that.
Across the fallen leaves on the lake
if you can.
Understood.
No, that last bit was just...
I'm so jealous.
I want to try crossing this lake, too.
Do you think I could walk on those leaves?
One day...
I promise to show you one day.
Okay, Dad?
How I wish I could hear you call me that
a thousand times more.
I wish...
you didn't have to die.
If only you could have lived...
grown up...
How I wished that for you.
Did you see that?
I believe I made three whole steps.
Sir?
What is the matter?
Are you feeling ill?
After granting me this miracle,
I told her,
"I don't believe there is a God,
but if there were, it would be you."
Are you sure I can have this parasol?
Yes.
-I thought I could fly a little further.
-You went far enough.
You were able to fulfill
Olivia's "one day" wish.
One day?
Farewell.
Thank you for using
our Auto Memory Doll service.
No, thank you.
Violet Evergarden.
With the very hand
that took the lives of so many,
you write letters
that bring people together?
You don't realize that
your body is on fire and burning up
because of the things that you did.
-I'm not...
-You are burning.
You'll understand what I said someday.
And then you'll realize for the first time
that you have many burns.
Major.
Live.
Am I allowed?
Be free.
I was used as a weapon to kill people.
Do I deserve to live?
I've probably taken away
so many "one day" wishes.
And those people
most likely had loved ones.
I'm not burning.
I am.
The fire is spreading across my body
from all the things I've done.
I am on fire.
Oh?
If it isn't you, Violet!
Madam.
Please forgive me
for being disrespectful before.
I sincerely apologize
for hurting your feelings.
Violet, you don't have to apologize
for that. Please stop bowing.
I'm so thankful
to see how far you've come.
I am sure Gilbert can rest in peace, too.
Rest in peace?
You said he was alive!
The major is safe, right?
That's...
He's alive, right?
I'm sorry. I just couldn't
bring myself to tell you.
After the Final Battle of Intense,
you were found alone on the ground
under a church.
Most likely, he pushed you away
right before it was bombarded.
While we didn't find his body,
we did find his ID tag under the debris.
-And so, he was deemed missing in action.
-So, we do not know.
-But given the situation...
-I'm sure the major is alive.
-Violet...
-He's alive!
Violet, please understand,
he's already...
I won't. I don't understand.
How could I be the only one to survive?
The major was there with me.
And he...
Violet, you have to accept it,
even if it's difficult.
Violet!
Subtitle translation by
Zensho Yamamoto