I don't regret anything at all! I can't!
Because...
...what I did was definitely not wrong!
It's strange.
Even after...
so much time has passed,
something can save you,
coming in like a storm
from a completely different direction.
Hina...
Thank you.
You are...
my lifesaver.
I promise.
I'll stay with you.
Rei...
Even if it takes the rest of my life,
I will pay you back.
Small World
Sniff-sniff.
Here's dessert!
It's the cherries that Kiriyama brought over.
Cherries!
Thank you, Kiriyama.
NOM NOM
Delicious!
They smell sour-meow.
I'm not crazy about fruit.
Huh? Are you sleepy, Momo?
Maybe we should take a bath.
Although it's a bit early...
So, Hina, do you want to try playing? Shogi.
SHAKE
W-Will you go easy on me?
Yes, yes, of course!
Then would you take it upstairs?
I wanna play some more...
I'm going to give Momo her bath.
*Kawamoto House's
bath changing room
is the living room.
I wanna play with Rei.
Kiriyama.
Are you sure that's all you need?
HINA
KIRIYAMA
Yeah.
Are you positive? Just this much?
All right!
Apparently the first time in Hina's room...
Then I might be able to win!
- Then let's get started.
- Okay.
Why aren't I going first?
I thought you were going easy on me.
There's a rule that with handicap shogi,
the player who's short of pieces goes first.
What? Oh, but... okay. Go ahead.
FIVE MINUTES LATER
I-I lost.
GLOOM
One more! One more time!
Hey, yo, pineapple, lalala,
a strange magical fruit...
I know! I'll just play with two pieces,
the king and a gold general!
Damn it!
Why am I so bad at this?
Oh. You're taking my Pawn at 5-5?
Good one.
If anything, the chairman is skilled at making
his opponents look good and enjoy themselves.
Okay, here's a hint.
With strong pieces, you...
B-Back off and then strike!
Correct.
Mr. Yokomizo takes the time to amuse
and teach even oddball players. It's great.
It's about communication, Kiriyama.
Imagine what your opponent is thinking
and what they want to do.
Then get close to their feelings.
In the waiting room
of his first shogi event
Look at your opponent closely.
Well, calm down, and let's take it easy.
Okay.
STARE
Thanks, Rei.
I think I'm starting to get the hang of it,
so I should be okay for the next one.
I'm no match for her!
This middle school student is consoling me again!
Okay, one more time.
What's the point of coming here to console her
if she's the one consoling you, Rei Kiriyama?
And suddenly I felt a lump in my throat.
Over the years, how often has this girl smiled
and been considerate
of other people's feelings like this?
Hina.
Listen...
Will you tell me?
A little bit at a time is fine.
About what's happening at school...
Right now, I guess this is what it's like.
Like everyone is looking from afar.
Hina thought and thought,
slowly sharing bits and pieces with me.
Our groups are set up by order of name,
but at lunch, I can tell
that everyone gets so stiff.
They hardly ever look at me.
It's like only my group is at a wake.
And then the silence is suddenly broken by
the loud laughter of the girls who bullied Chiho.
Their loud, loud voices...
Their laughter...
It's like there's an invisible hierarchy
within our class.
And your ranking decides
how loud you can laugh
or how much freedom
you're allowed in the classroom.
That's the atmosphere of Hina's class.
I'm sure this is a story that everyone
has experienced at one time or another.
There shouldn't even be such a thing.
But... But there is.
It's been there all the time.
Ever since elementary school...
Hey, Kiriyama, what is that?
That atmosphere...
Who's cool? Who's not cool?
When and how is that decided?
Who decides it?
Even though we're all just
the same middle school students.
the same human beings.
SILENCE
DISTANCE
Is that what she really said?
What a loser!
CACKLE CACKLE HAHAHA
CACKLE CACKLE CACKLE
CHEW CHEW
MUNCH MUNCH
I'm-telling-you
- Isn't that nuts?
- Totally!
Thank you for the meal.
That's hilarious!
GLOOMY
Th-This feels so awkward.
Is Kawamoto here?
T-Takahashi?
STING STING STING
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
No way. I totally tossed that lightly.
I heard from Kiriyama.
At lunch time...
if things get difficult, let's just play catch.
If you want more people,
I could call my baseball team buddies to join in.
They're already staring.
A girl!
Damn you, Takahashi!
This is outrageous!
Kiriyama came over to my house yesterday
to coach us while playing.
Oh, I see. Now I've got it.
For the Silver at 4-3, you go with Pawn at 3-4.
Professional shogi players are so amazing.
That's why you're a professional.
Yeah. I see.
Well, it's a surprise tactic.
Dad and Grandpa were delighted.
Grandpa's been staying in bed recently,
but he was up and about for this.
Invite me over again for curry.
With the fried chicken.
Last time Dad and Grandpa were hogging
Kiriyama, so I couldn't really to talk to him.
Sure.
That hurts!
That can't hurt.
Small World
Letter
Thank you.
Oh, thank you.
Good game, Kiriyama 5th-Dan.
Thank you.
CLENCH
That's four wins!
Yes!
Just one more win and I'll be
in the Kishousen preliminary semifinals!
Things are looking up this month!
At the moment, I've got two consecutive wins
for rank-deciding matches.
I'm still in the running for Kishousen,
the Lion King Tournament,
and the Newcomer Tournament.
I'd like to win the Lion King Tournament.
If I can win in group five
and participate in the challenger tournament...
...then I'll hit my financial target!
But with the Newcomer Tournament,
prize money aside,
I want to win one more match,
get to the finals, and build up momentum.
All right, I need to practice.
I'm not going to lose!
I will become the Newcomer King!
Good morning.
Good morning!
STOP FLIRTING AROUND, MORON
I couldn't finish eating everything.
Is this what they call a stomach ache?
Why didn't you show up?
T-Takahashi!
Bitch.
Um, thanks, Takahashi.
But today, I...
Uh, I think we were
in the same class first year.
Hey, Takagi. That's you, right?
You want to play catch too?
Here I go! You ready?
You go first, Megu!
No way! I'm scared!
It'll be fine! Go on!
Here I go!
One-two...
Jerk! You suck!
I'm out of here! That guy's insane!
Megu, wait!
Huh? What, you're leaving already?
Hey, what's wrong?
Takahashi...
Y-Yikes.
Takahashi.
They tossed my glove on the ground
and ran off.
The one who changed schools
was Chiho Sakura, right?
During the overnight field trip in second year,
the wind blew my bento box over
and sand got all over my food.
Then she gave me half of her bento.
She smiled and said, "Here."
At the time, I thought that anyone who
shared their own food was a good person.
So let's play catch anytime.
I kind of feel like it's a good idea
to show them that there are allies too.
I see.
But... I'm sorry.
Takahashi is so handsome, huh?
I get it. Now they're envious.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't think that far ahead.
There are bad people-meow.
No good-meow.
Yeah. Bad-meow.
No, Kiriyama! Don't take it like that!
I'm going to keep playing catch.
After all, it's fun.
And Takahashi seems to remember Chiho.
So I can talk about her,
and that makes me really happy.
Nobody talks about Chiho in class anymore,
so it's like she was never there
from the beginning.
One person has gone away.
So why?
Huh? Sorry.
Here. Take this.
Rei, thank you for always listening to me.
You're always asking me what I want to do.
MIDDLE SCHOOL
But I...
I don't know what I want to do...
...so it's frustrating!
What do I want to do?
I want to yell "Idiots!" and punch them!
I want to beat the crap out of them!
I want to do to them what they did to Chiho!
And then I want them to realize what they did!
3-2 SAKURA
But it's too late.
Chiho's already gone!
She sent Chiho a letter,
but never got a response.
Instead, she received a response
Chiho hasn't got back to school, even here.
Right now she's in rehab with a counselor
at a place called "Heart Care Center."
Chiho would like to write to you, but...
from Chiho's mother.
Besides, it's impossible!
Even if I make them apologize...
I don't think Chiho would ever
want to see their faces!
HINATA KAWAMOTO LOVES GUYS
PERVERTED GIRL
BITCH IDIOT
There's one thing that I realized.
I had thought...
...that if things got tough,
you can just get up and leave.
3-2 KAWAMOTO
When someone treats you improperly...
...you don't have to respond in a proper way.
But...
Stand up!
Bow!
HINATA KAWAMOTO LOVES GUYS
PERVERTED GIRL
BITCH IDIOT
Wh—
M-Ms. Kawamoto, what's the meaning of this?
I don't know.
I'm not the one who wrote it.
Chiho Sakura: Absent/Absent/Absent
I think you're misreading it, Ms. Kawamoto.
You shouldn't turn
every situation into a bad one.
It was already written on the board
when I came in this morning.
A-Anyway, let's begin the lesson.
Ms. Kawamoto, please see me
in the faculty room after class.
Come on, concentrate! Stop your whispering!
Let's have a good game.
That's right.
She's not only in pain.
She's angry.
In fact, she's seething
from the pit of her stomach.
Letter
Next Episode Preview
Episode 29
No, don't look at me!
Sis, get me a bath towel!
What should we do?
It's terrible!
Finally! We finally made it to this point!
I'm the only one who can go
from our family.
I bought peaches. Maybe I should've bought
ice cream instead.
ILLUSTRATION:
KOZUE AMANO
Yoohoo, yoohoo, cherries!
Derere, yummy magical fruit!