Kochi kite hayaku! Kochi kite suguni!
こち来て早く! こち来てすぐに!
Hurry over here! Come over here now!
San-nin mou jishitsuwase
三人も実質わせ
We need all three of us!
Jugyou no ato de Sensei ni Bye Bye!
授業の後で先生にバイバイ!
Say "Bye Bye" to the teacher after school!
Taisou fuku wa motte kaeru
体操服はもって帰る
Get my P.E uniform and go home!
Koutei shuugou asobimasuka
校庭集合遊びますか
Wanna play in the school yard?
Demo demo datte iiwake shinai no
でも!でも!だって言い訳しないの
But but I wont make any excuses
Shukudai nante hottoko yo
宿題なんでほっとこうよ
Who cares about homework!
Tetsubou shuugou mawarimasu yo
鉄棒しゅうごう回りますよ
Just swing around the metal bar in the yard.
randoseru wa sou akai tsuyoi
ランドセルはそう！あかい！つよい！
Our bag is all red and mighty!
hitotsu futatsu
一つ！二つ！
One, Two..
mitsu narabete mujubaku naru
三つ並べて矛盾ばくなる！
The three of us make no sense!
houkago wa dashu!
放課後はダシュ!
After school, you dash!
abarete wasurede genki dashite
暴れて忘れで元気出して
Just forget all about it!
Ignored.
Sen Nou!
セン、ノウ！
One, Two!
Oni-san, achira! sono kado magaru
鬼さん、あちら！その角曲がる！
Hey, its over there! Round the corner!
Koutei Dai-shugo!
校庭大しゅご!
Schoolground big parade!
Watashi wa dare deshou?
私はだれでしょう？
Who the hell am I?
Tanoshii de mainichi ookiku nare ba
楽しいで毎日、大きくなれば
If you have fun and grow up everyday.
asobenaino, shiritai, shiranai, shiritai!
遊べないの? 知りたい、知らない、知りたい！
Dont you wanna play? I wanna know, I dunno, but I wanna know!
Tanoshii de mainichi chiisai na koto de!
楽しいで毎日小さいな事で!
Enjoy all the little things everyday.
warai aidara sore wa sore de ureshii
笑い会えたら、それはそれで嬉しい
Just seeing a smile makes me happy!
sore mou kore mou dore mou
それも、これも、どれも！
Like this one, that one, and that one too!
sanningoko setsuwase wow!
三人五個せつわせ！　ＷＯＷ！
Then its the fine whether its three or five!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
There's lots of intruders.
Hey Futaba, did you catch a cold again?
Even though it's already summer.
Satou Shinya
...probably
a role-model student.
This is an experiment!
an experiment?
Yep!
An experiment to see how much cooler it feels to not wear panties in summer.
E-Eh?!
It really works!
Come on and try it, Shin-chan!
A-As if I would do something as stupid as that.
Shin-chan sure is cold.
Geez... that idiot...
Hey Satou.
What's up, Chiba?
You sure get along well with Futaba.
Not really, we've just been friends since we were little.
So... have you seen them?
Seen what?
Futaba's panties.
O-Oi! T-There's no way-y...
What are you doing anyway...
I was just wondering if I could see the heroine's panties in this manga.
Chiba Yuudai
A nice and healthy Boy
Did you get hit on the head?
I'm just kidding.
You shouldn't even bring manga to school in the first place.
I guess it's about time to move on from manga and get my hands on some porn.
That's not allowed, Hitoha-chan...
You can't bring those kinds of books to school.
D-Don't bring that any closer!
What kind of book is it...
A-Amazing...
It's bloody amazing!
What's wrong?
I-It's nothing.
Geez... that Chiba...
Are panties that exciting to look at?
Music Room
Wanna try going without panties?
Chiba and Hitoha...
I wonder where they're going.
Eh? You don't?
I'm begging you!
Please let me have a look!
What do you mean have a look?!
Don't tell me... he's trying to take a look at her panties!
Please! That's all I'm asking.
Nope.
I'm even begging like this!
Just a peek! Just a peek will do!
Nope.
I'll even be your slave for a day!
Tell that to Mit-chan...
Please wait, youngest of the triplets!
Satou... you heard it all?
Chiba, even I feel ashamed now.
Do you really want to see them so badly?!
Damn right I want to see it!
Just having a look will reveal an unimaginable world of fantasy!
Endure!
a world of fantasy?
Just now...
I saw a little bit back in the classroom.
You serious?
Damn, it was beyond imagination.
Eh?! Hitoha's, right?
Yeah.
R-Really...
I guess you really can't judge a book by it's cover.
If she won't let me see it no matter what...
I'll just have to take it by force!
Take them by force?!
Don't do it! It's a crime!
I'll return it afterwards, won't that be fine?
That's not the problem here!
Damn it! I don't want to hear this from a serious and righteous guy!
Oi!
That Chiba went on ahead...
At this rate, he's really going to become a criminal.
What should I do...
Oh...
I can just ask Futaba to bring a pair of her sister's panties.
I brought this many just for you Shin-chan!
Nevermind... that's a bad idea...
If I ask someone like her, it would just make everything worse.
Ah, maybe...
I'll sneak into Hitoha's room and steal some panties...
W-Wait, then I'd be the criminal!
Youngest of the triplets...
Satou!
Catch her for me!
Oi, snap out of it, Chiba!
Listen, Chiba...
I won't let you get any further...
Alright! Satou...
Let me have a look at it!
Let me see your thing...
My... my what?
My thing?!
Hurry up and show it to me!
Even though I'm a guy?!
Let me take a look at the inside!
The inside?!
Now!
Stop it! Don't touch me!
Just let me see it; it's not like you have anything to lose!
The real one's over here.
I'll take responsibility!
It's not good for you!
Hey, Hitoha-chan.
Do you always go home by yourself?
Yeah.
Where's Mitsuba-chan and Futaba-chan?
I don't know...
It's been quite dangerous lately...
I'll be fine.
But... Hitoha-chan's really cute and all...
Pedophile...
I'm not!
Try talking to those girls over there.
Impossible.
Just say "Let's go home together"...
I don't wanna. Are you trying to get me killed, sensei?
You're exaggerating things!
Yabe-cchi.
Bye bye!
Give it a go.
Hey...
Eeeks!
She went "Eeeks!"
W-What's up?
I failed...
Let's forget about it...
H-Hey, b-be careful on your way home.
Eh... is something going to happen...?
Let's hurry home before the sun goes down!
I just wanted to say "Take care on your way home"...
See! It didn't work!
Don't blame it on me!
Relax a bit and put on a smile, okay?
It sure is a pain to be on clean-up duty.
The little sister?
Rehearsing.
She's talking to someone... or something...
Ah, it's a mosquito.
She's fighting something invisible...
Run away.
Run away!
It's going to suck on you...
It's going to suck you dry!
What are you going to suck on...?
You did it, Hitoha-chan!
We're actually going home together...
is it really all thanks to the practice?
Hey, are you really that sort of person?
What sort?
Is she talking about the mosquito earlier?
Well, I guess they do like to target me.
They target you?... so it's true after all.
It must be really troublesome.
Not really...
Well, there are a lot of them in summer.
Oh that's right... there's the Obon in summer.
Ah, my name is Matsuoka Sakiko by the way.
I know.
Oh right, we're classmates after all.
I don't even know her first name...
Maybe I should talk about something...
You know, I've always...
...liked you!
So I'm really happy that we got to go home together today.
The little sister... she really can see spirits and ghosts!
D-Does this mean...
Do you think that this is wrong?
N-Not really...
I've never even talked to her before!
I get really excited when I see scary things...
I research them by watching videos at night.
Occult Special!
Tonight we'll show you a world
that no one else has seen before!
Videos in the middle of the night?!
Onee-sama!
You're so cute!
But from now on...
There are a lot of techniques...
that I...
want
to learn
from
you.
What's wrong?
You've been acting a little strange.
Hey...
I wonder if Hitoha-chan's alright...
and is she getting along well with Matsuoka-san?
Take that! Stop possessing her!
Disperse, evil spirit!
W-What are you doing?
Get out of the way!
We're in the middle of a ritual!
You're still not going to show yourself?! You evil spirit!
Take that!
Take that, take that!
I'm to blame for all this...
It's this annoying season again.
Hey, summer is the most spiritual season, right?
Occult-Loving Girl
Matsuoka Sakiko
It's a busy season for a smart and beautiful exorcist like you, right?
The evil spirits that keep appearing...
It sure is gloomy.
This girl... is still misunderstanding something.
Do your best, little sis!
I'm not really that...
Geez, you don't have to be so modest!
Don't worry! You really are beautiful.
I'm not talking about that...
Oh yeah, the pool is opening tomorrow.
I can't wait!
Pool... swimming...
What a meaningless thing for humans to do.
Pool... who cares about the pool!
The pool...
Pool? What's wrong with the pool?
Could it be... that there's something at the pool?!
Hey sis, do you want to sneak into the pool tonight to prepare for tomorrow's opening?
Let's do our best for the opening!
I'll do my best to support you!
This is how you do the breaststroke.
That's the way, keep going!
Matsuoka-san...
Without further ado,
it's time to start the exorcism!
Exorcism?!
Just what I'd expect from you sis...
You sensed evil spirits from that far away!
What on earth am I doing here...
I even wore my swimwear underneath my clothes.
Eh? What's that?
Oh crap.
It's equipment for the exorcism, isn't it?
W-Wait!
You use it like this, right?
Give it back!
Hey, where are you going?
What about the exorcism?
I didn't want it to be like this, but...
Don't get involved with me anymore.
Sis, does that mean...
I'm still a novice at this.
It'd be better if you didn't get involved in this other world.
How modest and kind of her!
I-I made her cry.
Don't worry, I'll be fine!
I came prepared for this!
See!
I've set inscriptions on my whole body to protect myself from spirits!
Oh.
My.
God.
Oh, did you get a hold of it already?
You're the one that needs to get a hold of yourself...
I'm not tired yet, so don't worry!
I'm still full of energy!
Hey...
I think there's really something wrong with you...
Something wrong with me?
Possessed
You mean something possessed me?
So you have the power to tell something like that too!
Don't come any closer to me!
Sis!
Oh I see, she's found the evil spirit already!
That's why she told me to stay away!
H-Help me...
W-What a fierce battle!
Evil spirit, begone!
Go get 'em sis!
N-No, come h-help me...
I'll join in the fight too!
Namu Amida Batsuji!
Hand me that thing!
That thing? Oh you mean...
Swimming boa-
You wanted this right?
Not that!
This one?
You want this?
I guess that's it for me.
I'm going to curse you Matsuokas forever.
Curse you...
Curse you all!
What are you girls doing here?
Thanks for your work, did you purify the evil spirit?
Evil spirit?
Wasn't she just drowning?
No way, she's not that kind of pathetic person!
Right, sis?
It was a formidable opponent!
See?
Damn it, I'm really going to curse you forever!
Matsuoka-san?!
I-I wrote it with a oil-based marker...
Gross!
What was she thinking?!
There was an evil spirit in this pool!
It was all for the sake of purification!
S-Stay away!
It's working...
my curse is working.
I'm not going to run away!
Sis, tell them what happened!
G-Guys!
Girls' changing room
That was really fun!
After all that, it'd be fine if I don't take a bath today.
It's not fine at all!
Huh?
Those girls... they wore their swimwear to school and forgot to bring their panties.
Kinda suspicious.
Father of the triplets
Marui Soujirou
Eh?! All three pairs of your panties got stolen?!
Geez, how vulgar.
Well, since my panties would sell for a high price, I can't really blame them.
But that only applies for my pair!
You know, they probably weren't stolen...
Did you search thoroughly?
Of course I did, I searched very  throughly.
Where the hell were you searching?!
If they really were stolen, the culprit would wear them, right?
Why are you asking me?!
This is their pool right...
Mit-chan...
Isn't it strange how only the triplet's panties were stolen?
I guess you're right, if it was only my pair...
No, like I said...
Ah! Maybe three of them as a set will sell for more!
One pair
100 Yen
Three pairs set
500 Yen
So that's why!
That's too cheap!
They're not trading cards you know...
Oh it's too cheap?
I wonder what he's doing over there...
Well, I guess I'll help you guys find them too.
So, what kind of panties did you girls wear today?
Umm...
I don't remember...
Like I said, we didn't-
That bastard!
What color panties did you girls wear today?!
What are you doing to my daughters?!
Isn't there...
Isn't there an entrance somewhere?!
That person is trying to sneak into the school!
Hello?
What's wrong?
They can't find their panties...
Alright everyone, let's help find them.
I can't just tell them that we forgot to bring them, now that everyone's involved...
I see now.
The culprit is...
Yabe-cchi!
I've always knew that you were giving me weird looks!
Futaba, I'm sure he's wearing three layers underneath those shorts!
No!
I guess I have to climb over!
Take a good look!
Where am I hiding them?!
That bastard!
Just you wait!
Take a good look at my panties! Take a good look!
I-It's the culprit!
Daddy...
Papa...
You pervert!
T-That's my line!
A-Are you guys alright?
Don't get any closer to those girls!
H-Here, you girls forgot these, right?
You finally realized...
Hey, don't tell me you didn't bring them in the first place...
H-Here...
Don't touch me, you panty-thief!
What are you saying...
Give it up, you trespasser!
You've got it all wrong! I just brought them their panties!
Hurry up and take him away; he's disgusting.
Oi! You three!
I wanna go and have a look!
You shouldn't approach the trespasser.
W-Wait a second! Hey!
Ah, they left.
Why?!
We already apologized didn't we?!
I'm sorry...
We're sorry!
Geez.
Kotei ni yuuhi ga ochite
校庭に夕日が落ちて
The sunset reflected on the schoolgrounds.
te wo futte ie ni kaeru
手を振っていえに帰る
Let's hold hands and go home.
bedo no naka de mata konya
べドの中でまた今夜
Laying in my bed tonight.
kyou no kimi ni aitetara ii na
今日の君に会えたらいいな
It would be nice if I could meet you again.
ikou! Nemurou!
行こう！眠ろう！
Let's go! Let's sleep!
Asa made matte nai
朝まで待ってない！
I can't wait till morning!
totemo suteki sa
とても素敵さ
It's really wonderful,
sora motomeru no sa
空求めるのさ
just wishing upon the sky.
kimi to te wo tsunai de
君と手をつないで
Just holding hands with you,
Mune ga itaku nata
胸が痛くなた
makes my heart beat.
Yume no naka demo
夢の中でも
Even though it's only a dream,
Yume iro no koi
夢色の恋
it sure is a lovely dream.
Next time, it's a story packed with boobies and panties, Shin-chan!
Why are you telling that to me?!
I'll take care of all the boobies, so I'll leave the panties to you, Shin-chan!
Episode 4
Kids, panties, and milk!
Like I said, why does it have to be me?!