This doesn't seem to be it either, does it?
We still have a long way to go.
We're just gonna have to
cross them all off, one by one.
You're right. Okay, then!
Absolutely no pushing
yourself too hard.
No, no!
This is nothing, I promise!
Ayato-senpai and Julis
should be battling about now.
I've got to give it my all, too!
Yeah, that's the spirit.
Scrambling
Sorry to keep you waiting, everybody!
There are now only two more matches
left in the Phoenix Festa!
AYATO AMAGIRI
JULIS-ALEXIA VON RIESSFELD
ERNESTA KUHNE
CAMILLA PARETO
DOROTEO LEMUS
ELLIOTT FORSTER
Who will vie for supremacy
against Arlequint in tomorrow's final?
Will it be Seidoukan
or will it be Galahadworth?
I thought I was used to this
feeling of powerlessness.
But I just can't take it this time.
For now, let's just have faith in Saya
and Kirin, and focus on our match.
Right... I hear you.
Now, then, the Galahadworth team...
First... ranked #12
despite being in junior high!
The young prodigy,
also known as Claimh Solais...
Elliott Forster!
His teammate is Rank #11,
Doroteo Lemus, a.k.a. Brightwen!
This is his third Festa.
He's a seasoned veteran!
I'd prefer to get this match
out of the way,
but since we're up against Galahadworth's
True Knights, that's not happening.
Not only that, but this time
you can't even use the Ser=Versta.
Well, about that...
I'll figure something out.
All right, then, I'm leaving Forster to you.
I'll take on Lemus!
Roger that.
Phoenix Festa Semifinal Match #2!
Battle start!
Burst into bloom, Amaryllis!
Nice to meet you, too...
Glühen Rose.
Well, well!
Where did this armor come from?
Right, it was generated
by Lemus's powers.
It's highly protective,
and it's also a headache because it repairs
itself as soon as you destroy it.
I see!
Not to mention, the armor's even
protecting the school badge, too!
So you're going all-out from the start.
I'm up against the Glühen Rose herself.
Why wouldn't I be?
Let's go!
Julis...
I thought I was your opponent.
Ayato Amagiri...
I've been looking forward
to battling you.
I wish you wouldn't keep me waiting.
Sorry about that.
By the way, where's your Ser=Versta?
I hope you're not holding back on me.
Unfortunately, something came up,
and I can't use it right now.
Oh, well, whatever.
Let me see those sword skills
the student council president's mentioned!
Huh? That's weird!
I've never shown that move
in this tournament before.
I see...
So you're skilled at counterattacking.
That first strike was a decoy, huh?
Well, I guess I'd have to say that it was.
But be warned
that counterattacks aren't...
...my only weapons!
So you're just as good
as you say you are.
Based on talent alone,
you might be a match for Kirin.
That goes without saying!
But that sword of yours is...
still too light!
Not in terms of power, but resolve!
As if I'd let you!
Amagiri Shinmei Style...
Twin Demon Bees!
AMAGIRI SHINMEI STYLE
TWIN DEMON BEES
Elliott Forster... badge broken!
No way...
Burst into bloom...
Primrose!
Riessfeld can only go on the defensive
against Doroteo's lance charge!
We really should be astounded
by Doroteo's powers.
Creating such a complex image
and moving it so smoothly...
Come out, Loropetalum!
Burst into bloom, Anthurium!
Fine, I wouldn't have it any other way.
Burst into bloom...
Longiflorum!
Looks like my lance got to you first.
Whoa, whoa!
What are we supposed to make of this?
Most likely, though Lemus's armor
was able to protect him from the flames,
it couldn't block their heat, I guess.
Meaning that he's been fighting
while being roasted?
Seriously...
What a reckless man you are!
Well, since I wanted to end this quickly...
Even so, charging right into a wall
of flames is going too far.
I just took a gamble and lost.
It can't be helped.
Come on,
get it over with, will you?
Doroteo Lemus... badge broken!
Winners, Ayato Amagiri
and Julis-Alexia von Riessfeld!
Another dead end.
AYATO AMAGIRI
Ayato...
Saya, how's it going over there?
Sorry. We still don't have
any real clues.
I see. We're going to get ready
to head over as soon as we can.
Meaning... it's over already?
Yeah, thanks to you guys,
we made it to the final. Thanks!
All right, can you send me that map?
Gotcha.
I'm so glad to hear that our senpais
were able to advance!
In Ayato's case, that's a given.
So next is the final?
I think it's going to be tough
for even Ayato
to beat those two
without the Ser=Versta.
You're probably right.
We've got to find Flora
before the final starts.
Saya?
It's so frustrating.
Yes.
Let's go. There's still something
we can do right now.
Right!
Saya and Kirin say they still don't have
anything to go on.
Is that right?
TODAY'S MATCH HAS FINISHED
FINAL MATCH WILL START AT NOON TOMORROW
Tomorrow's final starts at noon,
so that gives us
another 18 hours, huh?
If we factor in the inspection
before the match...
that gives us even less time.
Come on, let's join the search!
Yo! Congrats on making the final...
Wait, huh?
Hey, what's going on?
What's with the gloomy vibe?
Uh... There's a reason for that, see?
If there's anything I can do,
I'll be happy to help.
Actually...
I see...
Just as the president suspects,
it's probably a sure bet
that Dirk Eberwein's behind all this.
Do you know a lot
about Grimalkin, Yabuki?
Nope.
When it comes to secrecy,
they're better than all the other academies'
intelligence-gathering organizations.
I see...
I'd rather not get mixed up
with those guys.
But this is a special case,
and if you're only out to find
this Flora kid, I'll help you out.
Sure, of course that'll be enough.
I'd almost rather
you didn't have a hand in this.
Thanks for that... at least,
that's what I'd normally say,
but as a lightweight regular student,
I'd rather have
a little more insurance.
Let's see, that guy's number...
I know I saved it in here.
I don't care, but if it's going to take long,
we're going to go on ahead!
Sure. Well, I'm going to do
everything I can,
but don't count on me too much!
I see.
Julis, I'd like to investigate
another avenue myself.
Another avenue?
Fine by me...
but I think you'd be wasting
your time asking.
I know it's a long shot, but I'd like to ask
just for the sake of asking.
Who knows, we might get
some kind of clue out of it.
So you came.
Hey, don't turn around.
Fine. But you didn't have to
go out of your way to meet me here.
Idiot!
No way could we have
discussed that over a call!
Sorry.
Never mind.
So let me get straight to the point.
There's nothing I can tell you.
I see.
Don't get the wrong idea, now.
It's not like they asked me to be quiet.
- Actually, it's the opposite.
- Opposite?
You don't really think the Tyrant wouldn't
guess you'd contact me, do you?
And yet, I haven't received
any kind of memo.
Basically, the information I have
wouldn't do you any good...
and he knows it.
Gotcha.
Sorry... I shouldn't have bothered you.
Hold up, Amagiri.
It's true that I have no information.
But I can still speculate, at least.
Speculate?
You said you've narrowed your search
to the Redevelopment District, right?
Yeah. What about it?
Normally, you'd probably be right.
But since we're talking
about a kidnapping, I wouldn't bet on it.
What do you mean?
If I'm not mistaken,
that place is a hotbed for criminals.
That's why the Police Unit is always
coming around to patrol the area.
It's not a good place
for crimes like kidnapping
where you need to lay low long-term.
Basically, Grimalkin
is all about working solo,
so they want to avoid the hassle
of dodging an investigation.
If that's the case,
where would she be?
Who knows?
But the place that would
give you guys the most trouble?
My guess would be Rotlicht.
Why do you say that?
In the Redevelopment District,
you could search as you wish,
but in Rotlicht, both legal
and illegal shops are clustered together.
You couldn't just barge
into one of those places, could you?
But then someone would
have to be in on it with Grimalkin,
since they work solo, right?
Well, yeah, since money talks
in that place as long as you pay up.
Hey, hey, Camilla!
How about snapping
out of that bad mood?
We might've lost instead
if we hadn't used you-know-what.
You knew that yourself
from the start, didn't you?
You and I are striving
for different things, Camilla.
Your final goal is "Ultimate Universality."
In other words, a weapon
that can be wielded by anyone...
By any kind of person at all, right?
That's right.
But no such weapon exists in this world.
So we're going to create beings
that can wield weapons, puppets,
that humans will only
have to issue orders to.
Such puppets have no need
for a will of their own.
Actually, they shouldn't
have a will, right?
Right.
So what I want is to produce autonomous
puppets that can cry, laugh and grow.
For them to gain the same rights
as humans one day, that's my goal.
Do you remember
the day we first met?
Of course. How could I ever forget
anything with that degree of impact?
Good point.
When my parents' workplace was attacked
by anti-government forces...
The guards were decimated
in the blink of an eye.
My parents tried to fight back,
but there was no way civilians could
hold their own against trained warriors.
Half of my body is the body
of a puppet you made for me.
And so I swore to you
that I'd give you half of my life.
That it was yours.
Yep, you gave it to me, all right!
So... I have no intention
of criticizing your dream.
I admit that we have different goals,
but that's another story!
Then why are you so mad?
This is my rage as an engineer!
That was too dangerous
to put into practice!
But if we'd lost then,
it would've been game over for us!
You must have
enough results by now!
My only goal is to win it all!
And then I'm going to have AR-D
and RM-C accepted as students here!
If that happens, see, people will embrace
autonomous puppets, more and more!
Seriously...
Master...
I am very sorry to trouble you,
but there's something
I'd like you to do for me.
Huh? What's up?
I was wondering if you could possibly
leave this scar carved into my face, as it is.
Sure, that's not a problem...
But why would you ask for that?
Needless to say,
as proof that I fought this battle.
You mean it's a badge of victory?
No, nothing as grand as that...
I have learned various things
through this particular battle.
What I perceived after exposing
my own imperfections...
this wasn't purely
a matter of learning data,
but what humans call...
That's right... growth!
I believe I achieved actual growth!
And I want to leave behind proof of that.
Prodigious!
Don't tell me he's aware
of his own growth?
Master, I, too,
have a favor to ask of you.
Hey... you, too, RM-C?
When I transfer limit control to AR-D...
Yes, yes...
It would help if you could
narrow the range a bit more
when my external armor is detached,
or adjust it somehow.
As it's humiliating...
The thing is,
since there are technical issues, see...
I don't think it can be done
in time for tomorrow.
Understood, Master.
I guess we can thank Saya Sasamiya
and Kirin Toudou for this, too, huh?
It would be great to see this
again during the final, too.
Who knows what's going to happen?
What am I gonna do now?
Not a single clue
after all this asking around, huh?
I guess I'll have a look
further down there.
Hey, you there!
It's you, right?
The bastard who's been sniffing
around here for some reason?
No, no, I'm just looking
for someone, that's all.
Then how about you come with us?
Sorry, but I really don't have the time.
Come back here, you!
That bastard! Where the hell did he go?
If I go into the alley,
I'll only get cornered.
Guess I'll head back out for now, and—
What should I do?
I can't cause a commotion now
and risk getting noticed by the perpetrator.
Hey, you...
Is someone chasing you, by any chance?
If you're in trouble, I can help you!
Episode 19
Battle Song
What did you think of that, Ayato?
My singing...
It's not half bad, wouldn't you say?