It's here!
It's here! Here! Here! Here! Here!
It's here! Here! Here!
So much for my day off...
I'm beat after spending the
whole day baby-sitting!
Did you have fun baby-sitting?
No, not at all!
It wasn't the least bit fun.
I'm exhausted as well.
Yeah. Kei, didn't you
two have work lined up?
Next time you and Izuru can do it!
Police Chief for 1 Day
You can be chiefs for a day,
play with kids,
and get your pictures
taken in swim trunks!
Not another word!
Izuru, what were you up to?
I was-
It's here! It's here! It's here!
Oh, Suruga.
Tell us later.
IT'S HERE!
What is?
The new one!
New dried sea-ear wrapped around squid?
NO! It's a new AHSMB!
It's the new AHSMB model!
"The Aloof Ace"
Ain't it awesome?
Did they level up the unit's firepower?
It also has superior mobility.
It's big and black...
And sparkly...
What type of review is that?
As part of the New
Self-Maintenance Plan,
Black 6 used our AHSMB
data as the foundation-
So, who's gonna pilot this puppy?
Your underclassman.
This would is your new
team member, Kuroki Ange.
A hot guy!
A hot girl!
Which is it?
Ange, allow me to introduce
the members of Team Rabbits.
This is your leader, Izuru.
And this is Asagi,
Suruga, Kei and Tamaki.
It-it's...a pleasure to meet you...
Sirs.
Have you worked out Black 6's pit crew?
Black 6's pilot will be its pit crew.
It's so highly automated that it
doesn't require a specialized pit crew.
Naturally, the ground crew will
handle its regular maintenance.
Makes sense...
If we're going to mass produce AHSMBs,
we have to simplify maintenance first.
Currently, the AHSMB are the
only thing that can fight
on par with the Wulgaru.
We worked ourselves to the bone
to get this new model done ASAP.
You don't look happy.
Well, yeah...
This means you'll have
to send an increasing
number of your students
to the frontlines.
Hasn't the new pilot arrived?
I'll introduce you later.
But I'm worried about how everyone
is going to take to this new kid...
He called us, "Sirs!"
Dang, we've gotta be sure to teach
her all of the ins and outs!
So, is that a male or a female?
Are you curious?
Nah, I couldn't care less.
A welcoming party...
Why don't we hold a
welcoming party to help
the new recruit feel at home?
Why should we?
Why not?
I think it's a good idea, Izuru.
Totally!
I'm in!
I'll bake the cake!
Putting the cake aside,
I should go invite Ange.
Why are you putting that aside? Well?
We're holding it right now?
I'll go get him!
Same!
No, this role should go to...
I should ask him for a
fresh take on my series!
Uh, um, Officer Ange!
Do you have a minute...?
Why don't you come in?
Sir, have a seat...
Uh, so I was thinking-
Right! I was thinking the same thing.
Let's...
...have one right away.
One what?
A mock battle.
What?!
I've been following your
battles at the academy.
I'd love to personally duel each of you.
Please!
Why the heck are you two
holding a mock battle?!
It just sorta worked out that way...
How did it "work out" that way?
Hey, it's all cool!
I've been wanting to
see Black 6 in action!
I can't believe you agreed to
that without authorization!
But I couldn't turn him down!
A mock battle?
Right. They'd like to see the
new recruit's abilities before
entering actual combat.
Very well.
Are you sure?
I wanted to confirm the new AHSMB
model's maneuverability myself.
Now we get to see what he's got, huh?
Hang in there, Ange!
Good luck, Ange!
Best of luck, Izuru...
How do you fight in a mo-
Mock battle, start!
Wow, she's good!
Impressive!
Too cool!
What the heck?! She's
taking this too seriously!
What's with this onslaught?!
She's fast!
He's overpowering Izuru...
Officer... Ange...?
You were great.
It's reassuring to know
that we have a pilot like
you on the team.
Honestly, I was dropping
by your room to invite
you to a welcoming party.
If you like-
I don't need a welcoming party.
I was born to fight.
Aside from fighting,
I don't need anything.
Ummm...?
Move.
What is that?
I was hoping a new pair of
eyes could look over it...
Your theme is stale and your
story lacks excitement.
Your panels are poorly blocked
and the designs are a mess.
Bluntly put, it sucks.
It's just like you.
What was that battle today?
It was pathetic!
Stop right there!
How dare you!
Wh-what was I doing...?
I'm sorry!
Officer Ange, we're holding a
welcoming part in the mess hall!
I'm the one who should apologize...
Thank you, Kei.
Did you actually invite him?
It wasn't much of an invitation...
Maybe she's really shy...
Ange must be the super shy type.
Should I go fetch Ange?
This might conflict with his
schedule or something...
Going by this, do you think we're
going to work well together?
After the Battle of Ceres,
the Wulgaru have been going
around destroying our bases
on 2493 Elmer and 1272 Gefion.
We expect them to strike 4 Vesta next.
We have a supply base located there.
It would appear that a
Wulgaru reconnaissance
unit has already located the base.
This is where the GDF has been
extracting Helium-3 and water.
We will suffer a tremendous
loss if we lose this base.
We must defend it at all cost!
Increasing backup engine's output.
Activating the turbine's
activation sequence.
Disconnect all equipment.
All hatches are closed.
External power has been established.
APU activated.
External pressure increasing.
Main engine, military!
Blast off!
Not another mission.
Where are we headed this time?
Now that your team is
stronger than ever,
I am sending you on a new mission.
Commence Operation: Iouto!
Godinion, enter Combat Formation I.
Main control: Move CIC.
Navi bridge: Closed.
Bulkhead: Locked.
Whole control room: Move complete.
Completed.
We get to see the new
AHSMB in actual combat...
Think it'll be okay without
its own specialized crew?
It's automatized, so it
doesn't need the likes of us.
Don't make me depressed!
Pick up the pace, primitive creatures!
How is attacking my dust cloud
gonna save your butts, slowpokes?
What is it?
Legatus Klein, it would appear that
those units are headed our way.
Yeah? Cool!
We'll break off the assault on
the base and prepare an ambush!
Sulfur is emitted around the Vesta
Base, creating poor visibility.
Furthermore, it would appear that
there are also some sulfur geysers.
Bear that in mind when on the move.
The enemy strikes in
swift, tight formations.
First, focus on breaking
their formation.
Rose 3, that's your job.
Got it!
Purple 2, ascertain the enemies'
movements and report them
to the rest of the team.
Yes, Ma'am!
Once Rose 3 charges in, Blue 1, Red 5
and Black 6 are to attack
from different directions.
Red 5 will issue the orders. Understood?
Roger! Yes, Ma'am!
Hey, Officer Ange? Are you okay?
Uh, yeah...
All units will reach 4
Vesta in 180 seconds.
I can't see the Wulgaru's
enemy fighters...
Where on Earth did they go?
Is the sulfur jamming our sensors?
Should I increase their sensitivity?
Purple 2, can you sense them?
I'll try.
I knew it...
They're here.
But where?!
I can't see a thing through this sulfur!
Asagi's AHSMB reacted before he did!
Its evasive skills are still
on a league of its own, huh?
Do you think Ange'll be okay?
This is his first real battle...
You'll be fine, Officer
Ange! Just keep calm.
Uh, right...
Where'd the enemy go?
It's so quiet. I don't like it.
Kei, find them yet?
Wait.
Over to your three o'clock!
Then I'm off!
Wait! There isn't much
noise out that way!
The main unit is-!
To our right!
This was a decoy?!
Wulgaru formation in the
10 o'clock direction.
Several fighters are approaching!
I'll pick off that one first!
Red 5 and Blue 1, offer
Purple 2 support!
Damn it! I can't move.
We've gotta get past these guys!
Miss!
Her IE gyro is toast!
Purple 2 is hit!
This doesn't look good.
I can't hit 'em!
Asagi, take care of Kei!
You got it!
I have your back!
Officer Ange! Officer Ange,
help Asagi defend Kei!
I can't get near Kei!
Hit home! Hit those freaks!
Officer Ange! Officer Ange!
Hurry and help Kei!
Ange, can't you move?
Ange? Ange?!
Black 6 has begun moving.
He's ignoring the team's formation!
What's this?!
And here I was gonna save it for last!
I'll hunt you down first!
The enemy units are
headed toward Black 6.
Is he going to take them on by himself?!
Black 6, pull back! Black 6!
I'm gonna crush them all!
I'll turn them into scrap metal!
I'm gonna make this my lamata!
I'm not done yet!
Officer Ange, don't chase after him!
He's movin' too fast!
Don't chase him too far!
Pull back, Officer Ange!
Ange, above you!
Quit naggin' at me
over every damn thing!
And don't tell me what to do!
Shut the hell up and watch!
Black 6 is still pursuing the enemy.
Black 6's Harmonic
Levels are increasing!
Who knew one of those primitive
creatures could keep up with me...
I think I'll take advantage of that.
Ange, you shouldn't pursue
the enemy by yourself!
That's right! Keep hot on my heels!
Black 6, cease pursuit of the enemy!
That's a-
Ange!
You probably think I've fallen
for some trap, but keep dreaming!
There's no way your shitty
excuse for brains
could devise an intelligent
plan, you damn swine!
Harmonic Levels are still increasing!
This is the highest
level we've ever seen.
You're a friggin' pig
with nothin' but speed!
Did you think you could beat
me off of speed alone?!
You're a worthless numbskull!
Who is this person...?
That's Ange, isn't it?
That verbal onslaught...
Just listening to him makes me dizzy.
Go to hell!
FRIGGIN' DIE!
My lamata-!
A swine's subordinates are swine!
Anyone part of that freak's
formation are freaks!
Damn Wulgaru! I hope you go extinct!
Don't let me see your
ugly hide ever again!
That one unit fought off
their entire squad...
Is that his real personality?
So it would seem.
Uh, is that how he always acted?
I'm struck speechless,
in more ways than one.
"AHSMB's Shadow"