Central Flognarde is well into fall.
There was a short panic that
occurred after the Heroes return,
but now everybody is relaxing
in their own country,
and we can finally relax!
And so...
Today I'm going with the
princess and Hero to play...
I mean, we're going to go on
an academic research trip!
Exploration at the Crystal Mines!
It's been a long time since I've
gone anywhere with you, Rebecca-san.
Yeah.
I hope you can enjoy the
fall scenery on the road.
Right!
Hey!
Princess!
Rebecca-sama!
Here we are!
Morning, everyone.
Morning, Shinku, Rico-chan.
Good morning.
So this is what we're taking, Rico-chan.
Indeed.
You've got a lot of stuff.
Do I?
Exploration tools, lunches,
change of clothes...
It's all needed.
And things to play with.
Yukki! Shh!
This is supposed to be an
academic research trip.
That's right.
Biscotti and Pastillage are
doing a joint research project.
That's right.
And when that's done, we're going
into a natural hot springs.
Last time we went, we found
a great hot springs spot.
I can't wait!
I wish Eclair could've come.
She says we'll meet her before the sun sets.
She's with Cou-sama right now, right?
Yeah.
When we meet up, Eclair will guide Cou-sama.
Right.
Now then, let's get going.
Yeah!
The wind feels so good.
Yes.
Sorry to ask you to come with me.
No, I was planning to go to Pastillage anyway.
As a way of saying thanks,
I'll let you pet my tail, specially!
Well?
Come on, go ahead!
No, I'm not worthy.
Well, let's finish up our job today
and go to the hot springs with the others.
Yeah!
Let's do our best!
It's bright red!
It's really pretty!
Isn't it amazing?
This is Biscotti's famous crimson highway.
The tree spirits are singing an autumn song.
This place is the best
area to take autumn walks.
The trees leave nuts and berries
behind before they lose their lives.
At this time of year you can gets
lots of nuts, berries, and seeds.
I see.
Thanks to that, honey buzzards and big
animals are able to get ready for winter...
And the animals are able to
enjoy the blessings of fall.
That's just like Earth.
Yeah.
The winter and fall spirits in Biscotti
and Pastillage are very active.
In winter, it turns into snow.
But in Galette the winter
spirits don't do much.
It doesn't get that cold in winter,
but the people of Galette
don't enjoy snow very much.
Galette looks forward to spending
winter indoors where it's warm.
I really know how they feel!
Okay, if we go to where the
path splits on this road,
we're almost there.
Let's hurry there.
Okay.
Rico, we're heading to a mine, right?
Yup.
That's where the crystals for
Crystal Magic are produced,
and there are a lot of crystals
growing in between the trees,
streams and waterfalls...
The scenery is beautiful, and the place
seems like something out of a fairy tale.
We've only been there once,
but it was wonderful.
Yes.
I'm sure you two will both like it.
This is...
Amazing.
People don't come here,
so it's a little hard to
walk around some places,
but I'm sure you'll be fine, Shinku.
Yeah.
You can fly, Rebecca-sama,
so there's no problem for you.
Yup!
Okay, work first!
Let's get ready!
Okay, so the way to investigate
is what I just explained.
Okay, we're going to check the amount
and purity of the crystal ore here!
Okay!
I'll look from the sky.
Mercurius!
Broom Mode!
Princess, want to go with me!
I will!
Okay, bye!
Bye!
This purity is far greater
than I anticipated.
So is this!
What are you using this ore for?
They're usually used to
activate crystal magic.
Yeah?
Yes, for example,
this white crystal is very important for
making circuits in crystal magic machines...
And...
That red crystal can be turned into
parts that amplify your power.
Their growth rate is impressive, too!
Even with nature-friendly gathering
methods we could get plenty!
Really?
Shinku.
These crystals grow off
the power of the land.
Thus, we only take the part that naturally
grows, and don't take the whole thing.
That's called nature-friendly gathering.
We don't disrupt the natural order.
We just take a little bit of
the blessings of the land.
I see.
Crystals and ore are very important
for making our lives convenient,
but the land and nature
are just as important.
I see...
Hey, Princess...
What is that?
I think... I'm about done here....
Okay.
It's time to move to another area.
Hero!
Shinku!
Shinku, are you okay?
What's wrong?
Well... there were these little people.
Little people?
Could it be...
Those are the forest people.
The forest...
Forest people.
They're a type of spirit.
Forest people, please don't be scared!
We want to be friends.
Is that okay?
Thank you!
Here.
They're cute.
Hello.
They're kind and very curious.
Look.
Hello.
This nut... is that for me?
The forest people help humans and
animals when they're in trouble.
Hero, you were hungry, right?
I am, actually.
Thank you, forest people.
And they like this as an offering.
What's that?
Rock salt.
The forest people love salt.
I'm glad I had some on hand for Onmitsu.
Are they trying to say something?
What is it?
There's a problem.
That's... the mountain pass?
There are demons living
in the cave on the pass!
And the forest people's
princess was kidnapped?
We have to go!
Shinku, this is Rebecca.
Becky!
Good timing!
Trouble, everyone!
There are demons on this mountain!
That thing is huge!
It seems to be a lower-class demon,
but it's so big.
It's just chowing down
on the crystal trees...
And it just ate a bunch of ore.
At this rate it's going to eat all the
ore and crystals on this mountain.
Where is your princess?
Inside its stomach?
She got eaten?
That monster seems to swallow crystals
and spirits to slowly absorb their power.
If it seems like a lot of time hasn't
passed since she was eaten...
We can save her!
Hold it!
All creatures eat other things.
I won't blame you for that.
But I can't let you get
away with this brutality
towards the forest spirits or your gluttony!
If you can understand us then listen.
If you can't...
In the name of Biscotti's Hero,
And her leader...
We're going to punish you!
This voice...
Don't listen to it.
I won't let you!
Princess!
Yukikaze-style Ninjutsu!
Senka Souretsu!
Oh, no!
Yuki!
No way!
It's all sticky!
Special Move: Shining Blast...
That's...
This is terrible.
I need to hurry.
That's it!
Shinku! Shinku!
Shinku!
Just wait! I'll save you—
I won't let you get away.
Give back the Hero!
It can't get me here...
He got me.
You're the forest people's
princess, aren't you?
I'm here to save you.
It's okay now.
We're going to escape, so sorry,
but get in here.
Okay!
That's not enough, huh?
Then this!
Double Shining Blast Fist!
Special Move:
Flame King Fang!
Shinku!
Hero!
Yukki! Rico!
Shinku!
Becky! Princess!
I'm so glad!
Sorry to worry you, princess.
Yuki-chan, is that monster...
Yeah...
It was a cursed sword demon.
No wonder it was strong.
But Shinku beat it on his own.
Yup.
Our Hero is great.
But you saved the princess.
I'm really grateful.
I'm glad everybody was safe.
And after that,
Yukki sealed the cursed sword.
The frog god whose body it was
inhabiting went back to its old nest.
And of course, the princess
returned to the forest people.
And peace came back to the mountains.
And since our demon-fighting and
research were all done, of course...
This is paradise.
I feel so warm.
The temperature is great.
It feels perfect.
I'm so happy.
You guys did good work, too.
This place is amazing.
Huh? Princess?
And the other forest people...
What is it?
You're giving me this?
Thanks!
That's wonderful.
Is it fruit juice?
It smells so good.
Thanks!
It's... good.
Wh-What is this?
Shinku!
What's wrong?
We're leaving.
Shinku!
Shinku?
What's wrong?
He had some of the Forest
People's Nectar Water, huh?
Is that...
It's a drink the forest people make.
It's extremely healthy,
but people who aren't used to it
end up looking like
they're drunk, like this.
They'll pass out or get nosebleeds, but when
they wake up they'll feel 100 times better!
Don't worry.
I see.
Forest people, don't worry.
The Hero Shinku will be fine.
We got here earlier than expected!
Going at top speed was a little rough.
Don't worry.
Once we're in the hot springs,
all that tiredness will go away.
Let's rush in and surprise them!
Here we are!
Excuse us.
Couver is here!
P-Princess...
Princess...
What did you...
No.
Eclair, this isn't what you think.
This looks fun!
I'll join in!
Rico. Yuki.
Explain what happened.
Eclair, calm down.
Calm down.
This isn't what you think!
We're taking care of him!
If we're playing tricks
on him, leave it to me!
It's not like that!
Hero, what were you doing to the princess?
It's not like that! It's a misunderstanding!
Let me play, too!
See you next time!
The Lion's
Arranged Marriage
Yup!