It was raining...
You're always reading that book, boy.
Is it that interesting?
It's good.
I've read it many times now.
There are so many more
stories out in the world
that are far more interesting
than what's in that book.
Where's Part Three?
Part 2 of 3
I don't have Part Three.
I've looked and looked,
but I've never found it.
Now it all makes sense.
That story's Part Three is
the worst of the worst.
You should consider yourself satisfied
with just the first two parts.
I'm saying this for your own good.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
Then you write it.
Me, write?
That's the only way you can
keep that story perfect.
Part 2 of 3
To write a story is
to write about a person,
and how that person should live and die.
From what I've seen,
you have the qualifications.
Who are you?
Me?
My name is...
Are you awake, Odasaku?
How do you feel?
I feel like I'm experiencing
all the hangovers I'll have
in the next fifty years
all at the same time.
I saw Ango at the place you told me about.
So Ango was there, like I suspected.
Yeah.
He vanished into the dark
with soldiers in black.
Sounds like black special ops.
It seems recent events can be
divided into two categories.
Are they a separate organization from Mimic?
They're different.
But we can pretty much ignore the
black special ops guys for now.
Mimic is the more dangerous enemy.
Akutagawa-kun and other
combat squad members
are dealing with conflicts in the city,
but we don't even know what the
enemy leader's ability is.
We're at a disadvantage.
That Akutagawa is one of your
subordinates, isn't he?
I heard his ability has high
offensive capabilities.
He's a naked sword without a scabbard.
I'm sure he'll become the strongest
gifted mafia member in the near future but,
right now, he needs someone to
teach him how to sheathe his blade.
Sorry, that was a tangent.
This morning, the council of five
top executives convened.
They made a decision to attack Mimic
with everything
the Port Mafia can muster.
Just now,
my subordinates, including Akutagawa-kun,
were hit by a surprise attack.
They're still fighting at the art museum.
Odasaku?
You're not serious about going, are you?
We're hitting them with
everything we've got, right?
I didn't think you'd be interested in conflict, since you don't kill people.
I'm not.
Then why?
I've acquired a lot of debts in my life.
If your subordinates are in a tough spot,
they need help.
You should forget about your debts.
Episode 15
Some Day in a
Room with a
Seaside View
No one remembers what you owe to them.
Guns are the weapons of fools.
All too weak.
So you're the one they speak of...
The gifted one in black.
Who are you?
My name is Gide.
I am the leader of Mimic.
He will never acknowledge me,
no matter how many underlings I defeat.
I'd like to challenge you.
I'd like to ask a question.
Is your ability sufficient to release
our souls from original sin?
Want to find out?!
You're not getting away!
It seems you are not the one.
Impossible!
Is this an ability?!
Bastard!
Can you read my moves?!
In a few more years,
you may have grown powerful
enough to grant our wish,
but we cannot wait.
Kill me.
Defeat means death.
I regret that I could not
be the enemy you wanted.
Farewell.
Did you get shot in the leg?
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?!
Let me down!
Let me go!
I'm Oda Sakunosuke.
I heard about you from
Dazai and came to help.
I've heard of you from Dazai-san.
You're one of the lower-ranking members.
That's right.
And I heard you're a friend to him.
Is that true?
I have a policy of not using
that word lightly.
Dazai-san said
I wouldn't stand a chance against you,
not in a hundred years.
Now's not the time to be having a falling out.
Why...
Why doesn't Dazai-san...
Are you the same?!
Sorry.
I have to bring you back,
especially for a friend who
has high hopes for you.
I did have a premonition.
What are you talking about?
I had a premonition that I'd be able to
meet the person I seek in this country.
I am Gide.
I came here in search of the one who can
release the souls of ghosts like us.
I can get you a discount with an
undertaker I know if you want.
There is no need.
I just found the one we were looking for.
What?
What's the matter?
I haven't even fired a single round.
What did you do?!
I just saw a future where you
would dodge to the right.
Therefore, I adjusted my aim.
But you saw that future,
so you adjusted as well.
Which I also saw.
The ability to see a few seconds into the
future if you are to be in any danger...
I can do what you can do.
The predictive ability
we have is omnipotent.
You are the only one who can
kill me and end this war.
If you are one of the Port Mafia,
killing me, the enemy leader,
must be your greatest desire.
No thanks.
I'm only here to help one of my own.
What?
You're not one of the mafia?
There are different types in the mafia.
Guns are tools for murder!
And this is a war zone!
I'm not interested in fighting.
What I'm interested in is living.
There is nothing more important
in life than death!
Good, that's how it should be...
What?!
Are you refusing to fight me, then?
There is a reason I don't kill.
Look elsewhere.
Why?!
My subordinates and I have been
wandering the whole world like ghosts,
looking for a place worthy of our deaths.
You are our only wish.
Fight me!
If you refuse—
The reason I can't do as you wish
is because I have a dream.
Some day when I can quit the
Port Mafia and become a free man,
I want to sit down at a desk in a room
where I can see the sea, and...
Then you write it.
That's the only way you can
keep that story perfect.
I want to become a writer.
I want to throw the gun aside,
and only have pen and paper.
One man told me that to write
a story is to write a person.
A man who takes lives
cannot write about lives.
That's why I won't kill.
And that's the reason why you
refuse to enter our battle?
So that's your answer?
That's right.
Stop!
A bullet-proof vest.
That pain that is a privilege of the living.
It's something we lost long ago.
We are already dead.
We're just soulless husks
being controlled by ghosts.
You're not dead.
I don't know what happened
to you in the past,
but you can still think
about how you want to die.
Why won't you understand?!
You are the only...
You will not kill me.
That's because you don't understand my wish.
And I won't kill you right now,
because you are the only one who can guide
us to the battlefield of purification.
I will make you understand
who we really are.
Then you will understand
that, between the two of us,
there can be only one.
You should look forward to it.
The night is a good time.
It's a time that belongs to the Port Mafia.
What now?
I don't know.
That was quite some trouble
you got into, though.
Who would've thought that the enemy leader
you'd just met would turn
into such an earnest suitor?
They're weird, looking for war so that they
can find a place worthy of their deaths.
Are they?
Their wish to be creative about their deaths
is something I hadn't thought about.
How long will this conflict last?
Mimic's soldiers aside,
their leader's ability is a nuisance.
Surprise attacks won't work.
That means we need inside info.
Any leads you can think of?
Only Ango.
I agree.
I wonder if there's some
way we can find Ango.
There is.
There is?
To be more precise,
there is no need to find him.
Here?
Where else?
Hey there.
I started without you.
You could've called.
I had a hard time losing my tail.
But today's fine.
I can spend as much time as I want here.
Well?
How'd you know to find me here?
Just a hunch, I suppose.
I'm lucky.
I didn't think I could drink here again.
You're pretty sentimental for a mole.
Even before you joined the Port Mafia,
you had a different identity.
And that's as a secret agent of the state.
You were an agent of the
Ministry of Internal Affairs'
gifted special operations division.
Your mission was to monitor the Port Mafia.
Though the division oversees
all gifted within the nation,
should there ever be an all-out
war with the Port Mafia,
the division will suffer heavy casualties.
The division's primary purpose is to
manage, not annihilate, the gifted.
That's why they had an agent infiltrate the
Port Mafia and monitor their movements.
Then Mimic came up at the table.
The gifted criminal organization
had been planning to enter Japan.
They were a headache for the division,
so the division decided to have you
monitor Mimic... as the Port Mafia's spy.
As a lowly salaried government worker,
it was a job entirely above my pay grade.
So, in other words,
Ango wasn't a double agent,
but a triple agent.
Tell us about Mimic.
I heard Gide and Odasaku-san traded blows.
Did you see Gide's ability?
I did.
Gide is elusive, and his location
is never made known to us.
The brass intends to let the
Port Mafia handle this case.
Well, that's very convenient for them.
But even the Port Mafia would have a
hard time dealing with his ability.
Of course,
that's if we don't consider a certain
lowest-ranking member in the organization.
Both our abilities only entail looking
a few seconds into the future.
If push comes to shove,
the outcome will be dependent on
our skills in combat and shooting.
The unknown variables will matter a lot.
There's also "the singularity
of the ability" to consider.
The singularity of the ability?
Didn't something unusual happen when
you used your ability against Gide?
Yeah, it did.
The government has observed that
when some abilities interact,
they may careen off into an entirely
unexpected direction in rare cases.
I wasn't really supposed to tell you that.
It'd become a major issue if the brass were
to know that I am meeting you like this.
I'll have to go underground
for the time being.
Well, well...
You're talking as though you
will leave this place alive.
Are you planning to make this a war zone?
It's my fault.
I was wrong.
I selfishly thought that here,
I could actually meet with you two
without having to consider my position.
Ango.
Go before I change my mind.
I'm not sad.
I knew this from the beginning.
Whether you were with the gifted
special operations division or not,
anything I would never want
to lose is always lost.
It is a given that everything
that is worth wanting
will be lost the moment I obtain it.
There's nothing worth pursuing at the
cost of prolonging a life of suffering.
Dazai-kun, Odasaku-san...
If there ever comes a time when the division
and the Port Mafia don't exist
and we all become freer men,
let's come back here and—
Don't say it, Ango.
Don't say anything more.
What?
Mister!
Kosuke!
Katsumi!
Yu!
Shinju!
Sakura!
A map?
My throat hurt.
I couldn't breathe.
I heard someone screaming.
I realized, because my throat hurt so much,
that I was the one who was screaming.
Then you write it.
That's the only way you can
keep that story perfect.
I can't write it anymore.
I can no longer write a story.
Next Time: Episode 16
Bungo Stray Dogs