Everyone's having a great time!
Chocolate
It's Valentine's Day, after all.
I'm gonna do my best, too!
It's so expensive!
Everything is more expensive than yesterday.
I guess everyone's thinking the same thing.
Oh, Serara...
Nyanta!
Is something wrong?
No... Um...
Oh, coconia fruit, is it?
It's a southern fruit used
to make all kinds of things,
like sweets and drinks.
Oh, really?
I knew that, though.
And People of the Land have a legend about them.
If you get the one you love to eat them
on February 14, your love will be returned.
Come to think of it, in the old world,
today was Valentine's Day.
Th-That's right.
Anyway, um, I have things to do!
Meow...
2.14  A Sweet Trap
2.14  A Sweet Trap.
Master Naotsugu,
please train me again today!
Oh, sorry.
I have something to do today.
Marie wants to see you, right?
Yeah.
You know, it's Valentine's Day...
Valentine's Day, huh?
Come to think of it,
we were once put through
serious hell over that.
That was Kanami, right?
You were in the legendary Debauchery
Tea Party, weren't you, Shiroe?
So was I.
And get off me.
I heard Kanami was the leader of the Party.
And she was beautiful and everyone loved her...
And she was older than you.
Hey, could she be...
Your girlfriend?
What are you talking about?
It wasn't like that.
Really? But you still like her, right?
I've never heard this.
Who is this woman, exactly?
It's written all over your face!
And my lord, who never reacts
to anything, is freaking out.
It is not.
Liar! You can't fool me!
Could she really be his love?
Older than he is?
Broad-minded?
Hey, Tetra...
If you're a girl, have a little modesty.
A girl will wilt if she doesn't have
good food and tales of love.
Hey, has Master Naotsugu really
not realized that Tetra is a guy?
Seems that way.
It's so obvious, though!
Should I tell him?
I'm not sure what to do.
Is it "Miss Tetra" or "Mr. Tetra"?
And I'm not sure if it'd be
"Big Sis Tetra" or "Big Bro Tetra."
Brother
Sister                                                                   Brother
What are you talking about?
N-Nothing, Big Sibro Tetra!
"Sibro"?
Crap! I combined "Sis" and "Bro"!
Actually, we were talking about what
it would be best to call you.
That's an easy one.
Just call me "Tetra"!
I figured it wouldn't work.
It's rare to see you in the kitchen, Isuzu.
Rare?
What brings you here?
Actually, I wanted to use these
to make some sweets.
Are these coconia fruits?
Yeah.
I don't really mean anything by it,
but I'm thinking of making some for Rudy.
Oh, my.
But I'm not a cook.
Then why don't we make them together?
If I make them, they turn into gel...
I've got the perfect item.
Newlywed's Apron Dress
The Newlywed's Apron Dress.
I'll lend it to you.
Oh!
In exchange for a temporary level drop,
it gives you a moderate cooking sub-skill.
Wow!
Even I'll be able to cook!
It looks great on you.
But why do you have this, Chief?
It was a quest reward.
Now, then.
Since you've professed that
you're not a good cook,
I'll start by teaching you how
to make simple sweets.
First, peel the coconia fruits and
cut them into slices, and then boil them.
Once you can stick a toothpick clean through,
move them to a bowl,
and mash them with a spatula
while they're still warm.
If you strain them now,
the taste will be much smoother.
I see!
Add sugar, egg yolks, cream, then butter,
and mix them up.
Once they've cooled,
roll them into balls with your hands,
and brush on some egg yolk.
Then put them into an oven warmed
with salamander heat,
and cook them until they turn brown.
And you've got sweet potato-style coconia.
It smells so good!
I'll go give them to Rudy before they get cold.
Thanks, Chief!
Now, then...
It's still early in the day. I guess I'll clean.
It's Valentine's Day, so I'd like
to give Shiroe a present.
But if he takes it in a weird way,
it'd be embarrassing...
No, if he doesn't do anything,
that'd be even worse.
In any event, it's just to thank him.
Could she be...
Your girlfriend?
Kanami...
Hey, there!
Tetra, did you need something?
You're curious about Kanami, aren't you?
Wh-What are you talking about?
You're so easy to read.
Why not make it clear?
No, no.
Make what clear, exactly?
Here.
It's called a coconia fruit.
They say it has a special
effect on Valentine's Day.
A special effect?
Here! Look at the flavor text!
"Coconia Fruit."
"A southern fruit,
used for many applications, such as
making various dishes and drinks.
If you feed them to someone on Valentine's Day,
you may find out who they heart-heart."
What does that mean?
You've heard that flavor text has
been coming true lately, right?
Which means you might figure
out who Shiroe loves.
Wouldn't it be better to find out
from Shiroe himself, rather than
sit here alone and suffer?
Bye!
Coconia fruit...
Coconia fruit!
Even if you have stat boosts from the item,
you're still doing quite well at this.
Today's the day girls work hardest, after all.
Girls?
Wh-Who is she making them for?
It's been six weeks since the magic
circle protecting Akihabara vanished.
It's more peaceful than I expected.
Akihabara was always a place
for high-level adventurers.
No monster would willingly wander in,
and any that did were wiped out immediately.
The Round Table hasn't received
any reports about PKs, either.
Eins was really worried
We Have Chocolate!
when the Royal Guard system went out of whack,
but it's actually working out.
Still, we need to keep an eye out to ensure
that no People of the Land get hurt.
Well, the combat guilds are
taking shifts to handle that.
That's right.
By the way, who's on duty today?
West Wind, I think.
Come to think of it, I haven't seen them.
Today, of all days...
Soujirou!
Leave Your Valentine's Day Chocolate Here
Please accept this as a sign of my love!
Wait, I was here first!
I was! Sou!
Okay, okay.
Stay in line.
Thanks.
I'll make sure to eat it, okay?
Soujirou, thank you!
Hey, no cutting!
Crusty's been missing ever since that day.
Jeez, where is that monster?
And what is he doing?
I bet if he wanted to, he could
come back right away.
Princess Lenessia, why are you
in such sloppy dress again?
It's past noon.
I don't have any public duties today.
That isn't the problem.
It's important to remember your station.
Coconia fruits were sold out today,
so I used something else.
Here, have some.
Thanks, Elissa.
Honestly...
What does he think a knight's
pledge means, anyway?
It's sweet and delicious!
Well?
I feel like I'm getting the hang of it.
I'm glad.
There's still more to be done, but...
I'll look for ingredients that don't
put so much stress on the body.
We at Radio Market are working with
the Roderic Merchant Guild on it.
Don't worry. It'll work.
Thank you.
But where did my right arm go?
From the fact that healing magic doesn't work,
we can be certain it isn't a type of
damage that was in the old game.
We can only guess that it's in the same
place as Crusty, wherever he is.
Either way, this is a very extraordinary case.
Don't worry.
Just focus on getting better.
I'll work super hard until my lord returns!
Yeah, thanks.
My lord...
Nyanta!
They were cheap, so I bought a lot.
I bet they weren't cheap at all.
Nyanta!
Yes?
Since Shiroe is always so good to me,
I wanted to make something for him...
Meow?
N-Not like that!
It's nothing special!
I understand how you feel.
I'd be glad to help.
Nyanta...
Excuse me, master.
I've returned from a training quest.
As a reward, I just happened
to receive a large number of coconia fruits, so...
You just happened to get all those?
I wanted to make my lord some...
Minori?
Akatsuki?
She has coconia fruits, too.
For my lord?
Look how beaten up she got.
Does she also...
Wh-What a problem.
This is one of the worst things to
happen in Log Horizon's history.
Oh, man.
This is too funny.
They're rivals in love.
Okay, then!
In that case, why not work together?
You're both after the same thing.
Work together?
That's a great idea, but I only have
one Newlywed's Apron Dress.
Look!
I got one from Marielle!
Very well. Master, please teach me.
Fast!
M-Me, too.
All right.
Go! Go! Maidens!
But remember that I'm the center of the galaxy!
That's strange...
Where did Rudy go?
Oh, well.
I'll head back.
Sorry for keeping you.
Naotsugu!
Today's Valentine's Day, you know, right?
Y-Yeah.
So... So...
I made you a present! Candy!
Thanks.
Naotsugu, you know, I... Um...
Lately, I've been thinking...
You have that cute girl in your guild now.
I mean, she doesn't bother me, but...
What kind of girl is your type?
O...
"O"?
"Original style?"
Pa...
"Pa"?
...nti—
What happened, Naotsugu?!
A new type of Royal Guard system?
Akatsuki?
For a second, it looked like you vanished.
You imagined it.
I swear...
Naotsugu's such a jerk!
Even if he wanted to dodge the question,
there must be better ways to do it!
Shouryuu?
Hi.
Oh, right.
Want some candy?
I made too much.
For me?
Bye.
I-It still makes me happy!
I'm back!
I'm back.
What the hell was that about?
What's wrong?
I just got kicked, out of nowhere.
Welcome back.
That looks good!
Let me take a—
It's not for you!
This is an offering from us to my lord.
For me?
That's right.
These two made this special cake for you.
They made it?
You mean they cooked it?
Indeed.
I gave them the necessary items
and helped a little. That was all.
I cheered them on, too.
Come on!
Sit down.
Stare.
What is going on here?
And I have mild trauma when it comes to cakes.
My lord, hurry.
Please taste it.
Y-Yeah.
I'll try it.
This is...
It's good!
All right!
Isn't that great, Akatsuki?
Yeah.
Meow?
This is it!
This is the Valentine's Day-only
effect of the coconia fruit.
He'll answer anything we ask him now!
Quickly, quickly!
But what should I ask?
Who he likes?
If it's Akatsuki...
No! I'm too scared to ask!
What if he says "Kanami"?
Who is Kanami, anyway?
It's no use.
I can't do it.
Jeez, that Rudy...
I never did find him.
And I spent all day training. I'm so hungry...
I'm starved.
What's for dinner tonight?
I like curry!
Shiro, we all know that. Why say it?
Did I say something?
That's right.
Okay, let's have curry today, then.
Huh, so Shiroe likes curry more than love, huh?
But you know...
This may have been for the best.
This is for me?
Yes.
I saw them being sold in the market,
and I thought they were pretty.
I was going to make him some sweets,
Coconia
but coconia fruits were all sold out.
And I couldn't find a Newlywed's
Apron Dress anywhere...
These flowers have thorns.
Did you pick them just for me?
I'm very grateful.
Oh, we're having curry tonight, by the way.
Why not join us?
Can I?
Of course.
Thank you!
I'll help!
I would appreciate that.
Okay!
I'm back.
Where the heck have you been all day?
Oh, sorry...
I had something to do.
Oh, whatever.
Here.
What is this?
Sweet potato-style coconia fruit.
It's not quite dinnertime,
but since I made them, try one.
That was nice of you.
Okay, I'll try one.
This is great!
Thanks, Miss Isuzu.
Good!
Huh?
Er... Rudy?
I love you all!
I see.
So it isn't limited to romantic love.
I love you, too, Big Bro Rudy.
I see! I see!
What's gotten into them?
No idea.
Shiro...
Nureha...
You're not using your bed again.
Intix?
Were you thinking about Shiroe?
Were you?
Don't talk about him.
I told you.
I told you, didn't I?
He's no good.
He's a man who can't be connected to any group.
He isn't even a player.
Just powerful interference.
He is not a man you can have.
He's just a traitor.
But he is smart.
You could say he's fastidious.
So he knows the smell of the gutter.
Do you honestly think anyone
will ever care about you?
Given how dirty, selfish, and ugly you are?
Stop it!
You're covered in lies.
There isn't the tiniest bit of truth in you.
Once someone gets to know you,
they'll find your past smells worse than a sewer.
You, who just kept staring longingly
at us with that creepy smile...
Stop it!
Please understand.
Don't be arrogant enough to
think that someone like you
could ever be connected to anyone.
I'm the only one who would make a contract
with a filthy woman like you.
You're the perfect princess for
looking at from a distance.
Please realize that things
aren't like they were when this was your salon.
Not here in Plant Hwyaden.
You'll collect lots of wooden dolls
and make yourself a castle.
And I will gain the entire Yamato server.
That was the deal, right?
You're going to create a place
where you belong, aren't you?
The Council of Ten Seats is about to begin.
Well, you're only a figurehead,
so just come if you feel like it.
No.
Not anymore,
Intix.
It isn't just about my contract with you.
I...
I can give you what you want more
easily as a foe than a friend.
I'll be your enemy, whenever you
decide to find a reason.
I have a promise!
This is the China server.
The chaos of the Apocalypse
continues across the world.
But one adventurer gathers friends,
and fights to protect the people.
She is the former leader of
the Debauchery Tea Party.
Her name is...
Next time: Kanami, Go East.
Kanami, Go East
I have friends to run with me.