Perfect.
Tea and Distance
One moment, Miss Ririchiyo.
You have a stain on your shoe.
Who's that?
That's Shirakiin.
Is that her boyfriend?
Wow!
I can do that myself!
No, I cannot allow you to dirty
your hands with such a task.
I shall do anything dirty for you.
I shall be your hands and feet...
Fine, just hurry up!
All done.
Finally.
Then, I'm off.
You look perfect yet again today.
I just wish to keep gazing at you.
You're never going to
let me leave, are you?
If I keep humoring you, I'll be late.
Miss Ririchiyo...
I am so sorry.
I have inconvenienced you...
Actually, I realize
that even wishing to be
with you for longer
is impudence for a mere dog like myself.
I understand I should feel honored by
simply being allowed to serve you.
I am a greedy animal.
Y-You needn't go that far...
Are you saying I may wish for something?
Wish away.
May I ask that you exit,
the second your class ends?
No problem.
And then, would you stay
with me after that?
Easy.
You really are a kind and wonderful person.
Huh?
I think I just got played...
Watch out!
I'm so sorry!
Quite all right.
Thank you so much.
Is your hand okay?
It's fine.
Are you sure?
You need not worry about me.
I am your bodyguard precisely
for moments like these.
It is my honor to be your shield.
I still can't figure out
why he feels the need to humble
himself to that degree...
Watanuki.
Did you train today, too?
Yup.
I ran all the way to school.
That's all?
Well, I was really...
I feel as though the other bodyguard-clients
are far more like friends.
Does anyone know the answer?
Me! Me! Me!
You're pretty gung-ho about participating,
for such a delinquent.
You dropped this.
Thank you!
You're pretty kind, for such a delinquent.
Cafeteria
Here's your change.
Thank you.
You gave me ten yen too much.
Oh, my!
You're pretty honest, for such a delinquent.
What are you talking about?
He used to serve him.
I'm not honest at all!
That's why he knew who I was.
Because I'm that man's fiancée.
He said that I saved him.
I wonder if it has anything
to do with that.
Shirakiin, you're next.
Roromiya, you're next.
Oh, wow!
Miss!
Roromiya's eating a taiyaki.
No. I'm the problem...
He always notices everything about me,
but I don't know anything about him.
What are you drawing?
Meat and potatoes.
Yeah, but why?
What can I do,
Understand
him.
to better understand him?
Welcome back, Miss Ririchiyo.
I've been waiting for you here,
and even this short distance felt
like a thousand miles.
How unfortunate.
So, where are we going?
Where would you like to go?
You said you wanted to be
with me after school.
Doesn't that mean you had somewhere
you wanted to go?
This morning, you cunningly
made me agree to it.
You misunderstand.
It is impossible for me to expect
you to go anywhere for me.
All I want is to be with you.
It's that gorgeous car again...
Wow!
Is he devious, or is he really pure?
So, what did you actually do
while you were alone?
Well, today I spent the morning
reading the message you sent me.
The entire time?!
How was school, Miss Ririchiyo?
Fine.
Really?
I've noticed I spend a lot of time
with Roromiya and Watanuki.
Food tastes better when you eat together.
It tastes the same.
You're so rigid.
It's not really in my nature to mingle.
That sounds like fun.
Hardly.
But Watanuki always has
a really fancy lunch.
Watanuki's grandpa always brings it for him.
What a spoiled little rich boy...
I'm a delinquent!
Roromiya's always trying to feed me.
Say "Ahh..."
As you can see, it isn't fun at all.
I'm so glad to hear that,
Miss Ririchiyo.
I guess he did notice
that I was worrying about school...
And how I'm actually really glad
that Roromiya and Watanuki are around.
I never say what I mean,
but he still notices.
Even though I don't know
anything about him.
I want to reciprocate.
I want to notice.
I want to understand him, too.
I want to
understand
him, too.
Want to eat together, Chiyo?
Again?
Do you like eating with me or something?
That's weird.
Says the one who already has
everything prepared.
I just happened to have three paper
plates and three paper cups.
Well, I'm a delinquent, so I just happened
to be walking past this place.
Please.
Oh, thank you.
Eating together makes the food taste better.
It also makes you closer friends.
I suppose you have a point.
They do say people are defenseless
while they're feeding.
That reminds me!
I've never had a meal with Miketsukami.
Actually, I've never seen him
eat anything since I
arrived at Ayakashi Kan!
What's wrong?
Even with that, he takes
extra care to humble himself.
This is no good!
I must level the field more.
No wonder I don't understand him.
Eating together...
But what?
I've got it!
I'll make him coffee,
with all my heart,
just like he prepared my tea!
I'll make my famous coffee,
and have tea time with him!
What the hell?
Eating with Chiyo is fun.
It's perfect.
The goal is to have tea together.
But if we do this,
I want him to enjoy himself.
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
It isn't like I expect him to
be grateful or anything,
so you can shut up, Murai.
This is what I have to do!
All right.
Then I just need to invite Miketsukami
tomorrow morning, and...
But how should I invite him?
Ways to Invite Miketsukami
Idea One
"Miketsukami, I'd like to buy some coffee beans.
Care to come along?"
"Of course. Will you
be preparing the
coffee yourself?"
"I will, yes. My coffee
is quite delectable."
"I would love to
try some of your
tasty beverage."
He'd never say anything like that!
Idea Two
"Have you ever heard of Ethiopian
Andromeda coffee?"
"What would that be?"
"It's an extremely rare variety,
grown entirely wild in the forest.
I've managed to procure some."
That's a lie!
I can't say that.
Idea Three
"I've discovered a new
variety of coffee.
Help me taste it."
Why am I ordering him around?!
Idea Four
"I'd like to drink coffee with you."
I can't say that!
Good morning, Miss Ririchiyo.
Good morning.
Is everything all right?
I'm fine.
But, Miketsukami...
Yes?
I w-was wondering if today...
If you might like to have coffee with me?
Today...
Yes?
T-Today... Co-Co-Co-Co-Co...
Today, I want some corn potage.
Understood.
O-Once we're in the lounge, I'll calm down.
How is the corn potage?
It's good.
I am so glad to hear that.
Say "Ahh."
Eat it, Ririchiyo!
Let Auntie see you getting fed!
Ahh...
I'm going to turn you into a dust cloth.
Dude, can you believe her?
Say "Ahh," Watanuki!
Get the hell away from me!
Oh, how cute. You're embarrassed.
Am not!
You're embarrassed!
I need it to be quieter than this.
Why can't I "ahh"?
Miketsukami.
Yes?
I can do this...
Miketsukami!
First period is Home Ec.
We're going to be late.
R-Roromiya!
Have a good day.
You aren't going to eat?
Is the high-level art of inviting others
impossible for me, after all?
No. Don't give up...
Ask him when he comes to pick you up.
Welcome back, Miss Ririchiyo.
Miketsukami!
Yes?
W-Would you...
Would you...
Wouldn't you say it's a beautiful day?
I would.
Nice boobs.
Yeah, right?
The fact that they're losing to
gravity is so perfect.
You have your eye in the right place.
Thanks.
Here you go, Watanuki.
It's important to rehydrate
yourself after your bath.
What's with the dog bowl?
You expect me to lick that?!
But that would be dirty.
Why can't I...
If you stay with me,
sooner or later you'll get hurt, too.
Why don't we try it, then?
I apologize for calling you
here at this hour.
Please don't apologize.
I am happy to meet you anywhere,
at any hour.
You've seemed ill at ease all day.
Is something wrong?
Is there something I'm not doing for you?
Not at all...
I-I feel like I'm being a nuisance.
I apologize.
But...
You really do observe me well.
Of course I do.
You were quite pale this morning.
And then,
though you always step into the
elevator with your right foot,
this morning, you entered with your left.
What?
You also added 1.5 grams more sugar
into your tea than usual.
And though you habitually fasten your
seatbelt once you're seated in the car,
today, the car had almost started
before you fastened it.
J-Just one second...
And normally, you wipe your right lens first
when cleaning your glasses,
but today, you began with the left.
You pour soy sauce clockwise on
your eggs. Yet today, the motion
was counter-clockwise, with an
extra shake of black pepper.
What's more, while you were
washing your hands...
What the hell have you been looking at?!
At everything that you do.
No detail is too minor for me to notice.
I was an idiot to ask.
There's nothing wrong with me.
And I am certainly not dissatisfied
with you in the least!
But you aren't being fair...
You only care about me,
but you don't let me know
anything about you.
It isn't equal.
It's unpleasant to be in that position.
I am unworthy of your kind words.
To think that you'd have
such compassion for me,
when I am but your dog.
That sort of behavior is exactly
what I'm talking about.
But...
I don't know
how to interact with someone
other than to serve them.
That's how I've spent my life.
Miketsukami...
I am the least qualified person
to lecture anyone
on how to communicate with others.
But I feel like
the distance between us is far greater
than that of everyone else here.
Miss Ririchiyo...
Wh-Which is why tomorrow,
you're joining me for tea.
And I'll make the coffee.
During this time, we will be equals.
You are forbidden to be formal with me.
Wh-What's wrong?
Don't tell me you hate coffee.
No...
My head was just so filled with you
that I lost control of my breath...
You were actually panting.
So you can drink coffee?
Do you like it?
Yes... I do.
I like it.
I really like it.
I love it!
O-Oh, that much?
Yes. If I were to express
it in words, I would say,
As usual, I can only interact with
others in a distorted way.
without it, my world would
be shrouded in darkness.
But today, I feel
That much?!
like I got to know you a little bit.
I could never say enough about it.
If necessary, I could speak of my love
until the night turns to dawn.
You're a little like me,
and that made me happy.
Let the first Ayakashi Kan
partner games begin!
What are we doing?
We're playing games in pairs.
In other words, a fateful moment in time
when the bond between partners is tested.
What the hell are you talking about?
Will he understand me?
Does he actually understand me?
I... I... Oh, I just can't wait!
Next time, on Inu X Boku Secret Service:
Day of the Promise.
Stop ignoring me!
Zange!
Day of the Promise
There will also be a wardrobe malfunction.
Hmph, definitely do watch the next episode, too.