Shisuda Municipal
Elementary School
My name is Gouda Takeo.
I may not look like it, but I'm
a first-year in high school.
He's my friend, Sunakawa Makoto.
I call him "Suna."
We live next to each other,
and we've known each other since kindergarten.
Achoo!
Why are we friends, you ask?
I'm not really sure myself.
Hey.
That guy... Isn't he kinda sketchy?
I wonder if he's up to something.
Get off this train at the next station!
Thank you.
That was when I fell in love.
Her name is Yamato Rinko.
However...
I'll get going.
Huh?
You're leaving?!
It seems she's fallen in love with Suna, not me.
Well, throughout my long history with Suna,
that's been a common occurrence.
4/23 Yamato Rinko
Subject: Morning~
Morning!
Today's another nice day.
I hope you'll have a good day, Gouda-kun!
*blush*
And I've made a decision!
I'm going to be their cheerleader,
to ensure they can have a
successful relationship!
My Romance
One more round!
So, in this fashion,
Japan modernized, following the
Meiji government's inception...
The Charter Oath of Five Articles
illuminates the Meiji government's basic policies.
Stare!
Stare
I can't see...
He's so cool.
I wonder what he's reading.
Hey, isn't he hot?
Really hot!
Try talking to him!
No way!
Stare
So tired.
Oh, what a handsome man.
Stare
Cool!
I don't get it...
How long ago did Suna move here?
We were in kindergarten,
so it must've been over ten years ago.
Even though I've seen him pretty
much every single day,
we've never talked about girls,
so I have no idea what kind of girl he likes.
I don't get it!
Suna...
What kind of girl do you like?
In order to help Yamato's feelings bear fruit,
I must know!
Hey!
Suna, I'm coming in.
Dude, you always say that after you've come in!
What's with your getup?
I just took a bath.
Wow, you're early.
You're studying?
But it isn't like we have an exam.
Takeo, you know you're supposed
to study every day, right?
So?
Suna, I know this is sudden,
but what kind of girl do you like?
That sure is sudden.
Let's talk AKB. Who do you like there?
Sorry, I'm not familiar with celebrities.
What if you had to choose between
Sayla-san and Fraw Bow?
We're doing anime now?
Okay, then what about the Song
Lady or the Exercise Lady?
Maybe the Exercise Lady.
What about between Main-chan and Sui-chan?
Main who?
So the Exercise Lady, huh...
Wait, that's your conclusion?
But...
Which one is Yamato-san?
Th-Thank you.
Thank you.
You're a hard one to read, you know.
When it comes to girls you like,
you're like an open book.
You like anyone with whom you
have a halfway decent chance.
You like girls who smile a lot
and get along with everyone.
The cute ones.
He might be right...
Suna, let's get some air.
Huh?
It looks like a butt every time, all right.
Oh, this is a guy's butt.
Hey, it's a guy's butt, right?
I wonder why I never saw that before...
I've been looking at it for over ten years, too.
Suna, do you have a girlfriend?
What's with you today, man?
You're asking that while looking at the butt tree...
Do you?
No.
Why not?
You're popular with the ladies!
You never think about dating girls?
You're way too close, man
I dunno...
It makes me tired.
Huh?
When I think about what I'd have to do
if I dated anyone, it makes me tired.
What?!
It should make you happy!
Are you sure you have a pair?
Sure.
Then why aren't you interested in girls?
I never said I wasn't.
Then you are interested!
Seriously, you're too close
Sure, as much as any other guy.
Okay, got it!
There's hope!
What's wrong?
Suna, a word of advice.
If you find girls tiring,
refrain from acting in ways
that make them fall for you.
I don't think I'm going out of
my way to act like that.
Even so, restrain yourself!
Got it?
Response?
Okaaay.
Say, "Okay!"
Okay.
Put more feeling into it!
The first basic sentence structure in English
grammar consists of a subject and a verb.
It's a complete sentence, not requiring
an object or complement.
Sentence Structure #1
Stay awake, okay?
In such a sentence, the verb
needs to be intransitive...
4/24 Yamato Rinko
Subject: Hello
Hello!
It's Yamato.
I baked the sachertorte.
Can I come over tomorrow, so you can have it?
What's with her text?
It's...
real colorful...
An example would be "I go."
A-n-y t-i-m-e w-o-r-k-s.
Next, let's discuss the sentence
"I go to the park on foot."
Great!
Thanks!
Can I call you "Takeo-kun"??
Holy crap! The crap moves!
T-h-e-n I w-i-l-l c-a-l-l y-o-u "Y-a-m-a-t-o," t-o-o.
Sent!
Yamato-san is a nice girl,
and Suna's a nice guy, too.
They make a great couple.
Song
Exercise
Let's go!
I have to come, too?
Come on...
So...
This way. Let's hurry.
Why me, too?
Don't ask questions.
Just be yourself.
What are you talking about?
Trust me!
Oh, hello!
Hi.
Good.
Leave it to me!
So good!
So this is sacherotote!
sacherotote
sachertorte
I've never had a more delicious chocolate cake!
I'm amazed you can eat so much of it.
You'll get fat.
It's okay. I work out!
Dude, stuffing yourself and working out
would make you a sumo wrestler.
Hup!
Sumo wrestler, huh?
You honor me.
It wasn't meant as a compliment, but okay.
I'm gonna get something to drink.
Oh, sorry.
I should have thought of that.
Want anything?
I'll get something for you, too.
I'll go with you.
No need.
Well done, Suna.
Subtle!
Suna's cool.
You think so, right?
Um, sure.
Of course you do.
We met when we were three,
so we've known each other for over a decade.
But he's always been a great guy.
When we were in kindergarten, I played
the main part in a class play.
It was The Red Ogre Who Cried.
The Red Ogre Who Cried
I think Takeo-kun should play the Red Ogre!
Ditto!
Okay, I'm gonna do this!
I'll be the Red Ogre!
The Red Ogre Who Cried
The Red Ogre
Who Cried
As the Blue Ogre, Suna was
a child prodigy at acting,
and made all the moms cry.
My acting was more on the dumb side.
The boy playing the Red Ogre looks really strong.
When we were in first grade,
I accidentally peed in my pants during cleanup
Nooooo!
because I always used to
hold it till the last second.
Crap!
Pfft
Suna was in stitches,
but he soaked himself with a
bucketful of water with me,
so no one else found out.
And the time I got so excited on a field trip
that I flipped over my bento box...
Suna was all in stitches again,
but he gave me more than half his bento.
More than half!
Oh.
Man, why is it that when I try to talk
about what a great guy Suna is,
I have to discuss all the embarrassing
things in my past?
Um...
Is something wrong?
Oh, no.
Keep it together!
You decided to cheer them on, didn't you?
Yamato!
Yes?
Suna likes the Exercise Lady,
and he's interested in girls.
Oh, I see.
Yeah.
He doesn't have a girlfriend!
Is there anything else?
How do you help people in things like this?
Hmm?
I think I just tasted something
that isn't chocolate.
Oh! That's the prize!
I put in one prize!
Yay, a prize!
Prize?
O-Oh... Yeah, the prize... is a chestnut.
A chestnut...
Yeah, I mean you just get to eat it, but...
I see, a prize.
It's good!
Can I bake something again?
Sure.
Oh.
Here.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Oh, I should pay you back!
Don't worry about it.
You're always baking for us.
No, please!
Letting things like this slide doesn't feel right.
Oh, okay.
Thanks, then.
It's going to be okay!
You two make a great couple, Yamato.
Well, thanks for the cake.
You're welcome.
Oh, um...
Well, uh...
Can I text you again?
Like, when I want to ask you what kind
of cakes you like and stuff...
It's going to be okay!
I get you, Yamato!
Sure!
I've got your back!
Suna, give her your info, too!
Huh, why?
I mean is that okay?
I guess, sure.
Oh, okay then...
Did you get it?
Yeah.
Okay, see you later.
Sure.
Yamato!
See you later!
Yeah, till next time!
Take care on your way home!
Dude, not so loud.
Okay!
Yamato!
Takeo-kun...
Go... Hurry!
You've got this.
I see...
It never works because, in this kind of
situation, I go to the falling beam...
That's why...
I can't be the knight in shining armor...
Well, that's okay.
At least she'll be okay.
That's all... that matters, right?
Be more careful, will you?
If it'd landed on anyone else,
they'd be dead.
Secure the cables, quick!
Suna, you...
I'm... actually...
pretty strong...
Takeo-kun, you're bleeding!
Oh, it's nothing.
Wait!
Do I have it?
I think I do!
Yay!
I do!
Now that I think about it,
you're always helping me...
Thank you.
Takeo...
Takeo.
Takeo!
You've walked into a pole.
Perm
Haircut
Good Evening
That isn't a person.
Takeo, you're stuck.
Dude, you'll die for real.
Hey, Takeo!
Pig Gorilla!
Old-Man Face!
Yamato-san.
Those cakes were really good.
Were they?
Yeah.
I see.
I see...
Yamato Rinko
Incoming Call
Damn.
I have to keep my crap together.
I decided to cheer them on.
To help Yamato with her relationship!
Hello?
Oh, Takeo-kun?
Yeah.
Are you doing okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Thank goodness.
Thanks so much for helping me today.
No, thank you.
The cake was great.
Please bake one again.
Sure.
Oh, and, well....
Next time, could it be without Sunakawa-kun?
I... I'd like it to be just the two of us.
Huh?
Oh...
Okay, sure.
Then how about next weekend?
In front of the park fountain again?
Come to think of it,
I haven't really asked Yamato
about her feelings yet.
After seeing Suna so many times,
I'm sure they're solid.
Yamato Rinko
Call Ended
02m 30s
She's finally ready to ask for
advice with her relationship.
My Blue Ogre
Next time: My Blue Ogre.