Kiss Him, Not Me
I'm at a Disadvantage
The usual place.
The usual friends.
The usual conversation.
No, that's not true.
I noticed something's different.
Okay, today's handshake.
So you can get used to me.
Okay.
Okay!
Are you a bit more used to it?
Well, yeah. It's just a handshake.
Then, let's turn it up a notch.
Squeeze
Oh, sorry. Did I surprise
you? It's just a handshake.
Right! Just a handshake!
Wha—
Jeez...
My lord, you're priceless...
Akane-chan, you're priceless...
Kachu Rabu is so deep.
There's so much to it!
And these two have been getting along
real well since their pairing fight.
They're like, really close.
Take this!
Special skill!
Sametora Flame-Horned Slugger!
It's the Sametora Flame-Horned Slugger.
Senpai.
Whenever I see it, I remember
how brave you were.
Oh, no!
You were really cool, too, Senpai!
Are you talking about your battle
against that soldier's ghost
during our pilgrimage?
That's right! Even though
I know it was an illusion...
Serinuma-san! Get a hold of yourself!
Huh? What the... Huh? What was that?
What's the matter?
N-Nothing.
What's wrong with me?
I can't look at his face!
That's right. I've noticed.
It's not the same as before.
Something's even changed
between her and Shinomiya!
I'm the only one falling behind!
As long as Puri Puri Moon is here...
The moon will never be shrouded in darkness!
Let's go!
My advantage was that I kind of
look like Shion from Mirage Saga.
But, since Akane-chan showed up,
Shion's been shifted to the hall of fame,
meaning he's out of the picture.
And something definitely happened
with all of them during that trip.
I've got nothing.
Diamond, let's go! We can't lose this fight.
Right! We'll keep standing up,
no matter how many tries it takes.
In other words, never mind having
an advantage; I'm at a disadvantage.
Onii-chan. Onii-chan, the dance is starting!
Yeah!
I'll be Diamond!
I'll be Ruby, then.
Listen to the feelings in my heart.
I'll be honest about how I feel,
so the most amazing miracle
is sure to happen!
Puri Puri Puri Moon!
Sparkle, shine!
My smile is my gem!
An innocent girl's heart is a full moon.
Every day!
Heart!
Spread your arms wide
and you can fly all the way to the moon!
Puri Puri Puri Moon!
Tomorrow, we'll also be
I'm getting nowhere because I'm dancing
away my Sunday with my little sister!
Onii-chan, I'm hungry.
Oh, should we eat?
How do you want your eggs?
Sunny-side up! Well-done!
Okay!
Next break we have, I'll get myself
a date, no matter what it takes!
Starting tomorrow, I'm going all out!
Senpai!
Can you help my circle out?
Beaten to the punch right away!
Sorry. I'm working every
day during our next break.
Working?
Why the sudden job?
Well...
Next month, the Kachu Rabu
sales marathon starts.
Iga
Ka
DVDs, character song albums, voice actor
events, Kachu Rabu Café, lots of new merch,
a special collab with all convenience stores...
There're even rumors of
a new live stage show!
All these new events are around the corner!
And I've used up the six month advance
on my allowance for our pilgrimage!
Sob Sob Sob
So, for now, I can't go to any events.
In other words, I have no money.
The truth is, I even got an
advance on my New Year's money.
Where is your part-time job?
Usami Land!
I heard they were hiring lots of part-timers!
Part-time Jobs at Usami Land!!
- High school students and older welcome!
- Job assignment decided after interview.
- Paid training.
I got my first choice job,
to work in the Puri Puri Moon show!
I'm playing Ruby.
Yusuke
Male
I'd like to apply for the Puri Moon show.
Manager
Chief
General Affairs
I always watch Puri Moon.
I love it.
Who's your favorite character?
It's gotta be the main
character, Puri Puri Moon.
No, that's the title of the show.
The heroine is Diamond-chan!
You don't watch, do you?
No. But I like it!
Manager
Chief
General Affairs
I have just the job for someone
bold enough to bluff like you.
Igarashi Yusuke, assigned as
an exciting cruise leader!
I'm applying for the Puri Moon show!
But, I have to focus on my circle work,
so I can't really come often.
I often go on overseas trips during breaks,
too, so it'll be hard to find time.
Are you even interested in working?
I've got the perfect kind of shift
work for someone like you, though.
Nishina Shima, assigned to
the pretty boy butler café!
Um, I'd like to apply for the
Puri Puri Moon special show.
But I'm happy working backstage, so—
Forget behind the scenes! I knew the perfect
role for you the moment I saw you!
Shinomiya Hayato, assigned
as Princess Usamimi!
Why?!
I'd like to apply for Puri Moon.
I like kids, so I'd like
to interact with them.
Oh, is that right?
Mutsumi Asuma, assigned to
selling balloons as a mascot.
And now...
I watch Puri Puri Moon every
week with my little sister!
I know all the songs, dances,
and signature phrases!
There's no one better suited
for the Puri Moon show than me!
I-Is that right?
Yes!
Diamond's pose?
As long as Puri Puri Moon's here, the moon
will never be shrouded in darkness!
Dark Prince's pose?
Hmph. Fools!
I shall summon the darkness.
You're hired!
I did it!
Can't wait to work with you, Serinuma!
Iga
Ni
Shi
Mu
Let's do our best!
Yeah, same here!
Finally! I'll definitely get
closer to her this way.
My time has come!
You're going to play the role of
Dark Prince in the Puri Moon show?!
Really?!
That's right!
Amazing! Amazing!
I wanna see! I'm gonna go!
But, that means I need to go to practice
on the weekends and I won't be here.
Will you be okay?
I-I'll be okay! I'm not a kid!
Do your best! I'll be your coach
if there's anything you don't get!
An innocent girl's heart
is a full moon every day.
How was it?
It's okay,
but you need to put your hips into
the Ruby pose to get it perfect.
My hips?
Like this.
Oh, you're right! So cute!
That's Nanashima-kun for you!
Thanks. I'll try that!
Nana's really done well for himself.
An innocent girl's heart is a full moon,
every day!
But, well...
It looks really lame.
Usami Land
Training Center
I see. You know so much about
this because of your little sister.
The story's pretty complex.
You can't underestimate it
just 'cause it's a kids' anime.
I get you! It's really deep!
This is so fun! What fun days we're having.
We get to spend more time
together, and there's no one in our—
Hey!
Let's go home together.
No, I spoke too soon.
Are you done your training, Igarashi-kun?
We've still got more to do, so go on ahead.
No, I'll wait.
Go!
Nope.
Igarashi always comes after
his training is done.
He's a serious pain.
But, who cares about that?
My Lord!
Good night!
Serinuma
"We're meeting tomorrow morning
in front of the ticket gate, right?
See you then!"
This is going great!
Right now...
I'm the closest to Serinuma!
You're leaving already, Onii-chan?
Yeah, I overslept.
A cold?
I fell asleep last night
without drying my hair.
Will you be okay?
I'll be fine! I'm gonna go now!
Usami Land
Training Center
Well then, let's have the poses.
Think of this as a real performance.
Okay!
Puri Puri Moon! Diamond!
Ruby!
Sapphire!
Emerald!
Alexandrite!
Next, it's the prince.
Right.
Huh?
What's this?
My legs feel...
off balance...
Nanashima-kun!
Nanashima-kun? Nanashima-kun?
Huh?
What a relief.
You fainted from a fever, remember?
The director said to go home and rest.
A staff member gave you a ride home.
You'd better eat something
before you take any medicine.
I'll borrow your kitchen.
Puri Puri Moon
Stare...
I-I'm being watched.
Are you Onii-chan's girlfriend?
No, I'm his friend!
We work part-time together!
You mean in the Puri Moon show?!
Are you in it, too?! Who are you playing?!
Um, Ruby.
Ruby's my favorite after Diamond!
B-But that doesn't mean
I'm giving you my brother!
You always take care of
the house on your own?
No. When Mommy and Daddy
aren't around, Onii-chan is here.
Ahem
But, right now he's busy
with the Puri Moon show,
so I told him to put that first!
I see.
I'm the one who taught him the dance,
so you have to try your best as Ruby, too!
Yup!
But Onii-chan is gonna marry me!
Serinuma came to my room.
To my room...
This is the first time I've
been into a boy's room.
Sorry. It's small, isn't it?
No, not at all.
Besides, that means we can be closer.
It makes me happy.
Serinuma.
Nanashima-kun.
Nanashima-kun?
Can you get up at all?
How's your fever?
Kiss Him, Not Me
Huh? They went home already?
Yeah. Dark Prince wasn't feeling
well, so Ruby took him home.
Serinuma-san did?
Wait. What?
H-Huh?
Serinuma.
You're so cute!
N-Nanashima-kun, are you still asleep?
Let go of me!
He won't budge! No way!
Nanashima-kun! Get a hold of yourself!
Nanashima-kun!
Nana!
What the hell are you doing?!
Serinuma-san!
Igarashi? What happened?
I'm sorry!
Hey! You asshole!
I'll kill—
I like you, Serinuma!
Serinuma! I love you!
I love you, Seri—
Take your medicine and wake up!
Huh? That... wasn't a dream?
Nope.
No way! No way, no way!
I have to apologize!
Never mind a step forward,
this is a huge step back.
Kae-chan? She said she's home with a cold.
She didn't tell you?
Serinuma
I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry!
I really wasn't myself!
Seriously, please let me explain!
She's not answering my calls.
She hasn't read any of my messages.
She's ignoring me!
Of course she is.
I wonder if I'll see her
at practice tomorrow.
Who knows?
Ruby apparently has a cold.
Will the performance will be okay?
We'll have to consider a stand-in.
I bet she doesn't want to see me.
Well, of course not,
after what I did to her.
If she won't answer, I can just go to her—
No. I have no right.
I'm home.
Welcome home!
Good luck
Guess what? I drew this!
You can have it!
It looks just like me. You're so good!
This is Dark Prince and this is Ruby.
Show it to the girl from the other day.
It's a good luck charm
so the show will go well!
Kirari, Nii-chan's gonna go out again!
I'll be back soon!
Cut it out! That's not what I meant!
Is that right?
That's not what your
body's saying, Senpai.
S-Stop!
It's so good when it's in BL!
But, when it happens in
reality, it's just scary.
Igarashi-kun
Apparently Nana doesn't remember
a thing because of the fever.
He's not the lying type,
so I think that's the truth.
I hope you at least
understand that much for now.
I understand that.
But...
Kae. You have a visitor downstairs.
Nanashima.
H-Huh? Tell him I'm not home.
Huh? Why should—
Just do it!
I get it already! You can't stay
rolling around in bed forever!
I can't! I can't see him just yet!
Serinuma!
You're there, right?
Just listen to me, please!
I'm really sorry about what happened.
I know it's not much of an excuse,
but I really wasn't myself!
You don't need to forgive me.
S-Stop it!
But, Kirari is really looking forward
to tomorrow's performance!
So, please, at least go to it!
I beg you!
Shut up!
Salt
Why are you yelling in front of our house?!
You're a nuisance!
Go home!
I'm sorry!
Please, give this to Serinuma-san!
This is just unfair.
Ruby's still not here?
Not yet.
We don't have a choice.
Have the stand-in get ready.
I'm sorry!
I'm late.
How do you feel? Are you okay?
Yup. I'm in tip-top form.
Then go get changed.
You really came.
Ah, I'm sorry.
Um, I know you were acting
strange because of your fever,
so don't worry about it.
But, I'm still scared.
Yeah, of course.
But... Thanks for coming.
Winter Break
Puri Puri Moon
Diamond Show
It's packed.
We'll have to stand.
The front seats are
reserved for the little kids.
There are quite a few "big kids," too.
Huh? We lined up properly.
First come, first serve, right?
You have a problem with that?
Th-Then, please watch quietly.
Ugh, those guys are at it again.
Those three really have a bad rep.
All right everyone, let's call for
Puri Puri Moon as loud as we can!
Puri Puri Moon!
Iga
Ni
Mu
Shi
Oh, it's that kind of show.
Puri Puri Moon Moon Puri Moon Moon!
Please sit—
Diamond's panties!
Look over here!
We can't see!
Hey, move!
Diamond-chan!
Diamond!
Puri Puri Moon, it seems I have an enemy
I must deal with before facing you.
How about we call a truce for now?
Nanashima-kun!
This isn't in the script. What should I do?
Let me handle it.
Don't worry about it.
Oh? Puri Puri Moon and the Dark Prince
have formed the Dream Team!
Everyone, let's cheer them on!
Do your best!
Onii-chan!
Now, fools, begone!
What was that?!
Don't get in our way!
Watch out!
Nanashima-kun!
Are you okay?
Serinuma... Thank you.
How dare you touch my Ruby!
I swear I will never again hurt you.
Nanashima-kun... I mean, Dark Prince!
Let's go!
Understood!
Dark Moonlight...
Attack!
Victory for the Dream Team!
Yay!
Good job. Now it's time
for the group dance.
Sorry, Director.
I think I sprained my ankle in that fall.
What about your sub?
I'm the only one here today.
I'll do the dance!
Let me do it!
It's the group dance you've
all been waiting for!
Let's all dance together!
Puri Puri Puri Moon!
Sparkle, shine!
My smile is my gem!
An innocent girl's heart is a full moon.
Every day!
Heart!
Spread your arms wide
and you can fly all the way to the moon!
Puri Puri Puri Moon,
tomorrow we'll also be Puri Puri Puri Moon!
Good job!
Nanashima-kun, I'll believe
what you said out there.
Right. It's a promise.
Onii-chan!
Good job!
I knew it! You were Diamond
during the group dance!
I could tell!
Oh, really?
Good boy! You did well!
Thank you, Kirari.
Wh-What's with that getup?
It's great.
You look cute.
You jerks! I didn't have a choice!
You really do look lame.
Don't say that so earnestly!
I know this really must look so lame, though.
This is why I'm falling behind.
I want some pics. Can you strike a pose?
No way!
Princess Usamimi is a hundred
times better than this.
You're both very cute.
Cute! Er, not. But it's still cute!
You too, Kirari?!
Just cut it out!
Nanashima-kun was really cool today.
Boys can be scary, but they
can also be very dependable!
Isn't that weird?
We're sorry.
Serinuma-san, I put everything
together for the history club,
but I'd like you to draw something.
An illustration? Sure!
What a relief. I'm just terrible at drawing.
Is that right?
You seemed like the kind of
person who could do anything.
That's not true at all.
When I was little, I couldn't
tell my left from my right.
Oh, and I couldn't remember
how to move each shogi piece.
Huh? You play shogi?!
I'm not good at all, though.
December comes in like a tiger! It's here!
Next time:
The Beach! Bathing Suits!
Time to Get Serious!
Look forward to it!
If you ask me, you're the one—