Now, why don't you come with me, tiger boy?
It's happening again.
Yet again, I'm...
Wait.
Weren't you with the Port Mafia?
I'm not.
My name is Kyouka.
I'm with the Agency.
What a barbaric nation.
For such a young girl to be so...
You, wait!
Oh, dear.
I've been looking for you.
Where were you all this time?
In alleyways and slums.
Where I used to be.
But I didn't belong there anymore.
I called the city police
from the shop phone.
It won't be so easy for the
Guild with the police around.
Kyouka-chan...
You could have stayed out of the war
if you just stayed missing.
The Agency is my only home.
Kyouka will soon kill many people.
So long as her abilities are
darkly entangled within her soul,
she will never escape the darkness.
For the first time in my life,
I aspire to be something.
So I will fight.
Even if that means I have to use
everything that lurks within me.
They're here.
Excuse me.
What happened?
We were attacked with weapons.
What?
Captain!
Unit 07 here, calling headquarters.
Headquarters.
Your location?
Dock Three.
We have information that a serial
murderer is on the loose in that area.
A girl of fourteen, dressed in Japanese clothes.
I repeat.
We have information that a serial
murderer is on the loose in that area.
A girl of fourteen, dressed in Japanese clothes.
How old are you, miss?
Headquarters, we—
Captain!
How could you do that?
Hang in there, Captain!
Requesting backup!
Flawless.
Even the target's escape
measures are accounted for.
Miss Louisa's strategy proposals
are perfect, as always.
Guild Operative
Mark T.
Ability: Huck Finn
& Tom Sawyer
Bullseye.
It won't kill you, since it's a rubber
bullet, but it's painful as hell.
Good work, Mark.
Well then, my little princess,
I'm taking your boyfriend.
No!
Anything but that!
Mr. Herman.
Understood.
Guild Operative
Herman M.
Ability:
Moby Dick
It's been a long time, my friend.
We've only just met,
but allow me to give you some
life advice, my little princess.
You aren't cut out for helping people.
I assume you understand
what you are cut out for.
Why?
Why did you show me the light?
Why did you give me hope?
Hands up!
You're under arrest on
suspicion of serial murder.
Goodbye.
Episode 20
Though the Head May Err
Please don't give me any more light.
And a week has passed...
Let's play.
What should we do?
It's so fun being outside.
There's one!
Hey, Mister, let's have fun.
You're from the Guild, aren't you?
Have fun?
With a child?
Here you are, a dachshund.
No thanks.
Okay, now it's my turn.
Boop, boop, boop!
Ta-da.
Look, you get that handprint
when you hurt me.
Now, show me, Mister...
Show me complete madness.
I don't get it.
Is this what you mean by madness?
You've been sleeping well, pastor.
Lord Francis.
How do you feel?
Where's Margaret?
In critical condition.
She may never wake up.
What a foolish woman.
She protected me in the end.
That's how I survived.
Margaret said she would take
back her family's honor.
So why...
She joined the operation in
order to repay her family's
massive debt and re-establish
their reputation.
Alas, that's nothing more
than a fleeting dream.
It was never fleeting.
Not until you made it so, Lord Francis.
What?
I will depend on you no longer.
I will take back her honor myself.
Ms. Louisa.
Show me the emergency plan.
But that plan will cause a
lot of collateral damage.
It'll turn Yokohama into a sea of flames.
Everything here belongs to me.
The ship, the desk, the pens,
the window dressing...
And you and my other people, too, of course.
Thus, I won't allow my people
to be hurt any more.
As you are my property,
I have the right to protect you.
Notify everyone that the
emergency plan is in effect.
Y-Yes, sir.
I'll end this in the blink of an eye.
Dachshund.
Hey, how's it coming?
My body...
It hurts.
Well, if you're looking for someone to blame,
try the officers who made this emergency plan,
or yourself for coming up with the foolish
idea of trying to destroy Lovecraft's mind.
I'll kill you.
I'll kill you!
Ow!
Are you enjoying your
cruise on the Moby Dick?
Excuse me.
Why is she here?
Oh, Ms. Lucy?
She has no strategic value, given that her
trick's known now, but she insisted on staying.
Now, where were we?
We're looking for a book.
A book?
There's only a single copy in the world.
It's said to be impervious to any degree
of firepower or special abilities.
Someone with a gift foresaw that it would
be found sealed away here in Yokohama.
What does that book have to do with me?
You're literally the tiger
beetle... The guide post.
In fact, I brought you here because
I couldn't have you turning to ashes
along with the rest of the city.
What?
The Gifted Special Operations
Division is neutralized.
All that's left is the Armed Detective
Agency and the Port Mafia.
These two organizations
happen to be quite a pain.
We've decided to burn down the entire city.
It'll make our search easier as well.
No one has such a powerful gift!
Does this not look familiar?
Said emergency plan is, basically,
a combo of our two abilities.
My gift gives me the ability to share
senses between a host and other trees,
across my vines.
I've connected every tree
in Yokohama to you.
The unwitting go on as usual,
walking on the roots,
hitting the trunks,
and cutting down branches.
That pain is being sent
into you as we speak.
Now, it's time for a quiz.
What do you think will happen to the city
if you engage your curse right now?
The moment I rip this doll's head off,
roughly 20 percent of the town will be cursed.
This is the emergency plan.
Also known as the Yokohama
Incineration Operation.
Your town will be destroyed,
all because of you.
Why?
I never asked for this ability.
So why do all these terrible
things happen because of me?
Isn't everyone equal in
the eyes of the Lord?
You're right.
But this is the world we live in.
So let me tell you the truth:
God exists.
But He doesn't love you.
No!
No! No!
I'll burn this world down!
I'll curse it!
Say, dear.
Yes?
Did you always have that scar?
Looks like it's begun.
All I need to do now is to destroy
this doll and trigger the ability.
Okay!
I surrender!
The Agency and I will help
you unconditionally.
So please don't destroy the doll!
I see.
That is an interesting proposal.
Very well. Let's form a
cooperative framework.
But only with the survivors.
Damn, traffic jam.
It's so peaceful.
How is it peaceful?
What the hell?!
Minoura-san!
Let me out!
Damn it.
The city... I need to do something.
Oh my, I came to check on you
on my way to the garbage.
This is a pleasant sight.
You're...
Please.
Let me out of here.
No way.
I hate privileged people like you.
Maybe you'll know how I feel
when the city burns down and you're
discarded like this useless doll.
I know your pain well.
Don't talk like you know!
Have you washed dishes all
day with bloody fingers?
Have you ever been tortured
with a hot iron poker?
Do you have any idea how much pain
and agony these scars give me?
On the first day, it's the bone that hurts.
But it's the third day
that it hurts the most.
The burn chafes every time you move.
It hurts like hell.
I was there, too.
I know your fear and loneliness well.
But loneliness wasn't a king
lording over us forever.
Loneliness is just a soft, puffy cloud
forming and vanishing on a whim.
Many people on the ground
carry wounds the way we do.
Abandon them, and you're
abandoning your past self.
Is that what you want?
Where am I?
It's too late.
Yokohama's done.
No, there's still a way.
Dazai-san only needs to touch
the doll to end the curse.
Are you stupid?
We're in the sky.
How do you think you're
going to give him the doll?
I see.
You're doing it.
You'll get shot and killed by anti-air guns.
Or you'll hit the ground and die.
Or you'll get shredded up by
the madmen on the ground.
You know those are your only options,
and you're still going to do it.
There was an old book at the orphanage.
It said, "I've never regretted
anything I've done."
"I've only ever regretted the
things that I didn't do."
What was the name of the author?
It's a parachute.
I kept one hidden in case
I needed to escape.
I connected the white door
to Moby Dick's plating.
Really?
The Guild won't let you
off for letting me go.
I've always been lonely.
Besides, as long as I'm
in this room, I'm safe.
Hey, are you really going to be safe?
I know you're invulnerable in this room.
But doesn't that mean you
can never leave this room?
You're so dense.
It's just an excuse.
Live.
And save me from this place someday.
I'll be waiting.
All right.
The tiger has escaped.
To your stations!
I repeat.
The tiger has escaped.
Prepare anti-air cannons.
It's...
Control the traffic!
We won't have anywhere left to do business.
Protect it with your life!
I see.
So that's what's happening.
Now, then.
Mark here can hit a falling
target, no problem.
Peek-a-boo.
What the...
Tom has captured the target.
Good boy, Tom!
All right, Huck, load the second shell.
Yes, sir.
Trajectory and firing velocity, check.
Compensating for relative velocity
with target body, check.
Huck's shot ripped through the parachute.
Yeah!
So, how's the tiger boy?
Passed out from the blast.
It looks like he's going to hit the
ground and be smashed to bits.
What happened to your order not to kill him?
I'm sure his own country's gifteds will
figure it out, as long as his body's still there.
So I really am no use.
There's nothing I can do.
It's you.
Of course.
You despise me, don't you?
I hate me, too.
Thanks for everything.
I'm alive.
I have to deliver it!
I need to stop it immediately.
Amazing.
He survived a huge fall, and my rain of
bullets won't so much as scratch him.
I guess he's that desperate
to deliver that gross doll.
This isn't a hunt, then.
This is a duel between two men.
What?
Has that thing always been here?
I don't recommend losing
your focus, tiger boy.
There's no telling from which
way trouble will come.
An oil truck!
It's over.
Stop resisting.
You've reached your limit.
Shut up.
You win, Atsushi-kun.
Dazai-san...
It's dangerous here.
They'll shoot you from above.
I wonder about that.
Smoke?
That's not all.
Heat sensors and radars disabled.
It's a sensor jammer.
He's been setting them up all over town
believing he'd be coming with the doll?
You got me.
Good job, Atsushi-kun.
Yokohama is saved.
Or so I wish.
But as long as the enemy have Q,
they'll repeat this carnage
as many times as they need.
Now, what do we do?
Dazai-san, I'm reminded of a line
from a book I read a long time ago.
"The head may err, but never the blood."
I have an idea.
It may seem out of the
question to everyone else.
Yet to me, to my blood and soul,
it seems like the only correct answer.
What's the idea?
An alliance.
They're the most powerful in Yokohama,
and they're trying to defend this city.
There's no better organization to
help us in our fight against the Guild.
And which organization is that?
Episode Twenty-One
Double Black
The Port Mafia.
"The head may err, but never the blood." -
Nakajima Atsushi, in Light, Wind and Dreams