Galactic Imperial Calendar, Year 211
This is the first time you've been
here, isn't it, Highness?
I've heard lots of stories about it.
It's in textbooks, too.
It's Rune light!
Is that it?
Yes, that's Sakimori Academy.
Where our empire began.
And a land of curses and blessings.
Inuzuka-senpai...
What am...
What am I gonna do?
I'm not picking up any radio signals.
Tetraxion particle interference?
Calculating our location based
on the position of artificial
satellites, this is the site of an old gravity reactor explosion.
An area with a radius of 100 km was
quarantined as a contaminated zone.
Communications gear unusable.
No spare air, either.
The conclusion I'm led to is...
What am I thinking?
It's not like I have
a reason to live.
This is Captain Cain of
the Dorssian Lunar Orbital Forces,
tasked with the extermination of
the Class 7 Special Hazard Organisms.
We will now tow Module 77
to Dorssia Sphere #1.
We finally got our hand
on one of these things,
so why aren't we allowed to pilot it?
They say that no one but
those students can pilot them.
Come on, that's a lie.
I saw Captain Cain piloting one.
Oh, you did?
So, this is a Valvrave. I've never
seen one up close before.
What do you say?
Would you care to try piloting it?
I do wish you would relax.
As long as we are
following Council policy
of keeping the Magiuses
a secret, we are friends.
Friends?
Yes. Friends.
It is an enemy machine,
but it is a thing of beauty.
Quit screwing around, Sashinami!
As long as we have no proof that you're
human, I can't let you aboard this shuttle.
Don't give me that crap!
What do you think Inuzuka-senpai
was trying to prove when he protected you?!
And I'm grateful to him. But
I can't accept your whole story yet.
You stubborn broad!
There are a lot of people
that I have to keep safe!
You betrayed our trust. Do you
have any idea how much Haruto—
Come on, that's enough!
But she's—
Sashinami made the call that
she had to make as a leader, that's all.
Yamada, did you have
a better idea at the time?
I didn't have any choice.
How can I trust someone who lied to me?
This one's no good, either?
If I can pick up a different
satellite, maybe we can—
You're wasting your time.
30 minutes of air left, huh?
Saki Rukino. You were
there too, weren't you?
The person who shot
my eye out was...
It's exactly as you imagine.
The L-elf who shot out your eye
was body-jacked at the time.
Just as I thought.
L-elf, you...
This country has changed.
The Dorssia Military
Pact Federation...
Initially, it was an organization
dedicated to military mutual
assistance meant to stand up
to more developed countries.
But now, it's a political power
player that pursues interests
and power just as much as
ARUS. No, even more so.
A former prince certainly has
a higher perspective on such matters.
It is not because I am royalty
that I am lamenting that fact.
It is because I am
a Dorssian citizen.
That, L-elf, is why I am gathering power
with the intent of liberating Dorssia.
I know full well that it is
a grandiose dream. Nevertheless...
No, it's not that, A-drei.
I'm laughing because
I plan to liberate it, too.
I was the one who lost faith.
L-elf. I found a signal flare!
You can repair it, can't you?
We can use this to call for help.
Impossible. Not without
a piezoelectric fuse.
You want to be rescued?
Why are you trying to survive?
Because all our schoolmates
are in danger!
We have to get back there right away!
You're still spewing that nonsense?
You've been abandoned.
By even Shoko Sashinami.
The only ones who eat humans are
you and the other monsters!
Don't touch me, you liar!
All this time...
You've been lying to me.
Y-You're wrong!
It... it was because
Shoko's the prime minister!
That's why she—
Learn when to give up!
Haruto Tokishima. There's no
going back to the way things were.
You are a monster!
An enemy of humanity!
You're wrong!
You're the enemy of
Shoko Sashinami!
You're wrong!
How am I wrong?
Face reality!
You're the ones
who created that reality!
This all happened
because you attacked us!
Don't try to shift the blame!
Every choice was made by you!
Crap!
All I do is lose people
that are precious to me!
Inuzuka-senpai,
Marie, even Aina-chan!
All because...
All because of you!
You're not the only one who
lost someone! I lost Lieselotte!
Don't think for a minute
that you're the only one
who's allowed to dream of a future!
You don't have a shot with her now.
You killed Shoko Sashinami's father.
In the battle before we
arrived in lunar orbit,
you annihilated the enemy's fleet, remember?
Shoko Sashinami's father was
aboard one of the ships.
Why didn't you tell me?
What good would it have done?
You only would have
tortured yourself over it.
I didn't know, and I...
Give up on her. It's impossible
to repair that relationship.
Not for someone who's a monster
and her father's killer.
Don't get the wrong idea.
Without the Valvrave,
you can't possibly beat me!
Yamada, if the Allied Forces attack,
will you still defend
Sashinami and the others?
I ain't gonna act like
I ain't the kind of guy
who picks and chooses who he helps.
Ain't that right, Inuzuka-senpai?
Is apple okay?
Yes, sorry.
It's okay. If you're
hungry, just say so.
Say, Shoko... Did we
do something wrong?
What did we do
that was so bad?
Nothing. We didn't do
anything wrong at all.
I guess you're right...
We can't afford to let
the Valvraves sit idle.
Haruto isn't coming back.
So that means I...
"Do you resign as a human being?"
Hurry up and press "Yes"!
Haruto isn't piloting me, so I'm hungry!
Starving, starving, starving!
Haruto?
Haruto pressed the "Yes" button?
Yes. He wanted revenge.
He said he wanted to get revenge.
For someone named Shi... Shoko, I think.
Give up my humanity?
That's right. This won't
work if you're still human.
What won't work?
The Valvraves?
Yeah. Where did I put it?
It was on the first day, so...
Found it!
Work! Work! You're
a weapon, aren't you?!
I have to avenge Shoko! Please!
Haruto, you didn't...
You did it for me?
Please don't do this! I won't
let you touch the Valvraves!
Haruto...
You've gotten on my nerves
from the day I first met you.
You're always looking
down on everyone!
You and your "halfsies"!
You talk just like Lieselotte!
If you're so smart, why did
we get into this mess?
If I'd had a Valvrave,
I would have saved Lieselotte!
You monster!
What are you so desperately
trying to survive for?
Your survival means
the devouring of many human lives!
If you insist on spouting
idealistic crap about wanting to
save others, die here so you
won't cause any more suffering!
Your princess was
a "monster" just like me!
What?
Lieselotte was a Magius.
What a pathetic lie.
If she were a Magius,
she wouldn't have been held prisoner!
She had sided with humanity.
That's why she had a falling
out with the Council.
Council?
An organization that keeps the existence of
Magiuses secret from the world.
Preposterous.
Could an individual
have built the Phantoms
and gotten the UN to take action?
The girl you fell in love with
was a Magius.
Shut up!
She was ageless, had lived
far longer than you,
and was a monster who fed on human life force!
Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut your mouth!
Lieselotte, I can't believe
that you were a Magius...
An ageless being who had
lived for centuries.
The top of the food chain.
I can't believe I had been
trying to save someone like you.
What a joke!
Tears...
Oh, right... It's because
I made him sad...
And not just L-elf.
Is that why I'm being punished?
Don't you think you've
done enough, Haruto?
Senpai?
Hey, you've done
more than enough.
It's okay to finally rest,
don't you think?
That world is nothing
but suffering, you know?
Have I done all I could?
Yeah. You put up a good fight.
Thank you.
I'm sure that I wanted
to hear someone say that.
Me?!
I had it all wrong, thinking
you were being held prisoner.
Because you were
one of them all along!
She had sided with humanity.
That's why she had a falling
out with the Council.
You're wrong. Lieselotte really
was being held prisoner.
What reason could she have had
for siding with humanity?
The only clue is Lieselotte's words.
Her actions.
She worked with the Royalists
and assisted us.
I've had enough.
I'm just going to pack it in here.
So you're dying for nothing.
You gave it everything you had, even
becoming a Kamitsuki.
But it was all for nothing.
You're wrong.
So what was I even
born for, anyway?
To have my body tinkered with
and be used as a lab rat?
You're wrong.
To pilot a Valvrave?
To kill people?
Of course not!
Why, then?
Why did Lieselotte, who had
probably lived for centuries as
a Magius, side with humanity?
What happened to you?
Michael...
You are very young, aren't you?
But there is no path
ahead of us to travel down yet.
Wait, were you trying to
create a path?
For both human and Magius?
My Runes are almost gone.
I'm out of time.
That's exactly why. Let's at least
go out kicking and screaming.
There is something left
that you can do, isn't there?
I can't spend my life with you anymore.
But I can carry on your dream.
When I was prepared
to die, I felt free.
I don't care what
anyone else thinks of me.
What matters is
what I want to do!
That's why...
...I can't die yet!
L-elf!
What was that?
What just happened?
Haruto Tokishima,
what was that just now?
I don't know.
But that light, it was...
Yes, it looked just
like Cain's light.
True, it should come as no surprise that a Kamitsuki
would be capable of the
same feats as a Magius...
L-elf. Do you think we can use
this power to save ourselves?
It might be able to ignite
the signal flare you found!
L-elf. I really do care
about everyone at school.
I want to laugh with them again.
We'll build a place where human
and Kamitsuki can live together.
Yeah. This time, it won't
be a replacement for JIOR.
We'll create a country
for us and by us.
The light that Cain produced
was probably Runes.
The key to triggering them is
information in the form of speech.
Like a magic spell?
But I don't...
You spoke words that were
close to being a spell.
It wasn't perfect, but they were
words close enough to trigger it.
Even if we send up a signal flare,
it doesn't mean it will be
an ally who comes for us.
It's a gamble.
One with rather poor odds.
But they aren't zero.
L-elf. Together.
Right.
As I said, I...
...can't die yet.
A world where human and
Kamitsuki can live together, huh?
It's going to be a long fight.
It's all right.
You have an idea?
Nope.
Hey, now.
I'm saying that we'll all
think of something together.
The students, you mean?
The whole world.
To do that, they have to know about
the Magiuses and the Council of 101.
I follow you. Expose the truth of
the world, in other words.
Hiding the truth caused
nothing but misery.
L-elf.
What?
There's nothing else that
you're hiding from me?
There is.
Me, too.
Someone's coming!
I see it.
Class 7 Special Hazard Organism
and deserter located!
Will now exterminate in accordance with
UN Harmful Organism Control Law!
From beginning to end,
we were a terrible team.
Well, we're polar opposites.
Unit 4?!
Miss Rukino?
Haruto! L-elf!
I found you again!
It's a Class 7 Special Hazard
Organism! Shoot it down!
Haruto Tokishima.
Let's forge a new pact.
To expose the truth of the world.
You're wrong, L-elf.
This isn't a pact.
This is a promise.
L-elf, H-neun, and now you...
What on earth is going on?
This isn't a betrayal.
This is punishment
directed at me.
Next time, episode 23.
"The Operation to Retake Module 77."
Valvrave the Liberator...
The system that will expose
the truth of the world.