during my forlorn years in this world
Saitama Hundred Poets Tournament
We appreciate all your help, Mrs. Oe.
Please!  Call me Rieko!
Kana-chan, do we really have to
wear hakama for every tournament?
Of course!
It's a Mizusawa High School
Karuta Club tradition.
What?
In that case,
I should probably learn how
to put one on by myself.
Desktomu-kun!
Oe Traditional Clothing
offers lessons for wearing hakama!
Oe Traditional Clothing offers a new line
of cotton hakama for competitive karuta!
Er, u-uh...
This will be my first official
match after making Class A
that isn't limited to high schoolers.
First, you need to win!
After that, your goal is to win the
whole thing so you can advance in rank!
Let's get serious!
Yeah!
Mashima, you're fired up.
So am I.
Me too!
Are you nervous, Chihaya-chan?
Shouldn't you be used to
playing in tournaments?
K-Kana-chan, I feel like
a rookie out of high school in
his first major league game!
Huh?
Class A is completely different
from the lower classes.
This is what I've always wanted:
to play in a Class A tournament.
Chihaya Furu
Verse 18
The
Plum
Blossoms
Still
Smell
the
Same
My first Class A match...
Chihaya-chan, stop taking
cards with your speed.
This will lead me to the Queen...
but I need to win my first match.
Oh, that's a pretty hakama.
Huh?
I love how colorful your hakama is.
Thank you very much...
If I were a little younger,
I would love to wear a colorful hakama.
Y-You look adorable!
I know.
She knows.  Oh...
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
My opponent in the first round.
Kanai Sakura-san.
I can't let my nerves
get the better of me.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
Stay calm.
Today, my goal is to not move too fast
and not make faults.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
Play a balanced style
that allows me to take
cards from both sides
of the opponent's field.
When I must hide these burning feelings,
I screwed up!  I totally screwed up!
Wow, you're so fast.
Young people have such
excellent reflexes.
I can't keep up.
I feel as though my body is
on fire with Ibuki mugwort
Though my hatred...
Ah!  That's the wrong card!  A fault!
Wow,
you really have fast reflexes.
People with fast reflexes tend to mix up
similar-sounding first syllables.
Lucky me.
I see.
She's right.
Fast reflexes and sharp ears
can be powerful tools,
but they can also cause mistakes.
Stop concentrating on speed.
That's why Dr. Harada told me to stop.
While it pains me...
Lucky me!
The tail feathers of...
I wish I could show...
Lucky me!
You let me take another card.
and I have yet to visit Amanohashidate
or read my mother's letters
I'm having trouble attacking her...
Why?
Lucky me!
I get to play a girl who only has speed.
Why did she have to say that?
My goal today was to not move too fast.
have been soaked red with tears of blood
Would this old palace courtyard...
A dead card!
be as dear now, those
were the good old days
Since I could not hide my love,
Dead card!
Impassioned vows exchanged...
Again?
Look for the sound...
Another dead card!
I know that my heart...
Five dead cards in a row.
and by no fault of mine
Nobody wishes to see the
beautiful cherry blossoms
The next card has to be one in play.
The next card...
I really want to move!
covered by the smoky mountain fog
So the flower has wilted during
Seven dead cards in a row!
the long spring rains, just
as my beauty has faded
A fault...
You couldn't hold yourself back, huh?
Lucky me.
Then I'll send you
the red that is the Tatsuta River
this card.
She sent me the "Impassionate gods" card...
I can do this!
I'm gonna take the next card.
While it brings me no joy...
Take the next card!
I'm in luck again.
I should have been able
to take that card.
If I'd been ready to move back from
"While it may" to "While it brings"...
I have faster reflexes!
Stay calm...
This may be my first Class A match,
but I can't lose!
If I'm not the strongest
female Class A player,
I don't even get to challenge the Queen!
If I lose here, I can never
take on Shinobu-chan!
This is no fun.
Huh?
Ayase-san, it feels like you're
only playing against the cards.
it is as though pearls have been
strung across the autumn plain
She sent me "Since the," which is a
one-syllable card now because
"Since I could" not hide has been read.
I was hoping to take
that card from her...
She's so hard to play against...
She's making it hard for
me to play against her?
Right, she also sent "Impassionate."
The opponent's right side
doesn't have many cards left.
Her cards are positioned
to prevent me from
using my speed effectively.
Wow, you really have fast reflexes.
Ayase-san, it feels like you're
only playing against the cards.
She addresses me by name
and watches how I play.
Vs. Ayase
Ayase
Komano
1) The "Impassionate" card in my right middle row is taken by Ayase.
She sends "The sound of people" from her right lower row to my right lower row.
2) I take "In order to" from her right middle row.
"In order for" is on my side and Ayase was focused on taking that card from me.
I send "I feel as" from my right middle side to her right middle side.
But you have trouble with
three-syllable cards,
so I would place those cards in
region B and constantly attack them.
I'm sure you'll come up against people
who use these strategies.
Excuse me.
I have a habit of going for every card
as though it were a one-syllable card.
That's why I end up using too much force.
In that case, I should
move back my start line.
Just a little bit.
Find the position that
lets me take the lead at the goal line!
Oh, she moved back?
She was on the edge of
the boundary before.
Ten centimeters?
No, she moved back fifteen centimeters.
Can she still reach the cards?
She must have a plan.
I love it!
Youth is a wonderful thing!
Said night was young when
the false rooster's crow
Whoa!  A dead card!
That was close.
But I can reach the farthest
row on both sides.
Her arm is so long.
She can easily reach
any spot on the field.
If she finds her rhythm...
I'm moving a card.
Huh?
She moved "Said bed" as soon
as it became a one-syllable card!
Keep worrying your pretty little head.
So innocent and cute!
I feel as though I am...
Lucky me.
The emotions experienced...
I have to take the cards
that are there for me.
The cards that are there for her?
Is this all part of her plan?!
She finally noticed...
Her karuta has something that mine lacks.
I need to watch her play.
Figure out what Sakura-san
has that I don't.
The way she's been watching me play.
banish any lingering memories of the past
My fear is not of...
Oh.
We used the same three-syllable
timing to take the card,
But since we touched it at the same time,
it's mine.
Three-syllable timing...
Timing...
Timing!
There's another way to play karuta!
A way that doesn't rely on speed!
The way Sakura-san plays!
In order for us to find our way home,
Thank you very much.
I lost by six cards...
Kanai Sakura-san!
Oh!
Yes?
Th-They're adorable!
I know.
So she knows.  Oh...
Thank you very much for your help today!
I'll do my best to become a player
that doesn't rely on speed!
I want to become Queen!
Oh, dear.  So do I.
Huh?
Does it sound strange coming from
an old lady who's been
playing karuta for 35 years?
35 years?!
20 years ago, I was much cuter
and considered a karuta idol like you.
Not a karuta idol
I've never won any major tournaments,
and no matter how hard I try,
I keep losing to younger players.
But I love karuta.
I still dream about becoming Queen.
What?  Then I also want to become Queen!
Me too!
Oh?  That makes us rivals then.
I'll see you at the East qualifier.
And so, I had just lost
my first Class A match,
yet I had no idea that I was
about to experience the
worst moment of my life.
The Class B final is
between Taichi and Porky!
The Class D final is between
Desktomu-kun and Kana-chan!
The other four members of
the Mizusawa karuta club
trumped their captain
by reaching the finals!
Wh-Who do I...
Which match do I watch?!
Who do I root for?!
What should I do as their captain?!
Retro-kun!
Y-You were in this tournament.
How did you do?
I didn't do anything!
I ran into Mashima in the first round
and lost by three cards...
I had all the momentum!
This is what it means to win
the battle, but lose the war!
What about the other Hokuo members?
Amakasu-senpai and the
others already left.
I lost, so I'm leaving.
I'm going to take whatever
I can from the winners!
Next month is the East Master qualifier.
This may be my last chance
to advance in rank.
I have to win here!
I bet that's what Mashima's
thinking right now.
I'm not too interested
in the Master final,
but I can't let Mashima beat me!
I admire Kana-chan.
Her elegant playing
style, her tenacity...
and she has the stats to show for it.
She averages 0.6 faults a match.
During practice, she comes
back to win 74% of the time.
Due to her size,
she rarely goes on the attack.
Her personality makes her
more defense-minded.
Gulp.
I know Kana-chan!
I can beat her!
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
Everybody's playing against
each other for a chance
to advance in rank.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
This will never happen again.
I have to serve as their witness!
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
The emotions experienced...
Huh?  What?
My life means nothing...
What?  What?!
This is impossible!
I have no idea what's
going on in either match!
Who got that card?!
Who got it?!
Can you calm down?
I want to watch them play!
Huh?  Kana-chan...
She isn't sitting back the
way she does in practice.
Has her exercise paid off?
I will not cast myself into Naniwa Bay,
But she just started...
Is it because of the hakama?!
but I will risk my life to see you again
As my love first came to realization,
Excuse me.
Oh!
Now that I think about it,
this is the first time
I've watched Kana-chan
play in a hakama.
When wearing a kimono,
you must maintain proper posture
and suck your stomach in,
as though you have a board
running down your spine.
My obi helps to support me.
All alone, I step outside
my house seeking comfort,
It helps to strengthen my center!
How lovely.
Kimonos are so beautiful.
She's so pretty.
Chihaya-chan is very beautiful,
but she's beautiful no
matter what she wears.
Kanade isn't necessarily beautiful,
but she knows how to use a kimono.
She is the true poster girl
for Oe Traditional Clothing!
Kana-chan attacks better when
she's wearing a hakama.
She can play 100% when
I practice with her every day,
and I can still learn new things
about her in a real match.
Still, the normal Kana-chan is there.
There is one card that I can
always take against Kana-chan.
While it brings me no joy...
It's quite simple.
Ayase cares about the "Impassionate" card,
and similarly, Kana-chan believes that the
"While it brings" card belongs to her,
and I have yet to visit Amanohashidate
or read my mother's letters
because her name is Oe.
Plus...
Whenever "While it brings" is read,
her attention is drawn to "The storm will."
The autumn paddy shacks...
Which delays her response
to the other cards.
Because Lady Izumi Shikibu
and Koshikibu no Naishi
Daughter
Koshikibu no Naishi
While it brings me no joy, the
road beyond Mount Oe is too long
and I have yet to visit Amanohashidate
or read my mother's letters
Mother
Lady Izumi Shikibu
The storm will soon carry
me to the afterlife,
so I wish for a memory
of you to take with me
were mother and daughter.
Desktomu-kun is really calm.
He understands Kana-chan's karuta.
Kana-chan doesn't
recognize cards just by syllables
the way other players do.
Ariwara no Narihira
Impassionate gods have never seen
the red that is the Tatsuta River
Brothers
Ariwara no Yukihira
Note that though we may
be apart, if I am to hear
that you pine for me as the Inaba
mountain pines, I shall return to you
When Ariwara no Narihira's card is read,
she looks for his brother, Yukihira.
Lady Sei Shonagon
Said night was young when
the false rooster's crow
but the gates of Afusaka remained shut
Father and Daughter
When Lady Sei Shonagon is read,
Kiyohara no Motosuke
Impassioned vows exchanged
over many a tear shed to last
until the day waves crash
over Mount Suenomatsu
Rivals
she looks for Kiyohara no Motosuke,
Lady Murasaki Shikibu
Long last we meet, only for
me to leave hurriedly,
for I could not recognize you, like
the moon hidden behind the clouds
as well as Lady Murasaki Shibu.
Kana-chan values the meaning
and history behind every card,
but the syllables are what
matter in competitive karuta.
As I wait for someone...
I screwed up!
A fault!
I have trouble differentiating
between "As I" and "As this".
My focus is on the syllables,
but my hearing isn't as good as Ayase's!
Desktomu-kun reacted as
soon as "As" was read.
Which card will Kana-chan send?
Huh?
I can look up and see the
snowy cap of Mt. Fuji
Kana-chan, why is "No matter" always
the first "No" card you send?
I would send "Note that" first,
since it sounds different
from the others.
My hearing isn't as good as yours,
so "Nobody", "No more", "No matter",
"Note that", "None are," and "Nothing"
are all difficult for me.
But the bigger something is,
the easier it is to notice.
No matter where I stand
on the shores of Tago,
I can look up and see the
snowy cap of Mt. Fuji
She's drawn to the image
of Mt. Fuji!
No matter where I stand
on the shores of Tago,
I didn't hear a thing.
Her motion was flawless.
Straight as an arrow...
I'm not here to cheer them on.
I'm not here as their captain.
I'm going to take whatever
I can from them!
Meanwhile, there was another
intense match going on,
but only Retro-kun was watching!