You can't blame them.
Working at an inn is hard.
People who aren't interested
won't be able to work long-term.
Hey, there are lots of
things I want to do.
I'm going to pick the one thing I want to
do the most and make it my career.
Running an inn is not on that list.
Episode 15
Sunny With a Chance of Beans
Office
We're very short handed now that
all our waitresses have quit.
I'll call the union and ask
if they've got any waitresses available today.
We'll ask around too.
Thanks.
Yosuke.
Hello?
What are you drifting off for?
If only I'd managed them better...
This ain't the time to be blaming yourself.
I'd like to help out!
You're...
I'm a waitress at Kissuiso,
so as long as you don't mind...
Kissuiso?
Thank you for your kindness and concern.
Yes?!
However, this is our inn's problem.
I cannot allow a guest of ours
to be troubled by our problems.
You're currently on a field trip.
Please enjoy yourself.
Don't worry about it.
We're the customers here.
Wow, I want to go here!
I know, but...
I just can't stop thinking about it.
You're too nice, Ohana!
Come on, we're on a field trip!
Forget about it!
O-Okay...
Your free time starts now.
Don't go too crazy!
Meet back here at 4 p.m. sharp!
Don't be late!
Oshimizu!
Howdy!
Time to buy gifts!
For Madam Manager,
the young master,
and Jiromaru...
Tomoe will love this!
Sake for Mr. Ren,
and for Tohru...
Tohru
I'll get this for him.
I can never find one
with my name on it.
What's wrong?
N-Nothing.
Hey, guys.
How lame.
Oh, it's them.
What?
Man, I'm glad I quit.
Yeah, remind me to never work at an inn again.
I don't like them.
Well, working at an inn really is a pain.
Right, back to gift shopping! Gift shopping!
Ohana?
It's so tiring, and the manual's super specific.
And on top of that, the owner's son is such a dick.
What a pain in the ass.
Mango ice cream with
fried chicken topping.
Oh, that's mine.
You're the pain in the ass!
What's wrong with you?!
M-My shoe! And it was brand new too!
Mango ice cream
with fried chicken topping...
Hey! What's your problem?!
Hey, blame her!
What?
Let's get out of here!
H-Hey!
Get back here!
Jeez... What did you think you were doing?!
Hey, don't you think they were rather callous?!
What?
Hey, who were they?
They were part-time waitresses at
the inn we're staying at.
They quit without any notice.
What? Then isn't the inn in a huge mess now?
Yeah, I guess...
I mean, they've got to be, right?
I still think I ought to help them.
I mean, think about it.
It's about as much trouble as
100 customers suddenly
staying at Kissuiso today.
I believe we've only got two groups booked for today.
It's an example!
So, what are you planning to do?
We're allowed to do whatever we want
during our free time, right?
I'm off!
H-
Can you buy everyone's gifts for me please?
Oh, I think Jirormaru would
love to have something perverted for his gift!
What?!
Huh? Ohana?
Taxi!
Hey, taxi!
Well?
No luck.
All the inns seem to be busy.
Please excuse me!
A-Are you sure you
don't need an extra waitress?!
You're...
I'm Ohana Matsumae, 16 years old.
Weren't you supposed to be coming back this evening?
Yeah, but...
After I started imagining a similar
situation happening at Kissuiso,
I sort of started to panic!
How should I explain it...
I feel like a dog who
would love to be fed.
No! What am I saying?!
I noticed that I was drooling!
Are you saying that it's a
conditioned reflex for you?
Yes!
That's it!
So she's been trained by Mrs. Sui.
She acted on instinct.
Very few waitresses can do that.
You know Madam Manager?
I was trained at Yunosagi.
Ms. Matsumae.
Yes?
We're in the middle of a crisis.
I'll call and let my mentor know.
What?!
Would you mind helping us out
using your skill as a waitress?
Of course not!
The robot collects the dishes
and carries them to the floor above.
Do you have any questions so far?
Nope!
I've been dying to try out your secret weapon!
Weirdo.
Thanks for helping us out.
If I had done a better job at supervising those part-timers,
none of this would've happened.
You're right.
You weren't doing a very good job.
But don't worry about it.
I figured it would be better
to be stricter with part-timers.
How do things work at your place?
How are the people at Kissuiso supervised?
With a slap to the face from Madam Manager.
That's worse than me!
It helped me learn my job, though.
I learned my job!
Your Madam Manager must be something else.
I... guess?
There it is!
Okay, time to work!
I'm counting on you.
You're really cute!
Hey, wanna come and karaoke with us?
Sorry, I'm in the middle of a field trip.
Where did everyone disappear to?
Don't tell me they actually went...
Yes! Yes! I'm coming!
I-I've got to speed up!
N-No way!
Idiot! You can't carry that many!
I-I'm sorry!
Minchi...
Nakochi...
Wh-What about the gifts?!
Is that all you're worried about?
We're also helping out, Ohana.
We've informed the head clerk already.
I've brought the waitress uniforms!
Thank you.
What would you like me to do?
After all, I usually work in the kitchen.
How about you and the head clerk take care of the loading,
while Ohana and I set the tables, okay?
Sounds good.
Sure.
Okay!
Yes, of course.
Thanks for coming back and helping, Nakochi.
I figured that since I couldn't swim right now,
working wouldn't be a bad alternative.
Only this many have been set...
I hope we make it in time
for the dinner at six.
Don't worry! We have a secret weapon on our side!
But we should hurry, just in case.
Hello?
Seriously?!
Minchi?
The robot's broken!
It's no use. It's not responding.
It looks like we'll need to call a mechanic.
So, that's the end of our secret weapon?
This is really bad timing...
What are we going to do now?
The shower tactic!
What?
S-Shower...
When I was at home, I used it all the time!
If my mom came home before
I had finished making dinner,
I would send her to have her shower first, and make dinner with
whatever was left in the fridge while she was in there!
I called it "The shower tactic!"
In other words?
Oh! You're suggesting that
we ask them all to take a bath first?
Before dinner is served, right?
Exactly!
I see. The shower tactic.
Right, bath time is at six,
and dinner's at seven.
Adjust everything to that schedule.
Right.
We'll take care of the baths.
Waitresses,
please finish setting the
tables in the meantime.
Okay!
That was so much fun!
Yeah!
I'm so hungry!
Yeah, I wonder what's for dinner!
Listen up, gang!
There's been a change of plans!
You'll have your bath before dinner!
Everyone, bath time is at six!
What?
Seriously?
Okay!
Everyone's back!
They're all back!
We've got to hurry! Hurry!
I'm so excited!
You're the only one who's excited!
Wow, they really are working.
Jeez... they're festing it up too much.
Young master,
the women's bath is ready!
Good job!
Do you want us to help you over there?
Nah, I can finish this.
Go help set up the tables instead!
Sure!
I'm coming in!
What are you doing here, Yuina?
Sight-see-ing.
This place hasn't changed at all.
Remember when we used to
take baths together in here?
Do you think everything's going to be okay?
Yeah, thanks to that
curly-haired girl from Kissuiso.
Ohana's hair is a natural perm!
They're really good-natured,
helping out in the
middle of a field trip.
She's completely different from you.
She's also the granddaughter of an innkeeper.
The owner of Kissuiso, right?
She's helping out because she knows
precisely how difficult it is to run an inn.
Question!
Why do you insist on
doing such hard work?
Don't you think there might be
something else that would suit you better?
Such as being a designer,
a creator, or even an artist?
I think it's better to do
something you like as your career!
I've got to get up early in the mornings,
and I don't get any breaks.
I can't go out and have fun either.
But even then,
there are things I like about this job.
You've never worked, so I doubt you would understand.
You're right. I've never worked.
Sorry about last night.
Just forget about our past promises.
Why?
You don't like
working at an inn, right?
Then there's no way we can get married.
You're the one who proposed to me,
and now you're calling it off?
That hurts my pride.
I only want to marry someone
who will work here with me.
Someone like that curly-haired girl.
You don't get it, do you, Yosuke?
I know how to work too.
I just choose not to.
It's not like I can't work!
It's not like Ohana's anything special!
Why isn't this slimy stuff coming off?!
It just won't come off!
Jeez...
What? What?!
You have to rinse away the
cleanser when you're done.
See, it's all clean now.
How are the preparations coming?!
We're finished...
W-What? Yuina?
5:55 p.m...
I wouldn't have been able to
finish this without Yuina's help.
Really?!
I've got a blister thanks to you.
Have you finished setting the tables?
Just about!
Everyone came and helped us!
Ohana, we're finished over here!
Are you sure you don't need us
to help with anything else?
Yup!
Us waitresses will handle the rest!
Looks like the bath's been cleaned, too.
It's time for you
customers to enjoy your baths!
Huh? Is that Yuina?
Yeah!
Wow, were you cleaning the bath for us?
Wow!
It's so clean!
Man, I want to go in!
Hello, I'm Yosuke Hiwatari,
the head clerk here.
I'd like to say a few words before
you enjoy your meal.
You've all gone through a lot
of trouble because of me.
It's thanks to you that we were
able to deliver this dinner at all.
I'd like to represent this
inn and thank you all.
Thank you all so much!
You cleaned the bath, Princess Yuina?!
What?
Y-Yeah.
The princess cleaned the bath for us peasants...
Thank you, God...
I swear never to take a
bath in my own home again!
O-Okay...
Hey, do you have some free time later?
This feels great...
It was nice of him
to let us have the outdoor bath to ourselves
as a thanks.
Yeah...
I'm glad we managed to finish in time.
Thanks for helping us, Yuina.
My blister hurts!
You got a blister from cleaning the bath?
Hey, it was my first time!
It's the first time I've worked!
This job is really hard work, isn't it?
My blister hurts and so does my hip.
I even got really sweaty,
but it was surprisingly fun!
Of course it was!
You were able to sit in an outdoor bath as your thanks
for your first time working!
There's no way it wasn't fun!
I was thanked with a slap
from Madam Manager
the first time I worked!
A really hard one at that!
Really?
Stop exposing yourself.
I sleep on a crappy futon, and my roommate is Minchi...
That's got nothing to do with work.
Oh, that reminds me...
Did you get a perverted
gift like I asked you to?
Buy it yourself!
Ohana!
If you're drowning, inhale through your nose
and breathe out with your mouth!
I don't think she heard you.
Balut!
Did everyone check their rooms?
Make sure you didn't forget anything!
From today,
I'm going to start studying again.
I've got to learn to think
about those who are working.
I've got to learn to think with them,
instead of giving them all the work to do.
Yeah!
I'm also going to start learning about inns.
You've decided to become Madam Manager?!
Yeah!
But of Fukuya Inn.
Jeez...
Just kidding!
I'm still undecided.
Really?
So, coming and working
here is also a possibility?
That's also undecided!
Let's go, Yuina!
Coming!
Yunosagi looks really pretty in the sunset.
I was born and raised in the inn.
I was too close to it,
which is why I thought it would be hard.
But...
it's up to me to try and find...
things I like and want to do.
Well, I guess I better fest it up.
I'm home!
Come on!
Mom!
Episode 16
That Sky, This Sky