Nao?
Good morning, Yuki.
Clydesdale Platoon has returned from
Mazuurek Landing Castle recon mission.
Roger that. Open well dock.
Okay, all units have returned to base.
Warrant Officer Kaizuka.
Yes?
Come to the captain's quarters later.
You've been requested.
Me?
Yes, it has to do with the Deucalion.
It's on its way back, apparently. To Earth.
Port Aden has been chosen
as our return point.
Calculate our reentry time and report.
Yes, ma'am.
Always on the move... The top brass must be
trying to wring every last drop out of us.
Are you sure it doesn't mean that they value
the Deucalion's power really highly?
If anything, the vibe I get is that
they don't know what to do with us.
I need your final approval for
the resupply list, ma'am.
I finished it a while ago.
Go ahead and transmit it.
Yes, ma'am.
Attention, all hands.
At 1300 hours UTC, we will begin our
Earth reentry sequence as ordered.
That's Calvados.
Thank you, but no.
I see.
So, is it true that we'll be acting
as the Deucalion's escort?
It's temporary. It's only while they
take on supplies and make repairs.
Plus, the base they're assigned to
isn't very far from here.
It's not like you two don't have
ties to that ship, right?
Though I hear that you were supposed to
serve aboard her, but turned it down.
Being on that ship only opens up old wounds.
I understand that your younger
brother serves aboard her.
His exploits have been
quite something, I hear.
Yes, I suppose...
May I?
Of course.
What did the other nobles do afterwards?
I'm told that none of them are
openly expressing opposition.
In Harklight's opinion.
Do you also believe that, Slaine?
No.
They are only holding their tongues for
the time being, thinking it distasteful
to raise objections while
the count is still being mourned.
It is an undeniable fact that Count Saazbaum's
death is a great loss to Vers.
I am the result of an indiscretion
committed on the Moon
by my father, Gillzeria,
the second emperor.
Father perished as a result of
his second sin, Heaven's Fall,
and the Moon we now stand on was shattered.
Count Saazbaum found me and offered his
allegiance when I had lost my family.
Although I never truly knew
what he was thinking deep down.
But that is fine.
It is actually more difficult to trust
those who have no talent for scheming.
Like it or not, you will have to bear the
brunt of their jealousy and envy, Slaine.
You have inherited all of
Count Saazbaum's privileges...
As well as his status as
Princess Asseylum's guardian.
I am prepared.
But it is a grave responsibility
that deserves to be envied.
That outfit looks quite good on you.
Do not forget.
The princess that you must
protect now is right before you.
I am keenly aware of that.
To think that he named some
nobody as his successor,
only to die an untimely death
immediately afterward.
Count Saazbaum had terrible luck.
Perhaps it was comeuppance for his folly.
He may have been caught
off guard and killed.
Are you suggesting that Count
Saazbaum was betrayed?
Enough.
Without any hard evidence, it will sound
like nothing more than idle gossip.
Whatever the case, the dignity
of all knights is at stake!
We mustn't allow him to continue
to do as he pleases.
Count Mazuurek,
I am aware that you go out of your way
to avoid destructive acts of aggression
because your priority is on
seizing Earth's resources.
No, I am not criticizing you
for taking such a position.
However, now is the time to press on with the
invasion of Earth, by force if necessary!
If this continues, the authority of the knight
order known as the 37 Clans will decline further.
This calls for a faction that will set aside
their power struggles and work together.
What are your thoughts, Count Mazuurek?
It is a poor knight indeed who
slays one who defies him.
The key is to show yourself to be so superior
that they will not defy you in the first place.
Wise words, Milord.
Count Saazbaum spoke them.
Which is why I must give them a reminder.
Condition, generally satisfactory.
I'm not seeing anything in particular
that concerns me.
That's what I've been saying.
I wish you'd cut me loose already.
Incidentally, what is happening with the war?
I would have thought that they would
be coming at us relentlessly.
After all, the odds of reconciliation
are effectively nil now.
Mars isn't monolithic.
Sure, some of them attacked
purely out of hatred of Earth,
but some of them would rather
seize it for our natural resources.
Ah, you mean that they're
restraining themselves.
But...
Hang on, you don't suppose it's because
they never imagined that their
main Kataphrakts would be taken out
one after another, do you?
Things haven't gone to plan and they feel
threatened and have gone into defensive mode.
Maybe you're right.
But it was a single boy
who gave us this chance.
You mean Inaho.
Yuki must be worried
sick about him.
Yeah, she wanted him out of the military,
so she kept asking the top brass.
Isn't that just a rumor?
That her pestering alienated them
and that's why she got stationed here.
Possible enemy Sky Carriers detected
east and west of Yemen,
as well as in the desert region
roughly 14km northeast of Aden.
We'll hold it off here to keep it from reaching
the urban area 6km east of here.
All units, wait for it to enter firing range.
When I give the order, commence attack.
Roger that.
Roger.
Attack!
Enemy Kataphrakt advancing!
Our rounds are landing!
Keep it up!
What the hell are those?
Our rounds, they're–
A tornado?!
No, windspeed, air volume, and atmospheric
pressure aren't showing any major–
My head... feels like it's being
squeezed in a vise!
Count Barouhcruz, pay attention.
The way I fight is worthy of the Orbital
Knights and my noble title.
W-Wait, Clydesdale 22!
A-Are you okay?
I barely got away...
Fall back! What the hell is going on?
Lieutenant... the gauges!
Look at... the accelerometer!
Gravity...
Are you telling me... that this thing...
is manipulating gravity?
My accelerometer...
is showing wild oscillations.
They're acting as gravitational-tidal pairs
and revolving at high speed
around the Kataphrakt...
It uses that to...
To create gravity waves?
Yes...
So any object that gets too close will
be torn apart by the tidal forces,
and any attack will also
be deflected, huh?
Is it also causing this sound
in our heads...?
Probably...
I bear this world's people no ill will, but
this must be done for the future of Vers!
Here it comes!
We can't just sit here and
let it reach the city!
We'll keep its attention
and draw it away!
But sir! How?!
Kaizuka.
Sir?
Call it in to the carrier.
Ask if there's any satellite bases
overhead with equipment
that can detect gravity waves!
Do you not see that your
efforts are futile?
It's no use! They're disintegrating
before they can connect!
Even if they don't damage him, they're having
the effect of keeping his attention on us.
We're another 10km away
from the urban center.
We're definitely managing
to draw him away.
Another 2km south. Just another 2km. That's
how much further we have to draw him away.
What's wrong?! Don't stop moving!
Clydesdale 22!
Clydesdale 33!
Crap...
Kaizuka!
I'll get his attention!
You go retrieve those two!
Lieutenant?
Come get me, you twister
son of a bitch!
It is pointless.
Why are you doing this?
What value is there?
Lieutenant...
This is bad, I'm too close...
I need to get some distance.
Just a little farther...
Come on!
I'm coming!
Crap!
Am I never gonna be free of these
memories no matter how hard I try?!
Thank you for luring it
into position, Lt. Marito.
A laser transmission?
Wait a second, Yuki.
Nao?
Its gravity waves are ripples that
propagate outward horizontally.
The gravity waves that propagate vertically
are integrated and lose their effect.
Correcting for errors...
0.2 degrees/second.
Locked on.
Fire!
It was a lucky break that we
got through to the Deucalion.
No, or maybe we were lucky
that he was there.
We begin reentry in 10 minutes!
Hurry up and get Mustang 00 inside!
We're no longer in an
area with a line of fire.
It looks like this is all the help
we can give you.
No, that was plenty, Kaizuka's brother.
TK-67, 68 are on designated
trajectory. Opening gate.
Trash cleanup is taking forever...
Well, that was a huge battle.
A ton of debris got scattered around.
It's a pain, is what it is. It makes it a
lot harder for shuttles to come and go.
Radar return detected!
No IFF signal detected...
Sorry, sir. We didn't pick it up right away
because it was mixed in with all the debris.
Just one unit?
What do they hope to do
with just one unit?
That's–
It's now 10km away!
I can't believe it...
How can it fly through a dense
debris field at that speed?
Launch Kataphrakt platoons, hurry!
Long time no see, Yuki!
Darn it, you up and left all
of a sudden! You scared us!
Sorry. Chalk it up to grown-up reasons.
We'll be able to fight
together again, right?
So, I hear you guys have been busy.
Yep!
And you haven't changed a bit, Yuki.
Rayet.
So, you liking it here?
It's okay.
I'm glad.
Inaho is doing fine, too!
It seemed that way.
Did you see him already?
He just said hello over the radio.
Maybe he thinks that's enough.
I see... The memories
resurfaced again, did they?
There doesn't seem to be any way
to escape the damn things.
Is it possible that perhaps they
were deliberately revived?
Shock therapy you chose to perform
to give a boost to your fading consciousness.
No way...
It's possible that you're using
the memories of that tragedy
to give yourself a reason
to fight, Lieutenant.
Of course, you're not doing
this consciously.
You're saying that I've beaten them?
At the very least, you've won the battle.
I'm sure it was around here...
I hope you accept that fact,
if nothing else.
Found it!
That's mine... That's where
you've been hiding it?
If you're confronting the past, your drinking
takes on an entirely different meaning.
Hey, these have been sterilized,
haven't they?
Lieutenant! There's an emergency!
It's Trident Base!
This is a recording from
the time of the attack.
It waited until the shuttles
had entered the docking bay
and then set off all the munitions
they were carrying at once.
Talk about lousy timing...
No, I think it was planned.
Planned?
There was just a major battle there, so it's
a safe bet that shuttles would come.
They probably checked to make sure that
the base's reinforcements had left.
They stood a good chance of winning,
so they attacked with just one unit.
But the service details of munitions shuttles
are supposed to be top secret.
All they really do is stuff like change their
registry numbers and alter the supply routes.
You'd be able to sniff them out with careful
cryptoanalysis and data sifting.
But...
We're probably dealing with
someone capable of that.
Milord Slaine, brilliantly done.
The fiend...
You mustn't overlook his results.
He did what he set out to do
and did it brilliantly.
We can't brand him a traitor, not now.
Causes always rally
around the powerful.
The mangy cur has transformed
himself into a wolf.
Harklight, we're returning to the Moon.
The Tharsis...
Slaine Troyard.
I guess I have no choice.