Don't...
Please, don't!
Don't!
Senketsu!
We're late, we're late,
we're late, we're late!
Hurry up and get dressed, too, Ryuko!
What am I gonna do,
what am I gonna do?!
Calm down, Mako!
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
It's 4AM.
Help me!
Help me, I'm being murdered!
Mako, your lunch is ready
and waiting in the kitchen!
Senketsu!
Good morning, Ryuko!
Good morning... Wait, that's my uniform!
I know!
It was filthy, so I'm giving
it an extra-thorough cleaning!
M-Ma'am, I'll take it
from here, so don't—
Nothing doing!
What is the duty of the student?
To go to school!
What is the duty of the housewife?
To do laundry!
Is that clear?
Now, hurry up and eat breakfast!
You'll be late for school!
But I can't go to school
without that uniform...
Oops, I forgot to panic!
Today's the big day, Ryuko!
Big day?
What?! Ryuko, you're on "that day"?!
You're fine in your PJs, just move!
We'll drop off your uniform later!
Don't worry about a thing!
Ryuko, wait! You're the
only one who can hear me!
So please don't leave
me! I'm begging you!
Are you okay, Senketsu?
"Senketsu"? What's that?
You gave your uniform a name?
Boy, you must be lonely to do that!
Wait!
All the more reason to go to school!
There's lots of friends there!
There's nothing but
enemies, and you know it!
In we go!
Sorry, Senketsu!
Ryuko! Ryuko!
That's surprisingly pleasant.
The wrinkles... The wrinkles
are melting away...
Melting away...
What's with this mass migration?
There is a day when all of
Honnouji Academy's No-Stars
put their entire youth on the
line when they go to school.
That day has dawned! Today is that day!
This is No-Late Day!
EPISODE 4
DAWN OF A MISERABLE MORNING
"No-Late Day"? What the heck is that?
I can see that you are
confused, Ryuko Matoi!
You're that Elite Four jerk—
Disciplinary Committee
Chair and one of Honnouji
DISCIPLINARY COMMITTEE
CHAIR IRA GAMAGOORI
Academy's Elite Four! Ira Gamagoori!
Allow me to explain!
No-Late Day is a school event
that comes once a semester,
in which the Disciplinary Committee
springs surprises on slacker No-Star
students to whip them into shape!
TRAP
When the siren goes off
in the slums at 4AM,
No-Star students must evade the traps
that the Disciplinary Committee
LATE
built with all the
technology at our disposal
and make it to school by the time the
first period bell rings at 8:30AM!
DISCIPLINE
And in the event that they arrive late,
they are expelled on the spot, so—
WHAT THE HELL?!
What manner of slacker outfit is that?!
My Kamui's in the laundry!
It'll be dropped off soon!
Spare me your excuses.
Leaving for school in a
slovenly outfit like that
is a mortal insult to both
the academy and Lady Satsuki!
MORTAL INSULT
Is it, though?!
Ryuko was asleep until just now!
It's perfectly normal for
sleeping people to wear pajamas!
No one can laugh at that!
Or do you mean to say that you dress
like that when YOU sleep, Gamagoori?
No, I sleep in the nude.
You'll catch cold if
you sleep in the buff!
If you were sick, could you work to
your fullest potential in an emergency?
Oh.
Please wear pajamas like
everyone else when you sleep!
What is your name?
Second Year Class K, Mako Mankanshoku!
The pattern on my favorite pajamas is
one Mt. Fuji, two hawks, and three eggplants!
Mankanshoku, you say?
I'll remember that.
Matoi!
I couldn't care less what you
happen to be wearing right now!
But do you think you can reach
the school without your Kamui?
Behold the Disciplinary
Committee's mighty barrier!
Shocker!
Look, Ryuko!
It's like the whole city's been
turned into an amusement park!
I've never seen anything like this!
And there's only 3 hours to go
until our first class, Ryuko!
The people at this school sure
love to hear themselves talk.
All right, fine. You're on.
I'm gonna bust through every last
one of the traps you bozos made!
As you wish! Students, commence commute!
Forward, march!
Mako, don't get separated!
'Kay!
A trap right off the bat, huh?
I'm falling! I'm falling!
Up you go!
CHECKPOINT
Congratulations on passing
the first checkpoint!
I neglected to mention that use of the
No-Star commuter cable cars is prohibited!
Obey the rules and stick
to the prescribed route!
And now, gentlemen, until
we meet again at school!
There's another 999 of these to go!
That's more than usual!
He's screwing with us. Come on, Mako!
Ow, that hurts so much!
You're our classmate, Maiko Ogure!
CLASSMATE MAIKO OGURE
Are you okay? Your arm is hurt!
Why, it's Mankanshoku!
And you're Matoi, the transfer student!
Yes, I hurt my arm in
that trap just now.
But I'll live!
I can't give up over
something like this!
Hey, don't overdo it!
Hey, Ryuko. Since Maiko is hurt,
let's take her with us to school!
No! I can't let you!
I'd only slow you down!
Oh, okay. We'll go on ahead, then.
Don't push yourself too hard, okay?
The pain!
Hang in there, Maiko!
If anyone can make it
on her own, it's you!
Ryuko!
For crying out loud...
Putting on a brave act, eh?
Hold on tight. We'll
go to school together.
Thank you, Matoi!
Don't sweat it.
I don't hate girls who push
themselves to be strong.
Ryuko, look at that!
Isn't that the 2nd checkpoint up ahead?
How the heck do you get up there?!
Damn it, if I had Senketsu,
that hill would be nothing.
Move it! Make way!
Back-alley doctor Barazo
is coming through!
Anybody who doesn't get out of the way
will get a Caesarian, even if it's a guy!
That's Ryuko up there!
Hey, we've got your uniform!
I can't hold on any more...
Maiko! Are you okay?!
It's no use!
- Oops! - Hey! Watch
what you're grabbing!
Keep your eyes on the road
when you're driving, you fool!
Dad! Are you okay?!
Your dad is done for...
Mataro, I have a favor
to ask you, man-to-man...
Take this uniform and—
Will do!
I'll make sure that this uniform
gets to Ryuko safe and sound!
Rest in peace, Dad!
I've got it from here!
Hang on, Ryuko!
Ouch!
Are you okay?!
Ooh! Cheese!
Cheese, cheese, cheese!
Cheese, cheese, cheese, cheese, cheese!
Mako, look out!
It's a pie! Pie!
That looks really tasty, Ryuko!
Ow!
Are you okay—
You can do it, Ryuko!
Damn it, I could really use
Senketsu right about now!
Ryuko!
Hey, that's her! I'll be right there!
My arm!
Are you okay?!
What a feast for the eyes!
Keep your eyes on the road, confound it!
Guts? Is that you, boy? I'm done for...
Guts, I have a favor to
ask you, man-to-man dog...
Stop it, vile hellhound! Ow! That hurts!
Don't bite down so hard, curse you!
What time is it?
8AM. Meaning that there
are 30 minutes left.
This might be difficult.
No! No! If we don't do something,
I won't be able to go to school anymore!
Hey, Maiko, what's that?
Pseudo-homeroom.
Students who have given up on
making it to school on time,
unable to face the reality that
they will be kicked out of
both school and their homes tomorrow,
take attendance with dead, vacant eyes.
That's too sad for words.
So this means that the condo district
up ahead is gonna be even tougher, huh?
Hey, a school bus is coming!
It's a minefield!
It's an armored vehicle though, so don't worry.
That's a One-Star bus for you!
It's passing the checkpoint!
No way, they have it so easy!
I wanna ride that! I
wanna ride, I wanna ride!
Oh, the pain!
Damn it, No-Star! Get out
of the road! Hurry it—
Righty, then! All aboard!
Hang on, Maiko, do you have a license?
Honnou Town is the private
property of the Kiryuin family.
If she has Lady Satsuki's permission,
even a student can drive!
I don't want to lose, either!
I want to show them that even
No-Stars have their pride!
Maiko, you can be pretty
bad-ass, you know that?
No-Star students have hijacked
a One-Star school bus.
They're clearing the traps.
Prevent them from reaching
school with extreme prejudice.
Okey-dokey!
What the hell is going on?!
Are preparations for the final
trap proceeding on schedule?
No one is here?
Wow, you gotta hand it
to these armored buses!
We're going to counterattack!
How?
With this!
Ryuko, this is totes fun!
It's not safe up there, Mako! Come down!
This feels so good.
RPG!
Retract turret!
Gosh, the view's so much clearer now!
Just a little further, and
we're in the Two-Star district!
RPGs from both sides!
Punch it!
Ouch...
Wake up, everybody!
We did it, you guys! We
made it! It's the school!
If we can reach our classroom
in 15 minutes, we'll be on time!
Awesome, that's a piece of cake!
A piece of cake!
We couldn't have done
it without you, Maiko!
I'm seeing you in a whole new light!
Nonsense, you did all the hard work.
Still, I'm happy you think so!
Shucks!
Yay, we're all friends!
Look, Ryuko! Guts has
brought you your uniform!
Hey, Guts!
Why is Guts bringing it?
Geez, what's your dad thinking?
Oh, the pain!
We're sliding, we're
sliding, we're sliding!
Where are you going, Guts?
What?
Maiko, what are you doing?!
You let your guard down, Ryuko...
No, Ryuko Matoi, I should say.
I've been waiting for
this moment for ages!
Maiko?
This injured No-Star classmate
was but a fake identity!
My true identity...
is Maiko Ogure, Disciplinary
Committee Head of Trap Development!
HEAD OF TRAP DEVELOPMENT MAIKO OGURE
Trap development, huh?
That's right!
A shadowy figure who remains undercover
among the common students,
spying on their behavior
and developing traps!
That is what the Head of
Trap Development does!
But I had grown sick
and tired of that life.
I had a flash of inspiration
when I overheard
your conversation with Gamagoori
over the surveillance cameras.
I would steal the Kamui,
a Goku Uniform which held
within it the power to go
toe-to-toe with Lady Satsuki.
Using this uniform, I
could be a Two-Star—
THREE-STAR
TWO-STAR
ONE-STAR
NO-STAR
No, be one of the Four Elites—
No, steal the throne from
Lady Satsuki herself!
STUDENT COUNCIL PRESIDENT
Yes! I'll become empress
of Honnouji Academy
and indulge in every luxury
the academy has to offer!
I can hardly wait!
Maiko, it sounds like
you had everyone fooled.
Maiko! Return that uniform to Ryuko!
You see, putting on
that uniform
and transforming into
something that
leaves her half naked
is Ryuko's only joy in life!
Oh, yes! The transformation!
"Life Fiber Synchronize," was it?
I have to try that for
myself right away!
Off with this! On with this!
What?!
Get real.
As if a deceitful bitch like
you could transform so easily!
I did it!
No way!
Life Fiber Synchronize! Kamui Senketsu!
KAMUI SENKETSU
Oh, come on!
I had so much trouble mastering the
Life Fiber Synchronization, but she—!
How can she do this, Senketsu?!
Forgive me, Ryuko. This
woman has no shame.
If it means power, if it means
standing on top of the world,
I'll gladly get naked
as the day I was born!
Oh, it's flooding into me!
The strength! The power! The strepower!
Now, let's try out this
strepower, shall we?
Naturally, we'll start with the weakest!
Mako!
W-What's going on?!
Why won't my body move?!
What the hell?
It's not working!
It's as if my body's turned to stone!
Senketsu... Is it you?
W-What do you think you're doing?
S-Stop! Let's not be hasty!
I'm so sorry I tricked you!
What's up?
Aren't you going to try
out your strepower?
Please! I'll give back the Kamui!
Grr! What's wrong with
this stupid outfit?!
So uppity! So impertinent!
It's the outfit! It's all this stupid outfit's fault!
This stupid, broken outfit!
It's freshly cleaned.
I bet they just used too much starch.
Right?!
Making me drink that
grimy blood of hers!
I'm sorry I was late, Ryuko!
Yeah, but since you didn't
cheat on me, I'll forgive you.
Look, Ryuko! There's only five minutes
to go until the first period bell rings!
We have to hurry!
I don't wanna be late and get expelled!
Ow...
I hit my head on the air...
W-What the—?
What the hell is going on?
Moron!
This is my ultimate weapon!
I set it up on the off chance
that this might happen!
A fake school!
And now...!
It's all over for you!
Once my fake-school trap, "Begin
All Over Again," is activated,
no one can stop it!
Like hell it's over!
I'll just have to pound on you again and
make you tell us how to stop this thing!
How about now?
Wait! Are you out of your mind?!
Now that I've failed in
my plan to take the Kamui,
I swear on my pride as a
Disciplinary Committee member
that I will at least see that you are
forever branded as a tardy
student, Ryuko Matoi!
It will be Maiko Ogure's
final act of defiance!
All glory to Honnouji Academy!
Kidding!
Ryuko, be careful! It's coming apart!
Ryuko, help!
Mako!
Ryuko, put me on!
Right, I forgot!
Life Fiber Synchronization!
Kamui Senketsu!
KAMUI SENKETSU
What the hell?
This is the sea! This
is way past square one!
You'll never make it in
time, even wearing me.
You'll be late!
O! M! G!
This station is the nonstop
rope expresso-way to school
for rich folks that us No-Stars
could never ride in a million years!
I always wanted to ride this!
What? It's nonstop?
Hey! You No-Stars can't be in he—
Shut your mouth and take us to the
end of the line at full throttle!
Mako! Hurry, get in!
But we have to pay the ropeway fare!
No wallet!
There's nothing for it.
I'll just have to leave my precious,
precious croquette lunch instead!
Who cares about that?! Just get in here!
Yay! Yay! I always wanted to ride this!
I always wanted to ride this!
How many minutes are left?!
One minute! In one minute,
we'll be late! And expelled!
No way! One minute?!
I'm gonna get us to homeroom
on time, if only out of spite!
Curses, I came so close.
Well, no matter.
I'll play the good subordinate
for the time being
and wait for another opportunity
to present itself.
I heard everything, Ogure!
Master Gamagoori!
Steal the Kamui and overthrow
Lady Satsuki, eh?
That's far beyond the likes of you!
P-Please forgive me...
Never! You are expelled!
EXPELLED
You don't deserve to
attend Honnouji Academy!
Get out of my sight!
Damn that Matoi...
30 seconds!
Got it!
There's no time to get
out at the station!
Let's see, next up is... Matoi.
Ryuko Matoi.
Ryuko Matoi?
Present.
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
The man is silent.
SILENT
He says but one thing, and it is to
his prey when he has them cornered.
PREY
BUT ONE THING
SAYS
"TAKE OFF YOUR CLOTHES"
"Take off your clothes."
Next time on Kill la Kill, "Trigger."
EPISODE 5
TRIGGER