Overview
Tokyo
Depart from Harumi
Arrive at Harumi
The Shirase leaves port
in Japan in mid-November,
heads south across the
ocean towards Antarctica,
Fremantle
Arrival
Departure
Fremantle
Sidney
Cross the 55th Parallel
and makes a port call
in Fremantle on the way.
Australia!
There, they'll resupply and bring
the expedition members on board.
Then as December begins, they'll set
course for the continent of Antarctica.
The people don't board in Japan?
They haven't done that for a long time.
Fremantle           Sidney
Nowadays, people typically
board at Fremantle,
then fly home from Sidney.
So while the Shirase is in port there,
we'll want to take a plane
from Japan to Fremantle.
Fremantle
Cross the 55th Parallel
Then we'll board the Shirase...
and head for Antarctica.
Syowa Station
Depart Syowa Station
Will they let us on?
Antarctic expeditions are
typically a state enterprise.
The boat is manned by the SDF,
and the expedition members have to
pass strict screenings and training.
High schoolers would never be allowed in.
However...
This year is special.
What's this year?
Civilian Antarctic Expedition to Take Place for the
First Time in Three Years
A revival of the "Antarctic Challenge,"
the first civilian Antarctic expedition held
three years ago, has been announced.
"Civilian Antarctic Expedition to Take
Place for the First Time in Three Years"?
The moment I saw that smile,
I felt a shiver run through my heart.
"Is this what trembling with
anticipation means?" I wondered.
I'm currently making the
most preposterous, absurd,
and enormous plans I've ever made.
Hand-Roasted
Beans
Port City Cafe
Hey, is that a submarine?
Yeah.
Subj:  Dear Mom
A Place Further Than the Universe
#MustBe18 #PartTimeJob #Seduction #Robots
Kabukicho Fremantle
2 Likes
2 Comments
Short-Term Jobs With High Pay
Easy Work For Beginners
Girls' Tea Series
Girls' Strawberry Tea
Gotta be eighteen for this one, too, huh?
Oh? Looking for part-time work?
Morning. And yeah.
I told you about the cost of
the plane ticket yesterday.
Shirase-chan wants me to earn it in advance.
Antarctica, huh?
Yeah. She also said, since I'll
have to take time off from school,
I should attend every day now while I can.
Hey, look! This one's perfect!
What is it?
They're hiring high school-aged girls!
It's in the hospitality industry.
It's a job where you talk to boys
and go on walks with them and stuff.
If you do really well, you could
even make a million yen per month...
If they catch you, you're dead.
I'll be fine!
I'll turn in a part-time job
permission form to the school.
You're so ignorant.
Setting the money aside, do you
really think they'll let you go?
Yeah! Shirase-chan told me all about it.
She's got some friends on the civilian
Antarctic expedition that's going this year, so...
Easy on Hands
Sincerity Chalk
I did some research,
and it sounds a little dicey.
Struggles to Fund Civilian Antarctic Expedition
"Four years ago, with the
completion of new stations
and commissioning of a new icebreaker ship,
the Shirase II and Syowa Station
were sold to civilian interests,
but they've struggled with
maintenance and operation costs.
The expedition members and sponsor companies
involved in the last
expedition three years ago
have also been announcing
their withdrawal one by one,
and the safety of participants
may not be ensured.
As a result, more and more voices are
speaking up against the project itself"...
Tamaki-san! Tamaki-san!
Yes?!
Analyzing the assertions of...
Why does he assert that love and
courage are everything?
Would you kindly read the next passage?
Yes sir!
"This, combined with the financial problems,
is causing concern regarding"— Wagh!
And what comes after "Wagh"?
Rose Rose Rose Rose Rose Rose Rose Rose
Lemon Lemon Lemon Lemon
Depression Depression Depression Depression
Depression Depression Depression
Still so much to write...
I haven't had to write lines
since elementary school...
You shouldn't have been reading it in class.
But I just couldn't wait...
So, what else?
There's nothing else.
For now, there's nothing about
the project being canceled.
Then, it's okay, right?
You sure?
We lend manga
Even if it hasn't been canceled, it won't
be that simple for you to get on.
Just because it's for civilians
doesn't change that.
Oh, but Shirase-chan is the
daughter of an expedition member!
It's not like getting
family seats at a concert.
They're not gonna let you
on the ship that easily.
I see...
You're probably right.
You're going to see her soon, right?
You should just ask her straight up.
Okay... got it.
Depression Depression
Depression Depression Got it
Sorry!
Punctuality is crucial.
That goes double when we're in Antarctica.
A few minutes can mean the
difference between life or death.
But I told you, the teacher got mad at me...
Did you find a job?
I told you to pick one by today.
I know, but...
Look, it's just the cost of
a ticket to Australia, right?
I'm sure I can scrape up the
money over summer vacation...
You should have as much money
as possible, just in case.
Here, I looked for you.
Really?
Girls in high school.
A job in the hospitality industry.
You talk to boys and go on
walks with them, it says.
Nice wage, isn't it?
Yeah, it is...
Here come the PonPon Girls!
If you hit the jackpot,
you can take me home with you!
R-Really?
Yeah, Megu-chan had to
tell me about it, too...
I guess you can be pretty stupid
sometimes, too, Shirase-chan...
I'm not stupid!
I just didn't know.
High School Girl Outing Requests
Michika's Diary
T-san, thanks for always asking for me!
I went out with T-san and Tada who always ask for me!
I said I love barbecue, so he took me out to that famous restaurant!
New Message
Did you ask Antarctica?
What was that?
A friend of mine.
She's worried about whether or
not they'll really let us go.
You don't believe me?
It's not that I don't believe you...
Well, no big
Antarctic News
Did you ask Antarctica?
But there's no guarantee, I guess...
Struggles to Fund Civilian Antarctic Expedition
I mean, it's pretty worrying, right?
And even if it isn't canceled,
we don't know if they'll let us join...
They will.
I'm the daughter of
Kobuchizawa Takako, after all.
You're sure?
Is that enough to qualify?
I assure you, it is.
You think so? But...
If you don't want to do this
anymore, you can just say so.
How dare you try to blame it on me...
It's not that I don't want to do it!
I just don't want to fail!
I don't want to think
"I just shouldn't have bothered!"
I would rather think "I wish I'd gone!"
"I wish I'd followed Shirase-chan's plan!"
I really am aware of the whole situation.
I've thought up a plan, too.
You do?
Yeah.
I'll explain the whole thing, so you
should keep making your preparations.
Okay, sure thing!
Part-time Employees Wanted
I got a job!
Welcome!
Do you wish me to warm that up for you?
Well, you can learn it as you go.
First, handle the restocking.
Miyake-san over there
will tell you what to do.
Yes, sir!
Excuse me...
Um, I'm Tamaki. I'm joining
the team as of today.
I look forward to working with you.
Tamaki?
Tamaki Mari.
Oh, that's why you're "Kimari".
I'm Miyake Hinata.
How old're you?
Sixteen. Second year high school.
Same here! Nice to meetcha!
L-Likewise...
You go to Tatara Nishi High, right?
Yeah, "Tanishi."
Why the sudden need for a job?
There's a place I want
to go, so I need money.
Would that place happen to be...
Antarctica?
Polar
Drink
Weddell Seal
Soda
You want to go?
Yeah, apparently she's been
listening in on our conversations.
Hey, you make it sound
like I did it on purpose.
I wasn't eavesdropping.
You two were just talking so loud!
Loud?
"If you don't want to do this, just say so!"
"It's not that I don't want to do it!"
Enough! We get it!
That piqued my curiosity.
Then straight after,
Kimari came in to get a job, y'know?
And I got to thinking, it's gotta be destiny!
Just to be clear, this isn't a game.
I know that!
It's dangerous, and you
need to pay your own way.
We're heading out in December, so you'll
need to take time off from school, too.
I'm okay! It's all good!
I've got money from my job,
and I don't go to school.
What, really?
It's not that surprising, is it?
You see them from time to time...
Sixteen-year-olds who don't go to school.
Don't get the wrong idea, though.
I'm as smart as anyone.
I got my high school certificate
and I got an A rating
in the recent mock exam.
And you're still only in your second year?
Does that mean you're going to college?
Yep!
My current dream is to ace
everything and show up everyone
who goofs off in high school and fails!
But then how would you have
time to go to Antarctica?
A reasonable question,
but I still have almost two
years before entrance exams,
and when I think about how I'll spend
next year knuckling down for exams,
it makes me want to do something
special while I can.
I get you! I so get you!
If you don't do it this year,
you'll never get another chance, right?
Exactly!
Ah, must my sixteenth year come and go,
with nothing but meat buns
and oden to show for it?
Precisely!
I'd love to have a drink out with you!
Even though I don't drink!
Same here!
Shut up!
I'm the one making the plans here.
You need to follow my instructions.
We never said we wouldn't...
What? Is she the irritable type?
A tad.
This describes my plan.
We'll put it into action this Sunday.
This Sunday, then.
Okay.
Bye-bye!
How'd it go?
What do you think of her plan?
Dunno!
Seems like it'll be pretty tricky...
Yeah, it does...
But she knows a lot more
about Antarctica than we do,
so it seems to me that we might as well try.
"If you can still turn back,
it's not really a journey.
When you hit the point of no return,
that's the moment it becomes a journey."
That sounds like a quote!
Who said it originally?
Me!
Oh.
I'm happy, though.
I've always liked you two.
You know? My store's close to Tanishi,
so students come in all the time.
Right...
But you two seemed different, somehow.
You've got a different sort of vibe, I guess.
No one's ever said that to me before...
I really hate the thought
of blending in with a crowd.
That's why I couldn't handle high school.
I really envied you two.
Envied what about us?
Hard to say...
The honesty, I guess?
Normal
Kuki
Do you feel sufficiently flattered?
Well...
That's how Hinata-chan works
her way into your heart!
See you!
Sure!
Well, we'll do the best we can
Shinjuku!
Shinjuku Station
Cool it with the gawking!
They'll know we're from Gunma!
But everything's flashing!
I don't know where to look!
Calm down!
Kimari! Wait for me!
Don't leave me behind!
Hey! That's not her!
Kabukicho Ichibangai
K-Kabukicho...
Y-You've never been here before?
Ladies' Cabaret Club
Mahjong
3F
Rental Rooms
I've never been here at night, I guess...
I said I'd be spending the
night at Megu-chan's, but...
Free Information Center
You don't think the police'll
take us in, do you?
I'll be fine, but your school might
get mad at you if they find out.
Just for walking around?
Well, it is Kabukicho...
Don't worry. Just act like you're in college.
Hey, here for a good time?
Just for a bit. Just stop in for a bit.
I'm with friends! I'm with friends!
What should we do?
It's funny. Just let it play out.
Free Information Center
Information on Entertainment, Bars
This way to entrance
I found it! The Antarctic
expedition informal meet-up!
Orange
Reserved Today
Antarctic Expedition Informal
Meet-up
Sexy Delicious!
Meat Festival
Really?
Information Center
Come right in!
Okay, do it just like we planned.
But this only says "lure someone out."
What does that mean?
Well, there are normally a lot of
male participants in an expedition,
so I thought, being high school girls...
Are you talking about seducing them?
Well, Shirase-chan is beautiful, after all.
Me? No, I didn't mean me!
Wait, were you planning
to make one of us do it?
There's no way!
They're here! What do we do?
Kimari! Please!
No! Hey!
Kimari! Go!
Information Center
Cabaret Club Girls' Bar
Marilyn
How old-fashioned are you?!
Then you do it, Hinata-chan!
Look! If we don't do something,
they'll go without us!
Show some leg!
I'm wearing pants!
Your breasts, then! Stick out your breasts!
Are you mocking me?!
Besides, the best breasts belong to...
No! No!
Go! You wanna go to Antarctica, right?
Yeah! It's not fair! You are the
one who came up with this plan!
No! Besides, it can't be me!
Why can't it be you?
Yeah!
Shirase-chan?
She never gives up, does she?
Who was that?
Why did you bow to them?
What is this, school?
Are you an honor student?
I told you it couldn't be me!
Why not?
They know me!
So if they see me, they'll catch...
Ugh. There's three of them...
Run.
Run!
Hey, you!
Hinata-chan, you run fast!
Over short distances, sure!
Think we should split up for now?
Yeah.
Where should we meet up?
Coordinate with cell phones!
All right!
Secret Path of Memories
They're still chasing us!
They're part of the expedition team,
so they've got tons of stamina!
Should we split up, too?
Sorry!
Okay!
What's so funny?
I was just thinking... this is pretty fun.
Fun?
Yeah. It's like... motion!
I feel like my youth is in motion!
Yeah... this is what it is.
Like anything could happen.
Like I could make anything happen!
The scenery that surrounds me every
day is changing at a dizzying rate.
Drinking outside really is the best!
Isn't it great?
Let's go drinking over there today.
Bye-bye!
Cafe Room
You didn't have to exhaust
yourselves running away.
It's not like we were trying to kill you.
Though she actually might.
Kanae.
But... Shirase-chan said...
Yeah, she said you'd have
our heads if you caught us.
I never said that!
This is quite a plan you
came up with, though...
In other words, get a male
expedition member on your side
so he'll smuggle you on board, right?
You naughty girls.
Whose idea was this?
Yeah, that figures.
Look, Shirase-chan.
I've told you many times before:
we can't take you with us.
It may be a civilian expedition,
but there are strict requirements for—
I know that!
I know I'm being unreasonable!
But... I really want to go.
Because... my mother is waiting there.
Shirase-chan?
What is this?
It's just what it looks like.
You're having trouble with funding, right?
Let me become one of your sponsors!
If you take me along,
you can have the money!
She really thought this through, huh?
Fine.
Come to Fremantle on December 1st.
Really?
Is that what you expected to hear?
You don't have to worry
about us. We're going,
no matter what.
Takako! Takako!
Well, I do understand how she feels.
It's been three years.
Are we really okay for funding, though?
I told you before, didn't I?
It might be tough, but I have lots of ideas.
Shiraishi-san...
Yeah. And here's step one!
Your mother, huh?
Well, don't get too down.
It's not necessarily ove—
We're almost there if I'd had a little
more money she would have taken it
so I just need a little more and
she'll definitely accept it...
A glass-half-full type, huh?
I guess.
Well, you'd have to be, to get this done.
Yeah.
However!
I am introducing an emergency motion!
I request a dismissal of
Kobuchizawa Shirase as group leader!
All in favor?
Me!
Majority rules!
Thus, you are hereby dismissed as leader!
Now, let's go to Antarctica!
Yeah!
Huh?!