I thought that maybe I could
get it to move, but...
Saito!
I knew it.
You're in love with him.
You're always staring at him.
It's plain as day.
B-But he's already...
He's married?
No.
Then you still have a chance.
You've got quite the
set of weapons there.
Why don't you use them?
B-But...
Huh?
It's Ari and Maddarf.
That's not what we agreed upon!
It was said that I could
watch over them...
I can't do anything about this.
It's an order.
Come on.
Hurry up!
What the hell are you doing?
The committee decided that they
want to reevaluate what
to do with you directly.
Just shut up and come with me.
Escape Through the Sewer
Once we pass over this range,
we'll be in elf territory.
That means we could be assaulted
by the elven army at any time.
What will we do then?
You have to ask?
We Undine Knights will fight and...
No.
We will just run.
The strength that the Ostland gains
from running on steam is her speed.
We'll run and run and run some more.
Th-That's the plan?
Yes.
Then we'll go their capital, Adil,
and locate Saito and Miss Westwood.
Let's do that.
The faster we get to them,
the higher the chance
that they are still safe.
Yes.
Saito...
You're still okay, right?
We're coming for you, I promise.
Hang on!
I've brought them.
Hey, Bidalsha!
If you harm Tiffa in any way...
Be quiet.
If you want to be safe,
just endure it, no matter what they say.
So this is her.
She has our elven blood,
but she gained the power of the demon.
How truly frightening!
Be careful around Eshmael.
He's known for hating
barbarians the most
among the elders of the committee.
When those who wield
the power of the demon
and their familiars gather,
four and four in number,
the Spiritual Continent
will be destroyed.
Everybody knows this
6000 year old prophecy.
Right now, the barbarians are
busy gathering those who
wield the demon power,
and this time, they will not stop
until they've destroyed us elves.
That's not true!
Nobody wants to do that!
There is one thing we can do
before the nightmare
of 6000 years ago is repeated.
That is to kill these demons,
thus preventing the four and
four from being united!
That's right!
Kill them, kill them!
If we do that, how are we any
better than the barbarians?
Locking them away would
be enough to keep the four
and four from uniting.
He's exactly right!
We elves are a noble race and—
Open your eyes!
If it was only the barbarians,
I could potentially accept it.
But to think that one who looks like us
carries the power of the demon!
Like this corrupted girl!
Don't hurt her!
My blades!
You all saw the foul ways
of these barbarians.
Do you still dispute the
need to kill them?
Kill them!
We cannot forgive them!
Kill, kill!
Hold still.
Ouch...
Thank you, Tiffa.
No, thank you for standing up for me.
And...
Tiffa...
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Hey, I told you before.
You've got nothing to apologize for.
But they're doing this
because I'm a half-elf.
Saito, leave me here and run away.
I'm sure you could make
it if you were alone.
What are you talking about?
I could never do that!
I'm staying here with you.
And I'm going to protect you.
Saito...
I love you.
At first, I thought I was just jealous,
because Louise had found
a dependable familiar,
but now I know that's not it.
Whenever I'm around you,
my heart beats so fast.
That means I love you, right?
I guess so.
I know I shouldn't, but just once.
Just once will be enough...
Saito?
Saito? Saito? Saito?!
I see...
So I was summoned back when you did
the Summoning Ceremony in Romalia.
Yes, I think so.
It felt like you had
appeared from the gate.
But I figured that wasn't possible,
since you are Louise's familiar.
Yeah. I've never heard of anyone
being two people's familiar
at the same time.
But then again, these runes did appear.
I wonder what these mean.
Oh, what's this?
I thought you'd be all depressed,
but it looks like you're doing
pretty well for yourself.
Derf?
What the hell are you guys doing here?
That's not a very warm welcome
to those who came to help you escape.
Just so you know,
I'm here to guard Bidalsha and Lukshana.
Both of them absolutely
insisted on doing this.
Come.
I see it.
Sir! Malicorne spotted an elven ship
with his far sight magic!
Is it a fleet?
He said he saw only one ship...
Then it's a patrol ship.
Guiche, set the steam
engines to full power.
Aye, aye, sir!
We'll accelerate and escape.
If we do get attacked, I'm
counting on you, Miss Zerbst.
Leave it to me, Jean.
Just threaten them.
We didn't come here to wage war.
Yes. I understand completely.
An unidentified ship is
approaching from the front.
What?
Looks like a barbarian ship.
Is it a merchant ship?
No.
A merchant ship can't move that fast.
Prepare the artillery!
It's moving too fast.
We won't make it.
Turn around and follow that ship!
Alert others in the area for backup!
Scramble the dragon riders!
My uncle designed this sewer
system when he was younger.
He knows all of these
passageways by heart.
I hope this isn't a trap.
Thanks for trusting us.
Well, you're the ones who
abducted us in the first place!
I already told you.
I only participated in this
for research purposes.
Not to kill you.
Now I see why my uncle
was against it, though.
I guess he saw something
like this coming.
He was against it?
I did suspect that upon seeing you,
many of our comrades would not be able
to keep their hatred in check.
The history of violence
between the barbarians
and us is just too long.
I thought it could work if we
kept you secluded in her oasis,
but then Eshmael overruled everything.
Why did you take Joseph's side?
Out of fear.
Fear?
When we heard that the
demon powers had returned,
I approached Joseph to
investigate it further.
I needed to understand the
truth behind this power.
So that's why you did those
horrible things to Tabitha?
It was his condition.
If we wanted his cooperation,
we had to bow to him.
That's when I knew that
the true terror was not
in this power alone,
but in the hearts of those
who wielded such power.
Like the fire stones that were used
for peaceful purposes in Neftes.
In Joseph's hands, they became
weapons of mass destruction.
I swear that I will never
use the power of the Void
for a negative purpose
or to hurt people!
Yeah! Louise would never do
something like that, either.
I can guarantee it!
I believe you.
Once you exit this door,
you'll be just outside the town.
You can use the dragons to cross
the desert and return home.
Uncle, what's wrong?
They expected this.
It was Bidalsha who tried
to help them escape.
Just as you anticipated.
You've sealed the sewers, right?
That's the only place
that he could run to.
I wouldn't have imagined that I
could rid myself of my long-standing
enemy in such a manner.
Send the troops there!
It's been sealed with
the power of sprites.
No sword will open it.
Huh?
Maddarf?
You came just at the right time!
I had been forced to play along with
Lukshana's crazy demands again.
Please take these barbarians
back to their cell already.
Ari!
Maddarf, what are you doing?!
I have orders to kill the demon
and those who consort with it.
Good work, pal!
Derf, we're breaking through!
Don't kill anyone!
It will only fuel the flames of hatred!
She's right.
We're gonna chase them all away!
Yeah!
Roger.
Ice Storm!
It's a fleet!
We've been ambushed!
Our speed is...
Sir, the engine's power is waning.
It can't handle any more.
I see.
Stop the engine.
But, sir...
There's no way we can outrun
their fleet at this speed.
We'll stop the ship and
see how they respond.
Wait, Miss Vallière!
I can take down the elven ships
with my Explosion spell.
Taking down those ships
will serve no purpose.
It's far more dangerous to
reveal to them that you are a Void Mage.
Siesta, please take Miss
Vallière somewhere safe.
Yes, sir!
This way!
Mists of Sleep!
Crap!
He's copying Ari...
Guys, please help us.
This way.
I can't get it open.
They're over there!
After them!
Turn into a wall.
You can't escape anyway!
Are these all the people on the ship?
Did you really expect to face
us with this band of children?
Our only objective was to rescue
our friends who were
abducted by you elves.
Once we've fulfilled that objective,
we will return home at once.
Abducted?
Have you heard of this?
No.
We finally made it to the desert,
but is this as far as we go?
No. I won't give up.
I won't rest until I
see you again, Saito.
Saito... Saito...
Even my uncle's magic is
not powerful enough...
What the...
Listen up, demons!
Once I break a hole in that wall,
I'm going to fill it with poisonous gas!
Poisonous gas?
Saito, we're done for.
We can't give up.
You just have to believe
that it will work out!
I will see Louise again.
Louise...
Saito... Saito... Saito... Saito...
Louise!
Saito!
What the...
Ken, gyolf, hagaras...
Soyl, beorc, daeg...
Miss Vallière?!
Son, wyad...
Louise!
Saito... Saito, is that you?
Yeah! It's me!
Saito!
Louise...
My power is being replenished...
Saito, I missed you so much!
I missed you too, Louise.
Tiffa, come on. Quick!
R-Right!
Saito!
Oh... I guess the relief got me...
Hey, can we come, too?
If we stay here, we'll be killed.
Uh... Sure.
Lukshana, what are you talking about?
We can't ask barbarians for help!
Say your prayers, demons!
Huh?
Right now, we can't
confirm whether your
story about this abduction
is true or not.
For now, I'll have to take
you into custody and—
Sadly, it is the truth, Raiid.
You're... Master Bidalsha!
It's been a while.
I'm filled with pride to
see that one of my students
has risen to the rank of captain.
What are you doing here?
I will tell you the details later.
At the consideration
of our past as teacher and student,
I ask that you let this ship go.
Tiffa, I'm so glad you're safe!
Everyone was so worried about you!
Thanks, everyone.
So, how did you get Saito and Tiffa out?
I don't know.
I was wishing really hard
that I could see Saito again,
when suddenly something
like a window opened.
When I looked on the other
side, Saito was there.
This must be some new Void magic.
And then, when I grabbed Saito's hand,
it felt as if power was flowing into me.
Oh yeah, I was glowing back then.
It looks like I've become
Tiffa's familiar, too.
I got these runes on me.
Sir, can you tell me what this says?
Now hold on!
You became Tiffa's familiar?
So that means you k-k-k-ki...
Kissed.
That is what that means, right?
Huh?
Is that really true?
Well, I guess we did,
but that's not what's
important right now.
What's going to happen to us now?
Back in Adil, we're wanted people now.
Then let's not go back.
Let's stay on this ship and go
to the barbarians' country.
What?
We can't do that!
That's a good idea. You should do that.
You, too? You can't be serious!
They won't follow you there.
I will go back to Adil,
but I will stay underground for a while.
Take me with you.
No. It's too dangerous.
Stop right there, Saito!
You promised you wouldn't cheat on me!
And you've already got me for a lover!
I won't forgive you...
You're not listening to me!
You stupid perv dog!
Saito was supposed to be my
familiar, but now you're telling
me he's Tiffa's familiar, too?!
Do you think that's reason enough
to get all cozy with Tiffa?!
Next time:
Tabitha's Coronation.
I am your number one master!
Tabitha's Coronation