Huh?
Mizusawa High School Athletic Festival
It's time for the main event in the
second half of the Mizusawa
High School Athletic Festival!
The finals for the club relay!
We have six teams who won their
way through the prelims,
including the favorite, the track team,
as well as the speedy
baseball and soccer teams!
Our Nationals-bound tennis team
has also shown their ability to run!
You'll want to watch the basketball team
as they use a ball for their baton!
However, all eyes will be on the
Karuta Club
non-athletic Karuta club,
which has managed to sneak in to sixth!
the red that is the Tatsuta River
On your marks.
Set.
How can this be?!
The Karuta club had the best start!
They already have a considerable lead!
But the track team is also fast!
Taichi!
Their second runners take over
at almost the exact same time!
Mashima-kun!
The second runner for the
Karuta club is just as fast!
They're neck and neck
with the track team!
What's this?
The basketball team and soccer
team have dropped their batons!
The tennis team and baseball
team are also having trouble!
Meanwhile, the track team and Karuta club
are on their third runners!
The cheers are deafening!
Hang in there, Karuta club!
Oh!  But the fourth runner
is falling behind!
The baseball team and soccer
team have caught up!
And now each team turns to their anchor!
He's fast!  Surprisingly fast!
Who said this team wasn't athletic?!
They're clearly athletes!
Oh, no!
The track team lost their baton!
Our favorite has fallen in the last leg!
Nobody could have seen this coming!
As our runners turn the final corner,
the baseball team and
Karuta club are in the lead!
Can the Karuta club stage a comeback!
Will the baseball team
hold onto its lead?!
Who will be our winner?!
Recruiting
new members
Incredible!  The Karuta club has won!
Chihaya Furu
Verse 17
World
Offers
No
Escape
Nobody's coming...
We worked so hard to win.
To get everyone's attention...
Chihaya-chan, a girl shouldn't
lie on the floor.
But...
Some people came to watch us play,
but they left because
it looked too hard.
We came in first,
but it was mostly luck.
I was slow.
What are you talking about?
You were fast!
Our summer training really helped!
You think so?
Hey, guys.
We finished our research.
Looking at the tournaments near Tokyo,
we have the Saitama tournament
in late September
and the Kawaguchi tournament
in early October.
There's also the East
Master/Queen qualifier
for Class A and higher players in late October.
The Eastern qualifier...
for deciding the East
representative to challenge
the Queen next January.
The most important
tournament every year.
Chihaya needs to play
more matches to get experience.
Nishida and I need to win
a Class B tournament
so we can make Class A.
Okay!
Oe-san and Komano,
you'll need some Class D wins,
so you can start moving up.
Then we should all focus
on our individual g-
Oh, excuse me for a second.
Yeah.
Okay, fine.
Let's break up.
Then we should all focus
on our individual goals!
What?!
No luck with girls
Prez!  What was that?!
No luck
with guys
Didn't even bat an eye!
No luck with girls
It took him a second to dump her!
No luck with guys
I never knew you had a girlfriend!
Let's practice.
It was the girl who called him "Ta-kun"!
Arata...
Will Arata...
be in the Western qualifier?
people would always ask if
I was pining for someone
After I determined...
I can make it in time!
In the sleepy...
Make Class A before October...
a whirlwind of flower petals descends
...so I can play in the Eastern qualifier!
Thank you very much.
Okay, let's take a ten minute break
before we get one more match in today.
The training we did over the summer
Mizusawa Fight!
was hard, but fun.
On!
Fight!
Mizusawa!
Especially compared to
last summer, when I spent
all my time studying alone.
But...
Even though I trained as
hard as everyone else,
I'm still small and can't build muscle.
Kana-chan.
When you have time,
you should do sit-ups
and back extensions at home.
Huh?
I noticed something
after watching all those
matches at nationals.
When girls and thinner boys play Karuta,
they tend to sit back,
so you end up only
using your upper body.
It's probably because your muscles aren't
strong enough to support your weight.
I've been training at home,
but it hasn't really helped.
Don't worry!
You just have to keep working at it!
I need to go to the restroom.
What is it, Desktomu-kun?
Oh, you're working hard on your swing.
I've been thinking.
I can't beat Chihaya-chan and the other
members at cards that are farther away,
but I can win the cards that
are closer by bringing them in.
If I can move in a straight line
to the cards that are farther away,
I'll be in a position to take advantage
of my opponent's mistakes.
It won't matter if I'm
not athletic enough.
After the athletic festival,
everyone was saying
that Karuta was a sport,
but I consider Karuta an art.
Because men and women
can compete against
each other in Karuta.
I won't let you beat me, Desktomu-kun.
This isn't happening!
I don't get Karuta at all!
I'm glad I chose to
give Karuta a chance.
I can change.
I know it.
And not just physically or mentally...
Hey, is there a point to this exercise?
I'm not sure, but don't stop!
I need to hone my reflexes if I'm going
to put up a fight against
the Queen, I think...
Too slow!
Straight to the card...
How can I learn to do
what Shinobu-chan does?
Hey, I'm going to the tournament
in Kanazawa this weekend.
Wanna come along?
Huh?  Kanazawa?
Wasn't it in Saitama?
The Saitama tournament is next weekend.
There's another tournament
before that one in Kanazawa,
for Class A and B players.
I'm coming!  I'm coming!
Is Kanazawa really far away?
How much will it cost?
It's 8,000 yen if you
take a one-way, overnight bus.
Add in the participation fee,
and it's around 20,000.
Well, I doubt anyone
else can afford it.
I'll go by myself.
No fair!
That's no fair, Taichi!
I'll buy you a souvenir.
Lucky you.  Kanazawa, huh?
That's near Fukui...
Mommy!
Don't look.
Impressive.
I hate myself for being so sneaky.
MISSING!
For trying to become better at
Karuta before everyone else.
For trying to go on a
trip with Chihaya.
Chihaya.
What?
I'm...
I'm going to make Class A.
Good luck.
Hmm?
Huh?
What?!
What are you doing, Nishida?!
What about you?!
You never said anything about this!
Over there!  Keep it down!
There was someone else just as sneaky!
Why are you here?
A senpai from my Karuta
society invited me,
so I have dibs.
Dibs?  That's bull!
What about you?
Took a plane.
Stupid rich boy!
So you're trying to reach Class A first!
So are you!
No, I need to focus on my match.
Concentrate...
We will now begin memorization time.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
Win.
I have to win!
Like a boatsman adrift...
H-He's fast!
While autumn leaves crunch...
Since I could not hide...
Impassionate gods...
the red that is the Tatsuta River
Chihaya-chan has really improved.
Her match against the
Queen must have helped.
You'll notice once you play against her.
She's much faster now.
Her opponents aren't even
close on her sweet cards.
She can give the Queen a run
for her money on those.
I still see her in my dreams.
I need to match her speed, her edge!
Impassioned vows exchanged
over many a tear shed to last
when I should have gone to sleep instead
Oh!  Oops!
Ow, that's a fault.
That's where the "Impassionate"
card was before.
Chihaya-chan hasn't been able
to cut down on her mistakes.
She's too concerned about
the "Impassion—" cards.
Thank you very much.
I was doing okay for a while,
but I ended up losing to you
in the end, Hiroshi-san.
You may be fast, Chihaya-chan,
but you don't scare me.
Huh?
Chihaya-chan, stop taking
cards with your speed.
The 1st Career Survey
First Choice
Second Choice
Queen
The survey is due on Thursday.
We have materials in the career
guidance office, so drop by.
This is your own future,
so think very carefully!
Yes, ma'am!
Kana-chan, you'll be going
to a university that has
classical literature, right?
Oe Traditional
Clothing
I know what I want to major in,
but I'm not sure which
university I want to go to.
Is Chihaya-chan acting like that
because of the survey?
Beats me...
What's wrong with them?
Brutal...
Qualifying for Class A is brutal!
Ayase!  Get out of the
corner and play me!
Hey!  That's no fair!
I have to play strong
opponents to get better!
Come on!  Let's play!
Uh-huh...
Huh?
What's wrong, Chihaya?
Did something happen?
Chihaya-chan?
Chihaya-chan, stop taking
cards with your speed.
Huh?
What do you mean, Dr. Harada?
I can't win without my speed.
Chihaya-chan, what did you think
about the Queen's Karuta?
She was super fast!
I couldn't believe how fast she was!
Anything else?
She was accurate!
Like she was always aiming for
a certain spot on the card!
But she was still fast!
Every player wishes they
could have her speed...
You don't have to be fast.
Chihaya-chan, how many
sweet cards do you have?
Five?  Ten?
It doesn't matter if you can
take a few cards really fast.
If you lose all of the other
cards, you lose the match.
Stop concentrating on speed.
Huh?
That's what Dr. Harada said?
What does Ayase have,
if you take away her speed?
She doesn't use any strategy.
So your sharp senses are
actually hurting you.
Hey, Chihaya.
Is she actually trying
to think this through?
Usually, when she runs
into a difficult problem,
she gives up within ten seconds!
I look too.
I don't get it.
Why shouldn't I take cards fast?
What is he talking about?
The next round is Nishida vs. Mashima
and Ayase vs. me, right?
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
Impassionate gods...
That's the problem!
He's talking about how
you move too fast!
Oh, he means this?
Seriously, none of the
other Impassion cards have been read yet.
My body kinda moves by itself...
Primal instinct.
Are you finished?
I'm going to read the next card.
the red that is the Tatsuta River
In order to restore my faith...
My own sleeves are like...
Look for the sound...
A 15-card win!  Good!
Today, there were 6 B cards, 10 C cards.
And 0 A and D cards.
What's that?
The distribution of the
cards I've won against you
over the course of the 28 matches
Vs. Ayase
Ayase
Komano
1) The "Impassionate" card in my right middle row is taken by Ayase.
She sends "The sound of people" from her right lower row to my right lower row.
2) I take "In order to" from her right middle row.
"In order for" is on my side and Ayase was focused on taking that card from me.
I send "I feel as" from my right middle side to her right middle side.
we played in August and September.
One percent of the cards I take come
from region A on the opponent's side.
Sixty-seven percent come from
region B on the opponent side.
Thirty-two percent come
from region C on my side.
Zero percent come from
region D on my side.
What?!
You've been keeping track of all that?!
That means I win almost all
of the cards in A and D!
But that also means that
I'm able to take a considerable
number of cards from B and C.
I can't take any one-syllable
cards from you,
but you have trouble with
three-syllable cards.
So I would place them in C, where you are weak,
and constantly attack your left side.
I'm sure you come up against people
who use these strategies.
Hey, what about me?
Show me mine!
Not for nothing.
You hog!
It doesn't matter if you can
take a few cards really fast.
If you lose all of the other
cards, you lose the match.
Chihaya-chan, you
commit a lot of faults.
Huh?
You gamble because you want
to take a card faster.
For example, take "May the time
spent" and "May the time we."
Oh, a lot of people have
trouble with those.
Since the poems are also similar!
Silence!
"May the time we" is #19.
"May the time spent" is #88.
They're separated by two
hundred years of history!
Years?!
May the time we spend
apart from one another be
as short-lived as the
reeds of Naniwa Bay
May the time spent in
our one night together
bring a life of everlasting love
Both poems were written by women,
and they describe similar situations.
I find it moving that
two women separated by 200 years
would express themselves in similar ways,
but that's not important right now.
Chihaya-chan.
You told me that the
"Impassionate" card looks
bright red to you.
"May the time we,"
from the 10th century,
refers to the withered green
reeds of Naniwa Bay in winter.
"May the time spent,"
from the 12th century,
refers to the new green reeds
of Naniwa Bay in spring.
That's how I picture it.
Or you could say that
the Naniwa Bay in #88 had
more prostitutes at the time,
so the card should be rich green.
Kana-chan...
You really love poetry.
In my mind, Karuta is about
the meanings of the poems.
I was sad,
because, for me,
Karuta was about speed.
Goodbye, Ms. Miyauchi.
Yes, goodbye.
What?
Ayase-san is in the library?
Do they keep manga in there?
Ayase-san, you haven't turned
in your career survey yet.
Hurry up and...
Interpretation of
Hundred Poets
Speed isn't enough.
I need to learn from Desktomu-kun.
I need to learn from Kana-chan.