Karasuno              Aoba Johsai
Oikawa, you're back.
How's the ankle?
It's fine. I can get back
to regular practice.
It was just a slight sprain.
For crying out loud! Be careful.
You're the one that asked
to play against Kageyama.
What do we do without our official setter?
It's embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
Oikawa-san, take care of yourself!
Kageyama-kun, who's that laid-back guy?
I find him unpleasant.
He's the captain of Seijoh.
Oikawa-san is a super-aggressive setter.
His attack power is also
at the top of his team.
Even Kageyama acknowledges
that player's abilities...
And he's got a terrible personality.
Coming from you, that's scary...
Maybe even worse than Tsukishima.
He must be really bad.
Do you know him from Kitagawa Daiichi?
Yes.
He was my senpai in junior high.
A senpai of the King.
That would make him...
The Great King.
Yoo-hoo! Long time no see, Tobio-chan.
Haikyu!!
Long time no see, Tobio-chan.
Episode 7:  Versus the Great King
So nice to see you.
You still doing the King thing?
I learned serving and blocking
by watching him play.
His skills are extremely high.
He taught him those killer serves?
But we have to focus on the match now.
We're going to win the final set for sure.
Y-Yeah.
Tanaka-san, please stop
with the intimidation.
Anyway, go get warmed up.
Even more than usual.
Yes.
I'm crushing him. I'm serious.
Aoba Johsai              Karasuno
When's Oikawa-san going to play?
Idiot. He has to warm up
or he could get hurt.
That wouldn't be good!
Here, here, here.
Aoba Johsai              Karasuno
One more point.
Only one more point...
and we will beat Seijoh, rated in
the top four in the prefecture.
Don't get cocky!
Kindaichi, nice.
Don't mind, Tsukishima.
Oh my. We're in a crisis.
Did you get warmed up?
Perfectly.
Leave the rest to your senpai.
Yes.
He's here! The Great King!
Stop that.
Does that mean we're switching setters?
No, I think he's a pinch-server.
Oikawa, nice serve.
No matter how strong your offense is...
It means nothing if you can't connect to it.
What?
He aimed it at Tsukishima.
Tsukki.
Just as I thought.
I watched part of the match...
You, number 6, and you, number 5.
You're not good receivers, are you?
You must be first-years.
Like Kageyama...
No, even more powerful than him.
His ball control allows him
to hit it anywhere he wants.
So this is the captain of Seijoh.
Okay, let's score another one.
Tsukki!
Damn.
Don't mind, Tsukishima.
Tsukishima is always mean.
I hate him.
But this time...
Aoba Johsai          Karasuno
Oh. One more point and we're tied.
Hey. You, Great King.
Aim at me. I'll receive it. Aim here.
"Great King"?
Stop raising a fuss. It's embarrassing.
What did you say?
We're in real trouble,
and he still irritates me.
But... but...
Listen.
In volleyball,
everyone on this side
of the net is your ally.
What a beautiful adage.
All right. All of you scoot to the back.
Tsukishima, you go closer to the sideline.
Yes.
All right. Bring it.
Hmm.
Net
So Captain-kun, expert at receiving,
is expanding the defense...
However...
you can't defend it all by yourself.
Tsukki!
He's aimed it directly at the edge.
But he sacrficed some of his power
to get that accuracy.
It went up.
Tsukki, nice.
He got it. Good for him.
Maybe I made it too easy for him.
However...
This is our chance ball.
Damn.
There. A sweet, sweet chance ball.
Score it good, guys.
All right.
This is bad.
Our rotation has no height for blocking.
Kindaichi.
All right, I'll completely thwart the block...
The shrimp... how is he here?
It's up.
Nice one-touch.
Chance ball.
Damn! I'll slam it down the next time.
I can't catch up to him if I'm
one step, one second behind.
The only thing that can catch up to him...
is the ball.
Aoba Johsai          Karasuno
What was that?
He came from the other end
of the court, in a flash.
That toss was like it got sucked
into the spiker's hand.
Wow...
All right.
Line up.
What's the matter?
That was amazing.
Oh, right.
Today is your first time seeing
Hinata and Kageyama's attack.
Aren't they amazing?
I mean amazing, even scary.
Please coach us.
Sensei, maybe give a critique or something.
O-Oh, I see.
Um... I'm just a beginner when
it comes to volleyball, but...
But even I can tell, that something
amazing is going on here.
We have some amazing
first-years this semester.
They were hard to handle in the beginning,
but I learned something today.
We're nothing if don't cooperate.
A chemical synergy happens when
each one encounters the other...
Even this very moment is giving birth
to other encounters
that will change the world.
Maybe in some far, remote country.
Maybe on the other side of the planet.
Or maybe at an ordinary volleyball club,
at an ordinary high school,
in a northern countryside
on a small island in the east.
I think that encounters like that
happened to Karasuno today.
I know I can't prove what I say,
but it's better than not believing.
All of you will most likely
become stronger. Much stronger!
Sorry! That was a little too poetic!
Are you turned off?
No, no, no, of course not.
Thank you.
Oh, y-yeah.
Kindaichi.
All of us have had enough of him.
Sure he's got individual attack power,
but he's clearly impeding the team.
Kitagawa
Daiichi
To be frank,
we're better off without him.
Don't apologize!
Because I won't apologize, either.
Yeah.
You're still an oppressive king,
as far as I'm concerned.
You're irritating, and there's no one
I want to crush more than you.
Yeah.
So don't apologize.
I'm not reconciling with you.
We weren't friends in the first place.
Yeah.
And the next time, we'll win for sure.
The next time...
Toilet, toilet, toilet...
Who am I?
The guy who'll become the ace.
Oh crap. There's bad blood
between those two.
This vibe tells me I should stay back.
Kindaichi.
The next time we battle, we will win again.
What were you guys talking about?
He... said "we."
Did you cry?
He used to always say "I" like
he was the only one playing.
Of course I didn't cry, idiot.
Now go use the toilet.
You can't fool me, Kageyama-kun.
Hinata, you dumbass.
Damn...
I kind of feel defeated.
Wh-What was that for?
Thank you very much.
Takeda-sensei complimented us,
but frankly, if we were facing
Seijoh and Oikawa in an all-out match,
we'd be lacking.
Spoken like a true captain.
You know your stuff.
The Great King makes his entrance.
You got a problem, dude?
What do you want?
Wanna fight, huh?
Don't be so hostile.
You, little one.
Huh?
Your last one-touch and
broad attack were amazing.
Oh...
Let's give it all we got the next time,
right from the start.
You didn't get to see our set up.
Oh, yes, and we'll be
improving our serves, too.
That's true.
Those serves would come
continuously from the start.
It's true, your offense was amazing,
but your receives are slow.
You'll reach your limit very quickly.
I'm not the only one who
hits powerful serves.
The Inter-High preliminaries
are coming up soon.
Don't get eliminated, okay?
Because I...
want to pulverize my dear underclassman,
setter-on-setter, in an official match.
The receivers will train.
Hey, let go.
Receivers don't improve overnight.
Ask the captain. He should know.
There's not much time left
'til the tournament.
I look forward to seeing you there.
Don't let him get to you.
He likes to razz people like that.
It's true. We don't have much time
before the Inter-High preliminaries,
but he should be coming back soon.
Who's coming back soon?
The guardian deity of Karasuno.
Kageyama has become more amazing.
Yeah. That genius was spinning his wheels,
but finally found his best destination.
No commoner could a hold
a candle to him now.
Yeah? You're no match for him either, huh?
When it comes to the toss.
There's probably no one in the prefecture
who could match Tobio's toss.
But he's not better than me at
serving, blocking, or spiking.
Ouch.
Damn it, Oikawa!
Don't say his toss is better than yours!
You're a setter, aren't you?
But I'm only being honest.
That's why we have to break their receivers.
Because no matter how
amazing his tosses are,
if the ball doesn't get to the
setter, it's all for nothing.
If we can play against Karasuno
in the official tournament,
we can make a mess out of their receives,
and not even give them a chance at a toss.
Just having one good player
doesn't mean your team will win.
How I want to say "don't mind" to them.
How I want to say it.
What? Geniuses get irked by stuff like that.
I get more irked by guys
who get cheered on by girls.
You shouldn't be jealous Iwa-chan.
It's embarrassing.
Hey, quit fooling around.
Coach'll get mad.
All right, let's clean up quickly.
Then we're done.
Good job today.
Good job.
Hey.
Sensei, thank you for everything today.
No, no, everyone did a good job.
I'm shocked by how we beat
Aoba Johsai High School.
But we're still lacking.
Our offense is effective now due
to Hinata and Kageyama's dynamics,
but if Hinata gets in the way of the blocks,
Hinata, that's enough mopping. Go home.
or if the receives get broken
like they did today,
Look at that, Tsukki.
we would definitely find
ourselves at a loss.
Amazing.
And when that happens,
I don't know if I can guide the team
as a director or coach could.
I see...
I apologize. I'm not saying
that you're not good enough.
I know, I know.
I'll take care of finding a coach.
I have a lead.
Oh? Really? Who is it?
Foothill Store
I've been asking repeatedly, and
haven't got an affirmative yet,
but I will definitely make it happen.
Can I leave the rest to you for today?
Oh, yes.
Take-chan has an air of
confidence about him.
Yeah.
Equipment room
What's this?
This mop looks dangerous.
Can I throw it away?
Oh, don't worry about that. It's all right.
We can fix it, and still use it.
Huh?
Good job, everyone.
Good job.
Foothill Store
Chinese dumplings?
We have Karasuno
High School
Hallway slippers
The soccer club bought up the last of it.
Besides, we're closing for today.
I'm starving.
What a lazy clerk!
Shut up. Go home and eat a proper meal.
You won't get muscles if you don't.
Here.
Thanks.
Eat a proper meal.
Hooray~
Yes, yes.
Hello, Foothill Store.
You again?
But I gotta say...
Laid-Back sure has an amazing serve.
We would've been in trouble
if he'd played from the start.
He's Kageyama's junior high
senpai, after all...
Wait a second. Why are you
at Karasuno, Kageyama?
The strongest school in the
prefecture is Shiratorizawa.
Shiratori?
Shiratorizawa.
They're top in the prefecture.
They're a powerhouse school ranked
among the top eight in the country.
Oh.
I didn't make Shiratorizawa.
You didn't make it?
I never got a recommendation from them,
so I took a general entrance exam.
I don't know what
the meaning of that exam was.
That school is super hard to
get into by conventional means.
I guess the King isn't very good at studies.
See ya.
But why did you come to Karasuno?
Are you an admirer of the Little Giant, too?
I heard Director Ukai is
coming out of retirement.
Ukai?
An outstanding coach who took unknown
Karasuno to the spring nationals!
Wow.
The name "Ukai of Karasuno" is famous.
They called him the director
in charge of vicious ravens.
Second and third-years got
some coaching from him.
He was pretty Spartan.
Why do you look so envious?
Director Ukai was going to officially
come out of retirement, but...
He was hospitalized?
There's no information about
his recovery prospects. Sorry...
But I figured, no matter
what school I attended,
I'd be up against high
school students like me.
There's no reason why I couldn't win.
Cut the sour grapes.
You can act cool about it,
but you failed just the same.
That's not true.
I'm not acting cool about it.
We did defeat a top four
team today, didn't we?
True, 2-1 against Seijoh.
I was able to score one free, too,
thanks to Hinata's decoy.
Thanks.
But how was your
debut battle for you?
You really went crazy in that first set.
You scored as many points as you lost,
so don't get complacent.
Why must you say things like that?
That's right.
We're lacking in a lot of ways.
Today's victory was by
the skin of our teeth.
I-I will train a lot!
Oh, yeah. Individual level-upping
is important, too.
But Karasuno, as it currently stands,
is fundamentally short of members.
That's true.
We need a libero, especially for defense.
And we need an ace spiker who can
battle three blockers all by himself.
A-Ace? That can be me.
I told you, you're the best decoy.
But didn't you say the
"guardian god" is coming back?
Yeah.
We're not powerful, but we're
not particularly weak, either.
We had outstanding players in the past, too.
We were never able to apply
their strengths effectively.
But if all of us unite,
and we also have new strength
coming from our first-years,
if we're able to connect all
those strengths together...
we could definitely win...
...the Summer Inter-High
National Tournament.
It's not just a distant goal.
It can really happen.
The Summer Inter-High Tournament.
I've heard about it.
But that person who's coming back...
where has he been all this time?
He was suspended for one week,
and banned for a month from club activities.
A delinquent? He's a delinquent?
No... he just gets too fired up.
He's a good guy, for real.
If Tanaka-san says he gets "too fired up,"
how extreme could this guy be?
And not only that, he is...
a player we could say is
Karasuno's unique genius.
But not unique any more,
because now we also have
cocky-as-crap Kageyama with us.
Call him "senpai" when he comes back, Hinata.
You'll make him gleeful
like an idiot, like Tanaka.
Like an idiot?
"Guardian god"... I wonder what he's like.
Hey, we're leaving you behind.
Oh. Yes.
It's going to hit.
Hey, get out of the way,
dumbass Hinata!
That could've hit.
I got it. I got it.
You didn't get it, dumbass.
You hit a home run.
I'll go get it.
Idiot.
I got it this time.
Match for
a Thousand
He perfectly stopped
the momentum and rotation,
and accurately sent the ball
back to the setter.
That was a perfect receive.
Y-You're... shorter than me!
Next Episode Preview
What? What? What was that?
He came out of nowhere!
His receive was solid. The return floated.
That was kind of intense.
Well, it's not that we can't communicate...
Episode 8: He Who is Called "Ace"
Next time on Haikyu!!
"He Who is Called 'Ace'"