Just as was announced at
yesterday's music festival,
today is finally the day when the joint event
between the three countries begins.
Ahh, showering is the best way to start the day.
Union Fest
Yeah!
Oh yeah, that reminds me.
At yesterday's meeting,
you know how the Biscottians were there, too?
Yup.
Don't you think Ecle-chan
was acting a little strange?
Hi, Ecle!
Huh?
She seemed to keep her
distance from Sink.
Sink looked surprised.
I wonder if something happened.
Do you think they had
a fight or something?
Sink looked like he
didn't have any idea what was wrong.
This is quite interesting.
Yeah, Ecle's been quite distant.
Are you sure you didn't do something
to make her mad again?
Well, Eclair is leaving
her childhood behind,
so she's got her moods.
I'm sure you'll make up in no time.
I hope so.
I'm sorry, Princess.
It looks like Cou-sama is
totally enamored with Sink.
No need to apologize.
Isn't it kind of heartwarming?
Oh, Cou-sama, how are you on time?
Oh, yeah.
I guess I should get going.
Hero Sink, your lap was
excellent for resting on.
Thank you.
Bye, Millhi-nee, Sink.
Once the war starts, we'll be enemies.
Understood.
We won't hold back!
It'll be fair and square.
See you later.
Indeed!
It's finally the opening day.
It looks like today will
be full of excitement.
Yes. I'm sure it'll be a
lot of fun with everybody.
Biscotti Front Lines
Captain! Everybody under the command
of the Imperial Guard has been deployed!
Please get some rest
until the event begins.
If you'll excuse us...
We'll see you on the battlefield.
Looks like Emilio and Ange
are both quite excited.
Yeah.
Both of them are in line for
a promotion to captain soon,
so of course they are.
The Knights of Biscotti
are becoming stronger and stronger.
That's a good thing.
You're right, that is a good thing.
Still...
you seem like something
is really eating at you.
What are you talking about?
I've told you again and
again, it's about the Hero.
I've known you for a long time.
Even if you try to talk around
it, I can see through you.
Ecle, you love the Hero.
You love that he always has a
smile for you when he sees you.
That he can run into battle
at the same speed as you.
That he always expresses his trust,
courtesy, and gratitude in words.
But since you're so serious,
you're actually ashamed
that you're wondering
if you love him or not.
Not to mention, there are a whole lot
of wonderful girls around the Hero.
So you're like, "I'm just a knight,"
or "I'm the captain of the Imperial
Guard," and you keep worrying.
No, you're...
Getting angry won't work with me.
Truth be told, I am a little
angry today myself.
I'm sorry.
I do know that you love the Hero,
but I am really...
No, no. That's not true.
It is true that I really
like the Hero a lot,
but I do not hide that from anybody.
The reason I am angry is
that you still
haven't managed to become true to yourself
and you keep everything locked up inside.
I told you it's not that...
Anyway, it doesn't matter right now.
It's not a matter that should
be discussed here and now.
Now's the only time to discuss it!
Everybody is worried about you.
Just leave me alone.
You don't have to worry,
I'll do my part in the war.
See! That's the sort of
deflection I detest!
So now you're ignoring me?
You're not being cool right now...
I'm fine with being uncool.
I don't have courage and
I'm not being honest.
If you want to think that's
pathetic, go ahead.
That's not what I meant at all!
I just...
I don't give a damn!
I told you to leave me alone.
There's an important war today!
Let me concentrate.
I felt the need to talk about this,
especially because
it's an important war.
Because today's a very special event
that'll stay in our hearts.
Ecle you... Ecle...
I hate you!
I'm so sorry.
It's the Queen of Inventions.
What's the matter?
Rico, are you all right?
Leon-sama, Noir...
I see, so a trivial argument
escalated into a fight.
It happens all the time.
Once we've cooled our heads,
we usually both apologize and make up.
Well, the cause of the
fight must be Sink, right?
Because you're still not
being honest about him,
you're making everybody worry.
Well, love and affection are not
things where thinking helps, I hear.
Even so, having someone you love,
then that's a fun and happy thing.
I'm sure that's the sort of message
Rico was trying share with you, too.
You should try to not think too hard
and be more honest to yours-
You disappoint me,
Captain of the Imperial Guard.
I heard your story.
Eclaire, with that kind
of weak attitude,
you won't stand a chance in this war!
However, as I too am a
knight, I have to say
that I understand why you're so awkward.
How about a little bet
between us to make sure you
don't have time to worry
about trivial matters?
A bet?
Fight me one-on-one in today's battle.
Obviously, the victor wins the bet.
Naturally, I'll give you an edge.
All you'll have to do is destroy
my weapon or my armor.
It goes without saying that
I won't use Grand Vert.
What do you say?
These conditions are
quite extraordinary.
That's certainly true, but...
What are we betting on?
If I win, you'll be
Galette's Captain of the
Special Commando Troop for the day.
Then you'll be able to fight against
your rivals in love, Millihi
and Rebecca, all you want!
Hold on Leon-sama,
I think you got the wrong idea...
Not to mention, I don't have
the authority to decide
something that big by myself.
What?
You're that afraid of losing,
even with this handicap?
Have you really become this pathetic?
And if I...
...win?
I'll listen to any wish you might have.
Not that you could defeat
me in your current state.
Fine, I'll show you.
Eep, this got out of hand quickly...
Don't worry, Leon-sama
will handle this.
Okay, it's almost time!
Are you all ready?!
This war will be carved into
the history of the continent.
Naturally, she will be
giving the start signal:
Princess Millihiore!
Hello!
The joint event of the three
countries, Union Fest...
is finally beginning!
Leon-sama, Cou-sama,
are you ready?
Yes, any time.
Of course!
The let's all call it together.
Three...
Two...
One...
Fight!
It looks like battles
have already begun in several places.
What is this?
Galette's general, Lady Leon,
has broken rank and is charging ahead!
Oh! Could her aim be
Biscotti's second squad?
Captain!
Captain, your orders?
Yeah...
Meanwhile, the princess has returned
to Biscotti's main camp, after
signaling the start of the event.
She will now take command.
Right. Let's begin
our advance, as well.
Okay!
Couverte-sama and Hero Rebecca
are moving in on Biscotti's main camp!
Eclaire and Lady Leon are moving
towards Prizet bridge!
Now the captain of
Biscotti's Imperial Guard
and the Ruler of the
Lion Army are about to...
Bright Ice Blade!
CLASH!
Your gear sure is
flashy, but it's weak.
Just like your friends worried:
if you have doubts in your heart,
your sword will waver
and your Bright Power
will become unstable.
Right now, you're totally useless!
Put your spirit into it and come at me!
I do have spirit.
This crazy one-on-one fight...
If I lose...
I can't return to my country.
If you lose, you won't
be obligated to return.
Isn't that fitting?
Lady Leon's seal cannon!
But Knight Eclair is displaying
amazing spirit here!
Blast Wave!
Falling Doom!
A devastating blow!
Is Captain Eclaire in danger?
Ecle...
I guess it wasn't a full hit.
Ugh, I want to go cheer her on.
We have to stand our ground, Hero!
Lady Leon is approaching
Captain Eclaire.
Is this one-on-one coming to an end?!
My body...
won't move.
I ended up just like Rico and Yukikaze
were worried I would.
In this important war...
in this one-on-one
I can't afford to lose...
I went into all this with so
many doubts in my heart.
Now choose.
Do you want me to finish you off,
or do you want to surrender?
If I'm like this,
Rico and the Hero might
even turn away from me.
Knight Eclaire is in big trouble!
Will Biscotti lose their Captain
of the Imperial Guard?!
Ecle, don't lose...
I want you to fight.
I'm really sorry that I
bugged you right before
this important war and
got in a fight with you.
I was conceited and couldn't
actually tell you what I wanted.
All I wanted to do was to cheer you on
because you're too serious.
When I said that I hate
you, I was lying.
In reality, I love you!
No matter what!
Forever and ever!
The fault...
lies with me...
You didn't do anything wrong.
And I...
love you, too.
Just like the princess and
everybody in the Knight Corps...
The country Biscotti...
and our Hero...
Everybody that I met is important to me
I hold them dear and I
don't want to betray them!
That's why I won't lose.
Big words, but what do you plan to do?
I am going to win.
I am going to defeat you
and advance with our Hero.
Then we'll bring victory to Biscotti!
You eyes finally look
like a knight's eyes.
Fine. Bring it!
Captain Eclaire has recovered!
But what will she...
Here I go...
Bright Power release!
Bright Ice Blade! Dual wield!
What?!
Air Splitting
Bright
Cross Slash!
This is actually quite...
I win.
Damn.
Looks like you're right.
Fair and square.
Captain Eclaire has won!
Her Bright Power move has cleanly
destroyed Lady Leon's sword and armor!
My my, I let my guard down.
My lady, thank you.
How was it?
Putting your feelings into words?
Did it help you a bit?
Quite a bit.
I am going to stop mulling
over things by myself.
Should you have any
problems regarding love,
come talk to me.
Castle Vannette is all women,
so I understand the female heart.
Then I will take that
right as my reward.
Very well, it's a promise then.
The war's just begun.
Let us return to our places.
Yes.
With that, the one-on-one
on the Prizet Bridge goes to Biscotti!
It's a retreat rather than a defeat,
but it still gives a huge
boost to Biscotti's score.
Ecle!
I apologize. I worried you.
Not at all.
Now let's go.
Let us advance together,
just as we planned!
Okay!
What's happening at
Biscotti's main camp
after the victory of their captain?
I see the princess's
favorite Blanchir, Harlan, out...
Could this mean...
Eclaire was so cool.
I hope you'll pet her a lot later.
Of course!
It looks like the princess and the chief
will go up into the skies together.
It's finally time.
Yes!
Here we go, Princess.
Right!
I am going to fight Rebecca-san
without holding back, too.
Even if we didn't get
much screen time...
We still are...
Genoise!
One-On-One In The Skies and On Land!
Don't forget it!
Owww!
Hero!
I'm going to shine next time!