Closed today for my daughter's culture fair -Kokageya
It's raining.
Radio forecast says it'll let up by afternoon.
Are you going to a wedding?!
Your mother always told me to
dress appropriately for concerts.
That's over the top.
Oh, since today's Sunday,
the dining hall's closed, right?
I made a lunch for you.
Thank you.
Good luck, Wakana
Of course...
Mom, I'm off!
Hamada Tetsu
The artwork's done!!
It's a true masterpiece!!
Gonna crash in the art room, so
wake me up when you get to school!
Tai-kun? It starts at one, right?
You don't have to come.
Mom wants me to take pictures
and send them to her.
This waterproof case was a smart idea.
This is a little embarrassing.
Don't be so spoiled. You don't
know if anybody else will show.
Yeah. Well, I guess
Konatsu might like it.
Sis?
What?
You're going to—
Ugh! You've gotta stop that.
Take it off?
You're doing the White Festival
even if you're all alone, right?
Of course.
Even if it keeps raining?
You bet. We'll be in the gym.
You coming?
No, someone from the newspaper
club wanted to go.
I have other plans with my friends.
I see. Then ask him to
put us on the front page.
Front page? It's the school paper.
You're useless.
Whatever.
Well, do your best.
I will, thank you.
Entry to school grounds
prohibited due to construction
Shirohamazaka High School Board
Final Episode
Sunny Days and Crying and Sometimes Singing
I didn't expect them to go that far.
Bad news. It's the same at
the bike lot entrance.
And they have security guards
at the parking lot...
This would be easy to climb over.
But the people coming to see
us won't be able to get in.
Oh, yeah.
Should we sing here, then?
I have a raincoat, so I'm fine, but...
I guess I was a bit naive...
Hello? Yeah. You woke up?
Why don't we at least go in?
There's not much time.
Shall we cut the chain?
What? All of them?!
Okay, got it.
Hamada said the doors
to the gym are locked.
Shall we be on our way?
Those pests.
Be careful, Taichi.
Yeah.
Ta-da!
Think you can climb over it?
That won't work.
What are you doing here?
It's Sunday.
We forgot some things
in our class room.
My gym clothes.
My recorder.
Exactly. Right?
Yes.
You're here for that unauthorized
culture fair.
You're the choir club, correct?
And sometimes badminton club.
May we ask who you are?
I'm the chairman of the school board.
You know you're not
allowed here on Sundays.
Please give us permission,
just for today!
We all prepared for this!
You should have gotten my permission
before you started preparing.
Would you have given
it to us if we'd asked?
I would have considered it.
We'll do it even if
you won't accept it.
If you do something silly
merely to sing,
and are penalized for it,
won't that affect your futures?
That's unfair!
Is that a threat?
It's education.
You need to learn how immature
and powerless you youngsters are.
Hold your culture fair.
I will allow it.
Principal Ikezaki?
I am the principal of this school.
The permission of the chairman is
not needed for a culture fair.
Also, the chairman does not have
the authority to directly
penalize students,
though he does have
the authority to fire me.
I am sorry.
Please forgive me for never helping you,
despite being your advisor.
What are you talking about?
This situation arose because
your education is subpar!
You dare speak of education?
You know nothing about the
weaknesses that people have,
nor the wonderful songs that soothe them.
This place might only
be an asset to you,
but it means so much more to them!
Why can't you just let
them gather and sing?!
We're human beings!
In times of turmoil, we have to sing!
Enough!
I'm dismissing you.
Don't bother coming in tomorrow.
They're broken...
Have people stand at the
bottom of the hill to
advise that it's cancelled.
Yes, sir.
Hang o—
You caused all this extra work
because of stuff like this!
Madam Vice Principal!
By the time the dismissal
procedure is over,
the culture fair will be long finished.
The vocal club and the wind
instrument club will be
your main pillars of support
from the music school.
This is the sheet music for the
chorus and the accompaniment.
The vocal club and the
wind instrument club have
been practicing it recently.
Is it all right to use this?
Yes!
Miyamoto-san.
Would you let me conduct
this stage you've set up?
Of course! We'd love that!
I said enough!
I have no intention of unlocking
the school gate or the gym.
I sent the security guards
at the parking lot away.
We will guide the guests
inside from there.
What about the stage?
The rain has stopped.
This is so stupid.
It's not like anyone will come.
Oh, looks like I'm early.
This is the place, right?
For the White Festival?
Watermelon, watermelon!
Yeah!
We're not the first ones here.
It doesn't matter.
You better sing well.
He's like a mini Konatsu!
Pardon me?
You're way too early!
Ridiculous. We're leaving.
Hurry along, the other students
are setting up inside.
Okay!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Ueno-san!
I knew you'd come!
Hirohata-san asked the vice principal.
Hey, don't make up weird stuff!
Hirohata-san, thank you.
Well, the vocal club needed
a goal to work toward.
General Building | Music Building
I guess this is stage left.
Then the piano would be here.
And the orchestra pit is there?
Yup.
The quality is amazing.
That's nice. Could you help?
We can rehearse once at most, if that.
Just do it like you practiced,
and we'll adjust on our side.
Impressive!
White Festival
Please enter here for
the White Festival!
The White Festival is this way.
Thank goodness it stopped raining.
Yeah.
No weird improv during
the real performance!
Don't worry.
I put a lot of thought into it
so it won't ruin the script.
That's what I'm worried about!
This is the Country of
Sound, Shirohama Saga.
Our tale begins as Konacchine
sets out on her journey.
Here goes!
I cannot remain in this country!
Wait!
Where will you go now?
To the faraway land of Amano Iward.
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit!
I'm the frog, Taiichi.
And I'm the prince of frogs, Wienaria!
Prince?
Damn him.
We overcame many difficulties.
But now we're finally here.
Though we lost much along the way.
Family and friends.
Dreams and pride.
Even our beloved homeland.
Now, we're alone in a world
shrouded in darkness,
on a path that can't be seen.
Fear not.
The sound of singing will show us the way.
Then let us sing.
So that we may be
each other's humble guides.
Even if it won't bring about a miracle,
for that single moment of rest...
We'll pour our feelings
into this song...
And start walking again!
Under the blue sky
we spread our arms wide.
Doubt and pain are
proof that we had hope.
We'll go at our own pace.
We'll always have faith.
A passing shower will
eventually come to an end.
Even filled with tears,
our hearts can be free.
Because, look, someone will be
there to pat our backs.
This melody will bring out the light
and reflect tomorrow in
these sparkling eyes.
Filled with dreams,
our hearts will always be free.
Because, look, someone will be
there to laugh with us.
This melody beckons the light.
Even if the path is a winding one,
everything will be all right.
We can set out with
smiles on our faces.
Jan!
Look at him, with his happy grin.
Fall, fall, fall, fall.
He can't help it.
He was accepted based
on his recommendation.
What are you going to do?
After graduation.
Abroad?
Yes.
There are equestrian
schools abroad.
If I go, there's a chance
I could still be a jockey.
Seriously?!
Yes.
It will be really difficult,
but if I come back from there,
I might be able to be a
jockey here in Japan, too.
That's amazing!
How's your dad?
Against it.
That school will have exams, right?
That's why I want to go over
there as soon as possible,
and start learning the language first.
When's that?
Next month.
But what about school?
I considered dropping out,
but when I talked to our teachers,
they said they'd
still let me graduate.
Maybe they don't want to lose
graduates because of what's happening.
So it's a done deal?
Yeah.
Wow, that's fast.
For how long?
Until I'm satisfied.
Do your best!
Don't come back crying!
Of course!
Are you taking Sabure?
I can't.
A fresh wind races through the grass and leaves.
Make sure you spend time with her now and then.
Where abroad? Mongolia?
The view is clear, as far as the eye can see.
And now, a graceful light is flooding,
softly illuminating everything.
Even if you can't see the stars
because of the rain,
the future you're dreaming of
is still right there.
Let's sing every day
with all our hearts,
our song echoing to the skies,
and beyond.
And if it should ever
reach you again somewhere,
I want you to remember
the days we spent with sparkling eyes.
Sakai-san...
Melody of the Heart
This is your sheet music, right?
That's right.
The days we spent with beaming smiles.
After the competition we signed
each other's music and exchanged it.
Whenever I was with Mahiru,
I felt like I had talent as well.
But I wasn't able to walk the same
musical path that she walked.
I was jealous and ashamed,
but I still couldn't throw it away.
I think my mother would tell you not to.
I found this when I was sorting
through her belongings.
Melody of the Heart
Takakura Naoko
My mother always seemed to
have fun singing this song.
Mahiru was always having fun.
There were times when that
made me jealous and angry, too.
I think I understand.
That feeling that things
come to her so naturally.
I want to dedicate myself
to studying music.
I might not be able
to make it this year,
but I want to go to that
kind of university.
Could I talk with you about those
kinds of topics
even after I graduate?
I am a music teacher.
I want to hear the voice
of the white beach,
so let's climb that winding slope.
2nd Shirohamazaka High School
Graduation Ceremony
The friendships we forge during
these brilliant days and moments,
create a harmony that stretches across eternity.
Allegro.
Vivace.
Hurry up!
Wait a sec.
Okay.
All right, I'm taking it.
One plus one is?
Two!
Huh? What's this two business?
Tell me these things ahead of time!
Please take another one.
Don't worry, it's a great shot.
Tanaka, don't you have
anything special to say?
Shut up, shrimp!
Aw, he's embarrassed.
Sawa, I'll come visit you sometime!
Oh, me, too!
Now, the Shirohamazaka
High School's Choir
and Sometimes Badminton Club
will sing one last song!
One, two, three.
A new wind blows,
laughing, crying, and trying to sing.
Open your closed heart.
Hum the harmony of the sea breeze.
Jan!
Matsuhiro!
Miyamoto-san, have you
picked a club yet?
Huh? No, not yet.
How about this? Join us!
August will see quite a
few nice summer days,
ushering in the summer holiday
atmosphere to the whole country.
And now, the forecast
for the Kanto region.
I'm home.