DASH
You dropped this!
S-Sorry.
I'm Gouda Takeo,
Thank you.
a first-year in high school.
I spooked her.
You have a heavy tread.
I see.
If that happens again,
I'll approach without making a sound.
That'd be scary in its own way.
You're like the bear in that song.
I love her!
Oh, the one where the bear finds a lost
earring and chases after the owner.
The first time I heard that song,
I wondered what the bear really wanted to do.
That's deep...
What is?
After all, who wouldn't run if
a bear came after them?
But wouldn't bears run after someone
if they'd found something of theirs?
Still, the girl did realize that the
bear was a good person, right?
You mean a good bear, not a good person.
And I'm sure they became good friends.
Oh, maybe.
Hmm?
Sorry!
I may have said that in a bad way!
Huh?
Um...
Even if another girl you save falls in
love with you, I won't lose to her!
I've been thinking this for a while,
but Yamato has a huge misunderstanding.
Yamato, I'm not that popular with girls.
Huh?
No way!
It's true.
Suna's the one who's popular.
There is a girl who fell
for you, though...
Right, Sunakawa-kun's a good person.
I know that, but...
Okay.
I can't believe it!
Then you aren't popular with girls.
You and Suna are the only
ones who think I'm cool.
Oh!
The girl in the song danced with the bear,
I understand.
That's a relief...
but that was all.
She never fell in love with the bear...
Sports Festival Event Assignments
Swedish Relay: Takeo
Okay, Takeo!
You're down for the Swedish relay
and the softball throw!
Right.
Huh?
Takeo should be on the tug of war!
Why can each person only
compete in two events?
Isn't that because Takeo's too strong?
Either way, the coed Swedish relay is
the sports festival's star attraction,
and it counts for a lot of points!
If we win this, we can win the entire competition!
We're counting on you!
Yeah!
Let's win this!
1st Runner
2nd Runner                                           1st Runner
2nd Runner            3rd Runner            1st Runner
Anchor                                      2nd Runner            3rd Runner            1st Runner
My Girlfriend
A sports festival?
But the one before...
That was the soccer tournament.
Oh, okay.
What's a Swedish relay?
Four people run the relay.
Swedish Relay
The first runner runs 100 meters,
the next, 200, then 300 and 400 meters,
for a total of 1,000 meters.
It's called the "Swedish relay"
because it originated in Sweden.
Relays are all about when
you pass the baton, right?
Yeah.
When I pass or receive it,
I always get super nervous.
You can practice all you want,
but you might still drop it.
Since elementary school, you've always run relays.
Really? Wow!
That's so cool.
I'm a slowpoke, so I admire
people who can run fast.
I see.
So Yamato's slow.
Everyone called you cool, right?
No, I think everyone laughed
their heads off when I ran.
That or didn't say a word.
Huh?
I wonder why.
It's probably a human response to seeing
something outside of comprehension.
I see.
I'm fast, but I'm not popular.
Huh?
Sorry, that's just how my mind works.
So embarrassed...
You're the coolest person I know, Takeo-kun!
Cute!
C
She's so cute.
The cream puffs
I made today
puffed up
pretty well
You're the cutest person I know, Yamato.
You're...
C
I can't tell her!
Here.
Okay!
Have one, too, Sunakawa-kun.
Thanks.
I'm too embarrassed to tell
her what I'm thinking.
Even though if I told her I think she's cute,
I'm sure I'd make her happy...
I can't say it because I'm too embarrassed to,
chomp chomp
but you're really cute!
You can sure eat a lot
I swear!
Okay!
Well?
The baton pass should lower
our time by 0.3 seconds.
Yeah!
Okay, let's give it another try!
Man, Gouda's so fast
Infirmary
It's a sprained ankle.
I'm afraid you can't run in
the relay with this leg.
I'm so sorry.
Guess we'll just have to choose someone who
hasn't been assigned to two events yet.
Swedish Relay Women's 300m
Rock-Paper-Scissors Qualifier
I lost
Huh? Me?
Sorry! It's all my fault!
Come on, Rei.
I mean, Mariya isn't that strong a runner.
Just hand the baton to Takeo!
Having her run 300 meters?
Huh? Okay...
Trot Trot
She's slow.
All the fast ones were already
signed up for two events.
Sorry, it's all because I got injured.
Well, we still have Takeo.
Yeah, we should scrape through.
Loom
Is he mad?
Cringe!!
Is she that slow?
I've never really paid attention
to how fast people can run,
but I guess Yamato isn't a fast runner, either.
Takeo-kun, are you free today?
I know we didn't have anything planned,
but I'm wondering if we can meet.
I'd like us to.
I have relay practice after school,
but that's over at four.
Then let's get together for a little bit.
I'll come over to your school.
I love her!
Class 1-6
Huh?
You have a stomachache, Mariya?
Sorry...
Huh?
Why are you alone?
Practice was canceled because one of
the members got a stomachache.
Oh...
Are you slow at running?
Even if you move your legs super fast?
I move them super fast, with everything I have.
But no matter how hard I try, I get left behind.
Do you swing your arms fast, too?
Arms?
I've never thought of that.
Want to try running?
Sure!
I have a feeling I'll be fast this time!
Trot Trot
Even though she moves her limbs fast enough,
Trot
she isn't really moving forward.
I think I'm running a little faster than before...
At least for me.
I see, that's good.
But I'm much slower than you, Takeo-kun.
I guess so.
I'm jealous that you're so fast.
I wish I could've won first place, too.
Yamato's cute.
She may be slow, but I love her anyway.
Choke
cough cough
Hey, is your stomachache better?
Huh? Stomach?
Um...
Er, well...
You were faking it?
No!
I-It wasn't fake.
It really did hurt up till a while ago...
I see.
You wouldn't understand, Gouda!
I don't understand
Understand what?
He's mad!
Sorry!
Huh?
Gouda...
Hey, wait...
Huff, puff...
Don't run...
I was walking.
You walk fast, too.
I was hungry, so I may have been walking fast.
Sorry.
No, uh, well...
About what?
Well, for being slow.
You aren't that slow.
Huh?
I thought you were average.
I'm not!
I'm slow!
Well, why are you sorry?
Because I'm a burden to everyone
else on the relay team.
A burden?
I've never thought of you that way.
It's normal to be fast or slow.
Huh?
See, you don't get it because you're fast!
I wish I could've won first place, too.
Do you want to win first place?
Huh?
Well, sure...
If you want to practice, I'll practice with you.
Huh?
Okay, let's start now.
Do you prefer
tough or easy
practices?
Huh? But I don't have my track suit!
Tough, please...
Then we'll start tomorrow morning!
Seriously?
Swing your arms!
Faster!
Like this!
En Route to School
What are you
doing so early
in the morning?
Brooding
Is there a good way to help
someone run faster?
He's mad.
Saijou!
Why is she running away?
I'm sorry!
I'll try harder!
You dropped something.
Oh, sorry.
Just now, you ran fast.
I'll run after you,
so try running before me.
Okay.
Don't Run in the Hall!
Noooo!
Wow!
Her time's gone down!
I'll have him chase me later, too.
Good!
Eh?
Relays are coed?
Yeah.
I'm not popular, though.
That isn't it!
I was just surprised it was coed, that's all.
I see.
What's your role, Takeo-kun?
I'm the anchor.
Wow!
That's so cool.
Cute!
C
I'll be off, then.                              Later, Takeo-kun.
Yamato, you're cute!
Hey...
I don't think you're as unpopular
as you think with girls.
No, I am.
You should know better than anyone.
Well... Never mind.
Goodnight.
Night.
Takeo-kun, good luck tomorrow.
I'll be cheering you on, too.
Don't worry, Yamato.
I'm not popular with girls!
Shuuei High School Sports Festival
Go!
Sunakawa-kun!
Listen, if we win this relay,
we'll get a comeback win!
Yeah!
We're counting on you, Mariya!
For me, too
O-Okay...
O-Okay.
We're gonna win!
We're gonna win!!
Crap...
They all look super fast...
Now my stomach really hurts.
Saijou!
Huh?
Run as fast as you can,
and pass me the baton.
Leave the rest to me!
It'll be fine!
Remember your training!
Thumbs Up!
Nod
Ready... Set...
Go!
Go, Murata!
Go, class 6!
Saijou!
Class 6 Victory
Crap!
Saijou, it'll be okay!
There he goes!
Go!
Wow Wow Wow
ha ha ha ha
Class 1-6 wins by a landslide!
Roar
An amazing comeback, after falling in last place!
Wow!
Super awesome!
Amazing!
Thumbs up!!
Before, I felt I'd totally go to
the ring for Takeo-kun
if anyone else developed feelings for him,
That might take a while
but how do you think I should fight for him?
Do you even need to?
But...
What if the girl who danced with
the bear had so much fun,
she wanted to see him again?
Gouda...
Hey... You fell. Are you okay?
Oh, yeah.
Um, sorry.
And thanks.
Sure.
Bear
Hunter
How to fight, huh?
Maybe work on your looks first?
A self-improvement thing?
You aren't in his school,
so you should definitely show
that he has a girlfriend.
Make him use the same phone
strap, to show your closeness.
I can do that right now!
Great idea!
How about this?
You can't even put it
in your pocket
No, if you put that on, your cell
won't fit in your bag anymore.
Oh, it's a pouch      You can't even put it
in your pocket
It's pretty handy                Oh, it's a pouch      You can't even put it
It gets kind of clunky.
R-Right.
We knew, but...                                    Stare
She really loves him, huh?
Takeo-kun, I want to give you something.
Can we meet in the park later?
Hmm?
Guess she's going to give me something.
Huh...
Since she's bothering to text you,
I guess it isn't sweets.
Maybe a rabbit?
Takeo-kun!
Gouda!
Oh, Yamato, this is my classmate, Saijou.
Hello.
Saijou, this is Yamato.
She's my girlfriend!
"My girlfriend," huh?
Oh, um, Saijou-san...
You wanted to talk to Takeo-kun
about something?
Oh, I wanted to give Gouda something.
For me?
Oh, because you helped me
out so much with the relay.
Can I open it?
It's a towel.
Yeah, it's a thank-you gift.
Takeo, you always use a washcloth, right?
Oh, you don't use towels?
Well, that's just what my mom likes.
I don't care either way.
My first towel
I guess I'll finally have a towel.
No way!
Towels are fluffy, huh?
Of course!
I'll get going, then.
Sorry, it isn't like I did anything.
It's okay.
I just wanted to thank you.
Later.
Um, Saijou-san was with you on the relay?
Yeah.
What did you want to give me, Yamato?
Oh.
I can't believe this is my cell phone.
And all it took was one little strap!
W-We'll have the same one.
The same one, huh?
Thank you!
Gouda Takeo got a towel from a girl?!
But it was a thank-you gift, right?
If that's what she said, that's what it was.
A towel...
I wonder...
But your boyfriend can run really fast.
She could've fallen for that, I guess.
Was she cute?
Huh? Yeah.
She was cute and seemed nice.
And she had a nice chest and everything.
A chest!
That's what caught your eye, Rinko?
But Takeo-kun introduced me
as his girlfriend, so...
You're so naïve, Rinko.
Some girls find guys more attractive
when they're already taken.
Well, but I'll fight.
I won't lose.
That's right! Tell it to her, Rinko!
Yeah, don't let her underestimate you
because you go to an all-girls school!
I'm shocked. That's how they felt?
I bet they think same-sex school students
should date others like them.
If she really likes Takeo-kun,
I guess we're on the same wavelength.
Huh?
We might have become really good friends.
But it won't happen.
If you like the same guy,
you can't be friends.
Rinko!
Go wait for him at their school gate!
Show her you're his girlfriend!
O-Okay.
Shuuei High School
I guess love really is war.
That cell phone strap...
Yeah, Yamato gave it to me yesterday.
It matches hers.
Wow!
Matching straps and a couples shot
as your wallpaper? So overkill.
What, why? It isn't!
Oh...
Gouda... Wait!
Sorry, wai—
You all right?
I said you walk fast!
Sorry...
Ow.
What's wrong?
Did you twist your ankle?
Lean on my shoulder.
Drape
What about my shoulder?
Guess I'm too tall, too.
Maybe I'll walk you home.
Huh?
If you don't mind a piggyback ride, I'll carry you.
It's fine with me.
No, let me.
This is unusual for you, Suna.
Do you like her?
I want...
I want a piggyback ride on Gouda!
Okay!
Takeo—
Yamato?
What's wrong?
Did you come here to see me?
Yeah.
Oh, sorry...
Saijou twisted her ankle.
I'm going to take her home.
Can you wait here with Suna?
Eh?
Is she okay?
I'll be right back!
Your girlfriend's a nice person.
Yep!
Sunakawa-kun, do you think
Saijou-san likes Takeo-kun?
Maybe.
But she can't do anything
about Takeo's feelings.
Right.
Yamato!
Gouda?
Hey, is your leg better?
Yeah.
Um...
I need to talk to you.
After school, could you meet
at the chicken coop?
Sure.
Oh, where's Takeo-kun?
What's wrong?
Do you have a stomachache?
No!
I mean, so...
I like you, Gouda!
A-As a person!
So can I call you "master"?
As a person?
I don't deserve to be called a
master by any means,
but since she's being sincere,
I can't turn her down...
Okay!
Oh...
So, that's it.
I look forward to learning from you.
Okay!
Likes him as a person...
Oh, Yamato?
You came again?
I'm relieved!
I was anxious because I thought
she had feelings for you.
I made her worry.
My bad...
I said I'm not popular.
Yeah, it's better that way.
Er, I mean, you might prefer it the other way...
What are you saying?
I don't need to be popular with girls.
As long as I'm popular with Yamato, I'm fine.
My Disciple
Next time: My Disciple.