"Battle of Ceres"
Initiate the tactical
heavy laser system!
Fire!
But it hasn't fully charged yet!
I don't care! Fire!
And here I was gonna show off!
Why were we put on reserve?
I've got the usual,
plus two massive anti-ship
guided missiles,
four racks of high-mobility
four mobile mines
and two midrange impact cannons.
Just what are the Wulga anyway?
You mean "Wulgaru," not "Wulga".
Aren't they mysterious extraterrestrials
that came to invade Earth?
But what do they look like?
Do you think they're all slimy
and have wobbly antennae?
If they're from space,
they've gotta be monsters!
That's every man's dream.
They could be silicon-based entities.
Maybe the ships we're fighting
are their true form.
This was left blank in
our files on them...
You actually read those?
You're so mean!
Izuru, shut up!
Huh? He's angry at me?
The operation isn't
supposed to start yet!
Fire!
Well? Did we get them?
It hit our target. Currently
determining its effect.
Change in mass: 0.04.
Change in orbit: 0.
That's absurd!
Check those results!
I've confirmed an enormous change
in the mass around the target!
See? I told you!
The mass is speeding toward
the first line of defense.
It's the enemy!
Incoming report from the
first line of defense!
Numerous enemy vessels
are headed toward them.
"We are currently under attack!"
What?! That can't be!
Recharge the laser! Be quick about it!
Begin bombarding the enemy!
Didn't we have 25 minutes
before Zero Hour?
We began preparing for
battle five minutes ago!
The enemy is right in front of you!
Just attack the monsters!
We have no other choice.
All vessels, begin the assault!
All vessels, begin firing at Target A.
Guided sublight speed missiles
will accelerate in ten seconds.
8...
7...
6...
5...
4...
All missiles have been destroyed!
What?!
Normal ammo has no effect!
What about the free electron cannons?
The alarm?
We're starting the operation?
But it's too soon!
Stupid! The enemy took us by surprise.
Orders to sortie?
Not yet.
We need to be ready to leave
as soon as they come in.
We're starting the operation early!
All units, prepare to blast off!
The situation doesn't look good.
The enemy has broken past
the first line of defense
and is currently headed
straight for our second line.
The free electron cannons are worthless!
What's that mean?
The free electron beams are curving
around the enemies' magnetic fields.
The enemy carriers are equipped
with defensive magnetic fields.
That should make them easy to track.
The Wulgaru probably don't care
if we know where they are.
Aren't they bursting with confidence?
And here we vastly outnumber them.
Considering the situation,
numbers don't matter...
What situation?
How is it going?!
Not good!
The second line of defense's
attacks have no effect!
We have lost over 40% of
the first line of defense!
Send out anyone you can!
Oh, yeah! Don't we have some reserves?
So it's finally our turn, huh?
I was getting tired of
holding your reins back.
No one asked ya to!
Now then, everyone, let's head out.
Team Doberman is taking off!
I was gonna say that!
All units, take off!
Don't let the enemy near Ceres
until the laser has finished recharging.
Roger!
Let's go!
Asagi, slow down!
Stay in formation.
What's wrong with you?
Wait! Wait up!
I'm counting on you.
<All vessels, take the
Shahaa Formation.>
<Lay them to waste!>
The 1st and 3rd Mobile Strike Forces
are down by 45%.
The 27th and 102nd FA Squadrons
have been obliterated!
The 28th and 43rd FA Squadrons
are no longer fit to fight.
The enemy has broken through
the first line of defense!
The enemy will reach us in-
Where'd they come from?!
They've destroyed the Wilber and Lassen!
Anzio has been hit!
We're no longer receiving
its distress signal!
Hurry and attack the enemy!
Roger! Relay to all vessels:
When engaging the enemy, set your guns
on full auto and attack anything!
I repeat: Set your guns to full auto
and attack anything!
Annihilate all of our foes!
Damn it!
What in the-?!
Tally ho!
The cavalry has arrived!
If it weren't for you, we would
have gotten here quicker!
You're blaming me?!
This is Team Doberman.
We are here to offer our support.
Hey, Patrick! Don't steal the best
line right from under me!
I'm sorry, Sir.
It's the Comedic Three...
All vessels, retreat to Point Mike!
Now is our chance to regroup!
Roger!
The enemy is retreating.
Amazing!
I can't believe Team Doberman
was capable of all that!
Crap! A carrier's coming!
The magnetic field-!
It...!
The beams curved?!
Wow! They hit the enemy ships
that were hiding behind it!
They're using the magnetic field
to bend the particle beams
to hit other enemy ships!
These guys are nuts!
Is it all that impressive?
They can't be human!
We should give our allies a hand
while they regroup.
What's the plan?
Kei, do your thing!
Roger!
I've finished analyzing the situation.
I'm sending the data now.
Thanks.
Uh... Gold 4, hook up with the fleet and
lay down suppressive fire to cover their retreat.
Blue 1 and Purple 2, offer him support.
Uh, Rose 3, well...
umm... You can... Uh...
Kaboom!
Asagi and I will fight
in the frontlines!
Kei, analyze the situation and
issue orders as you will!
Tamaki... is fine as she is.
Roger!
<That is...>
<It is time I set out!>
<The enemy has clearly
laid a trap before us!>
<A trap? Then I will tear through it.
Come or be left behind!>
High-speed objects are
approaching the minefield!
What?!
The high-speed objects are
approaching from dead space.
Red 5, please intercept them.
Huh? But...
That's an order from your commanding office!
Where's your response?!
Yes, Ma'am! Red 5 will intercept!
Asagi, you handle things here.
You can count on me!
Red 5 is proceeding to intercept
the high-speed objects.
He will reach them in 10 minutes!
Why'd it suddenly stop?
It's moving on its own!
It's that white fighter!
<I've found you, my prey!>
<You have improved!>
Does he have eyes in
the back of his head?
<Petty decoys will not work on me!>
How about this?!
<A waste of time!>
Over there!
That didn't even touch him?
Moron!
Stupid! Stupid! You're in my way!
It's big!
You twit! Stay outta my line of fire!
Don't detonate on impact!
Damn! Those are 2 hundred million each!
There are too many of them!
What happened to Izuru?!
He is currently fighting in dead space.
I know that!
Then don't ask!
<Out of my way!>
He killed his comrade?!
<You had best not divert
your attention!>
I have to do something!
Red 5 has commenced
battle in dead space.
Team Rabbits is also in the
midst of battle, but...
What's wrong?
Speak clearly when making your report.
Everyone is acting independently.
There isn't any semblance of teamwork.
Bluntly put, they suck.
So Izuru was doing a surprisingly
good job leading them, huh?
Guys, are you okay?
Izuru?! Of... of course we are!
After all, I'm giving the orders.
What a relief!
I've got my hands full
with some crazy strong bogie over here.
Asagi, you're the leader.
Look after everyone!
Leader...
That's right! I'm the leader!
What's this?
Is it from Kei?
That's it! Kei!
Summarize the situation for me! Please!
The enemy units are located...
If I mess this up,
Irina and the girls are going to
tease me again when I get back!
I've got to do my best!
Open all sensors to maximum reception.
I am displaying their
location on Secret Code F.
The enemy's main forces are moving
from 13CM to 13IC at a speed of 45.
The enemies from GK to BF are decoys.
Tamaki, move from FF
to EI at full speed.
Ten seconds thereafter,
launch all of your missiles
and swing over to EK.
Uh, I don't really get
it, but you've got it!
Suruga, defend our flagship while
driving the enemies into Point EH.
You can count on me!
Kei, set up a trap at EH minus Tango.
Roger!
Enemy units are approaching the
remaining ships in the frontline!
They have destroyed 24% of our convoy!
Over 400 new enemy units are appearing
from Point OM, Sector 3!
Wha-?!
Kaboooom!
Is anyone seriously
gonna come out this way?
Firing 90mm high-quality particle beams
at the target point!
Take all of my high-mobility guided
missiles while you're at it!
Sweet!
Asagi, go to your assigned position.
Roger!
Yikes! Move! Move!
Tamaki, fire all of your ammo!
You've got it!
I got them good!
We rock!
The enemy is sending reinforcements!
They'll have the upper hand
in a close-range battle.
All units, defend the flagship
as we slowly pull back!
Roger!
I've gotta lighten my load!
<Hmmm, what an intriguing idea.
That is what makes you my prey!>
Blue 1 has taken the lead
and stabilized the situation.
The fleet has begun to retreat.
Red 5 is stalling the
enemy in dead space.
I guess things are working out...
Gold 4 is almost completely
out of ammunition.
The other units are still able to fight.
I see. Have Gold 4 retreat and-
This is Gold 4.
We're switching to a
close-to-midrange battle.
I need a heavy laser for my main arm
and a close-range particle
diffusion cannon,
a MIRV launcher and a scatter impact
cannon for my sub weapons.
This is Mother Bird. You've got it.
Hurry on back.
It looks like they're
finally starting to get a
grasp on their units, huh?
Gold 4 has always been
a weapons encyclopedia.
Izuru, we're doing fine on our end.
We're retreating to the
third line of defense.
It's not easy being leader!
Then I can't afford to lose here!
I can see it!
<Excellent! Just what I would expect
from one that has managed to strike me!>
<Through hunting, the prey
and the hunter communicate!>
<We predict each other's
moves, constantly
reading one step beyond the next.>
<We fight desperately, trying
to outwit the other!>
<I'm enjoying you, infidel!>
Damn it! I'm still not fast enough.
Bingo!
We're ready to outfit
it just like you wanted!
It looks like you finally understand
the teachings of Muscle-dom!
With these muscles, swapping your
armament'll only take a second!
Man, could you quit
going on about muscles?
Moron! The world is made from
weapons and muscles!
Have some protein!
Seriously, gimme a break...
Finished swapping his armament!
Finished replenishing supplies!
He's all set!
Blast off!
Roger!
What is the situation?
Currently 76% of our remaining
forces are converging
around the third line of defense.
They are regrouping.
The Bela-Russian and
Great Chinese fleets
have broken from the battle.
Did they suffer heavy losses?
They weren't horrible.
I imagine they are reserving
their forces for future battles.
There... Zoom in on Red 5.
Roger!
What's he doing?
It looks like he's in quite the fight.
He's putting tremendous strain on Red 5.
Pull up all of the data on Red 5!
Roger! I'll put it on the main screen.
A duel? Why isn't he using his guns?
It looks like his opponent is too fast.
The JURIA-SYSTEM is already
working at full capacity.
Is his enemy that powerful?
Yes, he's a fearsome foe...
We'll need to figure out how to deal with him.
Tamaki, Kei, go replenish your supplies!
Roger!
But-!
Suruga and I can handle things here!
Be careful.
Tryin' to act all cool!
You bet! You've got my back.
Suruga, can you keep up with me?
Who do you think I am?
Great. Let's go!
Well?
Five minutes until it activates!
You can make it back
to the Pit, can't you?
Get going!
Who do you think you're ordering around?
He who has run out of
"Otto" and "Herman"
has no right to complain!
What the heck?
That's what the army
used to call fuel and
ammunition a long time ago!
Just say it like a normal person, idiot!
Screw that!
This is part of what makes my identity!
What're you doing?!
You scared me...
Hurry up!
I finished stocking up! Asagi, hurry up!
That won't be necessary.
We'll send the supplies to you instead.
Huh? Don't tell me you're going to...!
We're firing the supplies,
so catch them!
Wait a sec! I stink
at this merging stuff!
Here I go!
Regrouping: Complete.
All squadrons, gather around
the third line of defense!
Has it recharged yet?
Just finished.
I will begin the firing sequence.
Count down:
60...
59...
58...
9...
8...
7...
6...
5...
4...
3...
2...
1...
Fire!
Did we get them?!
What is it?!
There are enemy vessels
above the beam cannon!
What?!
They didn't appear on the radar earlier!
It's the enemy!
<Now!>
Crap! We're in a Catch-22!
I'll plot a navigation route!
Give me 10 seconds.
I'll have it in five.
What?
I'm sending you the data.
All right, men! Charge!
Amazing!
Most impressive, my dears.
Care to go on a date with me later?
Huh?
I'll have to pass.
Could you try to be serious
every now and then?
Um, is he always like this?
Of course not!
Yeah, he is.
Why you little...!
I'll whack you!
Hey!
Our tactical heavy laser
has been destroyed!
Incompetent fools!
You've made a mess of my perfect plan!
Arms and legs are supposed to do
as the head tells them!
<That's right. A hunt that
lacks dignity and respect
is merely a massacre.>
<It is without any sense of beauty!>
<En garde!>
<This duel was amusing.
Let us fight again, primitive creature!>
I'm sure he looked human...
And he could even talk!
I never expected our
enemy to be like this...
He resembled that girl.
"Disclosure"