The salinity in the Narunami area around
noon is expected to be 57 per mill.
Around 6PM, it will rise to 60 per mill.
Because of the saltflake snow,
the water temperature
is expected to drop,
and the temperature of Shioshishio
is expected to drop to 15 degrees.
Next is the weather on the surface.
It actually falls on the surface.
The Shioshishio Peninsula
will continue to be sunny.
The saltflake snow?
I wonder what that was...
It was different, even a bit creepy.
I wonder if everyone in Shishio
knows it fell on the surface.
As soon as they find out,
they'll say it's Ooshi's fault because
they refused to do the Ofunehiki
and the Sea God is meting
out divine punishment.
You think so?
Knowing how Dad and the
others are, I'm sure of it.
Dad...
I'm sure that Dad is worried about you.
That's not—
Hikari, I think you should
go home after all.
W-What are you talking about?!
Look!
I got a whole bunch
of snow and made this.
What is that?
A fish cake?
It's a snow sea slug!
Did you know what it was, Aka-chan?
Of course!
Here.
It's even better if you add these.
I wonder if it'll last till Daddy gets home.
It won't melt that fast.
Really? Thank goodness!
I wonder if Daddy will
know what it is...
Of course he will.
Look how cute it is.
I heard that saltflake snow
fell on the surface...
So it's going to keep getting
colder the way the prophecy said?
We haven't forgotten about the Sea God.
But haven't you noticed that the sacred
fire's going out faster lately?
Well...
Chief Priest!
Did you find out the reason?
What should we do?
Chief Priest!
You're so noisy.
U-Uroko-sama.
Come now. Hurry and take your seats.
Uroko-sama, if you would.
There is only one reason I have
asked you all to gather here today...
I would like to talk to you about
the calamity that approaches us.
Episode Nine:
Unknown Warmth
Looks like the snow
didn't fall for very long.
Yeah.
I wonder if the Sea God is mad...
Huh?
Hii-kun?
Dad better not be drinking a lot and
skipping meals just because I'm not there.
Actually, what's he doing about food?
Good morning, Hikari.
Hey.
Mornin'. Whatcha doin'?
I was trying to figure out where to fix it first.
What are you guys doing here so early?
Well, we were sort of thrown out.
We were told that adults had
an important meeting to go to,
so we should head to school early.
What's that all about?
I wonder if it has to do with the
saltflake snow falling on the surface.
Adults are always like that.
They think it's okay to keep
everything a secret from kids.
Ojoshi-sama's right here.
We'll be doing the Ofunehiki!
We really want to do this to the end.
Let's do the Ofunehiki
With just us.
Well, we might as well finish.
And we feel bad for Ojoshi-sama.
I'll ask my Gramps for a boat to use.
There you have it.
We can do this, right, Sensei?
You guys...
Yes, let's do it!
Let's all make sure it's
a success no matter what!
Once we're done, I'll definitely
treat you guys to ramen this time!
Gramps said we could use this.
Wow!
But it's smaller than I thought.
Let's repaint it.
We should probably reinforce it first.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
It's not a problem.
You're putting too much into it.
Huh?
Why?
You're gonna get hurt like that.
Hii-kun...
That's more like it.
I think we're all getting hungry.
Oh!
Then I'll go make us something!
I'll go get some things from Saya Mart!
You better not be doing this
just so you can have a snack.
That's not it!
I'm going to support her.
You're just gonna get fat!
Hikari's trying really hard...
Don't say that!
I'm just kidding.
It's heavy...
Oh, I'll help.
You're a lifesaver!
You guys came!
Yeah!
Well, then...
This is my awesome creation.
Don't drop it.
That's the hip microwave!
Leave it to us!
Why are there shumai?
I wonder what'd be good...
Oh, Manaka-chan?
Oh! Akari-san!
Something that'll keep you
warm is probably best.
This summer's a bit chilly.
Something warm and from the sea...
By the way, has Hikari said anything?
Huh?
Like about the sea or home.
I wonder if Hikari's
not worried about Dad.
That's not true!
Hii-kun really is worried...
Hii-kun's worried about your dad...
I see.
They both care about each other,
but this isn't going well...
Pardon the intrusion.
Oh, this is...
Oh, could I use your—
Always Smiling
Saya Mart
Um, this is, uh...
I-I'm sorry!
Tsumugu also did that quite a
bit when he first came here.
"When he first came here"?
Tsumugu-kun wasn't born in this house?
He came here on his
own when he was nine.
Huh?
Why did he come by himself?
His parents live in the city.
Tsumugu-kun came by himself...
So Tsumugu-kun has always been
Tsumugu-kun since he was little...
U-Um.
I've thought that
Tsumugu-kun is really good
at finding himself and
things that are around him.
I'm sure he found his love for
the sea when he was young, too.
I think that's why he
chose to come here.
His precious...
Because he knows what's precious to him.
Here.
Thank you very much!
Did you know? Apparently Café
Triangle is the place for meets.
Meats?
You mince meat there?
No!
It's a place where guys and girls
are friendly with each other!
Looks like your mouth's
working just fine,
but how about your hands?
Th-They're working!
All right. Good.
We'll do more and—
Kaname!
I'm gonna head back to
school and get some tools,
so could you see if there's
wood in the back for reinforcing?
Roger.
All right, I'm counting
on you little ladies.
Want me to help you paint?
Your Ena probably dried up.
Hey!
Look!
We painted it really nice! How's tha—
Where's Chisaki? Did she go somewhere?
I-I don't know.
I see.
Thanks for earlier.
I'm okay now, don't worry.
So you can head back.
Do you still need a sea slug?
No, I don't.
I don't need one anymore.
Does that mean you're
giving up on Hikari?
Why?
"Why?"
Because I have to change... so...
So that's what "change" means to you?
I mean, that's what it means
to become an adult, right?
You can't just keep thinking about yourself,
and you have to keep moving forward.
So that's why you're
neglecting your feelings.
What?
Because you can't forgive
how you are right now.
Tsumugu-kun, you don't...
You don't understand anything.
I don't dislike how you are right now.
Chisaki!
Chisaki! Did something happen?
I'm not feeling well, so I'm going home.
I'll go with you.
I really hate him!
So he makes you make
expressions like that.
Kaname?
The village...
is different from usual.
Mom?
Hey, do you need this anymore?
Oh, this?
Sorry! It took me a while.
Thanks for your hard work!
You're late!
We're already done for the day.
Huh? Where'd Chisaki and Kaname go?
They went home already.
I wonder if they had something to do.
Oh? Looks like the food's ready.
Oh! That's the shumai for
the inside of the microwave.
Oh, sorry.
Nice catch!
Hey! Be careful with my shumai!
Do you know how hard I
worked on that thing?
That smells good.
It's seafood and pork soup!
What?
Putting pork in seafood soup is wrong.
Yep!
Y-You think so?
I thought it'd be nice if things that were
raised in the sea and on the surface got along.
The sea and the surface...
The hell are you doing?!
That's for making my knees buckle.
That's totally different!
That's different for a lot of reasons...
Hii-kun, I...
I'm here right now because you
were there for me, Hii-kun.
Thank...
Thanks for everything.
What are you being all serious fo—
You feel reassured when
someone is with you.
You taught me lots.
Well, we're friends...
So... And so...
If it's hard for you to go
back home, I'll go with you.
Wh-What are you talking about?
It's not like I—
I feel reassured when you're next to me,
and I'm sure your dad feels the same.
And I know you do, too.
If you can tell each other you care
about each other, you'll become stronger!
You'll be happier!
Huh?
Ow!
Damn it, what the hell?
I said that I'd support her...
But I don't think I can control myself...
Food's ready!
We've been waiting!
Looks great!
I'm so hungry!
Mom? Dad?
Did something happen?
Come here.
What's wrong?
Manaka, you can't go
to the surface anymore.
What?
Sakishima
Manaka's your friend.
She's your friend, you.
All right!
Now if you'll open your
textbook to page 48—
I'm late!
I couldn't really sleep
well last night, and so...
I'm sorry!
So at least you showed up, Hikari.
Huh?
Well, all of the Shioshishio
kids didn't show up today.
I tried to contact them
but couldn't reach them.
Have you heard anything?
Those adults are trying to
stop the Ofunehiki again!
I'll go.
I'll go back to the village and
settle this once and for all!
Hey, Hikari!
I'm gonna tell them!
I'm gonna tell all the old guys
and Dad... All of them!
What... is this?
Where'd everyone go?
Hikari!
Hey! Did something
happen to the village?
So you've come back.
Thank goodness.
Come on. Let's hurry
and go see Uroko-sama.
Why do I have to go see Uroko-sama?
Just come on!
Let go!
I said let go!
Hii-kun!
Manaka!
I... Hii-kun...
Manaka, you were told
not to leave your house.
Hey, Hikari!
Come on!
Wait! Hikari!
What happened?
Since I was gone, the
village totally seems...
When I got home last night,
there were a lot of adults waiting and
they said not to go up to the surface again.
My dad wouldn't let me out of the house.
Don't go up to the surface?
Why?
That's just what they
said when I got back.
But why? Why'd they say that?!
I don't know!
They said it was
dangerous on the surface.
So they said that
Chii-chan and Kaname...
that none of us could leave the village.
Then why'd you come outside by yourself?
Because...
Because I had to tell you, Hii-kun!
Even if we care about each other...
Manaka's feelings and my
feelings are different.
But I...
I had to tell you...
The way I feel about Manaka...
Because I had to tell you.
No!
I-I'm sorry...
Dad.
That's enough, Hikari.
Come home.
What's going to happen on the surface?
The world becomes more and more gray...
The humans will forget the Sea God...
This is the story of
humans themselves...
The humans will not be able to bear
the cold that is about to come.
Episode Ten: The Saltflake
Snow Falls and Falls
You need to make your choice.