Was it me?
I...
Huh?
Wh...
-What should I do...
Don't think about it.
Don't think that hard about it,
Kaito Kirishima.
It's not like you admitted to her
that you like her yesterday.
Senpai didn't even realize what
I meant the day before yesterday.
Relax, Ichika.
You're older than Kaito-kun.
You need to keep it together.
Make breakfast like always,
try a little bit harder, and make lunch.
That's right. There's no problem.
Senpai's just living
with me, that's all.
That's all.
Calm yourself, Ichika.
Act calm and normal like always.
Relax, relax, relax.
I can do it if I try.
I just need to be confident.
Maybe it's weird to say
"I can do it if I try."
Maybe it's better if
I just don't try to—
Good morning!
G-Good morning...
N-Nice weather.
Yeah...
It's sunny today.
Yeah.
We'll have finals pretty soon.
I'm not very good at studying.
I see.
I don't even remember
what I ate this morning.
Good morning, Kirishima-kun.
You're up pretty early. That's unusual.
It happens from time to time.
Oh, Tanigawa, sorry about yesterday.
We got separated and I
never met back up with you.
No, I'm sorry, too.
Actually, it's Remon-senpai
and Mio's fault.
I already apologized a lot yesterday.
Oh, yeah, get this, Kaito-kun.
Remon-senpai wasn't the
only one there yesterday.
Tetsuro and Mio were watching me, too.
Oh, really?
Sorry, Kirishima-kun.
No, it's fine.
Did something happen?
S-Something? Like what?
You're not acting like you usually do.
You think so?
Not really.
I'm acting pretty normal.
You went to Karuizawa yesterday?
Huh?
Study hall
Yeah, I guess so.
Why were you there?
Just buying some things.
Kirishima-kun was there, too.
At Karuizawa.
I-I see.
Kirishima-kun.
Interesting.
I bet
she's uncomfortable now.
No, I'm not.
Huh?
It was just so sudden, I was surprised.
I like you, too.
Really?!
Really!
Yay, we feel the same way!
This is great!
I don't swing that way.
That's how I should have reacted.
Here you go.
A lunch box?
Ichika-senpai gave it to
me a little while ago.
She told me to give it to you.
Senpai did?
She went through the
trouble to make it for you.
Don't forget it at home.
Oh, yeah.
You're right.
Hey, Tetsuro.
Huh?
So, hypothetically speaking...
What if this guy, A, kind of
told this girl, B, he likes her.
I like you!
Right after, B went straight home in silence.
Ever since then, B's been
kind of weird around A.
What is B thinking?
Isn't she uncomfortable?
Thought so.
This girl, A, was kind of told by
this guy, B, that he likes her.
She was so surprised, she just left.
So here's the question:
How should A act?
She should tell him how she feels.
Yeah, I thought so.
So how does A feel about B?
She doesn't dislike him at all.
She thinks he's cute.
Then why not go out with him?
The problem isn't that simple.
Why?
That's because A...
...will eventually leave this town.
The girl, B, is definitely
uncomfortable.
But I have no clue whether
she wishes it'd all go away,
or she just doesn't know what to do.
I think it'd be best for the guy,
A, not to rush things.
Not rush things...
Found the slacker.
Oh, Tanigawa.
What is it?
You tired?
Yeah, a little.
I didn't get to ask you this morning...
After we got separated yesterday,
what did you do?
I just went back home, since
there wasn't anything to do.
I see.
Sorry.
Did you look for me?
Huh?
Oh, if it isn't Kirishima-kun
and Tanigawa-san.
Oh, it's you, Remon-senpai.
That's quite the greeting,
considering an attractive
upperclassman...
...is showing her alluring
swimsuit-clad body to you.
Alluring...
That's a normal school
swimsuit, you know.
Remon, we're supposed to gather up...
L-Let's go, Remon.
Right.
It seems that A has a rival, C.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Are things still pretty
awkward between you
and Takatsuki-senpai?
Yeah, I guess...
You need to pull yourself together!
Huh?
Takatsuki-senpai isn't
from this country,
so she might be having
trouble communicating and whatnot.
But she might be kind of scared or lonely
since she came here by herself.
So you need to make
sure she's doing okay.
Yeah, that makes sense.
I think you're right.
I've only been thinking about myself.
I shouldn't do that.
But I think it's good that
you think about others' feelings.
Thanks.
Good luck.
Wow, C over there just doomed herself.
C?
I gotta pull myself together.
Ichika-senpai.
Wh-What is it?
About what happened yesterday...
I'm sorry I acted the way I did.
But that's not what I meant back there.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, I see!
So let's act like this never happened.
Never happened!
All right! That's it.
I'll use that technique to
change the status-quo.
I can do it!
I'll do it!
I've gotta do it!
I want to do it!
You need it that bad?
That's right!
Of course!
Wait, huh?
Ma-Manami-san?
How about I help you out then?
Help me out with what?
What, indeed?
I have no clue what
you're talking about.
Acting all innocent.
Well, whatever.
Kai, I'm going shopping.
Come with me.
I don't have a choice, do I?
Correct.
Kaito-kun.
I was really happy to hear
how you felt about me.
But we've just met each other,
so could you give me some time?
I'll think hard about things,
and then give you an answer.
So let's act like things
are normal until then.
Yes. I understand.
I will do as you say, Senpai.
All right. If I say that to him...
Kaito-kun...
Who's that woman?
Wh-What's going on?
Yesterday he told me...
I mean, it's my fault
for not having given
him my answer yet...
But it hasn't even been a day
and he's already going on
a date with another girl?
I don't believe this!
I was stupid for even
worrying about this!
Just do whatever you want, then!
Rinon,
jump me with the linkage.
If you don't answer me today,
I can't promise what will happen to you.
Rinon, you know...
Onee-chan-san told me to
take care of Kaito-kun.
She left him to me.
That's all there is to this. That's it.
Episode 4
Senpai was amazing.
I'll take this, this... and this.
You're buying that much?
It's a real fight this time.
I see.
So,
where are we going next?
Wai— Manami-san!
You know you like it.
Of course I don't!
They're walking around like that?!
This is...
Um, are you done yet?
Kai, you wanna look?
I'm fine!
What you think? Looks good?
It looks great!
Just b-b-buy it already!
He can't be...
Kaito-kun...
Kaito, come here.
Okay.
Good boy.
What do you think?
I'm better than that
Ichika girl, aren't I?
Of course.
You should forget about a
girl who wouldn't respond...
...to you saying you like her.
Okay.
Rinon!
I'm going to take a shower,
so have some tea or
whatever you'd like.
Right.
Kai,
you wanna take
a shower together?
I wholeheartedly decline.
You're not cute at all.
Man...
I need to talk to Senpai
when I get back.
About what?
Huh?
S-Senpai...
Why are you here?
That doesn't matter.
But...
We're going home.
Huh? Why...
We're going back, okay?
W-Wait a second.
Do you want to stay here that badly?
I-I should at least say goodbye...
Senpai?
Jerk!
Huh?
Why?
Why am I getting so...?
Um, Senpai...
I think you've got the wrong—
What's all the noise out here?
Who's this girl?
Is she your—
-No!
Then who are you?
I-I was asked by Onee-chan-san
to take care of Kaito-kun!
By Nanami?
That's right!
So I'm not going to let
Kaito-kun stay here!
Senpai, uh...
Kaito-kun, you stay quiet!
Sorry.
Who cares?
People can love whoever they want.
You seem a lot older.
Age doesn't matter.
Kaito-kun is a high school student!
Obstacles are a part of love.
Manami-san, what are you say—
Kaito-kun, be quiet!
I'm sorry.
You don't get it?
Get what?
You're out of place here.
I have a duty to protect Kaito-kun.
That's all?
And that's why you came
into someone's house without permission?
Was I not supposed to?
It's pretty odd.
Why not just say it already?
The real reason why you came here.
There is no real reason.
Really?
There isn't.
Kai, this girl is pretty dim.
What do you mean?
You, too, huh?
Just do whatever you want, then.
I suppose that's fun at your age.
Nee-chan?
What? You came again?
Onee-san?
Oh, Kai.
Ichika-senpai's here, too.
Did nee-chan bring you guys here?
Something like that.
Well, make yourselves at home.
And don't walk around in that.
Get dressed.
Fine, fine.
Ishigaki-kun...
What did you mean by Onee-san?
She didn't introduce herself yet?
She's my sister, Manami Ogura.
Ogura... Her last name...
She's married.
Every time she has a
fight with her husband,
she comes here and complains.
I'm not going to forgive him this time.
Why are you fighting?
He erased the program I recorded!
That's ridiculous...
I really wanted to watch it!
Just get back to Satoshi-san already.
I won't forgive him even if he grovels.
Forgive him already!
I've run out of patience this time!
Don't!
Whose side are you on, anyway?!
The right side!
I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry!
No, it's fine.
Actually, I'm sorry for worrying you.
I was completely in the wrong.
Manami-san was acting misleadingly.
So it makes sense.
Let's go.
Hey, Kaito-kun.
Let me make it up to you.
I'll do whatever.
Whatever?
Yeah, whatever you want.
Back then,
what I
really wanted to hear was
the answer to yesterday.
I wanted to know how she thought of me.
But I...
I'm bad at studying.
Could you teach me, Senpai?
Huh?
Okay, I'll do what I can!
You're spelling that wrong.
It's not "e," it's "i."
I'm sorry.
Once we're done with English,
we'll move on to math.
Senpai, shouldn't we go to sleep?
We have school tomorrow.
We don't have much time until finals.
Onee-chan-san will worry if
you get marks like these.
We need to at least get
you above average.
It doesn't matter as
long as I don't fail.
It's that attitude of
yours that's the problem!
You're the one who told me you wanted
my help studying, right?!
Y-Yes.
Now solve this problem.
I-I shouldn't have said anything.
Hey, Kai.
You okay?
-t it see...
Tits?
But it seemed Senpai wasn't like that...
Kaito-kun,
time to study!
English ability test
Takatsuki-senpai.
Senpai, it's lunch right now...
You can study while you eat.
We don't have any time.
R-Right.
Looks like he's going through a lot.
But I'm glad.
About what?
Kaito-kun and Takatsuki-senpai
don't have that awkwardness anymore.
Yeah, I'm glad.
C didn't realize what was going on.
What are you doing?!
Don't just touch a girl's head
out of nowhere like that!
A girl?
You're a girl, huh?
What the heck!
Try saying that again!
Final Exams
Math I
English
Classic Japanese
Closing ceremony
Kaito-kun.
Senpai.
Let's go home.
Summer break was about to start.
One we'd never be able to forget.
An unforgettable summer.
I'm sure...
...everyone felt the same way.
Happiness and sadness. Pain.
All of it put together in one package.
There'll never be another like it.
-That summer is about to begin.
Episode 5
Senpai is the heroine
I know what Ichika-senpai really is!
Don't say it! If you do, I'll...
Tetsuro-kun died!