Yukigaoka         Kitagawa Daiichi
My first and last official
match of junior high...
My team was defeated.
My opponent was the "King of the Court."
I'll get my revenge against that "King"!
That's what I pledged before
starting Karasuno High School.
But...
W...
Karasuno
Why is he here?!
Episode 2: Karasuno High School Volleyball Club
Why?
Why is this guy at Karasuno?
Maybe he's just a lookalike.
What are you doing here, anyway?
You make it sound so easy.
I'll be the last one standing.
What were you doing for the last three years?
No, no. There's no mistake.
This guy is Kageyama Tobio!
I met you last year...
But I don't know your name.
M-My name is Hinata Shoyo.
You probably don't remember
the team you beat in the first match!
I remember you very well.
Your well-developed
physical agility and reflexes...
But he doesn't put any of it to good use.
What? You wanna fight?
You were lousy!
D-Don't make fun of me.
Sure, we got slaughtered by you guys.
Next time, I won't lose!
That's what I pledged to myself,
so what are you doing here?
How can I defeat you
if we're on the same team?
Shouldn't you be at some
other school with strong players?
Why didn't you go there?
The strongest school in the prefecture...
rejected me.
You didn't make it?
Even though you're the King of the Court?
Don't...
...call me that!
Huh?
The first setter of Kitagawa is on our team?
But the guy's totally cocky.
Don't try and intimidate him, okay?
I-I wouldn't do something like that.
Hello.
Karasuno High School
Volleyball Club
Hey, hey, hey. Who said you guys could...
You're Kageyama?
Osu.
Glad you're here.
You're quite tall.
He needs an initiation, Suga-san!
Let's give him a reason to be
intimidated by us third-years!
Tanaka, stop with that face.
Kageyama is slightly taller.
But high-schoolers are kinda big...
That's right. I'm at Karasuno now.
Alright...
Osu!
How tall are you?
180 cm.
Oh...
What? You're cocky!
Hello!
Huh?
Oh! You!
Shorty #1!
So the other applicant here, Hinata, is...
You?
I'm a little surprised...
I see.
So both of you are here at Karasuno.
Um...
We saw your match last year.
You're way short and sucked bad,
but you've got guts.
Thanks!
Your jumps were awesome, too.
But you haven't grown much since.
I may be little, but I can jump!
I'll be Karasuno's ace!
Hey, hey.
The newbie says he's gonna be the ace?
You've got some nerve.
It's good to be ambitious, right?
I'll do my best.
If you want to be the ace,
I hope you've improved.
If you goof around,
you'll waste another three years.
What did you say?
Why must you say that, Kageyama?
I played with all my might.
Yukigaoka     Kitagawa Daiichi
But...
But don't tell me
everything I've done is a waste!
Guys...
You know, you're not enemies any more.
Volleyball is about teamwork－
I'll challenge you.
Hey! Daichi-san is still talking!
Challenge me to what?
Volleyball, what else?
How do you expect to challenge me one-on-one?
L-Like a passing contest!
How do you compete at passing?
Listen, damn it!
What's the commotion, volleyball club?
Yikes. The dean!
Sensei.
You'd better not be fighting.
Of course not.
Just a friendly rivalry. Right?
This dean likes to make trouble,
so keep it down.
Serve! I'll return them all.
Hey!
I was only able to get
one of your serves last year.
Right in the face...
But I've been training
with all kinds of people.
I'm not the same person as last year.
Not the same as last year, huh?
I'm not the same as last year, either.
Now, now, guys.
Let's not get carried away.
Is he a first-year student?
Relax. Don't be intimidated.
Remember, you've trained
at this with the old ladies!
Here goes.
A jump serve?
Last year he didn't—
I'm not sure I could've returned that one!
None of the girl volleyball players
or old ladies served like that!
How's that different from last year?
One more.
Hey. Enough is enough.
They don't listen to their captain.
This could be a problem.
He has quick reflexes!
He's right in frontー
If this keeps happen—
He was wearing a wig?
You just noticed?
Everyone at the entrance ceremony could tell.
You guys! Shut up!
Tanaka, you shut up, too.
Sawamura-kun, I'd like a word with you.
Fortunately, he's not punishing us.
And no apologies necessary,
provided you all agree that you saw nothing.
But, you guys...
All because you couldn't hit a serve! You suck.
What's different from last year?
Are you kidding me?
I was dumb to even think it.
You suck!
You talk too much.
Hey.
I want you to listen to me.
I don't know what your motive
was for attending Karasuno.
But I'm sure you came here
with victory on your mind.
Yes.
Of course.
Karasuno was one of the top teams
in the prefecture till a few years ago.
It happened only once,
but we even went to nationals.
Now we rank at best in the prefecture's top 8.
Neither weak not strong.
Other schools call us things like,
"Fallen Rivals,"
and "Unflying Crows."
I remember well when Karasuno
competed in spring nationals.
Students from my neighborhood,
I'd pass by high school students
competed against the country's best teams,
in a huge gymnasium in Tokyo.
It gave me goosebumps.
We're going to go there again.
I'm going to the same court
as the little giant.
There are many
schools dreaming
of going to nationals.
You bastard...
Don't worry.
I mean what I say.
For us to make that happen,
our team has be unified.
And we can't have the dean
keeping an eye on us.
I'm not telling you guys to become buddies.
Even if you were enemies on opposite sides
of the net in junior high,
I need you to understand that now,
you're on the same side.
Do you get it?
No matter how outstanding you are,
no matter how willing
you are to give it your all,
if you fail to get along,
and hinder your teammates...
You're not wanted!
Until you realize that you're both teammates,
you won't be participating in this club!
Haikyuu!!
What does it mean to realize
that we're teammates?
How do you do it?
Who knows?
Please let me in!
Please let me play volleyball!
I'll get along with Kageyama, too!
Please!
Are you sure about this, Daichi?
They're still members.
Teams come together gradually, anyway.
I know that, but...
Out of my way!
I apologize!
I swear I'll get along with this guy.
Please let me participate in the club.
Are you sure you mean that?
If I had to cooperate
with that guy in a match,
I'd rather receive, spike, and toss all by myself.
How could you say that?
I can't believe you just
told me your true feelings.
But I think that's a good thing.
Still, in volleyball, you can't drop the ball,
you can't hold the ball,
and one player can't touch the ball twice.
How do you plan to play by yourself?
Let me ask you something.
Are you actually stupid?
Right!
Tanaka, block and follow properly.
Osu!
The court and ball are in front of my eyes.
And it sucks that I'm not allowed in...
Dammit! I have no time to waste like this.
I'm gonna make them let me in.
You realize we're teammates now?
I'm a force to be reckoned with.
That's reason enough
for me to be on the team.
Just what I'd expect from the King—
Anyway, what are you going to do?
I'll challenge them
to a two-on-two match.
If we win, they have to let us in.
If we team up, we'll appear friendly
no matter how we feel.
That will speed things up.
We're going to challenge our senpais?
What if we lose?
We won't lose.
You have me on your side.
Is this guy for real?
Does he really mean what he says?
You just need to do the best you can...
...to not to get in my way.
Huh?
Do you think anyone would agree to that
and be all, "Yes, I'll do the best I can"?
So what do you suggest?
Keep gazing through that window?
In junior high, I was only in one real match,
the one against your school.
We didn't have enough team members
to apply for a tournament till then.
I couldn't have real practice,
so I trained wherever I could.
The gym, hallways, random corners...
In hallways?
So that first tournament...
When I stood at the center of the court
in that huge gymnasium...
I felt the spotlight on me,
I got worked up, like "Gwaaa!"
"Gwaaa"?
I wanted to stay there, but...
Staying on the court...
Men's Volleyball prefecture tournament
Kitagawa Daiichi, bitterly defeated
Only the strong can stay.
Well, what are we going to do?
If we don't go in together,
they'll slam the door.
If I can play volleyball...
I can endure anything, for a little while!
No matter how obnoxious you are,
I'll do my best to keep from seeing you!
That's my line, you idiot!
Um...
Can you let me through?
Kiyoko-san, good to see you.
I'll get that for you.
Never mind. I'll hold it myself.
Kiyoko-san, you're beautiful as ever today!
It turns me on when she ignores me!
Good job, everyone.
They'll probably say,
"Let us in if we can beat you in a match."
That's possible.
But all they have to do is show just
a little contrition, that's all.
Captain!
Let us challenge you to a match.
The two of us against you senpais.
Are these guys for real?
One-two...
We'll prove that we can cooperate as a team.
I heard them say "one-two"...
But I can't say I dislike these guys.
And what if you lose?
We'll endure any penalty.
Hmm...
Club Application
Then now's the time.
There are two other first-year
applicants besides you guys.
It'll be a three-on-three
match against them.
We always play this game every year,
just to see what the new members are made of.
But how does it become three-on-three?
Who's our other team member?
Tanaka. I want you to be on Hinata's side.
What? Me?
You don't dislike them, right?
That doesn't mean I want to play with them.
I see. I thought you'd be
the only one here
who could discipline these troublemakers.
Oh, well! I guess it can't be helped.
I'll do it.
Aren't you glad?
And if you lose the match,
as long as we third-years are here,
Kageyama will never play setter.
That's all?
That's because our team can't win
with a self-centered setter.
A guy who banks on his skills, but loses.
What's the matter?
I'm not ejecting you from the club.
You'd be good in other positions, too,
wouldn't you?
I'm a setter!
Then win.
You're here because you think
you can win by yourself, right?
I... I'm here, too!
The game will be Saturday morning.
Listen up!
Tanaka-senpai's gonna teach you a lesson.
Understood?
Are we being a little
too hard on those guys?
That's true.
You're stricter than usual, Daichi-san.
Do you have some special reason in mind?
Dammit!
What? Are you mad because
you're gonna eat the penalty?
But even if you're not setter,
I'm sure you'd do fine as a regular.
And...
spikers are cooler than setters anyway.
Wham, like that!
Bastard!
The setter is the team's control tower!
It's the setter that handles
the ball the most in a match.
It's the most dominant role!
It's the coolest!
Huh?
And your favorite, the spike.
You can't shoot without the setter.
But setter looks difficult,
and it's not very flashy...
You... Have you ever seen
a huge tournament live?
I haven't.
It's hard to tell from the angles
they show on TV...
But if you watch from the
end side of the court,
you can see the setter's
super-fast toss really well.
Zoom. From one end of the court to the other.
The ball goes past the enemy's block.
You think to yourself: "Hey!
Can they really return that?"
But before the toss,
the spiker jumps, and hits it.
Wham! Like that.
O-Oh...
Sure, spikers are cool. But...
But the setter tricks the enemy blockers.
The setter tears down walls for the spiker.
It's difficult, it's cool, it's
fun, and that's the setter!
I understand why now you want to be setter.
Kageyama will never play setter.
Damn... why is that?
All you have to do is win.
You were full of confidence taking
on the senpais, weren't you?
That's right. I can't get anxious.
I can't rely on this guy,
but I can send tosses to that second-year guy.
Hey. We better do something about that
sorry receive of yours by Saturday.
Sorry? Well, but we can't use the gym.
Oh, yes.
Morning practice is at 7:00 AM tomorrow, right?
Of course, but why did you
ask that all of a sudden?
Oh, uh, well...
Was the dean's wig undamaged?
Hey, stop talking about that!
Tomorrow...
5:00 AM.
Don't be late.
You don't be late.
My bag! I forgot my bag!
Just as I was afraid of... it's locked.
Then find a window you can get in from.
We'll get in trouble if we're
caught. Are you stupid?
5:00 AM sure is rough.
Tanaka-san?
Get out of here before 7:00 AM.
Tanaka-san!
Thanks!
What a good senpai I am.
Call me Tanaka-senpai.
Tanaka-senpai.
Once again.
Alright. Time to practice.
That's true. You're stricter
than usual, Daichi-san.
Do you have some special reason in mind?
You guys saw their match last year.
Kageyama had outstanding ability
as a junior-high student...
But his ability hasn't yielded any results.
And he's self-centered, which means
he'll repeat the same mistakes as in junior high.
He'll get in the way of the team for sure.
But what's different from junior high...
is that Hinata is on the
same team now with Kageyama.
Hinata? Well, he's sort of a ball
of athletic reflexes, but...
Yeah. He's far removed from
his true potential,
but he has rare speed and
reflexes, and his jump...
He didn't get the chance to play
with a setter in junior high.
And Kageyama is seeking for a fast spiker
who can hit his tosses.
Those guys are imperfect
on their own...
But put their abilities together...
if we can utilize that combination...
Karasuno will make explosive improvement.
Don't you agree?
Cut it out! I'm going first.
Tanaka-san is in there. He was first.
If that's what you think, move.
Hey. There's no time...
These bastards have more problems
than teamwork...
Ah, the gymnasium.
You were here yesterday.
The little giant practiced here, too.
Alright.
Let's do this!
Preview of next episode
Damn, I'm off to a terrible start
because of that Hinata.
That's because you said you wanted
to do it all by yourself.
I'd rather do it alone than with you.
That's the wrong attitudeー
Hey, you didn't get up early just to fight!
Osu.
Next episode Haikyu!: "The Formidable Ally"
Episode 3 The Formidable Ally