I like you.
I always have.
From the first time I saw you, I think.
I don't think I knew,
but I fell in love.
So it... was all a dream, then?
You said that yesterday, too.
Senpai.
I know it's summer,
but you'll still catch a cold
if you fall asleep out here.
So...
W-Wait.
Now I feel better.
I had this dream.
What was it about?
We started dating.
That wasn't a dream.
I still can't believe it.
This wouldn't have happened
without Tanigawa-san.
She helped me realize how I felt.
I wonder if Tanigawa is
still under the weather.
This is terrible...
I'm still swollen.
I can't let everyone see me like this.
You shouldn't worry about it.
You don't look that differ—
Anyway.
Did you tell everyone?
I told everyone you had a summer cold.
Well, that's good at least.
Thanks.
Well, we have known each other forever.
About the day before yesterday...
I haven't told anyone,
so don't worry about it.
Yeah.
I'm about to make lunch.
Tetsuro-kun, you want some?
Oh, sure—
Tetsuro has something to do!
He's going home soon!
I guess I am.
I love Kaito-kun.
I love him.
Kanna,
I...
Hey.
I'm going home.
Huh?
Wai—
Don't follow me!
I'm sure...
right now...
she's...
You're Kitahara-san, right?
We went to the same grade school,
but this is the first time we've
been in the same class, huh?
I'm Kanna Tanigawa, nice to meet you.
Yeah. Me, too.
We're in the same class again?
I just can't get rid of you, can I?
You took the words
right out of my mouth.
Oh, this is Tetsuro Ishigaki.
We've known each other
since we were kids.
Nice to meet you, Mio Kitahara-san.
You know my name...
Huh? You know her?
Nope, I know the name and
face of every girl here.
I don't know whether to be impressed
or think you're an idiot.
Can't you just say I'm a gentleman
who's also a feminist?
I don't think so.
It took a long time, you know.
Yeah, and what a waste.
It's been...
...three years already.
Yo.
Tetsuro-kun.
You headed somewhere?
I was going to see Kanna.
Oh, you probably shouldn't.
Her eyes are—
C-Cold...
Her eyes are cold?
I meant her cold.
She doesn't want to spread it.
She wouldn't let me see her, either.
So you were at Kanna's place, then.
We've known each other
forever, after all.
Mio?
Are you hungry?
I made cake for her, and I'd
hate to see it go to waste.
Thanks for the food.
No problem.
Thanks.
What's that?
Oh, I thought I'd sort out
some of these films.
Remon-senpai taped a bunch.
So it's been piling up...
What's wrong?
Does something have to be wrong?
That's not what I meant.
I think I like cuddling.
Do you not like me like this?
No...
I... think I like it, too.
Good.
Don't mind me.
Keep going.
I mind.
So you two are a couple now, huh?
I-I guess so.
Have you guys done—
Wh-What are you going on about?!
That's not fair!
Good for you, Ichika.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Kirishima-kun.
This is a present from me to you.
Wh-What was it?
What was what?
She just gave you...
Remon-senpai!
Treasure this miraculous
joining of two souls well.
Thanks for the cake.
Man, I ate a lot.
Your cake is really good, Mio.
Yeah, but that's the only thing
I've got in my favor.
But it's good you have something.
You have things going for you, too.
You're tall, you're handsome,
you're good with your hands...
You're good at remembering the
faces and names of girls.
I wouldn't say that's in my favor.
Is it okay if I ask you something difficult?
What is it?
Why did you invite Takatsuki-senpai
to make a movie with us?
Because it seemed like
that's what Kai wanted.
I never thought she'd say yes, though.
You knew how Kanna felt, didn't you?
You're so close to her.
I noticed, so I'm sure you noticed, too.
Why did you ask Takatsuki-senpai?
If Senpai and Kirishima-kun
ended up getting closer...
That wasn't it.
Then Kanna would...
I said that wasn't it.
I just wanted to support
Kai, so I asked her.
And if Kanna joined us
in making the movie, too,
then I thought she'd be
able to get closer to Kai.
I didn't know how it'd turn out.
I just wanted to help both of them out.
That's all.
Then what happens to your feelings?
Where are your feelings for
Kanna going to end up?
What? What are you talking about—
I've been watching you this
whole time, so I know.
You've only been focused on Kanna.
That's not true.
I...
Why do you lie to yourself?
Time isn't going to solve everything
if you keep avoiding the problem.
You're the one who told me to
just say what I want to say.
That's why I tried to be brave for once.
I like you.
Tetsuro-kun... I like you.
I love you.
I told you I didn't need
an answer back then,
but will you tell me now?
Mio, I...
I don't dislike you...
But right now, I...
I understand.
I'm going home.
I'll stay normal.
We're all going to have fun filming
that movie over summer break.
We'll make the movie, and
show it at the school fair.
And I'll just keep being
the usual Kanna Tanigawa.
That's what I've decided.
Kanna...
Tanigawa? Tanigawa went back home—
She likes you, Kai.
I love Kaito-kun.
I love him.
What am I supposed to do?
What can I even do?!
Ou...
Episode 10
Senpai and our...
Ouch.
Senpai.
What is it?
Would you like to go take
a walk to cool off a bit?
Sure...
Oh, I know.
Since it's been a while...
Rinon.
Oh, wow.
I know, right?
I thought it'd be really
nice here at night.
And we have memories here.
There's so much nature still around.
It's weird. My first time
coming to this planet,
yet it's almost like I can
remember seeing all of this.
Um, Senpai.
I'd like to help you find that
place of yours, if it's okay?
Huh?
If I could help you out, even a little—
Kaito-kun.
Thank you.
I, uh...
But, it's okay now.
Sure, that's why I originally
came to this planet...
Actually, I just wanted to go on a trip.
I didn't really have a reason.
I just thought I wanted to do something.
Me, too.
I wanted to start something using this.
I thought, "If I could just
put something together..."
I see.
I guess we were the same.
That makes me want to help
grant your wish even more.
Right now, I want to be with you.
I want to make the movie
with you and everyone else.
That's my wish right now.
Is that all right?
I knew.
Nothing in this world lasts forever.
Can't tell him because you're an alien?
And you can't be with him because
you can't stay here forever?
Are you going to use that as an
excuse to just keep running from him?
That was the best thing to do.
Now Kaito-kun will get what he wants.
That was for the best.
What's going on?
Ow.
You haven't said anything
since you got back home.
Did something happen?
You can tell your sister.
You know, that's your problem.
Nothing's going to fix
itself if you keep quiet.
You can't just keep acting cool.
You might look like you're
doing fine day by day,
but I know you're just a kid at heart.
You're here because you left
your husband. Don't lecture me.
I didn't leave him.
I just ran away for a while.
Basically, I still have a home.
A fight between wife and
husband can take many forms.
But you haven't even gone out with a girl,
so I don't think you'd understand.
Man, it reeks of virgin in here.
Then get the hell ou—
Oh, he's here.
Thanks for the room, Tetsuro.
Anyway, good luck.
You took so long!
I had to wait all that time.
And so she just leaves again?
Hello?
Tetsuro?
Oh, what's up, Kai?
I want to start filming again
the day after tomorrow.
That fine with you?
That's fine, but...
Kaito Kirishima
Senpai will be there, too.
Oh, I see.
Huh? Did you and she...?
Oh, I'll tell everyone about that
when we actually meet in person.
Then you really did...
Yeah, I guess so.
Then what about Kanna?!
Kaito Kirishima
That's why I need to talk to everyone.
And tell them how I feel.
Tetsuro, I...
Tetsuro?
What am I doing?
On location in Okinawa!
All right.
Now I should be fine
for tomorrow's shoot.
I'll be fine.
Yeah, I'll be fine.
Kanna, phone for you!
On location in Okinawa!
Coming!
Welcome to Lookout Garden
Why did you call me out here?
I'm supposed to be getting over a cold.
Who cares?
You're not all swollen up anymore.
Yeah, I guess so.
All right!
Magic!
Shoot, defeated.
We came here a lot when
we were in kindergarten.
Yeah, we did.
I was taller than you back then.
And now look how much taller you are.
And you always saved me
from getting bullied.
The Kanna punch is invincible.
You were pretty cool.
Why are you acting so creepy?
Actually, you didn't just call me out
here to talk about the past, did you?
Hey, what happened to your foot?
J-Just a little accident.
So what do you want?
I, uh...
If you want to say something
about Kaito-kun, don't bother.
I already know.
I'll be fine.
If you don't need anything
else, I'm going home.
I thought everything would be fine if
things worked out between you and Kai!
But I didn't want to see that happen!
So then I ended up being stupid,
hoping that if Kai and Senpai hit it off,
you'd be open to whatever.
But that'd never happen.
Tetsuro...
I played with the heart of the
girl I like, only to make her cry.
And now I can't do anything about it!
The girl you like...
Y-You're kidding, right?
I'm serious.
Since when?
For a long time now.
God...
My mind's already a mess and
now you decide to tell me this?!
You jerk!
I know the timing's really bad.
But I was finally able
to get it off my chest.
Tetsuro...
I know you really like Kai, don't you?
Yeah.
Kai likes Ichika-senpai, but that
doesn't change anything, does it?
Yeah.
And that's what I liked about you.
Why do you get to say all that stuff,
and look all happy that you got to?
When I...
I...
Don't hold it in.
You should just stay Kanna.
D-Don't touch a girl's hair like that!
I already know that!
Thank you!
You can cry, you know?
I'm not going to cry.
Stubborn, aren't we?
Shut up.
Actually, it's not fair of you to come here.
Girls are tenacious.
You're strong.
You can do a lot when you're in love.
I was able to change because of you.
No, I can at least think about changing,
about being stronger, because of you.
So, thank you for that.
That's what I want to say to you.
I...
I'm...
Kaito-kun!
Tanigawa...
Is your cold better?
You want some watermelon?
Kaito-kun.
I like you.
I've liked you for a long time now.
I love you!
Sorry, Tanigawa.
I like Senpai.
I know.
Thanks for hearing me out.
Let's work on that movie.
Yeah.
Even if nothing in this world lasts forever,
we'll still...
The camera's ready.
We're ready here.
All ready.
Scene #275, ready.
Go.
I'm sorry, Black Man.
But I still want to stay on this planet.
There's a lot on this planet I care about.
So I will...
Remon-senpai said we'd be
filming a lot until this evening.
I wonder how much longer
all the filming will take.
I think we'll still finish by
the end of summer break.
Another week, huh?
Ichika!
You're alive, Ichika!
Do you know how worried
I was about you?!
Onee-chan?
Ichika!
Onee-san?
Episode 11 Don't go, Senpai.
Onee-chan, why did you come to Earth?
Oh, I know.
I bet she came to give us her blessing.
Oh, come on, Onee-chan!
It's too early for that!
Or is she?