Stop!
Don't hurt Saizo any more!
Well, this is interesting.
Does your sadness awaken the
power of the Kushimitama?
Shunko!
Kasho Zanmai!
No!
If he had never met you,
never had anything to do with you,
this never would have happened to Saizo.
My...
Isanami, don't listen to him.
All the other braves should have
drawn their last breath by now.
It's all your fault.
Isanami...
The Wail of Darkness
Bored, bored, bored!
Everyone's so serious about
what's going on with Isanami.
Don't worry. Saizo is with her.
I wanna fight Saizo!
Hey, squirmy! Have you gotten darker?
Hey, wait up, squirmy.
Play with me.
What are you doing, Princess?
You bastard.
Quit running your mouth and fight me!
You're rather tough, aren't you?
But you should learn your limits.
Where am I?
I can't see anything.
Is this where you've been, Princess?
That shadow...
How long are you going to hide in there?
Oh, right. I was hiding.
Do I have to go?
Do you really not want to
go to tonight's banquet?
You call it a banquet, but it's
a matchmaking meeting, isn't it?
I'm not interested.
The one who likes you would
be very sad to hear that.
No one like that exists.
Most men don't like my red
hair or these family tattoos.
Not that I care, though.
Is that so?
I think they're beautiful.
Both your tattoos and
the color of your hair.
His warm hand reminds me of that time.
"That time?"
Princess!
I've been looking everywhere for you.
Hurry up and change.
Which would you prefer? Choose.
I don't like any of them.
They're uncomfortable.
Princess.
The princess insists she
does not wish to go.
How dare you say such
a thing, Raizu-sama?
Well, Princess...
What?
I shall prepare a flower bath for you.
Really? I love baths.
Wonderful. I'll get the flowers right away.
Okay.
I shall take my time and
prepare the bath with care.
All right.
The water should be just right by the
time you return from the banquet.
No fair.
Princess.
Fine. I get it.
Just make sure you use roses, okay?
Just as glamorous and boring as usual.
Is everyone really so
desperate to get married?
I can't think of anyone I'd want to marry.
But if I did meet someone,
I wonder what he'd be like.
I feel like... I've forgotten
something important.
She's so weird.
Can you imagine, a woman with tattoos?
Isn't it a family tradition?
But it's so crude, and her
hair is such a dull red.
Not to mention she's scrawny.
It's no wonder no lord is interested in her.
Who cares if I'm not popular?
I like my hair and tattoos.
You have no right to
talk about me that way.
There you are, Princess.
I've come to retrieve you.
Your bath is ready. Shall we go?
Yes.
The warm water feels wonderful.
This must be true happiness.
Don't you agree, Raizu?
Are you bothered by
what those girls said?
They're right about one thing.
I like my hair and tattoos,
but I'm not a fan of this
thin, unfeminine body.
It's cute in its own right.
I will love you however you are.
Could my soul mate be
closer than I thought?
Princess?
I like this place.
So do I.
It feels nice to be loved.
I want to stay here forever.
Then you should stay here forever.
You won't laugh at me for
not getting married?
I would never laugh.
In fact, I would be delighted.
Really?
I'm so comfortable here
that I don't want to move.
Please stay here, Princess.
You're right.
I'll surrender myself to happiness
and stay here forever.
Stay here with me forever.
Those loving eyes... That sweet smell...
I want to stay wrapped
up in these forever.
Is that all you've got?
Are you sure you haven't lost your edge?
I want to take my time killing you.
I'll have to reject your offer.
I don't care what you want.
This is all about her.
How does it feel knowing your friends
are being erased one by one?
Well?
"Well," my ass!
She doesn't need to answer the question.
We'll find out soon enough, won't we?
Don't listen to this freak, Isanami!
You don't have time to
worry about others.
Shut up already!
No, I want his cold piercing glare.
Princess?
No.
Princess!
Are you hurt?
Are you all right?
I want the smell of blood.
Sweet smells make me puke.
He smells of blood and rust and dust.
Princess?
He has the petrifying gaze of a killer.
Wh-What are you...?
I want supreme pleasure.
The primal rush of killing one another!
Princess, wait.
I'm not your princess!
That was a disgusting trick, you bastard.
I'll kill you! I'll freaking kill you!
Hitotsume no Muraji!
You can't escape, you moron.
No one has broken my illusion before.
Seduced by a fairyland you've
never experienced before,
in the warm embrace of your lover,
deep in a world of
happiness until you die.
I gave you ultimate pleasure.
Where's the pleasure in that?
That lukewarm experience will
never give me what I want!
I live for violence.
Fighting, short of breath,
blood flowing, and mind numb!
This very moment!
This is the best.
I see. You like pain, do you?
Then I will give it to you.
I, Iga Ninja Kuchiba,
shall make my move.
Iga Ninja Technique.
Chimatsuri.
I can't catch anything but small ones.
These wouldn't even be good with drink.
Are you gonna catch
some for me, Veronica?
All right. By the time
you get back, I'll...
Got a big one.
Gotcha.
All right.
Ice?
Nice to meet you, brave number ten.
I am Anastasia.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I've been looking forward
to meeting you.
The busty blonde.
You're just like he described.
Now we can finally get
to know each other.
We'll be saying good bye soon.
You're no fun.
Why don't we give it a go?
Just try touching me.
You'll freeze.
Damn, it's cold.
Are you cold on the inside, too?
I wonder.
You're cold all over.
That's right.
Iga Ice Technique!
Sohyoga!
That was easy.
Sorry, but you can't beat my spear.
Iga Ice Technique.
Gokuhyojun!
That was close.
Why are you trying to kill me, anyway?
Because you're a brave.
That's just what that lord said.
I've got nothing to do with it.
No matter!
Seriously?
I've been ordered to
kill all the braves!
Are your orders that important to you?
You're quite a talkative
brave, aren't you?
Why don't you shut your mouth?
If you're gonna keep me quiet,
I prefer you use your lips.
After all, we're just a guy and a girl.
I'll kill you.
Just die already!
What a request.
I'm afraid I can't do that,
even for a woman.
I've got big plans for myself.
Shut up!
What a terrible face you're making.
What?
Your frozen face is melting.
Damn it.
Kill him. Kill him!
That's how you've always lived.
It's all for your dream.
Mama?
I've struggled to survive since
I ended up in this country.
To take back my proof of royalty
and return to my homeland...
Everything I've done, I did for my dream.
Isn't this wonderful?
If you want it, let's make a deal.
I haven't wavered until now.
I lived only to accomplish my own goals.
Alone in this cold, bloody, dark world.
I never looked for warmth or comfort.
No such thing exists.
Ana!
How cute.
There's no such thing as a cozy home.
It's all a lie.
Let's end this.
You've put up quite a fight,
but you cannot win.
The Ice told us everything she
knew about your abilities.
Even though she called herself
a brave, she hated you all.
He's lying! Don't listen to him!
It's up to you whether
or not you believe me,
but if you think about it,
you'll understand.
The way you pretend you're
a family is disgusting.
I'm sure she said something like that.
Ana.
Isanami, don't listen to him!
Where do you think you're looking?
Saizo!
She joined us when she
realized it was a lie.
Those who don't see it
are destined to die...
...in the hollow name of friendship.
Whoops.
You're merciless.
Ow!
My leg!
That was close.
I won't miss this time.
Hey, come on now.
Let's stop this already.
Begging for your life?
You're an unbelievably pathetic man.
I don't plan to die here.
I've got people and the whole
wide ocean waiting for me.
I bet there's plenty of
good women out there, too.
Sorry, but you're going to die here.
It's your fate.
My fate?
You can't tie me down with that!
I don't take orders from anyone!
I live freely!
I won't have anyone
force their ideals on me!
Freely?
Are you stupid?
The strong will always control the weak.
You have no freedom!
Are you the same way?
Bingo.
Shut your mouth!
Iga Ice Technique!
Eikyu Todo!
You finally shut up.
Now you're imprisoned forever.
I abandoned my freedom.
I live coldly, strongly.
Strength is all I need.
I know nothing else.
Your frozen face is melting.
You could never...
...melt my ice.
You think this'll kill me?
Just run, Saizo.
You know he can't do that.
Let's not give him false hope.
Don't cry, Isanami!
No one's gonna die.
I promise I'll be fine.
It's my fault.
It's because I'm weak.
Because I can't fight like everyone else.
I cause everyone pain.
I'm useless.
Worthless.
Do you want power?
I do.
Great power?
Overwhelming power?
I do!
Then cast aside your hairpin.
Do this, and the power will be yours.
Don't, Isanami!
Power!
The sun...
It's disappearing?
What's going on?
Isanami.
Isanami...
Sasuke, Kakei-san, Rokuro-san, old sea dog,
Seikai, Benmaru, Kamanosuke.
I won't let your deaths be in vain.
I will save Isanami!
Hold up!
We're not dead yet!
This isn't over.
I will not lose.
Neither will I!
Isanami!
Who are you calling a pervert?!
I didn't call you one!
And shut up! I wish you
would've stayed asleep!
The final episode of Brave 10
is "The Warrior of Light."
The Warrior of Light
Bring it on!