I wanted to feel the wind...
A faster wind than any I could feel in this world.
How much can you narrow down the time frame?
I'm sorry.
All Pitz knows is that it'll be tonight.
But he's sure it'll be somewhere in this area...
Tonight, huh?
Be careful.
Remember how Akari was kidnapped last time.
It was no big deal...
It most certainly was a big deal!
It was my fault.
It's nothing you should worry about, Teppei.
I should have been with you.
Everyone, I'm sorry that I can't
be with you at a time like this.
We're a team. We cover for each other.
That's right.
But I'm the only one not helping the team, again.
Teppei...
For a combat unit,
the most important thing is to
know your own capabilities.
Right now, the testing being
done at Tanegashima
of your abilities and those of the
Livlaster is your top priority.
If it goes well, the Midsummer's Knights
will be twice as powerful.
We're counting on you, Teppei.
Just as the rumors say...
What rumors?
That there's a woman who can ride her
bike, as if she were riding the wind.
Do you think no one can beat you?
Only because no one can.
What's your name?
Lin.
Where do you go to school?
I don't.
You have a nice machine.
Are you rich?
This is a good wind.
On the Windy Planet
Seaside University
Hey, Marimura-sensei...
Who's the "Robin" funding this research project?
You want to know?
Everyone's asking about it.
Ban-kun...
Until a few years ago, I was researching
the use of transcranial magnetic stimulation
to control the dreams of
sleeping research subjects.
A system that would let you
dream whatever you want?
If that worked, it would have
any number of applications
in psychiatry and clinical psychology.
Robin was the one who took an interest
in the research and offered to fund it.
But I don't know if Robin is the
name of a person or a group.
But now I understand.
This project's name, "Install,"
refers to installing dreams.
No.
That isn't what it means.
Hey, you're here, Mao.
Oh, Lin...
Welcome.
Hey, you can't speak to Marimura-sensei like that!
It's fine... She's a friend.
What brings you here today?
Need more allowance?
I'm glad we're on the same page.
Yeah.
I want a faster machine...
Come down, Pitz.
Let's go.
Sorry!
Wait a second... My pendant got stuck.
I got it.
Yeah.
Ah, such innocence.
Teppei...
I feel bad for what I said to Teppei.
I didn't know it was such a big deal to him.
From now on, we should be careful.
Roger.
But personally, I'm kind of glad that
Teppei felt bad not being here.
Yeah.
She's under complete hypnosis.
Why is she so important to you?
Securing her is very important
to this project's future.
Now, Lin...
You are in a world deep within your
heart, where your soul is free.
How do you feel about your daily life?
I love the speed of my machine.
I want to go faster.
That's right, Lin.
The machine gives you freedom.
But doesn't anything bother you
about how you're living now?
Not as long as the real me is somewhere else...
The real you?
That's an interesting thing to say.
What is the real you?
It's...
Who are you?!
This place is off-limits to non-personnel!
Get out of there!
I'll contact security!
Wait...
Look at the way this brain
MRI spectrum is changing.
Can you believe this is the same person?
Wonderful...
Marimura-sensei?
You are also designer children, aren't you?
What are you saying, Sensei?
We are the Planetary Gears.
We reveal the dream of the world.
I knew he'd be here.
Daichi Manatsu-kun?
Should we eliminate him here?
He's the Earthling who drove Albion crazy?
I'd like to play with him a bit.
Do as you like.
But he's a Neoteny.
Don't forget that.
They look so happy swimming around.
I'm sure the reason they can enjoy it is that
they don't know they're going to die.
Well, there are some things
you're happier not knowing.
But all living things die.
They're all the same.
They aren't the same.
Dying means you're incomplete as a living thing.
Why do you guys believe that only
humans that don't die are real humans?
Because it's true...
You people aren't real humans.
That's why you're sure to die.
Hey, what do you think about
the fact that you'll surely die?
Doesn't it make you feel pathetic,
to only live for such a short time?
Someone told me that when you die,
you should do it with a smile.
That's right...
All creatures like you can do is smile as you die.
No...
I don't think that's what he meant.
Stop quibbling, Neoteny.
Where'd he go?
When did you...
You're fast.
I was on the track team.
Is that the Livlaster Tanegashima?
Slowly raise your hands, and give me the gun.
We'll finish this later, Earthling.
This machine is fast, right?
Yeah...
Faster than anything you've ever ridden.
You know how it works, don't you, Lieban?
Yeah.
I'll settle things with that Neoteny.
Abreaction!
MM bus signal detected!
I've located the epicenter of the
Machine Goodfellow activation area.
This is bad...
It's underwater!
Hana said it would appear in this area...
It will be near me.
And I'm sure she'll come to
finish her fight with me!
She?
You made contact with her?
All right.
I believe in you, Captain.
Captain, ready?
Go ahead.
Earth Engine Ordinary, launch!
I knew she'd come.
Let's fight, Earthling!
An underwater fight?
She's fast!
You were a fool to dive into the sea,
former track athlete!
Captain, there's no time!
I know!
What?
This is the end!
I win.
I lost her.
Yes...
This is it.
This is the real me...
And this is my real speed!
AEO confirmed.
A Kiltgang Type-4!
Manifestation area is within defensive
zone 1, Omicron sector!
Area Impacters are beginning interception!
You let her escape, Daichi...
Call off Teppei's test!
No, I'm going up.
What are you going to do, Teppei?
The Tenkaidou has an Impacter ready to
go that can expand with this machine.
That's a modified development prototype.
And how did you even know about it?
Did Akari tell you?!
Stop!
Since your Aramusha was changed into
that machine, it hasn't flown once!
This isn't the Aramusha anymore.
It is the Nebula Engine Ordinary.
I instructed him on using the basic weaponry.
I just hadn't gotten around to asking permission.
Science Chief!
Teppei can do this!
Let me go, Commander.
If my captain let her escape, I have to do it.
We're a team, so we cover for each other!
Commander!
Daichi, you're listening, right?
You are the captain!
What should we do?
Give me the order, Captain.
Do it, Teppei.
Roger, Captain.
Governor Yomatsuri...
I'm sending up the Nebula.
Are you serious?
Understood.
Mia...
Right!
Initiating expansion sequence.
The Regenbogen is purging the Nebula Engine!
The Nebula Engine's energy is charging!
This light... Orgone energy?
Lieban?
A Livlaster?
Too slow!
You're too slow, Neoteny!
She disappeared?
You're too slow to keep up with me.
This speed...
It's too fast to follow with the eye.
Feel it...
The flow of the Orgone energy.
It's over,
second Neoteny!
There!
This light...
What is it?
The Nebula Engine has successfully
repelled the Kiltgang Type-4.
You were correct.
They'll make a great team.
We did it!
He took it back again...
There was another Neoteny.
What?
But what is that energy the Livlaster emits?
It felt like a wonderful wind...
What are you saying?
Wake up, Marimura-sensei!
Oh, good...
Who were they?
Anyway, let's talk to the police.
Wait.
There's no need for that...
There's no need for that.
Sensei...
Welcome back, Mao-san.
You were waiting for me?
I'm home, Setsuna.
Only two unawakened designer children remain.
We've followed one of them to a
medical equipment manufacturer.
But Hana says her premonition
isn't as clear as usual.
Huh? An enemy Machine Goodfellow
isn't going to activate?
What do you mean?
Next time, on episode 10 of Captain Earth:
Through the Window of Setsuna.
Through the Window of Setsuna
Earth Engine, scramble!