The head may err, but never the blood.
I don't feel like working.
Stop sounding like a broken trumpet
first thing in the morning.
I don't even feel like holding a
conversation right now, Kunikida-kun.
The town was saved from annihilation
thanks to you and Atsushi.
So why have you ended up like this the next day?
The boss has me lined up for this new job...
Is it what Atsushi and the boss
were discussing yesterday?
It is.
Good morning.
Dazai, are we making progress on our
secret meeting with the Port Mafia?
I've made arrangements, but...
Do you think the Port
Mafia boss will be here?
I'm sure.
It's a perfect opportunity
to kill our boss, after all.
That is preferable to having
bloodshed among our members.
Oi, Dazai...
A secret meeting with the Port Mafia?!
Atsushi-kun's idea has
turned into a huge deal.
Even though the Guild is
now our biggest threat...
Wait a second.
I have no idea what's going on.
First of all, why are you the
one arranging the meeting?
Because I'm originally from the Port Mafia.
What?!
Everyone knows about it apart
from you, Kunikida-kun.
What?!
There have been over a hundred deaths
in our organization alone.
I hate to admit it,
but if that tool, Dazai, hadn't
neutralized the curse,
we would have had ten
times as many casualties.
I have no face to show
to the previous bosses.
Kouyou-kun.
Dazai kicked me out of the
Agency office, saying he had
no need for a useless prisoner.
He even had me running errands
in exchange for my stay.
This is from the boss
of the Detective Agency.
An invitation to have tea, it seems.
Oh?
So that's the hand he's chosen to play.
Eight years ago
How are you, Boss?
Doctor, tell the board...
This is an order: Kill
all enemy organizations,
military police, and anyone who
opposes the Port Mafia by sundown.
That's irrational.
I don't mind how many of our own need to die.
Kill them.
Just kill them.
Kill them all.
Kill them.
Very well, Boss.
The boss has succumbed to illness.
He left a will, entrusting me
with his position as the boss.
You're the witness.
Understood?
Welcome, Boss.
It's been four years.
Do you still wear the coat that I gave you?
Of course...
I burned it.
Port Mafia Boss, Mori Ougai.
Armed Detective Agency Chief
Executive, Fukuzawa Yukichi.
So the time's finally come.
If the government brass were to
find out that the leaders of the
two most powerful organizations
of gifted are engaged in a
secret meeting, they
would froth at the mouth.
I'll get straight to business.
A new member of the Agency proposed
an alliance with you, the Port Mafia.
Oh?
I objected.
The idea of cooperating with criminals
goes against the Agency's standards.
But the proposal came from
someone who, countless times,
was shot, slashed, and
kidnapped by the Port Mafia.
His words carry weight.
Therefore, as the leader of the Agency,
I was left with no choice but to lend an ear.
We are both in quite a difficult position.
I'll get to the point.
Alliance aside, I would like to
request a temporary ceasefire.
Have you ever read the works of Schelling?
Or perhaps of Kissinger?
Both are researchers of strategic studies.
Taught by you-know-who.
I do read Sun Tzu.
There is a parallel between state
warfare and the strategies
of illegal organizations such as ourselves.
No one exists to punish either of
us, should we violate agreements.
What if the Port Mafia
suddenly breaks a ceasefire?
What if the Agency betrays us?
The party that trusted in the agreement
would be the only one to suffer.
Under circumstances that reward
the first to commit a betrayal,
a limited ceasefire cannot be established.
The only possibility is
for complete cooperation.
That's also impossible.
Indeed.
The Port Mafia is an organization
of face and resentment.
Many of my people have been
dragged through the mud.
Many of mine have been brought
to the brink of death, as well.
But they didn't die.
And that is a source of great
shame for the Port Mafia.
Then how about this.
We settle our accounts here and now.
I thought you had discarded your katana...
Kokenshi Ginro Fukuzawa.
And you still haven't grown past your habit
of killing people with a scalpel, Doctor Mori.
You still think like a little girl.
Do you still talk to cats?
A hologram ability.
That was an enjoyable meeting.
Let us continue it on the battlefield.
The Agency will be recovering Q tonight.
And?
Don't get in our way tonight.
For the sake of both of us.
Why?
Because that's our sole similarity:
That we love this city.
As people of this city, as organizations
that work to protect it,
we cannot allow foreign gifteds to raze it.
The Guild is powerful.
The Agency stands no chance.
That is all from me.
Dazai-kun, the offer still stands for
you to return to the executive team.
No way.
You're the one who kicked me out of
the Port Mafia in the first place.
Did you not quit because you wanted to?
You were afraid, weren't you?
That I might someday aspire
to take your position
and put a knife to your throat.
Just as you did to your predecessor.
Evil expects evil from others.
I don't agree to allying with you, either.
Our troops?
Deployed as ordered.
Boss, I've been with the Port Mafia longer
than I had during the previous boss's time.
You're quite a senior here.
The organization was in ruins
towards the end of his tenure.
He was ill, and his orders were erratic.
The Port Mafia engaged in conflict aimlessly.
Sooner or later he would
have destroyed this city,
if you hadn't taken his seat.
What is your point?
I just wanted to point out that Dazai-kun
surely understands your intentions.
So this is where Q is being kept.
Good evening.
Our strategist is adept at
reading the enemy's actions.
Of course, it's a trap.
Even if Dazai-kun didn't intend to dethrone me,
my decisions were all rational and optimal.
I have no regrets.
But if Dazai-kun had still
been my right-hand man,
the Guild would have been no match.
Evil expects evil from others.
Hirotsu-san, the communicator
for the frontlines.
I already have it here.
Despite what I said to the Agency,
there is a rational path
towards a proper alliance.
Advance payment is the
essence of an alliance.
One pays a loss up front, and a profit
is made a hundred times greater.
Only then can an alliance make up for old grudges.
Those two once defeated an enemy
gifted organization overnight.
Their alliance was called the most
devastating rivalry in history.
The alliance returns just for one night.
Let me set one thing straight.
Once I'm done taking out
the trash, you're next.
I knew it.
This is why I wasn't
feeling up for it today.
I never heard anything about this surprise
attack in the strategic forecasts.
Sorry, you don't get to do that.
The gift-disabling ability.
This seriously sucks.
That's my line!
Let's take back our lead.
It's our common front against the Guild.
The launch of our retaliation.
Episode 21
Double Black
Dammit.
This is the worst day in years.
Yo, Dazai, ever heard of Pétrus?
The flabbergastingly expensive wine.
The night you vanished
from the organization,
I opened an '89 bottle in celebration.
That's how sick of you I was.
I remember setting a bomb
under your car that night.
That was your doing?!
I can't stand you.
I hate everything about you, too.
The only thing I like about you,
maybe, is your taste in shoes.
You think?
Just kidding, of course.
You...!
Give it up.
I'm familiar with your attacks.
Your timing, your thrusts...
I was going easy on you.
If I were serious, I would
have pulverized your skull.
Oh?
How scary.
There he is.
The sleeping beauty awaiting his savior.
Sleeping beauty, huh?
Hand me your knife.
Oh, wait, I swiped it off
you earlier, just in case.
You...
Aren't you going to stop me?
The boss ordered me to take him back alive,
but seeing that kid's face,
I have flashbacks of the bodybags
my people came home in, thanks to his curse.
Kill him.
I see.
All right, then, I will.
You softy.
Your hypocrisy makes me retch.
As long as Q is alive, you still
need my ability as a safety measure.
The Port Mafia won't be able to kill me.
It's a rational decision.
I don't know about that.
Yo, Dazai, you asshole, hand over that doll!
No way.
It's my insurance.
I'm going to kill him someday.
My shoulder's been stiff for some reason.
Am I working too much?
What was that ability?
I'd expect no less from the Guild!
What amazing resilience!
Get off me!
He's coming, Dazai.
What should we do?
What do you mean?
Bring on any gift, and I'll take care of it
with a touch of my finger.
Dazai!
A heavy fist.
Are you all right?
You're hurt pretty badly.
Those tentacles sure are strange.
I can't disable them.
No way.
Is that even possible?
There are no exceptions
to my disabling ability.
There's only one possibility.
It's not a gift.
I should get my work done and go home early.
Seriously?
That's hilarious, man.
If it's not a gift, then what is it?
All right, let's do things the old way.
How about Operation Shame and Toad?
What is this, Rain Beyond the Window?
It's more like the Lie of the Fake Flowers.
Chuuya.
When have my tactics ever been wrong?
Dammit.
I'm so hungry.
Hey.
Dispatch the enemy and...
go home.
The man in front is a decoy?
Gravity manipulation.
My gift controls the gravity of those I touch.
Take a nap, octopus.
Good job.
Bastard, ordering me around like a sheep dog.
I'm so sleepy.
I feel lazy.
I'd use a sheep dog if I had one.
But I don't, so I had to make do with you.
But I have to fulfill my
contract with Francis.
You...!
Dazai!
Dude, what kind of joke is this?
This is something inhuman.
You... Your arm...
Chuuya, there's something I
want you to hear before I die.
What the hell?
This isn't your place to—
Boo!
I'm going into a fight injured.
Why wouldn't I do this?
Why don't you stop wasting
time on magic tricks
and start thinking about how we're
going to deal with that nightmare?
No way.
Let's just give up and die.
We only have one more course of action.
Don't tell me...
you're going to do something disgraceful.
It's after we wrecked an entire
enemy organization overnight
that we started being called
the devastating rivals.
But if I'm late to support you, you'll die.
I'll let you choose.
You'll let me choose?
Whenever you say that,
I never actually have another choice.
Grantors of dark disgrace,
you need not wake me again.
What the hell is that?
Are you curious, Guild worker ant?
That's the true form of Chuuya's gift.
Chuuya's corrupted form allows him
to manipulate nearby gravitons.
The graviton bomb is a densely-packed
black hole, swallowing everything in its path.
But he has no control over this ability,
so his rage continues until he
consumes all his energy and dies.
But just what is that thing, anyway?
No matter how much he chips away at
it, it just regenerates immediately.
You must know what it truly is,
given that you're his partner.
Who knows?
Why would I tell you, even if I did?
This is bad.
Chuuya's body won't last.
That's a shame.
There's no way to destroy Lovecraft
from outside when he's in that state.
From outside?
So you can get him from inside.
Finish him, Chuuya.
You annihilated the enemy.
Take a break, Chuuya.
I told you to stop me as soon as it was over.
I was going to, but it was
entertaining, so I had to watch.
I used Corruption because I trusted you.
You...
better take me...
to the extraction point.
You got it, buddy.
I can't believe it.
The Lovecraft...
Who are you people?
The bad guys' enemy.
I'm leaving Chuuya
behind, obviously.
-- Dazai
Episode 22
Part 1
Poe and Rampo
Part 2
Moby Dick,
Swimming in
the Sky