Richie. I'm sorry for lyin' to you.
Be good to Ri'ko.
Take care.
What should I do?
I forget what I was like before I met you
The wind caresses my cheek
♪Lullaby of Birdland♪
Kick my heels going down the slope
As my worthless shadow grows
It's like an endless summer vacation
Feels like sneakin' into the swimming pool
Hey, let's swim with our clothes on, jump in!!
A shocking seductive spiral
This beat that pierces my heart is strange
(It flares up, then vanishes)
Every miserable day is swell,
dress it up
A high-speed swing surrounds us
(What's this dance called? I can't stop)
Don't you go, it's twined around my ears
and won't leave me ever again
This melody...
...is like love
Where are you going this
early in the morning?
I thought you were acting odd last night.
Looks like the sneaking
suspicion I had was spot on.
Hey, wait!
Wait, I said!
Let... go of me!
Move!
I'm not moving, you idiot!
If I do, you mean to go
away for good, don't you?!
You're going to run off somewhere!
Are you planning on leaving
everyone and everything behind?!
Sorry. I can't be here anymore.
Since when did you become such a coward?!
Where's the guy that told me "nothing
good comes out of being afraid"?!
What the hell are you guys doing
this early in the morning?!
Richie-rich... Are you okay?!
Bro?
So you two were fighting about the festival?
I understand that you're
really into it, but...
I couldn't sleep last night...
The truth is I was scared, too...
Is something wrong?
Let me stay like this... just for a minute...
Ritsuko! Did you bring in today's paper?!
Yeah! I left it by the phone.
Oh, I see it!
I'm home.
It's Dad!
Welcome home, Dad!
Welcome home!
Did you bring us anything?!
Dad, your hair's turned gray!
Has it? I suppose it has...
Did you bring presents?!
Yes, I bought you stuff.
Yay!
Let's have 'em!
Hey, at least let him set
foot in the house first...
Welcome Home, Dad
Everyone, I'm sorry for
being away all this time.
You look cute!
Look, Bro!
That's great, Taichi.
And this...
...is for you, Sentaro.
Um... I don't know if you'll
like it or not, though...
It's a fountain pen!
You're lucky, Bro!
Wow...
Something expensive like
this is wasted on me...
A child doesn't go turning down
a present from his parent.
Oh, looks like everyone got a present.
Sachiko, pass these out.
Okay!
A child... His parent...
Are you coming to practice today?
Yeah. Startin' today, I'm gonna
practice my ass off for the festival.
You mean it?!
I mean it!
What the hell? That was a weird
way to greet to each other.
Mukae
Me, at the festival?
Yes, I was hoping that you
would play bass for us.
You're asking me out of the blue...
Adults have a lot of things
on their plate, you know.
And there'd be so much to prepare...
You can't do it?
You're totally prepared!
Ain't no way we can lose now!
Hey, hey!
How's it goin' for you guys?
Oh...
Right now, we're in the middle
of getting our costumes fitted.
There's no way we're going to
lose against you guys this year.
It's so flamboyant...
We, on the other hand...
...are plain. Way too plain...
We don't have any razzmatazz.
At this rate, we might not
be able to beat them...
That stuff doesn't matter.
All we gotta do is put our music
face-to-face against theirs.
I know! I know that...
...but this is our last school festival.
I just don't want to have any regrets...
Easy to say...
But appealing to people who have no
interest in jazz is a tall order.
W-What are you saying?!
I can't sing!
Don't worry. There are still ten
days left. We'll work it out.
Ri'ko, if you're gonna
refuse, now's the time.
'Cause if you decide to do it,
we're not gonna go easy on you.
You don't wanna sing, tell
us to shove off right now.
Though I hope you don't turn us down...
I agree with Sen.
Would you help us out?
Alright. I'll give it a try.
Raindrops on roses and whiskers on kittens...
Kit-tens...
No, you've got no swing!
Raindrops on roses and whiskers on kittens
Bright copper kettles and warm woolen mittens
Brown paper packages tied up with strings
These are a few of my favorite things
Cream colored ponies and crisp apple strudels
Doorbells and sleigh bells
and schnitzel with noodles
Wild geese that fly with
the moon on their wings
These are a few of my favorite things
Girls in white dresses with blue satin sashes
Snowflakes that stay on my nose and eyelashes
Silver white winters that melt into springs
These are a few of my favorite things
I simply remember my favorite things
And then I don't feel so bad
"My Favorite Things"...
My own favorite things are...
The footsteps of a certain person
heading towards the house...
The sound of the piano and drums
riffing in the basement...
The laughter of two boys...
Silly, I know...
Drums and watermelon and onigiri...
Those are a few of my favorite things...
What the heck is that, Sentaro?
Go on, Richie. Your turn!
Tell us your "favorite things".
I don't have any!
Even before Ri-chan said hers,
I had something in mind.
My "favorite thing" is
this time... right now.
Tomorrow's the day...
All that's left is playing
our best at the festival.
Richie... How about playin'
"Moanin'" one more time?
Hmm... Nah, let's save it for tomorrow.
If we started jamming now, we wouldn't stop.
I see. Yeah, you're right.
Well, see you tomorrow then. Don't be late.
Yeah!
He forget to take this...
Ah, well, you don't need a score for jazz.
An' I can just give it to him tomorrow.
Oh. Where are you going?
I'm gonna run to deliver
something he left behind.
Kaoru-san left a while ago.
You might not be able to catch up.
I know, I know.
19th School Festival
Sen's late...
Hey, hey!
It's almost time for our battle.
Huh? Where's your partner?
Don't tell me he's late?
No, uh...
Seiji, come on!
Okay! Well, see you later!
Ri-chan...
Sentaro...
He got into an accident on
a motorbike last night...
...and was taken to the hospital.
S-So... how is he?
I don't know! What should I do?!
Kaoru-san...
Sentaro is... Sentaro is...
Ri-chan, calm down! I'll go to
the hospital to see how he is.
Stay here until I get back.
Dammit!
I've dashed down this slope countless
times, but it's never felt this long...
City Hospital
Um, excuse me!
I'm looking for...
I'll help you when it's your
turn, so please get in line.
Wait!
U-Um...
I heard there was an accident...
They've finished operating...
but it's serious head trauma...
Still hasn't regained consciousness...
No Visitors
Might never wake up again...
the doctor said...
Don't talk like that!
But...
That's right! Even when Sen is all bloody
from a fight, he just laughs it off!
Um... Sachiko is the one who's in there.
I don't know why... but Sis was riding on
the back of Bro's motorbike last night...
They got hit by a car...
Then how is he?
He's hurt, but not too bad.
He was sitting over here just before...
I see. Thanks!
That's right! The place he's
most likely to go is...
Gotta be...
I've seen this angel before somewhere...
If you're gonna take somebody to Heaven,
could you make it me an' not Sachiko, angel?
Why do I end up hurting the
ones I most want to protect?
Why... was I even born?
Richie? What's wrong?
Hey... What are you cryin' for?
This way, we don't have
to see each other cry.
What do you mean "we"? I ain't...
It's okay to cry, Sen.
You've been keeping it
bottled up all this time...
Sa-chan!
Thank goodness...
Huh? Sen...?
At the time, it looked like
he was just stepping out...
...but he disappeared, and the festival
was over before it even began.
And then...
Richie...
Kaoru-san...
Um, here. If you're able to eat these...
Do you know where my big bro, Sen went?
He would normally never
give me a ride on his bike.
But I had a twisted ankle and
kept complaining about it to him.
The accident was my fault...
I have to apologize to him...
Sa-chan, right now, if you focus on getting
better, Sentaro will come back soon!
You want to show him that
you're healthy again, right?
Yeah.
I said all that to Sa-chan,
but the truth is...
Kaoru-san, what'll I do if
Sentaro never comes back?
Ri-chan...
We're talking about him.
I bet when we least expect
it, he'll suddenly turn up.
Don't you have that feeling?
Yeah. You're right. He
will come back, won't he?
Sure.
Kaoru-san... Don't go anywhere, okay?
Um...
Excuse me...
Oh. I remember you. Richie-kun, right?
Do I know where he might be?
No, I'm afraid I don't.
Um... Father, he left this behind...
He once told me the reason he always wore
the rosary as a necklace was because
he was afraid that if he lost it, he
would be abandoned by the world...
Se...!
I thought maybe Sen had come back.
Pops... He's not coming back.
I'll never be able to
practice with him again.
W-What are you talkin' about, Richie?
Never again...
I waited for you on that slope
For our after school promise
There was a 'goodbye' blurred far away
I was so weak, so awkward, and so fragile back then
But you gave me a small pair of wings
In the twilight hour of the sky,
I'm searching for a gleam of light
If only I could have said that I love you…
The note that I wrote in the corner of my textbook
has never been delivered to this day