I hadn't realized...
that humans could die so easily.
But as long as I have a vessel,
you can be with me again.
You can smile at me again.
July 24th
Shinjuku Ward Kagurazaka
There's a nasty demon that
goes around collecting women.
That's what Huehuecóyotl said, right?
Yes.
An Another shrouded in black sand.
#7 "Sense of Loss and Proof of Despair"
That's probably who took Arata's childhood
friend and the girls in Toyama Park,
as well as Kyoichi's sister.
And you tried to use Arata
to get information on it?
Yeah.
Even if that meant negotiating with
Huehuecóyotl and the Another.
Theo-san, he said he didn't mean negotiating!
That's an obvious lie!
The fact that he got you involved proves
he was willing to do whatever it took.
If it meant giving up an arm or
whatever, I would have given it.
Wha—
You didn't tell me because
you knew I'd try to stop this.
I've been searching for her for 17 years,
and now I finally have a clue.
I couldn't let it go, no matter the cost.
Then...!
Then you should've gotten me
involved from the start.
I would've helped in another way,
without manipulating Arata,
you damn moron!
I feel the same... It makes me sick,
hearing the truth like this.
That said, please don't apologize.
If you do, since you've done so much for me,
I know I'll forgive you.
So instead, you owe me one.
Got it.
Storage #1
July 24th
Nocturnal Community Relations Division
Now then, let's find the entrance to Hell.
We're starting with zero clues, though.
What are you talking about?
You've already got clues, right?
Unsolved Missing Teenage Girl Cases in Tokyo
These are all the cases involving
missing teenage girls up until now.
And to narrow it down...
What do we do?
That sand affects the gravity
of the space around it.
So if we put in data on gravity fluctuations,
we'll understand the range
in which it operates.
When did you get that data?
Just recently.
I was curious about the black sand, too.
I've been spending a ton of time on it.
Theo...
Okay, there we go.
So, this is the path traveled
by the black sand Another?
There's one part where
it's concentrated, right?
Yeah.
That's probably where its hideout is.
But there're so many...
Start deleting the oldest incidents.
Roger.
Um, we're looking for a demon, right?
Is there anything demons don't like?
Don't like?
Like how cats don't like baths.
My cat is still like that, even
though it's an Another.
Something to use against it, huh?
If it's really a demon, we can
remove areas near churches.
And areas with lots of angels.
Let's try it.
Add in this data and that...
And how about this?
First, areas around churches.
Second, areas where angels live.
We narrowed it down to four spots!
Can you magnify this?
Sure.
Higashi Inada Girls High
A girls high school?
No way...
Is this...
All these areas are near
all-girls high schools!
But when you think about it,
they're the perfect spots, right?
Yeah, it's the perfect place to find prey.
Sakaki-san, Kohaku said it would be
over tomorrow morning.
Then there's no time. Let's visit them all.
If there are only four, we can make it.
Okay, let's go!
Right!
July 24th
Higashi Inada Girls High
Shinjuku Acet Girls Academy
July 25th
Shinjuku Aizenin Girls High
Shinjuku Shurin Girls High
This is the area with the highest
gravitational numbers, huh?
Dawn will be here in an hour and a half.
Let's split up to find the entrance.
Got any Ibn Ghazi spray?
Roger.
What's wrong, Miyako?
That's not going to work.
Even if you use that to find
the entrance, you can't go in.
And I told you to stay out of this
if you don't want to die.
Or do you want to die after all?
I'm amazed you found this place, either way.
Kohaku, take us to Izumi!
If I do, you'll die.
You don't know that!
Don't just say that!
I never even thought about that...
Where does that self-confidence come from?
Don't make fun of me!
I'm not. I'm actually interested now.
It would be interesting to see you
escape from that obnoxious guard dog.
Then...
I'll take you there.
Make your escape and entertain me.
Time to go to Hell.
What is this place?
It's all doors.
Is this Hell?
Hell is up ahead.
Every one of these is connected
to a different place in the world.
Of course, one leads to Hell.
Come on, let's hurry.
Hey, Kohaku.
What, are you tired?
No.
We've walked a long time. Are we there yet?
Almost there.
Azazel is just up ahead.
Azazel? Is that the demon's name?
Azazel?!
You know him?
He's one of the biggest names there is!
He was originally an angel who broke a taboo
by falling in love with a human
girl, and then became a devil.
That's right.
He swore eternal love to her,
but she died, and now he's
trying to bring her back.
He's been trying for years.
Where am I?
Is there someone here?
Be quiet.
My left hand won't move...
It's done...
All her limbs are ready.
Now...
Don't worry. It won't fail this time.
Don't worry. Don't worry. Don't worry.
So the one girl's leg and
the other's voice were...
Yes. They're like the parts
needed to bring her back.
But they keep getting rejected,
so it doesn't work...
And that's why he...
So that's why he's been going around
kidnapping girls all this time?
But he didn't care about
the girls who didn't work,
or the ones he'd already taken parts from,
so he just gave them to Kohaku.
So that's what was up with
the girls in Toyama Park?
Huh? Flowers?
Flowers? Flowers in a place like this?
Is that... wolfsbane?
Wait a second! Is the "guard dog" Cerberus?
No way!
What's wrong, Theo?
Wolfbane blooms from Cerberus's drool!
If there's so much here,
that means Cerberus is around!
What will you do?
Go home before you're found?
Or keep going?
This smell... It's been so
long since I've had meat.
Where is it? Meat! Meat!
Where is the meat?
And then there's the usual smell
of Coyote and sweet candy!
Is that Cerberus?
That's right. Have fun running!
Kohaku, you...
Is that you, Coyote?
It's coming!
Found it!
This is his favorite. Sweets.
We can use it to distract him!
Run!
That actually worked!
But...
You'll need more than that!
We won't last a second
if that thing catches up!
I know that!
Now it's all here.
The arms, the legs,
the hair, the body... all of it.
I have all the parts.
She'll be as she was. As she was.
Hey!
All that's left are the eyes.
The eyes are hers.
I'm taking them back.
Amazing! All three of you are still alive!
Kohaku!
Sakaki-san, over there!
The exit!
Theo!
Did that work?
No!
Theo-san!
I'll eat you all!
Miyako!
You can't have him.
He's mine.
Go.
You win again, huh?
I'm saved...
Sheesh...
I told you it would kill you.
Next time, do as I say.
Kohaku.
What?
I never thought the day would
come when I'd thank you.
But thank you.
I don't care about the other two,
but I can't have you dying.
You okay?
Sorry for screwing up at the last moment, guys.
Come on, let's hurry.
Yeah.
Izumi!
Izumi! Are you okay?
She's fine. Just unconscious.
She's in no danger.
Good...
Nee-san!
You bastard!
Don't interfere.
I can't move.
Stay put, and I will release you.
I promise.
Miyako.
He's saying not to interfere.
I missed you...
Again... You woke me up again!
This body isn't mine!
It feels disgusting! It feels disgusting!
She's extremely upset.
She says the body isn't right.
Are those sounds words?
Then is she an Another?
Look at the way he tried to bring her back.
Of course she'd stop being human.
What's wrong?
Look. It's me, Azazel.
You can smile at me like you did
the first time we met, right?
You keep putting me inside these
things over and over and over again!
It's disgusting! Disgusting!
Disgusting!
Let me sleep!
Release me!
Who are you?
I failed! Failed! Failed! Failed! Failed!
I have to do it again!
What went wrong this time?
This is wonderful!
He's always so unemotional,
and now his face is filled
with wonderful despair!
Why? Why?
As promised.
We can move again.
Nee-san!
Begone. There is nothing for you here now.
You piece of shit!
Wait!
Our goal is to get everyone out of here.
Not to defeat that devil!
Did you forget that?!
You've already gotten Arata involved in this.
Fine.
July 25th
Onee-chan...
Whose voice is that?
I can't see right now...
Is that you, Kyo-chan?
How did you know?
You just called me "Onee-chan," right?
That's what you always used to call me...
But your voice sounds like Dad's...
It is you, Kyo-chan!
Did I worry you? Were you lonely?
I'm sorry.
I wish I could see your face...
This is...
You've grown up so much, Kyo-chan!
And you look so handsome now!
Onee-chan...
I'm your big sister, but now
I'm younger than you.
You're safe...
And that's all that matters!
Well, this matters to me!
I can move my hand, too.
I'm so glad...
I don't get what's going on here.
Explain it to me, Arata.
Okay.
That must've hurt.
Just look at him.
Not yet...
That's right. It's not over yet.
Next time... Next time... Next time...
At this rate, he'll go forever.
It's fine.
As long as he repeats it forever,
and despairs forever...
That despair proves my conclusion
that a happy marriage to
a human girl is impossible.
Don't you agree, Azazel?
I found you.
#8 "Old Coyote and the Garden of Falling Stars"