Hats and Underwear go on your Head!?
AM 2:00 - Night Before the Sports Meet
Entrance
Exit
What're you doing out here?
Out for a late night stroll, huh?
Well, you can tell me all about
why you're skulking
around a middle school down at the station!
N-No, I'm just watching over my daughter!
Daddy! Daddy!
Daddy?
Daddy.
He's really my dad!
I'm really her dad.
She doesn't look anything like
him...I don't believe it.
Always judging me on how I look...
How long have you been here, daddy?
Futaba! You can't go out on
your own this late at night!
I-I'm sorry...but tomorrow's
the sports meet,
I was so excited I couldn't sit still!
You come in too, daddy!
I wanted to do a final rehearsal.
R-Rehearsal?
Will you help?
Yeah, I guess...sheesh.
Entrance
We're starting with the opening ceremony?
Lead the pledge!
Huh? Me?
Yeah!
A-As athletes we pledge
to be good sportsmen
and to compete fairly and honestly!
The principal's speech!
I have to do that too?
Err...uhh...May today be a lucky day...
And uh...do your best everyone.
Yes sir!
You're in the obstacle course, the tug-o-war,
the piggyback battle...
And the relay too?
Yup! The obstacle course is first.
Let's go! Whoo!
Whoo-
Is this supposed to be a balance beam?
I gotta hold the tape too?
Goal!
First place!
Good job, you were fantastic.
Now the tug-o-war!
Oh? Where's the rope?
Me?!
A crushing victory!
Good...job...
Pat me!
Way...to go...
I'm the horsey.
Aren't I too heavy?
Not really.
And I'm the anchor for the relay race!
Wow...
Okay...bang!
First runner
Second runner
Third runner
Fourth runner
Oh no, I've gotta hold up the tape!
She's so fast!
I'm her father...her father...
I won't let my daughter beat me!
O-Oh crap!
You okay? Futaba?
First place...blew everyone away...
First place...first place...
She's still a little girl.
What're you doing?!
Leave me the hell alone.
The day of the sports meet
Girl's piggyback battle
The piggyback battle...what a stupid event.
Let's grab everyone else's hats!
No...we should keep observing and
wait for the crowd to thin out...
I want hats now!
I wanna get in a chicken fight!
Don't move without warning me!
The ground's so...the ground's so far down!
This is bad luck...
Bad, bad luck...
We're the unlucky ones.
Come over here, enemies! Face
me fairly and honestly!
Why won't anyone come?
Don't run away!
Positioning self in enemy blind spot...
They're staying away 'cuz they
think they'll be cursed.
I feel like someone's calling me...
Enemy hats! I want enemy hats!
I want 'em all!
You're the noisiest horsey ever.
We're not even trying to help, either.
See?
Owie owie, lemme go!
Sorry! I was aiming for your hat!
Look at Micchan, she's having a ball.
She's not even going for the hats,
she's just trying to inflict pain!
Mitsuba's inhumanly cruel to
allies and enemies alike.
Who said that?
Micchan, please stop treating my
eyebrows like a steering wheel!
Sugisaki-san and Miyawhatever-san said
you're a disgusting cow, Micchan.
Wha-
MiyaSHITA, I'm MiyaSHITA.
And I never said a word about her!
Look.
Look at all the hats I've got!
I'm leading our team to certain victory.
Aww, you guys don't even
have a single one?
Bow to me in gratitude for winning!
And you were so worked up, too. Guess
you just have bad luck, Futaba!
Stuck with our lazy sister Hitoha
and two lame horses!
Curse you, Mitsuba...
Futaba-chan?
Hats...enemy hats...I want...
I want enemy hats, lots and lots
and lots!
What's wrong with you!
We're on the same team! See?
C-C-Calm down...
She can only see the hats now...
The sports meet is like an aphrodisiac
to her, making her mad with desire.
Stop your stupid rambling and
get her under control!
Come on.
No- Stop moving...
There you go, Futaba. Get her!
Mitsuba's pissed me off!
Get away from me, this is pointless!
So high...gonna fall, gonna die...
I'm dying...I'm dead, my life is ending-
Charge, Futaba!
Freakin' hyenas!
S-So scary!
I was so scared!
No, I came to watch my daughters!
That's what they all say.
I just want to see them trying their best!
You're trapped Mitsuba, hand over the caps!
The caps...they're gone!
You thought I'd let you losers
steal my glory? As if!
You don't have boobs, Micchan.
S-Shut up! And get off me!
Why does this always happen to me?!
Because you're dirty and dishonorable.
You're one to talk!
Look, the hats are the only
way to stop Futaba.
Even a couple would do
it...I'd give them up.
Why? I got them fair and square.
Does that really matter now?
Okay, okay!
Just a couple!
That's all of them, you cheater!
So it is.
Youngest got 'em?
All of them?!
See, all you had to do was try!
I'm impressed.
Whoa-wait-stop, stop!
My fantastic achievements...
Stop, Futaba.
Spit them back up this instant!
Yabe-sensei collapsed with
a fever during class.
Study Hall
Yabecchi's lessons are boring anyway, I don't
mind having study hall every now and then.
Yesterday's idol sports meet ruled.
I doubt it's anything big, but everyone gets
noisy during study hall, so I'm out.
Nurse
I want him cured.
Wh-What're you-
Oh, Youngest-san.
I'm still writing sutras on Yabecchi's body.
With the way he collapsed so suddenly,
there's no doubt in my mind he's in the
clutches of some malicious spirit!
There's been a lot of weird stuff going
down in the room, you know?
Things keep getting destroyed,
healthy people being injured...
It's cursed, I know it!
I'm sorry...I'm her sister...
It's not your fault, Youngest-san.
Maybe you tend to draw spirits
to you as a result of your work,
but anyways, what's your opinion as
a beautiful genius prodigy exorcist?
Wiped
I think he's wiped out.
His soul's been swiped out, eh?
Swiped
Oh no!
Get ready to exorcise!
Gotta finish this first...
What kind of ceremony is she prepping?
Matsuoka-san!
How are we supposed to exorcise the demon
without covering his WHOLE body in sutras?
Off these go...
There! Now for the back.
Youngest-san, help me flip him over.
I'm going back to class.
Wha-but what about the exorcism?
Yabecchi will die if we don't do anything!
Nice assist, Youngest-san!
He really COULD die if he falls on his head.
Another ploy by the demon ghost!
Don't blame your screw-ups on ghosts.
What a high fever...he must be sick.
...Why did you use water-based ink?!
It needs to be washable, right?
I've learned from my previous mistakes!
Someone's coming.
L-Lock the door!
Right, we can't let anyone interfere!
It's locked...
Wh-Where are his underwear?
You need Yabecchi's boxers?
Hold on a second.
Hitoha-chan?
Have you been here the whole time?
Sorry to worry you...I'm okay now.
You really need more sleep.
Please go back to bed.
Hitoha-chan...
She's being awfully considerate for once...
Youngest-san, here's the boxers!
Boxers!
Okay, you've got Yabecchi's underwear,
just like you wanted!
Thinks they're for the exorcism
Do it!
Exorcise to ghost
Why did you strip me naked?!
What're you trying to do?!
And why do you want my boxers?!
Yabecchi's got his energy back!
Nice work, Youngest-san!
Hitoha-chan! Take my underwear
off this instant!
Yabe-sensei's being a sicko again!
Mitsudomoe...
Look at my new Pianissimo pencil case.
My mom got it for me.
How cute!
It's a limited edition, you can't
get them anywhere anymore.
Ooooh...
And what exactly is up with
YOUR case, Mitsuba?
It's made of gym clothes!
Hey-
Pretty lame.
Don't you think?
I, umm...
Oh, that's the pencil case
I made from my dogi.
You're still using it!
Oh yeah.
You made three, didn't you Futaba-chan?
Give that back!
It's no big deal!
I ruined mine a while ago.
I threw mine out.
Argh!
Good for you, Eldest!
You're okay in my book.
Yeah, I'd be grateful too.
You can be surprisingly sweet.
I'll throw it out right now!
Now, now...
I lost...
At what?
Bah, just because something's expensive
doesn't make it better!
Damn you Mitsuba! You're just a filthy
peasant but you drive me nuts!
All right then...
I'll tail you
find your weak point
and embarrass you
in front of everyone!
It's a text from my mom.
Wow, that's the latest model
phone isn't it Sugi-chan?
Sure is!
It's even got video and audio
streaming through 1-Seg!
And it's got like a 20 megapixel
camera, too.
Of course, a peasant like Mitsuba-san
wouldn't care about that, I'm sure.
If I'm not supposed to care then
don't wave it in my face.
Lemme see!
Hey, you've got lots of pictures
of Micchan on here.
Huh?
What's this all about?
I was...looking for your weak-
Sugi-chan must really like you Micchan!
S-Sugi-chan...
N-No! Get real!
Mitsuba can drop dead for all I care! Die!
At this rate I'M gonna end
up being humiliated!
There must be something...
This'll do.
So then I says-
Move it.
Shoo, shoo!
Stupid boys...
Still keeping up the holier-than-thou act?
Miss baby bear panties!
H-How'd you kn-
Aww, they're so cute!
Why don't you go back to kindergarten?
What do you all think of this shocking truth?
I win. Mitsuba's position in class
will drop to the bottom!
I'm finished. All the power and respect
I've worked so hard for, gone!
That's so old.
We all know.
It's common knowledge.
Wh-Why? How can I be so far behind...
B-But it's still lame!
I wear cute, sexy adult panties!
I win!
Cute and sexy...
Well, that's news to me.
But you know what they
say, seeing is believing.
O-Oh no!
You're obviously lying.
It's true!
I was winning, I was winning!
But I can't prove it...damn it!
Hey everyone, Sugisaki says she's gonna
show us all her fantastic underwear!
Hey-
Well well well...
Let's see what you've got.
Fine! But I'll only show Mitsuba!
I'll only show my panties to Mitsuba!
Who wants to look at your
big butt granny panties?
Please...look at them...
Look at what?
My panties...
WHY do you want me to see them?
Look...
Say it so everyone can hear you.
Please look at my panties!
You pervert!
Why're they making US do
the preview, Sugisaki?
We don't really interact much, huh?
I noticed you're both into panties!
Shout out your shared love for panties
for all the world to hear!
Episode 7
I Can't Help Being in Love!
It's not like that!