That's my swing, loser.
What did you do to him?
What's it to you?!
Sis...
Maybe we could've moved the
audience more if we'd had the whole choir...
Sis, about the choir club!
Perv!
I'm quitting.
What?
The recital's over.
Are you kidding me?
We're just getting started.
Go right ahead and tell mom about my books.
I don't even have them anymore.
Oh, and my friends are all quitting, too.
You've got to get real
members, on your own.
Want me to tell
you how I found out
where you stash your dirty books?
I asked mom.
Episode 3
Swinging and Meeting
Let me have a look at that for you.
Thank you very much.
No problem.
Do my eyes deceive me?
Could this be... Yes!
Yes, your eyes and
hair match!
I can't understand...
You are so cute!
My lovely princess!
I am no money! Thank you!
Wait!
Miyamoto!
We're quitting the choir club.
Why?
We got to see Kumagai Tetsuji.
Right!
Here's the sheet music we borrowed.
Thank you!
Club Dissolution Notice
Choir Club
Due to the reasons listed below, club
activities are hereby terminated.
-Less than 5 members
Principal
I can't allow your clubs to continue
without the minimum five members.
Huh?
In short, your clubs have been dissolved.
But I have the prefectural
competition coming up soon.
All other clubs have found adequate members,
are staying within their limited budgets,
and are complying with school regulations.
But that's...
Why does your group
deserve special treatment?
It doesn't, but the principal didn't...
The school regulations are written
in your student handbook.
While the principal remains hospitalized,
I am standing in for him as the
administrator of this school.
Go wave your racket around in some park,
if you want to play
badminton by yourself.
She actually said that?
Not with words, but it's what she meant.
Sure sounds like her!
This is hopeless. Nothing will work.
I can't enter the competition...
What are you going to do?
I figured out that I can't have fake members,
so I'll just have to find real ones.
We've still got three people.
One, two...
Three.
We'll still have opportunities to
sing at the cultural
festival or at graduation.
Hey, Tanaka.
Why don't you quit badminton
and join the choir club?
What?
I mean, if you can't compete
in the prefecturals,
your club's toast, right?
Don't say that!
I haven't given up on the competition!
Besides!
I'm badminton's...
Huh?
Shut up, short stuff.
What's with the name-calling?
He's got a point.
Excuse me?
Go on. Get it.
All right.
That's it, come here.
Wien!
Whatcha doing?
I see you've got squirrels
in Japan as well.
Huh?
So, anyway.
Wanna play badminton?
This is the first time I've been recruited!
Yeah, people don't usually go after seniors.
Will I play in the competition too?
Oh, uh, I'm not sure.
I hope your application gets in on time.
And besides, I still need three more people...
We can do it! Slam!
Have you ever played badminton before?
Nope.
My grandpa had a badminton team at his work,
and he took me to see a few games.
I was really young, though,
so I don't remember much.
Shoot, I forgot to lock up my bike.
Go on in. My room's in the back.
Sure.
Hey. I'm borrowing the A/C.
Bouncy, bouncy, bunny hop!
The hell...
Sorry. I didn't think my
sister would be around.
No problem.
Sorry about before.
Tai-kun is so wrapped up in badminton,
he never brings friends over.
No, I am the one who is
truly reprehensible.
Huh? Tai-kun?
Get out of here!
I'm going, I'm going.
Hello.
Ah, Sawa-chan.
Could I work at your beach house
again this summer, Nagaoka-san?
Of course! You know we're
more than happy to have you.
But will you still have time to study?
Plenty. I have it all worked out.
That's great.
Then, I look forward to summer.
Me,too.
We're starting the strategy meeting for our summer
project: "Ignite the Western Shopping District"!
See you.
Let's go, Sabure.
Planning something like a cabaret...
Kids these days...
Yeah, and in summer,
customers are drawn to the ocean.
Actually, the beach house will have it rough, too.
We need to attract men and women of all ages.
Western Shopping District Event Planning
Let's make this summer a hot one!
Swimsuit Contest - Fireworks Contest
What about a swimsuit competition?
Not again.
That brings us right back
to where we started.
The beach is crowded enough.
What about music?
Music?
It goes beyond male or
female, land or sea.
Cosplay Contest
And since it's summer,
performances could be held outside.
We could call it the
"World Music Festival,"
and turn the town into an international village!
So if I win, you'll both
join the badminton club?
You got it. But if we win,
you have to join our choir club.
Deal.
Can Tanaka even sing?
I thought you said you needed real members.
Remember Ms. Takahashi's
farewell party?
Oh, that's right, he did sing then.
I think he'd be useful,
if he put his mind to it.
Yeah, but do you think he would?
Sure! He seems easy to manipulate.
I'm pretty sure Tanaka
went to nationals last year.
Are you sure you can win?
Totally. It'll be three against one.
Three against... I'm three?
I just need you for ten minutes at lunch!
Please?
Do you hate sports?
I don't hate them... But Okita-san...
You can call me Sawa.
If you really don't want to,
the two of us will go,
though you can always change your mind.
You came!
Thanks!
Three people?
What were you expecting?
There's three people in the choir club.
Taichi, you're so mean.
You need to tell me our practice schedule.
He's in the badminton club?
Just tell me where to go!
Okay...
We have two people, since there
are two people in the badminton club.
Just pretend you're playing for fun.
If we do this, I want to win.
Let's get started!
We don't want to run into each other,
so a rule of thumb is
to stay in your area.
Got it.
We'll serve first.
Best two out of three wins.
Hey! All of you are serving at once?
Of course!
You scared?
Bring it on!
And, one!
Sawa!
Wien!
I've got this one!
Wow! You see that, Taichi?
It's stuck!
Nice, Wakana!
Nice, Sakai-san!
Wa-Wakana?
You were great, Sawa!
Sawa?
Archery does keep me fit.
You were pretty close,
yourself, Miyamoto-san.
Yeah...
I'm sorry, Taichi.
Don't worry about it.
I would've still lost, even without you.
Are you crying?
Shut up!
Is your goal to be a professional singer?
I haven't really thought that far ahead.
What about you?
I've been thinking I want
to continue badminton
in college, and then go pro, if I can.
Then aim for the world championships...
Why are you blushing?
It's weird to see him all timid.
Shut up! Lay off me, guys!
You'll go to the competition.
New Club Application
Club Name: Choir and Sometimes Batminton Club
Name: Miyamoto Konatsu
Club Activities: Singing,
dancing, occasionally batminton.
But you'll need to put just
as much effort into the choir part.
Miyamoto...
Hold up! You planned this all along, didn't you?
Obviously!
But if we'd lost, it would've been the
"Batminton and Sometimes Choir Club."
You're in the choir group, too, now.
Um, I'm confused...
In Japan, it's important to participate in both
cultural and athletic clubs,
to cultivate cultural and martial excellence.
Konatsu!
Cultural and martial excellence?
What does that mean?
By the way, it's "badminton",
not "batminton."
What am I going to do?
I'm sorry.
When I asked the principal if
he would be our advisor again,
he told me to get everyone.
It's fine.
I don't have any more supplementary
lessons until summer vacation.
Those must be a pain.
You make it sound like you're not affected.
The Choir and Sometimes Batminton Club...
It's badminton.
Either way.
Just don't embarrass me too much.
Thank you very much!
You know, our choir club used to be quite
famous for having won
a national choir competition.
The choir club?
Not the music club?
That's right.
You must be Sakai-san.
Yes.
You do resemble her.
Your mother was one of my students.
She never told you about that?
No...
Meeting her changed the very
meaning of music for me.
Back then, you could have
described me as morendo...
Come in.
Sir, there are some documents
here I need you to review.
This many?
Ms. Vice Principal, I'd like
you to approve a new club.
Did you actually think this
thing would get approved?
Why wouldn't it?
You caused enough trouble at the last recital.
I will not stand to see
you make a mockery of music.
I can't let you do that.
You will pick that up and throw it away.
I guess I forgot to put my seal on it.
Where did that darned thing go?
Why did you become their advisor again?
I might ask why you're so against it.
I'm not...
When I think back on those times,
my blood really gets pumping.
Isn't it the same for you?
Or is the choir club already—
Sir.
Can you please look
over those documents?
Not bad, napping in the
beach house on the
first day of summer break.
I'm thinking.
If we only have a regular daily practice,
it's hard to keep the members on their toes.
Oh yeah, practice starts at four today.
Hey, what are they building out front?
Oh, that? It's a stage for live music.
For that, there.
Participate in our popularity
contest and win shopping coupons!
The beach house and the
other businesses are
going to each pick a country and build
a small stage based on that theme.
Their singers will perform there.
Ah, Shiho-san!
Large green tea snow cone, please.
Comin' right up!
Customers will vote on their favorites,
and the winner will perform live on the
main stage at the end of the event.
Voters can even
win shopping coupons.
How can you participate in that?
Each business is responsible
for finding their own singers.
One large green tea snow cone.
Would you let us sing for you?
Um, well, we have a prime location here,
so we were hoping to get someone
who could really steal the show.
Then why don't you let us audition?
We might fit the bill!
Please consider it!
Summer Supplementary Class Schedule
Mon|Tues|Wed|Thurs|Fri
Eng.|Contemp. Lit.|World History|Jap. History|Politics & Econ
Eng.|Classic Lit.|Eng. Classic Lit.|Contemp. Lit.
Everyone must be at the beach house.
Aren't you going?
No, I'm not.
Okay then, see you later.
Stop! I need to talk to you!
I won't let you get away today.
I don't money!
I thought it was at four.
It is four.
The competition's coming up...
I don't want to waste
time doing anything else.
Say that again?!
Fine, let's get this over with.
What'll we sing?
The same as the recital?
I don't know that song.
Then, the school song?
Perfect!
One, two!
I want to hear the voice
of the white beach,
so let's climb that winding slope.
Thank you!
The friendships we forge during
these brilliant days and moments,
Sorry for the ruckus.
Oh, not at all.
create a harmony that stretches across eternity.
Allegro.
Vivace.
Amorosso.
Let's sing! Let's sing!
Let's sing, Shirahamazaka High!
You're so cool, Mister!
I can't sing all by myself...
Stalker! Stalker!
Is that falsetto?
Why isn't Miyamoto coming?
Episode 4
Getting Angry and Dancing
I'm quitting the choir club! You jerk!