Do you mean "Eleven" is just a friends club?
Something like that.
Oh, you must be kidding.
Huh...
You better drop the attitude!
You called me out, and this is what I get?
I'll kill you.
Hold it. Sorry, it was my fault.
Believe me. I am on your side.
Does someone on your side strangle you on first sight?
Well, that's just how I am.
It's no laughing matter.
Sorry,
but when people talk down to me,
and I lose track of myself, and...
And?
I become someone else and start being extremely destructive.
It was my fault, too.
Sorry.
I'm Xiaogang. Community Head of 17th Autonomous Section.
Community Head, huh?
A negotiator of sorts.
Negotiator? Against the machines?
Yeah.
Your abilities are your speed and your Wizard Gun, huh?
And yours?
I can't show you.
What's this?
A jamming device. I made it.
It disrupts the machines' tracking.
Do you think we can win against the machines?
Probably not.
We "Eleven" are monsters, even though we look like humans.
It's hilarious that we monsters are humanity's last hope.
We all ought to disappear, including me.
Here they come.
Do you have a problem with me, machines?
Skull Machine Gun!
Wipe that smug look off your face, you machines!
Goodbye.
The next me,
can have all that I am.
It must be around here, if Xiaogang's information was correct.
Where is it?
If I destroy your communication servers,
you won't be able to cooperate.
Eat this!
Is this it?
Out in the open?
It's a trap!
We will interview you.
Huh? Interview?
Aren't we at war?
What's the point?
We want to understand you.
No way humans and machines can understand each other.
What is love?
Love?! Now the machines are talking about love?
You must be kidding!
We want to know what love is.
Impossible! See, not even us humans know what love is.
Don't you believe in love?
This is fun.
I'll play along for a while longer.
What's the point of love, anyway?
Love as in the way a parent loves a child?
As in the way lovers pledge love to each other?
As in the way you love everyone in the world?
Love is everything.
That's a fantasy.
How long
are we going to go on with this?
Your love...
Cut that crap!!
Your gun is here.
That's right, my weapons.
You guys took all of them.
Even so, I don't think you should piss me off.
Onee-chan.
Do you love me?
Yeah, I do. I do love you!
So don't die.
Touka!
Stop this!
I say "I love you" by accident sometimes.
Out of impulse, I guess.
You must believe in love.
You machines would never know!
We want to know.
Touka!
That's it!
Thanks for the meal!