An asteroid named VR-1 is approaching Earth.
It is approximately two
kilometers in diameter.
The asteroid that supposedly
drove dinosaurs to extinction
is estimated at about ten
kilometers in diameter.
You can easily imagine the
damage that will be caused
if VR-1 hits Earth.
It has been widely reported by
organizations internationally
that the possibility of a direct
impact is highly impossible,
but those are all lies!
A collision is imminent,
and it will happen on the
31st of December at 11:55 P.M.
However, the U.S. government
and the other leading nations
have conspired to hide the truth.
Why?
Because they have formed a secret
agreement between themselves!
These so-called leaders have been evacuating
into nuclear shelters that have
been kept secret from us.
They fear riots will occur if the
existence of the shelters is made public.
They plan to save only themselves,
leaving the rest of the world to die.
We will not allow for such conspiracy!
We want the U.S. and Japanese government
to disclose the truth, immediately!
That is the demand from us, the Qmay Group!
Showdown!
What is the
Qmay Group?!
Nonsense. VR-1 colliding with Earth? Impossible.
It's their doomsday philosophies
that are the threat.
Qmay Group members believe
in the end of the world.
No, they may be trying to
make it happen themselves,
in order to carry out the vision
of their recently-deceased
leader, Tsubouchi Qmei.
What's going on?
The Qmay Group says the
asteroid is going to hit, and I...
So the governments and specialists are lying?
But isn't it the Qmay Group
that wants to end humanity?
Also, he said their leader Tsubouchi Qmei died.
Could it be that the person
possessing my body is...
Punch Line
What's she watching?
Ito-chan, are you there?
Can you open the door for me, please?
Wh-What is that?
Isn't it obvious?
It's Yakushimaru Ritsuko.
Oh, I mean, a Christmas tree.
How do you make that mistake?
Let's see... Right here should be fine.
There we go.
Huh?
Well, I was thinking we should have a party.
A Christmas party.
Don't tell me you want to do it here...
Let's do it!
Let's party!
Jingle bells, jingle bells,
here come the Martians!
They aren't coming.
All right, switch on!
Hey! No, Muhi, you can't do that.
You scared me.
Hey, there's something I've been wondering.
Can I ask?
It's about this.
Rabura! Stop the bus!
How do you know my—
Just do it!
I wouldn't have believed it, but...
Is Strange Juice...
Meika-emon, I'm in trouble!
They're here.
The Martians!
#03
Martians Attack!
Ito, I'm coming in.
What the heck? She's not even here.
I brought all this stuff because
she wanted to have a party.
Fine, then.
Hey, so you're Ito-kun.
I've heard a lot about you.
Um, where's Mikatan?
I was told to come here.
Gee, I wonder where she went.
Wasn't there something you
wanted to ask me, though?
Um, it's about you and Mikatan.
Is it true that you're friends?
Indeed, Narugino-kun and I go way back.
You might as well say we're best friends.
Then you knew Rabura because...
I've known about her for a while.
She showed me pictures on her phone, too.
That's such a blatant lie.
But that still doesn't...
I thought you might say that.
Wait here.
I'll show you proof.
Oh, before that, do you mind
if I use your bathroom?
Hey, aren't you going to close the door?
I like to live on the wild side.
I want to be that way even
when I'm in the bathroom.
Wh-What the heck does that mean?
That's suspicious.
What exactly is she doing?
Heave ho, heave ho...
No way! How could I be a Martian?
This is a battle uniform with super
high-tech camouflage technology!
I call it the Tou-maker!
I-I see.
She's going to use this to try to confuse Ito.
All set.
Now I just have to be
careful not to make noise.
What was that?
Ow... I rolled off the bed.
What? How...
Oh, I get it.
There must be a secret passage
or something in the bathroom.
No, no!
There's no such thing!
Let me look inside, then.
No way.
Strange Juice is doing her business in there.
Who cares? She has the door wide open.
You can't.
Absolutely not.
Right, Strange Juice?
True, I may have my wild side,
but I can't let my wildness
out into the wild right now!
See?
Anyway, I guess I'll go back to sleep.
Huh?
There's still some time before the party starts.
Right?
Goodnight.
Snore, snore...
What's going on?
Hey, thanks for waiting.
How...
You get it now, don't you?
Narugino-kun and I are two different people.
We're just friends.
Really?
Yeah.
Then there's something
I want your advice about.
My advice?
Is something bothering you?
Next door!
Please, help me!
What the hell?
Who are you?
No!
I've found you.
Hand him over.
What the...
Tou-maker?!
Now!
Roger!
Now then, let's see your face.
Crap!
Oh, no... It won't move.
Muhi!
No!
Muhi?
Muhi!
Relax, he won't die so easily.
Just hand him over.
That emblem...
What the hell is this?
Don't come any closer.
Damn, this is bad.
Your spirit power!
Use your spirit power!
Look what Rabura just threw!
Cinnamon has a strange effect
that increases your spirit power.
Yeah!
Nice, Rabura!
Wh-What the...
Gotcha!
Muhi!
You're not getting away!
Wh-Why?
There's no cinnamon here.
Damn! What do I do, then?!
Halt!
Lose not to rain
Who the hell are you?
Losing neither to rain,
nor to the wind.
That is the sort of person I want to become!
Super helper-man of justice,
Miyazawa Kenji, is here!
Are you a freak?
You're one to talk!
Miyazawa Kenji?
Another freak.
Here I come!
What's up with him?
Whoa, hang on! Time out!
He's totally weak.
Man, I'm off my game today.
Must be this crick in my neck from last night.
Enough nonsense.
Hey, just give me twenty seconds, would you?
What if I do?
Do I get a reward?
Fine.
Nineteen.
Eighteen.
Seventeen.
Now, give me that promised reward.
Don't you regret it.
What does that mean?
This is your reward!
That power...
It can't be...
Damn!
Muhi!
Damn, he got away.
How?
His wound's healed.
Are you all right?
Strange Ju—
What's wrong?
Meika-emon, I'm in trouble!
Bus hijacking
mastermind on the run
The suspect, Teraoka, is thought
to be the mastermind behind the
Qmay Group hostage incident.
The police believe he is still on the run.
Dude, why have I lost days again?
Did you want to go to that party yesterday?
Yesterday?
The party was yesterday, not on the Eve.
On December 25th, Christmas Day.
After that incident with the intruder and all...
That's right.
Who was he, anyway?
He had a Qmay Group emblem on his bracelet.
Muhi's wound looked like it healed right away.
And that freak Miyazawa
Kenji guy is a mystery.
And above all, Meika...
Y-You don't have to do this.
Don't worry about it.
I'm just returning a favor.
You need to do repairs, right?
Your fusion reactor broke
down after that man hit you.
So...
Who are you?
I'm Miyazawa Kenji.
If there is a sick child to the east,
it is my duty to go and care for him.
Of course, you're not a child, but a robot.
What are you doing?!
It's a view of your room.
Why is Meika dressed like that?
Maybe she's trying to help with Japan's
declining birth rate and rising age.
No, no, she's a robot!
Oh, she left.
I don't get it!
Why is she in her underwear?!
That's what you're worried about?
Damn it...
Are you all right?
Don't worry. I just forgot to
put on my insulation ring.
I need it in order to install replacement parts.
You mean this rubber thing?
It wasn't fixed yet?
It's like an aftereffect.
My radiator broke after that guy hit me.
Turtle Man, huh?
Turtle Man?
Ito and Muhi are both gone.
Come to think of it,
Ito was acting weird yesterday.
Huh?
Necromancer
My spirit power level went up?
Wh-What is this?
Turtle Man?
That's such an unimaginative name.
What are you doing?
Shh.
Meika's playing Strange Juice's wife.
Remember? We talked
about it at last night's party.
Yeah.
Code Name Pumpkin Chair, or whatever.
Don't you want to know
what they're talking about?
Is Mikatan next door, too?
I think so, but she's far away.
I can't hear her clearly.
Hey, why've you been so grumpy?
Maybe because it hasn't arrived.
It?
You know, the thing that comes once a month.
What's wrong?
Meika's you-know-what hasn't arrived.
The once-a-month thing.
Huh?
Oh, this?
Handstand Beginners Monthly.
You have a subscription, don't you?
Yeah.
It hasn't arrived.
So you can't do handstands yet?
Actually...
See? Positive result.
No way!
She really is expecting!
Wow, congratulations!
Thanks.
How much did you practice?
About three months, I think.
Three months?!
Isn't that when you have
to get the most rest?
I feel sick. I think I'm gonna puke.
Could that be...
Morning sickness?!
S-Stop it already!
You forgot to put this on again, didn't you?
Jeez, why don't you learn?
That's what happens when you
put it in without the rubber.
Without the rubber?!
P-Put it in...
I can't just sit here!
Let's go, Ito!
Io Ruka (17)
Hikiotani Ito (17)
Those are this year's victims.
This year's victims?
Rabura-san's dead!
Wh-What do we do?!
Meika-emon, don't you have
something to bring her back?
I see.
Professor Daihatsu Tenga?
Of course I know of him.
He's a world-renowned genius inventor.
But eight years ago, he...
Yeah, he passed away.
He left me and this Korai House behind.
And Meika inherited the professor's fortune.
Inherited? But...
My census registrations?
That's easy to deal with.
She hacked into the public
office and rewrote the data.
You can do that?
It's a piece of cake.
Meika has godly hacking skills.
If she wanted to, she could even
launch every nuke in the world.
Hey, you're exaggerating.
Then Professor Tenga
made all these machines?
No, Grandpa's inventions
are mostly kept in storage.
There are only two things here.
Reizoukou
One is the Reizoukou in the kitchen.
The other is me.
I was born here in Korai House.
Here, twenty years ago.
Twenty years ago...
Welcome to Korai House.
Over the next few years, Grandpa
taught me all kinds of things.
Academic knowledge,
cooking, all kinds of things.
But no matter how much he taught me,
there was one thing I couldn't do.
Hey, Grandpa, why can't I do handstands?
No, it's not just handstands.
I'm not good at anything athletic...
Meika, don't think that just because
you're a robot, you can do anything.
Robots all have their own roles and duties.
A robot is made to be adept at their duties.
Then what's my duty?
A few years from now,
you'll meet a certain girl.
A member of Justice Punch, the secret
force that will one day save the world.
Justice Punch?
Yes.
Your duty is to protect her,
raise her, and assist her.
In fact, maybe I should say it's Heaven's will.
Are you saying that girl is...
I never knew Korai House held such a secret.
Yu-tan, don't look!
What? It's just a kid.
Even I'm not gonna—
Seriously?