Kawagoe Seminar   |   Azumi Kotarou
Koumei Private High School
I'm applying.
I haven't even told my parents yet.
Clubs
All right.
It seems like Kotarou...
has started studying for exams recently.
The Kawagoe Festival's over now, too.
I suppose he's finally taking
his future more seriously.
Just as Dazai said...
"To decide that I'm hopeless before
I even begin is nothing but laziness."
He's been so absorbed in
his novels and the festival,
he wouldn't listen to me at all.
Is that so?
We'd prefer it if he went
to a local public school.
A municipal high school would be convenient.
I think that would suit his abilities, too.
So your preference is a municipal school?
No.
A private school.
Koumei High School.
Koumei? Isn't that...
the same one as Mizuno-san?
Yeah.
Kotarou, what is this about?
Tell me!
What's going on here?
Um...
You didn't tell me about this!
Uh...
Where is Koumei?
You never said a word to me.
Why didn't you talk to me first?
Because I just recently decided.
Just recently?
That's not for you to decide by yourself!
Your future depends on this!
Do you understand?
I do.
Kotarou, why did you choose that school?
Koumei, was it?
Because a girl's going there?
Say what?
The teacher mentioned that a girl
in his class is applying there.
I was so embarrassed.
This is important!
And you chose it just because
a girl you like is going there?
I've thought this through.
You obviously haven't!
I have.
Then can you tell me why you
would go all the way to Chiba?
What do you hope to do there?
That's what I thought.
Shut up.
Kotarou!
Sorry.
You shouldn't corner him like that.
How is he—
You're being too complacent!
Is that really in his best interests?
I say this because I care about—
Either way, I've made up my mind.
Wait!
Kotarou!
You're welcome
Are you up?
Yeah, I was studying
Working hard, huh?
What about you?
Got in a fight
with my parents
About to start studying
Okay, good luck
Thanks
Aren't you prepping for entrance exams?
But...
Don't blame me if you fail.
Fine.
Now, then...
Done.
Stockinette Stitch
You can't be serious.
A hand-knit scarf? In this day and age?
Wh-What's wrong with that?
Things are going well, huh?
Yup.
Oh, but what are you doing
after you graduate?
Long-distance?
It's fine.
There's your inexplicable confidence again.
We're going to the same high school.
Huh? What?
You mean your boyfriend's applying
to the same school as you?
Don't tell Mom and Dad.
Don't do that!
It's not like you'll be
together your whole lives.
What happens when you break up?
Will you take responsibility?
I know how you feel, but...
We won't break up.
Akane...
Let's look at the summaries.
The present progressive
form is "am waiting."
The past progressive form is "was waiting."
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Kotarou, have your dinner.
No, thanks.
What?
You need to have something to eat.
Really?
There he is.
He's actually doing it?
You're kidding.
Kota, you're awesome!
You're applying to Mizuno-san's school?
People are talking about you.
They are?
No way! Seriously?
That's insane!
No, it's nothing.
You're insanely in love!
Just marry him already!
I hate you.
Lucky bastard.
Damn it!
Mizuno-san has good grades, doesn't she?
He'll make up for it with the power of love.
Life's not that easy!
Mercy! Mercy!
Are you serious?
About what?
You'll never get into Koumei.
You need a standard score over 60.
I mean, I could do it, but...
I'm rooting for you, Kota-chan.
Get off me already.
Dude, you're so creepy.
Science
Synthesis
Decomposition
Oxidation
Thermal Decomposition
Properties of a Circle
Solutions of Quadratic
Equations -- Problems
The results of the mock exam are in.
Azumi.
Subject
Total
worth
Score
English
Mathematics
Language
3-Subject Exams
Science
Social Studies
4-Subject Exams
5-Subject Exams
I heard you're applying for Koumei.
Oh, yeah...
That's awesome.
My first choice is a public school.
Yeah?
Hello, my son is in Class 3-1...
Hello.
Thanks for coming in.
Thank you very much for having me.
Reception
Exams are brutal, huh?
My grades aren't good.
I see...
I might not get into the school I want.
You look pale.
You're pushing yourself too hard.
Your family must be worried.
My parents are against it.
They probably hope I fail.
Don't be afraid to rest when things get rough.
It's important to clear your mind, too.
Why don't you try talking to your parents
again after things settle down a little?
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Don't overdo it
Yes, sir!
Can we meet up for Christmas
tomorrow, at least for a bit?
It's so cute!
Sorry, were you waiting long?
No.
It's been a long time since
it was just the two of us.
Yeah.
Hey...
Sorry, I know you're studying.
You, too.
H-Hey...
Merry Christmas.
Thanks.
I have something, too.
Can I open it?
Sure.
I thought it might be useful for your club.
It's so cute! Thanks!
Me next, then.
Yeah.
U-Um...
Sorry it's so bad.
It was my first time knitting.
R-Really?
Wow...
Huh?
No way... Why?
I followed the book...
Huh?
Sorry.
It's fine.
See?
It's warm.
Thank goodness.
Thanks, Akane-chan.
You're studying really hard, aren't you?
Huh?
You look sleepy in class.
Are you always up late studying?
Yeah.
I see.
I'm running out of time.
My mom's against it, so I want to
get my grades up and show her,
but it's not working out.
Yeah.
Having your family's support
is important, isn't it?
At my last meet, my mom left a
message in my lunch box saying,
"Good work over the past three years."
Yeah?
I realized she'd been watching
over me the whole time.
I cried a little.
Yeah?
Either way, I'm just going
to have to succeed.
Aitai
Fortune
Kawagoe
Hikawa
Shrine
Yeah.
Me, too.
Exams start right after New Year's.
Let's do this.
Yeah.
Sorry it didn't turn out
so great
I'm glad you liked it,
though
And thanks for the handkerchief
I'll use it at my club
Thanks for meeting up today
I feel like I'm ready to study
again starting tomorrow
I hope we both do well
Yeah!
Akane's getting her result today, right?
Yeah.
I passed
Did... Did she...
She passed?
Yup!
All right!
Yes!
Congrats!!
Good for her.
Yeah.
You can do it too, Azumi-kun.
Morning.
Were you up all night?
Yeah, studying.
About your high school...
I've heard enough.
You can apply to Koumei.
But if you fail, you're applying
to a municipal high school.
Got it?
Can you promise?
Yeah.
Got it.
Your mom got called in by your
homeroom teacher the other day.
She said you shouldn't try for
Koumei with your current grades.
But your mother apparently fought back,
saying she wants to give you a chance
since you're trying so hard.
She can be naggy, but...
Well, there you have it.
Oh.
What is it?
Are you hungry?
I was just about to bring this upstairs.
Have a seat.
Why don't you go back to sleeping earlier
and being awake at normal times?
You're putting so much work into this.
What good will it do you if you
aren't fully awake at the exam?
Yeah.
Here, tea.
Goodnight.
Don't overdo it.
Do you have your exam ticket?
I got it.
I wrote down your transfers
and departure times.
Don't you dare take the wrong train.
It's really far.
I know.
Kotarou, here.
Thanks.
Hurry up, now.
You don't want to be late.
I'm going.
Off you go.
Dazai once said, "I must
live up to my promise.
That is all that matters to me now."
An Encouragement of Learning