Thanks for treating us to breakfast, too.
We are country people
so our food is not fancy.
But I'm glad to see you've rested well.
Yep, sure did.
I haven't slept so well through the night
in a long time.
This is a great room.
Nice and quiet.
Stay as long as you wish.
Jeez, thanks but...
We have rooms to spare.
If you are not in a hurry,
do stay with us for a while.
You're really generous in such hard times.
Can I have some more?
I know not about other places,
but our village has nothing but peace.
We are not rich,
but we do not need for anything.
Thanks.
We are able to live thus...
all thanks to the blessings from above.
I'd been trying to think of a way
to have him let us stay.
I never imagined he'd come out
and invite us to.
I won't let the demons go free.
That huge one might come
straight for you next time.
That would be good.
I'm going out to talk with the villagers.
I'm curious about the nun
and the burnt-out temple.
How about you?
I will watch Sabame.
Yeah. Well don't do anything crazy.
That old guy might just be brainwashed.
He looks creepy,
but don't judge a book by its cover.
Betrayed this world
And it simmers within
Rupturing my innards
Swelling a reddish black
Until the sun burnt skin ruptures
There is a light
in the depths of the seething darkness
Confirming each other's voices
in the distance
As if to stroke with wet fingertips
I'd like to touch you one day
There is a light
in the depths of the darkness
Confirming each other's voices
in the distance
As if to stroke with wet fingertips
I'd like to touch you one day
#15 The story of the scene from hell
Yeah, yeah. Hah! Take that.
Hey, thanks for taking your time out
to help me.
Nah, it's nothing. What are neighbors for?
Ow...
Whoa, watch it now.
I'm getting old.
We'll get through winter now.
What a blessing.
Just a bit more work to do.
All right.
You all must be tired.
Take a break and have some tea.
Thanks.
Hey, wait for me!
Guess it's like any other village.
What a cool tower.
Grandma, who's that kid over there?
Hey, want some rice cakes?
-Me?
-They're really tasty.
I see, you're Lord Sabame's guest then.
Yeah. He's really nice
for letting a stranger like me stay.
I'm really thankful.
Rice cakes!
Here you go.
Thanks. This looks so good.
Lord Sabame puts this village
before everything.
We are able to live like this in peace.
All thanks to Lord Sabame.
He's a really great guy, huh.
How dare you address him like that!
Uh, sorry.
By the way, I saw a burnt-out temple
on my way here.
You know about it?
Time to go now.
Must get some more work done
while the sun is still high.
Aww, but Grandma...
Now, off we go.
But Grandma...
This is my favorite place.
I have a full view of the village
from here.
Something's fishy.
A grand storehouse in the woods
away from the village?
So fishy...
Something's not right.
There's something going on.
Maybe there's hidden treasure in it.
Nobody's guarding it, either.
Darn, just another rice storehouse.
This sure is a hard-working village.
If you have a full belly,
your heart will be calm and gentle.
Keeping true to your ambition
when it could mean life or death...
that isn't something just anyone can do.
But they've really saved up a lot.
Way too much for me to handle.
Ouch... Huh?
What's this? A hidden trapdoor?
I can't see a thing without a torch.
Of course you can't.
Ow... What the heck was that for?
Sorry, kid.
It's to protect the village.
My ancestors protected this land
for generations.
I was born and raised here.
I became the lord, and here I am.
I know not of any other places.
As a traveler, you may not understand
what that's like.
This village is my everything.
No matter what happens,
I will protect it.
You came here to kill
the ghouls that live here, correct?
-Right.
-I won't let you.
They, too, are my people.
I must protect them.
Hey, what the heck! Let me out of here!
Let me out!
What's the deal with them?
These people are crazy.
I gotta let bro know.
I need to find a light.
Is this what I think it is?
Bro!
Our village was in
the clutches of hell, too.
The samurai who escaped wars
and became brigands
came and raided our peaceful village.
The fields were left unattended
and ravaged by wild beasts and insects.
My people were hungry,
and stole from one another.
It was amidst such hell
that I encountered "them".
The ghouls.
If it is our destiny
to live on in this land,
I must protect the land and its people.
I didn't care that they were ghouls.
I was ready to give up my soul if
it meant my people could escape this hell.
The ghouls ate the brigands
and killed the beasts.
They kept their promise,
and our village prospered again.
And I welcomed "her" into my home
as my wife.
Let me ask you one thing.
Why do you kill ghouls?
Dang it, I'm not dying here
to be eaten by you.
Ouch...
Dang it.
Oh no...
Why...?
I don't care
what you're trying to protect.
I will kill the demons.
And get it all back.
-You saved me...
-Dororo is kind.
So I save Dororo.
Oh wow...
Don't let the kids escape!
You're going to be fed to Maimai-onba.
It's for the village. No hard feelings.
That's too cruel.
For the village? But...
You're so kind, Dororo. Thank you.
Don't cry. We must hurry
or Maimai-onba's children will awaken.
Follow me.
A vagabond like you
would never understand.
Bro!
They've finally awakened.
You will fill their empty stomachs.
The same... You are the same!
Out of my way!
Bro!
Listen bro, it was the villagers.
They killed the nun and the kids.
What's that?
The village, it's burning.
I was pushed down a trapdoor
in a storehouse.
Then those huge bugs came at me.
They almost ate me up.
But that big baby thing saved me.
And then...
That baby ghost, it was the murdered kids.
Are you listening to me?
Yeah.
I found the oil too.
The oil used to burn down the temple.
I know it. It smelled the same.
I made sure they couldn't do it again.
Lord Sabame, all the village's rice
has been burned.
-We won't last through the winter.
-Lord Sabame.
-What should we do?
-How will we survive this winter?
Hey, isn't there still a stock of rice
at your house, Ishi?
Your home hasn't burned down.
Hands off. That's my rice!
You're going to hog it all?
Sabame, do something!
I heard Lord Sabame's guest
started the fire.
The lake?
The baby ghoul said so.
Bro!
Bro.
What happened?
The whole village...
Why?
Why did this happen?
Bro, did we do the wrong thing?
This happened because we came, right?
Not my concern.
Even if you defeat a few demons
here and there,
it won't change the world at all.
All you think about is killing the demons.
Say something.
This isn't right.
That'll just make you one of them.
Can you not perceive distance
with just one eye yet?
Not yet. Again!
It's not my concern.
Dororo?
I wish bro would listen to me more.
Stupid bro.
Hey, Dororo. Long time no see.
Oh, Itachi.
Aww, come on.
I've been looking everywhere for you.
Still a midget, eh?
Shut up!
Ta-da. Now show me the other half
that you have.
Born into this world
There is no salvation
The distorted shape of the heart
Yet it beats courageously
There is no turning back
Even from the path of evil
Witnessing the withering seasons
We search for the truth
In our ugliness
We don't even recognize the pain
As we peel back the skin
We are forever tormented by our stupidity
But if the dawn never comes
Through the painful night
You who distrusts nothing
You will be able to love
this accursed world
Now that we carry the world
on our shoulders
It's time to take it back
"Maimai-onba"