Gust of wind...
Yes!
The sound of birds crossing...
What do I do?
I can hear everything.
I can hear the sound,
but my body, my left hand won't...
Chihaya Furu
Episode 21
But
its
legacy
continues
to
spread
awakens the guards of
Suma Gate at night
My life means nothing...
She's swinging at multiple cards?
In order to restore...
She hit seven cards there.
She counts as a man
Porky was right.
Strong swing!
She's powerful!
Calm down.
The match has just begun.
My reach and pivot point
are completely different.
I feel bad about her injury,
but she thinks she'll win with her left hand?
That's absurd.
This is my chance
to avenge our loss yesterday!
My stance is towards the other side.
My center of gravity is on the other side.
I usually put my weight on my left knee,
but now it's on the right.
I can't think too much about it!
Use a natural stance.
After many, many years...
My hand will reach.
I just have to swing!
now bloom inside the nine-fold palace
For you, I head out to the fields...
Yes!  Yes!  Yes!
It won't work...
I've never practiced covering
with my left hand...
Those girls are very similar.
They're both easy to read.
while snow falls upon my sleeves
The hazed early dawn
A multi-syllable card
on the opponent's side!
She covered!
mist over the Kawagiri River
Huh?
Wait, I touched it?
Who got it?!
Was Yuube-san faster?
You won that card!
Honest
I've never thought about
how to use my left hand,
or how to approach the card with it.
How do left-handed players
see a right-handed cover?
Yuube-san just lost "The hazed
early dawn mist" on the outside,
but she has another multi-syllable
card, "My only thought as I,"
at her lower right.
Right-handed players only know
how to play against other
right-handed players.
...nets in the shallows
But for a left-handed player...
My only thought as I am put out
to sea is to ask the fishermen
It's open to take!
I lost two cards the same way...
Ayase-san's doing a wonderful job.
Is she actually left-handed?
She's winning multi-syllable
cards she's struggled with.
I can do this.
I can do this!
I can come back.
So spring ends...
Attack to come back!
Huh?
Would the mountain cherry blossoms...
What?
When winds send waves...
I have no problem taking
cards on the opponent's side.
So why
doesn't my body move when it's on my side?
What's going on?
It feels like riding a bike with
the brakes held down halfway.
Thank you very much.
Their match is already over?!
How?!
There haven't been 25 cards read yet.
He won by 27 cards?!
He was perfect, plus he got his
opponent to commit two faults?!
What the hell?
How does that even work?
May the scarlet kadsuras...
The Queen is next to finish.
She won by a perfect 25-0 score.
What about Chihaya?
What kind of karuta does Chihaya play?
How does Chihaya
play karuta now?
Huh?
Her right hand's injured?
She's using her left hand?!
Impassioned was your promise...
My own sleeves are like...
Why?
I can take cards on the opponent's side,
so why can't I take them from my own side?
If I were using my right hand,
I could take these without thinking.
Why is a brake holding me back?
That's crazy, Chihaya.
Karuta isn't that simple.
Said bed was cold as I lay awake
You've gotten used to taking
cards from your own side
without any thought.
Your cards are placed for
a right-handed player.
I'm 10 cards up now.
She'll probably give up soon.
Most players would give up after
injuring their right hand.
You worked hard to get here.
You put on a performance worthy of
the captain of the team champions.
I should have just played
with my right hand.
I would have been able to
last one match at least.
No.
If I only get one match
to use my right hand,
I should save it for Arata!
for the night would drag on
when I thought of my beloved
In the sleepy spring sunlight,
She attacks the opponent's side quickly!
Um, excuse me.
Can I move my cards?
Uh, sure...
Sh-She moved all of them?
She flipped her cards around?
I've never seen this before.
I have to win until I play Arata!
Wait.
It's bad manners to move
so many cards at one time.
Of course.  I'm sorry.
It's fine.  Leave them.
Huh?
Leave them in that order.
She's playing with the handicap
of having to use her left hand.
Compared to that, shuffling
her cards around is nothing.
She's so manly!
Thank you very much!
But I have no idea how this helps.
Redo my memorization...
If she's trying to confuse me,
she'll end up hurting herself.
It's suicidal to mess around
with your card positioning.
This is a gamble.
Don't think.
Do what I usually do,
only with my left hand.
a whirlwind of flower petals descends
Rain takes longer...
I did it!  Just like normal!
Everything's normal, just flipped!
The storm blasts...
Note that though we may be...
Why is she suddenly so much faster?
Why?
I see.
Instead taking cards from this
direction to that direction,
she's taking them from that
direction to this direction.
It's less confusing if you just
mirror your normal motions.
The flow has changed since
she moved her cards.
This will be tough for her opponent.
Amazing, Ayase-san!
Please wait.
Excuse me.
I can't lose to her.
No matter who my opponent is.
The sky may hold the same moon
She sent Ayase-san's hand flying!
The headband girl recovered.
She has a powerful swing.
She goes for the card in front
as well as the one that's read.
She even knocks away her
opponent's hand at times.
That's playing rough!
Yuube-san didn't hit my hand away.
She passed through the
opening I left her.
Amazing...
Don't panic.  Stay calm.
This fall, I'll be aiming to
become Queen with Megumu!
I can't win with weak attacks.
If I hesitate, I'll lose the card.
Focus.
Chihaya...
She's playing hard with her left hand.
Having fun...
Now that I think about it,
Chihaya took her first card
from me with her left hand.
Must be fun...
Playing karuta with Chihaya must be fun.
Thank you very much.
Shock
Yes, I eked out a win.
Ayase: won by 2 cards.
Okay.
Don't get the wrong idea!
I didn't lose to you!
I lost because my memorization
wasn't good enough!
I'll work on my memorization
by studying for college exams,
so I'll be back!
She even treats college exam prep
as preparation for karuta!
Marvelous...
Chihaya.
That was incredible, Chihaya.
You won with your left hand.
That was incredible!
I believe that you have
the talent for Karuta.
We will now announce the
pairings for the second round.
Please check the chart and sit
at your assigned position.
Hey, Ayase.
You survived the first round?
Yep, you too?
Oh, yeah!
I avenged Tsukuba!
Ayase, I feel like I can't lose today.
Nishida Yusei
vs.
Wataya Arata
Shock
Kaneko Natsumi
vs.
Ayase Chihaya
Kaneko-san from Akita.
I didn't get paired against Arata again.
Chihaya, see you later.
S-Sure.
Can I reach him?
Or is he still out of reach?
I want to know.
I'm not crazy about karuta
the way Ayase is.
I prefer to avoid playing
stronger players.
I'll take all the easy wins I can get.
But...
I have to go back to being
crazy about karuta.
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
When I'm up against you...
Komano-kun and Oe-san won
their first round matches.
Tsukuba-kun won with a bye.
Hanano-san won?!  Amazing!
Everyone's doing great!
to tell the people in the capital
that I make for the islands
You're not supposed to make any
sound when a card is being read.
May my sighs be blamed upon the moon,
They're so into the match.
These parents must care
very much about their child.
Arata!
Mom, Dad...
If I win the high school tournament,
I have a favor to ask.
I want you to let me attend
a university in Tokyo.
Arata...
Most scholarship offers will
come from private schools.
It would take 4,000,000 yen in the
first year to cover registration,
tuition, and living expenses!
You're smart enough to attend
a local public university!
Lose your match!
May I see you never forget...
Hang in there, chubby kid!
I'm no longer the kid I used to be.
Yusei, you should work on game
awareness instead of game sense.
With your mastery of
the basics, you can do it.
Make assumptions about the places
where cards will be read earlier.
I'll teach you how it works.
You'll learn how to take
control of any match!
You rock, chubby kid!
Way to go!
Amazing...
He's following a methodology.
I can see his training in his playing style.
The presence of his coach in his play...
Chihaya's high school is really special.
They have different types
of karuta players.
That's amazing.
When the misty bridge...
He's fast!
What was that?
...is nearly past
So the flower petals are scattered...
He went from his own lower
right to his own upper left.
...withers and wilts
Nothing can be worse...
He crossed again!
Three different points this time!
Arata, why are you participating in
the high school tournament this year?
Couldn't you wait until next year
when you're a third-year?
Why this year?
If I get into a school early by recommendation,
it'll be easier for me to focus.
On the Master Challenger
tournament in the fall
and the Master match in the winter.
Why?
Why is he so much better than me?
I've played karuta since I was little.
I've practiced hard the whole time.
What's the difference?
Ayase...
If I injured my favored
hand, I would forfeit.
It must have hurt when she was
playing in the final yesterday,
but all she cared about was
winning the team championship.
Desktomu-kun and Hanano worked hard
to collect data on the other teams.
One win for Pizusawa!
Kana-chan secured a victory
right after my loss in the
semifinal to ease the pressure.
I'm not doing this for attention!
But I'm here!
Tsukuba kept appealing to
us for a chance to play.
Three wins.
We're getting three wins, guys.
Mashima never gave up.
That's why we were able to win.
What did I do?
I can at least...
I can at least refuse to give up!
Don't give up!
Thank you very much.
Are all the players at Mizusawa like this?
You played five matches yesterday,
yet you're still playing your heart out.
You bet.
I don't play anywhere as
hard as the other members.
Mashima, Desktomu-kun, Kana-chan,
Ayase, and the first-years
are all playing harder!
Damn...
Don't forget how he swung from
his lower left to his upper right.
Damn!  Damn!
Don't forget how he attacked
from his opponent's upper left
to his opponent's lower right in a line.
This is why I hate strong players!
They make me want to beat them!
They make me want to work harder!
Ayase-san did it!  She's
through the second round!
Thank you very much.
I did it.  I made it to the Top 8.
Snore
This takes a lot more
concentration than normal,
but I have to do this.
We will now announce the
pairings for the third round.
I have to use my left hand
until I get to play Arata.
Ayase Chihaya
Wakamiya Shinobu