Where are they taking us?
Sorry, Vivian.
There are girls in here.
Not so rough, okay?
Don't worry, Ange.
Huh?
No matter what this world is like,
I'll protect you.
You're right.
Those people spoke our language.
If we could speak to them,
we might learn something about this world.
Th-That's true...
What?
I mean, you're being your usual self.
Huh?
Are you frustrated because you didn't get any?
They stopped us right when
things were heating up.
Well—
This isn't the time.
Men.
Hey, watch where you're touching!
It's not on purpose, I swear!
Stop being horny!
I'm not, I'm not!
Shut it down! Close shop! Sit, boy!
The Other Earth
We're here.
Get out.
The high priestess will see you.
This way.
Vivian!
What have you done to Vivian?
We've brought them.
A woman from another world...
...and a man.
State your name.
You should introduce yourself
before you demand someone's name.
How dare you disrespect the high priestess!
Ange!
We haven't opened a singularity.
How did you come here?
You're before the high priestess. Answer!
That machine... did you ride it here?
Is that a real man?
That daughter of Sylphis...
Why is she with—
Shut up!
Ask one at a time, if you must ask.
I'm full of questions, too.
Just what is this place?
When are we?
What are you people?
Hey, Ange!
You're so lively.
You!
I am the direct descendant of progenitor Aura,
and princess of the Freyja family,
Lieutenant Guardian Salamandinay.
Welcome to the true Earth,
people of the false Earth.
You know of them?
That one.
She's the Villkiss pilot who fought
my machine to a standstill.
Villkiss's pilot?
She's dangerous! We cannot allow her to live.
Dispose of her. Now!
Do it.
I'm used to execution orders.
But...
Don't think you'll actually pull it off.
Wait, everyone.
She can operate the Villkiss,
which means she's special.
I believe the best strategy would be to allow
her to live until we learn that machine's secrets.
Please leave their lives to me.
The two of you are dismissed.
B-But...
This is quite a fancy jail cell.
I don't intend to treat you like prisoners.
You will be allowed to meet with the
daughter of Sylphis once she has been treated.
We will take responsibility
for repairing your machine.
This way, please.
What's this about?
You must be exhausted from your journey.
My name's Tusk. I'm Ange's knight.
Can I ask you something, Salamandinay-san?
Anything, Tusk-dono.
Is this really Earth?
Yes.
Then who are you?
We're human.
But Earth is our world, and we're humans.
Then this place...
What if there were two Earths?
Another Earth in a parallel universe...
A number of humans abandoned this
planet to migrate
to your Earth in the other universe.
They abandoned Earth?
What for?
Have you not seen in the ruins
what happened to this Earth?
War and pollution.
So it's like this.
You're here, and there are two Earths.
Ange!
That means there's a way back, isn't there?
Princess!
Salamandinay-sama!
Come closer and I'll kill her.
You savage!
We should have executed you!
Unhand the princess!
Otherwise, this man's life is forfeit!
Huh?!
Try it. I dare you.
What?!
Tusk said he'd sacrifice his life for me.
That's...
He said he'd gladly die for me.
What do you hope to do when you get back?
All that awaits you is a life of
using machines to kill your fellows.
Do you miss it so much?
Shut up.
False Earth, false people, and false battles.
You are much too oblivious.
Let's go.
We will show them the truth.
Hey!
Naga, Kaname, you will stand guard.
P-Princess!
Wait, I'm the one holding you hostage!
We're here.
There's a Dawn Pillar here, too.
We call it the Tower of Aura.
It used to be a Dracunium
regulation facility.
Dracunium
is an extremely powerful super-symmetric
particle discovered at the
end of the 22nd century.
It was supposed to bring light to the world.
Instead, it was immediately used for war.
Pollution, ethnic cleansing, poverty...
None of these problems were
solved before human society collapsed.
Some humans became disillusioned
and set out to find new land.
I've heard something similar.
The remainder of humanity made a
decision that would allow us to to survive
on the tarnished earth.
We would rebuild our own
bodies and adapt to the environment.
Rebuild?
Yes, we rebuilt our entire ecological
system through genetic modification.
What is this place?
Aura was here.
Aura?
Aura.
The great progenitor who first adapted
his own flesh to this polluted world.
In your terms, the first DRAGON.
We accepted our sinful history
and chose to live for
cleansing and redemption...
...alongside Aura.
The men transformed into massive DRAGONs
and devoted themselves to
the cleansing of the world.
Cleansing?
They ingest Dracunium and convert it into
stable crystals within their own bodies.
The women, at times,
transform to work alongside the men.
And when the time comes,
they bear and raise children.
We began down the road of
cleansing and recovery alongside Aura.
But...
Aura is no longer here.
Why not?
He was taken.
The culprit is the one who discovered
Dracunium, created Ragna-mails, and
destroyed the world before abandoning it.
He's the villain behind it all,
Embryo.
Embryo?
Do you know what power
dominates your civilization?
The Light of Mana.
And its energy?
The Light of Mana is created infinitely.
No...
The Light of Mana.
Utopia.
A world of magic.
It is the Dracunium energy emanating
from Aura that sustains all of that.
But that energy is quickly depleted,
and so must be replenished.
It became necessary to kill DRAGONs,
extract their crystallized Dracunium,
and supply it to Aura.
That is your war.
That is the truth of the war
you've risked your lives fighting.
Our people are killed in order
to sustain your world's energy.
Their hearts are torn out,
and their crystallized Dracunium extracted.
So that's what that was...
Do you understand?
That is what I meant by a false Earth,
false humans, and false battles.
Will you still return to your false world?
Of course.
Even if everything you say is true,
that's still my world.
Then I must restrain you.
I cannot allow you to kill
any more of my people.
Just try it.
I won't let you catch me so easily.
You're finally showing your
true colors, you lizard bitch!
I will not kill you.
We are unlike you barbaric, violent people.
You wrecked Arzenal. Who are you to talk?
That was an initialization
test for the Ryushinki.
You were a potential threat
to Aura's liberation.
How many people do you think died for that?
I will not ask for your forgiveness.
It was done to protect our world.
Wouldn't you have made the same
choice in that situation...
...Princess Angelise?
I've heard a lot about you.
From Lizardia.
Would you recognize her if I
used the name Riza Randog?
Riza.
She's one of yours?
You think I'm stupid!
You were simply unaware.
You think I'm stupid. Dammit!
I hate your eyes...
Huh? Sorry.
What happened?
I got beaten up.
Yeah? By who?
A savage, violent lizard woman.
Is that...
...me you're speaking of?
You scared me.
Vivian.
Sup!
Vivian, why are you human?
Quiz time.
How did I get back to being human?
Beep, too bad.
The answer is...
Umm...
What was it?
I adjusted your D-type
gene regulatory factor.
You should be able to maintain your
human form without medication now.
There we go.
Are you hurt anywhere?
Not really.
That's good.
Salamandinay-sama must have gone easy on you.
Gone easy?
Tusk was so worried about you, Ange.
Tusk?
Help me!
Anything but that!
Stop!
Stop it!
No! Not there!
Tusk!
Let Tusk go!
Ange!
Tusk, let's run!
What is this?
Why are you naked?
What's going on?
Great.
It's not like that, Ange, it's...
Thank you for your cooperation, Mr. Tusk.
We don't get to see many
fully mature humanoid males.
We've all learned a lot about sex.
Cooperate? Sex education?
Yes.
I see.
I'm going through hell, and you're...
Wait, Ange, calm down!
You animal!
Stop, stop!
Ange, have you calmed down now?
I'm filthy now...
I guess he doesn't care
if it's a lizard or whatever when he's pent up.
Stupid Tusk.
You appear to be fine now.
Lamia, it's her.
We've confirmed it by genetic testing.
She is your daughter.
What?
She's the missing daughter of Sylphis.
Your daughter, Mii.
Mii. Is it really you?
Mii.
No, I'm Vivian.
I know this smell.
You smell like Ersha.
Who are you?
I'm your mom.
Mom? What's that?
She's the person that gave birth to you.
Vivian's mother?
Yes.
Vivian must have wandered into the other
world while chasing after her mother.
Everyone, prepare a festival.
Let us celebrate.
One of ours has come back
for the first time in ten years.
Princess! It's the princess!
Salamandinay-sama!
What are we doing now?
Just do as Salamandinay-sama does.
We thank you for delivering this daughter
back to us, despite massacre
and other tribulations.
Oh, Aura.
Oh, Aura!
It's a strange scene.
Please, stop being angry.
I really didn't do anything.
My heart belongs to you.
But not your body.
But...
Stupid.
The moon's the same.
Huh?
Another Earth, huh.
I don't know if this is a
dream or if it's reality.
But I'm glad...
...that Vivian's human again.
Yeah.
What's going to happen to us now?
Why did she want us to see this?
She wanted you to learn about us.
And, in turn, to learn about you.
That is Salamandinay-sama's wish.
Learn, and then what?
We killed your people.
You killed our people.
That's all there is, isn't there?
Anger, sadness, revenge...
All that comes from them is destruction.
But humans are able to accept and forgive.
And so, move beyond that.
These are all the princess's words, though.
Please enjoy your stay here.
That is the princess's message.
What are we to do about the
princess's friendliness?
She'd kill you if she heard that...
Enjoy our stay, she said.
Do you trust them?
I don't know.
But Vivian seems to be happy.
Should we go back?
Huh?
Arzenal. Libertus. Embryo.
If we really don't have to fight anymore...
Preview
Ange, we're facing off next week!
I'm done.
I'm sick of doing previews with you.
We're running out of ideas.
It's not even much of a preview.
You say that now?
I'm leaving.
Wait, Ange, come back!
Resonant Battlefront