A tall, tall wall looms in front of me.
What's the view on the other side?
What does it look like?
It's a view I could never see on my own.
The Japanese National
High School Volleyball Tournament
Miyagi Prefecture Qualifiers (Boys)
Finals
Shiratorizawa vs. Karasuno
The View From The Top
The view from the top...
Let's go, Hinata.
Yeah!
Haikyu!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Episode 1: Greetings
Sawamura!
We came to cheer you on!
Michimiya! You really came.
Wow! You're really going
to play in the finals!
That's amazing! It's so... insane!
All right. Let's go, everyone.
Yeah.
What's insane is your lack of vocabulary.
Yui...
U-Um...
So, here!
Certain Victory Charm
Well, um, it's not just for you personally.
It's for all of you guys,
and for us, too... so it's not like...
Oh, thanks!
You're the best, Michimiya!
You're so thoughtful.
Huh? I-It's not a big deal...
I'll put it on the bench.
Hope you'll cheer us on!
Leave it to us!
I'm impressed you were even
able to give it to him.
The Japanese National
High School Volleyball Tournament
Miyagi Prefecture Qualifiers (Boys)
Finals
Shiratorizawa vs. Karasuno
Wow...
So this is the finals...
There're so many people.
Ryu, this is no time to be scared!
I'm not scared.
Listen, Ryu. Picture this.
The finals... Our opponents
are Shiratorizawa.
What do you think is going to happen
when we play to a crowd this big?
What's going to happen?
They always look so much cooler
when they're good players.
Hup.
Bam.
Yeah!
Nishinoya-kun! Tanaka-kun! You're amazing!
Nishinoya-kun, Tanaka-kun.
D-Do your best out there.
Noya-san, I'm gonna do this!
I'm gonna become a hero after this match.
I'm not gonna lose, Ryu!
They seem more hyped up than usual.
Hey, you're embarrassing us,
so stop screaming!
Guts! Guts! Guts! Guts!
I'm glad those guys never change.
Shut up, you two!
As expected...
Come on, let's go.
Yeah!
Hinata, do you need to go to the bathroom?
I just went!
Sho-chan!
I-Izumin! Koji!
Hey, it's been a while!
Oh! They're from my middle
school volley... I mean...
They're the people who helped me
during my volleyball match!
I was on the basketball team.
I was on the soccer team.
I was wondering why there was
someone with really good footwork.
He's...
Why's he here?!
I said the same thing at first.
He had a lot going on before.
Isn't that the King?
Are you sure you'll be okay, Shoyo?
Just watch.
Hey, let's go, Hinata.
Oh, well, I hope you cheer us on.
Do your best.
Yeah!
We texted, but only about what I was up to.
Who knew they'd have a reunion...
Who are they?
So Sho-chan finally made some friends.
They were in the match
with me in junior high.
Shut up. Like I remember
everyone I played against.
Yeah...
And that's exactly why you don't
have friends, Kageyama-kun.
Why, you...
Hey! Stop it, you two!
You're wasting energy before the finals?
Are you guys completely stupid?
Well, we might immediately lose anyway.
Good grief. Come on, let's go.
All right. As soon as we put our
stuff away, we're going to warm up...
Ow! What the heck, Daichi?!
Up until recently, they couldn't
even get past their second match.
Karasuno couldn't fly or crow.
Hopefully them making it to
finals isn't some fluke, either.
Oh, that guy's here again?
Do you know him?
Nah, he would just show up
to matches every so often.
I don't think he's someone's relative,
so I think he might just be a high school
volleyball fan that likes Karasuno.
He'll cheer for plays he thinks were good,
and boo the bad ones.
Where's Karasuno's cheering section?
You should at least make that clear.
He's always been easy to read.
Have you guys seen him before?
Yes. When we were still first-years,
he came to one of our games...
We'll never let him say that
we're grounded crows again.
Japanese National High School Volleyball Tournament
All right, here we go!
Yeah!
Certain Victory Karasuno
So they finally made it this far...
Huge Bargain Sale
Yeah. Let's give it our all, too.
Yeah.
All right!
Ladies and gentlemen from the
Karasuno shopping district,
Karasuno Alumni Cheer Squad,
and cheer squad hopefuls!
First, let's beat Shiratorizawa at cheering!
Fly
Karasuno High School
Volleyball Club
Listen up, everyone!
Two, three,four...
We need to cheer as loud
as we can so our cheers
Five, six, seven, eight...
become the players' strength!
Right!
The vice-principal sure seems
worked up about this, suddenly.
Come on. We need to practice once.
Ready, and...
Was he always like that?
Go, go, Karasuno! Push it, push it, Karasuno!
Hey! We just practiced this yesterday!
Sir, you say we practiced,
but it was just a little bit after school...
A-Are they going to be okay?
We can't panic!
Look at them! Look how confident they are!
I'm going to the bathroom again.
I-I need stomach medicine.
Me, too...
Center court...
Noya-san, cheer! Cheer!
Are you okay, Yamaguchi-kun?!
So jealous! Damn it!
Tanaka, Nishinoya, shut up!
You guys are panicking way too much.
E-Every... Everyone, calm...
This is Karasuno?
I'm not anyone suspicious!
I saw this suspicious guy wandering around.
He ran when he saw me, so I caught him!
Hey!
I thought he might be a Shiratorizawa spy.
What?!
W-Wait! I'm a relative!
I'm Tsukishima Kei's older brother!
Tsukishima's older brother?!
Shh! Shh!
He told me not to come to the match.
Those two are nothing alike...
especially their personalities.
Huh?
Shiratorizawa!
All right, here we go!
Be Courageous Warriors
Our opponent today...
...is Karasuno High School!
Nice to meet you!
All right, here we go!
Be Courageous Warriors
Wow...
Yeah, they definitely feel
like a powerhouse school.
Come to think of it, the other
team hasn't shown up yet.
Yeah, they're late.
Damn it. They must be
taking their sweet time.
Shiratorizawa
Academy
Maybe it's their dignity
as champions, or something.
All right, here we go!
Are they underestimating us?
They're here!
Shimada Mart
Everything
50% Off
Haikyu!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
All right, let's start our meeting.
Shiratorizawa Academy
Countermeasure Documents
Hey, I know you're tired from
already playing two matches today,
but you'd better listen.
Tomorrow's the next match.
First, I'm going to start
with my honest opinion...
If the most complete team in
the prefecture is Aoba Johsai,
Shiratorizawa is the most incomplete
team in the prefecture.
Incomplete?
Do you know why I think that?
That's because I looked at the
file your managers made
after they found out everything
they could about Shiratorizawa.
Kiyoko-san did that for me?!
No, it was for all of you.
That's about all that we can do, so...
Right, Hitoka-chan?
Oh, yes.
We wanted to be of some use to you all...
Thank you, Yachi-san!
You guys had better not let it go to waste!
You'd better clean out those ears and listen!
Right!
Um, so what do you mean by "incomplete team"?
If you'd call the attacks we and most
other teams do multiplication,
Shiratorizawa is addition.
Their addition consists of adding
powerful strengths together.
We use speed, the differences in positions,
and time as techniques to get through blocks.
Shiratorizawa also uses
the difference in time,
but when their receives are a bit off,
or in cases where they want
to score, no matter what,
they set really high to their wing
spikers, especially Ushijima.
There is only one reason for that.
Because they can absolutely
get a point that way.
Sorry!
They'll come out hitting without
thinking twice about our guard,
with power we've never experienced before.
You'd better be prepared!
He managed to hit that all the way up here?
He hits so high!
They're simply destroying everything
with their one ultimate spear.
That's the kind of team Shiratorizawa is.
Though Ushiwaka is their best,
it's not like the rest of that
team is ordinary, either.
Here!
They look like they're hitting it so lightly,
but it looks like it would break
my arms off if I tried to touch it.
Fire it up, Wakatoshi!
Ushiwaka's amazing...
I'm excited!
Yeah.
Fire it up, Eita!
Yeah!
Thanks!
Fire it up, Wakatoshi!
He's Benkei...
That guy's totally Benkei.
Fire it up, Wakatoshi!
Leon-san.
What's up?
Leon?!
That little kid totally gave
Leon-kun the nickname "Benkei."
Sorry to shatter your dreams.
So that's one of the guys from
Karasuno's first-year quick combo.
Oh, it was?
Bring it!
Look! There's a tiny kid!
I wonder if he's a sub.
Nice kill!
I sort of feel bad for him.
I always feel like I want
to cheer for the underdog.
Nice kill!
Hey, you two. Do that
thing you did yesterday!
But I can say the following
with confidence...
We definitely won't lose when
it comes to scoring points!
First...
Conquer this fight.
That shrimp shot straight down!
More importantly, he's fast!
Did the setter even touch it?
I was surprised that Seijoh
didn't make it this time,
but Karasuno's pretty fun.
Yeah.
It doesn't matter who we're up against.
We'll shut them down!
Talk big when you can actually back it up.
Now, now, now...
I see that your bangs and your
words are as cool as ever, Tsutomu.
Thanks!
And I think you babying him
is exactly the problem.
Harsh! You're so harsh, Taichi!
I'm just counting on him.
I mean, he's a first-year and a regular
and the one who's going to become the ace.
I'll do my best to not let you down!
Right. Do your best, future ace.
His head will get even more
inflated, so please stop.
First, receives.
We're counting on you yet again,
Wakatoshi-kun.
You need to work harder.
Don't just rely on Wakatoshi.
What are you, his right arm?
Are you Benkei?
Ushijima-san!
I'll prove that I'm the one
who should be called the ace
in these finals.
Yeah. Do your best.
He's actually honestly saying that,
so he's sort of a jerk.
Their starting lineup is just as we thought.
Did you memorize their characteristics?
Yes!
We're not going to let Ushijima
decide how this goes!
If they score, switch gears and get the
ball back! That's all you need to do!
They aren't machines over there.
They'll mess up sometimes.
You know what you need to do, right?
Yes!
All right, everyone. This is the finals.
Since we got this far,
let's win and go to nationals!
Yeah!
Japanese National High School Volleyball Tournament
We will now begin the Japanese National
High School Volleyball Tournament,
Miyagi Prefecture Qualifiers, Boys' Finals.
Miyagi Prefectural Karasuno High School
versus Shiratorizawa Academy.
It's finally starting...
Ah, Sho-chan. He's really
standing on this stage.
Yeah, but really, are his opponents
actually high school students?!
Wow, there're tons of TV crews here.
We will now introduce the Karasuno
High School starting lineup.
#1, Sawamura Daichi.
#3, Azumane Asahi.
#5, Tanaka Ryunosuke.
Ryu!
Yeah!
#9, Kageyama Tobio.
#10, Hinata Shoyo.
#11, Tsukishima Kei.
Kei!
Hey, stop!
#4, Libero, Nishinoya Yu.
Yeah!
Coach, Takeda Ittetsu.
Next, we will introduce
the Shiratorizawa Academy starting lineup.
#1, Ushijima Wakatoshi.
Ushijima-kun!
Waka-kun!
#4, Ohira Leon.
#5, Tendo Satori.
Yay!
#8, Goshiki Tsutomu.
#10, Shirabu Kenjiro.
#12, Kawanishi Taichi.
#14, Libero, Yamagata Hayato.
Yeah!
Coach, Washijo Tanji.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please cheer on both teams
and wish them the best.
I'm totally starting to feel their nerves.
I thought they were doing okay when I saw
the one shot Hinata took after their warmups.
This is a path they've gone down many times.
On the other hand, our guys
are facing their first finals,
and their first center court.
You can't blame them for being nervous.
Since it's their first finals,
is this their first five-set match, too?
Five sets?
Up until now, they played three-set matches
and whoever got two sets first won.
In the finals, they play a five-set match
and whoever gets three sets first wins,
just like the top-level games you see on TV.
What?! That's gonna be super tiring!
Yeah...
I'm worried about their stamina.
We can't be the ones who are down!
This is a different start than usual.
All right, let's go!
They usually start with a strong
server or Hinata on the front line.
Aren't they going to try to match up
the highest wall possible against Ushijima?
They'll have to see how they
handle their serves, too.
Shiratorizawa           Karasuno
Bring it!
...but words from someone who lost to Aoba Johsai
and couldn't even stay in the
prefectural finals mean nothing to me.
Daichi-san, nice serve!
Got it!
Ushijima-san!
It's coming!
I got it.
Be Courageous Warriors
Nice kill, Ushijima!
Ushijima! Ushijima!
Don't mind!
Next, next!
Shiratorizawa               Karasuno
Well hello, Left.
So, what's up with your disguise?
A cap and huge sunglasses are
like the classic disguise!
Oh, yeah. Kageyama-kun had
a similar disguise before.
See?
That just means you're both
equally simpleminded...
Episode 02: The Threat of "Left"
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"The Threat of the "Left."