The landscape around here has become a lot spikier.
Our depth is...
Let's see...
6,750 meters, I think.
Riko, I can see something down there!
It's the Goblet of Giants!
It's fine - it's just hot water.
Still, it is terribly humid here.
The goblets of giants...
the flat-creepers are responsible for that.
I also hear the landscape is blue due to the mixing of
the vapor they put off with the light from the force field.
Oh...
You know, the part that supports the flat-creepers
is actually a different plant.
The prey-trapping mechanisms of all these creepers
stretching out before us wither up every 2,000 years...
But it's said that then the plants below
all compete to grow,
giving rise to a completely new landscape.
So those are prey-trapping mechanisms?
Amazing...
It's quite amazing...
We actually made it here to a place like this.
Compared to how I envisioned it in my dreams,
it's so much damper.
And my voice echoes like CRAZY!
It smells kinda vinegary here, too.
Reg, let's go!
Riko...
We need to find a decent place and make camp.
You might not say it out loud,
but I'm sure you understand...
That no matter how much we gloss over it,
this place is right in the belly of the netherworld.
The strain of ascending in the fourth layer
makes you bleed out of every orifice in your body.
It truly is a curse...
If Riko's body was to undergo that, it's likely that...
No matter what...
protect her!
The fourth layer...
Commonly referred to as part of "the depths,"
the probability of returning from this layer is so low
that the third layer can't even begin to compare.
Sprawling out here are the netherworld's goblets,
which fill up with and spill out
various lives and aspirations.
Will those who reach out their hands
be presented with fine spirits that quench their thirst,
or will they instead receive a burning poison?
Daremo ga sakaraezu ni mogutteiku
Sono me o tomoshibi yori kagayakasete
Mezasu saki wa fukaku
Massugu ni mayoikomu
Kuchiaketa naraku no wana
Shinjitsu no ato o oikakeyou
Ima kotae ga mitsukaru nara zenbu nakushitemo ii
Sono koe o hanasanai youni kodama ga mada hibiiteru
Rashinban wa zutto
Yami o sashita mama
Nigeba no nai
Hou e
Sore ga noroi demo
Kodou wa honmono
Nidoto akogare wa tomaranai
The final section of the third layer
had those spiky eggs, right?
Yeah...
If one hatches...
I hear it'll become one of those squid-looking things.
That species still hasn't been given a name, though...
But, you know, less than ten percent of
the creatures in the Abyss have even been named.
There are tens of thousands of species that-
Shh!
What's wrong?
Never mind...
I'm sorry.
For a little while now,
I've been sensing a strange presence...
Huh?
What is it? A creature?
Don't tell me it's a White Whistle...
It only moves while we're talking.
It's not moving right now...
But it very likely has good hearing...
And I bet it can understand our speech, too.
I suppose it could be also be another cave raider
other than just a White Whistle...
It's certainly strange...
I can't even begin to pin down its position.
It's kind of eerie...
Maybe we should get out of this place...
Good idea!
These "umbrellas" and the steam provide good cover,
but walking here is difficult and visibility's bad.
Riko, you alright?
Yeah...
At the very least, we need to find
somewhere we can camp.
What's the matter, Reg?
Was it this one?!
No, don't!
Reg, run!
That's an orbed-piercer!
Reg, don't fight it!
I was told that an orbed-piercer's spines
can penetrate even steel...
They're also laced with poison, and more than
one hundred cave raiders have already been kill-
I didn't sense it until it got close!
So this is a beast of the depths, huh?!
Wha...?!
The backpack...!
I thought I dodged that...
It's fast!
Or rather...
it predicted my line of retreat!
Reg, the Blaze Reap is...!
It's down by its feet!
This is bad...
What's with this creature?!
Does it actually know what that thing is?!
Be careful, Reg!
The primeval creatures of the depths that
Ozen was talking about have amazing intuition like that.
Here it comes!
Reg, take this!
It should recoil from things bigger than itself!
So, use this Scaled Umbrella!
Alright!
Halt!
I-I don't think that thing was nearly big enough...
It didn't work, Riko!
Let's make our way toward the Blaze Re-
R-Reg...
Th-the poison will...
We need something to constrict it...
S-sorry, Reg...
Reg!
Riko, this is going to hurt a little.
What should I do?!
Riko, hold out your arm.
What do I have to do to save Riko?!
The Blaze Reap is...!
Damn!
It's submerged...
Even if I act as a decoy,
Riko can't search for it in her current state.
My Incinerator?!
No!
If I faint for two hours, what will become of Riko?!
Escape...
Escaping is our only option.
However, given its quickness
and ability to predict our movements...
we won't be able to shake it by running.
If that's the case...
Up it is!
But, the strain of ascending in the fourth level is...
intense pain throughout the body and bleeding...
Riko!
Do it... Please.
Y-you say that, but...
Please!
I'm sorry, Reg.
Seems... I don't have... much time...
Riko, pull yourself together! Riko!
Please wake up!
Reg...
Reg, what's the matter?
I feel kinda strange....
Riko, what are you talking about?
Get a hold of yourself!
Oh?
It doesn't hurt that much...
What is this?!
Riko, doesn't it seem like the Curse of the Abyss caused
the poison to be expelled first before your own blood?
I see...
Well, now to just stop the bleeding and...
Yes... That's it...
Reg...
I'm... alright...
After... the poison's out... stop the bleed-
Riko, wake up!
Reg, I'm alright...
Damn it! Now she's also hallucinating!
Is that 'cause we're close to the third layer?!
After I wipe the blood, more streams out...
Calm down!
At any rate, I need to check on the wound...
I-it's swelled to several times normal size...
H-her glove... I need to take it off.
D-did that hurt? Sorry...!
Reg...
Riko! I'm here!
It's, uh... too swollen, so I can't get the glove off.
What should I do?
What can I do to save you?!
Does it hurt? Please just say something.
Cut it...
Huh?!
Cut it... off.
A-are you out of your mind, Riko?!
If I do that, you'll...!
R-Reg...
Please...
If you don't...
I-I'll die...
Reg...
I'm scared...
I'm so scared...
Reg...
Back then...
if only I had made Riko stay farther behind me...
First...
you need to break the bone.
A Black Whistle who had this happen...
said that cutting it off was tough.
Back then...
if only I had quickly used my Incinerator...
if only I had been a better shield...
This is no time to cry!
The more I hesitate, the more Riko suffers!
Here it goes, Riko.
Wh-what am I even doing...?
Reg...
Don't leave me!
Riko! It's me! I'm right here!
Don't... go...
Me, too... together... to the netherworld's... bottom...
Riko... your consciousness is already...
I'll definitely take you there!
You've got an awful fever...
Don't YOU go and leave ME behind...
Hurry...
Hurry!
M-my hands are shaking...
Pull yourself together!
Otherwise, Riko will suffer all the more!
Damn you! Don't get in my way!
Not near Riko! Stay away from Riko!
Get outta here!
Damn it!
She's not breathing!
Riko!
Please breathe!
Riko! Riko!
Riko!
Riko...
hold on...
Don't leave me behind, Riko!
Riko!
Open your eyes!
Please open your eyes!
Riko!
You're so noisy...
That girl...
Her heart is still beating...
It's likely to stop any moment now, though.
Wh-what are you?!
I'm a just a fluffy stuffed doll.
I've come here to comfort you two...
Wh-what?!
Just who the heck are you?!
I'm happy to properly introduce myself...
but first wouldn't it be best to hear
about how to save her?
Riko...
This's quite bad...
What should I do...?
Please tell me! I want to save Riko!
What can I do to get her breathing again?!
Just blow a breath directly into her.
Like a kiss, you know, a kiss.
Do you know how?
Like that?!
That's the way, but go a little slower.
And pinch her nose shut.
Okay!
Also, tilt up her chin to open her airway.
Otherwise, there's no point to this.
Got it!
She's breathing again.
I'm so glad!
Thank you!
I can't begin to express my gratitude...
It's still too early to relax.
Huh?!
Well, it seems she's not regaining consciousness.
Th-that can't be!
What should I do?!
Calm down!
If she was to wake right now,
it's not like she'd be able to bear the pain anyway...
But...!
You, come on and carry the girl back to my hideout.
Huh?
I'll find a way to do something for her...
Really?!
Even though you don't know anything about us?!
Well...
Just keep a little distance between us, okay?
Still, the way things stand now, her arm will break off...
You need to reinforce it,
so hurry and fetch some branches.
So you can do something about her hand?!
Understood!
But let me warn you:
It's not going to go back to the way it was before.
Jeez, he's not even listening...
H-hey, hold on!
Hm?
If I climb up this, Riko will...
Well, I guess you can't see it then, after all.
Huh? What?
What are you talking about?
Just take it easy.
The Curse isn't present right now, you see.
If we don't hurry, her whole body
will swell up like her arm has.
Damn it...
What is this place...?
Cave-raiding equipment...?
Besides that...
Are those... whistles?
H-hey... who exactly are you?
Ah! I suppose I never told you my name...
I'm Nanachi.
I'm what you cave raiders would call...
a Hollow.
Sora ni ukanderu hikaru nami o
Tabanete niji no hashi o kakeyou
Ayaui ashiba, suberu slope
Kako to mirai no michishirube
Kimi no hidarite, boku no migite o
Tsunaide tsunagete hajimeyou
Itsumo soba ni iru yo
Kako mo ima mo mirai mo
Dakara mayowazu ni aruiteikou
Irotoridori no yume kasanete
Ashita wa doko ni mukau
Kimi to issho ni iretara, sekai wa kagayakidasu yo
Saihate no chi ni saku hana o sagasou