What is that?
Isanami?
I shall destroy everything.
Return to the abyss!
Isanami!
This is...
Rokuro!
You mustn't get up yet!
Sir, this darkness...
Is this Isanami's doing?
We must act before the darkness
consumes everything.
Don't strain yourself.
You're not fit to move yet.
Troubling you would be the greatest
dishonor as your servant.
However, I can still see the prophecy of
Izumo that was engraved in my lost eye.
I must go.
Rokuro.
Let's hurry.
Sir.
I am grateful.
The Warrior of Light
Isanami!
This foreboding atmosphere is wonderful.
Isanami...
Is she the goddess of death with the
dark power to destroy the world?
No...
I will destroy everything.
No.
My dark self is growing...
I see.
This must be a control device.
With the Kushimitama, I should
be able to bend her to my will.
Hanzo!
I can tell you're desperate to
recover the Kushimitama,
but what are you thinking?
If you're not trying to kill me,
you don't stand a chance.
This is where your
lukewarm team gets you.
Your desire for nice little
friendships makes you weak.
A ninja's only ally is himself.
You can only count on your own ability,
your own body, your own senses.
You think someone who has forgotten
these things can fight me?
This isn't even funny.
What a sad man.
What can a man who only thinks
of himself do with that power?
What do you want to do?
I'll do far more than a fool who doesn't
even attempt to use such power.
Because I think only of myself,
my actions are pure.
Besides, this power is too great for you.
You have none of the exceptional
qualities of a great man.
Truly irresolute.
It is your fatal flaw.
The ease with which the ice infiltrated
your defenses speaks to your weakness.
I'm a generous man.
That woman took my bait
hook, line, and sinker,
while spouting idealistic nonsense about
the restoration of her homeland.
She played her part well.
I suppose she was a useful tool.
Shut your damn mouth!
Ana was never your tool!
She was putting her life on the
line for what she believed in!
It's something you'd never understand.
Saizo!
You might as well be shouting at nothing.
Just watch from down there as the
darkness falls under my control.
It won't be that easy.
She will do anything I teach her to do.
Pure destructive power.
Perfect for a man of pure desire.
Come, Isanami!
Isana...
Why?
I have the Kushimitama.
She should obey me.
The darkness will consume me!
It rejected Hanzo...
and the Kushimitama?
Rokuro?
Rokuro-san?
The prophecy under Izumo...
"When the power of darkness rises again,
dispel it with the lives
of the nine elements."
If it's true...
The prophecy of Izumo?
You mean the inscription?
I lost my right eye,
but I am still one of the
warriors of the elements.
If my life will do anything
to stop the darkness...
Rokuro, no!
Yukimura-sama!
Please forgive this final
act of disobedience.
Rokuro!
Rokuro, Saizo!
We're supposed to stop this
darkness with our lives, huh?
Bring it on.
Saizo, you saw what happened to Hanzo.
That isn't Isanami any more!
Act carelessly, and it
will destroy you, too!
That's Isanami!
Acting without thinking and
causing nothing but trouble.
She's grown into a bigger form,
but nothing else has changed.
Prophecy?
I'm not going to let that bullshit rule me!
Saizo.
I'll cut open that darkness
and bring her out my way!
Isanami!
Wake up already!
Everyone's waiting for you!
United by our common identity as braves,
we could face any opponent.
That's our true strength.
I don't know much about fate,
and I don't care either,
but because of you...
I feel like we rallied around you!
Isanami!
Without you, we'll always be one short!
Saizo!
Saizo has...
Is this...
Is this what you really want, Isanami?
Isa...
The gods will save mankind.
Naturally, those who serve
the gods will save men.
Do not be so arrogant, Seikai.
Even the gods cannot do everything.
Then what are gods?
According to the Buddhists,
chanting invocations alone will save you.
No good will come from staying
in this narrow-minded shrine!
I'm leaving!
I will find the true
meaning of the gods!
Onii-chan.
Where are you going?
Isanami.
It's already dark. It's scary outside.
It's all right.
Stay here and wait like a good girl.
Okay! Bring me back presents.
She was smiling then.
I thought that smile would
always stay there.
What a disaster. Is everyone dead?
No, I heard one of the
priestesses survived.
I must find her.
I must teach her, now that I
have achieved enlightenment.
Isanami is waiting for me with a smile.
But now...
Everything I believed in...
Don't give up, old man!
You've got me. Give me a try.
I lost.
The gods I believed in
have abandoned me.
Then believe in your friends!
Believe in me!
If we work together,
she doesn't stand a chance.
Done.
Benmaru Special Explosive,
Hinokagutsuchi!
What is this?
Are you ready to die, kid?
Hit it!
What's going on?
The darkness is confusing the insects.
Sasuke!
Right.
This ends now.
Koga Hi-Ougi.
Mangokusatsu!
How weak.
You thought that would
be enough to get me?
Move, and it will cut deeper.
Poison?
It burns!
My face!
No!
How pathetic.
Let me put you out of your misery.
I gave you the pain you wanted.
Not that you can hear me anymore.
I haven't felt this way in a long time.
Good, good, good!
This red world is fantastic!
Let me show it to you!
Isn't it great?
Not that you can hear me.
I'll be taking this back.
Hekireki Hoko!
Shocking, isn't it?
Not knowing my abilities
was your undoing.
Breaking your ice was no trouble.
Was the jolt too much for you?
Well, I've lost too much
blood to get it up,
so I guess we're even.
Hey, you're pretty warm after all.
Promise me...
Promise me you'll return, Saizo!
I'm alive.
This thing hasn't lost its power, then.
Isanami.
Saizo.
Leave.
I'm scared.
Then what're you doing in here?
Let's go!
I wanted power.
I will take a thousand lives.
I wanted to protect everyone.
I will take them again and again.
But it's too late!
I'm not human anymore.
I can only hurt you.
My heart is full of darkness.
What are you talking about?
Of course it is.
Everyone's got some
darkness in their heart.
You're not any different!
I cause everyone trouble.
So what? I've gotten used
to it since meeting you.
What's gotten into you?
Bring on the forceful personality
and ridiculous fantasies.
Don't run from them now.
I've had enough.
My heart hurts!
Your heart hurts because you're human!
Don't you remember what you told me?
You said you'd always believe in me.
You sounded like an idiot.
Are you saying that was a lie?
I don't care if you're a human
or some goddess of darkness!
To me, you're just you!
You're one of us!
You're one of the ten braves!
Come out, Isanami!
Saizo!
Saizo, Isanami.
Old man.
I knew you were the light.
You dumb girl.
Wake up, idiot.
Ow!
Yukimura-sama.
I...
I'm glad you're all right.
Let's go home.
Okay.
Good work, guys.
Everyone...
You guys are looking good.
Saizo.
You're so bright.
How ludicrous.
I can't believe it was fake.
I've been looking for you.
I'm surprised you can move so
soon after taking my bolt.
You're chasing me now?
Good work.
Do whatever you like.
I don't mind letting you off the hook.
What are you saying?
Saizo and Sasuke would
never forgive you.
Don't you mean the lord?
You're right. I don't think
even he'd forgive this one.
After all, I am a traitor.
I have no regrets, but my dream is gone.
I have nothing left.
Nothing left? Sounds nice.
When you have nothing left,
you're free to do as you please.
It's a chance to start over.
So? What're you gonna do first?
You're right.
I'd like to do something
about how terrible I look.
A dark power to consume everything?
Even if such a power exists,
we should not seek it.
Ieyasu must truly be a fool
to want such a thing.
However, we must do something
with the power we have.
We will defeat Ieyasu.
This is getting interesting.
Yukimura, the next time we meet
will be on the battlefield.
I see you're including
me in your numbers.
It seems the real treasure was not
the Kushimitama, but the girl.
Well done, Sanada Yukimura.
You are not to be underestimated.
But, even if we know
what the treasure is,
we must still be careful.
Masamune-sama, where to?
We'll attack head on.
We'll take on Ishida Mitsunari,
Naoe Kanetsugu, and all the rest.
We just have to start a war!
A big one!
It's time to shake the world!
It's like it never even happened.
Saizo, today's the day.
You promised we'd go until I gave up.
Saizo!
Kamanosuke's quite obsessed with you.
But Kamanosuke's not the only one.
Isanami won't stop whining
when you're not around.
Can I ask you something?
What?
Did you gather us knowing
what would happen?
How could I predict such a thing?
What sort of answer is that?
We almost died.
If you had told us before...
Could you have stopped it?
More will come seeking her power.
It may cost us more next time.
However...
I'm counting on you to
handle it when it happens.
It's all on the braves, then?
We're just like pawns in the
palm of your hand, then!
You're pissing me off!
Don't be so angry.
The only thing I can do is believe in you.
I may be another pawn
moved by an unseen power.
Some large power like a civil war.
Guys, let's eat.
Manju, huh?
Why'd you bring so many?
Aren't you each going to eat ten?
Are you stupid?
I'm not stupid.
Ten times eleven is 110.
That's not what I'm talking about.
Don't you have any limits?
What's your problem?
I made these for everyone.
Why can't you just say thank you?
No one asked you to make them.
You can be so annoying.
Hey, Saizo.
You bastard, how dare
you insult Isanami?!
Onii-chan, the tea!
If you spill it, I'll never forgive you.
Okay.
These are delicious.
Miss, these are really good.
Aren't they?
I'll make them every day from now on.
I'm on snack duty starting today.
Snack duty?
What's that?
You each have your own duties.
You decided for us.
Ben-chan, your job's heating the bath.
Listen to me.
I'm good with fire.
Don't side with her.
Onii-chan, you're on strong duty.
Leave it to me.
That's not even a job.
Kakei-san, you'll make the beds.
What?
Found you, Saizo.
Kamanosuke, your job's to be quiet.
What'd you say?
Amaharu is mine.
Squirmy!
Then there's...
Give him back.
Hold on, that's enough.
Why? I worked hard on these.
We don't need jobs.
But we will need a captain
for the ten of us.
Kakei-san, why don't you do it?
I decline.
I make frequent trips away from Ueda.
Then what about Sasuke?
He's a monkey, so ruling this mountain
should be right up his alley.
You're so short tempered!
Not the issue.
What'd you say? Get ready, you monkey!
No, prepare yourself.
Stop it!
What's gotten into you, Sasuke?
I am not the captain.
What?
That is your job.
Huh?
What? Is that why you got mad?
Do not say it again.
Saizo!
No fair.
Why won't you fight me?
You're so annoying.
What a noisy castle.
You've got some nerve.
Bring it on!
Fin.