Sakura-chan isn't with you, is she?
We can't find her anywhere!
Sakura-chan's missing?
Joyous Fighting
It was the beginning of a long night.
Sakura! Sakura!
Sakura!
Sakura-chan!
Sakura, where are you?
She's been spirited away.
Grandpa, there's no such thing.
Erika, what's illustrated
here isn't fantasy.
It's even said his first victim
will be a young child.
I heard she was heading
towards the ocean.
This is the work of the dragon.
Ten-year-old Usami Sakura.
Approximately 144
centimeters tall.
What is her connection to JF1?
I do not know yet.
We do not know JF1's
current location either.
It will be too late if we
wait for something to happen.
We should secure JF1.
Find the girl first. Hurry.
Tapioca, what should I do?
Sorry, everyone.
I won't do it again.
Good.
Sakura!
Where did you go? Sakura!
Nii-chan, watch out!
Come on, Nii-chan. Let's go.
Sakura!
Where'd you go?
Damn it.
Natsuki, calm down.
I know!
I'm sure we'll find her.
I'm sorry for what I said earlier.
But, I really do think
Sakura-chan was sad.
I think she might have been
overwhelmed by all her pent-up
feelings and sadness.
Are you saying Sakura
chose to disappear?
That's impossible.
Sakura would never do that!
Stop.
I don't know.
I don't know anything about
parents or siblings.
My parents are gone.
I don't think they'll ever come back.
I'm sure families have
a lot to deal with,
but I'm jealous of you.
I've never laughed or
fought with anyone.
I'm sorry I don't understand,
but I'm worried, too.
Don't act like you're alone.
Sakura!
Where'd you go?
Sakura...
Natsuki.
When searching for someone,
you must put yourself in their shoes.
This is nothing more than
my personal opinion.
I believe she went to see her mother.
What does that mean?
Think. Only you know the answer.
I don't care about Onii-chan
any more. It's his fault.
I won't apologize to him.
Sakura.
Onii-chan!
I'm... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
So this is where you've been.
We came here with Mom.
Whitebait ice cream. We had that here.
You must have been lonely.
I'm sorry I didn't notice.
Mari-chan.
Sakura-chan.
Yuki, I'm sorry.
Akira.
Thanks.
Mari-chan, I'm sorry.
It's fine.
It's all right, Sakura. I'm sorry, too.
I'm glad. I'm so glad you're all right.
La la la, dum ta-dum.
Good, good, good, good.
Haru.
Why don't you tell me the truth?
I'm sure you already know,
but I am a member of the
alien investigation and
apprehension organization, Duck.
Why did you come to Earth?
We came to catch him.
Him?
Do you mean the beast
under that bait ball?
Yeah, he's one of our kind who came
to Earth a long time ago.
He's been traveling
Earth's oceans doing naughty
things like moving ships around.
Alien life forms really are
responsible for Bermuda Syndrome.
We don't know what he'll
do if we leave him be,
so we came here.
We came here to catch him
and take him back home.
How did you plan to catch him?
The only way to subdue him is
to get him out of the ocean.
Communicating using water's
normal for our kind,
but for some reason,
when we try to use water
to talk to people,
we end up controlling them.
We don't get along well
with humans at all.
And he forgets his own strength a lot,
so he's really dangerous.
Is that why you intended to
fish him out of the water?
Yeah. I was going to
catch him with Yuki.
Why didn't you try to
catch him yourselves?
We've never fished before.
Besides, if we're not careful,
we'll be affected by him
and go crazy, too.
We were going to have Yuki catch him
while we suppressed his powers.
He was strong.
He took total control over me.
He really is strong.
I'm not even sure if the two
of us together can stop him.
It's not too bad now,
but if he gets even stronger...
What will happen?
His voice might even reach
people through the moisture in the air.
What if the humidity were
to suddenly increase,
such as when it rains or storms?
That'd be the worst.
If the air's filled with water,
everyone on Earth
will fall under his spell
and dance the Enoshima Dance.
Thinking about it makes me hurt here.
Go back to your planet.
Let Duck handle this.
Catching him won't be easy.
Regardless, you tried to involve humans.
Now that I know that,
I cannot allow you to
continue what you're doing.
What's a whitebait cafe?
It's a whitebait cafe.
I said...
I'm renovating the place.
Instead of whitebait and Enoshima bowls,
I'm gonna sell all kinds of stuff.
Whitebait bowls, whitebait pizza,
whitebait ice cream, whitebait steamed buns.
You're overextending yourself.
You can't be sure until you try.
Everything's like that.
If you think of something, try it.
You won't know until you try.
Do whatever you want.
What are you gonna do?
I'll... I'll think about it.
Do whatever you want.
Just keep moving forward.
I'm sure you'll be happier that way.
As long as you're serious about it,
I'll support you.
Thanks.
When he's by himself, he's thinking
about something important.
Isn't that right, Nii-chan?
Why don't you take a bath?
Okay.
I'm glad Sakura-chan is all right.
Yeah.
I...
Yes?
I was so happy we found Sakura-chan.
Yes.
Natsuki's going to have a new mom.
I'm really happy for him.
Yes.
You can tell me about it.
I don't know anything about families,
so I don't know about
parents or how he feels,
but I just wanted to
tell Natsuki something.
I couldn't help it.
I said I was jealous of him.
Since then...
I've been messed up inside.
I realized I must have been
lonely for a long time.
But I could never say it.
I mean, saying it wouldn't have helped.
I thought saying something would've
screwed everything up.
But I... Grandma, I...
Yes?
I've got people I can
talk to about this.
When I realized I could tell him anything,
I was just so happy.
Yes.
I was lonely, but that was fine.
I can't go back,
and I'm not embarrassed
about what happened.
I had you.
I've been fine with having
you as my dad and mom.
That's why I'm grateful to you.
I love you, Grandma.
Yes. I love you, too.
Thank you.
No, thank you.
Koko.
What?
Koko, do you like Enoshima?
I do.
The whitebait's good,
and everyone's so nice.
I love it.
I like it, too.
I love it!
Nii-chan, what's wrong with you?
I've decided. I've decided!
Nii-chan, you're an idiot.
You really are an idiot.
Oh, come on.
Welcome home, Haru.
I'm back.
Is your sadness all better?
A little.
I see.
Keito, are you all right?
Yes. Thank you.
Eat lots and rest lots.
I will.
Don't carry anything heavy.
Okay.
That's all.
Haru.
What?
What do you say when you leave?
Good bye.
That's right. Be sure you
say it when the time comes.
Okay.
Don't leave without saying anything.
If you do, I'll be mad.
Okay.
Be nice to everyone until you leave.
Smile and hold your head high.
No fair, guys!
We haven't settled our match yet.
We'll let size decide.
The guy who catches the smallest one...
Another punishment?
I'll play, too!
You said you wouldn't fish any more.
I will. I'll do it!
Okay, bring it on.
Eno... shima... Bowl!
I wish I could stay like this forever.
I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
Forget what I said! How embarrassing.
Me, too.
I wish I could stay like this, too.
Even if the world ends tomorrow,
I know I'll be fishing.
The world won't end.
It'd be sad if it ended.
I love Enoshima.
I had fun. Everything was fun!
Don't talk like you're leaving.
Sorry.
Yeah! What are you talking about, Haru?
Sorry, sorry.
Got one!
Seriously?
Haru, calm down!
Okay. Raise your rod,
and... What was it?
You're hopeless.
Yuki, it's okay. I can do it myself!
Akira, 62 centimeters.
Haru, 56 centimeters.
Yay!
Yuki... 78? Seriously?
Yuki, you're amazing.
What about you, Natsuki?
Huh? I...
Natsuki...
43!
Natsuki, punishment! Bi bi bi bi biii!
Well, I'll let you guys off easy today.
You're bitter.
It's fine. I'm going to catch a bass.
A black bass. A really huge one.
You're aiming to be a professional?
Isn't that a lot of work?
You won't know until you try.
I know you can do it.
Thanks.
Akira, Natsuki's punishment.
Who, me?
What do you want, Akira?
There's something that's
been bothering me.
Yeah?
Natsuki, don't you think
your hair's too long?
What?
What are you smiling about?
I've got scissors!
Seriously? Stop!
Yuki, isn't it great?
Huh? Is what?
Everything's fine now.
What are you talking about?
Those bastards.
Onii-chan.
Oh, sorry. I woke you.
Your hair!
They went and cut it.
So? It looks good.
You're terrible.
I've never done this before.
Watch. It's like this.
Onii-chan.
I love Mari-chan.
Yeah.
But sometimes I want to talk about Mom.
Yeah, let's do that when
it's just you and me.
Okay. Hey, do you remember
that time on Mom's birthday?
Tapioca, I've made my decision.
This isn't the opinion of an individual.
It is the objective opinion
of a Duck investigator.
Thank you, Tapioca.
Yuki.
No, it's nothing.
What's up with you?
You've been acting weird today.
I know now
what Haru tried to say to me then.
This is Yamada.
I have important
information regarding JF1.
JF1 is not a dangerous alien.
He holds the key to explaining
Bermuda Syndrome.
Good work, Yamada.
We have sent a combat unit to Enoshima.
A combat unit?
We have determined the unusual
events occurring in the
vicinity of Enoshima to be the
product of Bermuda Syndrome.
Our mission is to attack
and remove aliens
who pose a threat to humankind.
JF1 is one of them.
Please wait! Haru is...
JF1 is not dangerous!
I have confirmed this with my own eyes!
Are you really Yamada?
Are you really a proud
investigator of Duck?
Haru was telling the truth.
The typhoon which appeared
in the ocean,
west of the Mariana Islands,
is slowly growing and
moving north towards Japan.
Danger was at Earth's doorstep.
We didn't have much time left.
Continued in #9