Jeez, who's here this late?
What do you want?
Did you get dumped again?
What do I do?
If we don't do something, we'll all...
Please help,
Meika.
Punch Line
Meika, I've gotta ask you...
What were you doing around four this morning?
Where's this coming from?
Just answer me!
I think it was around 3:30.
Rabura showed up all of a sudden
and started babbling nonsense.
Of course, I didn't believe her at first,
but I figured I could at least
look into it for her.
Oh, God...
What's wrong?
I don't know what's going on,
but the server was fine.
There weren't any viruses,
and no signs of hacking...
The Fall
Meika used the satellite connection
to hack the AFSPC servers.
The Qmay Group physically
intercepted that connection,
using that device.
They've already used the
AFSPC server to launch
several dozen nuclear missiles
from the U.S. military satellite.
Soon, they'll arrive at VR-1,
where they'll all detonate at once.
That'll change VR-1's trajectory
just a little bit—straight for Earth.
Why didn't you tell me?
Humanity's future has to be
determined by humanity itself.
That's the law in the spirit world.
Nine Years Ago
No! I won't let you!
Why not?
Because that's...
What's the matter?
Give it back already!
No!
Give it back, I said!
Are you okay?
Guri-chan, you jerk!
Hey, Guriko.
Wait here.
I'll put some antiseptic on it.
No.
You suck at applying it.
I want Guri-chan to spray it on me.
Please, Guri-chan, spray it on me.
All right, fine.
It doesn't hurt, does it?
Nope! Thanks, Guri-chan!
I'll start with the conclusion.
The Human Preservation Project was a failure.
There's no chance
that you'll ever arrive at a supremely
peaceful and happy future.
Man,
how can you be so nonchalant about it?
Well, there'll be a next time for me.
Not for you, though.
To be honest, I secretly
had a lot of hope for you.
I thought you could lay down
a new rail, an unknown future
like none the world has seen.
But now that it's turned out this way...
Honestly, I'm a little disappointed.
Well, you know you're going to lose.
Now you have to prepare for your defeat.
I don't need to tell you
what you have to do, do I?
You have to pass the baton to the next Yuta.
Pass on that hope.
Indian Holy Text
Nandala Gandala
Yuta?
Oh, so you are home.
You look awful.
What's wrong?
I didn't say you could come in.
Are you feeling sick or something?
Just leave me alone!
What's this?
"Nandala Gandala"?
Going through your pretentious
middle school phase?
A fantasy diary!
No!
Who cares what it is?
What do you even want?!
We're all getting together for hotpot tonight.
Why don't you join us, Yuta?
Tonight?
Ito in danger!
Hey, Ito, have you gotten any weird emails?
Weird emails?
Telling you to come to the
shrine tonight, or something.
No, I haven't.
Oh.
Okay, then.
Why?
No, it's nothing.
Don't worry about it.
So, how about that hotpot?
Are you in or not?
Where?
It looks like it's going to stick.
Ito sure is late, though.
What's she doing?
She said she was going to get milk for Muhi.
Maybe she went to some farm to milk a cow.
I'll go check on her.
I'll go with you.
Ito-chan?
It couldn't be...
What is it?
Inbox
To: Narugino Mikatan
Subject: No Title
I have Ito.
Come to Ishinogari Shrine.
Bring Iridatsu Yuta with you.
Wait!
You stay here!
You know I can't do that!
Tomoda should be in the hospital, immobilized...
Who the hell is it?!
Ito-chan!
Don't worry.
She's just sleeping.
You're...
from the bus hijacking!
It can't be...
That scar...
Guriko.
What a strange reunion party...
Originally, it was supposed
to be me in Chiyoko's body,
Chiyoko in Pine's, and Pine in my body.
Guri-chan, why?
There's a favor I want to ask of you two.
A favor?
I want you to become Ws.
W?
I see, so Chiyoko's completely clueless.
And if I refuse?
I'll kill her.
Put the gun down.
Put the gun down now!
No, Chiyoko!
Your body's already...
Ito-chan is...
Ito-chan is my
precious friend!
Are you okay?
Mikatan...
Poor thing.
You're approaching your limit.
But don't worry.
If you become a W,
your body will recover naturally.
In fact, you can stay Uberfied indefinitely.
Isn't that fabulous?
Don't be fooled, Chiyoko!
Everything he says is a lie!
You can't become a W.
W's still...
I'm lucky it was just a finger you broke.
If it had been my arm, it would
have taken three days to fully heal.
No way...
Don't you need Muhi's regenerative
capability to create a W?
Did Tsubouchi's spirit tell you that?
That old man didn't know anything.
Ws are already complete.
I'm living proof.
I was giving false reports
to Tsubouchi the whole time.
Why?
Because he'd get better otherwise.
He was finally getting weak from the Uberfying.
The Qmay Group's ideals in
and of themselves are great.
I truly love the Qmay Group's teachings,
from the bottom of my heart.
That old man drowned himself in money
and carnal desires from day to day.
Honestly, I'm glad he's dead.
We can't have that perverted,
vile old man at the top of
the organization forever.
Guri-chan...
Guriko doesn't exist in this world anymore.
She's dead.
What happened to you, Guriko?
All suffering in this world stems from
the fact that humanity is imperfect.
Therefore, humanity must
evolve into perfection.
I became his disciple,
received a new name,
and rose to the top ranks.
At this point, I have full authority
over the whole Qmay Group.
I've waited a long time for
this moment of revolution!
All this time...
Alone.
But
I've found my friends.
On December 21st, we miraculously
met again on that bus.
I missed you, Pine.
Isn't this destiny?!
Guri-chan...
What happened to you?
I've missed you all this time.
I wanted to go shopping
and see movies with you.
I wanted to walk around
town having pancakes
and cream anmitsu until
we couldn't eat any more.
I've been imagining that all this time,
waiting for that day to come.
And yet... yet...
This isn't destiny!
Go back to being the Guri-chan I loved!
The old humanity will soon perish.
If you want to be saved,
you'll cut ties with the
imperfect and become a W.
Then, I'll let you on our ark.
You have two more days until your time is up.
Think it over just one more time.
Understood?
Unbeijini nyopurasara,
I'm going to put a spell on you.
Unbeijini nyopurakura,
I'm going to eat up your demons.
The magic song isn't working at all.
Why, Pine?
Hey, what's W?
What does he mean, humanity's going to perish?
You don't have to worry about a thing.
I can't just ignore it!
Because I'm...
a hero of justice!
Saving humanity is the duty I've been given!
There's nothing else we can do.
It's over.
Everything is over!
To be honest, I secretly
had a lot of hope for you.
I thought you could lay down a new rail,
an unknown future like none the world has seen.
I've been really scared.
You're insensitive.
Why aren't you saying anything?
I got disowned.
Mikatan, what are you doing?
I'm going to protect you, Muhi.
You seriously piss me off!
Are you all right?! Hang in there!
Yu-tan, hear me out!
He might hate me if he finds
out I'm a fake exorcist.
Don't come any closer.
Spirit-san, spirit-san, if you're here, uh...
Hey, what's up with you?
Shoot me, if you're going to shoot.
Isn't that right, Iridatsu?
I was born here in Korai House.
Strange Juice, move out!
Who's that, then?
I call it the Tou-maker!
What are you talking about, Narugino?
Have we met before?
You give me a really nostalgic feeling, somehow.
Good evening-ning.
Well, I was thinking we should have a party.
Thanks.
Sorry!
Korai House is the best!
I missed you, Pine.
Pine!
All right, Chiyoko.
I was wrong.
I was about to give up on everything.
I thought there was nothing else we could do.
But that's not true.
That's not it...
That's not it at all.
There's nothing in this world
that we can't do anything about.
I'll lay down the third rail.
I'll make a new future.
A new future?
Yeah, a super happy and peaceful one.
What are you talking about?
Anyway, don't worry.
I swear I'll protect you.
And Meika, and Rabura, and Ito, and Muhi.
All life on Earth.
I'll protect
all of it.
And Guri-chan?
You'll protect Guri-chan, too, right?
Yuta, this history is a mistake.
It's a future that mustn't happen.
Change this history.
Many of me have attempted it
and made the same mistakes.
Still, I leave my hopes with you.
No, all of our hopes.
You're going to change destiny. History, Yuta!
Hey, don't just bust in like that!
Sorry, but we have an emergency.
An emergency?
Pumpkin Chair, I need your
help to save humanity.
Iridatsu!