See ya.
S-See you later?
I thought it was pretty.
Huh?
This fish has scales
I've never seen before.
"Fish"?
And you...
This sake is rather weak.
Must be dog piss.
Perfect timing.
My side dish to go with my sake is here.
Um...
What is it?
Take that!
Take that, and that,
and that, and that...
This isn't the taste of
Mukaido's granny's cooking.
I-I made it.
Oh?
I did something rather rude to you...
and wasted some food on top of that.
Are you... going to curse me?
Episode 2: The Chilly Desert
Good morning!
U-Um...
Th-Thank you for yesterday.
How are you feeling?
Y-Yes, I couldn't be better.
How's he doing?
He?
U-Um,
I'm doing well.
I-I mean...
Thanks for taking care
of Manaka yesterday.
Hii-kun?
I'll tell you right now.
Surface people have no business concerning
themselves with the Village of the Sea...
Um... Jeez...
Hii-kun!
Hii-kun! That was really rude!
Seriously?
I heard about it! You had a rough
time because of him, right?
What? That's not true.
It's because of the surface people!
He's guilty by association!
B-But... Tsumugu-kun saved me!
"Tsu-mu-gu-kun"?!
Huh? Wh-Why are you so mad?!
You're suddenly sounding
so buddy-buddy with him!
Huh?
Th-Then Tsumugu... san?
W-Well, I don't know his last name!
You're acting really
strange lately, Hii-kun!
And you're always so angry!
Oh, is that right?
Huh?
What's wrong, Manaka?
Eh?
I-I messed up!
"Messed up"?
Tsumugu-kun saved me...
But Hii-kun worried
about me a lot, too...
and I yelled at him.
I messed up!
Yeah.
Hikari was really worried
about you, Manaka.
Chii-chan.
Really worried...
Even though his Ena was dry, and
he couldn't breathe that well,
he was really determined...
Y-Yeah...
Hikari isn't really mad.
So try not to be afraid of him.
That'll just annoy him even more.
Okay.
How do you know all this, Chii-chan?
About Hii-kun's feelings and my feelings.
Well... It's because I've been watching
you guys since we were little.
Both you...
and Hikari.
Hey, stop, Forehead.
Huh?
You're the two from the other day...
Do you know that woman?
"That woman"?
Oh.
Do you know her?
She's my older sister.
Liar! You octopus-head!
"O-Octopus"?
He was calling her by her name.
They've got to be a couple, Miuna.
Uh, I don't really know
what's going on here,
but shouldn't you two be in school?
Your teacher's going to get mad...
Don't treat me like a brat, you brat!
I don't need some brat telling me that.
What's wrong?
You brought backup, you cheater!
Seriously, you're one to talk.
Come on, Hikari.
You shouldn't pick on little kids.
Are you okay?
D-Don't touch me with
your fishy-smelly hands!
Oh, sorry.
Ow!
Sayu!
Serves you rice dumplings!
The hell?
All right, that's the end of class for today.
Oh, that's right.
Who here wants to try
to make an Ojoushi-sama?
What's an "Ojoushi-sama"?
Do you mean the doll we'd
send off in the Ofunehiki?
Right.
Originally, when the Ofunehiki started,
a girl would be sent off as a
sacrifice and offered to the Sea God.
Nowadays, instead of an actual girl,
we send off a wooden doll
called an Ojoushi-sama.
Why do we have to make an Ojoushi-sama?
Aren't adults supposed
to do that kind of stuff?
Oh, I heard they weren't doing
the Ofunehiki this year.
Yeah...
that's why we were
thinking of doing
something like a voluntary
Ofunehiki at our school.
What?
What the heck?
So annoying.
Hikari, calm down.
Is there anyone who wants to do it?
All right, Tsumugu.
Why do we have to...
This is the job of the surface people!
Then you shouldn't have volunteered.
The surface people don't have a clue.
That's why we have to
keep an eye on them.
Jeez.
Why did you offer to make this?
My family are fishermen.
We live off the sea, so I wanted the
chance to give the proper thanks.
That means we need to do the Ofunehiki.
I heard that Uroko-sama actually exists.
Huh? Yeah.
He's sort of a pervy old man though.
He's sort of in between an
old man and a young guy.
I see. So he does exist.
Then what about saltflake snow?
When salt falls down like snow.
Oh, and if sacred fire
burns inside the sea,
then how do you actually
get it to go out?
You know quite a bit, Tsumugu-kun,
about Shioshishio.
Yeah.
On days that are really sunny,
because of the refraction of the light,
there are times when you can
just make out the village.
White roofs reflect
light among the swells...
Just like the sound of waves,
I can hear singing resound
farther, then nearer.
I think the Village of the Sea is great.
For someone on the surface to
care so much about the village...
Isn't that great?
What are you talking about?!
Oh, it's about time you
sea kiddos headed home.
We'll do the rest.
Thank you.
Bye!
Thanks for your hard work!
Be careful heading home!
Sensei.
I have something to ask of you.
Sensei called us "sea kiddos."
That was actually kind of cute.
I sort of get that he's not a bad guy...
But...
Hey, isn't that Akari-san?
Akari?
K-K-K-Ki...
No, Manaka!
I wonder if that's her boyfriend...
She never even mentioned having a guy!
Not to mention a guy from the surface?!
Akari-san is reaching the age when
she's old enough to get married.
I wonder if she plans
on leaving the village.
What?
There's no way it'd work out
with a guy from the surface.
Even if they got married, she'd
end up coming right back.
Huh?
That's not possible.
Not possible? Why?
Of course it's not possible!
Because Akari-san looks like
she'd make a great mom.
She wouldn't end up coming right back.
That's not what I meant.
If you end up with someone
from the surface,
you'll be banished from the village.
"Banished"?
What the hell—that's
an awful thing to say!
What are you yelling at me for?
I believe that rule's
been around for a while.
I've never heard of that!
But Satsuki-san from the candy store,
and Koji-niisan from
the Hara-san's family
went up to the surface and
never came back, right?
Oh...
I always thought that the
people who didn't come back
just didn't come back because
they threw away the sea...
That's so mean!
Manaka...
There's nothing wrong with wanting to become
family with the person that's precious to you.
It's a wonderful thing!
And for them to be chased
out of the sea...
Does that mean... you think you want
to get with a guy from the surface, too?
S-Stop it!
I hate it when you say
perverted things, Hii-kun!
And I hate it when you say
perverted things, too, Manaka!
I haven't said anything like that!
You did too!
You're really grossing me out lately!
Manaka, wait!
I understand how you feel, but
that was so mean to Manaka...
What do you mean you "understand"?!
What?
What the hell is with you, always
acting like you're the adult?!
You act like you know everything.
What the hell do you know about me?!
Uh...
That really wasn't right.
You just took it all out on her.
What?
I understand why you'd get
irritated with Manaka, but...
See ya.
What the hell is with those guys?
Repeating that they understand
like a broken record.
Even I...
don't really understand
exactly how I'm feeling...
The saltflake snow is pretty intense.
And since no one cleans it up...
It would have been nice to be
able to stay at Nami Junior High.
So you think things like that, too...
That you want to stay here forever.
It's not that I don't like
the people on the surface,
but I want to stay in the sea forever.
With Manaka, you... and Hikari.
You want to stay here just
because that's easier, right?
Eh?
If you start longing for other
places, it'll become difficult.
It's sort of unexpected.
The fact that Manaka was the first one
to take the first step out of here.
Akiyoshi, Ukita, Kamon...
Kihara Tsumugu.
Kihara-kun, Kihara-kun, Kihara-kun...
Now Hii-kun won't get angry.
Kihara-kun...
If they got your DNA,
it sucks to be them.
You idiot! You saw the
footage! It was super cute!
Oh, man...
H-Hey, Akari...
Today, you...
And this is our baby!
How cute!
Oh, how cute. Does she
look more like you?
Aw, it's a girl... I'm envious.
When I have a kid, I want
it to be a girl, too.
Well, she might have her father's eyes.
Huh?
I wanted a younger sister.
Lately, she started mimicking
me. Did you know?
I was totally bummed when you came out.
I didn't, but what does she do?
What was that?!
I really am envious...
If I say "me," she'll say "me" back,
and if I say "mo," she'll say "mo."
But if I say "memo"...
If you end up with someone
from the surface,
you'll be banished from the village.
Your baby will continue to grow.
It's a lot of work, but
every day is a lot of fun!
Spoken like a true mother.
What happened to the
girl from Shioshishio?
Oh...
She's fine.
I see.
A guy from the surface, huh...
I just... wanted to protect her.
I wanted to protect her like Ena does.
I wanted to protect her from
everything that could hurt her.
And yet...
She wants to cast off all of that?
Cast off everything...
And go to the world outside...
I wonder how big the kimono should be.
Oh, um...
Tsumu—
Kihara-kun!
What's up?
U-Um...
We were wondering how wide the
Ojoushi-sama is around the waist.
One sec.
I wonder why it still sounds pervy...
even when I use his last name.
Oh... It's n-nothing.
How's he doing today?
He... seems to be sleeping today.
I see.
65 centimeters.
Th-Thanks.
So Manaka really does...
Not to mention,
if Manaka were to disappear,
the one next to Hikari would be you.
I'm awful... What am I thinking?
This is...
They apparently used to keep carp there.
Oh! I-I'm sorry.
There was still garbage.
It's a little small for
four people to get in.
"Four people"?
Oh!
I'm sure it'd be annoying always having
to consider the time while you work.
Sensei said it'd be fine to use as well.
What? You're going to make
a watering hole for us?
Would it be a bother?
N-No! Not at all, thank you!
That's good.
The girl with the really round eyes...
You mean Manaka?
I hope her fish is happy about it, too.
"Fish"?
Please don't... be so
kind to Manaka anymore.
Manaka has...
Hikari.
Curse me, please!
Exactly why do you want to be cursed?
Um, w-well...
because it hurts to lie.
Why are you lying?
Well um...
I'm not sure...
You've always had
someone protecting you.
Hikari, Chisaki, and Kaname...
You should have just kept
stumbling along behind them.
And now you're trying to go
somewhere they can't protect you...
You may need a small lie
or two to protect yourself.
Huh?
Please don't!
Stop...
Just get over here, Akari.
You're gonna have to tell us
everything in front of Uroko-sama.
Let go of me! I'll tell my dad myself!
What's going on?!
Akari?!
Oh, Hii-kun!
This doesn't concern you two.
Just stay out of—
Wait. It's about time they know too.
What?
Just what happens when you
break the rules of this village.
"What happens"? What
are you talking about?!
What's the matter?
Dad...
So you've come, Chief Priest.
Akari is seeing a guy on the surface.
Someone saw them.
I'd like you to leave for today.
Chief Priest...
I will talk to Akari myself.
Chief Priest, this is a problem.
If someone from your family
ends up leaving for the surface,
it's going to look really bad.
Yes, I know that.
You guys, leave.
Huh? B-But...
Akari...
You're so cute.
You've got horrible taste in guys!
You can say that again.
Did you just fart, Uroko-sama?
Akari's crying because of you!
Episode 3: The Legend of the Sea
A storm's coming.