I Can't Help Being in Love!?
Die, die!
Serious Squadron!
Gachi Rangers!
Live-action superheroes...
Face me, if you dare!
How insipid.
Are you okay, Red?
Darn, what incredible power!
You're finished, Baby Rangers!
Okay, everyone, our hearts must be as one!
Yeah!
Gachi...Knuckles!
Argh...That won't be enough to-
Gachi Suplex!
Die, Dogron!
Curse you, Gachi Rangers!
Dog...ron!
We will end all hatred and anger!
What're you doing?
You telling me to clean up my face?
Yes...
Ick...the wind's getting a
little too frisky today.
I wanna tell them how awesome
the Gachi Rangers were.
I want them to understand.
But I doubt anyone in this
crowd would get it.
How sad.
Gachi Rangers has been
really good lately, huh?
That new superhero show?
I've only caught bits and pieces of it,
but the black ranger's actor is pretty cool.
Yeah, yeah!
Umm...
Oh please, you watch Gachi Rangers?
That's for kindergarteners.
I just saw a glimpse of it while my
little brother was watching!
'Scuse me...
I...I didn't even know you were there.
I...I saw...
I saw it...too...
Saw what?
A ghost? A ghoul? Or maybe a poltergeist?!
N-No...
Let's go.
W-Wai-
What did you see, Youngest-san?!
A ghost, in the science lab.
What?!
I want to tell everyone about
the Gachi Rangers...
Morning, Hitoha-chan.
Good morning.
Who's texting me...
That ringtone...
Hmm?
You know the opening to Gachi Rangers?
Not really...
I'm actually really into 'em.
I try not to broadcast that, though.
Umm...did you see yesterday...
Did you see them?
I didn't see anything!
Oh...you didn't see them?
Gachi...Suplex!
Would you be happy if I had?
They're something else.
Really...
What amazing self-confidence.
But I never expected Hitoha-chan
to watch Gachi Rangers.
I wonder if she saw yesterday's episode?
You...You watched, didn't you.
I sure did!
That last blast was awesome,
I was pumped!
Gachi Knuckle!
B-Blast?!
Blue's my favorite, though!
S-Sensei...
Huh? Wh-What?
She's acting very distant all of a sudden...
Wait, she never actually said
if she LIKED the show or not,
but I just started rambling like a total spaz!
Well, I know it's a kiddie thing but
plenty of adults are into it too.
It's like...a hobby, or something.
H-Hobby?!
If you stick with it you'll understand
how great it can be, Hitoha-chan!
Don't touch me!
Hey, don't look at me like
I'm some kind of freak!
Or are you one of those "all
otaku are sick" types?
You're not an otaku, you're a pervert!
I'm a pervert because I like
superhero ranger shows?!
I see! Well, you can't help what you love!
I feel this hot, burning passion
every time I see them.
It's romantic and manly at the same time!
You should be executed, Sensei!
How...could you...
The Gachi Rangers...ARE wonderful...
G-Gachi Rangers?
Why's Sensei on his knees?
He's crying...
We will end all hatred and anger!
It's...It's...
It's a show for perverts!
He's dead!
I really DO love the Gachi Rangers...
My Gachi Rangers!
Mitsudomoe...
Whoa, who's this hunk?
That's me back in high school.
N-Now that I look closer he's fugly!
Who's this, daddy?
Oh, that's me when I was
in sixth grade, I think?
I guess I forgot to put it in a sleeve.
Can I keep this one?
Sure, just take good care of it.
Now you'll always be with me, daddy!
Keep it in your backpack, please.
I'm telling you, shape's more
important than size.
Whatever.
Man, I dig it when they do
the cotton wrap thing.
Ogata Airi
Leader
Hopelessly in love with Satou
Itou Shiori
Katou Mayumi
I win!
We lost again...
We sucked in a ton of Satou-kun's air.
Now we'll be able to make
it through the day.
What's this?
What is it?
Holy cow!
A naked picture of Satou-kun!
It's got a bit of glare to it, but a candid shot of
Satou-kun like this has gotta be worth millions!
Kamobashi Elementary Picture Auction
Hey, how'd you get that picture Futaba?!
It's my FAVORITE.
G-Give it to me right now!
I love him a billion times more than you!
Never.
I love him the most!
We take a bath together every day!
No...way...
Oga-chin, wake up!
Oga-chin!
"And then, Kakimoto-kun wondered...
Uh...Is this bravery, or-"
Boobies...
Whoops, I meant Takihara-kun,
not Kakimoto-kun-
Poor little Futaba's/
She always leaves herself wide open.
Now what?
We'll make color copies
in the teacher's room.
We need three each, one for looking, one
for saving and one for around town!
N-No...we just wanted
to make c-c-copies...
Futaba!
Talk about passion.
This is the fourth floor!
We don't stand a chance...
Where'd daddy's picture go? Where could it-
The picture is mine!
Oga-chin!
Cut it out!
This photo's my treasure!
I don't care how close you are to him...I
won't let you...keep it to yourself!
I've always loved him!
I won't lose to you!
You can have it, then.
Futaba...
I didn't know you loved him
that much, Oga-chin.
So you understand I'm your rival now?
I know, let's all take a
bath together tonight!
As friends. No?
I'd love to!
Oga-chin's so lucky...
Duckie, duckie...
A bath with Satou-kun...
With Satou-kun!
Satou-kun!
He's coming...here he comes!
S-Satou-ku
Duckie, duckie...
NOOOOOOOOOOOO!
Shin-chan!
Morning, Shin-chan?
What's up with the skirt?
I need your help with a little
research project...
Research? Sure, I guess...
D-Did I give you a show?
Explain...what you're researching...
Well...
If people can see my panties!
Who thought of this stupid idea...Chiba?
How'd you know?!
It's so obvious...
Micchan can't wear this skirt
anymore 'cuz she got fat.
Don't run around telling
people your sister's fat.
Chiba said I should do some panty-related research
since I'm actually wearing a skirt for once!
Don't just do whatever he
says without thinking!
Plus he said I might get extra credit if I do
an independent project...Chiba's so smart!
You won't.
Next is the high left kick!
Whoa, whoa! Why ME?
Chiba said that you wouldn't close your eyes
'cuz you love panties so much, Shin-chan!
HE likes them the most! I swear!
D-Did you see?
N-No...I couldn't even see you move...
Next is a right-
No! Stop it!
Some-one-help-me!
Chiba!
Why are you messing with me like this?!
I know you saw that time!
Wait...Seriously, stop this!
That's enough!
Hopelessly in love
with Satou-kun Squad
We're the "Hopelessly in love
with Satou-kun Squad!"
What're you doing to Satou-kun!
He doesn't like it!
Stop this instant!
THAT is why I'm messing with
you, you lucky bastard!
It's...not my fault...
Shin-chan loves panties so
I'm showing him mine!
She's aggressive!
If we don't act Satou-kun will...
...end up liking Futaba!
I-I'll show you mine...
Me too...
Me three...
Satou-kun...
Good lord!
You're all insane!
Wait, Shin-chan!
We won't let Futaba have you!
What's up?
The other class...
We're gonna show Satou-kun
our panties so he'll date us!
Huh?
For real?
If you show him your panties...
He'll date you?
Your panties?
And he'll make you his girlfriend!
I could be his girlfriend?!
Found you, Shin-chan!
LEAVE ME ALONE!
Pan-ties pan-ties pan-ties!
Crap, the girls in the other
class want him too?
But I won't lose to anyone!
Help me, Chiba!
You started all this when you told Futaba-
It's GOTTA be your face!
So it doesn't matter WHAT kinda deviant pervert
you are as long as you're handsome, is that it?!
I'm not a pervert!
He...
The first person to show him their undies...
Chiba wins!
Chiba...is gonna be Satou-kun's lover...
Chiba...
Satou...
If only I was 50 years younger...
Forget it!
Mitsudomoe!
Someone has stolen Gachi Pink's underwear!
Who did Gachi Red and Gachi Blue
see at the scene of the crime?
Next time on "Serious Squadron
Gachi Rangers,"
"Monsters need Underwear too!"
We'll beat 'em next week, Gachi-style!
This program was brought-
This week's Gachi Rangers was awesome.
Gachi Knuckle!
I never knew there was such
awesome stuff on now!
I'm glad I got up early!
How long have you been there?
About 30 minutes.
Don't tell anyone what I was watching.
Why?
Because!
Then Red hit him with the Gachi Elbow!
Yeah, yeah! That was sweet!
And Pink's boobies were just-
Futaba...I told you not to tell anyone...
I didn't say YOU were watching too.
Hitoha-chan was VERY mean
the other day, you know.
If you mention that you like Gachi Rangers she
calls you a pervert and tells you to drop dead.
I...umm...See...
Despite the fact that it
really is a great show!
Yup!
So like I was saying...
Which makes our answer 7/15.
Next is Hitoha-chan.
Hitoha-chan?
Hmm?
Read the next problem, please.
W-Which one?
Page 128, problem five.
Pay attention please.
Weird, Youngest never messes up in class.
She's been spacing out a lot lately.
Maybe it's love!
No way...
You really like romance
stories, huh Yoshioka?
To Yabecchi?
Yeah...we had a misunderstanding and
I insulted him, so I want to apologize.
And...tell him that I feel the same way.
Oh cool, good luck!
Hey Futaba, what's the holdup?
Hey Shin-chan, I'm coming!
S-Sorry...I overheard you.
I didn't know.
Youngest-san's in love with Yabecchi!
I'm rooting for you!
Umm...
That's right, she...
Gachi Rangers has been
really good lately, huh?
Th...Thank you.
I appreciate it.
Feel free to ask me anything.
I'm Yoshioka Yuki, by the way.
I know.
Oh of course, we're classmates after all.
I never would've guessed, Youngest-san.
I just can't get enough.
I even have tapes.
I stay up watching them all night.
T-Tapes?
I can't stop watching.
Youngest-san, that's...
Tapes of Yabe (stalking)
Stalking!
I wanna start collecting stuff, too.
S-Stuff?!
Underwear / Used bottle / Used straw
Used chopsticks / Spare key
Like stuff Yabecchi used?!
You certainly are passionate...
I just love every little bit.
Yesterday was incredible.
Yesterday?
Like that mega-hit he landed
with his elbow.
You...he hit...
It felt awesome...
Everyone experiences love
differently, I guess...
Apparently Sensei's into it, too.
But I...I got the wrong idea and
called him a sick pervert.
You weren't wrong at all.
Hmm? What? You don't wanna talk anymore?
Oh no...I didn't mean to...
Of course. You're part of our
group too, Yoshioka-san.
Oh no...now I'm an accessory because
she told me everything...
I'd better get going.
You're going to do it?
Well, best of luck!
I hope you tell Yabecchi all about
how much you love him!
Hitoha-chan...you're in love me?
Y...Yabecchi!
Oh...Oh no, he heard me before
you could tell him!
I...we...no! That, that isn't happening!
H-He said no!
Youngest-san!
What do I do?
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry!
Save me...Gachi Rangers.
We never got to show Satou-kun
our panties.
We can't give up yet!
We've gotta keep at it until he gets
an eyeful of our underwear!
But...
Episode 8
RUNNER
If he's gay then maybe we'll see
Satou-kun's underwear instead.
That's it!