The girl I fell in love with
at first sight, Rebecca,
has successfully become
Pastillage's Hero!
I gave wings to the adoration
that I always held in my heart
and invited her into the skies.
That's the power of our treasure sword!
So let's go!
Let's bust in on Millihi-nee
and Leo-nee's war!
I'll do my best!
We unexpectedly have three now!
Pastillage's hero,
Rebecca, was just born!
Becky's a...
...hero?
Go, Rebecca!
Show them the power of Pastillage's Hero!
I will, Cou-sama!
With the Sacred Sword Mercurius.
Three Heroes!
I do this to turn.
She's flying!
Pastillage's Hero, Rebecca,
has mounted a broom and is
now soaring through the sky!
I have to push these buttons together
to change gears, and for special moves.
I did it!
Our Hero isn't the
only one who can fly!
Awaken, Heavenly Spear Crimaris!
My Bright Power Gear!
Pastillage's Princess Couverte
is joining the battle!
Go, Skyer!
Rebecca and I are going
to turn the tide now!
The Pastillage army's morale went up.
Couverte-sama seems to
be quite popular, too.
Rebecca!
Cou-sama!
Looks like my eyes didn't deceive me.
Your flying is great!
I've fallen for you once again.
Thanks!
This is kind of made like a video
game, so it's pretty easy to use.
I think I can handle this.
Next, you've got to attack.
Just do it like I showed you before.
Okay, Cou-sama!
Here I go!
What's that?
It's coming this way!
Really?
Here's my palette card set.
Fire!
She can freely control
those shots of light!
These are not emblem cannons!
Their trajectories cannot be predicted!
What a show!
Looks like fireworks.
Yeah.
That's Pastillage's Crystal Magic Shot!
Rebecca is a mage-type Hero, after all.
Rebecca-sama's got the
skies under control.
All right, we're going to join the attack!
Yes!
Our target: their main force!
All units, halt!
Mobile artillery unit, arm your weapons!
I won't let you go any further!
All units... fire!
Rebecca, our allies need help!
Okay.
We're taking down Rico's anti-air unit!
I'll help you!
Roger!
Looks like Hero Rebecca and Lady Couverte
are charging in together!
Everyone, intercept them!
Roger!
Hero Rebecca is dodging every
single shot in that bullet hell!
Wow, you're doing great, Rebecca.
I guess my experience with
3D shooters is helping.
Please miss!
Take that, Rico!
Garnet Spark!
She got us!
You're finished!
Excellent disrobing, Rico!
Cou-sama, how could you?!
All right, Rebecca.
Let's split up again and
attack their main force!
Got it!
I'm going to Galette,
you go to Biscotti.
What?
Go, Rebecca!
It looks like Hero Rebecca and
Couverte-sama have split up again.
Is Couverte-sama attacking
the main Galette force?
Couverte's attacking by herself, huh?
Go back, d'Arquien!
I will go head her off by the main force!
As you wish.
On the one hand, we've got the
Hero Rebecca flying off
to attack Biscotti!
Our Princess readies herself on the
rooftop to counter the attack!
In her hand is the Holy Sword Excelide!
Before that...
You'll have to fight us, Becky!
Rebecca-sama, watch out!
Infernal...
Neptune...
Twin God Fist!
She dodged it?
Explosion shot!
I did it!
That was amazing!
It looks like Hero Becky
destroyed Hero Sink
and Hero Nanami in one hit!
That was a shock...
Becky's incredible.
This is actually really embarrassing.
Hero Nanami's equipment
has been completely destroyed!
Your Majesty, I hope you're ready!
You won't get me.
They hit each other!
Both Hero Rebecca and
the Princess Millihiore's
armor are destroyed!
I'm sorry, Princess!
I'm going to retreat for now.
Of course! I hope I'll see you later.
Yes, Your Highness!
They are friends!
Even in the heat of battle,
they remain friends!
It makes one smile.
How is Galette doing?
Leo-nee, come out.
Fight me!
If you're looking for me, I'm over here!
Eek, Grand Vert?!
That's right!
This is Galette's holy sword,
Grand Vert, the demonic battle axe!
I've got nothing to lose...
Garnet Spark, maximum power!
Eat this!
Demon God Wind Slash Carver!
Huh?
Why?!
Leo-sama is not
"Peerless" without reason!
She bisected Couverte-sama's
signature move perfectly!
I thought I could maybe do
it with enough momentum...
In the fighting that
proceeded from there,
the heroes were the center
of excitement for all...
Time's up!
The battle is over!
And the final results:
As expected, the Galette Lion Army won!
As expected, indeed.
Thank you!
In second place, we the Biscotti
Republic, who unfortunately
could not best Galette's score!
In last place, we've got the
Principality of Pastillage.
That's too bad.
Oh, it hurts!
The war was a roaring
success to the end.
In the castle town,
a lively celebration
for victors of Biscotti
and Galette was held.
Which means we lost the war, but...
But Rebecca's already our Hero
and I don't want to give her back!
Is what she's saying...
Umm...
We can't do anything.
Talk to the responsible ones.
You, Heroes Sink and Nanami!
Yes!
Pastillage is right next to Biscotti,
and I'll make sure you'll have
plenty of time to spend together.
So please, let me keep Rebecca!
I'll join that request.
I want to stay Cou-sama's hero.
Then it's totally fine.
Cou-sama, please...
take care of Becky!
They asked me to take care of her!
But still, I don't think
they need to separate on the
day they arrived, right, Couverte?
Yes?
There was something I wanted to discuss:
a matter concerning all three countries.
So would you stay here
for about two days?
During that time...
The three Heroes are free
to do as they please.
Just relax.
Yes.
Thank you, Leo-sama.
Cou-sama, your ears are so cute.
Princess.
So Sink...
Will you take me on a walk
again, in the morning?
Yes, of course.
We can bring Rebecca and
Nanami, too, if they'd like.
Roger!
Let's all go!
On a walk?
All right then...
...we're off!
Palladion Form: Flying Disk!
Go Princess!
Okay!
I got it!
Nice catch!
You're so good, Princess.
You're so cute!
Millihi's so good!
Sink is treating a country's
princess like a lapdog.
Yeah, but I can
totally understand it.
I always want to pet Leo-sama
and the members of the Genoise.
You were petting the hell
out of them yesterday.
They said I was a very good petter!
That's good!
Pet my neck... the neck, the neck!
Yes...
So don't you ever feel
like petting Cou-sama?
I do!
Especially her bushy tail!
Ahhh, I say!
The princess is really cute, too.
Yeah, huh?
Sink is lucky to get that treatment.
Rebecca-san! Nanami-san!
Let's do it together.
Okay!
Then let's give you a
tour of the castle.
Let's go!
Let's start off with the kitchen.
Long time no see!
Welcome back, Hero!
You brought some cute friends.
Hello!
The Hero and I got a lot
of our snacks and treats here.
I see.
Here you go.
Eat up!
I'm so full, and so happy!
Rico, you shouldn't let yourself go like that
in front of other countries' Heroes.
Oh, it's fine.
Don't mind us.
Now I'm embarrassed.
Rico, do you like Sink?
I love him!
He's our country's Hero after all!
He always plays with me,
and he naps with me and snacks with me!
He pets me and he holds me.
Him being a hero's totally irrelevant.
This is the knights'
training grounds.
Hello!
Captain, Heroes, join us if you like.
Okay!
Shall we have a match then, Hero?
Fine by me!
I trained while you were gone, too.
Looks like Eclair-chan's does
the extreme catch, too.
It's all because of the hero.
See if you can handle my
newly leveled sword skill!
Take this, Hero!
Thank you.
Didn't Sink used to wear
the wristband that
Eclair-chan's wearing now?
Yup,
that was Sink's favorite.
Rico-chan, are Sink and
Eclair-chan friends?
They're a great combination.
You never get bored watching them.
Oh, welcome!
We've all been waiting for you.
A Japanese style building?
Thanks for having us over.
Stay as long as you like.
Make sure to get your cuddles from them.
Once again, it's been too long, Hero.
It has.
You look well, Lady d'Arquien.
Yes, Yukikaze and I are well,
and all the Onmitsu,
it goes without saying.
I am so glad that I was able to
welcome Rebecca to our country as a Hero!
Now all three countries have Heroes.
The war game matches are going
to get really interesting.
That's right! And Rebecca was even
more powerful than I expected!
She's waaay kinder and
cuter than I even expected.
I'm so happy!
You look happy.
If I were a boy, I'd propose
to her right away!
I'm sorry I'm late!
Cou-sama, are you going
to propose to someone?
Maybe I really should just do it!
I'm back!
Hi!
The bath hall is really big, isn't it?
Yeah! It was amazing!
Huh? Where's Nanami?
She said she was going to call home,
so she went over to Rico's.
It's pretty amazing that a
cellphone can call another world.
Yeah, thanks to Rico's invention.
Tatsumaki and Cheney can now
deliver letters and packages, too.
Oh, so that's how the organization
and invitations worked.
It's another world, but Flonyard
feels really close and familiar.
Being summoned and sent off used
to be really difficult, though.
Sink, will you do my hair again?
Okay.
And what can I do for you, Miss?
A casual braid please.
Certainly.
Lately, I've been wondering...
how much longer we can be like this.
What do you mean, "like this"?
Like hanging out together
and taking trips together.
I'd like to do that forever,
even when we're adults.
Me, too.
Once you get a girlfriend though,
we can't do things like this anymore.
You think so?
Of course!
Well, but isn't it the same for you?
I guess so,
but I can't see something
like that happening for me.
What are you talking about?
You're really cute.
Well, who knows what will happen.
I keep thinking it would be nice,
if we could be like this for a long time.
I hope we're friends forever.
You're done.
Thanks, Sink.
But you know, aren't you a
little conspicuous over here?
What do you mean?
You're all lovey-dovey with the princess,
and then you're all friendly
with Rico-chan and Eclair-chan,
and then Yuki-chan and
Lady d'Arquien also spoil you.
I won't tell anyone, so tell me:
who do you like the most?
It's the princess, isn't it?
Eclair-chan?
It's not like that...
I mean... I am Biscotti's Hero,
so I think being friendly
with everyone is natural.
I'm not talking about
superficial stuff like that,
but how you really feel.
I'm telling you, there's
no deeper feeling.
I'm the Hero, so...
So? I'm a Hero, too!
Tell me! Tell me!
Nanami-sama, you're going
to Galette tomorrow, right?
That's right. I'm looking forward to
taking my time traveling the country.
Oh yeah, what's Sink going to do?
The Hero is spending tomorrow
and the day after tomorrow
with Eclair, Yukki, and Nowa.
They'll set up camp near the
Fuugetsu lodge for training!
So you're lovey-dovey with the
princess and Ricotta-chan.
And with Gaul-kun you have
this male friendship.
So what's going on with
Eclair-chan and the others?!
Biscotti Summer Camp!
Anyway, tomorrow we're going camping
with Eclair-chan and the others.
Tune in next time.