I see. So it was your mom.
I'm sorry.
It ain't your fault.
But-
Don't get cheeky now.
It's everyone's problem;
not just yours.
Know your own limits, idiot.
Tohru...
I'm sorry.
Episode 12
See ya.
Can't sleep?
Same goes for you.
It's hard to get rest on a chair.
You can take my spot on the bed.
Oh, but that'll leave you
in there with Minchi...
But I don't think she'll mind that...
What?
N-Nothing.
It's all right, I don't mind.
Maybe I can rest easier on this couch.
Tohru, do you... have a girlfriend?
What?!
N-Not at the moment, no.
Figured as much.
You don't handle women very well.
But I think you're very kind.
That's why I think you need to
believe yourself and to fest it up.
Fest-
I thought you were depressed
about your mom.
The real cause is your
boyfriend in Tokyo, huh?
N-No!
Well, if I had made the right decision,
he would have been my
boyfriend now, but...
But...!
So I was right, huh?
No you weren't!
Why won't you believe me?!
You talk a damn lot,
but your face also shows
what you're thinking.
I-I'm off to bed!
Good night!
I'd like to kidnap Satsuki Matsumae.
What?
Satsuki Matsumae has no intention
to visit the Kissuiso.
Thus, I will force her to.
Hey!
Take a look at this.
This is her place of occupation.
Taking account her path
to work from the station,
it would be most wise to
ambush her in this back
alley and kidnap her.
We've got a car, and
there are three of us.
We should be able to win
against her monstrous strength.
What do you think?
What do we think?
Sure.
Thank you, Tohru!
Sure, but it comes with one condition.
We're taking this Koichi
guy along as well.
What?!
Tohru!
That's the condition to have
my help in the kidnapping.
But...!
Okay, Minko.
Let's do some Tokyo sightseeing
until Ohana brings Koichi.
But the breakfast...
Don't eat any more of that.
You'll gain nothing from eating
cheap toast like this.
Tokyo has many famous places to eat.
It's also important to visit places
as a customer to train your tongue.
Y-Yes, sir!
The number you have dialed
is not in service or-
Dialing: Ko
He must be mad at what
I did yesterday...
I'm supposed to take him along?
I don't even know how to face him.
But then again, there's no way
I can kidnap Mom alone...
Wait, what does Ko have
anything to do with this?
Now that I think about it...
No, I don't even *have*
to think about it.
It's strange!
I can't get in touch with him via phone,
and I also went to his work
to see if he was around.
I did everything I can.
Yeah. That's right.
I did what I can.
Tohru will forgive me.
You're... Ohana, right?
Oh!
If you don't have feelings for him,
let him go already.
Let him go?
Yes, let him go.
That makes me sound like a villain.
I'm not even...
Well, I *was* trying to
kidnap him, I guess.
What are you talking to yourself for?
That's creepy.
What?!
When I say "let him
go," I mean his heart.
By the way, this bench is where
I asked Koichi out.
What?!
On that day...
Hey... sorry.
There's someone I like.
Are you going out with her?
No, she's deferring her
answer to a later time.
What the heck?! That's awful!
Nah, maybe that's not her intention.
Maybe I'm waiting for nothing.
But...!
It's fine.
I'm used to waiting, and...
I'm afraid of her safety if
I'm not watching over her.
It's not fair.
You've made a nest on his feelings
and you're resting on it.
I-I do like him.
I do like Ko, and...
And then you're going
to say something like,
"I don't like him as a boy. I
like him as a human being."
N-No!
Then how do you like him?
W-Well...
As a hu-
As a living creature?
Thought so.
She...
What?
N-Noth-
Hey, Igarashi!
Your break's already up, you know!
I'm sorry! I'll be right back!
Please make the decision yourself.
If you continue to step all
over his kindness like that,
I'll never forgive you.
Keep going straight for a little
while and make a right.
Okay.
It's... like a date.
Okay, eat!
Gladly!
Eat!
Okay...
Don't leave a single grain of rice.
That broiled fish was half raw,
allowing us to enjoy the
differences in texture.
But taking into account the residual
heat and the time it was served...
I don't feel too good...
Throw up!
If you need to throw
up to eat more, do it!
We didn't come to Tokyo for nothing.
We need to learn the tastes
of the famous stores.
Ohana's case comes after that.
The town Ko lives in, which is
the town I used to live in.
The dramaless town which I despised.
She... was a nice girl.
She's able to face her opponent
clearly and seriously.
But doesn't living in a hot
spring inn sound dramatic?
If there was a drama
with us starring in it,
I'd probably be the antagonist.
Ko
The doors are closing.
Please watch your step.
H-Hello?!
Hey.
Sorry, it looks like
I missed a few calls.
I was napping.
O-Oh.
Thank goodness.
The girl at work gave me a call.
Huh?
You came to the bookstore, huh?
Y-Yeah.
I-I mean, no, I just kinda dropped by.
You remind me of how I used to be.
What do you mean?
I actually went to your place
when I was on break from school.
My place?
When you were going to the wedding hall
to look for whats-his-face.
I wanted to pay the Kissuiso a visit,
but you seemed really busy.
That's why...
Hey, Ohana? You listening?
I'm the antagonist for real.
Huh?
Listen, I need to take
my mom to Kissuiso,
and in order to do that,
I need to take you too.
What?
You're not making any sense.
And that's why I called you.
You helped me back then too,
but I seeked help from you again today.
I tell myself that I need to
work hard and to fest it up,
but in the end, I'm only
thinking about myself.
I wasn't thinking about the people
who are looking over
me and cheering for me.
I've been terrible to you.
You don't need to come.
I don't really get what
you're saying, but... sure.
I won't go.
Yeah. Sorry.
Later.
See ya.
Ko tried to look over someone
awful like me forever.
Even then, I...
I...
I said "later," but he
responded with "see ya."
Does that mean there
won't be a next time?
Don't cry.
I'm not the one who
wants to cry the most.
Not me.
Bonboris...
I threw up...
Nice.
Time for sushi then!
All right!
What happened to eating sushi...?
Here.
Okay, what should I get next?
Does the fact that Ohana is out
with another guy bother you that much?
I haven't even been
away for half a year,
but it all feels so nostalgic.
The town I hate.
But I always liked it
around this time of day.
The lights that look like bonboris
appear as though they
lead to the future.
I'm not the only one.
Everyone has bonboris.
Even Ko.
And I'm sure Mom has one too.
I hurt Ko.
Ko was festing it up for me.
I was hurt by Mom.
But I'm sure mom was festing it up too.
Everyone is treading their
paths with their own thoughts in mind,
trying to sparkle.
Go! Go!
I'll get it this time for sure.
Yes, slowly...
I need to grab the tag on the thing.
I want to ask him.
After he gets that,
I want to ask him about his feelings.
Missing line
missingline
missing
Minchi?
Ohana! How was it?!
Well, about that Koichi guy...
Huh?
What?!
You gave up?!
I can't take Ko with me,
and I wasn't thinking about
my mom's feelings either.
Hey!
Where are you now?!
What about your luggage?
It's over here.
Wow. You can open up a shop with this.
They're souvenirs for the
folks back at the inn.
U-Umm... sorry I decided
everything on my own.
We're heading to your mom's place.
Huh?
Even though we're not
kidnapping her anymore,
I agreed with it at first.
I won't be able to rest
until I yell at her
about her article.
Once again, I was going to try
and fest it up on my own...
Nothing.
Okay, I'll lead the way.
Umm... she should be in that building.
Ohana!
You're late today!
What's with the luggage?
Huh?
Are those people from the Kissuiso?
Wow, how lucky am I to
have people pick me up?!
You told me you were going
to take me there, right?
I was able to take a few days off,
so I was thinking about
going to a hot springs.
What?!
Wow, you have good taste.
I can actually get you tickets
through my work, you know.
Really?!
I don't get it!
You kept saying no when
I asked you to come!
I told you.
I was able to take a few days off.
The Yunosagi area is a good
place to go to avoid the heat,
but... what's the name
of that new hotel again?
The Yunosagi Silas?
Yeah, that!
That place is too popular,
and there's no way I can stay
there without a reservation.
The Kissuiso isn't like that, right?
Hey!
Could it be that you wrote
the article because
Yunosagi Silas paid you?
Come on, who cares.
We care!
Weren't you going to say
something to her, Tohru?
Huh?
Well, since she's coming
to the Kissuiso,
we can have a chat later.
Sounds splendid!
Let's chat over a few drinks, Tohru!
Could it be that he likes older women?
Or...
Could it be this family in general?
Huh?
Oh yeah, did you meet Ko, Ohana?
Is Ko short for Koichi?
Yup.
Your boyfriend, right, Ohana?
N-No!
Hey! I like this song, too!
Minchi.
Thanks for everything.
Take this as a thank-
It wasn't me.
Huh?
Tohru was the one who worked hard.
He's a lot nicer than I'd thought.
I take that back!
He worked hard, but not
as hard as you think.
Care for a smoke?
I'm a chef, so I choose not to smoke.
How diligent.
So why did you decide to
come all of a sudden?
Like I said-
I don't believe you.
You're only a few years
older than Ohana, right?
You're very mature, Tohru.
I don't really know...
Ohana really went all out on me,
which reminded me of
some things in the past.
I said the same things as a kid.
You don't understand anything.
You're always so focused on work.
I've been holding back all this time!
Stop fighting!
Well, my mother's work is a
lot more honorable than mine.
How did you feel as you
were writing the article?
While writing to discredit
your own home.
I didn't include a single
lie in the article.
That inn really is boring.
But I don't think you can write an
article with just your memories.
I'm sure it hasn't changed.
But we're always trying new things!
Right.
No matter how much you
decorate the exterior,
what's important is
what's on the inside.
Having consideration for the customers
and making sure they enjoy themselves.
She's got it right.
Yeah. Mom's always right.
I think Ohana is a pretty
lucky girl, you know!
Having a Mom who isn't
right should be amazing.
What do you...
Tohru.
We should probably get going soon, huh?
Yeah.
But hear this. Ohana is weird.
The first thing she did
was to get mad at me about the Kissuiso.
There should be plenty of other things
to get mad at me about.
"Why didn't you contact me if you
decided to come back to Tokyo?"
Well... you're right.
I've been floating from place to place,
but I've really started
to settle down recently.
That's when I was planning
on giving her a call,
but she came to see me
before I could do that.
You wanna come back, Ohana?
She's asleep.
That's why I asked her.
Why didn't I ever wish
to go back to Tokyo?
Ko is in Tokyo.
But I can't go back to the way
I was with Ko anymore.
I can't...
Don't suddenly start
acting like a mother!
You'd better show me what's
so great about this inn.
Mom's also festing it up!
I had a dream.
You're pretty light, aren't you, Mom.
Episode 13
Shijima's Girl
(Broken Heart MIX)