We can't be together anymore.
Wait, Shione!
Why?
Let's work together,
like way back when.
We're all waiting for you.
We can do it, the five of us together!
I'll be waiting for you.
The Meaning of Goodbye
Nonoka, did something
happen with Shione?
I thought we were friends again yesterday.
She said she'd work on it with us.
Is Togawa holding onto something again?
No, it's my fault.
I—
Oh, come on.
Shione's just being shy.
Yuzuki!
She wants to be with us,
but she's too embarrassed.
You don't know that.
She told me.
I said, "Do you like
Nonoka or not? Tell me."
I'm impressed you asked that.
What did Shione say?
"Of course."
So don't be discouraged, Nonoka.
Thanks.
I'll be fine.
I trust Shione.
Hokubi Festival Invitation
Noel.
Shione.
Huh, aren't you with
Nonoka and the others?
Noel, there's something
I want to ask you.
What is it, Shione?
What happens to the saucer
once you grant our wish?
Once I grant your wish, I get
called over to another wish.
Just like when you all called me.
Is that...
"Saucer-san, saucer-san, please,
grant my wish."
Your wish is going to be granted soon.
Right?
Huh?
Huh, are you leaving already?
I'm going to see the planetarium, too!
Nonoka!
Noel.
Nonoka.
I want a ticket.
But is the saucer going to be okay?
It is now.
So I'm going to see the planetarium, too.
Noel and Shione...
Everyone's going to smile now.
Thanks, Noel.
I'm hoping to go to the Hokubi
Festival on Sunday.
How are preparations going?
We're a little behind.
We have three days to
do something about it.
Yeah?
Hurry up and eat.
Fine, fine.
Time to eat.
Morning, Nonoka.
Morning...
Wait.
Why are you all here?
Koharu came crying to us.
She's was all, "We won't make it in time."
You're here for the rice cakes, aren't you?
It's true that we need the help.
You should have asked sooner.
We need more than four
people to make it.
Looks like we can get it
done on time now, huh?
Dude, get to work.
How are you supposed to know what
to do if I don't give orders?
Say what?
We don't need your
orders to do our work.
Get busy!
Who do you think you are?
Nonoka, I'm sure Shione is...
Don't worry, Koharu.
Shione will come.
She gave a Hokubi Festival ticket
to Noel, just like everyone else.
So I trust
Shione, too.
Let's make this a success!
Yeah!
Ow!
Yes.
No, it's not like that.
There's nothing you need
to worry about, Dad.
But I want to get there
as soon as I can.
Friends
Sorry.
I know I said I wanted to stay.
Snow?
Yeah, it snowed already.
It's finally tomorrow.
Time really flew by.
Shione's coming, right?
For sure.
Of course she will.
Yeah, once we're all here,
it'll be like the old days.
We'll celebrate with
Koharu's rice cakes!
Come on.
Close the door. I can see everything.
Souta, come here, look.
What is it?
Planetarium This Way                    Planetarium on Display
What do you think?
What?
I was just thinking,
your hobby's turning out to be useful.
It's not my hobby.
Closed for the day.
Everyone's coming.
I'll need about this many.
Mysterious Supernatural Encyclopedia
How to Call a Flying Saucer (UFO)
You're going to believe me?
No one takes me seriously.
You believe it, right?
Yeah.
Then I do, too.
Thanks, Nonoka.
I bet we're not the only ones.
What are you two talking
about so secretly?
I want to ask you to do something.
Help me call a saucer.
A saucer?
Sounds fun.
A saucer, huh?
That'd be awesome,
if one actually came.
Everyone would be amazed.
We might end up on TV.
Sounds nice.
See.
We'll be famous.
For Koharu, Yuzuki and Souta to smile.
And Shione, too.
That was their wish.
That's it?
That's too easy. No fun.
There's one more thing we need to do.
When we call the saucer,
we have to think about
something we want.
A wish?
The saucer is supposed to be attracted
to our strong feelings that way.
So we have to make a wish?
Does that mean the saucer
will grant it for us?
I don't know about that.
Okay, but what if we have a lot?
Just pick one.
You're so mean, Onii-chan.
What about you?
Me?
I already have one.
What kind of wish?
It's a secret.
It might not come true if I told someone.
I wouldn't want that.
Saucer-san, saucer-san, please,
grant my wish.
Morning, Nonoka.
Morning.
Just in time.
Wait, not yet.
Noel-chan?
I promised to meet her here.
Nonoka!
Noel!
Nonoka.
Thank goodness.
The saucer?
No, it's okay.
Hokubi
Middle School
The Melody We
Want to Share with You
Here.
Nonoka, can you show Noel-chan around?
Huh? But...
Leave all this stuff to us.
I'll call you as soon as we find Shione.
Me, too.
I'll go around school with this.
Let's go, Noel.
Okay.
It smells so good!
Let's have something to eat.
Really?
Yeah.
What do you want?
Um...
That!
Red Bean Soup
It's so sweet!
Do you like it?
So good!
Would you like to try it?
It really is sweet!
Huh?
Oh, it's a red bean bun.
It's sweet, but it's
all so warm and tasty.
That's good.
Hey Nonoka, where's Shione?
Frankfurters                                     Fried Chicken
She should be here.
She might be at the planetarium.
Let's go meet up with Yuzuki and
the others when we're done eating.
Okay.
Thanks for the food!
Planetarium
This Way
The planetarium is in here.
Planetarium
Welcome.
Take your time.
Hey, where's Shione?
She's still not here.
Okay.
Hey, guys.
The Hokubi Festival's just starting.
I'm sure she's coming.
Yeah.
Good, Komiya's here, too.
I just heard from the teacher.
Togawa's absent today.
Wait here, Noel.
Hey, Nonoka!
I'm going to Shione's place!
Do you know where she lives?
Jeez.
Oh, come on.
We'll be okay here.
Go with her.
Noel-chan.
Do you want to see the planetarium
while we're waiting for Nonoka?
I want to see it with everyone.
Don't worry.
We'll all be here soon.
Just wait a little bit.
Oh, Nonoka.
I'm leaving for a bit.
Hey, where are you going?
To my friend's place.
Planetarium
Where's Nonoka?
Nonoka.
She's so fast.
Seriously, it's because you're
carrying that thing around.
You should text her Togawa's address.
Huh?
Where was I going?
Shione!
Wait!
Welcome.
Nonoka, where are you?
I saw her, but...
Yeah.
I'll look for her a little more.
There you are.
Nonoka.
I thought I told you
not to come near me.
Why aren't you coming
to the Hokubi Festival?
Everyone's waiting for you.
Didn't you hear me?
Or did you not understand?
I said I don't want to be with you guys.
Are you not coming because
you can't forgive me?
Maybe you can't forgive me after
I made you wait seven years.
But Shione, I—
You must be stupid.
I told you, I don't want to
hear what you have to say.
So stop talking.
Noel's waiting, too.
You gave her the ticket because
you wanted to see it with her,
didn't you?
I want us all to see the
planetarium together.
The meteor shower.
I want us to have fun
together like before.
To talk and laugh.
Shione!
Have you forgotten?
I'll tell you again.
Stop using my given
name like we're friends.
Use it again, and—
Shione!
I don't want to call you Togawa-san.
We're friends, aren't we?
I...
...hate you.
I don't want to see your face.
Or hear your voice.
We aren't friends or anything.
How can I smile?
I can't!
Because Noel...
I'm not like you.
I don't make promises I can't keep,
and I don't say things
to get people's hopes up.
Goodbye, Komiya-san.
Buttered Potatoes                                               Fried Noodles
I wonder if Nonoka found Shione.
Jeez, there's no point to this if
the five of us aren't all here.
I'm here to help clean up.
Sorry, we'll do it ourselves.
Leave the cleanup to us.
Really?
Sorry to make you come here.
No, well...
I haven't given up yet.
You're right.
Huh, where's Noel?
She was there a minute ago.
Maybe she went after Nonoka.
I'll go find her.
Wait!
Noel?
Yeah.
Noel!
Nonoka.
Next episode of Celestial Method:
"Where Wishes Go."
Enjoy.
Where Wishes Go