Town of Minami
Japan Server
City/ No Monsters
PVP Permitted
Skill Use Restricted
Entry Restrictions/ Yes
Exit Restrictions/ Yes
Eighteen cases of EXP pots left.
Those damned adventurers...
Magic Circle Linked Path Train
Iron-Steel Train
They say what they really wanted
to make was a flying machine.
They're so greedy.
It was Miss Nureha, an adventurer,
who gave us People of the
Land the iron-steel train.
Watch your mouth.
Whatever you say, Captain of the Royal Guard.
You're supposed to keep an eye on this?
You always get the crappy jobs.
So where's Miss Nureha?
Not here yet.
Locked up in her room again?
What does Indicus intend to do with that princess?
She's a replacement for Kanami, right?
You think someone could actually replace her?
You're right.
It's been two years since she left the Tea Party.
Who knows what she's doing now?
She's heading straight here.
I met Kanami on the China server.
She's... Kanami's back in the game?
Yep.
And the scary thing is that
she hadn't changed a bit.
She was exactly like she was with us.
She was as much Kanami as ever.
Just after the Apocalypse,
I went to the continent to gather
information about this world.
Using Soul Possession to possess a white horse.
And there...
This is so great!
So much adventure!
Kanami
Race/ Human
Monk, Lv. 90
No Guild
Let's go, Froggy-nardo!
It's not Froggy-nardo.
It's Leonardo!
And I found Kanami.
Kanami, Go East!
Kanami, Go East.
There's no end to them.
I told you.
This is a raid-rank event!
The number of Daylight Shades
exceeds two thousand.
We can't use revivals or return spells to run, right?
Awesome!
Because of the Fairy Eye curse,
I can't finish any of them.
What kind of party is this?
A gap has appeared on the battlefield.
What?
Let's go, Eri-Eri, Froggy-nardo!
I'm not Froggy-nardo!
We have to go on foot?
Huh? You're KR?
I thought you were a horse someone sent.
You haven't changed a bit.
Didn't you move overseas in
real life, and quit the game?
I got back into it in Rome.
And now this happened.
And? What are you doing on the China server?
Heading to Japan!
To Yamato?
Kanami, it isn't that way.
Why?
In Yamato, they're calling this
the "Apocalypse," right?
I want to know why it happened.
Kanami says it might have something
to do with the Novasphere Pioneers.
The twelfth expansion pack
for the MMORPG Elder Tale,
the Novasphere Pioneers.
It's true that we were sent to this
world right after it went live.
But why Japan?
Japan is in the East.
The expansion was set to go live
at exactly midnight, on May 3rd.
So due to the time zone, it was only
implemented on the Japan server?
Right.
And as she headed to the East,
she had companions.
I miss giga-meat.
Leonardo
Race/ Human
Assassin, Lv. 90
No Guild
Leonardo, an assassin who'd used
fairy rings to come from the
America server and couldn't get back.
Supposedly, he'd just joined the party.
Do you desire healing?
Coppelia, a cleric Kanami had met on her travels.
Coppelia
Race/ Human
Cleric, Lv. 90
No Guild
No, I just want to eat some pizza.
And Erius Hackblade.
What?
The progenitor?
Erius Hackblade
Race/ Elf
Blademancer, Lv. 100
Redbranch Knights
A hero who belongs to the Redbranch Knights,
one of the thirteen orders of knights
who maintain order in the world.
He's a blademancer and a noble,
blue-blooded progenitor.
He's so famous, he's even on
the Elder Tale package.
But all the progenitors supposedly disappeared.
Just like the Izumo Knights on the Yamato server.
Why was he with Kanami, anyway?
Because she's Kanami, I suppose.
That makes sense.
Anyway, we continued our journey.
Sekek Village
China Server
Aorsoi: Zhympity
Field/ Monsters Present
PVP Permitted
Skill Use Permitted
Entry Restrictions/ None
Exit Restrictions/ None
And on our way...
Quick timeout!
What are you doing, Froggy-nardo?!
What's in there, Kanami?
A boy...
What's going on? His status...
What is he?
No, Froggy-nardo!
If we leave him, he'll kill someone!
Erius! Throw him here!
Understood!
Arms of the fairies of the black night...
Night Splash!
You threw him too far!
Oops.
Watch out, Coppelia!
He's a Person of the Land.
A non-player character.
I can kill him with Assassinate.
Don't worry about it.
He's only a program!
Froggy-nardo!
Don't worry.
I just stunned him with Paralyzing Blow.
Did you see it, too, Kanami?
His status was displayed in two layers.
What was that?
Has this ever happened before?
Yes.
One day people who'd been
acting completely normally
suddenly turned into beasts.
We call them the plague demons.
We don't know why they happen at all.
Plague Demons
So much mystery...
We can do it.
If we gather all the information we can find,
and if everyone wants to see something new.
In several days, a trader will be visiting the village.
We need information and supplies.
So we wait until he shows up?
Yep!
Hey, mister!
Why are you green?
Why are you a frog?
This is the sign that I'm a hero!
A frog ninja is a symbol of the most
courageous hero in the world!
I don't get it.
What's a hero?
Is it yummy?
Jeez... This is why I hate kids.
I guess there's no point in
getting upset at NPCs.
So one of the mares came
after you in the stables?
Don't laugh!
Are you really popular with the ladies, KR?
Shut up.
Well? How's Japan doing?
Is anything interesting going on?
Stop playing around
Shiro is?
Evidently he's at the core of some organization
called the "Round Table."
Though on the surface, someone else leads it.
That's my tour guide!
What's wrong, my lord?
I just felt like someone gave
me an impossible task.
During the game, you couldn't start
a new skill while still using the last.
But now that I have a physical body,
I can do cancels and combos!
Do you require healing?
No, I'm fine.
By the way, what do you think about
the Novasphere Pioneers?
I've been told it was applied
to the Japan server.
Then what about the Japan server?
Due to my master's wishes,
it's been plotted as a high priority.
And what's your master, Kanami, like?
My master is like
daybreak.
Huh?
On the other side of that sky,
the sun is racing forward.
It has just now set.
But tomorrow morning, at 0438,
the eastern sky will begin to brighten.
At night, the sky is dark.
At early dawn, it begins to turn dark purple.
Then bluish purple.
Then azure.
Gradually, the sky turns increasingly blue,
but there is still no light.
Because the sun has not appeared,
it's still dark.
But no one sees that blue and
doubts that the sun will rise.
That is what my master is like.
Several days later, the trader's caravan arrived.
Chun-Lu
Race/ Human
Cleric, Lv. 90
Rakurou Wolf Brigade
My name is Chun-Lu.
I'm a wanderer with the Rakurou
Wolf Brigade guild.
I was unable to protect the other
members of my caravan.
What happened?
Give them the fate of all who are inferior.
The truth of all solutions.
I'm sorry.
Normally, it would be our job to escort you.
It's fine. It's fine.
We're heading east, too.
The Rakurou Wolf Brigade has defended
the People of the Land
on their travels since the Apocalypse.
Yet...
No one blames you.
But...
But we come back to life.
Because we're adventurers.
You don't need to get upset
just because an NPC died.
The Rakurou Wolf Brigade
said they were going to try to wipe
out the nole army, right?
Yes.
We're going to try a ninety-six-man legion raid.
We're heading for the pillar ruins
known as Tone's Grave.
That's where the nole live.
There are four thousand enemies.
A team of level 90 and above
adventurers shouldn't have
any problem with that.
That sounds so cool.
I want to go, too.
We cannot leave the Corridor to Heaven behind.
It's fun to hurt tokens who have
no idea what they are.
We are the same.
Wiped out?
The Rakurou Wolf Brigade raid team got wiped out.
That layered status and a black dragon
were seen on the battlefield.
Parallel one...
Kanami!
A nole army is heading through
the zone we just passed!
Five hundred of them!
They're heading for the village we stayed in.
Noles live in caves and ruins,
and eat those who come close.
For some reason, they're moving
en masse in search of food.
Nice! Nice!
Five hundred dogs is a lucky sign!
You can't get this excitement in real life!
Huh?
No shortage of enemies! So much excitement!
You don't have to say, "Huh," twice!
Are you planning to defeat the nole
army moving toward the village,
and then go to Tone's Grave?
That's my KR!
You get it!
Are you stupid?
Didn't you hear how that legion
raid was annihilated?
Because they did a full-on brawl,
with no information.
So we won't do any brawling.
We'll attack, kill the boss, and run.
Perfect game!
We are champions!
So, what information do we have?
We heard a lot from Chun-Lu, right?
And how are we supposed to use it?
You figure that out, KR.
I can't!
It doesn't matter whether you can do it or not...
Then what does?
There's a need for us to go.
What do you mean "a need"?
A reason I can't say aloud.
Why do all this for People of the Land NPCs?
I agree with Kanami.
Not simply because I owe her a debt.
I am a progenitor.
I have had a duty to protect the People
of the Land since the thirteen orders
of knights around the world were born.
Yeah...
That's right.
He's an NPC, too.
The same as a Person of the Land.
What will we do with the villagers?
Chun-Lu, will you go let them know?
Got it.
I will go with you.
We can't win!
There's no reason for you to do that!
I am not a player character, either.
I am one of many MMORPG farming bots
created by a Chinese money-laundering group.
Didn't you go with Kanami and the others?
Something was bothering me.
After that, what did that girl tell you?
She was a farming bot.
Not a player.
She was just an AI that
only existed in the game.
In that village, I healed eighteen People of the Land.
I blessed forty-nine.
Whether it had any effect, I don't know.
I was thanked three hundred and
nineteen times for this act.
What would he do?
The unbeatable ninja hero.
I know what he'd do.
I've known from the start.
He'd go.
That's interesting.
Truly, truly interesting.
Are you KR?
KR
Race/ Elf
Summoner, Lv. 90
Plant Hwyaden
That's right.
How?
What did you do?
Swap Teleporting. Castling.
Servant                                                                               Caster
Swap Teleporting
Castling
It's an emergency escape method that
swaps the caster and their summoned creature.
Caster                                                                                 Servant
Which means...
I just teleported to this server from Japan.
I'll go with you.
Why?
I know
that frog mask, too.
I liked him.
If that hero is going to show off his new power,
then I have to show off mine, too.
Awaken, my friend,
the red dragon!
Awaken from thy garnet slumber
and fly through the sky!
Spirits of pure water,
become a thousand blades,
and shine across the battlefield!
Aqua Thousand Rain!
Leonardo?
I can see Tone's Grave from here.
Wait... Hey!
That's amazing.
That's a full- or double-raid rank...
The black dragon Chun-Lu was talking about?
Someone's riding it.
They're the bad guys.
The boss characters, huh?
Oh? More adventurers.
Models without power.
If it weren't for those two, could you keep
the black dragon away from Coppelia and Kanami?
Yeah.
Perfect.
Cowabunga!
Froggy-nardo! That was awesome!
Let's go!
I'm astonished, human.
My God.
Genius of Necromancy
Lasphere/ Genius, Lv. 89
Rank/ Normal
Lasphere,
level 89,
a normal-rank monster.
Genius of Healing
Paps/ Genius, Lv. 89
Rank/ Normal
Level 89,
normal rank.
His name is Paps.
So you read my name.
That is the special ability of these solutions.
A genius...
So you know that name, survivor?
Eri-Eri!
They're all slippery!
It is a strange combination,
but I should not let the progenitor,
or the rest of you, survive.
I'll eliminate you.
This is wonderful!
This is joyous!
Shut up!
Parallel One!
She's controlling a second name,
swapping it with her own status,
and using it to take damage for her?
Then I'll use the gap between
the charge and the motion...
Parallel Plot!
So this is pain? Or is this an ache?
More crimson than twilight,
redder than a lycoris flower!
A deeper red than a rose...
Did your companions fall?
Stop it...
Why do you not shut down?
Shut your mouth!
I know everything about the progenitors...
No, about the People of the Land.
You are all dolls,
puppets without will,
only personality software.
There are no fairies.
The progenitors and the People of the Land
are all false.
Be destroyed, false thing.
You must shut down.
You, who were born from nothing,
shut down your timeline.
Hell, no!
Don't be stupid!
Eri-Eri is real!
He's right here!
From now on, we're going to have a lot of fun.
Don't take him away from me.
You're just a tire-tube man!
I don't know what happened after that.
Worrying about it is a waste of time.
She's as terrible as ever.
I told you it's terrifying how little she's changed.
Miss Nureha!
Wave your hand, Lady Nureha.
That's right.
You need only smile with that pretty face.
Did you tell Indicus this?
Nope.
She doesn't know that Kanami
is back in the game, either.
That will make their reunion
even more moving, won't it?
Preparing to deploy magic circles.
Linked-path adjustment complete.
Ready to go at will.
It's time to start a war!
To the East!
The magic bag that holds anything,
the thing all beginners desire.
Minori and the others go on a quest
to get the materials for it.
Carrying five people,
both nervous and excited about
a world they've not yet seen,
the carriage sets off.
Next time: Setting Off.
Setting Off
I have friends to run with me.