I love this place.
I can walk on my own two feet here!
I command you in the name
of royal Versian blood!
Aldnoah, awaken!
Not only have you survived, you have
assumed command of our world.
I am most impressed.
I am proud of you, Asseylum.
Thank you, Grandfather.
You seem to have grown stronger.
I have been through much. People tend
to change as they gain experience.
From the red sands of our home,
I pray for your success in battle.
You never change at all,
...Grandfather.
Trident Base, this is Capt. Magbaredge
of the Deucalion.
Requesting docking clearance.
Welcome to Trident, Deucalion.
You are cleared to dock.
Please berth at pier 12.
Deucalion, acknowledged.
Course, Trident Base docking bay, pier 12.
Begin deceleration.
Beginning deceleration.
So that's the ship with
the Martian tech...
I hear she's crewed by children who aren't
even old enough for the reserves.
What's the world coming to?
Wow, look at them all!
They must have scrounged up every
squad capable of making it here.
Because this is going to
be a massive operation.
Deceleration complete in 5 seconds...
Three, two, one.
Engines, all stop. We are now
at a stop relative to pier 12.
Power down engines.
Once mooring is complete,
begin inspections and resupplying.
Ensign Kaizuka, are you in?
It's open.
How are you feeling, Inaho?
Not bad, I guess.
It still hurts a little, though.
Don't you have pills?
I feel better when I take them,
but it degrades the sensitivity of the neural link.
Oh, that makes sense...
It must be rough.
It looks like an
ordinary eye to me.
How well does it work?
I get by with it.
It's a developmental prototype,
so the code needs to be improved,
but I can make out most things.
Catch.
Thanks.
Weight, 49.2kg.
Have you gained a little weight?
H-How could you know that?
I used 3D measurements to calculate
the change in momentum
when you caught that 200g pack
and worked out your total mass.
I subtracted the estimated weight
of your uniform from that.
I'm not getting fat! I have more muscle
mass from exercising, that's all.
That's a lie. I can see stress in the
formant analysis of your voice.
Are you sure it's not broken?
It's working perfectly.
Now what?
I can see identical stress
patterns in her voice.
Especially here.
I, Vers Empire Princess Royal
Asseylum Vers Allusia...
Hang on! If that is a lie, it means...
she isn't really the princess.
This part's waveform is definitely a lie.
Have you been stress eating?
I haven't been stress eating!
Your stress went up again.
I'm not talking to you ever again!
Something wrong?
Not really. I thought it would
be easy to read Inko.
That clinches it.
You really are an idiot, aren't you?
You're telling the truth.
Milord Slaine.
Eddelrittuo, shouldn't you
be with Princess Lemrina?
It's all right.
I won't tell anyone.
I'm sorry...
Oh, right. We spotted that
ship you told us about.
The Deucalion?
It looks like they were
secretly repairing it.
Reports say it defeated Baron Yacoym
and came up into space.
We might be forced to fight them.
Do you suppose that would make
Princess Asseylum sad?
I wonder when she will wake up...
What if she never...
Don't worry.
We will see her smile again.
I know it.
Milady...
I have asked Asseylum
to do what you wanted.
Everything has been arranged.
You may rest assured.
I once lied to him that she
had been assassinated,
and now I am lying to him
that she is alive...
Slaine. What is your opinion
of Vers as it is now?
It is not my place to offer an
opinion on our sacred homeland.
It is all right.
You may speak freely.
I believe it is possible for our society,
with its powerless,
impoverished citizenry,
to become prosperous by conquering Earth,
making it a domain, and taking its resources.
However...
That wealth is likely to find its way
to only the upper classes
and will not improve the lives
of the citizens in the slightest.
What is your suggestion, then?
Aldnoah...
Those who possess Aldnoah
control everything.
That is the problem in a nutshell.
Well put.
We owe much to His Imperial Majesty
for unearthing Aldnoah.
But it was a grave sin
to hoard that power and create a society
where the powerful control all.
When we have achieved victory and seized
the Earth, that red world will change.
Lend me your strength, Slaine.
I will, Count Saazbaum.
Is my beloved steed ready?
We've finished its activation tests.
Once we've finished fine-tuning the sync
between each unit, it will be combat-ready.
Do that on the island!
Stygis Squadron, prepare to move out!
Yes, sir!
Tharsis, stand.
It's not powering up...
Its Aldnoah Drive is offline...
Why?
Princess Lemrina.
Is something the matter, Slaine?
Why have you deactivated the Tharsis?
Whatever are you talking about?
The only one here who can forcibly
deactivate Aldnoah is Your Highness.
Possibly.
Please activate the Aldnoah.
No.
Please.
Perhaps you should ask my sister?
It had always struck me as odd.
How could you, a Terran,
operate the Tharsis?
I'm sure she would be happy to know
you still love her in spite of her condition.
Even though we share a father,
no one pays me any heed simply
because we have different mothers.
That is not true at all.
We all admire you, Princess Lemrina.
Liar.
It is no lie.
It is. It's not me that you admire,
it's my activation factor.
Isn't that exactly why you came to me?
Lord Slaine?
Do you want me that badly?
Is Aldnoah so important to you?
Am I my sister's replacement?
I knew it, I am.
I hate you.
I was born on Earth.
When my scientist father died,
I lost my one protector.
I became a servant
of the Vers Orbital Knights.
I will not say that
I understand your hardships.
But I, too, have known cruel
treatment due to my birth.
I can understand your suffering,
if only some small portion of it.
You do have my heartfelt admiration, Princess Lemrina.
Lift your eyes, Slaine.
Now, activate it once yourself.
You have my thanks.
Good hunting, Sir Slaine Troyard.
Milord Slaine.
I apologize for the delay.
That display was touching.
I am proud that you are my master.
You saw that? How embarrassing.
All units, launch!
Destination, Marineros Island!
Everything that was yours,
I will take on as my own.
So rest easy, dear sister.
We will soon enter Earth orbit.
We will perform an aerobrake maneuver,
slingshot around,
and enter the Satellite Belt.
We will then make for
Marineros Island.
Milord Slaine, it is time.
Right.
As you are aware, the countless rocks
that comprise the Satellite Belt
travel in an elliptical orbit
around the Earth.
Trident Base is one of those rocks.
Now, this is the orbit of Marineros,
the frontline base of the Mars Army.
The two will make a close approach
in 72 hours' time.
The distance between them
will be a mere 7km.
That's close enough to be
seen with the naked eye.
For that reason, a large-scale battle
is expected between our two bases.
Operating under that assumption,
we have gathered you here
from both orbit and the surface
to assemble a powerful fighting force.
It is thought that the Mars Army will also
amass their forces for an all-out offensive.
Exercise caution while attacking.
The mission is as follows.
We've never fought a space battle
of this scale since the war began.
We predict an increase in high-density rocks
in the area at the time of the operation.
Do you think we can handle it?
As a result, long-range fire will be
thrown off course.
Who knows? But considering that it'll
be a first for the enemy, too,
Your chances of landing a hit will be low.
it's probably nothing
to be scared about.
But this will hold true for the enemy, as well.
Be that as it may, it is still
a subject for concern.
Judging from the Mars Army's
fighting style to date,
they have a tendency to put more emphasis
on offense than defense.
What a shame.
Ma'am?
As such, there is a high probability of them
mobilizing their base's mechanized units
If you let that endearing side show
every day, you'd be sure to get a date.
and engaging us in close-quarter combat.
Deceleration complete in five seconds.
Three, two, one,
clear.
A little something for the ride.
Stygis Platoon, show me
what you are made of.
Stygis 1, by your command.
Stygis 2, by your command.
Stygis 3, by your command.
Intense heat signatures closing
in from LEO at high speed!
Not reading an IFF signal!
From below?!
They will pass within 2km of this base
on a trajectory that will take them
to the Mars Army's Marineros Base!
Orders from HQ to intercept, ma'am!
Ships closing in at high speed.
7 mid-sized ships, and 3 small units.
They intend to launch a surprise attack
prior to the all-out offensive.
Scramble all operational shipboard Kataphrakts!
And prep the ship
for emergency launch!
Calm.
Is mine ready?
Repairs are complete. It's also fully
kitted out with a space loadout.
Thanks.
Are you sure you want to keep this gaudy
color? Give the word, and I'll paint it.
It's okay. It's supposed
to attract attention.
Huh?
Don't worry about it.
Ghanaati Platoon, in position.
Harroway Platoon, in position.
Mustang 11, in position!
Mustang 22, in position!
Relative velocity with enemy units
is 3kps. They'll pass by in a flash.
Meaning that their chances
of attacking are slim.
Stygis 1, commencing attack.
Stygis 2, commencing attack.
Stygis 3, commencing attack.
Fire incoming!
Bastard!
The wind is complicated. Neither one
of us will land a hit at this range.
Someone's shots landed?
At this range?
Mustang 00, commencing attack.
Inaho!
Compensating for gravity gradient
resulting from dense satellite clusters.
Ready.
Target set...
Fire.
Next!
The Stygis Platoon, it's–
Inaho!
Are you all right, Count?
Slaine!
I will act as a decoy
to draw their fire.
Mr. Harklight, take evasive action.
Understood!
They're going to hit!
He dodged it?
How did it move like that?
That's pinpoint accuracy! How are
shots landing in this wind?
Speed?
No, that's not it.
It's anticipating the rounds' trajectory.
But how?
Who is this person?
It's him.
An orange Kataphrakt...
It can't be!
I've been looking for you, Bat...
No, I guess you did a class change
and are Gull now.
Enemy convoy is almost in
effective firing range!
Fire at will!
Inaho!
Enemy convoy has passed.
Now breaking away.
Continue firing until enemy is out
of range! Give me a damage report.
Tharsis...
The personal Kataphrakt of
Orbital Knight Count Cruhteo.
Later owned by Count Saazbaum
and piloted by a knight under his command.
The pilot's name...
The orange Kataphrakt...
It's a trainer.
A trainer?
Yes, that boy prefers
to only pilot trainers.
That boy?
Yes. His name is...
Inaho Kaizuka...
So you're alive.
I've found you,
Slaine Troyard.