Don't.
That is far enough.
Do not touch Her Highness,
...Orange.
Bat...
Andalusia Leader to all units.
Target the transport only.
Even if they launch Kataphrakts,
do not engage.
We will use Kaufmann 6 as an anchor
to perform wire swingby
and return to Trident Base.
Good hunting, people.
Roger that.
Target located.
All units, commence attack.
Wind's too strong...
Our rounds are drifting!
Stay calm! They're in
the same boat!
Hit 'em before they can get close!
Multiple high-density satellites!
We can't hit them at this range!
Don't hold back on the bullets! Keep firing!
Andalusia 33, I'm hit!
Damage minor! Continuing missi–
Andalusia 33!
Andalusia 22!
That's not possible!
How can he land any shots in this wind?
What in the world?
Intense thermal reading approaching!
An enemy?
No, sir!
That's...
The Tharsis!
Please get clear. I'll handle them.
Sir Slaine Troyard...
Andalusia 11!
Bastard!
I'm not hitting... I'm this close,
so how can that be?!
The blessings of my lady, Princess
Royal Asseylum, are upon me.
Slaine Troyard has come.
Ever since I was young,
I idolized Earth.
Its blue seas. Its blue skies.
That world has the privilege of
water and air and sunlight,
and is blessed with an abundance
of life and natural resources.
I once lost my life
on that world of Earth.
And then, my eyes were
opened to the truth.
How outrageous it was for the Terrans
to live among that bounty
without appreciating it.
A foolish race that covets
resources, destroys nature,
and is devoted to the
pursuit of pleasure.
We mustn't allow them to have their way
with this precious world of Earth.
I, Asseylum Vers Allusia,
Princess Royal of the Vers Empire,
praise and commend all those
Orbital Knights who have died
in the name of that noble cause.
What's the point of watching that
pirate broadcast of theirs?
I'm curious, that's all... I wonder
what happened to the princess?
Who knows?
I thought she was
on Earth's side.
Who knows?
Maybe she lost hope in there ever
being a peaceful resolution.
If there's fighting, it's only natural
that she would side with Mars.
She's a Martian, after all.
Say, Inko...
What is it, Inko?
Oh, it's nothing. I was just thinking that
this might be our last chance to relax.
Yeah, we board the ship tomorrow
and lift off the day after that.
You sure it's not him
you're thinking about?
I-It's not! It's not like that!
Don't just stand there, people!
Are you training or aren't you?!
Y-Yes, sir!
We plan to be able to lift off
the day after tomorrow.
Troops whose arrival was delayed
should be here by tomorrow.
Are you referring to him?
I wonder what the top
brass are thinking?
We'll essentially be going into
battle with our vitals exposed.
If those vitals are competent
enough, it changes things.
They're telling us to put it
to effective use.
Hard to believe we'll be fighting
side by side again...
You can say that again, ma'am.
It's a miracle he made it back alive.
That landing was so skillful, one would never
guess we are in an uneven gravity field.
Your skills have improved
even more, Slaine.
Your compliment honors me,
Count Saazbaum.
Granting you the title of knight
was a wise decision.
How did the battle go?
I destroyed some four
enemy units.
Quite a coup, Milord Slaine.
Stop that, Mr. Harklight.
There's no need for
"milord" with me.
That won't do, Milord.
I am your manservant.
But you're older than I am, and...
I'm a Terran.
That does not change the fact
that you are a knight, Milord.
And I ask that you refrain from using
"mister" with me, Milord Slaine.
Enter.
Pardon the interruption.
You seem to be in good spirits,
Princess Lemrina.
I am weary, Count Saazbaum.
How fares the world?
The invasions of North and
South America are complete,
and their takeover is underway.
As for Eurasia and the Far East,
UEF counterattacks continue
due to the surrender of the
Landing Castles there.
Will I be able to
go down to Earth?
We expect the UE
to be exhausted soon.
When that happens, you,
who inherit the bloodline
of the Emperor of Vers,
will be installed as–
Do not say that!
Highness.
Princess Lemrina.
I have never been pleased with
the blood flowing in my veins.
On the contrary, I find it repugnant.
Am I only being kept alive
because of the value of my blood?
To merely be a tool that
exists to awaken Aldnoah.
My apologies.
No, I understand.
It was you who extended the hand of
friendship to me, Count Saazbaum.
Even if I curse my blood,
I am grateful to you.
Slaine.
Yes, Highness. What is it?
Will you teach me of Earth again?
Gladly.
Looks like we're together
again for a while, huh?
Yeah...
I hope we make it back alive.
We're not going to die.
We'll beat the Martians.
We'll beat them and restore
peace on Earth. Period.
We don't have time to die.
I guess not.
Surprise attack!
It's a Martian Kataphrakt!
Radar return confirmed, south-southwest,
20 klicks. Closing at 50kph.
All hands to battle stations.
We're leaving the dock.
But the antigravity device
is being serviced!
Sorry I'm late!
What on Earth are you wearing?
Where is the uniform you
were supplied with?
Well... it wasn't very cute.
Wasn't–
Fine. It won't hinder her ability to
helm the ship, so I'll authorize it.
Captain!
Mizusaki, shall I tell you
why you can't get a date?
Deucalion, activate! Kataphrakt squadron,
launch all operational units!
Any enemy intel?
Count Yacoym's Kataphrakt, Frozen Elysium.
Its Aldnoah Drive's unique capability
is Entropy Dilution.
Entro-what?
It saps the molecular motion of all matter
inside a field 1km in radius.
It creates super-low temperatures that can
transform the air and freeze it.
All right, Terrans. show me how
you defy the power of Aldnoah!
At its current rate of speed, it'll reach
the Deucalion's dock in 15 minutes.
We have to slow it
down somehow...
Slow it down?
You must be joking.
We're going to destroy it.
This is Harbinger Platoon. Target spotted.
We're going in
in cold-weather mode.
Turbine output to maximum. De-icers, on.
Commence attack.
What's that?
The de-icers aren't working? Impossible!
You are helpless before it.
It is not for nothing that
its name is Frozen Elysium.
Voltage is falling? The chemical reaction
in my batteries has stopped?
My hand!
Harbinger Leader!
Bastard!
My rounds aren't connecting! Why?!
A shield? It shouldn't have one!
We're out of options!
This is bad. We have to think
of a way to slow it down.
I thought you said we were
going to destroy it!
Call it a downward revision!
Measuring bullet trajectory.
Fall back, you two.
I get it. The warheads entered
a superconductive state
and were deflected by
the Meissner Effect.
Let's see how air burst mode works.
A dud? Oh, the battery in the warhead
froze and the processor locked up?
Where does the sapped heat go?
Is it shunting the molecular movement
energy somewhere else in our dimension?
Flight distance for the warheads'
electronic timer fuse,
about 50 meters should do it.
Radius of the field, 1km...
Basically,
20 rounds should do it.
Inaho?!
Charging enemy.
You'll freeze!
I just need to reach him
before then.
Hey!
How amusing. Come, then!
Grenade launcher, midair burst mode.
Safe distance, cut. Flight distance, 50 meters.
Fire.
Oh, well done.
Inaho!
I took more damage than expected.
I wonder if Calm will be mad...
Inaho!
Are you okay, Inaho?
Ensign Inaho Kaizuka reporting.
Per orders from General Headquarters,
I have been assigned to your ship.
Come on, what's with that?
You never change, Inaho.
Back at you, Inko.
I'm glad you're looking well.
You have changed. Quite a bit.
You can make polite small talk now.
That's not really a compliment.
Inko...
Welcome back...
Welcome back, Inaho.
It's good to be back.
Shoot, Slaine.
I have finished off the Terran soldier
who has been a thorn in our side.
I have finally made up my mind.
Please forgive me for all the wrongs
I have done you in the past,
and am sure to do
in the future...
...Count Saazbaum.
Many Terran troops have already
breached the castle.
Let's escape in the Tharsis.
And take Princess Asseylum with us.
I am the only one who can
save you now, Count.
Will you die with your
ambitions unrealized?
Or choose to live with
Princess Asseylum?
Your decision, please.
Highness!
What?
No!
Inaho! Inaho!
Yuki! Inaho's been...
Inaho's...
Dr. Yagarai! You have
to do something!
Inaho?!
Gunshot wound to the head.
Bullet went through the temporal
region via the left eye socket.
Patient unconscious.
Three cc's of adrenaline administered
as emergency treatment.
This is bad...
You'll save him, right?
You'll save Inaho, right?
He needs immediate
surgical treatment.
And a transfusion, of course. However...
We have tools and facilities
in the underground shelter!
Capt. Magbaredge!
Order the Deucalion to lift off!
The Aldnoah Drive...
is offline.
Warrant Officer Kaizuka...
Princess Asseylum...
Where is she?
Nao, do your best!
Blood?
Nao's blood...
No, not his...
It's blood splatter.
Whose?
It's...
The light of Aldnoah...
The activation factor...!
Nao...
Deucalion, lift off!
All ahead, dead slow!
All ahead, dead slow.
We've left the atmosphere.
Now coasting on inertia.
Course, Trident Base.
Electromagnetic grid, fire.
Monitor all wavelengths.
The Terrans who so foolishly squandered
the goodwill of the Vers Empire
are even now biding their time to attempt
to steal our lands from us.
The Vers Empire must exterminate them out of mercy.
We'll be fighting her. Is that okay, Inaho?
We shall take the blue Earth for Vers.
Let us liberate this world,
which possesses air and water
in such quantities that it diffracts light
and makes the sky and seas appear blue,
It's wrong.
from the hands of the barbaric Terrans.
It's Rayleigh scattering that makes the sky blue.
Water, please, Eddelrittuo.
Y-Yes, Milady! Right away!
How was that, Count Saazbaum?
Excellent. You were the very
image of Princess Asseylum.
No one would ever suspect
your true identity.
This is the problem with you men.
No one was speaking
of true identities.
Masterfully done, Princess Lemrina.
Your majestic words
are sure to have left an impression
on the Orbital Knights, as well.
Thank you, Sir Slaine Troyard.
I am more grateful for such concern than
any compliments on my performance.
I am extremely and humbly delighted.
If there will be nothing else, Milord Slaine,
I will take my leave now.
Thank you, Mr. Harklight.
I've returned, Princess Asseylum.
I see that you are in good
spirits again today.