Ethan!
Stella?
Mom, have you seen Ethan?
I can't find him!
Who's Ethan?
Um, about this...
Looks like it's working well.
It absorbs your excess magic and
makes crystal flowers by the morning.
Do you like it?
They're beautiful.
Good.
I'm glad.
Although it looks a bit crazy.
They look tasty.
Tasty?
They look tasty to the likes of us.
They do, huh?
Elias, also...
Lindel got you dragon castings.
And the fish is from Selkie?
Simon got you a wristwatch.
Angelica got you...
Ah, she does quick work, as always.
Chise, can you show me the
bracelet you got in Ant Hill?
Okay.
Yeah, that looks good.
With this, you'll be practically
unable to absorb or create magic.
It'll be perfect for your body.
Listen, don't do any experiments or
magic without my permission, all right?
Okay.
Thank you.
I can do hardly anything right now.
Everyone's given me so much,
and I can't give anything back.
I'll do whatever I can while
my body still moves.
Elias, I'm going to thank Simon-san.
I'll come with you.
I can't have you sneaking
off to London again.
I-I won't go without telling you anymore.
We'll see about that.
That's unusual.
There's no one out.
It's Christmas, after all.
Um, have you seen a boy around?
N-No, no one.
I've seen her before.
Wait, Stella, come back here!
What's gotten into her?
I have no idea.
She darted off, saying her
brother's gone missing.
Her brother?
She's our only child, though.
Elias, um...
Yeah, go for it.
Um...
Please!
Please help me find my brother, Ethan!
I'm Stella Barklem.
I came to my grandma's
place for Christmas break.
Along with my whole family.
I took Ethan to the yard, but...
He's frail, but he refused to go back inside.
Then we got in a fight.
You're such a selfish little brother!
I told them that Ethan had vanished.
But...
Who's Ethan?
I'm the only one who remembers my brother.
Why?
They suddenly forgot about their own child?
That's peculiar.
Elias.
How will you compensate us?
Compensate?
When we help people, we receive
an appropriate payment.
What will you do for us?
I...
Sweets.
When I come here...
I-I'm here at least once a month.
I'll make lots and lots of sweets!
More than I can carry!
If it's money you want, I'll work.
For my whole life, if I have to!
Sure.
That will be your payment.
Thank you.
M-Monster!
No, he's a mage.
A mage?
Are you one, too?
Technically, I guess.
You must be scared, with all
these weird things happening.
Of course I am!
But it's not any scarier than
not having my brother back.
Yeah.
All right, let's go.
The dog talked!
Is this where he disappeared?
It's dangerous to split up.
Don't stray away from any of us.
Okay.
Take this.
Wow, what's this?
It's pretty.
We can find you if you get lost,
as long as you hold onto that.
Ruth will.
I will.
Thanks, Chise. I'll hold onto it.
Someone's interfering.
What?
Let's ask the neighbors here.
I don't know if they'll give us
a straight answer, though.
Do you need help?
A Sleigh Beggy is a queen bee.
A queen bee gives birth to the children,
so the hive takes care of her.
It's not magic, so it's okay, right?
It's not a bad negotiation tactic, I suppose.
Tell me where her brother is.
That way.
Wh-What?
What are you talking to, Chise?
Don't worry about it, Stella.
It's dangerous.
Let's go.
Know... Want...
Shoot... I'm out of flowers...
Chise, we need details.
Half a teacup's worth.
No more.
Chise! Why are you bleeding?!
It's okay, don't wo—
You idiot! How can I not worry?!
What are you even doing?
She's paying her compensation.
You're mages, aren't you?
Can't you do it without hurting yourselves?
We aren't omnipotent.
I had a brother, too, but
I can't see him anymore.
So I want you to be able to see yours.
This is the only way we can find him for now.
I'm sorry I scared you.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to your sweets.
I'm going to treat that when we get home.
Okay.
Sorry, Chise. I didn't
want to make you do it.
I was the one who suggested it.
Hurry up.
Oh?
I should thank you for coming out this far.
Ashen Eye.
Ethan!
I found a young child abandoned in the snow.
Such a pitiful thing.
Give him back!
He's my brother!
Oh?
What an odd thing to say.
You are the one who
abandoned him, are you not?
We hear human words often.
Words and text are sounds
and shapes that bear souls.
Should they reach another,
they cannot be undone.
What does he mean?
You're such a selfish little brother!
I don't need you!
I didn't mean it.
It's too late now.
There's no telling what kind of creature
will appreciate the words you spew forth.
It's a good thing you didn't tell him to die.
You and your brother's bond has been broken,
former older sister.
Can you remember your dear brother's name?
Stella?
It's *****, isn't it?
What?
I couldn't hear it.
That's what it means for a bond to be broken.
To forget his name, his age, where
he's from, his face, his voice,
and whether he even existed at all.
No!
Stop it!
Stella!
This is mine now.
Can you pay the appropriate
compensation, have-not?
Then let's play a game, have-not.
Play?
Join us, child of the shadows.
Elias!
No!
You two shall find them.
Let's give you until sundown.
If you can find them before that, you win.
If you can't, they're mine.
We're at a disadvantage.
You don't lose anything.
This is too selfish.
Now, go.
Search frantically for them,
with that beastly nose of yours.
The days are short in the winter.
Oh, no.
Am I going to forget him?
Chise.
We just have to find them.
That's all.
But...
You're from the far east.
He's from the far west.
And yet, you managed to find each other.
You're not going to miss
him on this tiny hill.
Elias...
You're his older sister, aren't you?
You should believe in
yourself and your brother.
If you care about him enough that it makes
you cry, you won't lose your bond so easily.
Whether it's family or anything else, it's...
Ruth...
Chise...
It's all right.
Let's look for them together.
Ruth, can you track their scent?
They're hidden.
It's really faint.
Oh...
With that beastly nose of yours...
Beast.
Chise!
Ruth, take care of Stella for me.
Is it really safe to use that?
My place has already been decided.
We've been locked in.
I can hardly move.
I hate old creatures.
They're too powerful.
And Chise can't use her magic right now.
Where am I?
M-Monster!
You're just like your sister.
It talked!
Y-You know my sister?
Who are you?
Hey, hey, what is that?
Is this bone?
Wait, don't.
Are you wearing a skull?
Does it come off?
Or is it your actual skull?
Hey!
I don't know how to react.
That's so cool!
Whoa!
You turned human!
Do you remember your sister's name?
Huh?
Obviously.
Oh, no!
I don't know it!
Why?!
You said you don't need your
nagging sister, didn't you?
Do you really not need her?
Isn't family important?
I-I wasn't being serious!
I mean, it's embarrassing.
I don't really understand
families or marriage.
Would I understand those emotions
if I had blood relatives?
I've never thought about whether
we're related by blood or not.
Family is family, either way.
So it's a unit, a group of people who cohabitate
and help each other out for a long time.
You make it sound like it could be anyone.
I think I really want to
tell my sister I'm sorry.
I want to party with her again.
I don't want it to be anyone else.
I think that's what family is.
People that make you feel that way.
Find them! Find them!
Capture their scent.
Find...
Find what belongs to me.
Chise!
Elias!
Thank goodness, I found you.
Good work.
Elias...
Why do you look like me?
A child's curiosity is terrifyingly powerful.
We're going home.
Don't wanna.
I said, we're going home!
I don't wanna!
You don't want a brother like me, do you?
Does it suck having me as your big sister?
I don't mind having a kid
brother, as long as it's you.
It's not like I know of any
other brothers, anyway.
I'm okay with you being my older sister.
You mean you want me being
your older sister, dummy.
Do you remember his name now?
Nope.
Holy crap, my clothes aren't wet.
It's a pain not to be able to say his name.
That was fun.
That was a fun loss.
I can't keep up with you.
I had fun.
It's fun to watch people when they're serious.
A person's words are powerful.
That's why we stay nearby to listen.
Keep that in mind, have-not.
I'll have what bond you've lost.
No!
No,
you do have something.
This looks tastier.
I'll let you go.
He was messing with us.
Stella! Ethan!
Dad! Mom!
Unbelievable!
Where were you two?!
Dad... Mom...
Who's she?
Oh, uh...
Her name's Chise.
She's my new friend I met today.
Thank you so much, Chise.
Tell me where you live.
I'm going to keep my promise.
Stella's so pushy.
What was that?!
The girl's first friend
makes her heart dance.
But the existence of her friend slightly
warps her relationship with the mage.
Chise, where are you?!