Go, go, let's go! Let's go Date Tech!
Well? Are they winning?!
Don't push.
Date Tech         Aoba Johsai
Wait. They're still only two points ahead.
They're on the second set right now.
Who got the first set?
Um...
Apparently Seijoh got the first set.
Ah, Karasuno!
H-Hello, there...
Hey.
Heyo.
Karasuno's got some third-years left.
Yeah.
How's our new team doing?
Makki!
Damn it... They're seeing right through them.
Rule the Court
Great, great, Takahiro! Push it,
push it, Takahiro! One more!
Date Tech                            Aoba Johsai
Hanamaki, nice serve!
Sorry!
Kogane!
Got it!
Date Tech has a new setter.
Yeah,
I wonder what kind of toss...
What the heck was that?!
Haikyu!!
Episode 19: "The Iron Wall Can
Be Rebuilt Again and Again."
Kogane!
Got it!
Good! Go!
Kogane's moves still seem rough.
Well, as long as the ball goes up.
Left!
Right!
What the heck was that?!
Futakuchi-senpai, I'm counting on you!
It's too high!
I'm not good with high ones!
All right!
Sorry!
Lucky!
Futakuchi-senpai, don't mind!
A-A little lower, Koganegawa.
Right! Lower!
Don't make it too low.
I need it in the middle. The middle.
Right!
You sure you got it?
Of course!
Sorry.
No worries!
Date Tech's setter is a
first-year, right? #7.
Yeah.
He's big...
One touch!
Yeah, he is.
That's our new weapon.
The giant setter, Koganegawa.
Giant...
...setter?
Nice catch!
I'm sorry!
I'll run around the school a
hundred times to make up for it!
You should probably practice tossing instead!
H-He's still learning.
He just became a setter.
He'll eventually be a huge deal.
Th-Those kinds of mistakes
happen all the time...
Er, uh... He's definitely
got the potential! Really!
You're making Karasuno's captain
take pity on you, Moniwa...
Nice serve!
I was selfish, so I'm sure my
senpais had a hard time with me,
Bring it!
All right, bring it!
but I have to wonder about
being too serious, too.
Futakuchi is having
trouble with his junior...
Serves him right.
Date Tech                   Aoba Johsai
Matsukawa, nice serve!
They really don't want to let
them get any more of a lead...
Bring it!
Cut it off with the one!
Left!
Those are movements for a dump... It's high.
Above the block... But it's...
...completely obvious!
Huh?
Damn it.
Chance! Chance!
Iwa-chan!
Nice, Sakunami!
Futakuchi, get the last!
One touch!
Got it! Makki!
Got it!
The wing spiker, #3, did the toss?
Oikawa!
Oikawa-san!
Don't mind!
Kogane, nice block!
Learn to hold back, you idiot!
Right! Sorry!
Are you okay, Futakuchi-senpai?
No, I'm not! That's why I'm telling
you to learn to hold back!
It's my fault for not being
able to brace it better.
That was fine.
Right.
That is...
...our new iron wall...
Koganegawa.
New...
...iron wall.
He reworded it because it didn't
work out so well earlier.
Looks like we're up against
an annoying team again.
Honestly, that was sort of refreshing.
True.
I can hear you.
Now, then... What to do?
Nice receive!
Got it!
Kindaichi!
A counter!
All right!
I guess it's to be expected.
Seriously! You're totally obvious!
Sorry! But a dump is so cool
that I wanted to try it!
And that's why he's so obvious...
Look, you don't need to feint
when you do a dump attack.
Huh?
What?
Date Tech                      Aoba Johsai
Nice serve!
Oikawa-san, nice serve!
Rule the Court
All right!
Great, great, Toru! Push it,
push it, Toru! One more time!
It looks like Seijoh has the upper hand.
Date Tech is still flailing around.
Once their giant setter settles,
I'm sure he'll be an amazing weapon.
Oikawa, one more nice serve!
Damn it!
It's going over the net!
Chance ball!
Another quick is coming!
Left!
Center!
#12! #12!
Listen up.
Koganegawa's basically still
a baby as a setter.
Date Tech
So you need to help him out, Sakunami.
Go somewhere convenient
for Koganegawa-kun...
And receive!
Good!
When you receive the ball,
get it high enough for
Koganegawa to do a jump toss.
It doesn't matter if it's
not that close to the net.
He'll get it.
You don't need to think about
anything difficult yet.
Just get it from one high place...
...to another!
Date Tech                      Aoba Johsai
Nice kill! Aone!
So fast! So high!
Putting it right where the
spiker will hit it.
That's definitely a combo that's only
possible because of the setter's height.
Kogane, nice toss!
Thanks!
A toss that takes advantage of his height...
That huge setter's pretty fun.
Haikyu!!
Date Tech                   Aoba Johsai
Go, go, let's go! Let's go, Date Tech!
We're going to catch up!
One block here!
Jingo, nice serve!
Got it!
Nice receive!
All right!
Great, great, Toru! Push it,
push it, Toru! One more time!
And a dump!
Right when I thought he was laying low today.
So calm.
So frustrating.
Date Tech                     Aoba Johsai
One more point! One more point!
And now Seijoh is at match point.
Calm down! Let's break it off with this one!
Right!
Hanamaki, nice serve!
Nice!
The Seijoh players have
all improved their serves.
Cover! Cover!
Yeah...
Left!
Futakuchi-san!
All right!
Futakuchi, go!
Yeah!
All right!
Nice kill, Futakuchi! Go, go, Futakuchi!
You see our juniors?!
You'd better be watching!
And now,
their first-year setter
is on the front line.
All right!
Onagawa-senpai, nice serve!
Futakuchi's the ace, and good at blocking.
Then the center of the iron wall, Aone...
And then the third... Koganegawa.
Without a doubt, right now,
they are the best set of three
blockers in the prefecture.
Nice serve!
Sorry! It's a bit short!
Iwa-chan!
Yeah.
One touch!
Pantaloons!
Got it!
Kogane!
Right!
Or rather, you don't need to do
a feint when doing a dump attack.
Huh?
Smash it!
Whoa. This time, he did
a dump and smashed it.
Nice kill, Kanji! Go, go, Kanji!
You wouldn't be able to get
that even if you saw it coming.
Yeah!
All right! Break!
One more! Go!
Date Tech                        Aoba Johsai
Hey...
Hm?
Do what we usually do...
Let me take this challenge.
Got it.
Oikawa tossed away from
the net to avoid the block, right?
Apparently Iwaizumi didn't like that much.
Well, it does make it harder to hit.
One more point!
Nice serve!
Got it!
Saku-kun, nice receive!
But it's gonna go over the net!
It's up!
Just one more point!
Cover! Cover!
End it with this!
Stop it!
Don't let them have it!
Iwa-chan!
Yep!
Right now, I'm basically a
baby as a setter.
If there's anything right now that
I have that is equal to my senpais,
it's my height!
We're not going to let it...
...end here!
Your resolve is weak,
you little first-year!
It went through the middle of his arms!
That's awesome, Iwaizumi!
You awesome guy!
You're amazing, Iwaizumi-san!
Nice kill.
I guess I still have a lot to learn.
He faced those three blockers head-on.
I hate to admit it, but that was awesome.
Date Tech                   Aoba Johsai
Thank you very much!
I guess we know...
...who we'll face next.
Line up.
What do you mean, "Geh?"
Futakuchi, you jerk.
You still suck, Kogane!
I'm sorry!
And the new captain totally
has his hands full.
Do you understand how
important Moniwa was now?
I've always known that!
Good grief...
I only see potential here.
Not to mention, a lot of potential.
Keep working hard, even
more than you have been.
You guys will form the
ultimate iron wall yet.
All right, let's go.
Huh?
The fact that you guys are here means
you have time on your hands, right?
Come back and practice with us.
What?
I guess we don't have a choice.
Don't start stripping here.
Kamasaki-san, are you getting so bulked up
that you can't jump anymore?
Huh? Why?
Well, muscles are heavy.
Huh...
Seriously?
I...
I'll get to the point where
I can lift any kind of ball!
And I'll be able to block!
So I won't shame the title of the iron wall,
I'll make sure I'm able to stop anyone,
no matter how powerful or big they are!
Opponents that are hard to stop
aren't always big or strong.
Hinata Shoyo...
Next time, I'm definitely going to stop you.
Aoba Johsai                                Karasuno
I-Is everyone on edge for some reason?
Last time, they gave their
all against Aoba Johsai,
and still lost.
Y-Yachi-san...
Yes?!
D-Do you have any stomach medicine?
Are you all right, Yamaguchi-kun?
Shimizu!
Sorry, I'm just a little nervous.
I... I'm pretty confident when
it comes to being nervous!
Huh? Confident? About being nervous?
It's better when you voice your nerves.
Saying,
"I'm so nervous! What should I do?!"
instead of holding it in
makes you feel much better.
I regularly experience live-threatening
fear because of my nerves,
so I've done a lot of research.
Life-threatening dangers?
Like sports festivals and tests!
Tests?
Well...
Yes?
When we had our Inter-High
match against Seijoh...
When the team was in trouble,
I was brought in as the pinch
server for the first time.
Aoba Johsai                                Karasuno
We weren't that far behind in points.
If I had made it, we might have won.
And yet, I blew it...
When I think about that happening again...
Y...
You were put in charge of
something that important?!
Yachi-san?!
I'm getting nervous.
My heart's going to pop out...
right out of my mouth!
Swallow it back in!
Do you want some stomach medicine?!
Do you need assistance?! An AED?
What's going on?!
Yachi-san's heart!
Her heart! Waaah!
Calm down, Yamaguchi!
Should we call 110?!
It's 119.
Hey, where're you going?
I wonder if nerves are like a cold
and you get better when you
give it to someone else.
You all seem better.
Why are you trying to explain this rationally?
Kageyama-kun, are you having
your freak-out time, too?
Yeah.
Oikawa-san's strong.
You really can't handle the Great King, huh?
Well, I'm in the same boat.
You were looking forward to fighting him.
You can't help what freaks you out.
You're stronger when all
six of you are strong.
Huh?
I heard Iwaizumi-san say
that to Oikawa-san before.
Of course we're stronger
with six, you dumbass.
At the time, I was wondering why
he said something so obvious.
Of course you're stronger
if all six players are strong.
But now I really understand.
Iwaizumi-san was talking about
adding everyone's strengths together.
He was talking about multiplying them.
No matter what team he's on,
Oikawa-san is able to bring out the
spiker's strength better than I can.
Really?
Even if that's the case...
But we're Karasuno, remember?
All right, is everyone here?
It's almost time.
All right, let's go!
Yeah!
We're going to get our revenge...
...with our new quick!
Ma'am, can I get another pork cutlet bowl?
You're eating way too much.
That's your fourth one.
I'm gonna strive to become
the ultimate iron wall,
and try to grow until I'm two meters tall.
Er, you should be striving
to learn how to play better...
Episode 20: "Wiping Out"
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"Wiping Out."