Listen to me, Kousei,
I want you to study the
sheet music over and over,
and play it again
and again and again.
That's how you're going to perfect it.
Just what the score calls for,
just as the composer intended,
perfectly and precisely.
You're off again! How many
times do I have to tell you?
You're not going to bed until
you can play that passage!
Take a good look at it! It's
all there in the sheet music!
Arima's No. 1 again? Well, his mother
is a direct disciple of Mr. Hashimoto.
I bet there's sheet music
plastered onto those glasses!
Plus they'll hide the bruises
from when she hits him.
He practices seven or eight
hours a day, right? Everyday!
When does he get to play?
Most people couldn't
stand a life like that.
He really is just like a machine.
None of them know
what they're talking about.
I'm the only one who's on Mom's side.
Go!
But will you be okay? What about
practice? Have you rehearsed together?
No worries! We'll figure it
out! Because we rule!
Don't underestimate us jocks!
I can make you time to rehearse!
Wait, shouldn't you guys be in
school? And whose bike is this?
Hey, don't sweat the small stuff!
Just barely, but...
Safe!
Kousei!
*Twitch*
We're here!
We made it!
Let's do this!
*Grab*
*Drag*
Thank you both! We'll be going, then!
Kousei, your shoes!
Sneakers aren't gonna cut it!
Put mine on!
Hurry! Hurry!
Better than sneakers, at least!
Tsubaki... Watari...
Thanks. I'll be going now.
Get out of here, moron!
Come on! We're cutting it close. Run!
Slow down a little...
Move!
You think Kousei
can pull this off?
Spring will be here soon.
Huh? It's almost May, when
the cherry blossoms scatter.
Yeah. But... I just know...
...that spring will come.
Towa Music Competition Committee Sponsor
Second Annual Towa Music Competition
Violin - Middle School Divison
Next, No. 12, Nashida.
Please get ready.
All right! Your goal
is to go out on top!
Y-Yes, ma'am! I'm gonna try to
go out on top... I-I'll do my best!
Oh, man, that's putting the pressure on...
This is beyond crazy. I should have
spent a lot of time practicing this,
memorizing it with
my whole body,
fine-tuning it to the point where I
don't need the sheet music anymore...
But I'll practically be sight-reading
when I coordinate the piece with her.
And on top of that, such a...
Such an insanely
out-of-control violinist!
All set!
What tempo should we use?
Take-no-prisoners, maybe?
This is crazy, it's reckless!
No way can I turn in a
decent performance like this.
Do I look good in this dress?
It's brand-new.
If I just man up and back out
of this, it won't sting as much.
We're only gonna humiliate ourselves,
going out like this.
Ignoring me?
Whaaaat?
So tell me, did
that calm you down?
What's the big idea,
all of a sudden?
Look at me.
Look up, and look at me.
You're always looking down.
That's why you're imprisoned
inside that cage of music scores.
Don't worry, I know you can do it.
You were listening to it
all during lunch break, right?
The sheet music was always
somewhere in view, right?
I know you and I can do it.
Mozart's telling us from up in the sky...
"Go on a journey," he's saying.
"A man away from home
need feel no shame."
Let's go out there and
shame ourselves like crazy!
Together...
No. 14, Ms. Kaori Miyazono,
please get ready to go on.
Let's go!
Are you listening, Kousei?
Just what the score calls for...
It's all there in the sheet music.
Naïve... Bizarre...
It's like I'm on a rollercoaster.
I'm being jerked around and around.
It's like this girl herself is the
journey with no clear destination.
You're freedom itself.
No, I'm not.
Music is freedom.
This silence belongs to us.
Every single person here...
...is waiting for us to
start producing sounds.
Come on, let's go on a journey.
Saint-Saëns is waiting for us!
Here they are!
My Kaori-chan!
Hey, the accompanist is a kid, too.
Huh?
Wait, could that be...
I've been waiting for you,
Kaori Miyazono... Hmm?
She's got a different
accompanist. A kid, at that.
What are you doing?
I can't set my chair just right.
Hurry it up, you slowpoke.
Adjust it with both hands!
He somehow looks familiar...
It's Arima. The pianist.
Arima-kun?
I see. So that kid's
Kousei Arima, huh?
That's right. He's grown up since then, but
that's the face of the pianist, Arima...
Kousei Arima.
So they know each other?
Actually, why is he accompanying her?
Finally got it right.
Jeez!
Huh. Synthetic and all-natural.
Talk about a mismatched couple!
What kind of performance
do you have planned?
Elohim, Essaim... Elohim,
Essaim... I implore you...
Your face is totally frozen.
A song dedicated to the
virtuoso violinist, Sarasate.
Saint-Saëns's Introduction
and Rondo Capriccioso.
All right, that was a good start.
I can hear the notes, too.
I'm glad we're doing this song.
There are some parts
where I could go off-key,
but if I listen closely to the violin,
and keep an eye on the sheet music...
Technically, it's not a difficult song.
Ah... Kousei's playing
the piano again...
Kaori Miyazono... In a complete
departure from her previous performance,
she's being docile here.
Out of consideration
for Arima, maybe?
And now she's showing her true colors!
Awesome!
The notes...
They're vanishing...
The sound of the piano...
I can't hear it!
Huh? What's going on?
Huh? The accompanist...
The sound is out of sync.
Kousei!
The accompanist who
never played a false note,
who played with such
stunning precision...
...is starting to unravel.
As if I'm at the bottom of a
dark sea, I can't hear anything.
There's no one here.
It's dark.. It's dark...
It's dark. I'm at the
bottom of a dark sea...
...and I'm going to be all alone.
He's pounding on the keys, but
this isn't the accompaniment, is it?
This accompanist blows.
Too bad, I did like the violin.
In spite of your inexperience,
you were holding your own till now.
What got into you
all of a sudden, Arima?
The piano is destroying this performance!
Dammit, dammit, dammit!
I'm pounding the keys so hard...
So why?
Why is it that the only thing I
can't hear is my own playing?
Probably a smart move.
A deduction's inevitable,
but if he keeps on playing,
it could affect the violinist.
Lousy piano playing!
Don't mess it up for her!
You shouldn't have been
playing from the start!
Sorry... If I keep playing like this...
If I play... I'll only
make trouble for you.
No way! Now even the
violinist's stopped playing!
Does this mean
they're disqualified?
Well, not disqualified, but...
This is unheard of!
It's over for them.
Why did she stop?
There's no reason for her to
accommodate that awful accompanist...
And she was so cool...
Don't worry.
I know you and I can do it.
I hereby appoint you as my accompanist.
You still have to play!
But I want you.
I'm going to play with everything I've got.
So that the people who've heard me...
...will never forget me.
I'm a musician, after all!
Again.
Maybe there's only a
dark road up ahead.
But you still have to
believe and keeping going.
Believe that the stars will light
your path, even a little bit.
Come on...
Let's go on a journey!
Are they allowed to start over?
It's allowed as long as it's
within the time limit,
but nothing after
they stopped will count.
This competition is over for that girl now.
Then...
...what exactly is she playing for?
What are you doing, Kousei? Are you
gonna make Kaori-chan play by herself?
Kousei...
For you...
For you... I'm casting about
for an excuse again.
I know you and I can do it.
There was resolve in your eyes.
So what was it that you saw in me?
But you have me.
Look up, and look at me.
Look at me...
Brace yourself...
Now we're talking!
Kousei!
He started playing.
But they still sound out of sync.
What are you going to do, Arima?
Focus... Focus...
Focus!
Both the sound and the notes are
disappearing like nobody's business.
All week long, the sheet music
was always where I could see it.
All during my lunch
breaks, I listened to it.
Whatever I have inside of
me... Draw it out!
Focus, focus... focus...
Focus!
Are you listening, Kousei?
You mustn't play so violently.
The piano is you.
If you touch it gently, it will smile.
If you pound it with force,
it will become enraged.
Touch it like you're
caressing a baby's head.
All right, again.
Twinkle, twinkle, little star...
How I wonder what you are...
Up above the world so high...
Like a diamond in the sky...
Twinkle, twinkle, little star...
How I wonder what you are.
If you can't hear the sound,
then imagine it!
Play it with your whole body!
Draw out what Mom left me!
Hey, come on, Friend A...
Don't you dare try
to steal my thunder!
Are you kidding me?
Wow, Kousei! Kao-chan!
You're amazing!
She's beautiful.
Well, this is outrageous. They're both
out of control. It's like a brawl.
And the audience is
entranced by this brawl.
Of course he's not used to this.
He's not an accompanist.
He's a soloist, just like her.
She moves me.
With such power,
like the pounding of my heart.
I can hear your sound.
You're here.
April will be ending soon.
Bravo!
You were great,
middle school duo!
That was awesome!
Encore!
During a serious competition!
The dry air-conditioning,
the scent of dust.
I...
I'm going on a journey.
Departure
Episode 5
Dark Skies
Watch Again Next Week!
Two People on a Bike is Forbidden By Law