Bathroom...
Whoa.
Ow!
Sorry, Kobayashi.
Oh, no, it's all right.
Beer, beer.
Oh, pardon me.
Juice.
Kanna, it's cramped!
It's getting cramped here.
Lady Tohru, move!
A three bedroom apartment, right?
Yes. As close to this
area as possible please.
How's this?
Hmm...
Frankly, there's not much
difference between them.
By the way, the roof of this
property is a communal space.
Oh?
The sky's so vast!
It feels nice!
How is it?
We'll take this one.
Well, time to start moving preparations.
First, we clean up.
Yeah!
Cleaning, cleaning, la la la.
Beat the dust and crush it.
Weird song.
Leave no dust or trash behind.
Death to the world,
now clean, clean everything.
That sounds too dangerous!
Hey, Tohru, do you like being clean?
I suppose so. I like bathing
and brushing my teeth.
Brushing your teeth? Do you have
a dragon-sized toothbrush?
No, I use my claws to scrape out the bugs.
Bugs?! Not bacteria?!
Well, they're so small I never notice them.
Must be hard having a huge body.
Yes. I went through a lot of trouble
searching for places to live.
Ah, figures. What kind
of places did you choose?
Sometimes caves,
sometimes ruins,
sometimes mountains.
I've even slept up in the sky a few times.
Are you a migratory bird?!
Still, I guess you could
live anywhere in that case.
Well, actually...
Whenever I stayed in one place too long
humans would soon start coming around.
They were so annoying.
You were like a rare monster.
So not only did my body keep getting dirty,
I had a hard time bathing at all.
Hmm.
When we had no other choice,
we'd lick each other clean.
Huh?!
Kanna and I did that before.
That's naughty by human standards!
*They were actually in dragon form
Maybe so.
Well, most other dragons
don't even care about it.
We don't get sick or unhealthy either way.
Wow, I'm kind of jealous.
To be honest,
Miss Kobayashi, you're sloppy.
You leave beer cans scattered about,
you leave your clothes lying
where you took them off...
Wh-What does it matter?
That's one of the nice
things about living alone.
Also, you keep books arranged out of order.
Now that's just being too picky!
Ahem.
Understood. I'll overlook the books.
But please clean up your trash and clothes.
This is my home.
You can't. Because Kanna
will pick up those habits.
Fine.
My father must have felt this way
when my mother yelled at him.
Still, Tohru,
I keep doing that by accident because I'm
happy you're here to clean it up for me.
Huh?!
It's a piece of a cake for
a mighty dragon, after all.
Miss Kobayashi!
So please keep helping out, okay, Tohru?
Yes! With pleasure!
Simple-gon.
Scoundrel Kobayashi.
Well, next up's packing.
Though, nearly all of it is
my personal belongings.
Sorry for making you help out.
No, please ask anything of me!
I'll do my best, too.
Hey, Kanna. Pack properly...
Miss Kobayashi, so cute!
These dead-fish eyes are to die for!
Lady Tohru, you're a pervert.
What are you slacking off over?
Oh, this was still here?
Miss Kobayashi.
Whoa, sorry!
Miss Kobayashi!
Is this yours, Miss Kobayashi?
It is, but...
Please try it on!
I want to see you in a maid outfit!
I won't.
Huh? But you bought it
intending to wear it, right?
I got my arms into it and then
despaired at how bad I looked in it.
So I'm not wearing it again.
Then would you mind if I wear it?
Go ahead.
Thank you very much!
Sorry for the wait.
Lady Tohru, so pretty!
Yeah, I think it looks good.
Thank you very much.
Still, your clothes are bit
too tight in the chest for me.
That said...
Are you really a D?
I'm a D among dragons.
Ah, so good!
Good work, everyone.
Yeah, thanks, you two.
Bath, bath...
Hmm?
Does anyone know what happened to the towels
and change of clothes in the bathroom?
I put them away properly!
Huh?
Which box has the clothes and towels?
Good morning!
Sansan Moving Service!
Yes, welcome.
So this is a car?
Well, let's decide how to use the rooms.
This will be the living room.
This will be for the PC and books.
This will be my bedroom.
And this...
will be the room you two share.
Huh?
Our room?
Yeah. You two can use it however you like.
Yay!
A new life, huh?
Shall I wash your back?
Huh? No, it's fine.
You like it when I make things clean, right?
Ugh, that's your angle?
All right, come on.
Yes.
By the way.
Yes?
Isn't it easier to wash
your body in that form?
Well, it is, but it's a little limited.
Besides, there are a lot of
rules in this world.
It's all a little stifling to me.
You don't like having a human form?
No!
This is its own thing.
I see.
I'm coming in, too.
Lady Tohru, wash me!
Oh well, fine.
Cramped, it's cramped.
Here I go!
Morning, Tohru.
Good morning, Miss Kobayashi.
Tohru.
Yes?
I'll wash your body as thanks for yesterday.
Huh?!
Over here, over here.
Y-Yes!
Ah, feels so good!
Feels like I'm washing a car.
Thank you so much, Miss Kobayashi!
You're welcome.
Ah!
This is my old apartment!
Damn it, I screwed up!
Episode 3
Start of a New Life! (That Doesn't Go Well, Of Course)
Tohru, you're too loud!
Huh?
Do you see me as a loud person?
Sorry, sorry.
Kobayashi, does your hangover hurt?
Yeah.
Still, I can't believe it's
like this on my day off.
The noise is coming from the neighboring
apartments and the floor above us.
Shall I go make a complaint?
Yeah, could you, please?
Make sure not to let your horns stick out.
Roger that!
If they won't listen after I speak to them,
I'll murder, destroy, and pulverize them.
You don't have to do that.
Sasakibe
I'll start with Ms. Sasakibe on our right.
Coming.
Hello.
Oh, you're from next door.
I'm Tohru. Hello.
Hello. Did you need something?
Well, we heard loud noises and they've
been bothering us, so I came over.
My, was it that loud?
What were you doing?
Cooking.
Huh?
Hold on a moment.
Here, let me share some.
They're stewed rapeseed blossoms.
Thank you very much.
My apologies, but could you please
be more mindful of the noise?
Sure.
How does she make that
much noise making this?
Yana
Next is Mr. Yana on the left.
I'm playing music.
Music?
Yeah, want to listen?
Rar
Your voice sounds like Hades
is crushing Hercules.
What a phrase! I'm taking it!
Anyways, please try to keep the volume down.
Sure.
Soune
Last is Mr. Soune on the floor above.
I'm using a drill for work.
A drill?
I'm making hand-carved wooden ornaments.
Oh, is it a gorilla?
This is well done.
Anyway, one of us is
suffering from a hangover,
so please try to keep the noise down.
All right.
You're the loud one!
No, you two are being loud!
The loud one is the one calling people loud!
What's gotten into everyone?
That drilling is too loud!
That death metal voice is too loud!
That strange noise is too loud!
That's cooking!
Huh?!
Your voices are being too loud.
Sorry.
Humans keep making the same mistakes.
They're beyond help.
Guess I'll kill them.
Um, may I have a word here?
What bothers us the most is having others
be loud when we'd like some quiet.
So why don't we organize the times we
don't want each other making noise,
and make a schedule?
If there are still times that don't
work out, then we can use earplugs.
Are you all right with that, Miss Kobayashi?
They're all creatures that haven't learned
anything since they evolved from apes.
That goes for me, too, you know.
Well, anyway, I usually wouldn't
mind if I weren't hung over.
Besides, it's only natural
to cause some bother
to others when people go about their lives.
Especially so if they're neighbors.
Jeez, you're too kindhearted.
Besides,
I wouldn't like it if it
were too quiet either.
I'm going to rest a bit.
Okay.
Am I loud?
There are times when I think so.
Does it bother you?
It's difficult to give a precise
answer to that question.
But...
I think a life like this is acceptable, too.
I'm sleeping now.
Okay. Then I will, too.
You're too loud!
Everyone, thank you for your hard work.
Soon the cherry blossoms will be upon us again this year.
So with regards to that, we'd like to follow up on last year
and host a flower viewing party for company staff.
Please organize a list of those who wish to attend
within each team and deliver it to General Manager Furukawa. Please try to attend if possible.
The time and location are in the attached file.
That is all, thank you.
General Manager Furukawa
What should I do about this?
I don't like the consideration that
has to be shown when rank's dropped,
and not being able to order certain liquor.
Straight to the point, huh?
Well, then why not create
an excuse to refuse?
An excuse?
A party?
Yeah. I was talking to Takiya-kun
about gathering here at this apartment
as an excuse to turn down my
company's flower viewing.
Huh? You're inviting him here?
Come on, don't make that
face now. He's a nice guy.
Hmm, all right. I'll put up with that then.
Put up with it?
In return, can I call
some of my friends, too?
Friends? Like from the shopping district?
No, dragons.
Huh?
Don't worry.
They're all well-behaved dragons.
Hmm, I'm only worried.
I'm home.
Welcome home!
Pardon me.
Welcome, come on in.
I'm not welcome at all, am I?
You must be Kanna-chan. Good evening.
Good evening.
Nice goth-loli.
Where are your friends?
They should be here soon.
Yes?
Please wait one moment.
Mr. Fafnir, please arrange yourself
like in the picture I sent over!
Good grief.
This world is full of trouble.
Fafnir
Makes me want to end it.
Hostility
Miss Kobayashi, this is Mr. Fafnir.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
It's an honor to make your acquaintance.
I'm honored.
Your friend has been very kind to me.
I'm Kobayashi from Jigokumeguri
System Engineering.
That's a polite social greeting.
Polite social greeting?
I've been living with Tohru-san.
A magic set of words that allows
even shy people to greet others.
I hope we can get along well in the future.
Tohru!
I got a really hostile
feeling from him just now!
Well, he may have a slight
dislike for humans.
He's a cursed dragon who's been guarding his
treasure in a cave since ancient times.
He's a shut-in?!
You invited more?
This is the last.
Unacceptable
Oh, Tohru!
Hello, it's been a long time.
Miss Kobayashi, this is Miss Quetzalcoatl.
Quetzalcoatl
Nice to meet you. Lucoa is fine.
Why are all dragons so huge?
Huh?
Never mind.
Nice to meet you. I'm Kobayashi.
Something wrong?
Um, did you walk here in that outfit?
I did.
Your outfit is kind of slutty, though.
Wha?!
Care to try?
Once you cut into them, back away.
Yeah, like that.
Oh, you can't run in while
he's doing that move.
Try again.
Uh-huh.
Good job defeating him.
Now, ignore that treasure chest...
That was a mimic.
Ah, you died.
He's hooked.
Tohru hardly ever used to smile.
Must be thanks to you.
I'm just a normal human being.
That girl's never had
anything normal before.
Not just her, but her friends as well.
Lucoa-san,
I'm grateful to Tohru, too.
I didn't use to smile much myself either.
Though I'll never say it to her.
Food's ready!
Yes.
Well, let's eat then.
Can you drink?
Drink?
I can, but at least let me check
it for curses first.
Curses?
Long ago Ms. Lucoa was driven out of
her seat as a goddess thanks to liquor.
She was forced to drink liquor
her comrade had cursed,
and in her drunken stupor she
went to her little sister and—
Don't say it!
Dragons don't have very
good pasts, do they?
Like I said!
When it comes to butlers,
I fancy middle-aged ones!
This is out of the question!
Stop it! You'll make me screw up!
No, no, lately young, handsome,
but devilish butlers have been pretty
good in their own way!
I said stop it!
Not having that wisdom of life aura
means they're out! Got it!
She's a completely different
person when drunk, isn't she?
Yes.
Hey, you woman there! Become a maid!
Huh?
Tohru, you, too!
I already am one, though?
I've told you before, that's just cosplay!
If you've got complaints, then strip!
Besides, what's with all of
you and your absurd chests?!
Huh?!
Fafnir-dono! We must avert our eyes!
Why don't you share some with me?!
Stop it! I can't see!
But that's impossible.
Wha?!
If you can't, then strip!
Hmm, yeah, some people
move their bodies to it.
Next Episode
Fafnir-dono, ignore that treasure chest.
That's a mimic.
Ah, that chest is also—
That was a mimic, too.
Why do you reflexively
go after all the chests?
Episode 4
Kanna Goes to School! (Not That She Needs To)
It's my nature.