Now, go.
You have your power now.
The last place upon which you stand
will become your true home.
Chise!
Are you trying to mess with me?
Do you despise humans so
much for tying you down?
She'll be back if she longs to come home.
Besides, it ought to be more convenient for
you to keep her with you in a non-human form.
A human life is more brittle than that
of a failure born in the forest.
You all avoid me, saying that's what I am.
But I hate the cold.
How absolutely endearing.
It's so beautiful and fun.
I'm, um...
What was I?
Chise...
It seems like someone's shouting by my ear.
How far should I go?
I feel like I could go on forever.
To where there are no people.
Are you leaving?
I am.
I'm being called.
Where to?
Over there.
Is that what you want?
Yes, it's what I want.
If it's what you want, I'll go with you.
But is there nothing left
for you back there?
Back there?
I... What was it?
Chise.
Chise, there is a lot
that I still don't know.
I need you with me.
Do you really?
Yes, I do.
Without you, it's so cold and lonely.
I hate the cold, too.
So I'll go home.
It still feels like there's
a fog over my brain.
It's a kind of curse.
A curse?
This hide turns the wearer
into a werebeast.
Though this hide is that of a fox.
The hide of a werebeast
answers to one's wishes.
What an awful thing he left me with.
Ask me when you want to use it.
This certainly was mischievous of him.
And he's gone.
I don't want to use it.
What if I'd gone to the other side?
I'll stop you if that's not what you want.
Stop me even if I do want it.
Good night.
Chise!
Save Joel!
Chise.
He hasn't woken up all day.
I can't do anything for him.
Chise, get on!
But...
It'll be fine!
You are a good lock, an old lock.
I am your good oil.
I am your golden key.
Mr. Joel!
Mr. Joel?
Chise...
So this is why you bolted out.
Elias.
What's the matter with that man?
He's almost dead.
A Leannán Sídhe.
What's the matter? Aren't
you going to eat him?
He's your prey, isn't he?
N-No.
I wouldn't eat him!
Not even a single drop of blood!
Not even a speck of his life!
A human's fate is sealed...
once they're haunted by a vampire, is it not?
No...
No!
I'm not haunting him.
I have to get away.
If I go away, he might...
It's too late.
You've already put your hand on him.
Elias...
No matter far you go, it's...
Elias!
I'm sorry.
Can you keep an eye on Mr. Joel?
Sure.
I don't love him.
No.
I don't love that man.
I don't!
If I loved him, we would have to
follow through with that love.
Night time...
How do you feel, sir?
Are you the grim reaper or something?
Something like that.
My girl has been in your care.
Her name is Chise.
She sure was a good girl.
You don't have much time.
It's not something you can
have treated at the hospital.
Kind grim reaper, may I ask
how much time I have?
A week at most.
Will I suffer?
Likely not.
That's pretty good, then.
It's been a pretty good life.
Are you not afraid?
Of course I am.
Everyone fears death.
It's not something I can avoid, though.
My wife passed away young.
We were introduced to each
other through our parents.
We hadn't married for love,
but still, I was devastated.
But the rose garden that my wife had
left me saved me from my despair.
It must have been no more
than a midsummer illusion,
but I met a beautiful woman there, too.
I'm content.
That said, if I could just meet that woman
with eyes like red currants once more...
I ask for too much.
A fairy ointment?
May I make some?
Why?
We can rub it on his eyelids.
It'll let even an ordinary person
like Mr. Joel see her.
That ointment isn't meant
to be used on humans.
The neighbors would be
furious if they found out.
But I want him to have just one glimpse.
To share just one word.
No.
...is what I'd like to say, but okay.
I've never heard you make demands before.
However, you'll not be pushing yourself.
Got it?
Yes.
How did you let that happen?
I wonder.
You need to keep it in that state.
I can't help you this time.
Sorry, I can't help, either.
It's all right.
Fairies hate being seen. Even familiars.
Elias, do you think I can do it by myself?
I'd prefer that you didn't,
especially given your frail body.
I want to do it, though.
Just this once.
When I use magic, I stare really hard.
Then I can see light dancing. Playing.
This is what they call magic power.
One moment, it takes on the
color of the stars at night.
The next, it's blue as the sea,
or green as the forest.
At times, it whitens, like the morning sun.
Together, like a crib, entwined.
I did it.
Yeah, that looks good.
Now you have to maintain
it for the next five days.
Right.
Don't you dare push yourself.
If something happens, tell me.
Got it?
Yes.
I feel something important
leaving my body.
I'm scared.
Is someone there?
With the flowers that
bloom in spring water,
from old gold coins submerged
within it, an incense is made.
One day in the full moon, and then in each
of the four directions of the compass,
it's bathed in moonlight and sunlight.
I have to stay with the
medicine jar the whole time.
I can't even allow myself to sleep.
Even then, there's only a 50-50
chance that it'll work.
Why are you doing this for me?
That's what you do for others, isn't it?
It's just that I want people who
smiled at me to keep smiling for me.
Humans are so foolish.
And selfish, too.
How many days has it been now?
It's the fourth day.
A little longer.
I smell it.
There's a scent.
A scent of joy.
Huh.
They're up to something fun.
Oh no, I fell asleep.
Good work.
Elias...
Don't worry, it worked.
You just barely made it.
You can do with it as you please.
Do what's right for you.
Am I dreaming?
I couldn't even get out
of bed until just now.
I feel like I've been
sleeping for a long time.
I finally meet you.
You...
It's all because you found me.
It's your fault that I can't leave you.
It's your fault.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
You said you were scared!
You're scared of passing on by yourself!
It's my fault.
Thank you for loving me,
Leannán Sídhe, lover of poets.
It's not as if I never knew.
You can have my life, if such an
old life is good enough for you.
You can have all of it.
But, but.. I did nothing
but take from you, Joel.
I never gave you anything.
Sure you did.
Since my wife died, my life had
been going on nothing but inertia.
But one day,
just for a brief moment, our eyes met.
They were so, so beautiful.
I wanted to see you again.
That, by itself, gave my life
a push against the inertia.
You're such an idiot.
You're making it even harder
for me to leave you.
I don't know where I'm going next.
Maybe I'll even get to be at my wife's side.
But I will surely, surely
come to your side, too.
As long as I'm not alone,
as long as someone's waiting for me,
I'm not the slightest bit afraid.
So I want you to have this life of mine.
You idiot, I didn't even get to reply.
You humans really are foolish.
You're so selfish.
I'm going to stay here.
I'll wait here until the end
of the world for Joel to come back.
Thanks, Chise.
Are you sad?
I think so.
You're crying.
I don't understand.
What do you think, Elias?
I don't know.
But seeing you cry makes me
feel a little uneasy inside.
I'm sorry I couldn't be your teacher.
It's all right.
You should get some rest in bed.
Yes.
Boo!
Hey.
Oberon.
The fairy ointment: Eyelid Joy...
It's a big no-no for a human to make that.
Sorry, but can I have the rest?
Here.
The price of violating
the taboo was far too great.
The girl, consumed by the
festering shadows of death,
is given a hand by the fae, but...
These children become weaker and weaker.