This is Burnett, ARUS Golden News.
Did you all witness that shocking video
message from the Dorssian chancellor?
We have come here to Module 77's hangar.
What's he doing at the Phantom?!
What could be the truth
behind those images?
Phantom?
To be honest, this may be the first time
I have ever sensed anything this eerie.
What is this? It's full of people!
What are they doing?
What is being done to these people?!
Dad!
Dad! Dad!
Iori...
Dad!
No! Dad! Dad!
It's no use, he's gone.
What are they doing here?!
This is a JIORan ship,
isn't it? Answer me!
Hey, make them stop!
Murderers!
Stop this right now!
What are you talking about?
That ship isn't ours!
Eileen!
Why did this have to happen to her...?
This is the truth behind Module 77!
Upon learning of the threat they posed,
we made the difficult
decision to invade JIOR.
For the good of the entire world,
we took a stand against them!
They fought against us
with unkillable soldiers!
Before you censure Dorssia,
I want you to see the
reality for yourselves.
I will say this again.
The creatures that dwell within
Module 77 are not human beings!
They are monsters who survive by
draining the life out of humans!
What kind of house of horrors
have we stumbled into?
We've been lured into a monster's nest?
Prime Minister Sashinami,
I demand an explanation!
I have no idea what this is!
It's not like that!
We were going to tell you about
the Phantom after the summit!
Haruto? What is that?
What's this "Phantom"?
You knew? You knew about
that strange ship?
Well, I... I'm sorry.
This was a close brush with death.
If the Dorssian chancellor's accusation
had come just a little later,
we would have ended up on
these monsters' dinner plates!
No, it's not like that!
In accordance with international law,
I hereby designate the
residents of Module 77
as Class 7 Special Hazard Organisms!
This was inevitable.
They got too close to the secrets
lurking in the shadows of the world.
So, it played out exactly
according to your plan.
I should have known.
It is nothing that warrants
being praised over.
On the contrary,
I'm rather disappointed that the
resistance I expected failed to materialize.
What's going on?!
What do they mean, monsters?!
We're human beings!
There has to be some kind of mistake!
What have you been
going on and on about?
I'm asking you what you
guys did down on Earth!
Is it just the pilots
who are those monsters?
Hey, dial it down! We
didn't do anything—
You're another one like
Rukino, aren't you?
Fess up!
What are you people doing?!
Stop it!
Don't touch me!
We aren't monsters!
You guys are the strange ones!
What did you really go
down to Earth to do?
She's right! That weird ship
belongs to you guys, remember?
That's—
Is everyone who went
down to Earth a monster?
Stop it! Everyone, stop it!
We all risked our lives to go to Earth!
Please, Mr. President, hear
our side of the story!
Yohei?
There has to be some mistake!
Please, Mr. President—
He's been shot!
Yohei! Yohei!
They aren't human!
They're Class 7 Special
Hazard Organisms!
They're creatures who have survived
all this time by fooling us humans!
Don't waste your compassion on them!
Think of it as vermin eradication!
Wait, we aren't—
Stop it!
Stop!
Don't, Shoko!
No! No!
Don't shoot!
We don't know anything!
Please, no more shooting!
No more killing!
Over my dead body!
A Valvrave!
Keep this up, I shoot.
Mr. President, let's go!
I thought the hangar
was under our control!
Please don't... Please don't...
Let go! The students! The
students are being butchered!
Don't do it!
If you run out there without a plan,
you'll just get yourself killed!
This is the Moon! It's
neutral territory!
That rule only applies to human beings!
As far as they're concerned,
we no longer count.
Attention, humans of Earth.
I am the president of ARUS.
Today, we have come face to face
with a threat to humanity itself!
To meet this unprecedented
danger, we have made a decision.
The decision to set aside
long-standing grudges
and come together as
a single human race!
Today, we announce the formation
of the ARUS/Dorssia Allied Forces!
Our countries will immediately assemble
all our forces on the Moon's surface!
As a joint force, we will launch a
concerted attack against Module 77,
the threat against humanity!
This is a battle which we must not lose!
For the future of all humanity!
Valvrave pilots, can you hear me?
Allied Forces are going to
swarm all over us soon.
This Module is a lost cause.
I want you to rescue as many
students as possible and
guide them to the hangar.
We'll escape in shuttles.
Otamaya! Take your buddies
and get to the hangar!
What about Units 1 and 5?
I'll keep 'em safe! Just go!
Don't forget to bring the weapons!
I won't!
Hurry! Keep moving!
We have three shuttles!
Split up and get aboard!
You idiot, she's already dead!
No, she's coming with us!
Do you think she's gonna
come back to life?!
What are you talking about?
Because she's my friend!
I'm sorry, but we can't bring her.
In a situation like this,
we can't save everything.
But we've been friends
since middle school!
I'm sorry!
Let's move!
Stay calm, everyone!
Look at everything
we've survived so far!
So we're going to be
fine this time, too!
Have faith in the classmates around
you and let's make it through this!
I believe in you, too.
You had a reason for
this, right, Haruto?
This can't... This can't be happening!
Save the regrets for later.
I won't let anyone else die.
Let's get moving!
The space shuttles are
already launching!
We're all right now. We are, aren't we?
I hope so.
What is it?
I'm picking up ships!
This number can't be right...
Put it on the monitor!
That's...
Answer my question.
You had possessed
K-zwölf's body, correct?
In which case, you had ample
opportunity to kill me.
Why didn't you?
You don't intend to answer me, I see.
In that case, let's return
to the more pressing topic.
The matter of L-elf.
Our only option is a high-velocity
launch using the
mass driver to blast
through the combat zone.
All Valvraves, protect the
mass driver and ships until
all three shuttles successfully launch.
We're going on ahead!
Make sure you rendezvous with
the last shuttle, Akira!
I know.
As soon as they're ready,
meet up with them right away!
If you get left behind, it's all over!
I know!
One shuttle left!
Oh, no!
Mass driver damaged! Energy
supply system down 40%!
Necessary charging time for
launching now 720 seconds!
That long?!
It's impossible! We can't
possibly hold out that long!
Haruto...
Receiving external transmission!
It's... The president of ARUS!
ARUS?
My memories are disappearing?
That's what's happening?
We have a problem!
There are Dorssian soldiers
aboard the shuttle!
There's what?!
It looks like they snuck
aboard during the escape,
and they're holding everyone hostage!
Understood! I'll be right there!
Is everyone okay? Where's
the Dorssian soldier?
Haruto, don't! Run!
Run from what?
What's going on?
Haruto!
Iori, what are you doing?
The president of ARUS gave us his word.
If we handed over the Valvrave pilots,
he would spare the rest of us.
He what?!
Can you blame us?
After all, the rest of
us are human beings!
The only ones who eat humans
are you and the other monsters!
Iori! Don't!
Haruto! Haruto!
Haruto?!
Come on! Come on! You can't be dead!
No! No!
Why did you shoot him?!
Haruto's... He's...
H-He killed my father!
They killed him! Haruto
killed him and the others!
Haruto...
He was shot. Right through the heart...
He's alive. He really is one!
What did I tell you? He's a monster!
W-What happened?
Haruto...
You're one too, Haruto?
Shoko, hear me out...
You knew everything?
About Miss Rukino?
About that ship?
I...
Why didn't you tell me about your body?
I believed in you!
It was because you were there
that I was able to hang on.
No matter how bad a scrape I was in,
I always had faith that
you were the one person
who would always be by my side.
Just like in the cave when
we ran away from home.
Ran way? The cave?
Haruto?
What? We ran away? When was that?
My head hurts...
I'm sure there was
something more here...
You don't remember?
I'm positive that there
was something. But now...
there's nothing.
What did I lose?!
The Haruto that I knew is gone.
What are you talking
about, Shoko? I'm—
Don't touch me, you liar!
All this time...
You've been lying to me.
Prime Minister, your decision.
Shoko...
All Valvraves, please stand down!
Shoko-chan?
We are going to hand
over Haruto Tokishima
and surrender to the Allied Forces.
What?!
Shoko, what are you saying?!
This is the only way.
I have an obligation to
protect everyone's lives.
As prime minister.
You gotta be kidding me!
What do you think we've been
fighting all this time for?!
Don't make yourselves out to be heroes!
You're nothing but monsters!
All this time, you've been killing
people while you were
pretending to be our friends!
Just like you killed my father!
Monsters, huh?
He's got nothing to do with this!
There's no telling what he might do!
It's too dangerous to take him with us!
You give me too much credit...
Huh? What's it doing?
No! This isn't what he said!
The fools.
Did they honestly think
that the president
of a country would
negotiate with vermin?
He lied to us? No way...
Let's run! Fire the mass driver!
I can't! It's not charged yet!
Why? You're a monster...
We're not monsters!
We're Kamitsuki!
Aina came up with it.
She said we were touched by God,
so she called us "kamitsuki."
If he's everyone's God,
but is so stingy that
he only saves those
who believe in him, forget him!
Even if you don't believe us,
even if you hate us, I'm
still gonna save you!
Stay back!
What the hell are you saying?!
You and Akira, stick
close to the shuttle!
Escape with them using the mass driver!
What about you?
I'll rescue Haruto!
Inuzuka-senpai, what are you—
I've been watching you
and Haruto for years.
It's gonna end like
this? I don't buy it.
That's all.
Charging complete!
Oh, crap!
Yamada, I'll let you block
the shot! Use my shield!
Here it comes!
Senpai!
Damn it!
Now to... get Haruto!
Senpai?
Shoko and the others are in the clear.
The last order of business is you two.
I'll at least... get
you to the Module...
It's no use! Leave us
and escape by yourself!
Haruto...
Let me ask you something.
How do you feel about Shoko?
How can you ask me that
at a time like this?!
It occurred to me that I'd
never heard it straight
from the horse's mouth...
How about it?
I liked her.
No, I still like her.
And I bet I always will.
I knew it. I knew it all along.
Senpai!
Next time, episode 22.
"Fist of the Moon."
Valvrave the Liberator...
The system that will expose
the truth of the world.