Sakura Hall
"Let's Make a Game!" Pitch
I fell asleep...?
Good morning, kouhai-kun!
What are you painting on my walls?!
It's the Milky Way Cat, Nyapollon!
Nyapollon?
It's a character from a
full-length anime series that...
I've been working on since
I was in kindergarten!
That...
...is the robot protagonist, Nyapollon!
He's a weapon designed to protect Earth
from the Nyangoro space invaders.
After they beat their
first Nyangoro invader,
they study it, cultivate its cells...
and warp space-time to
create a hybrid robot!
However, it can only
be piloted by someone...
who has experienced the
worst life has to offer!
What a ridiculous plot.
Nekoko, the heroine,
has a boyfriend, Nekosuke,
who gets killed by the enemy
commander, Ein the Hunchback!
Nekoko decides to cast aside...
her sadness and pilot Nyapollon!
But Ein the Hunchback is so powerful...
that 60% of the human race is...
Um, how long does this story go on for?
already dead by the start of the series.
52 episodes altogether!
I could probably summarize it in three days.
How about you stop now!
I woke up early for once.
I don't want to be late on the
first day of second semester...
That clock's stopped.
Huh?
Because I removed the batteries!
Don't do stupid pranks like that!
And don't just carry on
drawing in silence over there!
Suimei University of the
Arts Cultural Festival
#09 The Fall Storm is Here
I just made it.
You should've said something
to me before you left.
Sorry. I'll start doing
that as of tomorrow.
Hey, did you hear?
Aoyama-san moved into Sakura Hall...
so she could be with Kanda.
I heard that Kanda basically ordered her...
to go and move in with him.
I heard that they share the same room.
Nanami's so forward!
This is strictly confidential,
but I heard that she's already pregnant.
I'm not pregnant!
What's this? You're not
denying the rest of it?
You really did move into
Sakura Hall, didn't you?
I did, but we have different rooms!
Kanda-kun, don't just keep quiet! Tell them!
I can't believe I've been caught up in this...
Save me, darling.
You can do it, husband!
Stop it!
Quit bothering Nanami!
Miyahara?
Miyahara-kun?
I-I mean, quit bothering
Nanami and Sorata.
Sorata's not an immoral guy.
Isn't that right?
But they really do live
under the same roof, right?
Miyahara, why are you
getting so huffy about it?
Well, because I... you know...
Sorata's my friend,
so I can't just ignore any
weird rumors about him...
I shared a room with Sorata...
in the regular dorms in our first year.
Of course you're gonna share a roof...
By the way, why are you blushing, Miyahara?
with someone if you live in dorms.
Huh?
I've got it! You're the one
dating Kanda-kun!
What?!
I see!
You don't want Nanami to take
your beloved Kanda-kun away!
Miyahara-kun, how gallant!
I support your relationship!
Oh, I see...
Kanda-kun and Miyahara-kun are an item.
They do make a good couple.
So they're both gay!
Miyahara...
How did it come to this?!
K-Kanda-kun! Don't worry!
You can love whoever you want!
Whoever you choose to love,
we'll still be friends!
Don't get carried away with the crowd!
...which is how I had
such a terrible first day...
of second semester because of weird
rumors going around about me.
It's all because of the way
the residents of Sakura Hall...
conduct themselves on a daily basis.
From now on, let's follow the rules...
and lead pure and proper high school lives.
All right?
Okay, okay.
Only say it once!
Okaaaay.
Don't draw it out!
I'm so glad you're here, Aoyama.
Thanks for the food.
I had terrible things
happen to me, too.
On top of that, I almost got hit
by a hearse on the way home.
When I tried to get out of the
way, I stepped in the gutter.
I even got clawed by a black
cat that just happened to be there.
Talk about an unlucky first day.
All I can do is pray
nothing else bad happens...
Don't involve us in your misfortune.
Kouhai-kun, settle down!
S-Sorry.
This weather really does seem foreboding.
Must be a fall storm.
Okay, okay.
Only say it once!
Good evening. I apologize
for dropping in so suddenly.
A-A foreigner?!
Are you dazzled by my beauty?
You're dazzled by my
beauty, aren't you?
I-I cannot speak English.
It's Rita.
Mashiro!
You seem to be keeping
well, Mashiro. I'm glad.
You, too.
She's a real doll!
She's a babe! Mashiro-chan,
do you know her?
Oh, it's Rita.
Good to see you
again, Chihiro-san.
Who is she?
She was Mashiro's roommate
when she lived in England.
I'm Rita Ainsworth. Nice to meet you.
But, Rita, what are you doing here?
Cinderella's magic has been dispelled.
Or as you Japanese might say:
I'm here to take Kaguyahime
back to the moon.
Mashiro, please come back...
to England with me immediately.
What?!
You came here to take
Mashiro-chan back with you?
Yes. I cannot allow Mashiro to
continue studying manga here.
I won't go home.
I thought you might say that.
But please reconsider.
Don't you realize how much
potential you have in those fingers?
Your paintings may even
go down in history.
There are lots of people itching
to see your next masterpiece.
Won't you scratch that itch?
You encouraged me to draw manga.
I only taught you how
to use a computer.
I never encouraged you to do anything.
Rita...
I can't sit back and watch you waste
your time and talent any longer.
Come, Mashiro. Together, we—
I'm not going home.
W-Wait, just listen to me, Mashiro!
Hey, are you sure about this, Shiina?
Mashiro, I won't give up!
I will take you back to England with me!
Do you hear me?!
You're going after her?
I can't just leave her out there.
You want Mashiro-chan to
go back to England?
I can't just leave her!
I figured you'd come.
You knew I would come?
When a damsel's in distress,
a kind boy always comes to save her.
I brought her back here,
but this is crazy.
She immediately said she
wanted to take a bath.
Honestly, English people...
Sorata.
Wh-Why aren't you wearing any clothes?!
I don't have a change of clothes.
I intended to return home straight away.
Just put some clothes on!
This belongs to Mashiro, doesn't it?
I do her laundry for her.
As her former roommate,
you must understand.
I see. You're on Mashiro Duty in Japan.
You did that in England, too?
Yes. Over there, I was on Mashiro Duty.
You can look this way now.
Mashiro drew half of this, didn't she?
You can tell just by looking?
I've been with Mashiro since we met...
at my grandfather's studio when
we were six years old.
I don't draw anymore, though.
Why not?
You'll let me stay in this
room tonight, won't you?
Y-You're staying here?!
I haven't booked a hotel.
Or are you the type of person who throws
someone out after you've taken them in?
Fine. I'll sleep in the dining room.
No, you'll sleep here, as well.
With you?!
I want you to tell me about
Mashiro's life in Japan.
Don't you want to know
what Mashiro's life...
was like in England?
Is Shiina really that amazing?
Mashiro's overwhelming.
Overwhelming?
It makes me wish she'd just disappear.
You should be careful.
If you stay by Mashiro's side,
you'll be destroyed, too.
Just like I have been...
Destroyed?
Her paintings will go
down in history...
Please reconsider.
Don't you realize how much
potential you have in those fingers?
Kanda-kun, it's already past eight.
N-No! Don't get the wrong idea!
Our relationship is pure, proper,
and appropriate for high schoolers!
It's fine that you let her stay here...
but you've become awfully
close, haven't you?
Sorata, are you on Rita's side?
No, I...
Yes, he is.
I have decided to stay in Sorata's room...
until you agree to come
back to England with me.
What?! Without even consulting me?!
Sorata's my enemy.
I'm not!
Congratulations, kouhai-kun!
You have now reached adulthood!
Today is the day I relinquish
my title of Flying Ace.
It's all up to you now, Sorata!
Kanda, I've always thought
you were pretty annoying.
That has no bearing
on this situation at all!
You're too loud first thing in the morning.
What is this place, a zoo
during breeding season?
Y-You...
I'm what?
You! You came out of your room?!
I haven't seen some
of your faces before.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm Akasaka Ryunosuke.
I'm the occupant of Room 102.
You have received a message!
Akasaka-kun, are my
lessons boring you?
I have no interest in most
things in this world.
And I hate women,
so don't talk to me.
You finally came to school for
the first time in five months.
It'd be nice if you at least stopped eating
tomatoes and listened to my lesson.
Tomatoes are nutritious and scrumptious.
I'm only here to increase
my attendance scores,
so there's no reason for me to listen.
If you have a problem with
that, you should come up...
with a lesson I can actually take
some interest in, Shiroyama Koharu.
How dare you talk
balk to your teacher?!
What's your problem?!
I'm going to tell
Chihiro-chan about this!
What are you going to do about Rita-san?
Do you want Mashiro to go back to England?
Some things can't be done over.
No good will come of me overthinking this.
Shiina's the one who has to decide.
Here, your laundry...
You idiot.
You're an idiot.
Ultimate Melon Bun
You're a Sorata idiot.
What kind of idiot is that?!
Let the "Japanese and English
Declaration of Friendship...
Lines I Always Wanted to
Say Once" event begin!
Here we go again...
I'll start!
I'll give you half of this world.
Next!
Driver, follow that car!
Nice, Rittan! You're next!
Me?
Do you want the good news
or the bad news first?
You're next!
I'm next? U-Uh, um...
Don't spout such nonsense... or something.
My turn.
Will you go on just one date with me?
If possible, I'd like to go out tomorrow.
Your—
What do you think you're saying?!
Unfortunately, I'm busy
for the next ten years.
Your turn.
I don't mind waiting ten years...
to go on a date with
such an incredible girl.
Back to you.
What are you guys talking about?!
He made that all up!
They're all lies!
We're speaking out of order.
We skipped Mashiro.
Mashiro-chan, it's your turn.
Sorata is an idiot.
Hey, have you come up with something
for this year's culture festival yet?
I guess I should do an oil painting.
Hey, let's go buy some paints together.
Yeah, let's.
Oh, Shiho.
Why don't you come with us, Shiho?
Let's all go together.
Huh? Okay...
Shiina, I'm here to—
I feel like I have to tell you
this now, so I'm texting you.
I'm confused, too.
She just suddenly turned up,
and said she was taking
you back to England.
When she said your paintings
would go down in history,
it really made me think.
It made me wonder what's
actually best for you.
I'm not on Rita's side,
but I'm not sure I'm
on your side, either.
It's just...
I'm really looking forward to
your serialized manga. I mean it.
Sending
Does she even know how
to check her messages?
Received Message
Shiina Mashiro
Re: No Subject
Received Message
Shiina Mashiro
Re: No Subject
You
What do you mean, "you"?
For "Sorata is an idiot."
That doesn't have "you" in it!
Men, the day has finally arrived!
Hey! Misaki-senpai, I
can see your underwear!
Come down from there, Senpai!
Now that we've assembled the
strongest warriors of Sakura Hall,
we must harness our power of friendship...
and take control of the culture festival!
In other words, she's saying
that the residents of Sakura Hall...
should band together and do
something for the culture festival.
Oh...
I don't mind.
Sounds fun.
Huh? Well, I'm all for it.
Ryunosuke says: "No problems here."
Everyone approves, so it's decided!
If we're gonna do something,
we should make something
only Sakura Hall could make!
Yeah, but...
Misaki-senpai and Shiina
could do the art,
Jin-san could write the script,
and Aoyama could provide the voices...
With talent like that, we could
make an amazing video.
And Sakura Hall even has the Dragon!
Ryunosuke
A programmer!
The Dragon?
She means Akasaka.
His name's Ryunosuke,
and the "ryu" means "dragon."
Mitaka Jin: Misaki and Mashiro will do the artwork, I'll
write the script, and Aoyama-san will do the voices.
Akasaka Ryunosuke: Same as always.
Mitaka Jin: Could you use your talents to help us make something
interactive like a game instead of just a simple animation?
Should we create something that
uses a controller, like a game?
I see.
But if we do that, only one
person at a time can enjoy it.
Is there any way...
that we can make it an attraction
everyone can participate in?
Everyone?
For example, when the audience claps,
the character moves,
or raises its arms...
I was just wondering if there was
a way to make something...
that allows everyone to work
together to move the story forward.
That's it, kouhai-kun!
I think that sounds fun, too.
I think it's a great idea, too.
Good, good! I knew you
could do it, kouhai-kun!
I can feel your burning passion!
I'll notify Ryunosuke.
If you've made a decision,
be sure to submit your plan to the
Student Council as soon as possible.
You can't participate if you
don't receive permission.
The Student Council...
Is something wrong?
No, nothing. In that case,
we'd better start developing
our content soon.
We're starting from scratch so
we don't have much time.
Nyapollon.
That's it, Mashiron!
Ryunosuke says that if
we borrow equipment...
from a hardware store, we can
turn Sorata's idea into reality.
That's amazing! Just what
is Akasaka-kun, anyway?
All right!
The director will be... Kouhai-kun!
It's up to you!
What?!
No objections!
We're counting on you, Kanda-kun!
Mitaka Jin: Sorata will be the director.
Akasaka Ryunosuke: No complaints here.
Sorata, fight.
What? I'm supposed to... lead this bunch?
A culture festival? That sounds fun.
Yeah, but the situation has
gotten a little out of hand...
Rita.
What is it, Mashiro?
Rita, sleep in my room from now on.
What brought about this change of heart?
You can't sleep in
Sorata's room anymore.
You don't have to worry about us.
Unlike Jin, Sorata's good for nothing.
Hey! Do you have any idea how hard...
my rationality's been fighting every night?!
I don't mind sleeping in Mashiro's room.
What?
But I have one condition.
Sorata.
What? Me?
This Sunday, go on a date with me.
What?!
Th-This is...
...where we're going on our date.
But this is a hotel!
It sure is.
You wouldn't embarrass me...
by turning me down in front
of a hotel, would you?
No, let's wait!
We should definitely wait on this!
Hey, stop it!
I'll be gentle.
What?! What are you going to do to me?!
Kanda-kun!
What a coincidence.
You said it.
I refuse to believe in
a coincidence like this!
Now, now.
Since we're all here, the four
of us should go in together.
The four of us?
European Young Artists
Modern Art Exhibit
So, this was your actual destination.
I-I'm kinda nervous...
Y-Yeah...
Sorata, over here.
Shiina?
I wanted to show you this painting.
It's the last painting Mashiro
did before she came to Japan.
Has this helped you understand
Mashiro a little better?
I read the manga Mashiro
wrote over here.
I don't really get manga,
but even so, I didn't think it was
worth giving up painting for.
What do you think, Sorata?
Shiina should...
return to the world of fine arts.
My routine has been upended
by that freeloader.
#10 Hate Hate, Love
Why's she going to the bathroom
at 6:45 in the morning?
That's the time I use it!