Ko!
Ohana...
Ohana!
Ko!
Hey, what are you doing here?!
I... Well...
The Kissuiso is....
What about it?
Why...
Why do you...
It seems like the Kissuiso is
going to be closing soon...
...have such kind eyes?
Ohana?!
Episode 24
Sui Shijima, The Final Boss
Have you calmed down a bit?
Yeah.
Ko, you get the corn kernels out of
these soups in a weird way, right?
Don't you pour water in it,
pour the entire thing into a cup,
then pick it out with chopsticks?
I... stopped doing that.
Huh?
I just leave the corn
I can't get in there.
Huh? But it'll rot.
No it won't. It won't ever change.
Remember when you said
that the scenery in Tokyo was boring?
I'd never even thought that in my life.
But after you left...
the scenery's been nothing
but boring for me.
Ko...
Your mom showed me
the video of you working
at the Kissuiso.
My mom?!
I was really surprised.
I've never been there,
so I didn't know anything
about it.
But you were there, and
just because of that,
I felt as though I'd seen it before.
I think that I enjoyed the scenery here
because you were here, too.
I'm not too swift on the uptake.
Listen, I've been really frustrated.
I felt like you left me behind.
But it's obvious enough...
I felt as though you picked
the Kissuiso over me.
...for even me to understand...
But after seeing it, I kind of
started liking the Kissuiso.
So...
...Ko's feelings...
...and what he's about to say.
I don't know what kind of
misunderstandings you have in your head,
but I...
Ohana?
Hey, what are you—
Don't say all these things!
I want to say them!
I'm the one who wants
to say things to you!
Listen, I...
I...
I want...
Want...
I want you to come to
the Bonbori Festival!
Sure.
Sorry.
I will.
Hey, Ohana!
Don't cry.
Ohana!
I realized that the scenery I'd
always found to be boring...
The scenery that has Ko in it,
was so beautiful.
Expressway Bus
Yes, okay.
I'll be going on ahead, Aun—
I mean, Sis.
Don't you want to see your mom?
Nah, not yet.
Not until I decide what I want to do.
All right!
Hey.
I figured I should learn lots of
stuff from you before you quit.
If only I'd been more competent,
things wouldn't have
turned out this way.
Ohana and Takako still aren't back...
Yeah...
It's the tourist season,
but we only have reservations
during the Bonbori Festival...
Maybe we really are done.
You can leave for school now.
Oh, but...
Hello, you've reached the Kissuiso.
Huh?
What are you dozing off for?
I'm sorry.
Mr. Ren's shift is over
early tonight, right?
Yeah.
He says he's going out drinking
with the owner of the next
inn he'll be working at.
When you're as good as Mr. Ren,
every inn wants to have you.
W-What about you?
To be honest, I've been
invited along with him.
Minko?
Hey!
Did you cut your hand? Let me see.
You're fine. Don't scare me-
Are you guys going to leave me behind?
Well, they're not going to
hire someone who's underage...
What should I do?
What indeed...
What should...
One man, and one knife!
I'll train my cooking skills
no matter where I am!
Yeah.
It's a line from a manga I used to—
"Teppei, the Wandering Chef"!
Y-You know that manga?
Yes! Teppei was the one who
inspired me to become a chef!
Oh, right!
Wow! These bring back so many memories!
Dude, the Tuna Bowl!
Yeah! He leaps into the
ocean because he says
it tastes best when it's alive!
He duels with a swimming tuna in the sea!
And then he makes a meal out of it!
Now that I think about
it, it's pretty gruesome.
Yeah? I thought it was
a pretty good idea...
Huh? You were also a fan of this?
Actually, the person who wrote this...
was me.
What?!
When I was starving, an editor
friend of mine encouraged me.
I wrote a draft.
Well, even though this
manga didn't really sell...
I still kind of like it.
I've always been inspired by Teppei...
So the one who determined
my future was...
this perverted freak?!
What's wrong?
You want an autograph? Do you—
There you are!
It's a crisis, guys!
I don't know...
Yo!
I don't know what's going
to happen to the Kissuiso,
but I'm going to stay
until the very end,
even if there aren't any customers.
I'm so sorry.
We appear to be fully booked on the 8th...
I'm... home?
Yes, please give me a second.
Nako?
I'm sorry, only the Wave
Room is open on the 8th...
Hello, you've reached the Kissuiso!
Mr. Ren, ten customers
are booked for the 7th!
Which means the meals will be...
That customer can't eat abalone or tuna!
Yes, you've reached the Kissuiso.
There's a fax.
No tuna?!
Uh...
Oh, Ohana!
Quick, help us!
Reservations just started
popping up out of nowhere...
H-Huh?
What's this ruckus?
Madam Manager!
Check this out!
Oh, welcome back!
This is a magazine I
bought at the airport.
The Kissuiso is on the opening page
and we got an amazing review!
What?!
Let me see.
Hey, let me see!
Did you have breakfast, Miss Satsuki?
Not yet.
Let's go.
Where would you like to eat?
I'd like some wine.
What?
What's wrong with that?
Kissuiso
This is amazing!
"They put so much effort into
every detail of comfort,
and their meals are comparable
to those of famous restaurants"!
Awesome!
But when did they visit us?
Another undercover person?
Who cares about that?!
We can do it.
Now we can do this.
Young master...
The Kissuiso!
If we start grabbing
customers with this,
we might even be able
to rebuild this place!
Y-Yeah!
Let's use this as the start to—
No.
The Kissuiso will close after
the Bonbori Festival.
It's already been decided. That's that.
Madam Manager...
But why?!
The calls for reservations
are coming nonstop!
Why should we quit when we
have the wind at our back?!
Mr. Ren,
I heard that you've already
secured a spot at the Hatago
Inn, along with Tohru.
Um, I'm free...
And I hear a small restaurant in town
is trying to scout you, Tomoe.
I-Is that true?
Hey, I'm...
I'll call them and cancel our offer.
We want to work here!
Yeah! As long as this
place can continue running—
Don't trouble your next workplace
for selfish reasons.
You're the one being selfish!
We...
We don't want to leave the Kissuiso!
Why are you being so stubborn?
"It's already been decided"? What—
Get back to work.
Madam Manager!
Don't accept any more reservations.
Do you hear me?
Madam Manager...
I wonder if the young master and
the others are still discussing...
Yeah.
They said they're thinking of a
way to convince the Madam Manager.
I wonder what she's thinking.
Everyone says they want to stay here.
Yeah.
She's so mean...
Nakochi?
Everyone loves the Kissuiso!
Things are finally looking up, and she's...
She's being so mean!
Nakochi's angry?!
I'm going to talk to her—
M-Madam Manager?!
That was fast!
N-Nakochi!
U-Um, about this morning...
I...
Um, there's something I want to...
The Madam Manager...
She bathes really fast,
and this place is cleaner than
it was before she came in...
I'll talk to her!
Ohana...
Madam Manager!
Why are you so fast?!
Ohana.
Yes?!
Don't be busy tomorrow.
Huh?
Ohana and the Madam Manager?
Yes.
They left early this morning.
To where?!
It's going to be busy this weekend.
Oh, and she said to send someone
to the Bonbori Festival
in the late afternoon
to help with preparations.
The Bonbori Festival?!
That's low on the priority list!
As I thought, the Madam
Manager won't budge.
Hello, you've reached the Kissuiso.
Oh, I'm sorry, reservations for next week are...
Yes, I'm sorry about that.
Reservation for the 9th?
Of course we're open.
Yes, a room for three?
Okay, thank you very much!
Young master...
I don't know what she's
being so stubborn about,
but we have to convince her!
Huh?
The Kissuiso can operate without her orders.
Enishing...
Grab a wet cloth.
Okay.
He'd be so disappointed
if he were alive.
Huh?
It wasn't possible to get them back,
the days we were full of dreams...
The busy days where everyone
was so focused on work...
"It wasn't possible"?
We still don't know that—
You don't need to pay the burden.
He and I started the
Kissuiso out of nothing.
We didn't know anything
about running an inn.
But the Kissuiso is different now.
It's full of the traverses we've made.
It's not nothing anymore.
It'll take a while to
even get to nothing.
Are you talking about money?
Everyone's already begun
walking their own paths.
There's no need for you all
to be stuck with our dreams.
You can start from nothing—
No.
We all love the Kissuiso!
We can't turn that feeling into nothing!
The inn doesn't just belong
to the two of you anymore!
We all want to work here.
It might even become our dreams, too!
Madam Manager?!
Hello?
It's me.
Oh, Enishi.
Thank you oh so very much for
having pity on the Kissuiso.
I didn't.
I just did my job and wrote
everything I actually felt.
And besides, all it created
was an opportunity.
Just a small oppo—
I know.
I'll use this as an opportunity
to have customers return more often.
I won't be in your shadow forever.
What the heck?
I'll make the Kissuiso popular.
Bye.
I'm sorry.
It's fine. Please rest for a while.
I'll leave some tea here.
Thank you very much.
I was so worried.
I thought you'd have to
be hospitalized again.
I'm just a little tired.
This isn't the first time I thought
about shutting down the inn.
Huh?
I realized it when Satsuki ran away,
saying she wouldn't succeed me.
"An inn to make Sui happy."
That's what it was.
I wanted to realize my dream with him.
I made Satsuki and Enishi endure
so much just for my selfishness.
I sacrificed them for my own happiness.
Madam Manager...
Enishi decided to be the successor,
even though there were other
things he wanted to do.
He, Satsuki, and I have all been
stubborn since Satsuki had left.
We were all focused on the Kissuiso.
But that isn't right.
Enishi isn't fit for this kind of work.
And so, all of the workers
will suffer because of it.
If Enishi and the workers are
going to be unhappy,
I just want to free them.
I want to free them of his and my dream.
You're old, aren't you?
You shouldn't get up!
Ohana, you...
I said that because I don't really
get what you're saying.
I thought perhaps it's really hard to
understand what old people are saying.
Madam Manager?
Sheesh, you're so...
Though I don't understand you,
my anger towards you is gone.
I can't agree to it,
but I'll fest it up anyway!
Until the Bonbori Festival!
Yeah, I'm counting on you.
Thank you.
Huh?
What is this about?
Everyone in the union is supposed
to help out with the Bonbori Festival.
It's unforgivable for only the
Kissuiso to not participate.
We're sorry.
We have so many reservations,
so we're still preparing...
This is what happens when
a magazine features you.
Hey—
I'm terribly sorry.
Madam Manager!
We'll send someone to help, too.
I don't care who, stop what
you're doing and go help.
You guys...
I-I'll go.
Ohana!
No.
Go.
Huh?
Ohana...
Well, then.
The Kissuiso will change.
Give back the Kissuiso I love!
Tsurugi likes you, Ohana.
Is work really about winning or losing?
Episode 25
The Kissuiso I Love