The Deucalion?
Why would they...
They had no choice but to
make a frontal assault?
Control! This is Mustang Leader!
Please respond!
Princess 1!
Highness!
Princess Asseylum confirmed alive!
Control to Mustang Platoon,
do you copy?
Lt. Marito!
Amifumi?
Is the Deucalion okay?
Is everyone on the bridge okay?
What about Nina and Calm?
Are they okay?
Somehow.
Well, maybe "We're all okay"
isn't quite honest...
This might be more of a "Don't worry,
go on without us!" kind of situation.
Inko, sorry...
Warrant Officer Kaizuka...
Princess 1, continue your mission.
Can you do that?
Yes, ma'am!
Amifumi. Kaizuka Junior. I want you
to cover Warrant Officer Kaizuka.
Acknowledged.
Roger that.
Warrant Officer Kaizuka taking over
as pilot. Princess 1, continuing mission.
Kick their asses for us!
Mustang 22, roger!
You awake?
This is going to get a little rough.
Hold on tight, Highness.
You are... Inaho's older sister?
You didn't seem to be hurt,
but if I missed something, speak up.
Why...?
You hate us... Don't you?
The Versians who did this to Earth
and took so many lives...
You hate us, don't you?
Seylum.
What does it take
to end a war?
Do you know?
Well, if both sides wish for peace
and set aside their hatred...
No.
Warfare is nothing but a means
of negotiation between states.
Wars break out even when
there is no hatred.
Territory, resources, or interests
that you are determined to own.
Ideology, religion, pride.
Wars are fought over those
objectives all the time.
Meaning that when those objectives
are met, the war will end.
That, or...
...the war will end when the
human cost outweighs the gains.
Anger and hatred, those are nothing more
than tools to tilt a war in your favor.
I'm not interested in
those emotions.
Inaho...
So I wouldn't hate anyone
just because they're Martian.
Oh? I would gladly hate
a Terran for that fact alone.
All units, scatter!
Saazbaum of the Vers Orbital Knights'
37 Clans has arrived.
Please make your peace,
Your Highness.
Count Saazbaum? It was you?!
How did he tap
our encrypted comms?
All units, restrict further
communications to laser comms!
Yuki.
Continue the mission. Inko, you
provide support for Yuki.
I'll hold him off.
Don't be stupid! You don't know
what his combat capability is!
You can't win alone!
I don't need to win. I only
need to slow him down.
Inaho...!
You aren't planning to act
as a human shield, are you?
That's an ineffective means
of buying time. Go, hurry.
Inaho...
Good hunting.
Thanks.
Let's go!
Yes, ma'am!
Inaho!
I like your reckless courage,
warrior of Earth.
But you will have
no mercy from me!
Decoys confuse guided missiles.
But unguided rockets are unaffected.
Mustang 11, path secured.
Don't get too full
of yourself, Terran!
Light of Aldnoah!
What?
Milady...
Give me your strength!
Behold...
...the Dioscuria!
My rounds, they're...
Dimensional barrier, activated!
Energy joints, linked.
Field generator, active.
Blade field, engaged.
Sword drawn.
That weapon, it's...
Is the princess
on that ship? No...
This is Oldenburg Leader.
Stand by for assist, Mustang 22.
No! Fall back!
Fools.
Fly, my servant!
Count...
Surrender, Martian!
Put your hands above your head!
Come on!
Terran forces have entered the castle!
We need to shore up our defenses!
You saved me?
Even though I'm a Terran?
Who are you fighting against?!
Who were you pointing
your gun at?!
I don't see anyone here who
turned his gun on his own!
So stop asking stupid questions!
Damn, one of 'em got in...
It's powering up! Contact the Kataphrakt
platoon inside the castle!
Auxiliary power system, start.
Will it work?
No luck, huh?
Its Aldnoah drive is shut down.
It will never move again without someone
who has been granted activation rights.
What do I do?
It- The Aldnoah drive
powered up?
But how?
I really wish they'd give it a rest
with those things!
There is an
inspection passageway.
It is a detour. It will take us
to the Aldnoah chamber.
It is not designed for equipment
access, so we will have to
abandon our Kataphrakts
and proceed on foot.
Mustang 11!
Roger!
Let's move!
Yes, ma'am!
Inaho?!
Princess Asseylum.
Your life, if you please.
Count Saazbaum!
Bastard!
He has a barrier, too!
Inko, get out of here.
Inaho!
Hurry.
No way, I can't just leave you!
Don't worry about me, just run!
Don't be an idiot!
Dodge it...
Mustang 11!
Like I thought, he has to lower the
barrier when he launches his arms.
It's because the arm thrusters
interfere with the barrier.
Hang on... Did you use me
as a decoy?!
You don't say?
The barrier needs to have a gap.
If you're watching at the instant he
raises the field, it's easy to spot.
The antenna to remote-control
the flying arms!
You try my patience!
Nao, run!
No, I've been waiting
for him to get close.
Why, you little...
And they can't raise a barrier
along contact surfaces.
Why, you...
Count Saazbaum?
I can't hit him!
How can it be that fast?!
It's like it's anticipating the
trajectory of our bullets precisely!
Princess, hurry!
Coming!
Now you, Inaho!
No.
You go on ahead.
I'll be right behind you.
Lead the way.
Of course!
This way!
Filthy Terran!
You dare?!
Damn you!
Your kind could never understand...
The envy and hatred towards Terrans
that had been planted in us
constantly tarnished our souls and robbed us
of our ability to live as human beings!
You, with your lives of indolence
in a land of plenty,
could never understand
how we feel!
The resentment at having that
hatred ingrained in you!
The sense of futility when
you realize what was done!
The regret of failing to protect
the one you love...
You could never understand!
Count!
Orange!
Go! We'll hold them off here!
Hurry!
Optical seeker, down. Routing auxiliary
sensor feed to main monitor.
Right arm, power cut.
Left arm...
I will defeat all who hate...
I will break the cycle of hatred...
In the name of
Asseylum Vers Allusia!
Count!
Sleep!
Milord...
Inaho...
Are you all right, Inaho?!
Princess Asseylum!
Seylum?
Inaho! Thank goodness...
I have shut down the Landing
Castle's Aldnoah drive.
The operation was a success.
Now, we should escape, too.
Sorry... I can't see very well.
I have blood in my eyes.
I am right here, Inaho.
I am right here.
Count Saazbaum...?
You saved me, Slaine...
Well done.
Don't.
That is far enough.
Do not touch Her Highness,
...Orange.
Bat.
December, 2014.
Count Saazbaum's Landing Castle,
which had attacked United Earth's
headquarters, had fallen.
The battle had ended in victory
for the United Earth Forces.
There were many casualties
on both sides.
The whereabouts of Princess Royal
Asseylum Vers Allusia of Vers
are still unknown.