Ow!
It's because you're wearing all that!
What's the big deal?
It's over anyway.
No, it's not!
There's gonna be a jump-rope
contest on the return trip, too!
You saw the red meat that
the winning team got!
We can't take last place again!
We need to pull out of fish tier, at least!
It's not red meat!
What?
Shirase-chan, you're quite
adept at jumping rope.
Is that weird?
No, but you just didn't seem like the type.
Why not?
Defying expectations is kind
of Shirase-chan's thing.
Like, she's clumsier than she looks.
More short-tempered than she looks.
More selfish than she looks.
What's that supposed to mean?
Someone's birthday?
Um...
I'm in love!
A Place Further Than the Universe
Antarctic Love Story
(Blizzard Arc)
30 Likes
1 Comment
#HowsTheLoveLife #CantPutItIntoWords
High School Girls' room!!
You gotta KNOCK
You're in love?
With the team captain?
Um...
Zaizen Toshio.
You're in love with her?
Something wrong with that?
Of course there's something wrong with it.
Everyone you tell gets so exasperated
they lose their capacity for words.
See?
You're wrong!
They're just so stunned
by my sudden confession...
We're too exasperated to speak.
Really?
By team captain, you mean Captain Todo Gin?
The beautiful, smart, determined...
Seems pretty out of your league.
That's so rude!
I'm allowed to be in love with someone!
I've always loved strong women like her!
Why?
I feel like... they could protect me.
You could just die.
Did you just say something to me?
Something truly cruel?
I'm really sorry.
You said it before, didn't you?
That you wouldn't bring romance onto the ship.
That's why I've held back until now!
But I can no longer stop myself!
I would love to hit you.
You basically are hitting me!
So, why did you come to us?
Well, I heard that the captain had an
old friend among the high-schoolers...
I was wondering if you had any information...
He means Shirase-chan!
How long have you known her?
I first met her about ten years ago, but...
Got any pictures from that time?!
Okay, you need to maintain a
five-meter distance at all times.
When was that decided?!
But she was just a friend of my mother's.
I never talked to her much.
I see. Then what am I going to—
Just give up on her, like I said!
Toshio, you're such a—
That's it!
Including the expedition members' love lives
in our reports will make them more exciting!
Report?
I see! That's a great idea!
We've never even touched on it before!
Isn't that in poor taste?
It's fine.
Apparently our views have
been in the pits lately.
You think people will watch?
Of course they will!
Whatever they might claim,
everybody loves things like that!
You mean, my love for the captain will...
...be broadcast to the whole
world over the Internet?
No, Zaizen-san, you can go back to your room.
We'll take it from here.
Sounds like you're in the way.
A Gift From Penguin Farms!!
Soft-Serve Day
Come eat!
What kind of person she was?
Yes! The captain's personality,
her relationships with men...
I told you before. She was just someone
my mom knew. I didn't especially...
She never really talked much.
I'm gonna buy some cabbage. Look after her.
Wait! What should I...
Here, your change.
You shouldn't give money
to people you don't know.
Serious?
Sounds more eccentric to me...
So, what about her love life?
How would I know about that?
I was still in kindergarten back then.
We'll just have to ask her ourselves, then.
Ourselves?
We'll set up an interview, and lead
the conversation in that direction.
Like a press conference with a celebrity!
"How's the love life?"
Why are you asking me?
Wait, who's supposed to go ask her?
No! No!
I feel like we've been through this before!
Have we really?
Why are you so desperate not to do it?
You talked to her on the deck
before we set out, remember?
You were watching?
Why would you ever think we weren't?
You seemed close enough to me!
No, we just happened to
run into each other, so...
You don't get along then?
I don't know if I'd say. It's more like...
There's a distance between us.
You talked to her on the
deck before, didn't you?
You saw that?
You seemed close enough to me...
No, we just happened to
run into each other, so...
We always had trouble
communicating with each other.
So whenever Takako would leave, we'd just...
A penguin!
What on earth?
I don't have any children,
so I had no idea what to even say to her.
Takako was just determined to—
But Takako's gone now.
Are you sure you don't want to talk to her?
About Takako?
She's said that... that her
mother is waiting for her.
We canceled the search.
It was my call.
Sorry for the wait. You can come in.
Hello!
Sorry to impose...
No problem!
K-Kanae?
Pardon us!
Where's Shirase-chan?
She had something else to take care of.
I see...
Okay, camera's rolling.
Wait a minute. What are you going to ask me?
We were hoping to ask some questions
about your personal life!
Your favorite foods, what you do back home...
And... your love life!
What's your "type"?!
I will not answer questions unrelated
to the Antarctic expedition.
Gin-chan, the high school
girls have questions for you.
Please!
Our views have been dropping lately!
We need this!
Her ears are bright red!
They are not!
Captain, did you just get out of the bath?
What's your favorite bath salt?
What's your "type"?!
Maybe we should make the
eyes a little larger...
I think she's fine the way she is...
They're so big!
They did say we were in the Antarctic Circle.
The sun's not gonna go down, is it?
Someone like a cloud?
What does that mean?
Dunno. But that's what she said.
There are lots of kinds of clouds...
Cirrus, stratus, cumulus...
You're so boring.
Why?
I think...
What big clouds!
Yeah...
Clouds are amazing, aren't they?
You can't grasp them, but when you
look up, they're always there.
And... what does that mean?
I don't know.
I think I have an idea, though.
Yeah...
What? What is it?
How did the interview go?
Did Kanae...
No, I asked.
I was just curious to know
if you and Kobuchizawa-san's
daughter were very close.
She didn't show up.
She probably hasn't forgiven me.
That is a problem.
A captain needs to be able to talk
to their members and check in.
From 0800 hours to 1200 hours,
training is permitted on-deck.
Ouch!
That looked like it hurt!
That happens a lot when
you exercise in winter...
Shirase?
Penguins!
You know what it means?
To be "like a cloud"...
I think so.
No way! What does it mean?
Tell me! What does it mean?
Can't put it... into words.
Why?
Why what?
Takako, you're trying to leave me
and her alone together, aren't you?
I sure am!
She needs your spirit, after all.
Hey!
She's your child!
Ow.
You can't do it?
No.
What are you doing?
What do you want?
I wanted to know how you feel... about me.
Do you want me to tell you that I hate you?
I don't hate you.
When my mother decided to
join the civilian expedition,
she told me over and over again...
that an Antarctic expedition
can be dangerous.
But you're still going, right?
Yes.
I was fully aware of the kind
of place Antarctica was.
But I was the team captain.
Did you make a mistake?
Was my mother left in Antarctica
because of poor judgment on your part?
I didn't have any other choice.
Then isn't that enough?
Fine.
Let me just ask one more question.
Is that how you really feel?
You really feel that way?
I don't know.
This is why I didn't want to talk about it!
I have no idea how I feel.
All I know... is that, even though
my mom wasn't coming home,
that day after day, my life
wasn't going to change...
I lived every one of those days
waiting for her to come home,
but nothing changed.
I told myself, day after day after day,
that it was like I was waiting
for her to come home.
If I want to change things,
I just have to go...
to where my mother is,
to the place further than the universe.
What?
All, slow astern.
It finally happened.
What is it?
We hit some fast ice.
We're going to ram through it.
You're right!
We're going to slam down on the ice?
Yes. We'll back up once, and then...
All, stop.
All, slow ahead.
We'll slam the ice...
with all we've got.
We use the weight of the
boat to shatter the ice.
That's why we call it an icebreaker.
What happens if the ice doesn't break?
We'll do it over and over again.
Again and again until it breaks.
Antarctica is tough, huh...
It's said that it's especially
difficult to reach land from here.
Is it?
Then why did we specifically come here?
It's the only place we can go.
Rules about Antarctic
exploration were formalized
after the second World War...
Ah, do you know about that?
Yes.
Japan had lost the war,
so many countries were opposed
to Japan sending expeditions to Antarctica.
Of course, Japan didn't have much
influence over the discussion.
In the end, we were allotted
East Ongul Island,
which was even said to be unreachable.
You mean, they bullied you?
I'm not sure if I'd go that far...
but maybe that is what it amounted to.
An "If you really want to go there,
go ahead and try" kind of thing.
That's very annoying.
But that just fired up everyone even more!
They raised large amounts of
money from all over the country,
and the shipwrights worked as hard as
they could to design and build a ship...
What then?
Time and time again,
they found themselves on the brink of giving
up, but they dug deep and pressed on.
Just like breaking through the ice.
Step by step.
Again and again...
Two-thirds ahead!
Go!
Get 'em!
We did it...
Not yet. There's a long way
to go until we get there.
Year after year. Again and again...
I'm home!
Again and again.
Takako!
Hey!
Kobuchizawa!
It's beautiful...
Takako!
It's so...
very beautiful.
Um...
Just for the record, I was
really, really, really serious!
I wanted to do something for her!
I told you, I get it.
But she didn't even notice me!
An expedition member can't help
their captain. They won't let you.
Why don't you respect that,
and find someone more within your reach?
Yumiko...
Y-Y-Y-You...
No! That's not what I meant!
No!
How did it all fit in there so neatly before?
It's a mystery.
What will you do?
Have you finished cleaning up?
Yes! All finished!
How can you be so comfortable with lying?
Would you like to step outside for a minute?
Can we?
Yuzu! The camera!
Right!
Is this it?
It's just a brief stop.
Stay within five meters.
Okay, let's go!
Is this...
...Antarctica?
What should I do?
Shirase, you go first.
After you.
One, two...
We're here!
We made it!
Goal!
Shirase-chan...
It's nice, huh?
It's where your mother was.
In your face...
In your face, in your face, in your face!
You made fun of me and looked
down your noses, but I believed!
You betrayed me, thinking it was
impossible, but I didn't give up!
And this is how it turns out!
Well? I'm standing in Antarctica!
In your face, in your face, in your face!
In your face!
That's your priority?
She must have been had a
lot of pent-up feelings.
It's okay. That's the Shirase-chan we know.
In your face!
One, two...
One Message
You have a new message from Shiraishi Tamiko-san