She's a pretty...
...big person.
Yup.
Sky Priestess Farine, are you all right?
Yes. No problem at all.
The Sky Priestess
and the Star People
You're from the surface, aren't you?
Welcome.
I'd love to put some
tea on and chat, but...
I'm a little busy now.
I see.
Pega said something might've happened
to you and the Star Whale!
I see.
Priestess, behind you!
Excuse me.
As you can see, the Star Whale is
battling an illness right now.
When it gets sick,
the foul air within it comes together and
appears in this form.
We call them Sickness Demons.
They makes the Star Whale feel unwell.
If the Sickness Demons overflow from
within its body, they may bring disaster to
the Sky Sea Islands
and even the surface.
I see.
So that's what's going on.
What will cure the Star Whale's illness?
The Star Whale loves songs.
The songs of the Star People
increase its self-healing powers
and allow it to maintain its health.
The Star People?
Is there a country of
people living inside the Star Whale, maybe?
Aria, was it?
I think the girl the prince saved
was one of the Star People.
She seemed a little strange
for that, though...
Aria?
You know Aria?
Yeah.
One of our friends found
her when she was lost.
Her legs seemed to be a little funny...
And she didn't remember why she was here.
I see.
Where is she now?
She's with a group that's somewhere else.
They're looking for the Fire
Dragon, since it got lost.
The Fire Dragon...  Them?
They've gotten big enough to fly
while carrying people, huh?
I'll find them and bring them to you.
You guests from the surface,
please go to the Star People.
We'll talk more there.
But...
One of my avatars will guide you.
Nice to meet you.
You go to get Sharl's friends.
You go look for the Fire Dragon.
Roger.
This is Guri.
Be good to him.
Maybe they're friends.
Aria-san, are you okay?
What's wrong?
Are you not feeling well?
I'm fine.
My head just hurts a little.
Everybody! We got a message
from Shinku's group!
We need to gather up because
someone's coming to get us.
Got it!
Let's find a place to rest.
Just hang in there 'til we can regroup.
The priestess
is really big, isn't she?
Yes.
I'm a servant of the surface land gods.
I'm in the same position
as that fox girl there.
I thought so!
A long time ago I decided to
live with the Star Whale,
and took the job of priestess.
Every day is so much fun.
Using the water mirror I can see
all around the Star Whale's body,
and outside, and even the Earth!
I see.
It's just up ahead.
This is the village of the star people,
blessed by the water.
Okay, we're heading down.
Priestess, jumping down from here
will be a little difficult.
Oh.
Don't worry.
We'll carry you down!
That statue!
It's just like the star
people in the fairy tales!
Yes.
This is a statue of the
first ruler of the village.
The star people can
breathe in water and on land,
and swim faster than fish!
Like mermaids on Earth!
I see.
But right now...
What's that?
Huh?
That's the priestess and...
People from the surface?!
And people I've seen before.
Everybody! Priestess Farine is here.
I want to talk with you,
the Dragon Priestess,
and the people from the surface!
A-Are you okay?
You all look sick.
They were hurt by the
sickness demons, as well.
That's right.
When the sickness demons possess
you, this is what happens.
Headaches, fever,
muscle aches, etc.
The pain in your throat is really bad...
A lot of people
can't talk at all.
This is the cause.
We're doing better than most people.
In the water, there are a lot more...
They're all suffering from illness.
Some people can't even get out of bed.
And Aria is missing.
About that...
Hey! Hey!
Everybody!
Here we are!
Nanami! Guys!
What's that boat?
One of my secret items.
Sorry. We've got a sick person here.
Is there any place she can rest.
Y-Yes.
A-Aria?
What happened?
Why is she with these people?
Aria!
What, you know her?
Know her? She lives here!
And she's our songstress!
She's the most important
person in the Star Festival!
She went missing two days ago.
We were worried.
From talking to her,
it seemed like she doesn't remember anything
except her own name and the Sickness Demons.
And more than anything, she can't talk.
I see.
But I'm glad Aria's safe.
I don't know why this happened,
but I'm sure if the sickness
is cured, she'll get better.
The Star Whale swallows many things,
especially poisonous air, air which
contains bad things in it...
The Star Whale swallows it
and purifies it inside its body.
The Star Whale purifies the sky.
I listen to its voice and the star people
sing festival songs and song of healing
to maintain its health
and keep the insides of its body bountiful.
This place is
usually much prettier.
It's not this dark.
There have been Sickness Demons in the past,
but when the people and the Songstress sang,
they got better immediately.
But now
most of the Star People can't sing.
And the songstress lost her voice and memories,
and is like this.
The Star Whale is suffering.
Even I can barely hear its voice.
I want to do something.
Would it help if we got rid
of these Sickness Demons?
The Sickness Demons are born from
within the Star Whale's body.
It would help if we could
reduce their numbers,
but that wouldn't really solve the problem.
Um, can I ask something?
Go ahead.
Does it have to be
someone special who sings that song?
Of course.
Someone with a wonderful,
kind, warm voice...
And they need to be a great singer.
Then um...
I happen to know somebody like that.
That's right.
There are people on the surface
who can sing, aren't there?
There sure are!
And she's a star who's known worldwide.
I just happened to
bring a video playback device!
I wondered why you
had that in your toolbox.
That's our Rico.
The princess's songs are an
important part of Biscotti's culture.
I wanted to introduce everyone
in the Sky Sea to them.
All set!
I know dreams will come true.
Wishes overflow.
Let's grab hold of them now,
inside the light.
What a wonderful voice.
That's a nice song.
Huh?
I feel better!
The fever and tiredness are better!
Wow!
I can speak!
Um... can I let everybody else hear this?
Go for it!
I see.
I'm sure she
could sing the song of the Star Festival.
Okay, Shinku and I will go get the princess.
We'll use the double hero express to
bring her back at the speed of light.
Okay, we're counting on you.
Leave this to us!
Priestess, please show us the way.
Yes.
Okay, we'll be back!
Take care!
Now then, what do we do until then?
This place is safe for now.
Maybe we should cut down on the
number of Sickness Demons.
I think my main body is summoning
the large Sickness Demons
and defeating them, but,
if you can help, that would be great!
Yeah!
Leave it to us!
Rico can be our communications HQ.
Stay with Aria-san.
Roger!
Can Sharl and the vanguard stay here?
If something happens, I'd be worried
if it was just the chief.
Roger.
Got it.
I want to kick the crap out
of a big one with our team.
Yeah.
We can't let things get
hard for the girl team.
Well, I don't think we
need to worry about them.
They know how to work together.
Yeah.
But
I'm worried about Aria...
You know, Gaul-sama
was really concerned about Aria-san.
That's pretty rare.
Part of it may be that she saved him, but...
Maybe it's because Aria-san's pretty.
Yeah.
That may be Gaul-sama's type.
Right?
So maybe Gaul's going to
find love after Leo-sama?
I wonder about Leo-sama.
I think she does like Leaf...
Gaul-sama, too.
We're his childhood friends and bodyguards,
so as for who'll be his wife...
We're very interested.
You don't think it'll be one of you guys?
No way.
I doubt it.
I don't think it's like that.
Even if it's not love or romance...
We're connected by a different bond.
A very strong bond.
You mean as a prince and his bodyguards?
As his childhood friends
who've always been with him.
We're basically siblings now.
To me you all are fun
little brothers and sisters.
I see.
Oh, there you are!
Let's get ready...
...and do this!
Let's do it!
Right here.
Yeah.
The Star Whale is opening
its mouth right now.
That's it!
The outside!
I'll follow you to the surface!
Thanks!
First we need to contact the princess!
And ask Cou-sama for help!
I wonder what happened to Aria-dono.
I don't know, but...
She looks like she's in pain.
I brought medicine, but...
I don't know if it's okay
to use on people here.
Thank you.
Just the thought is enough.
Aria always watched
the people on the surface.
She always watched the surface
people with the water mirror.
War games, did you call them?
The ones that are like festivals.
We do them a lot.
She liked those especially.
She said she wanted to go
to the surface someday.
We laughed and said it
was impossible, though.
It's not impossible.
But it's all land down there,
with not a lot of water, right?
They say that the most common
water is salt water.
That's true, but...
We can't get too far
from pure fresh water.
I'll use surface technology to help!
For example, we could get a big carriage
and use either a box or half-sphere
filled with fresh water...
Like this... like this?
Like this!
You could make these in
a lot of sizes depending on
how many people were coming.
There are technologies we could use to
purify the water and
maintain its temperature.
I see.
The Star People could use
this to visit the surface.
You're right.
It's wonderful.
I'm sure Aria will be so
happy when she hears it.
We should have started talking to the
people on the surface sooner.
The surface people
can't come to the Sky Sea easily.
We were only able to do it
thanks to the Fire Dragon.
The only ones who could get up here easily
are the Heroes of the various
countries or the leaders
who have treasure swords that let you fly.
Come to think of it, the last person
to come here was a Hero, I heard.
Yes, that's right.
The hero Adel and her party.
Her signature's on display
in my great-grandma's house!
Do you know the Hero Adel-sama?
Not only do we know her,
she told us
her story yesterday!
She's still alive! Wow!
She's still young.
And I was
raised by a member of her party.
The sky and the surface really
are connected, aren't they?
That's right!
Who's that?
I don't know,
but I think I've seen
them somewhere before...
Aria...
Something's strange about them...
Everyone, be careful.
Is it one of Aria-dono's acquaintances?
Move.
Farine-dono!
Priestess!
I won't let you!
This is... Sickness Demon poison!
Give back Aria.
Chief! Everyone!
Get the priestess and Aria somewhere safe!
Roger!
Senka Reppuu!
Got you!
Fox girl... priestess...
Seal evil!
Don't get in my way!
Hurry!
Aria...
Our promise...
Are you Verde?
You're in my way.
I heard
a strange sound from the village.
Seriously?
Aria...
Aria. Our promise.
Let me hear your song.
Only me...
Verde.
Aria's songs belong to me.
They belong to me.
Just wait, Aria!
Make sure...
Song of the Stars
...you watch next time.