Work Log
Is that so, Denroku?
Yes.
I see...
Episode 21
Rebirth of "Die"
What?! You're getting married?!
That's right. One can only
become a man through marriage.
But do you have to do it right now?!
Speaking from a financial viewpoint,
it's definitely a bad idea.
However, we have love!
Love saves the world!
We don't need a
wedding ceremony!
We're going to combine our efforts
and help Madam Manager!
Isn't that right, Takako?
Exactly so, Enishing.
"Enishing"?
"Enishing" means anything.
We have no secrets from each other!
We say anything to each other!
But, hey, I'm happy for you.
Congratulations!
And what are we congratulating now?
Madam Manager!
I was planning on telling
you formally, but...
Please, will you acknowledge
our forthcoming marriage?
Do whatever you please.
Please wait!
Takako!
Wait, Mother!
You don't trust me, do you, Mother?
But, mark my words,
I will definitely regain your trust!
I'm prepared to work at
this inn for the rest of my life!
So, please, Mother...
Could you stop calling me that?
Within the grounds of Kissuiso,
I'm to be called "Madam Manager,"
and not Enishi's mother.
However, there is one requirement.
What?
If you're getting married, make
sure you hold a wedding ceremony.
B-But...
Wedding ceremonies aren't
there for self-satisfaction.
You have a reputation to uphold as
the successor of Kissuiso.
If you can't even understand that,
you've got a long way to go
before you can take charge here.
It's leftover fish soup.
Would you care to join us, Miss Takako?
The scent of a reefy coast
stings my troubled heart.
Man... I wasn't expecting her
to be so stubborn about it...
Come on, she's just telling
you to hold a proper ceremony.
That's right! It's not like she's against it.
Holding a wedding reception
at an ordinary hotel would
cost at least 1,600,000 yen.
I-I didn't know it would cost that much to get married.
Why don't you use...
That's it!
Why don't you use Kissuiso for
your grand marriage ceremony?!
What?!
If we help out,
most of the costs would be covered!
That's a wonderful idea!
Takako!
Huh?
We can't do that.
We'd be interfering with
the inn's normal operation.
Like you've never done that before.
Don't let that concern you.
Tohru, you're in charge of
the food for the ceremony.
M-Me?!
That's right...
If I were to take on extra
waitress duties that day...
Ohana and Nako can...
Awesome!
I'm in charge of the food
for the reception?!
Right, Minko,
let's take a look at the market!
Okay!
Wow, it's finally begun!
I love you guys!
The days I just circled are
supposed to be the luckiest.
Wow, there's not even a month left.
Yeah, the Bonbori Festival takes
place in the fall, after all.
As the successor, I can't hold my wedding
when the inn is at its busiest.
Then couldn't you delay
the wedding until after that?
No, I can't do that!
What if Takako changes her mind?!
Enishing, about the cost...
Coming!
Welcome! Have a look!
How about some northern pink
shrimp and righteye flounders?
It's got to be food for a celebration.
I've got to keep the costs down,
but I need to make it
look festive as well as taste good.
It's a wedding,
so no one will blame me
if the food is a little too extravagant.
Oh, the dish I had at the
cultural festival was fun.
That omelet rice with
"LOVE" written on it.
Perhaps I could do something
similar with the carp...
Line them up and write
"LOVE" with miso and vinegar.
I-I don't know about that...
Mr. Nori, can I take a look at that?
Sure!
Getting married is wonderful, isn't it?
I'm at an age where I'm supposed
to start thinking about that kind of stuff.
A-Already?!
Yeah. I like kids.
I'd like at least five or so.
F-Five?!
I prefer families to be noisy.
Something wrong?
N-Nothing.
Want to stop by?
W-Wait, but...
Tohru!
Come on, now!
Take a deep breath!
You'll feel refreshed!
You've been acting a little
odd recently, that's all.
Listen, both Mr. Ren
and I have been in
the same position as
you, a commis-chef.
Huh?
You may come to a standstill
or get irritated
because things don't work out
the way you want them to,
but what you gain from hard
work will never betray you.
Everyone gets in a slump.
That's not what's been bugging me.
But... you're worried about me.
Umm, I...
Well...
I really want to make the young
master's wedding ceremony a success!
I want to work with you
to make it a success,
and after that...
After that...
there's something I want to...
"Make it a success"?
You're talking like Ohana now.
That girl always manages to
get others involved in things.
Before you notice it,
you're a part of it.
The atmosphere at the inn has
changed a lot since she arrived.
Takako used to be just a nuisance.
Yeah, let's make it a success.
Don't copy her too much, though.
We don't need two troublemakers.
What else do we need for a wedding?
There's got to be some form
of entertainment, right?
But we don't have the money...
Money?
That means naught
when up against love.
Money means nothing?
I suggest you make remarks like that
after you've finished paying your rent.
Wait a second!
It was just a line.
I was thinking that we could
perform a skit at the ceremony,
like re-enacting how they fell in love.
That sounds fun!
But can any of us act?
It'll be fine.
I've got the perfect line for you.
I-I'm going to get pregnant!
Sexual harassment?
Oh, they're back!
Welcome back!
Wow, you've bought so much already?!
I thought I'd practice making it first.
All right! Can I taste it?!
Dummy.
Welcome back!
I'll lend you a hand.
I touched something disgusting...
No, no...
Even if we keep the cost
of the dress this low,
we still have the rings
to worry about...
Enishing, I should get going now.
Oh, I'll see you out.
It's fine.
Besides, we can use a rental dress.
The ring can also be cheap-
No, it can't!
At least the ring's got to be nice!
Takako?
It's nothing.
Anyway, I'm off.
Your name's Nako, right?
Y-Yes.
Adieu!
H-Hey...
Did I say something bad again?
Oh, is it because I suggested
we hold the wedding here?
Is it too much effort for you?
But it's a wonderful thing,
and though it may be a lot of work-
What do you mean
by "a lot of work"?
You're the one who
said we should do it.
"Let's have the wedding here."
With your loud, annoying,
and disgusting voice.
Just hold on a sec.
I'm used to "loud" and "annoying,"
but "disgusting"?!
We're the ones who get troubled
by your whimsical actions.
Not just me.
Everyone.
Especially Tohru!
Tohru?
Yeah. You're always relying
on Tohru for everything.
Repay the debt!
What?
Go out with him!
Go out with Tohru!
What?!
Wh-Why Tohru and me-
You're always pretending that you don't know.
You always take the best parts!
Think about Tohru's feelings!
Take responsibility for
changing Kissuiso's atmosphere!
I don't know what
the heck you're-
Shut up!
I'm completely lost here,
but if I were to go out with Tohru,
what about you?!
Don't you like him?!
Why on Earth are you
saying such things?!
Shut up! Die!
Looks like "die" is back in fashion...
Hey! That's charred!
H-Hot!
What are you doing?!
I'm sorry!
Jeez... there goes breakfast.
I'm sorry...
Minko, don't worry about helping
out with the wedding anymore.
I'll do it myself.
What?
How can you expect to be trusted
if you can't even perform your daily tasks?
You'll be in Mr. Ren's way.
You look like you've
got something to say.
I don't think...
I'll ever be able to say it!
Minko...
Minchi!
H-How about we have lunch together?
Let's invite Oshimizu and we
can all have lunch together.
I'll give you some of my fried egg.
Oh, Oshimizu!
What's that?
Curtains.
The teacher said he
was putting up new ones.
But they still look new!
They're changing them to red ones.
According to color therapy, it's
supposed to be better for the students' minds.
A red classroom...
That's kind of erotic.
But it's kind of a
waste, isn't it?
It's not like we can help it.
Let's get this out of the
way and have lunch, okay?
I wonder if we can use this...
What?
Where's Madam Manager and the others?
I hear Madam Manager's at a meeting.
The young master is with Takako,
planning their wedding.
Planning their wedding, eh?
Takako's looking out into the blue.
She doesn't really seem to
be so gung-ho about the idea.
I'm sure she has a lot to worry about.
What was it... marriage browns?
You mean "Bryans."
But you know, we're helping out with their marriage.
Why is the person we're
helping out acting this way?!
Your natto's starting to bubble up.
What?
Natto tastes better if you
stir it until it gets bubbly.
Really?
That's what I'm talking about!
Perhaps I should search somewhere
nearer for someone to marry.
Ah, I went off the line!
We've got a lot of curtains,
so don't worry if you mess up.
Still, making a wedding
dress out of curtains, eh?
That's an incredible idea.
I wanted to be of some
help to Takako's wedding.
I didn't think you'd lend us a hand!
Oh, don't worry about it.
I love events like this.
Isn't Ohana going to use the sewing machine?
She's apparently not
very good with technology.
Oh...
What about cellphones?
I asked Minchi,
but she refused to help.
Tohru likes me?
No, that can't be true.
Well, I'm not exactly good at noticing things...
like that situation with Ko...
No, but Ko is...
No, it's...
W-Wow, she's so fast!
And so accurate!
Can't you make it cheaper?
I was your brother's classmate.
What? You don't remember me?
It's been 15 years,
but I still remember you.
W-Wait, don't hang up!
No, I'm not done yet!
Hello, I'm from Kissuiso.
We bought a large quantity of
futons from your store six years ago.
I'd like to call off the
wedding with Enishi.
I understand why you
won't acknowledge me!
I also understand why you can't
leave us in charge of this inn.
I... wanted to have a relationship
with you where we could
say anything to each other!
But you...
This is something I was
given by my late husband.
He and I worked at the same inn.
He was a chef, and I was a waitress.
Around the same time we
decided to get married,
the owner gave us an offer.
He asked whether we'd like to succeed
an inn that had no successor.
From then on, we worked hard
in order to restore it.
Denroku, who worked at the
previous inn, helped us too.
We had no time or money to
hold a wedding,
but he gave me this.
In hopes of Kissuiso
becoming successful.
"Kissuiso"?
Yeah, that's what our inn will be called.
What?
The kanji in the name means,
"an inn to please you," Sui.
But we should think about
the customers, not me.
We can't please our customers without
pleasing ourselves first.
But...
Besides, it's not just for you.
If you're pleased, so am I.
It's so beautiful...
Yeah.
He was always by my side after that.
He'd always wish for my happiness.
It's still the same even
after he passed away.
"Marriage"
is a promise not to let your
spouse be alone, ever again.
Your spouse...
Yes, even if one of
you passes away first.
So...
Takako, I entrust Enishi's
happiness to you.
I... thought I was always
being opposed by you...
When you told us to have
the marriage ceremony,
I assumed you weren't planning
on letting us succeed the inn.
Yes, that's correct.
I'm not.
What?
Now, for the baiser amor!
Come at me if you can!
I'm so touched!
What?
"Touched"? Oh, please...
Episode 22
A Determined One-Sided Crush
It's not weird.