I'm going to separate Takeo-kun and Yamato-san.
You should tell him how you feel.
Tell him how I feel?
Tell Takeo?
Your head almost exploded, just considering
it. You still have strong feelings for him!
I don't!
I'm over it, okay?
I want you to stop hurting yourself,
She's shaking...
picking Nishino Kana songs
at karaoke and all that!
Th-Th-That's not true...
They're fighting.
Yeah.
I just like her songs!
I do think he's a good guy,
Everyone in the seminar knows.
but I guess not everything works out.
Let's be honest here.
We should get going!
Let's go!
I'm done talking about this!
I won't be alone with Takeo,
understand?
Sorry about that.
Let's go.
Sorry Sorry
How will I ever get a chance,
if you don't settle this?
My Jinx
What a crowd.
I wonder if everyone's going to MM Land.
It's a long weekend, after all.
I hope they won't stop letting people in.
Oh, crap.
I forgot my cell.
It's okay!
I have mine!
I have mine, too.
I'm not sure how that helps.
If you get separated from the
group, just look for Takeo.
Yeah
That works!
You guys don't have to look
for me, even if I get lost.
Hey, Suna!
Don't be a stranger!
Hi, everyone! Welcome to MM Land!
Give me your passports, everyone!
I'll go get us speedpasses.
I'll come, too!
If you have help, it'll be easier.
Huh?
It's fine—
Where should I go?
Oh, he's back
You know, you're a really cool guy,
once I got used to your sheer size.
Yeah?
Wow, that looks super good on you, Takeo-kun!
That looks like
a claw-game claw
on you.
You're super good, too, Yamato.
You aren't going to try one on, Sunakawa-san?
Those aren't for me.
Aw, come on... We're trying to
forget the real world here.
Who said?
I think it'd look good on you, though.
What?
Nothing.
Hey, guys,
let's go on that ride that drops you straight down.
Wow! We're dropping straight down!
Wow! So fast!
This is fun.
I don't remember amusement
parks being this fun.
Takeo-kun, this is so much fun!
I'm laughing so much, my face hurts.
Me, too!
On Alert
Oh, it's MM!
Takeo-kun, let's take a picture together!
Top 3 Jinxes at MM Land
1: Breakup chance 100% if take photo with MM
2: Breakup chance 100% if watch Sparkly Parade together
3: Breakup chance 200% if go on date at MM Land
The top three jinxes at MM Land!
W-Would it be a date if I'm
just hanging out with you?
3: Breakup chance 200% if go on date at MM Land
Then why not go on a ride with me?
Why you?
Yamato-san, come with me!
Boo.
Want to go on a ride?
Sure.
Suna, what's a jinx, anyway?
It's more that it's the reality.
Reality?
Between couples who, after coming here,
stay together and those who'll break up...
Naturally, there'll be more of the latter.
I think it's more common for
relationships to not work out.
Reality, huh?
Yeah, I can see that...
Ever since we started dating,
we've had so much fun.
I've probably just forgotten about
how things usually go in reality.
I heard you a lot back there.
I'm easily spooked by stuff that jumps out at you.
I'm starving...
Takeo-kun, let's go get something to eat.
What? What?
Do you have a problem with it,
if it's just Takeo-kun and me?
Takeo-kun, how did you guys start dating?
Who confessed their feelings first?
I guess Yamato, in a way.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
I'd like to let Sunakawa-san
confess her feelings, too...
I'd like to let the other guy know how
she's been feeling all this time.
Otherwise, how could Sunakawa-san
find closure, right?
I see...
But if she ended up together with the
other guy, what would you do?
You like her, right?
If it works out okay, it'll be for the best.
I'll just cry a little, that's all.
I see...
Aren't those hot?
Don't point!
Whoa!
My hands have thick skin.
Wow!
Hey!
Was it crowded?
Thankfully Takeo-kun was with me
It sure was!
I see.
You'd better not have said anything to Takeo!
I gave up already.
It's gotten to be a huge chore,
so I decided to just have fun spending
time with you, Sunakawa-san.
After making some good memories, I'll go home.
Oda...
Sunakawa-san, you should have fun, too—
I think there's a restroom over there.
I'll go and soak this towel with some water.
Oh, it's fine.
I'll just go myself.
Chance...
Oh, hey!
That looks good.
Oh, popcorn!
Yamato-san, Sunakawa-kun,
come with me to get some.
Takeo-kun, don't move.
You're the landmark.
Right!
Huh?
Where is everyone?
What's with your stance?
They went to buy popcorn with Oda-san.
Huh, popcorn...
The three of us are going to the Märchen Zone,
From: Oda
To: Sunakawa-san
Subject: You're such a nice person
so you should tell him how you feel.
Also, I have Yamato-san's cell,
so don't bother trying to call her.
Sorry, Takeo!
We might have lost Yamato-san...
What?
She's somewhere in the Märchen Zone,
so let's go look for her.
Okay!
That popcorn's in the Future Zone!
This way.
Thank you!
The buildings in this area sure look interesting...
Let's take a look around.
Oh, but we should get back.
Oh, I told them to meet us in
the Future Zone, so it's fine.
They're on their way.
Um, thank you.
Thanks to you,
I was able to come to MM Land with Takeo-kun.
It's been so fun.
Any luck over there?
Nope.
I'm sorry, Takeo.
Huh?
Well, you know, Oda...
You let him stay with you, and he's been a bother.
Oh, that wasn't much.
Oda-san's a nice guy.
Well, he isn't a bad guy...
Maybe we should try to call Yamato.
Huh?
My phone's out of juice.
Huh?!
Oh, and before going to sleep, I pulled
out Takeo-kun's phone charger.
What's wrong?
He's a horrible guy!
I'll never tell Takeo how I feel, even if we're alone!
Let's just all meet up.
Why not?
Takeo-kun's been treating you like a big sister
because he has no idea how you feel.
You don't know how he'll react once he knows.
Don't you want to know?
What's wrong?
Once... he knows...
M Man
M Child
Takeo-kun and Ai-san...
Huh?
Were you able to get in touch with them?
Oh, I think they went to the
Resort Zone by mistake.
Huh?
That's on the other side of the park, right?
Yeah, sorry!
It's all because I said I wanted popcorn.
It's okay!
There's enough time before the Sparkly
Parade for us to get back together.
Resort Zone is that way, right?
I don't see them in the Märchen Zone.
You could tell in that split second?!
We're in the Future Zone now.
Future?!
Don't move!!
C'mon...
Just kidding...
We just went to the Resort Zone, actually.
What a crowd...
Takeo!
Hang on a second!
Oh, right.
She must be tired from trying
to match my stride.
Okay, I'm good.
Let's go.
Hey...
Let's go after we take a relaxing ride.
Huh?
Oh, but we should find Yamato-san quickly!
It'll be fine.
H-Hey...
What?
What's wrong?
Nothing's wrong...
I see.
It must be cramped because I'm so big.
But I can't make myself any smaller.
Sorry.
Centrifugal force!
She'll get crushed.
That was less relaxing than I anticipated.
Uh, yeah...
Are you okay?
You're too close!
Oh, sorry.
Hey, how about that one next?
Huh?
Oh, the 3D Dome?
It looks relaxing.
But...
But what about Yamato-san?
It's fine.
It's been fun.
I just have to find her again
before the Sparkly Parade.
Huh?
Really?
I really wanted to go on this!
Oh!
This is so fun!
Sorry.
It'll run into me!
It's gonna hit her!
Um, Takeo...
This is just 3D.
Right!
I might have embarrassed her.
I've always been like this.
Oops...
Mommy!
Where are you, Mommy?
Tarou!
Thank god...
You used to be the one getting lost all the time,
and now you're the one saving them.
You've grown, Takeo.
Do you remember how...
When you were in elementary school,
you said I look like a flower from a flower shop?
Flower?
I said something like that?
Yeah... Right, you don't remember!
Okay, let's go look for Yamato-san!
I'm all rested up now.
Okay, tell me if you get tired.
Unless you tell me, I won't get it.
I know.
A flower, huh?
I don't remember what I said
back when I was a kid,
but I think you look like that flower,
the white one in the middle.
That's the one!
You haven't changed, Takeo...
Takeo-kun's been treating you like a big sister
because he has no idea how you feel.
You don't know how he'll react once he knows.
Don't you want to know?
Takeo...
No New Messages
There's no response from Sunakawa-san...
Eh?
Did she really tell him?
Let's split up and look for them!
Yamato-san and Sunakawa-kun,
can you go look in the Märchen Zone?
Oh, sure.
This is crap.
Like hell anyone would be hypnotized.
space cadet
Wait, Ai-chan, are you under?
No way!
Do you see the person you have feelings for?
Yes.
Say the person's name!
Takeo.
Takeo?
Takeo-kun?
Gouda Takeo.
Is he your boyfriend?!
Not a boyfriend.
He has a girlfriend called Yamato-san now—
Okay, that's enough!
You guys are going too far.
Huh?
But we're just getting to the good part.
Hey! Sunakawa-san!
Takeo...
What?
I?
Huh?
What the...
Takeo, I... I—
The Sparkly Parade will start in thirty minutes.
Please follow park attendants' instructions regarding
parade route and observation spots.
Takeo! The Parade!
You have to watch it with Yamato-san!
Right!
Oh, but my cell...
You have to go look for her yourself!
Right.
Thanks!
I'll go look for her!
Takeo...
Don't cheat on her!
Yeah!
I found them.
They're right in front of White Castle.
Yep, I'll be here.
See you soon.
"Don't cheat on her"?
What's with that?
He totally sprinted off, too.
Oda,
I'll never tell Takeo, not for the rest of my life.
I like how he laughs like an idiot,
and thinks of me as his sister.
Ai-san! Oda-san!
Where's Takeo-kun?
Huh?
He went to look for you.
He ran off that way.
Go after him!
Oh, okay.
Oh, but if I see the parade with just him,
there's that jinx...
Forget about the jinx!
Have faith in Takeo!
It'll be fine!
You're right... Yeah.
I should just trust Takeo-kun.
I think you told me something similar
before to cheer me up, too.
Ugh, I'm so bad!
It's fine, just go!
Oh!
What?
What's wrong?
I wanted to give you this.
You helped me out a lot, so here's
a coffee chiffon cake.
I'll go find Takeo-kun, then!
Wow, she's amazing.
She bakes cakes, too.
She does...
Let's eat!
Oh, I understand.
It's made with you in mind.
It's coffee flavored, so it's slightly bitter,
but its sweetness gives it a gentle taste.
This cake...
Being told I look like a beautiful flower twice.
I think that's all I need.
I wonder if they'll find each other...
I'm missing my hat!!
You're already wearing it!
I'm missing a sock!!
You have both on the same foot!
Takeo's always sucked at finding things.
I'm sure it'll work out.
The really important things
will be found over and over again, for some reason.
Takeo-kun's not the only one searching.
People...
Yamato!
Yamato...
I found you because you're so huge.
I see. Then I'm glad I'm huge.
But I knew I'd see you, anyway.
We can, as long as we think we can!
Yeah!
I wanted to find you,
because I wanted to watch the parade together.
Right.
It's okay for us to watch it together,
just the two of us?
Yeah, I'm not going to worry about it anymore.
I see.
So pretty...
I guess being able to date you,
with all these people around us,
is kind of like a miracle...
I think I'll hold on to this feeling
and try not to forget it.
Yeah.
You're right.
Daddy, I can't see the sparkles!
All right!
I'll put you on my shoulders!
Oops, I should hunch down.
I'm tall.
Sorry I keep ruining the moment.
I'll be watching the parade, so don't mind me.
Carry on.
Crap!
The redeye bus is all sold out!
Not again                                                                Is it okay?
I decided I won't wait anymore.
I'll get the girl!
Good luck—
Aw, let's stay up and talk.
Tell me more about Sunakawa-san
when she was younger.
When she was in middle school...
When I went to Suna's place to play...
"I went to play,
and she came out in her jammies.
She didn't seem to mind at all,
but I got a bit nervous."
That's what Takeo-kun said.
Huh? Takeo? Because of me?
Yeah.
Nervous?
Crap!
Damn that Gouda Takeo...
Making Sunakawa-san look so cute!
My Girlfriend
Next time: My Girlfriend.