When we were kids, there was a
time that Manaka and I got lost.
We had gone to the
outskirts of the village,
into the outer sea to look for coral,
and gotten so wrapped up that we
couldn't find the way home.
Just as we got hungry, tired of walking,
and on the verge of tears...
The one who appeared in front of us
was Hikari.
Without saying a word,
Hikari just kept pulling on our hands.
Even now, I clearly remember
his eyes focused straight
in front of him and the feeling
of him holding my hand.
So...
I don't think I was too
surprised when I heard
that Hikari had found Manaka.
I think I knew somewhere in my
heart that it would happen.
Because I thought somewhere in my heart
that if someone were able to
do that, it'd only be Hikari.
Episode Nineteen:
The Lost, Lost Little...
Right...
At this rate, taking care
of her here should be fine.
Really?!
Hikari!
Well, we've been examining
her since yesterday,
and I'd have to say that she's pretty healthy.
There's nothing wrong with
her brain waves, either,
and judging from you two
who have already woken up,
she should wake up soon.
All right!
I told you, Akari!
There's nothing to worry about.
And her Ena may grow back.
Anyway, I'm just glad
that Manaka's okay.
You think that, too, right?
Ow!
Akira!
Y-You little... Oh.
Doctor, Chisaki, thanks.
Hold it!
So lively... how nice.
Kancho!
You fool! Like I'd keep
falling for the same attack!
At this rate, she won't be
able to stay asleep either.
Special move: kancho reversal!
This is so embarrassing...
Th-This is...
Seriously...
Kancho reversal reversal!
Hikari... Must be really
happy that he found Manaka.
Thank you very much.
Hiradaira-kun,
you can just have your self-study log in
to me by tomorrow morning.
Yes, sir.
This is the first time I've
seen you in your nurse outfit.
It looks good on you.
I almost didn't recognize you.
I still haven't gotten used to it.
Right now, it just feels like
I'm just wearing the outfit.
Since you're here,
want to have some tea?
I will, thank you.
Hey...
Manaka,
hurry and wake up.
The Ofunehiki...
Both Dad and Uroko-sama
said it'd be useless...
But I was hoping for
something the whole time.
Hoping that something would happen,
wanting something to happen.
And then something like
that ended up happening...
Did you save Akari back there?
What happened back then?
You said that you had something
to tell me after the Ofunehiki
was over, didn't you?
At the time, no matter how
far I reached for you,
I couldn't reach you at all.
But now even if you want me to,
I'll never let go.
I see...
Miuna-chan also likes Hikari.
How cute...
Putting her all into caring for him,
but not being able to
take the next step...
I always just thought of her as a child,
but that's right...
She's now the same age
as we were back then.
I see...
I'm almost the same age as
Akari-san was back then...
You still worried about the
girlie from the sea village?
Yes...
I believe she'll wake up soon, but...
She lost some of her Ena, so...
Her Ena?
You said she was found sleeping at a
graveyard of Ojoshi-samas, right?
Do you happen to know something?
There's a continuation to the story
about the Sea God and Ojoshi-sama.
Continuation?
There aren't many who'll talk about it,
because it's a story with a sad ending.
Huh?
You haven't talked since
you got back, have you?
Is something wrong?
Not really.
More importantly, Chisaki,
how's Manaka doing?
I still haven't had a
chance to go see her.
Right...
The doctor said that there's
nothing to worry about.
Thank goodness...
Now you guys will have
more data to conceal.
"Conceal"...
Apparently both Mihashi-sensei
and Tsumugu aren't going to
officially present the
details about the fact
that we were able to get into Shioshishio
or about Miuna-chan for a while.
Really?
Yeah.
Mihashi-sensei will put
it all in a thesis.
Then he'll send it to
an academic journal,
and the official presentation
comes after that.
I can't say that I agree to that.
Hikari, I, and Miuna-chan didn't dive
to Shioshishio and put our lives in
danger for the sake of your reputation.
Hey, Tsumugu.
There is a reason for that, right?
If the thesis isn't acknowledged,
we won't receive funding anymore.
All his research to avert disaster
from occurring on the surface
by establishing the link
between the abnormal weather
and the sea village will cease.
And then the media will
also get involved and
Miuna will go through a lot of trouble.
Jeez...
Tsumugu, you never explain enough.
Hey, Kaname.
Will you give him a chance?
There is a lot going on...
You're such an adult, Chisaki.
Thanks for the food.
Kaname, wai—
Damn it.
"An adult," huh...
Wow!
How nostalgic!
Huh?
Huh? You're kidding...
Take that!
Oh, no... It's...
Chisaki, the bath is getting cold.
R-Right. I'll be right there!
Whoa!
What's wrong?
Chisaki, I'm opening the door!
H-Hey, wait!
H-How long are you going
to stare, you idiots!
S-Sorry!
Sorry.
Jeez...
Are you hungry?
Oh, it's just you, Tsumugu.
Jeez, don't scare me like that.
Pickled Shallots
Chile Oil
Marinated in Soy
Oh...
Um, I was just looking
for Grandpa's plum wine.
You're still a minor.
It's fine!
I'm in the mood to drink some.
Since I'm an adult and
some lonely housewife!
Just wait a sec.
I'll prepare it for you.
Plum Wine
That's not how you're
supposed to drink it.
Hmph!
I was told that alcohol tastes
better when you're an adult,
Plum Juice Without Shochu
but apparently that's true.
You're saying that after
just drinking this...
Even if it's just plum
wine, alcohol is alcohol!
Yeah... plum wine is.
Quit trying to act like an adult.
Give me more!
I feel great.
I want to see what
Shioshishio looks like now.
Maybe I'll go.
Today,
Hikari was talking to
Manaka while she slept.
That wasn't much of a shock, but...
I don't think I'll be able to
have eyes like that ever again.
My body got all big on its own...
and yet things are spilling out.
Does becoming an adult mean
you lose a lot of things?
You probably do lose a lot.
But that just means you need fulfill
what you lost with new things.
Our time together these five
years has been like that for me...
You don't plan on doing anything
more than that, do you?
Yeah.
But we need to get her to bed.
Give me a hand.
R-Right.
I never did tell you, did I?
Tell me what?
My gratitude for saving
me at the Ofunehiki.
Thank you.
It's not something to thank me for.
Just so you know, I'm not being modest.
At the time, it really
crossed my mind...
"If I just overlook it, you'll disappear."
"And then I'll be able
to be with Chisaki."
"Don't save him."
"Just abandon him."
But you dove in.
Also,
if you were able to just
overlook something like that,
I'd never let you have Chisaki.
So the truth comes out.
Yeah.
But...
I really am grateful that
you guys came back.
Things were suspended this whole time.
Now both Chisaki and I
can move forward.
I drank quite a bit, but I
didn't get a hangover at all.
Maybe I'm pretty strong.
From this point, I dive
down seven meters...
How to get to Shioshishio
I have to face it one day...
Then...
I'm being swept away a little...
Um...
Huh? You're kidding...
Chisaki!
Hikari?!
Are you okay?
Yeah, thanks.
You're always so careful,
but at times, you end up
being really reckless.
Eh? You think so?
Anyway, what are you doing here?
What do you mean?
If we're able to get in now,
of course I'd come to see...
Well, I guess you have a point.
When he held me back
there, it surprised me.
He didn't feel rugged at all,
unlike the men I have to
touch during self-study...
Of course...
Because his smile, his body,
and his heart are...
Exactly the same as you
were five years ago... aren't you?
Huh?
Of course you are.
For you, the Ofunehiki
was really recent.
Well, yeah...
But you haven't changed either.
You're just the normal Chisaki.
You think so?
I thought I had changed quite a bit...
Nah, not at all.
You still look like you're listening
and yet not listening at all.
That's not true!
Also, the fact that you get pissed
off when I tease you a little.
What about you, Hikari?
What are you doing here
so early in the morning?
Yeah...
I just couldn't stay put.
I keep wondering why
Manaka's Ena's disappearing.
I thought I might figure something out
if I went back to where we found her.
I see...
I don't know if this will help or not,
but Tsumugu's grandfather
told me a story.
The continuation of the story
about the Sea God and Ojoshi-sama.
Continuation?
The girl that married the Sea
God eventually had children,
and their descendants flourished.
However, as more time passed,
it's said that the girl became
more and more depressed.
Because the girl had left behind
someone she loved on the surface.
Because of the man she loved,
she was never able to
forget about the surface.
After finding that out, the Sea God
did everything he could
to make her happy.
But in the end, she wasn't able
to forget about the surface,
so the Sea God had no choice
but to let her go
back to the surface...
Taking something in return.
"Something"?
I've been thinking about it...
but that might be Ena.
Hikari?
Ojoshi-sama...
in return for going to the surface...
Oh, sorry...
It was just a thought.
Grandpa also said that
this was just oral lore,
so he's not sure if it's true or not.
All right!
Huh?
It's decided!
Uroko-sama!
I'm going to find him and catch him.
"Catch him"?
I'm sure he knows whether
this story is true or not.
And if it's true, he may
know what needs to be done!
To tell you the truth,
I was at a loss,
but now I know what I need to do.
Thanks, Chisaki!
But man, the Sea God
is such a selfish jerk.
Taking people's Ena because
they don't obey him
and randomly giving people Ena...
What is he, a kid?
That might be...
Even after living hundreds
and thousands of years,
he might not have changed at all...
Well, that probably has
nothing to do with it.
It's not about position
or age, but how you feel.
"Feel"...
I'm excited for Manaka to wake up.
I'll do something about
her Ena no matter what,
and then help Tsumugu with the surface...
I'm not going to give up!
Oh... that's right.
I still do like Hikari after all.
And so, now that Manaka has returned,
our time that was frozen for the last
five years finally started moving...
That's what I thought at the time...
But...
Even after a week had passed,
there were no signs that
Manaka would awaken at all.
Manaka!
Don't princes do that often?
Kiss the sleeping princess?
How dull...
What do you mean by that?
Maybe they don't want her to wake up?
Episode Twenty:
The Sleeping Princess