Tsuritama Episode 4
Since Grandma went to the hospital,
our mornings have gotten busier.
Haru, don't forget the
flowers in the yard.
Okay.
There's a reason we're so busy.
Morning fishing.
Because of it, I don't have
trouble getting up in
the morning any more.
Feels good.
One more time.
What are you doing?
The bigger problem is...
Sorry, sorry.
Sheesh.
Yuki, look.
I told you not to put in too much soap!
I know he doesn't mean any harm.
He's an alien, but...
Listen Haru, don't do anything
else I don't tell you to do.
Okay.
Angry Landing
Enoshima...
Bowl!
Tamocchan!
Tamocchan?
Haru!
When did they become friends?
Tamocchan, how do you
know Enoshima bowl?
How? I came up with it.
What?
Here are your whitebait bowls.
Thank you, Mari-chan.
You're welcome.
Thanks for the food.
I see.
The friends Natsuki's been
teaching to fish are Haru and...
Yuki.
Yuki-kun, is it?
Be nice to Natsuki for me.
He's real grouchy,
but he's not a bad guy.
Hey, Natsuki. Your friends are here.
He must still be sleeping.
Natsuki, you shouldn't sleep in.
Haru-chan!
Sakura!
Sakura, you're friends with him, too?
Yeah. Haru-chan's so funny.
Yuki, Natsuki's family gets along great.
Tamocchan and Mari-chan
are best friends.
See, Mari-chan?
Huh?
I guess.
Is that their relationship?
I'll do the dishes!
You shouldn't have said that.
What do you mean?
Oh, right. What are you
guys trying to catch?
Something amazing.
Amazing?
Something huge living in Enoshima.
A huge fish?
Are you going to leave
once you catch it, alien?
I see. I hope you catch it.
Tamocchan, do you want to fish with us?
Huh?
Do you want to fish with
me and Yuki and Natsuki?
There he goes again.
Sure, but only if Natsuki
says it's okay.
Why?
We haven't been getting along lately.
Haru's so silly.
It's nothing to laugh about.
It's hard work.
We're busy at the crack of dawn.
And he's always saying things
he shouldn't to everybody.
But that's what's good about Haru.
What?
Haru has a strange power.
The power to melt everyone's hearts.
But it's not that great
for the people with him.
What would you do if Haru disappeared?
Would you still have fun every day?
Enoshima bowl!
I finally got it in.
Did you see that, Yuki?
You got lucky.
It wasn't luck. I did it, I did it.
Fine, okay.
Okay. It's time for the real thing.
The real thing?
You're going to cast into the ocean.
Are you sure?
Yeah. I promised.
All right! I finally get
to cast into the ocean.
Yuki, you look happy.
Shut up.
I'm happy if you're happy.
You still don't understand
the appeal of fishing.
What appeal?
The true joy of fishing.
You can't just fish.
You have to think for yourself and
catch something with your own hands.
My own hands.
Listen up, because I'll
only say it once.
First, establish your target.
Where are the sea bass?
Where? The ocean's huge.
Over there!
Those shadows.
Why?
Because the sun's hot.
Is he serious?
Close.
What?
Sea bass gather near rocks
and other obstacles.
They protect them from predators
and make it easier to feed.
I see.
What are you going to throw over there?
Food.
That's right.
Lures.
This little fish with a lip is a minnow.
We'll start with these.
You're going to make it act.
Act?
Bait the fish by moving the lure.
It's called a retrieve.
Retrieve?
IT Terminology
Retrieve: The act of getting information.
An IT term?
Basically, you pull in the line.
You should've said that first.
When you start, use a simple retrieve.
Simple retrieve?
Just reel the line in.
If your aim is right,
the fish should bite.
It's wiggling!
Try it.
Enoshima bowl!
Good.
Simple retrieve.
Yuki, you're retrieving too fast.
Don't rush.
Yuki, don't rush.
Shut up.
Next, use your imagination.
My imagination?
Think about how your lure
is moving in the water.
How the fish must feel seeing it.
What if the sea bass eat it?
If they take, make sure you hook it.
In other words, if you feel a
pull, lift the tip of your rod
so the hook is secure.
Ouch.
Until then, focus.
Focus.
You don't know when it'll happen.
Focus and make sure you don't miss it.
I'm nervous.
Shut up and fish.
Enoshima bowl!
I feel something.
Hook him!
Seriously?
Yuki, you got a bite!
Yuki, hold on.
I know.
Don't overdo it!
If he pulls, don't reel in the line!
Don't reel in the line?
The harder you try,
the more likely it is to escape.
I see.
It's a game. For now, be patient.
Patience.
He won't get what he
wants. Watch closely.
What?
What's wrong?
I feel some slack.
Reel him in!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Don't panic. He'll leap.
Right. They struggle like crazy.
There it is again!
No, don't reel it in!
Don't reel it in, Yuki!
Too bad.
You panicked at the end.
Yuki, don't worry about it.
It's because you wouldn't shut up.
Sorry, sorry.
Amazing.
The Stella SW is out.
Look at this quiet strength.
I just might fall in love
with this sexy thing.
What is the big fish around here?
Hold on.
What'd you just say?
Pardon?
He's a fishing boat captain
around here. Ayumi-chan.
I see.
Did you say you're looking for big fish?
I did.
Ayumi-chan's great at catching big ones.
As far as I'm concerned,
anything less than 60
centimeters isn't a fish.
I see.
I'll let you fish for
anything on my boat.
Mahi-mahi, skipjack, tuna, even marlin.
I hope you will take
me fishing some time.
No problem. Just let
me tell you one thing.
What is that?
Fishing's not about gear.
It's about skill.
Ayumi-chan, you're so cool.
Excuse me.
All right!
She said it!
Is he always like that?
She called me cool!
Yup. Isn't he cute?
Yes!
See you tomorrow morning.
Yeah.
We'll catch them tomorrow.
Natsuki, bring Tamocchan tomorrow.
Sorry, I can't. Later.
Why not?
Haru-chan's so funny.
I became friends with him in no time.
He is a little strange.
Welcome home.
Hey, Natsuki.
Put these in the fridge.
It's three whitebait bowls.
You're going fishing with your
friends tomorrow, aren't you?
I don't want those.
Don't be like that.
We got a weird call this morning.
Are you going to do
something to this store?
Who cares if you don't like whitebait?
Hey!
Haru, don't go ahead without telling me.
Yuki, look.
You're kidding. Why?
Natsuki and Tamocchan are friends.
Natsuki?
Oh, Yuki. Huh?
Sorry I bothered you.
What are you doing here?
What am I... Huh?
What's going on?
Natsuki, as long as we're
here, why don't we fish?
Natsuki, no.
Haru.
Natsuki, why?
Don't.
It's fine. Thanks, Haru.
Haru, don't tell me you...
I thought it would work.
I told you not to use that any more.
But I didn't use it on you.
That's not the issue.
But Tamocchan was happy.
You said it would be better
if everyone got along.
Yuki, are you mad?
I'm sorry. Sorry, sorry.
Enough already!
Why do you always have to
do things you shouldn't do?
But it's better if everyone...
It's not that simple!
You can't understand how humans feel
because you're an alien.
I don't understand, but I want to.
It's impossible. You even
broke your promise.
You're the worst.
I don't care what you do any more.
Yuki.
Don't follow me!
Go home already.
Go back to space, or wherever.
Yuki.
In other words, this bridge between
the island and the mainland
is the connection...
Keito, what should I do?
Well, it is your fault
you broke your promise.
Yes, it was bad. Yuki got really mad.
But I'm sure he's worried about you now.
Worried?
He's thinking about you.
He wants to see and talk with you.
But Yuki told me not to follow him.
He got mad when I said "sorry."
"Sorry" isn't just a word, Haru.
Huh? But "sorry" is a word.
Sometimes, it's not enough.
I don't understand. I'm an alien.
What would you do if Haru disappeared?
I'm fine without him.
Don't you want to go fishing?
It sure is quiet without him.
It's easier without that selfish guy.
You've started saying
those kinds of things.
When I met you,
I could never tell what
you were thinking.
You've changed.
Maybe.
It could be thanks to Haru.
Why do you say that?
He can be real intrusive, but you
can't help but laugh, you know?
I don't care. I just want
to catch something.
Do you remember what I taught you?
Imagination.
Feel it.
Focus.
I got one.
I told you not to panic! Lift your rod!
It's huge!
Wait for him to stop.
Imagination, focus,
patience.
Don't rush. Hold the line.
People and fish have the
same determined attitude.
Now!
Good. Reel him in.
That's your fish.
It's okay.
I won't let him go.
I won't let him go this time.
All right!
I caught one.
Good, good.
Look, he's pretty big.
A picture.
Huh?
Natsuki, take one. I need to show Haru.
Haru!
I did it! I caught a sea bass!
Haru?
Why isn't he here for this?
Do whatever you want, then.
Haru!
Haru, did you really go back into space?
I give up.
Haru?
Haru...
Haru!
Huh? Yuki?
What are you doing?
I got a little dry.
A little? What are you thinking?
Yuki, did you come because
you were worried about me?
Of course I did!
I can't swim!
Were you thinking about me?
Did you want to talk to me?
You idiot, this isn't the time for that!
I'm going to drown! Help me!
Yuki, are you still mad?
Of course I am.
You always do whatever you want.
But I won't say "I'm sorry" any more.
What? You're not sorry?
No, that's not it.
What are you doing?
If I get rid of this,
you won't get mad any more.
It's fine. I get it.
You really are hopeless.
There.
I'm sorry, too.
Why are you apologizing?
Because I'm always getting mad at you.
You're an alien.
It's not your fault you don't understand.
But I want to understand.
If I did, we wouldn't fight any more.
You're right.
Oh, right! I caught one!
A huge sea bass!
Crap.
Look.
Yuki, you shouldn't lie.
I'm not lying! I really did catch one!
Yuki, you're lying.
I'm not lying!
Tapioca, you don't think
he came to make friends, do you?
Don't get ahead of yourself, alien.
I caught a cold that day.
Haru stayed by my side the whole time...
His presence should've bothered me
more than anyone else's.
Continued in #5