Your Holiness!
I-I can't believe it...
The Pope...
His Holiness...
W-Was eaten?!
R-Retreat!
All men retreat!
Saito? Saito!
No, you've got to hold on!
Saito!
Louise's Choice
So long, pal.
Derf...
Derf!
Saito!
-Saito!
Where am I?
We're in the Versailles Palace in Lutèce.
We came back.
In Lutèce?
Wait, what about the Ancient Dragon?
What happened to the dragon?
Don't worry.
For now...
It stopped?
Yes, it suddenly stopped after passing
through the valley of Oltia.
I saw it, too!
That huge thing curled up
and solidified like a rock!
Could it be that the power
of His Holiness defeated the dragon?
I'm afraid not.
Its heart continues to beat.
I do not believe it is dead.
Which means it will soon rise again.
Indeed.
But that's not all.
You answered my call, Old Osmond.
Yes. I'm sorry to have kept you waiting.
What happened to His
Holiness is a tragedy.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Right now though, I'm focused
on the Ancient Dragon.
I believe that's what His Holiness
would wish for as well.
I'm sure you're right.
I suppose you summoned me because
of this Ancient Dragon.
That's right, Old Osmond.
Will you tell us about the research
you did along with your work at
the Academy of Magic?
I see.
It's still alive...
Then I guess we'll just have
to get him good next time!
We've got to avenge the Pope!
Right? Louise? Tiffa?
Y-Yes.
I'm really hungry!
Siesta, do we have anything to eat?
Yes! I'll go heat up
some soup right now.
Where are all the people
from the academy?
I heard they went back to Tristain.
Lukshana and her friend said
that they're returning to your mansion,
so they're still here.
I see.
It will be a while before
we can go back there, though.
Right, Louise?
I-I'm going to go help Siesta.
O-Okay...
Louise?
I couldn't watch anymore.
Saito didn't say a single
thing about Derf.
But I know he's really sad.
That's probably because
Saito's so strong
and trying his best to—
He doesn't have to be strong!
To be honest,
I wanted him to say that he could
no longer fight without Derf.
I wanted him to say he wouldn't use
the power of Lífþrasir anymore.
I'm not blaming you, Tiffa!
But I don't want to watch Saito
whittle away his life any further...
I don't want to lose him.
And that is all I have learned
about the Ancient Dragon
through my studies.
Which means Louise and Tiffania
have even harder trials to get through.
I will speak more to
those two about that later.
Maybe the mistake was to face
the dragon without the Four
and Four being reunited.
It is true that in the legend,
the dragon in the past was defeated by
the Four and Four.
However, it does not say that
nobody else can do anything.
Our culture has advanced much
in the last 6,000 years.
Today, there are bonds in Halkeginia
that transcend borders.
It is perhaps possible that
that's enough to cover
for the incomplete Four and Four.
Queen Charlotte, Tristain will raise
all of her military resources
to beat back this crisis.
Will Gallia join us in this fight?
Of course.
Let us ask for the
cooperation of Romalia
and the other countries as well.
We will protect the future of Halkeginia
with our own hands!
All the countries of
Halkeginia have formed
an alliance to fight the Dragon?
Yes. I was chosen to lead the alliance.
But in order to fight
the Ancient Dragon,
the Void Mages are needed...
Louise, we were all born in Halkeginia.
We were all nurtured by her.
We can't just stand by
and do nothing when our
world is in danger.
If it raises the chances of defeating
the dragon even a tiny bit,
we will join the fight!
Your Majesty...
I will also fight with my life.
As someone who was born in Halkeginia,
I will offer myself completely to her.
Thank you, Louise.
Let's overcome this crisis.
Come what may!
Yes!
As someone who was born in Halkeginia,
I will offer myself completely to her.
I was born here, so that makes sense.
But Saito...
Saito wasn't born in this world.
Can we actually involve him?
Get ready to sortie!
We'll defeat the dragon!
Have no fear!
I've got to do it.
This isn't the time to be sad.
Right, Derf?
Huh? The machine sunk in the oasis...
You mean that iron cylinder?
You're going to use that?
No, that one was broken.
But I was wondering if there
weren't more like it in the elven lands.
Locked away somewhere and kept safe.
Do you know anything?
Hmm... I haven't heard
of anything like that.
There goes that.
It was worth a shot...
If we had a fighter plane,
we could take that Ancient
Dragon down in one shot.
Saito...
So they're called "fighter planes"?
Yeah.
It's a weapon from my world that can
fly through the sky really fast.
And its missiles can
even sink a battleship.
Missiles?
If that's such a great weapon,
then why don't you go back to your world
and bring one back here?
That's a little...
Is it too far?
Then why not use Louise's magic?
You mean the World Door?
Would that work?
Is there a reason why
that wouldn't work?
But my world is...
I'll do it.
You mean you'll...
I'll try to connect the World
Door to Saito's world.
If it works, let's go get that fighter.
Together.
Louise...
Okay, let's do it!
All right, let's verify the procedure.
First, Louise will open a
window to Saito's world.
Using Saito's powers, she'll enlarge
it so they can pass through it...
Why is he telling them what to do?
He likes it.
Just let it slide.
Once you've got the fighter,
you'll use Louise's power
again to come back.
That's it.
Do you really think we can
get back to my world?
I'm sure we can.
Good luck, Saito!
We should get started.
Saito, give me your hand.
I'm going to use a little of your power.
Sure.
Send me an image of your world.
Ken Gyof Hagaras Soir Beok Daeg...
Please, door to Saito's
world, please open.
That's Japan!
Those buildings look so weird!
This is your world?
Louise, it's my world!
Let's go!
Louise, come on!
Hey, Saito.
You know, I really loved you.
Meeting you made me so happy.
So please remember
that the last thing you saw me do
was smile at you!
Louise!
Goodbye!
Louise, what are you—
Louise!
L-Louise?
Miss Vallière?
What the hell are you doing?
We need him to defeat the Dragon!
Saito came from another world.
There's no need to get him tangled
up in the fate of our world.
Even if he is a Void Mage's familiar.
Yeah, but...
Ari...
Miss Vallière...
Saito!
Louise truly loved him.
If she didn't, she could have
never made this decision.
What... What is this?
Louise...
Louise!
Saito is...
Yes.
I returned him to the
world where he belongs.
I apologize, but I... I...
I'm sure I would have
done the same thing.
Tabitha...
She's right.
I'm sure this is for the best.
Your Majesty.
I swear to you that I will defeat
the dragon with my own power,
without the need to borrow
the power of Lífþrasir.
I'll also bet everything
I have on this fight!
Well said.
Now let's go.
To the Academy of Magic.
I guess I imagined it.
It is true that once upon a time,
the Ancient Dragon was
sealed away by the Void Mages.
However, according to the texts,
Void Mages also enhance the
Ancient Dragon's powers
if they are eaten.
The dragon gets stronger
by consuming the Void.
Which is why he instinctively
seeks out places with Void Mages.
So the reason the dragon first
turned towards Romalia was...
He sensed the presence
of a Void Mage, the Pope, there.
And once he wakes again,
he will target...
Me, or Tiffa.
Which is why we're taking you
to the Academy of Magic.
There are no settlements around there,
so there's no worry of collateral damage.
Additionally, the military is set
up along the estimated route
of the dragon and will attack
him with all their might.
We don't know if it will have any effect,
but it'll buy some time.
But if we fight at the Academy,
the students will all...
Don't worry about it.
Mr. Colbert is evacuating everyone.
Siesta! I told you to return to the mansion
with Lukshana and the others!
But we're already here.
I asked her to bring us here.
I've always wanted to see
the Academy of Magic.
But it's not safe here!
Everyone's already been evacuated, and...
Oh, Louise, Tiffania!
You're later than I expected.
I was just telling everybody
about the formation
I came up with for defeating the dragon.
Come here, you two.
Yes...
Tabitha, weren't you just at the palace?
I flew at max speed and overtook you.
I am sorry, Old Osmond.
Everybody insisted on staying.
I thought this would happen.
But why are you doing this?
If you stay here, you might die!
Did you think we could just ignore this?
We also want to protect the
world that we live in.
It is our duty as the Undine Order
to protect you in Saito's place.
Yeah!
Besides, doesn't this kind of
thing make your heart race?
Jeanette! What are you doing here?
I hired them.
They're mercenaries.
They'll fight for anyone.
Yup.
Not bad to have us as allies, huh?
It's not like we want this
world to get destroyed.
You guys...
Will you two lend a hand, too?
Having another user of indigenous magic
would really make things easier.
Yeah, sure.
Thanks. That's really helpful.
Hey, Lukshana!
I guess it would benefit Nephthys
to get rid of the dragon.
How about a late night snack?
You guys...
It's my fault.
It has to be my fault.
It's because I made
such a pathetic face.
That's why Louise did
this to prevent me from
using the power of Lífþrasir again.
But without this power,
the Ancient Dragon can't be defeated!
Everyone will...
Louise will die!
Maybe... Maybe over there...
Here.
That day, the Gate of
Light opened here and
I was summoned.
Louise? Can't you hear me, Louise?
Louise! Hey, Louise!
Louise!
What's wrong with this guy?
"Louise! Louise!"
Did you get dumped by
your favorite maid?
Shut up.
Huh? Don't tell me you're crying!
You've got to be kidding me!
No wonder you got dumped!
I told you to shut up!
You bastard!
Showed you.
And it's all for nothing,
this loser's broke.
Let's go.
I can't get back to
Halkeginia by myself.
I can't see you again...
Louise...
What the...
The dragon is...
It's getting bigger!
It's huge!
Everyone, get back! Everyone back!
Scary...
Something is approaching from the front.
From the front?
That's the...
It's the Ancient Dragon!
I didn't know it could fly!
Fire! Attack right away!
You're not here anymore,
but I'm sure you're
living on in the world
where you're supposed be.
That's why I'm not afraid.
Next time, tune in for the last
episode, "Zero's Familiar."
Zero's Familiar
Thanks for everything, Saito!