What?
Chihaya Furu
Since my sister never
gets any screen time,
she's taken over with a
story from six years ago.
Chitose Furu
Got a problem with it?
New Year's Money - Part 1
Chitose-chan, here's
your New Year's money.
For Chitose-chan
For Chihaya-chan
Give Chihaya-chan hers for me.
Yay!  Thank you so much!
Chihaya, you probably haven't heard,
but kids over ten no longer
get New Year's money.
Huh?!
It's a new law.
Chitose!  How could you?!
I can pool our money to
buy expensive clothes,
and Chihaya will benefit in two years.
Man, I don't get New Year's money anymore.
100% of Chihaya's clothes are hand-me-downs
New Year's Money Part 2
Oh! A photo shoot!
Models have it all.
They always get to wear the latest name brand clothes.
What?
But you're still prettier than them.
Can I really have this?
You just bought it.
It's fine.
I can ask them to buy me another one.
Huh?
My sister is pretty and nice!
Bought using the New Year's
money stolen from Chihaya
New Year's Money Part 3
Hey, how much money did
you get for New Year's?
You probably got loads!
How much did you get, Wataya?
What do you mean?
It's against the law to
receive Christmas presents
and New Year's money after you're ten.
That's what my mom said.
Huh?  Are you stupid?
That's not...
Yeah, Taichi.
We're not allowed to receive
money after we're ten.
Huh?!
Lawbreaker!
Lawbreaker
What?!
That's impossible!
Everyone else got money!
Like me.
Me too.
So how much did you get?
Yeah, tell us.
Huh?  115,000 yen.
Lawbreaker!
Lawbreaker
Criminal!
Criminal
Oh, he couldn't have
received that much.
That would be
like Dad's bonus.
Ah—
He couldn't have received that much.
That would be like Dad's bonus.
New Year's Money   The End
Verse 16
The
Autumn
Leaves
of
Mt. Ogura
Huh?
Isn't this Hundred Poets?
Do you know how to play?
Well, we have a karuta tournament
at our school every year.
L-Lez play!
Huh?
What?
Wait!
I'll play, but we need
someone to do the reading.
I have a tape for that!
Um...  How does this work?
Line up 25 cards in 3 rows.
When the first verse of a poem is read,
you grab the card with the second verse.
Well, it's just a game.
What was that look?
Shall we begin?
Huh?
S-Sure.
The storm...
Huh?
Is this how you play karuta?
I should at least be
able to take one card...
Oh.
are joined at river's end
I know the first verse for that card.
"Swift waters parted by the jagged rocks"
It's just one card.
I have to get it!
Swift...
Sensei!
Can I take Wataya-kun's place?!
I don't mind.
Chihaya is obviously weaker.
I'm going to win this
match for Wataya-kun!
No...
the night is nearly past
I'm not doing this for him.
I'm...
I'm the one who's going to defeat Taichi!
That was a really fun match!
Karuta is so much fun!
But it would be a different story if
you were playing against Wataya-kun!
He's going to become a master.
That makes you the Queen, Ayase-san.
Queen?
It's the title given to the
strongest female player.
Queen...
Chihaya Furu
Use
Japanese
idioms to
describe
your
friends.
He sneaks a peek
when the manager
isn't around.
Use Japanese idioms to
describe your friends!
All work
and
no play
I already knew
that, Arata-kun.
"Not a care in the world."
Not A Care In The World
Huh?  What's that supposed to mean?
Then Porky is...
"barbeque pork"!
Barbeque Pork (Extra Large)
Hey!
Komano can be described as...
Data Miner
Come on!
"data miner."
You're doing it wrong!
Those aren't idioms!
For Kana-chan, I would use "wax poetic."
Wax Poetic
Oh—
What?  That's beautiful.
I'm so happy.
Oh, the president?
Um...
"J-Jack of all trades, master of none"?
Jack Of All Trades,
Master Of None
You've got it wrong, Prez!
We just needed a punch line!
Jack Of All Trades,
Master Of None
It fits you perfectly, Taichi.
Like rubbing salt in his wounds...
Not a
care in
the world!
What?  That fits you perfectly, Taichi!
"Master of none"...
We finally made it!
This is our clubroom?
Yeah.
I kept begging the Empress and
she finally gave it to us.
It's a storage room.
There's dust everywhere.
Don't complain!
Once we have five members,
we'll be recognized as an official club,
and they'll even assign us a teacher!
Can we even find three more people?
We can!
We absolutely can!
Rain takes...
leaving a hovering mist
above the trees and grass
Huh?!
What is this?
Don't tell me that...
...this is karuta?!
I can't play karuta...
I don't have the talent!
I'm not like you!
All I can do is study!
I belong behind my desk!
But...
Instead of a karuta genius,
I would rather have our new member
be someone who puts
in effort on the tatami.
If you have experience,
you should join the karuta club!
Join!
If you have experience,
you should join the karuta club!
Ms. Miyauchi,
We have 5 Karuta Club Members!!        (Introductions)
President 1-2 Ayase Chihaya        (I'm going to become a Queen!)
Vice President 1-1 Mashima Taichi        (Class B jack of all trades.)
Secretary 1-2 Komachi Tsutomu        (A very smart rookie.)
Equipment Manager 1-8 Nishida Yusei        (The roundest player in Class B.)
Treasurer 1-6 Oe Kanade        (A very reliable fan of classical poetry.)
Thank you very much!
You have five members, so you want me
to officially sanction the Karuta Club.
Hmm...
Very well.
Yay!
However, change the president
to someone other than Ayase-san.
Huh?!
I'll serve as the advisor for now.
Okay, dismissed.
While some dodge the famous waves...
Like the sound of...
She's fast!
Chihaya-chan, this won't work.
The gap between us is too big.
Kana-chan.
When I played karuta for
the very first time,
my opponent was someone who
was incredibly strong.
If he had gone easy on me,
I wouldn't love karuta the way I do now.
So, I'm not going to go easy on you.
I'm going to try my hardest,
because I need you guys to become stronger.
This summer,
the five of us will
participate as a team in
the national tournament!
Porky's T-shirts Part 1
"Starved!"
(HARAPEKO = Starved)
Huh?
Porky's T-shirts Part 2
"Extra large!"
Huh?
Porky's T-shirts Part 3
"Big helpings!"
Huh?
Porky's T-shirts Part 4
"Super-size!"
Where does Porky buy his T-shirts?
Good question.
My sister does screen printing as a hobby,
so she makes these for me.
I'll ask her to make T-shirts for you!
What?!
Mega-size
Please stop!
Porky, you don't have to!
It's okay!  Not necessary!
We can wear normal T-shirts!
I appreciate the thought!
Oe Traditional
Clothing
I love poetry
Victory for
Tsutomu
Three years
on the tatami
I don't make these T-shirts
because I want to!
He begs me to make them!
But let me know when you
want team shirts made.
Tsundere?!
M-Miss Piggy?!
You need team shirts, right?
I made
some,
so use
them.
You're the best!!
H-Hold on, Nishida!
Didn't you explain how team karuta works?
Huh?
Men's small    Women's Large        Men's Large      Men's Medium   Women's Small
With these shirts,
we can only use one lineup!
And why did she use this order?
It's based on how much she liked our looks.
Oh...
Wait, I'm last?!
I'm second-to-last?!
"Master of none"...
Oh!  I'm first?!
I can feel someone looking at me...
Badump
Lock-on
I can feel someone looking at me...
Lock-on.
Man Talk
Part 1
Between Ayase and Kana-chan,
who would you rather have as a girlfriend?
I take Kana-chan!
Kana-chan...
Hey, Mashima!  That's no fair!
Spit it out!
Don't be shy!
We all know you prefer Kana-chan!
Ayase is out of the question!
Out Of The Question
Who would you rather have as a girlfriend?
Out of the question
Kana-chan                       Ayase
2 votes
Depressing...
Man Talk
Part 2
-Taichi
Strikes
Back-
You guys...
like boobs.
You're only interested in her tits.
Ah!  You weren't supposed to say that!
Y-You're wrong!
Kana-chan is cute!
And she's sweet!
I can see myself on a date with her!
But!
I can't see myself on a date with Ayase!
We'd end up practicing karuta!
That's right!
Ayase is totally out of the question!
We like boobies!
Karuta fanatic
Kana-chan                       Ayase
Who would you rather have as a girlfriend?
Depressed...
3 votes?
They're right.
Please present this to the receptionist.
Match: Finals
Team: Mizusawa High School
Order| Name
Porky
Kana-chan
Taichi
Desktomu-kun
Chihaya
Here is Mizusawa High School's lineup.
Thank you.
Eyebrows!  Eyebrows!
Dr. Harada.
I heard you made it to the finals!
I'm so glad to hear that.
Chihaya-chan must be on a roll.
Doctor, I never knew that Chihaya
could succumb to pressure.
Huh?  Chihaya-chan?
I chose the wrong words when
I tried to stimulate her.
I didn't think she would fall apart...
So I need to accept that I
don't even understand Chihaya,
since I'm the president of this club.
I'll be going then.
This is why I can never stop watching...
I could spend my entire youth on karuta
without ever becoming better than Arata.
Remember all the time you
spent practicing your swing.
You've already become a different person.
You'll be fine.
You can do this!
When the wind sends waves...
Here.
After I determined to...
Feel the love...
That's what you get for not apologizing.
Got it!
I got it!  I took a card!
Yes!
Ayase!  I took a card from
the opponent's side!
You have to do the same!
I got the card, too!
I held onto mine!
I'm gonna take the next card!
In an individual match,
one card is one card, nothing more.
But now...
like a stream widening into a river
Every card I take is a card for our team!
My fear is not of...
Since the dew atop the blades...
I feel that my love is...
I hear the beating of cloth...
Nice job, Nishida!
Thank you very much.
The one thing I do have is my memory
of which cards have been read.
I can become the backbone of this team!
though you have never known that pain
I won't make a mistake!
I can win one card at a time!
Said bed was cold...
Thank you very much.
One win for Mizusawa!
Got it!
I got it!
Two wins for Mizusawa!
Impassionate gods...
Chihaya!
We did it!
Omi Learning Center
High School National Ogura Hundred
Poets Karuta Championship
Everyone!
One card at a time!
Yeah!
Chihaya?
Please wait!
Ayase forfeits.
I can't lose.
Attack.
It's not over yet!
I-I'm in the middle of a match.
I need to go!
Chihaya! You need to lie down!
You forfeited the match.
Forfeited?
Chihaya, stop!
Stay still!
No! Let me go!
There's no point in going back!
They won't let you play!
We worked so hard.
We promised to win together.
I-I'm sorry, everyone.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing, Chihaya-chan?!
You don't need to apologize.
Ayase! I got my first win today!
Huh?
That's right!
He actually won two games in a row!
But we lost to Fujisaki in the playoffs.
I wanted to play more!
Me too!
You need time to recover, right?
Maybe you should take the
bullet train home tomorrow morning?
I'm still shaking with excitement!
I'm going to recover!
I'll be in perfect health for the
individual tournament tomorrow!
Ayase Chihaya
Wakamiya Shinobu.
Wakamiya Shinobu
The youngest Queen in history.
So the flower pe—
—tals are scattered like the
snow by the passing storm,
Chihaya...
Here we go again.
She's already up by ten cards?
Wakamiya Shinobu's on a
whole different level.
She's probably ready to throw in the towel.
Chihaya is just as fast as the Queen
when she's focused on one card.
But there are dozens of cards on the field.
She can't focus on that many
cards at the same time.
But the Queen can do it?
I can't do it.
I don't see how
I can win.
This has never happened before.
I never show mercy.
I should at least be able to take one card!
I can't be mentally weaker now
than I was when I was 12!
May the time spent in our...
She hit my hand?
So it was close?
Oh, impressive.
—ust of wind...
Impassionate gods...
She got it!
Chihaya!
Here is #20!
My body's starting to loosen up again...
I want to become faster...
To become freer...
During a match...
So when I'm playing an opponent
who's so strong that I'm scared stiff,
I can move freely.
I still don't understand,
but is that what it means
to be a strong player?
Thank you very much.
I was only able to take five cards.
The Queen is still...
...twenty cards better.
A straight line.
Straight...
Straight and swift as an arrow.
My memorization has to be
better for this to work.
Memorize...  Memorize...
Straight! Swift!
Straighter!  Swifter!
Listen hard...
Harder...  Harder...
What do I have to do to beat her?
What will it take?
Today is the day.
The day Chihaya's dream became real.
Girl Talk
Part 1
Michiru-chan
A Classmate
Chi-chan, Kana-chan.
Which karuta club member
would you want to go out with?
Well, there's only one possible answer.
Kana-chan.
Huh?!
A perfect victory!
Kana-chan      Ayase          Mashima           Porky         Desktomu
Congrats
Kana-chan
Congrats, Kana-chan.
Girl Talk
Part 2
Michiru
wants to
talk about
love
That's not what I meant!
The boy!
Which of the boys would
you want to go out with?!
You don't have to limit yourself
to the karuta club members!
Do you want a serious answer?
No!  Wait!
Don't say anything that
will spoil the story!
It's not over yet.
Use Japanese
idioms to
describe
your friends
Again
I don't mind if I don't get
Use Japanese idioms to
describe your friends again!
Heart
And
Soul
Don't be stupid this time.
Gotcha!
Komano is a "smart cookie"?
Smart Cookie
Kana-chan has "brains and beauty."
Brains And Beauty
Komano-kun...
The president is, um...
"Easy on the eyes."
Easy on the eyes
"Fools rush in."
Fools Rush In
That describes Chihaya perfectly.
What?
Yep, yep
Yep, yep.
Porky is, um...
Pork Dressed As Lamb
"Pork dressed as lamb."
You mean "mutton dressed as lamb."
Mutton Dressed As Lamb
But why would you choose that idiom?
She probably couldn't
remember any other ones.
Wait, Ayase!  You're calling me a pig—
That's all.  Please keep
watching this year!
People who haven't memorized
Hundred Poets are bugs.
See you next week!