I've been thinking this whole time.
What should I do for Norman's sake?
The answer is...
to do nothing.
Mom told me...
to give up and free myself of the pain.
But...
I will never, ever give up.
I won't let Norman die in vain.
And you, Ray?
So we're always thinking
the same thing in the end.
Let's run away, Ray.
I came here to talk about that.
I wanted to talk to you, too.
These past two months, we couldn't really talk
since we were worried about Mom watching us.
Yeah. I didn't want Mom
to figure out our true intentions.
True intentions?
Yeah. Mom is really cautious.
Even though we weren't doing anything,
Mom never stopped watching us.
But we could use that against her.
If she's watching me, I could keep
her eyes away from people other than me.
Don and Gilda, huh?
Yeah. I left everything to them.
Training for the escape,
and all other preparations.
How far along are you?
Everything is ready.
Supplies, food, and warm clothing.
We can escape anytime.
That's pretty good.
Now, how will you run away?
I worked that out too. I have a plan.
Let's run away tomorrow afternoon,
before you get shipped out.
Wait. It's reckless to go out during the day.
The situation's different from before.
We should leave at night
when it's easier to hide.
Hear me out.
Sit.
Okay. There are two problems.
First, Mom's watchful eyes.
She's always watching us, and she's always
holding one of the younger ones.
She'll be doing that during the day,
and at night, the babies are in her room.
In order to escape with everyone,
we'll have to shake Mom off,
and separate her from the little ones.
And then, past the wall is a cliff.
We can't climb down from it.
If we're escaping, it'll be through the bridge.
But there's only one.
I'm sure there's security to begin with,
and once they find out there's been an escape,
the guards will rush there.
Plus, it's near the headquarters.
Those monsters should be everywhere.
So, what are you going to do?
I think this is the best answer.
Oil?
At night, we'll light the House on fire.
You're going to start a fire?
That's right.
When Mom is distracted putting it out, we'll lead
everyone outside, saying it's an evacuation.
If we seal the door to the secret room,
Mom can't notify headquarters, and
headquarters will think it's a fire, not an escape.
Then security won't go towards the bridge.
We can escape through it then.
As a bonus, I also hid ten Molotovs
behind some rocks in the forest.
Molotov bottles?
Don't underestimate
my six years of preparations.
Throw those Molotovs into the neighboring plants
on the way to the bridge.
If all goes well, there'll be another fire
to make security even scarcer.
Since it's nighttime,
no one will be in the forest.
No one will die.
So instead of tomorrow,
let's run away tonight, right now.
Can you do it, Emma?
Don't worry.
This place is the farthest distance away
from everyone's rooms.
They can escape before the fires get to them.
They've trained to run in formation
through tag, right?
Or is your leg still...
It's fine!
Then it's decided.
Ray.
But you know, Emma...
To tell you the truth,
I'm still against the idea of taking everyone.
Especially after hearing
there's a cliff beyond those walls.
Even if you do take some,
it should only be Don and Gilda.
You should at least leave the babies behind.
For their sake, and for yours, too.
But you won't listen even if I stop you.
And it's better than having you
stay behind and not escape.
So I won't say anything more.
You decide.
So what are you doing?
Go tell Don and Gilda.
You said...
to throw over the Molotov bottles?
Yeah. You, or maybe Don could...
And I'm worried about one more thing.
Even if we start a fire,
what if Mom abandons the building?
She might give up on putting out the fire and
refuse to take her eyes off of us, the merchandise.
You realized, huh?
There's a good possibility of that happening.
That's why starting a fire won't be enough.
If we don't stop Mom, then we won't have
any chances of escaping from her.
But don't worry.
I just have to do this.
Ray?
Isn't this the greatest?
The perfect scorer
with the set shipment date will burn up.
She won't be able to abandon me.
I've been waiting for this day.
I decided this a long time ago.
Many, many years ago.
It's a childish retaliation.
You know what, Emma?
I've never really been interested
in studying or reading.
But I endured it, and I worked hard
to improve my value to the highest it could be.
Twelve years.
I'm a feast that they've been waiting for.
I'm going to take that away from them tonight.
Right before the harvest
they've been looking forward to.
Don't think you can eat me.
Don't think you can serve me.
Food? Merchandise? I don't give a crap!
I'm a human being! Serves them right!
Ray...
Also, it's fine this way.
This is the best way.
I've watched my family die all these years.
I used them.
And they were all good kids.
They were kindhearted.
- Wait.
- Don't move.
Listen, Emma. You only have one chance.
Make this work.
Please, don't let me, or Norman, die in vain.
This is for you.
From that time...
I'm now 12 years old.
It was a life I wanted to curse, but the time
I spent with everyone was really fun.
No, stop!
Thank you.
Bye-bye, Emma.
Happy birthday.
Goodbye.
Ray!
What is this smell?
Ray! Ray!
Ray?
Emma!
Mom, help! Ray is...
Ray is in there!
Did he set himself on fire?
Mom!
Gilda, take everyone outside!
Also please get the babies in my room!
Okay!
If I can...
at least get his brain...
Emma, stay back.
Ray.
Why aren't the sprinklers working?
Emma, you need to get out of here too.
Or else, you'll also...
Emma?
What were those children...
wearing on their feet?
Oh, she's here.
Emma!
Thanks for waiting, everyone!
Thank you.
Bye-bye, Emma.
Nice catch.
You...
Sorry, but I'm not going to let you die.
Not me, nor the other children.
The other children?
I brought what you asked for, Emma.
And everyone's already good to go.
Thanks, Thoma and Lanni.
Okay, Ray. Get changed.
Done changing? Then next is...
Wait, but...
Emma, I'm...
Do you still want to die, you blockhead?
Stop yapping because we're escaping!
Emma, we're done here.
What's this?
Your replacement.
It'll create a certain smell.
Those braids...
Anna gave them to me.
Lastly, the tracking device.
I'll take it out, so sit with your ear toward me.
Emma, is this...
"You can die anywhere,
and it doesn't have to be here."
"I'll show you something cool,
so shut up and come."
A message from Norman.
Huh? Norman?
To my dearest Emma...
I'm going to write down the plan from here.
Ray is planning to die.
He's doing all this so you and I don't get killed.
That's what he said.
He didn't include himself in the equation.
He has no intention of escaping.
He plans on dying inside this House.
He's going to set himself on fire to distract Mom,
and let us run away.
That's Ray's plan.
I'm not going to let him do that.
No matter what.
That's why I'm writing down
the plan I came up with.
It'll happen in two months.
Probably the night before Ray's birthday.
Use the fire that Ray's planning to start,
save Ray, outwit Mom, and escape with everyone.
Don't worry. There's time.
I also got an unexpected item.
It was from Sister Krone.
I'm counting on you, Emma.
Please take care of Ray and our siblings.
And everything else.
Okay, let's begin, Norman.
Ray!
Okay everyone, let's escape.
We'll run to the wall!
Norman.
Hey, Don. What's going on?
Do they all know
about the House and the escape?
- Yup.
- How?
Emma told them about it.
Let's tell more kids
other than Don and Gilda, Norman.
Don, Gilda, and probably everyone else
aren't as immature as we think.
If we're going to run from those monsters,
I think it's better they know about the dangers,
and should willingly join our escape.
And Mom only suspects the oldest kids,
and not everyone else.
Do you think it's reckless?
It is.
But with this plan,
we can catch Mom off guard.
Realistically, this is the only way
to escape with everyone.
At first, we told four.
What do you want to know?
Go ahead. Ask me anything.
Really, anything?
Yes. Whether it be about the farm
or about the headquarters...
Nat.
There are humans outside
who haven't been eaten.
Anna.
Then you don't know how long
the demons have been around?
Lannion. Thoma.
We let them hear what Sister said.
Since that far back?
For the rest, we spent
two months slowly recruiting them in.
Mom probably didn't notice at all.
That Emma was only pretending to have given up,
but was actually giving everyone instructions.
Training for the escape,
and all other preparations.
How far along are you?
Everything is ready.
Supplies, food, and warm clothing.
We can escape anytime.
You guys...
Norman.
Nat and I will climb up first.
Then we'll pull everyone up.
Okay, everyone! Just do it
like how we trained, and you'll be fine!
Everyone's going to escape safely.
Wait...
It's burning. Everything is burning.
But...
They're still alive! Emma and Ray, and...
I won't let you escape, my adorable children.
Is this all of us?
Mom.