Did Suna say something?
From: Yukika-chan
Yamato-san,
Thank you for your help yesterday. Thanks to you
and Takeo-kun, I was able to invite Sunakawa-kun
to the zoo. Thank you for listening to me.
I'm in the city, trying to buy some clothes,
but I'm having trouble picking them.
If you happen to be free,
would it be possible for you to help me?
Yukika-chan, sorry to keep you waiting!
Thank you for coming.
You're going on a date.
Of course you'd want to get ready!
Yes!
But I don't know what kind of clothes to wear.
You want him to think you look cute!
With any luck, I hope he'll like me!
But I have no idea what kind
of clothes I should wear,
so that he'll like me...
Let's try asking Takeo-kun.
What kind of clothes does Sunakawa-kun like girls to wear?
Suna, what kind of clothes do you like on girls?
What kind of question is that?
Well, I guess
Maybe this fits the zoo theme?
Oh come on,      Maybe this fits the zoo theme?
anything normal is fine, if it suits the person.
Normal clothes that suit Japanese...
Wow these shoes have
really high heels!
I couldn't...                              Wow these shoes have
Traditional Japanese clothes?!
No, they can be Western clothes.
Cute
Cute                                                            But expensive
If we're talking clothes that suit anyone...
Subject:     Re: Sunakawa-kun
He says school uniform
I'll wear my uniform.
I'm sure he means wear anything, really...
Yukika-chan...
Yukika-chan's dressed up.
She froze when she saw Suna!
Yeah, Suna's good-looking...
Seeing him up close, she must be feeling
overwhelmed and paralyzed.
Talk!                                           Good luck!
But she has to talk.
What's the point of asking him out
if you won't talk, Yukika-chan?
Let...
Let's go to the zoo!
Busai Zoo
Okay.
The Letter to Me
The reason I picked the zoo is...
During an elementary school field trip,
Sunakawa-kun asked why
we call the giraffe "kirin."
No one knew the answer, so that ended it then,
but I knew.
I really wanted to tell him
it was because it's named after
a mythical beast in China.
But I just didn't have the courage to tell him.
That's why I wanted to make some
good memories at the zoo today.
Can you take our picture?
Sure.
So tell that to Suna!
You're right...
You're right!!                            Good luck!!
When I look back,
I think having Sunakawa-kun save
me from the ball in dodgeball
was my prime time moment.
Price time? What?
Prime time.
It means the best time of your life.
The Best Time of Your Life
That happened way too early!
It'll be fine. Suna isn't scary.
Hey, Suna!
Where do you want to go afterward?
Let's just follow the route.
Okay!
Try it.
Too Close
I can't!
What are you talking about?
Never mind. It's nothing.
Hey!
That's a pretty bird.
Um...
Uh...
A petting zoo!
Let's go!
She ran.
Petting Zoo
So cute!
Yamato, you remind me of a cute critter.
Oh, me?
How?
I guess I'm small, but maybe I'm a carnivore.
Roar!
I love her.
Oh, that one reminds me of Yukika-chan.
That? I don't think so.
Really?
Isn't it cute?
Oh, I see.
If that's what you think, I guess that's fine.
Um...
Hmm?
I'm sorry I took it the wrong way at first.
Oh, that's really impressive!
The gorilla reminds me of you, Takeo-kun.
You don't always hold back, huh?                     Does he?
Maybe, but I wouldn't stand
a chance against him...
I think he's really strong.
He is strong!
Why are you laughing?
Well, he would be strong.
A downpour!
I'm happy just to get out of the rain for a bit...
If it's with Sunakawa-kun.
So tell Suna that!
Yukika-chan, you won't make any
memories with him this way.
It'll be like elementary school.
I'll talk to him...
Do you look like him?
Now that I'm thinking you look like him,
Takeo-kun, I'm starting to really like gorillas!
I love her
Postcards
Th-There isn't a postcard of
the bird you really liked.
It didn't seem that popular.
I guess there wouldn't be one.
That's too bad.
Yeah.
I managed to talk to him!
All right!
There will be a trivia competition
in front of Monkey Mountain.
We encourage everyone to join.
What's that about?
I wonder, too!
Would you like to go see?
Sure.
We'll now begin the trivia competition.
If you would like to join, please form pairs.
Can the pairs join hands, so that
we know how many there are?
Crap!
Petrified
I should have paired up with Suna!
Thirty-two pairs.
You can let go of each other's hand now!
Thank you.
Here's the first question, then.
Whoa, it's starting
The giraffe's tongue is purple
in order to absorb UV rays.
True or false? Move to circle or X.
I think it's false.
It's false!
The answer is "false"!
Q2: Elephants have four teeth.
True or False?
Now for the second question...
It's true!
The third question...
Q3: Rhinoceros horns are shed and regrown every year.
True or False?
It's false!
The fourth question...
Q4: The Japanese serow is not in the same family as the deer.
True or False?
True!
False!
Yukika-chan's amazing.
Yeah.
Now we only have two pairs,
so here is the final question.
The first pair to answer correctly will win.
Which zebra is at this zoo?
Zebra...
Is it the mountain zebra, the plains
zebra, or the Grévy's zebra?
Got it!
It's the plains zebra!
Correct!
That was fast!
Amami-san, you know a lot.
Congratulations.
Here's the prize, coasters.
Congrats!
You're both amazing!
I didn't do anything.
It was Amami-san.
I like reading books, so...
If there's anything to read lying around,
I find myself reading...
You used to read a lot in kindergarten, too.
You, too, Sunakawa-kun! You're always reading!
Well... I guess I do.
I'll go walk Yamato home.
Okay.
Um, thank you for today.
Sure, it was fun. I hadn't been for a while.
See you at school.
You talked to him!
I was all nervous for you, too
I'm so happy for you!
It was like a dream...
Don't worry, it wasn't a dream!
It's because you summoned the courage.
Today was the happiest day of my life.
Slime time?
Prime time.
I talked about small things with
Sunakawa-kun today.
It was really nothing,
but Sunakawa-kun nodded and laughed.
I've always wanted to be that way with him.
I'm glad...
See you later!            Good luck at school, too.
Talking about nothing.
Nodding and listening to you,
smiling at what you said.
She's right... That might be the happiest thing ever.
Oh, they're talking!
First
Love
Yukika-chan, what happened?
What's going on?
Whoa, she's crying.
For real? Why's she crying?
She isn't a spectacle!
Rooftop Entry Forbidden
It's nothing.
Sunakawa-kun's so kind.
He's a very kind person.
He came to the zoo because he's kind.
He smiled because he's kind.
Because he's kind...
I don't think Sunakawa-kun dislikes me.
But it doesn't mean he likes me, you know?
He's just being kind.
No, it isn't that I don't like her.
If I didn't want to, I wouldn't go.
When I looked at him,
I knew I felt something off.
So that's what it was.
He doesn't not like her, but he
doesn't like her, either.
At night and stuff, I wonder what
Sunakawa-kun might be doing.
Sometimes, I want to see him.
I wonder if we might randomly
run into each other.
But...
I don't think Sunakawa-kun
thinks that way about me.
You can tell these things, you know?
Sorry, I don't know...
I see, you don't know.
How we feel about each other is so different
that I'm heartbroken.
I'm going to give up.
Thank you for everything.
Please tell Sunakawa-kun that, too.
I shouldn't have told him how I felt.
H-Hey!
She's right.
Not disliking someone is different
than liking someone.
Takeo, what are you doing?
You aren't going ho—
I don't sense Yukika-chan anymore...
Oh, Takeo-kun!
Yamato...
I got a text message from Yukika-chan.
Thank you for everything.
I'll never forget how you helped me
pick out clothes. Goodbye.
I don't think we'll be seeing each other again.
May you be happy with Takeo-kun.
Did something happen?
I replied to her text, but she hasn't written back.
She won't even answer my calls!
She...
She said that it was getting painful,
how kind Suna was to her.
That she was heartbroken because they
felt so differently about each other.
She said she was going to give up.
She asked me to thank you for everything.
Oh, okay.
I got it.
I'm going to stop by the bookstore.
So this is how it ends.
Just like that.
There isn't much closure...
It's kind of sad that it just faded out like that.
Yukika-chan was saying that she
wished she'd never said anything.
Do you agree, Yamato?
Of course not!
If she thought about it more,
she'd remember there were some fun times, too!
Right.
That's right.
Oh, hello.
The zoo yesterday was fun.
Delete Photo?
Delete    Cancel
Don't say sad things like you wish
you'd never said anything,
Yukika-chan.
Suna, you go ahead!
What?
It's urgent!
Okay.
Yukika-chan!
Oh, my god!
Yamato, I found Yukika-chan.
She's headed for the park!
Why are you running away?
You don't have to disappear from
all of our lives, Yukika—
Coward!
What's there to do now?
Just leave me alone.
Suna might only be nice to you now,
but aren't you just getting started?
I can't think like that!
How can I keep talking to him,
when I know he doesn't have feelings for me?
I'm not tough like you!
But, Yukika-chan...
I've seen the letter you left for Suna with
his chocolate, back in kindergarten!
You saw it?
Sorry...
I was really impressed when I saw the letter!
I thought, "This must be how it is
when someone really likes you!"
I'm still impressed.
That's why even Suna still remembers the letter.
I don't think he's nice to just anyone.
It's too sad to have things end this way!
Takeo-kun, where's Yukika-chan?
Inside.
Yukika-chan...
What are you doing in front of the ladies' room?
Are you a peeping tom?
We're discussing an important issue!
He's a friend of mine!
Oh, next time, try not to act so suspicious.
Yes, sir.
So my letter was impressive?
Yeah!
To tell you the truth,
it would be sad if I never spoke
to Sunakawa-kun again...
Right.
Incoming Call
Sunakawa-kun
What should I do?
It's Sunakawa-kun...
Take the call!
Good luck.
Hello.
Oh, it's me, Sunakawa.
Amami-san?
Yes, it's me.
Yes.
Yes, okay...
Yes, I know the place.
Okay, I'll see you.
He says he wants to meet with me.
I'll go meet with him!
Yukika-chan, we'll wait here.
Okay, I'll be back.
I wonder what Sunakawa-kun's going to do.
I don't know.
I don't know, but Suna is kind...
I heard from Takeo.
I'm sorry for asking you to come see me.
It isn't a problem!
Here.
Thank you for all the chocolates.
I've always wanted to thank you for them.
Thank you.
Library
I'm sorry.
Thank you for being so nice to me.
I really liked you!
I want to thank you!
If I see you at school,
can we still talk like friends?
Okay.
Yukika-chan...
Sunakawa-kun gave me this.
Wow, it's really cute!
He has such good taste.
This is exactly the kind of thing I like.
He said this was for all ten years
of giving him chocolate.
He apologized to me.
I had fun.
Talking to Takeo-kun and Yamato-san
until late at night.
Picking clothes with Yamato-san.
Going home with Sunakawa-kun,
though I couldn't talk to him at all...
Going to the zoo with Sunakawa-kun,
Still, I have a lot of happy memories!
His world and mine overlapped.
I'm glad I told him how I felt!
That hurt.
Sorry.
I'm fragile.
I'm a weakling.
I'd die easily...
My bad.
I wanted to be like you, Takeo-kun.
Huh?
He loves you, you know.
When he's with you,
Sunakawa-kun laughs out loud.
I like how he laughs when he's with you the most.
But I can't just jump into a river like you...
I can't write letters like you, either.
I like you, too, Takeo-kun.
Though in a completely different way from
how I like Sunakawa-kun, of course.
Were you able to tell Suna everything you wanted to?
Yes.
I don't need anything in return, so please like me.
I told him everything.
I've been telling him for the last ten years.
I don't need anything in return,
so I want him to like me.
That's all.
But I guess that was the
most difficult thing to ask.
She's right.
If someone you like returns the feeling,
you don't need anything.
I want Sunakawa-kun to date a really nice girl,
who's really kind and cute, and likes
Sunakawa-kun even more than I do!
I want Sunakawa-kun to like someone
and to date that person!
Right.
I'll walk home with Yukika-chan.
You had curry today?
Yeah.
Me, too.
Huh.
When Amami-san...
I'm sorry I took it the wrong way at first.
When she apologized to you at the zoo,
I thought she was a nice person.
I see.
I wonder why she apologized.
I still don't get it
Suna, do you like me?
Where'd that come from?
It's what Yukika-chan said.
Does anyone not like you?
Suna!
I hope you find someone you like!
Well, I'm having a great enough time as is.
Sometimes, you end up in tears
after liking someone.
The bird's name is the "Bali myna."
— Amami Yukika
But liking someone is still a good thing.
My Spring Break
Next time: My Spring Break.