Dreadful...
What is that?
Japanese?
You mean that country in Asia?
Where they do that "harakiri"?
I'm pleased to meet you, Lord Horikawa.
Welcome to the Kingdom of Albion.
I am greatly honored that you would
welcome us yourself, Princess.
It basically means our "princess of air"
is all they're willing to send
for an Eastern island nation.
They've likely considered the risks involved.
I doubt the Crown is unaware
of the assassination attempts.
The assassins' ringleader is Todo Jubei.
Apparently he's single-handedly cut down 100 men.
These undeveloped countries
and their overblown rumors...
It was in a European military report.
During the Boshin War, he boarded
an ironclad ship and sank it unaided.
But you know, now that
we have the Princess on our side,
I would hate for her to get caught up
in an assassination plot.
That won't be a problem.
That is what our Principal is for.
I've had the royal car prepared for you.
It will take us to London. This way, please.
All this, for us. We are deeply in your debt.
We entrust ourselves to your care on our journey.
Er, yes...
These Japanese people are peculiar.
I'm sure they'd love to hear that
from a native of the Black Lizard Planet.
I understand you came here
to revise the treaty, Lord Horikawa?
The current terms are far too one-sided.
Of course, this is a result of our own ignorance.
However...
Horikawa-sama, this is not the place.
Uh, yes.
Of course.
I see how important this is to you, Lord Horikawa.
I have no authority over it myself,
but I can promise you a meeting with my Grandmother.
Oh!
I am in your debt. Truly, truly in your debt.
Please, you mustn't!
It's nothing...
Someone's here.
We're on a moving train. No one could...
Who are you?
You Western women have no manners.
When you ask someone's name, you first name yourself.
Are you Todo Jubei?
I didn't expect you to be a woman.
Two handguns.
At your bosom and behind your waist.
And your left shoe...
You have something hidden there.
I hear the faint clinking of metal.
Jumping onto a train with no backup.
That's a legendary killer for you.
You little-!
Dorothy!
The world is truly vast.
To think I would find such martial skill in the West.
You impress me, too. So the story
about you killing 100 men was hardly fake.
Stop!
She is not the assassin!
Hold your fire!
She's NOT our enemy?
Chise-dono, what are you doing here?
You know why I'm here!
To slay Todo Jubei!
That is why
I have come to this distant foreign land.
I couldn't send you back alone.
For the time being, I will allow you
to accompany me as far as London.
Thank you, My Lord.
You have my word, I will protect you
and put an end to those rebels.
We agreed to take you with us,
but any fighting will...
I know Todo Jubei better than any of your samurai.
Yes, but...
I'm against it.
With Princess onboard,
I cannot allow any dubious characters to ride this train.
You question my intent?
You ARE a stowaway.
Then allow me to prove my trustworthiness.
Stop it, both of you.
Chise-dono, put your sword away.
Ange.
I want you to be Miss Chise's buddy.
What?
"Buddy," "buddy"...
It means "partner."
Me? Partner to HER?
Princess,
this isn't funny.
If this girl is dangerous,
that's all the more reason to put her
under the watchful eye of someone I can trust.
There's a platoon of 50 railroad security guards
riding in Car 5 and the caboose.
It will take more than a flimsy attack to kill Lord Horikawa.
Jubei's attacks are not flimsy.
Have you fought him?
Many times.
Why did you fight him?
Was it a matter of principle?
Or was it some matter between the masters you serve?
Is this an interrogation?
We're buddies. We need to get to know each other.
I hail from the Saga domain. A samurai clan. Age 16.
I like pickles.
And you?
Ange. Age 17.
I come from the Black Lizard Planet.
I see! That's how you learned those martial arts.
Princess Kaguya, too, came from the Moon.
It all makes sense.
You have Selenites in Japan?
Not only people from among the stars.
We live close to the gods, as well.
Close to the gods?
They reside in the mountains, the rivers,
even in the latrine.
What?
This is the only stop before we get to London.
Which is to say, if he were to attack, he would do it here.
Don't cry.
I will take the pain away.
Owie, owie,
fly away!
Better?
Uh-huh. I'm all right.
What did you do?
An Eastern magic spell
handed down to me from my father.
He cast it for me many times in the past.
Why are we helping Todo Jubei?
I have no interest in that eastern island nation.
I only hope he gets that woman
caught up in an assassination plot.
She may be only a figurehead,
but she's fourth in line to the throne.
We can't be sure someone won't move her ahead.
So he didn't come after us at Maidstone Station.
Even the fearsome Jubei is out of his element
in a foreign nation, it seems.
He will appear.
Jubei isn't such a simple opponent.
Why are you so obsessed with him?
Because Jubei...
killed my father.
Two years ago, time stopped for me completely.
And until I strike Jubei down,
my tears refuse to be shed.
And what do you think you're doing?
I was watching the janitor, too.
Are you Todo Jubei?
An explosion?
Stay here.
I'll go see what's happening.
What? But how?
The outbound trains should all have
stopped running for security reasons.
Then it must be...
Todo Jubei!
I see the Duke of Normandy kept his promise.
Fire!
Slow down the engine!
We need to get back to the soldiers!
Can't! If we slow down while we're
still connected, we'll derail!
He's boarding the train!
Everyone, draw your swords!
Fire!
Your Highness, get down!
Dorothy!
I'm sorry.
I messed up.
Where's Princess?
In the state car. Go to her, Ange.
With your C-ball, you can still catch them.
Take me with you.
That is where we'll find Jubei.
Please.
I'll take all the help I can get.
Follow my timing.
Two.
One.
Zero!
What?!
You would betray us, Chise-dono?!
You are the traitors!
Why you-!
SHE is here.
Go faster!
Yes, sir!
Don't fall behind!
They'll drag us off the rails!
This is bad.
What?
The tracks merge up ahead.
If the cars hit each other at this speed,
it will be a catastrophe!
Ange!
Don't let them board!
They went up top!
Such incredible skill!
I'll let you handle this.
As you wish.
Jubei-dono!
Oshima?
Forgive me!
No!
Lord Horikawa. I am here for your life.
Pathetic remnant of the Shogunate!
Protect our lord!
Your Highness, get back!
Beatrice!
Some sort of armor?
JUBEI!
Princess!
Wait!
Ange!
Let's stop these trains!
Princess!
Close the regulator valve!
Use the red lever!
Turn the reversing gear to the right!
Next, open the bypass valve!
And brake!
We did it.
You've grown stronger, Chise.
Chise, you...
Please be at ease, Lord Horikawa.
I have slain the traitor, Todo Jubei.
Jubei was your father.
The caring father who taught me the sword was dead.
The man resting here is nothing more
than a traitorous assassin.
Is this what you wanted?
I have no need for your sympathy.
Rather, I am proud.
I was able to surpass my father.
Let's go. Dorothy is waiting.
Chise...
Thank you for keeping Princess safe.
Owie, owie, fly away.
How strange.
Your spell isn't working, Father.
It won't take away the pain in my heart.
Should you really be drinking alcohol?
Oh, don't worry. My wounds have closed up nicely.
Wanna see?
No, thank you.
Excuse me.
You're-!
A new transfer student. Todo Chise.
Transfer student?!
We're glad to have you, Chise.
This room is our base of operations.
Isn't it lovely?
Huh?
Huh?!
Our respective employers have struck a deal.
I will be helping with Operation: Changeling.
I introduced Lord Horikawa to Control.
I thought he might switch over to the Commonwealth.
When did you s-s-seduce Lord Horikawa?
You nobles use such naughty language.
But wh-what else could I call it?
Ange. You made it possible for me to fight Jubei.
Allow me to thank you again.
Stop.
If you're going to live in our country,
I'll teach you how we do it in the West.
It's called a handshake.
These Western customs aren't so bad.