So you can fish at
this park, supposedly.
I'd like to try my rod out here.
Huh? You have a rod, don't you?
You know, one with a line.
A line of pus*y juice?
That's weird...
You just don't stop, do you?!
Dum
Tweet
Ousai Academy Student Council Rules,
Article Two, Paragraph Eleven:
Dum
You have to support each other...
when you're doing a seated cowgirl.
You're one rotten fruit.
Do you know what cherry
blossoms stand for?
No, I didn't know they
stood for something.
Tell her, Shino-chan.
Being well-cultured, noble,
pure, and innocent.
Ultimate legendary days!
Do you remember what I told you?
No problem here.
Of course.
Well-cultured, noble,
pure, and innocent!
It gets cold in
November, doesn't it?
Yeah, everyone starts
putting on extra layers.
I guess guys don't
really like it, though?
Not at all.
Autumn
Suzu Head
It's okay, Tsuda-kun!
The more someone's wearing,
the more you have to take off!
I see.
Why are they trying to
cheer me up, exactly?
Seitokai Yakuindomo
A pure reaction to
a double entendre
We've had new rules
since we became co-ed,
but I don't think many
people are aware of them.
I think we should write that in
the next student council article.
But I don't think it'd be possible
for us to write all of them out.
I guess we can always shorten them.
Okay, Hagimura, go over
the first new rule.
Any romance between students
is forbidden on school grounds.
People shouldn't have lives.
Well, that was direct.
It is forbidden to touch another
part of the opposite sex's body
other than the hand and arms.
Huh? I didn't know that.
That's pretty strict...
Looking
back
We've come in contact quite a bit.
People normally don't
think about that.
I guess that means
I can't step on Tsuda-kun.
What were you planning?
It'd a good thing for everyone
to understand that they should judge
their distance from others.
People seem to be acting
inappropriately lately.
Here's the report you needed.
Right.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
To be honest,
every time I see your braids,
it feels like my butt is
just calling out for them.
She's out cold again.
Igarashi is here.
She's not exactly paying attention.
Let's head to the conference room.
Oh, right.
Huh?
Tsuda, your jacket's folded back.
Huh? Well, that makes me look bad.
Guess I'll have to help.
I'll hold it down for you
until you get it fixed.
That's kind of sweet.
That's nice!
Oh.
A tennis ball fell here.
I guess I'll...
give it back later.
Huh?
Tsuda...
It looks weird in your
pocket like that.
Oh.
Put one in your other pocket!
I refuse!
I guess this'll do.
Aria, we'll put the tables we're
not going to use against the wall.
Help me out.
Sure.
Here goes.
No one said anything
about moving your boobs!
Here's the schedule for the
end of the year cleaning.
Right.
If we made sure we were
clean all year round,
we wouldn't need to have
this cleaning spree, but...
Suzu Head
I agree.
There's no helping it.
People are just like that.
They want to defile anything pure.
Right?
Don't look at me.
Now everyone's looking at me.
Tsuda, how are the volunteers
for the cleaning squad going?
I've gotten the fliers together.
Well, these aren't bad...
I'd like something that
draws a bit more attention.
Oh, I know.
How about we make fliers
printed on pink paper?
I think a lot of people will
take that the wrong way,
so maybe not the best idea.
La, la, la.
About the surprise inspection we were
planning for all the club rooms tomorrow...
It's possible that
information was leaked.
What was that?
Rustle...
Rustle, rustle.
So we have a leak, then...
I don't like that sound of that.
You should only have a
leak while taking a leak!
Clench
Or if you want to let
someone know you're horny!
Pretend this didn't happen.
So...
How did this happen?
In all likelihood,
someone involved mentioned
it out in the open.
I wouldn't let that happen.
I don't let my work get
involved in my personal life.
That's unfortunate.
When you tell people you're
on the student council,
it gets you a lot of "moe" points.
I'll negate them all.
Hm...
Can I voice my thoughts?
Take the floor.
I am standing up...
R-Right.
In order to prevent
information from leaking,
how about we use a code
that only we understand?
That might be kind of nifty.
But how would we do that?
Let's see...
Since we're raiding
these clubrooms,
how about we call
ourselves the tops,
and whoever we're going
to raid, the bottoms?
I think almost all of us can
agree that isn't going to fly!
Bottoms... Bottoms...
Okay, please submit the
final report later.
Sure.
Would you like some help?
Thank you,
but I'm fine.
Okay, thanks.
R-Right.
Run
If you didn't know she
was scared of men,
you might get the wrong idea here.
This is the first time I've heard
about an inspection tomorrow.
We didn't tell you.
We thought you'd be the
first to tell people.
Come on! I'm the student
council adviser!
Serious
Sure, I might give away the goods
with my butt, but not my mouth!
I'm not sure that
counts for anything...
Shino-chan, how many...
18.
Not that. I wanted to know
how much sugar you wanted.
Oh, crap. I just gave
the standard response.
Hagimura, how old are you?
How old do I look?
That response...
Prez, this is bad.
It seems like the information
from that meeting we had leaked.
What?
Hahaha...
Tops and bottoms, tops and
bottoms.... La, la, la...
They
did
kind
of
feel
like
that
The Vice-President is a bottom, and President is a top!
Suzu Head
Sorry, I must have misheard...
Well, I guess it's fine.
The actual plan
wasn't made public.
Tsuda, you panic too much.
Sorry.
Besides, I think this
worked out pretty good.
No, stop!
Huh? It wasn't true?
No!
The newspaper club
didn't understand
what was wrong
Oh,
there's a turtle living
in the school's pond here.
You just found this out?
Can turtles learn tricks?
What would you want to teach it?
Sausage fetch!
For a loggerhead, too!
Hahahaha
She thought that was funny?
Student Council
Let's see...
Next I...
Wait, I messed up.
Receiving Message
Someone sent me a message?!
Did I just lose the
text I was writing?
What should I do, Tsuda?!
It's fine.
Let me see.
R-Right.
The message should be saved.
One new message
Uomii
How about taking
Tsuda's dick together?
No!
I was trying to write
something else!
I wanted to write "taking
Tsuda walking together!"
Run away!
Seitokai Yakuindomo
That happens in some countries
Oh, it's from Uomii.
Hm?
So I guess Eiryou has its
cultural fair next week.
Hi there.
So she's inviting us.
Uomii here.
It might be nice to see another
school's cultural fair.
Sounds like fun.
There's more.
There's a lot of events outdoors,
so you should probably
wear a jacket.
Also,
any lost children will be taken to
the first classroom on the right.
Why would she write that?
One week later
That really is quite the hill.
It's worse than the one
for Ousai. Longer, too.
I know, right?
So Eiryou's the school on the hill.
There's so many booths to look at.
Meat!
I know, right.
You look like you're
from out in the country
when you're fidgeting like that.
I forgot to wear a skirt,
so I'm getting nervous
when people look at me.
And no panties either, huh?
How about we go in here?
Lost children
This is for lost children.
What are you going to do in there?
Huh? I'll get lost with them.
That's not what they're here for.
Hello, Ousai students.
Uomi-san.
Hey!
Taka-kun.
I'm "onee-chan," right?
So it wasn't a joke...
Right, "onee-chan."
Bang
Good job!
Oh, I was just trying
to making a thumbs up.
I wasn't really trying to shove my
finger up your as*, or anything.
Seriously. I wasn't.
Did you seriously think
I would think that?
Oh, I was greeting
you as my relative.
I should do this again.
Thank you for coming again
when you're so busy.
Don't be so formal.
We're friends, aren't we?
Amakusa...
You're right.
Our hym*ns have the same shape.
Aren't you guys supposed to be
student council presidents?!
Chemistry
Would you like take part in a fun
experiment by the chemistry club?
Arts
and
Crafts
We're making hand puppets!
The idea behind this fair
is to have fun doing things.
You've sure thought about this.
Um, you don't really have
to look into my eyes.
Nurse's
office
Yay, yay.
Yay
I don't think there's
anything you want in there.
Cooking
We're doing a cooking class.
That sounds fun.
Want to give it a try?
Cooking class
All right. Let's do this.
Uh...
Huh?
What's wrong?
There's no board...
You think so?
I've been growing lately. I'm happy.
What would you...
You wanna keep going, right?
They had a lot of passion.
I'm all excited now.
Me, too.
That's a chupacabra.
What?!
I'm laughing so much
my stomach hurts.
I thought my period came.
I'm not sure that's a good thing.
Eiryou High School
Thank you for coming.
No, we had a great time.
Taka-kun, Kotomi-chan,
see you again.
Right!
I don't think I'm going
to get used to that.
Um..
Do you go to Tsuda's house a lot?
Hug.
Hug
Huh?
Why all of a sudden...
That's a secwet.
The "secwet" I want to know
is why you
do this to me every single time.
You're sure aggressive.
She's holding me...
I wasn't always like this.
I wasn't outgoing when I was a kid.
I thought that was just who I was,
and continued down that bad path.
But then I became a
high school student,
and thought I needed to change.
That's when I decided to act like this.
I see.
That's a nice story.
But I don't think it'd be wrong
to become a "bad girl".
She wasn't talking about that.
I need more motivation
to get out of bed.
Maybe I'll change
under the covers.
Shift
I wouldn't want someone
to see me doing this.
I mean, it's not like someone would
reel back if they saw me naked!
Throw
Oh.
That's a lot of snow.
That's going to make
this morning hard.
Hm?
Prez, good morning.
So you're awake, Tsuda.
We should go to school
early because of the snow.
Yes, I know.
We need to have a snowball fight!
Before it melts!
Okay, I guess I didn't know.
Seitokai Yakuindomo
Play with the snow, Santa's Heirs!
Okay, we need to shovel the snow
away before the ending ceremony.
This is going to be hard.
Tsuda, what job do we do?
We're the student council.
That's right.
Our job is to pave the way.
Blush.
You didn't have to say it if you
were just going to get embarrassed.
I'm red because it's cold.
All right.
You guys are here.
Let's get this done.
Why are you acting like a teacher?
I am a teacher.
It's cold out.
It's cold.
I want to drink something warm.
I've gotta pee.
Looks like we both have
something to gain here.
No, I don't think so.
It's slippery, so be careful.
It feels so cold in my butt.
I must have misheard her.
I remember when I was playing in the
snow and made a snowman.
I guess I had snowball fights.
Riding sleds, for me.
I made shaved ice.
I did that.
I peed on it and pretended
it was lemon flavored.
I didn't do that.
Oh, yeah.
Winter break starts tomorrow.
I can finally head back
to my parents' place.
It's scary living alone,
so that'll be nice.
I guess you have another side,
Yokoshima-sensei.
That was surprising.
I do.
I especially get scared at night.
Restless, not knowing if I'll be alone
for another year...
I don't know what to say.
I guess this'll do.
It turned out well.
So this year's about
to come to an end.
A year passes by pretty fast.
I think we say this every year.
We could probably shorten it down.
Done already?
So soon...
Why are you saying that
while looking at me?
It's going to be pretty
cold going home.
I'd like to eat some stew.
Suzu Head
Takatoshi Head
That'd be nice.
Some oden, or something.
Tofu stew...
Takatoshi Head
Aria Head
Maybe some sukiyaki.
All right.
Let's all have surprise stew party.
Huh? That's what you want to do?
The broth's a bit strong.
Oh, well.
I wanted to make this dangerous.
Don't put that in!
I know we're doing a
surprise stew party,
but how about we only put things
in that will actually taste decent.
Yeah.
All right, let's put our stuff in.
Click
It's dark!
Can't see anything...
Swoosh
Have to make sure you don't put
something in the wrong spot.
I put something in the wrong spot
once, in a situation like this.
How about you never
mention this again?
Let's eat!
Boil
I guess this is oyster?
This chicken is good...
I just put in our leftovers,
so I feel kind of bad.
What's that?
abalone
That's from the Shichijous.
Eat
I thought Kotomi was quiet...
I guess crab really
does make people quiet.
I'm trying to be one of those
characters who never talks.
If you're telling us you're
trying, you're not succeeding.
This wiener is really big.
Nibble
Dejima-san, you're drooling.
Oh.
That was a clever way of saying
you noticed that I got wet.
I'm going to go change my underwear.
You're terrible!
That was good.
It's warm, so I'm going
to take this off.
I took something off, too.
You're wearing a
one-piece today, right?
Phew
I'm full.
You're going to get fat if you
go to sleep right after eating.
No, I won't.
If you go to sleep
right after eating,
your stomach acid will
enter your esophagus,
inflaming it, which is
known to cause cancer.
All right.
Let's get started.
Get what started?
I'm going to give everyone presents.
It's going to be a surprise.
I wanted to tell you,
since you live here.
I see.
Well, good luck, then.
I guess I'm own my own with this...
This is kind of hot...
Boobs really help.
The grass is always greener
on the other side.
I don't see any "grass" down here.
She's going to wake up.
I checked to see if she
had any stockings up.
I mean, she probably
believes in Santa.
Probably believes in Santa
Hm? Why are you dressed like that?
I'm Santa's daughter.
You've got the wrong person.
Santa's a foreigner.
I'm the daughter of his mistress.
Is this some sort of soap opera?!
So I guess you can't get to
sleep with a different pillow.
Yeah.
Dog body pillow
Also, I use a body pillow, so...
I see.
I want to help, since I'm Santa.
Hm...
Oh.
Wouldn't hugging Hagimura feel good?
Suzu-chan.
Let me sleep with you!
Don't get the wrong idea, Hagimura.
No, she wants to
share your bed!
Igarashi Kaede here.
Seitokai Yakuindomo
Next Episode Preview
Ever since we've become co-ed,
people have been
behaving so indecently.
Just gives me a headache.
Really?
N-Next time, we'll be using
Volume 5 #119 from the manga.
It's happy New Year
What it takes to stand
above someone
Vir*in
I can't believe
you're washing that
Hey, where are you going?!
Watch out! Watch out!
I always cut my
fingernails really short!