This is the place, right?
Yep, I looked it up on the internet.
So Mashima's also going to play karuta?
I actually have a life so I can't
spend all my time playing karuta,
but I'll be better than you in no time!
Taichi's skipping soccer
practice today!
Shut up, Chihaya!
Recycle
for a
better
Japan
Fuchu City Katamachi Cultural Center
Let's go.
as short-lived as the reeds of Naniwa Bay
Shiranami Karuta Society Practice
Let's go inside!
Wait!  Not right now!
Hello!
Sorry!
You're not supposed to move
when a card is being read.
Oh...
I'll start the tape again.
as my sleeves are wet with dew
For you, I would have given
I thought karuta was a card
game people played for fun.
But it's not...
Dagnabbit!
I recall how my own
efforts were in vain
Karuta is a sport!
Chihaya Furu
Verse 3
From
the
Crystal
White
Snow
Thank you very much!
Miyazaki-kun, why would
you place the card
I passed to you in this position?
That's foolish.
Doctor!  Dr. Harada!
And then...
Give me a moment!  We're reviewing his play!
Sorry, Dr. Harada is in charge here,
and he's really serious about karuta.
Doctor?
The person who was yelling really loudly?
You kids play karuta?
Uh?
Ye—
Yes!
You're welcome here!
I don't care what anyone else says!
Please, Doctor...
We hold two tournaments every year
and only manage to attract
one or two new players,
yet here we have three at once!
Hey, Hiro-kun! Kids!
We have new friends!
Retro-kun?
It's Hiro!
Kinashi Hiro!
Anyway, what class are you?
Oh, I've only learned
about half of the poems
that start with "the" and "may."
Chihaya, that's not it.
Huh?
You came here before you
even learned the poems?
This place is for competitive practice.
Why don't you play me before
you talk smack, Retro-kun!
Chihaya?!
It's Hiro!
Then let's have a three-on-three Genpei match!
Wataya! We're just gonna lose!
What are you talking about, Taichi?!
We won't lose!
Huh?!
Of course!  We're playing to win!
What?!
A Genpei match is a team match.
Each team gets 50 cards.
Oh...
Wait, you don't even know the rules?!
Zip it, Retro-kun!
Place this in front of you, Mashima.
So I'm responsible for these?
These are yours, Chihaya.
Line them up in three rows.
I haven't learned some
of these cards...
It's okay.
Once the cards have been placed,
you have 15 minutes
of memorization time.
Memorization time?
You're given time to memorize
the positions of the cards.
If you can't memorize the positions,
you don't stand a chance.
Naturally, you'll need to memorize both
our cards and the other team's cards.
Memorize?!
Memorize the positions
for all 100 cards?!
Um, this is...
Chihaya, come here for a second.
What?!  I haven't memorized
any of them yet!
We're allowed to go wherever we
want during these 15 minutes.
Let's hold a meeting outside.
First, Chihaya has all of
the "first syllable" cards.
You go for these cards as soon as
you hear one of the first syllables,
such as "rain" or "waves."
There are seven of these.
The rest are "second-syllable"
cards that begin with "the."
Uh-huh!
Mashima has the "long shot" cards
that need more words to be identified.
Hmm?
Such as "the hazy early
morning" and "for you, I."
There are cards that begin with
the same string of words.
They're called "long shot" cards because
you have to gamble on
which card to take.
It'll be your call to make.
Go for the cards as soon
as they're called.
I gave you most of the cards
that need more words.
Go for them as soon as they're called?
What if I take the wrong card?
You'll be fine!
Why's he taking the lead?
Rain, waves, long, gust,
all, look, swift...
Why do we even need a strategy?
You should have just played
Retro-kun by yourself, Wataya.
Wouldn't it be easier without
us to hold you back?
I wanted to play as a team.
We can be a team!
Look for...
That was a "one-word" card!
Aren't those supposed to be mine?!
But you were too slow.
For you, I head out to the
fields to pick spring greens
One of mine!
now together, I guard it dear
Darn, I guessed wrong.
It's okay.
while snow falls upon my sleeves
I took the right card.
But we touched the wrong card,
so they get to pass one of theirs to us.
It's a wash.
I'll help you on the "long shot" cards.
Even if you take the wrong card,
we still won't fall behind.
Th-This isn't called playing
as a team, you bastard!
He doesn't trust us to do anything!
Doctor?!
He's celebrating this
lucky pickup, right?
The boy with the glasses
is more than just good.
Rain takes longer to
dry in the autumn time
He took my card again!
I'm so mad!
I won't lose next time!
Why?
There's no reason to be upset
when he's so much better.
Chihaya...
There's no reason to try so hard.
Wataya said that he wanted
to play as a team,
but he wasn't expecting
anything from us.
He wasn't expecting anything.
The hazy early morning mist
over the Kawagiri River
Awesome!  I got the right card, Wataya!
but from the crystal
white snow of Yoshino
That's the other "the hazy
early morning" card.
Nice job, Taichi!
Huh?
Listen.
...of wind leaves fall leaves falling
hence the name fall leaves
I did it!
I finally got a card!
Sorry, Doctor!  Did that hurt?!
Was that supposed to be "gust of wind"?
No...
I couldn't hear the "gust."
Doctor!  This is the first
time I've ever taken
a card the way the real players do!
My first card!
A room full of experienced adults,
and she was the only one who moved.
My first card.
hence the name fall leaves
Karuta feels so good!
That's what happened last time.
I didn't drop my guard or anything.
I lose to Chihaya when it
comes to "first syllable" cards?
Th-These kids are fun!
hence the name fall leaves
Thank you very much!
I only took one card!
Stop it, guys.
Only five cards...
Retro-kun... Oh, sorry.
Hiro-kun...
Tell me your names.
Are you going to join
the Karuta Society?
I will!
I'm Wataya Arata!
A sixth-grader!
Wataya Arata?!
He's won the national championship
for his grade the past five years!
Huh?
That's not all.
The name Wataya is...
Is he the grandson of the
Eternal Master from Fukui,
Wataya Hajime, who won seven
straight years in the 80s?!
And what about you kids?
Uh... I'm, well...
Doctor, Doctor!
Hmm?
I can't memorize the cards!
I get more confused when
there are more cards!
I can never memorize 100 of them!
Really now?
But I'm sure there are a few
you have perfectly memorized.
There's the "gust of wind"
card I took today.
And then there's the
"chihaya furu" card!
Wataya-kun said that the card
has the same name as me!
Uh-huh.
You will learn to take
the cards you are
most attached to faster
than anyone else can.
There are a total of 100
poems in Hundred Poets.
Think of it as making 100 new friends.
What about you, Eyebrows?
Uh, er... I have cram school...
But I'll come!
I'll come when I can!
There's a tournament in March.
You should practice for it.
Tournament?
It's for teams of three.
It'll be the last tournament you
can participate in as 6th graders.
I wanna participate!
Right, Taichi?
The three of us will
win together, right?
Yep!
But in this tournament...
We'll be playing individually
instead of together.
Two of us have to win.
I know I'll win,
but can either of you win a match?
We'll need to train!
Train?
Train!
I'm home!
You're late!
I have an audition for
a commercial tomorrow,
so they bought me a bunch of clothes.
Isn't this nice?
Nice!
I also like this outfit.
Me too!
Chihaya is her sister's number one fan.
Is your dream still to see your
sister become the best in Japan?
Chihaya?
Sorry, Sis.
There's something else I want to do!
Huh?
As I wait for someone,
my body burns like the seaweed...
What is she thinking?
Waiting for burnt seaweed...
I don't see a problem.
At least she's found something
she's interested in.
She has nothing to gain from it.
What?
Chihaya should just keep gushing
about how great I am.
A mountain stream...
Your motion needs to
be sharp and straight.
Waiting for burnt seaweed...
Welcome home, Dad.
The world offers no change, I pray
Um...
when the fisherman who casts
his nets can seem dear
You're too slow, Chihaya!
The sight of the lonely moon...
reminds me of the lonely
dawns after we parted
For you, I would...
Chihaya!
Hey, Wataya-kun...
Arata.
I'm Arata.
Then I'm also calling you Arata.
Okay?
Taichi!
Arata!
What's with you, Chihaya?
Are you okay?
Arata!
Taichi!
Let's play karuta together forever!
So the flower petals...
So the flower petals are scattered...
Scattered flower petals wilt!
yet it is I who withers and wilts
Really?!
Way to go!
That's amazing, Mashima-kun!
Kaimeisei is really good!
What's going on?
Mashima-kun was accepted into
Kaimeisei Middle School!
That's amazing!
But his first choice is Shusai
University Middle School, right?
Since he can ride his bike there.
Nobody's stupid enough to not go
to Kaimeisei after being accepted!
Even if it's an
hour-and-a-half commute!
Taichi, you're not going
to that school, right?
You won't be able to play karuta
with us at the Doctor's place.
Wh-What are you talking about?
That's not going to stop me
from going to Kaimeisei.
Tai—
A-Arata...
Taichi said that he doesn't care
if we can't play karuta
together anymore.
He's such a joker.
My grandpa's sick back in Fukui.
Once I graduate,
I'm going back to Fukui.
We can't play karuta together forever.
Is your grandpa okay?
He had something called
a cerebral hemorrhage.
He's still in the hospital.
That sounds rough.
Chihaya?
I'm not going.
Huh?
I'm not...
I'm not going to the tournament!
Chihaya!
Huh?
Where's Chihaya-chan today?
It's my fault.
No, it's my fault.
I said that it's my fault!
It's because I'm going back to Fukui!
Freak!  Don't get too full of yourself!
I won't go to the karuta tournament!
I've known her longer!
It's my fault!
It's no fun to play karuta by myself!
Harada Internal Medicine/Pediatrics
Chihaya-chan...
What's wrong?
Ogura Hundred Poets
Poetry Karuta
I remembered that I
needed to return this.
Well, I'm impressed by Eyebrows.
He was accepted to Kaimeisei.
Most kids wouldn't be
able to manage that feat
while spending time at a
karuta society every week.
Oh, a shooting star!
Huh?!  Where?!  Where?!
You didn't see it?
That won't do.
Now I'm mad!
And Glasses's grandfather is an
Eternal Master who's famous
in the karuta world.
A Master?!
When I saw Glasses play,
I immediately knew that his
grandfather had taught him the game.
He must be worried sick to know that
his grandfather is in the hospital.
Oh, another shooting star!
What?!
Just kidding.
That's mean, Doctor!
Meanie!  Meanie!
I'll be sad if you also quit.
Fuchu City Katamachi Cultural Center
Grade School
Karuta Tournament
This is just a temporary truce.
I put up the money,
and you wrote the message.
I know.
Chihaya isn't here.
Are you okay?
Well, this little tournament
should be a breeze for you.
No...
The round boy we're
facing in the first round
was runner-up in the
national tournament.
I'm not sure if I can handle him right now.
Reception
We will start the first round now!
Chihaya?
Oh, there you are.
Here you are.
What's this?
Mashima-kun was here this morning
with a boy wearing glasses.
Team Chihaya Furu
That's right.  Didn't you say
you were going out today?
Wait!
Chihaya?
Chihaya-chan isn't here yet?
They're playing individual matches,
so they'll be fine if both of them win.
I was planning on defeating
Wataya-kun today.
So, did your teammate get scared
of losing and run away?
Shut your mouth, fatty!
Chihaya's running late!
But she isn't here.
I said that she's coming!
I'll go buy some pork buns.
You can buy your pork
buns after I beat you!
Chihaya!
Chihaya-chan!
You're late, Chihaya!
That's because I was stuck at a
railway crossing for twenty minutes!
I'm still mad at you guys!
You're both leaving me behind!
But I'm not the only one
who feels lonely, right?
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
Note that though we may be...
May the time we spend
apart from one another be
Impassionate gods
the red that is the Tatsuta River
Yes!
There aren't as many cards left.
There are only 100 cards.
I don't want this to end.
I don't want this to end!
Hey, are you okay?
Here, wear this.
Taichi...
I wanted to win Chihaya that trophy.
Sorry!  If only I had won my match!
Taichi!
Sorry!
Chihaya, say something to him.
I wanted...
I wanted to play more karuta together!
Why are you crying?
It was really fun.
Let's take a picture, Chi-chan!
East Osato Elementary School Graduation
Here goes!
Yay!
You get to wear blazer
jackets at Kaimeisei?
Chi-chan, take one with us!
Let's take one with everyone!
Arata, I'm going to say
goodbye to the landlord.
Can you go home and start packing?
We're leaving tomorrow, so you
need to put everything away.
Team Chihaya Furu
Arata!
Why did you go home by yourself?!
Play karuta with me, Arata!
In a serious match!
Oh, are you busy packing?
I wouldn't show mercy if I
was playing a 5-year-old.
Naniwa Bay...
Taichi, you suck!
Shut up!
You're supposed to follow
a 4-3-1-5 pattern.
I know that!
I'm supposed to pause
in certain places.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
After many, many years...
My fear is not of...
When the wind sends...
Like I said,
I will win.
Let's play!
I have a tape for that!
My dream is to become
a karuta master.
I won't lose!
After all,
thanks to you, I love karuta now!
Impassionate gods...
The same time!
When both players take the
card at the same time,
it goes to the side the card is on!
That's what the doctor said!
I win!
Let it go!
This is my Chihaya!
Th-Thank you...
Thank you for playing karuta with me!
Chihaya, Taichi...
I doubt we'll ever
see each other again.
Why?
As long as we have karuta,
we'll see each other again, right?
As long as we keep playing,
we'll see each other again!
I just know it!