None are left who know me
Thank you very much.
Impassionate gods...
Chihaya Furu
Verse 23
The
Night
Is
Nearly
Past
Yamamoto Yumi: won by four cards.
Yumin!
You're well on your way to
reclaiming the title of Queen!
Great Expectations
Get plenty of rest!
You'll have to play four more matches
before you reach the final!
So much pressure...
But if there weren't any expectations,
I would have run away already.
Chihaya!
I won't run away.
What are you doing?  Get out of there!
Please come out, Chihaya-chan!
Ayase, I have chocolate for you!
Sorry about cheering for
Yumin the whole time!
Cheer up.
I've heard that beautiful
girls look better bald.
I'll leave my e-mail address,
so send me an "after" picture.
Sudo-san...
We'll shave our heads, so spare Chihaya!
What?
I'm willing to cut my hair really short!
You stay out of it, Kana-chan!
What's that?
Whoever loses first has
to shave their head?
Chihaya-chan's so stupid.
We know!  Our captain is stupid!
Then Sudo-kun, if I beat you,
the bet is off.
I don't believe that you're my
opponent in the third round.
Are you planning on losing?
If not, we'll run into
each other at some point.
You better not lose before we play.
Worry more about yourself.
H-He's so cool!
What?!
No, I'll shave my head!
Me, too!
I said it first!
I probably look fine with a
shaved head, so I'll do it!
I'll look better than you will!
I-Is she asleep?
Isn't that what normally happens?
It's been an hour.
It's possible.
You can go back downstairs, Nishida.
You need to cheer for Yamamoto-san.
I'll stay here, so Oe-san
and Komano can also go.
We'll stay here with you-
She isn't asleep.
She can't sleep now.
Chihaya, Arata says he's won his
third round match.
I'm mail buddies with Arata now.
I was going to give you his address
once the qualifiers were over.
I'm not lying.
Got through the third round.
How's Chihaya doing?
He's really amazing.
Dr. Harada and Sudo-san both won,
and they're playing each
other in the fourth round!
We have to go cheer for him!
Chihaya, come out.
Let's go cheer him on.
Chihaya.
I know how much it hurts to
lose after trying your best.
You don't want to face anyone.
I know how it feels,
but my words won't be able to reach her.
Only Arata can help her.
What are you doing?!
You have to go watch
Dr. Harada and Sudo-san play!
Next year, they'll be
your rivals in Class A!
You have to go watch them
play, not cheer them on!
Chihaya-chan.
The prez stayed behind because
he was worried about you.
Oh, that's right.
Sorry.
Let's go, Taichi.
Yeah, I'm hopeless...
Hopelessly in love.
Sudo Akita
Harada Hidehiro
Yes!
He's so loud.
His knees are starting to give.
I should go easy on him
since he's getting old.
Except, I'm not in a position to do that.
I didn't want her to contest every card,
so I started moving
faster than I needed to.
That was a tactic I never knew about.
Aren't you cold?
Put this on.
Huh?  It's okay.
You look like you're cold, so put it on.
Everyone was cheering
watching outside, right?
Weren't you cold?
It was pretty warm during the day.
They were standing outside
the entire time.
Thank you.
Sorry.
I lost because I was
too focused on myself.
He did it!
Dr. Harada!
I lost by three cards.
He's not human...
He's an intelligent bear.
Roar
Dr. Harada!
Thank you for saving Ayase's hair!
Hmm?  What are you talking about?
Huh?
Oh!
He only cared about his own victory.
He never changes.
Chihaya-chan, you didn't thank
your opponent after the match.
That was wrong of you.
No matter how upset you are,
you must thank your opponent.
Yes, sir!
The semi-finals will
begin in ten minutes.
Will the players will please step inside.
Oh, it's time.
Only two more wins...
Two more wins...
Dr. Harada lost a close
match in the semi-finals.
The Eastern finalists this year
are Tsuboguchi Hiroshi
from the Shiranami society
for the Master match,
and Yamamoto Yumi from the Suihoku
society for the Queen match.
In one month,
they'll be playing a
best-of-three match
against the Western finalists
for the right to challenge
the Master and Queen in January.
Kanai-san...
See you next year, rival.
The long day is finally over,
and the rest of us will spend
the next year as losers.
What?
I see you every morning here,
and you're seriously cute.
Interested in going out with me?
You should turn him down!
What?  Just like that?
Of course.
It's a boy from a different school
who knows nothing about you.
But, but!
It's the first time anyone's
ever asked me out!
If I let this chance slip away,
I might not get another one!
The first time?
That's beauty in vain.
But after spending all
this time with her,
she doesn't even seem
that beautiful anymore.
I'm pretty sure that the reason nobody
from our school approaches her
is because she's always with Mashima-kun.
Why?
Go ahead and give it a shot.
Taichi?
You need to experience it for yourself.
It won't work.
Huh?
You can't go out with a guy who
hasn't seen you play karuta.
Oh...
But I'm already getting a bunch
of e-mails and phone calls...
You gave him your number?!
I blocked his number.
Huh?
Starting tomorrow,
wake up early and ride
the same train as me.
In the Tentoku Imperial Court Poetry Contest
Mibu no Tadami
As my love first came to realization,
word had already spread
Taira no Kanemori
Since I could not hide my love,
people would always ask if
I was pining for someone
that was held by Emperor Murakami in 960,
there were two poems that
were especially beautiful.
As I watch the prez,
those poems come to mind.
Poems about a love that
cannot be concealed.
The nincompoops in our
club have no clue!
nin
I've
never
blocked
anyone
before
com
Me
either
poop
Goodbye,
Watanabe-kun...
But I understand, prez!
Wataya Arata - Cell
Wataya Arata - Fukui Home
I haven't been able to bring
myself to send him an e-mail.
Wataya Arata - Cell
Wataya Arata - Fukui Home
Taichi even gave me his address...
Arata lost in the fourth
round of the Western qualifier.
How does he feel right now?
How upset is he?
There are so many things I
want to talk to him about.
I need more...
More practice, more effort, more time!
I was away for too long.
I shouldn't have stopped playing
karuta for a single day!
Thank you very much.
Takemura-san, the Western finalist,
wasn't especially good,
but he had the momentum of ranking
in four tournaments this year,
plus the stamina to last six matches.
The qualifiers are as
serious as it gets.
I'll have to treat every practice
match like a real one.
Let's begin the third match.
Oh, Daisuke-kun.
You're playing Arata-kun next.
What?  I don't wanna
play him.  He's scary.
Scary!
Coach, there isn't anyone
left for Wataya-kun to play.
And Murao-kun didn't show up again.
What is it?
You here to tell me to come practice?
Yes.
That's not like you.
You never used to stick your
nose where it didn't belong.
After all, you're the one who quit
karuta for a year and a half.
Yet, now you're telling
me I need to practice?
I know you want to get better,
but I can't help you practice.
Say "hi" to everyone at the
Nagumo society for me.
I...
I regret it.
I regret running away from karuta.
You can't...
You can't spend too much time
away from karuta, Murao-san!
You'll lose your chance
to become Master!
S-Scary...
Shiver
You really scare me.
The point of karuta is to become Master?
I can no longer play
karuta at that level.
Let me know if you ever
want to play for fun.
Good night.
It's not like me
to stick my nose in...
I'll be back.
Kana-chan, you look happy.
That's because there's finally
a match in formal dress!
The Tokyo Otsuka Karuta Memorial Hall.
Where the Master and Queen
challenger matches are held
between the East and West finalists.
The matches are best-of-three
and the players wear hakama.
The first player to achieve two wins
earns the right to challenge
the Master or Queen at Omi Jingu in January.
Master/Queen Challenger Final
Hosted by the National Karuta Association
I can't help but think...
If I hadn't lost my cool,
I would be sitting there right now.
I won the East qualifier
because Dr. Harada tired out
Kotegawa-kun in the semi-final for me.
Grunt
Watch me play, Doctor.
Best of luck
Don't be too arrogant.
Could I have been sitting there
if I tried a little harder?
Master/Queen Challenger Final
The players there represent
East and West Japan.
We will now begin!
They're representing us!
Here comes spring...
I'm scared!
Thank you very much.
Arata-niichan.
I'll become stronger!
I'll do my best!
I'll keep playing until I'm sick of it!
Okay?
We have our challengers!
The challenger for Master
is Takemura-kun.
The challenger for Queen
is Yamamoto Yumi-san.
That was tough!
Seriously, three games
against the same opponent?
Takemura-san is
like an armored tank!
It's so hot.
Can I take this thing off yet?
It's completely soaked with sweat.
The Shiranami society dream
is to produce a Master one day!
It hurts!
I want to be able to look back one day
and say it was all worth it.
I'm worried about you, Chi-chan.
Huh?
I'll be fine, Michiru-chan!
I placed 290th on the second term exam!
I'm not talking about school.
Huh?
Chi-chan, you're spending
all of your time on karuta.
Aren't there other
things you need to do?
Like making friends?
Anyway, take this.
Class 1-2 End of Second Term  PARTY
Time: 12/24  6:00 PM
At the "Italian Kitchen" next to Shinjuku Station
Entry Fee: 2,500 yen
Drink bar
Hosts:  Horikawa and Matsuda
A party on Christmas Eve?
You don't have any plans, right?
I do.  I'll be practicing karuta.
Okay, Ayase-san's coming!
So is Komano-kun!
Oh, our class is also having a party.
Class 6 will be having a hot
pot party on Christmas.
Our class is going bowling.
Then we'll take December 24th off.
Ooh
Ayase-san, that outfit's so cute!
What do you want to drink?
Your sister's a model, right?
I'm so glad I came!
Can I take a picture?
She's so cute!
Her legs are so long!
Her face is tiny!
Come on in!
So, the karuta club is working hard.
Oh, we're in the mountain climbing club.
We're a boring club with
only a few members,
but the karuta club inspires
us to do the best we can!
We compete to see who can
put up tents faster!
Oh, that sounds fun.
When we practice in the courtyard,
people give us funny looks.
Speaking of which,
Matsuda is the only male member
in the tea ceremony club.
What's wrong with that?
I get free snacks.
There are important rules to
follow for a seafood hot pot.
Turkey
I heard that this was a class party,
so why am I the only guy here?!
Ayase!
I got to talk to a bunch of girls!
Though, they were just asking
me about Mashima.
Oh, that's great!
You look like you're having fun.
Yep, there were a bunch of classmates
I never really talked with before.
Oh, but...
I would be having more fun if the
other club members were here.
I read in a book once...
When you find yourself wishing that
a certain person was also here,
that person is like family to you.
Regardless of how long
or well you know them.
If you wish that someone
was also here...
Who's joining in the karaoke?!
It's Christmas Eve, so the
bars will all be packed!
Hello?  This is Wataya.
Who is it?
Chihaya?
Sorry, I'm at the Nagumo society
Christmas party right now.
Coach Kuriyama is belly dancing!
It's Chihaya, right?
Chihaya?
The "misty bridge of magpie feathers"
spanned the river of stars which
separated Orihime and Hikoboshi,
so the bridge brought them together.
Arata.
Chi-chan, hurry up!
Cell phones are incredible
like the misty bridge!
Huh?
I'm glad I got to hear your voice!
Bye!
Bridge?
When the misty bridge of magpie
feathers comes into sight,
the night is nearly past