Welcome back, Lady Satsuki.
You did well in the Tri-City
Schools Raid Trip.
Thank you.
How did it go with
the Director?
She was pleased
at our results.
She has also decided to pay
a visit to Honnouji Academy.
Then—
Yes. It is time at last.
I'll be counting on you four.
Students of Honnouji Academy!
You did well in the Tri-City
Schools Raid Trip!
We eradicated the dens of the Kansai
forces and anti-clothing guerillas
and completed our mission.
For that reason, we will welcome Honnouji
Academy Director Ragyo Kiryuin,
and in the Ragyo Stadium
that bears her name,
we will hold a grand ceremony!
Welcome the Director by putting
forth all the energies that
you have stored up within you!
This is the Honnouji Academy Cultural
& Sports Grand Festival!
CULTURAL & SPORTS GRAND FESTIVAL
EPISODE 17
TELL ME WHY
That's funny.
I was just thinking that
I'd have to settle things with you.
Right now, you don't have
your Kamui or your scissor.
Do you honestly think a mere half-naked
high-schooler can beat me?
You think your threats
are gonna faze me?
I'll be happy to go
full-on naked for you, then.
No, you can't!
A girl only reveals herself
in her full glory
to the person the loves
most in the whole world!
Can you honestly say that you love
Mr. Mohawk that deeply, Ryuko?
Uh, that's not the point.
After all, the reason you wear Senketsu
is because you love him best, right?
If you didn't, you'd never be able to wear
a piece of living clothing cause it'd be icky!
That's what it means for a maiden to
entrust her bare skin to someone!
Ryuko, I am flattered that
you are angry on my behalf.
But if I may be so bold,
put me on.
Senketsu...
If you don't,
you'll catch cold.
That's what you're
worried about?
I can't believe you two...
Playing at being friends
with clothing again, huh?
I don't feel like
shooting them anymore.
This is Osaka?
This is horrible...
I suppose it is.
This is all the result
of the power of Life Fibers.
As well as yours and mine.
Yeah.
Mikisugi was right to keep us
in the dark up until now.
Even looking at this, it
beggars belief to be told
that Life Fibers are lifeforms from outer space.
This, coming from you?
I'm probably scared.
It's like, something
that was just a brawl
turned into some grand battle full
of crazy crap I don't understand
like the fate of humanity and
the extinction of the species or whatever.
"I don't give a crap about that!"
That's what I really wanted to say.
But I put the blame on you
for me getting mad.
No, you really did get angry
on my behalf, Ryuko.
That's the kind
of person you are.
What's his deal?
Tsumugu Kinagase's older sister
died in a Life Fiber experiment.
After Dr. Matoi founded
Nudist Beach,
his top assistant was
Tsumugu's sister, Kinue Kinagase.
Only Life Fibers
can fight Life Fibers.
To create Life Fibers that
would obey a human's will.
That's what Dr. Matoi and Kinue's
research was directed towards.
And during one experiment...
So she's the "foolish woman"
he mentioned, huh?
Earlier, he said that
I'd share her fate.
Oh, right.
"Please continue the experiments."
Those were Kinue's dying words.
Dr. Matoi made further improvements
and completed Kamui Senketsu.
Senketsu's Life Fibers have been
spliced with your central
nervous system's DNA.
What?!
That's why he can only
communicate with and be worn by you.
He's a combat uniform that
Dr. Matoi made especially for you.
Why would Dad
do something like that?
He said he did it
to protect you.
What the hell, man?
Your tea.
Thank you.
I've drunk a lot of your tea,
haven't I, Soroi?
Yes, I have been making it for you
since you were five.
Ah, yes.
Ever since that day.
The day father showed me
Junketsu for the first time.
That day, Father said to me...
"This will be your wedding dress."
Yes, I have heard.
I suppose it was on that day
that all this really began.
It seems like only yesterday.
Even this tea that I once
found so bitter is now
the most delicious thing in the world to me.
What is it?
You... found it bitter?
I never mentioned that?
From the very first cup, you smiled,
saying that it was delicious.
To think you were merely humoring me
and enduring the bitterness.
I beg your forgiveness.
It's fine already...
I suppose I was a
kindhearted girl back then.
Form up! At attention!
Listen closely!
Tomorrow, the Cultural
& Sports Grand Festival
will be held at Honnouji Academy!
All No-Star students and
their parents are to welcome
Director Kiryuin from the spectator seats!
Ceremonial dress uniforms
will be distributed to all of you!
Gather at the stadium entrance
in these uniforms by 8:30 AM!
Tardiness will not be tolerated!
Unkempt dress will not be tolerated!
Assume that even the slightest breach of
etiquette will carry the death penalty!
Dismissed!
Wait just one minute!
And who are you?!
Barazo Mankanshoku, father of Second
Year Class K's Mako Mankanshoku!
His wife, Sukuyo!
Their firstborn son, Mataro!
What a well-mannered family.
Even the dog introduces itself.
What do you want?
Where is Mako?
I heard that Mako was conscripted
into the Schools Raid Trip.
The other students have returned,
but not Mako and Ryuko.
Would you care to
explain that?
Matoi and Mankanshoku?
They are rebels.
As the family of rebels, your home
is to confiscated
and you are to be banished
from Honnou Town!
However, tomorrow is the
Cultural & Sports Grand Festival.
CULTURAL & SPORTS GRAND FESTIVAL
I will grant you
a special pardon!
CULTURAL & SPORTS GRAND FESTIVAL
SPECIAL PARDON
You will be allowed
to participate!
If you wish to atone for your daughter's
crimes, participate in the ceremony
CULTURAL & SPORTS GRAND FESTIVAL
SPECIAL PARDON
PARTICIPATE IN THE CEREMONY
and wholeheartedly toast the honor and
glory of Lady Satsuki and Lady Ragyo!
CULTURAL & SPORTS GRAND FESTIVAL
SPECIAL PARDON
PARTICIPATE IN THE CEREMONY
WHOLEHEARTEDLY TOAST
Is that clear?!
I'd like to ask you two things.
What?
Are the girls alive?
Yes.
Question two!
Will this ceremony be catered?
O-Of course.
Very well! On the honor of
the Mankanshoku family,
in order to remove our
daughter's stigma,
we shall clean our plates of this food,
leaving not one crumb uneaten!
Mark my words!
CULTURAL & SPORTS GRAND FESTIVAL
What the hell is this?
A video feed from hidden cameras I had
set up inside Honnouji Academy.
If Ragyo Kiryuin is coming, too,
this must be something big.
Ragyo Kiryuin?
The leading figure of the
Kiryuin Conglomerate,
and she's currently using
her position as REVOCS CEO
to sell clothing laced with Life Fibers
all around the world.
Good grief, she's blinding!
She's gaudier than Satsuki!
Like daughter skank,
like mother skank.
She's even more charismatic than Satsuki.
She's a formidable opponent.
What's this?
They're bringing in
Life Fibers in bulk.
What are they up to?
Oh, no... She plans to conduct the final
experiment at Honnouji Academy!
MILITARY REPURPOSING
GOKU UNIFORMS
EXPERIMENTATION CITY
Honnouji Academy
is an experimentation city.
Goku Uniforms, created to study
human resistance to Life Fibers.
Repurposing them for military use and
conquering all of the country's academies.
NATIONAL CONQUEST
Then forcibly distributing Life Fiber-laced
uniforms to teenagers,
those who have the
highest resistance.
After all that is complete,
she offers up every
last person gathered at Honnouji Academy
as human sacrifices
to the Life Fibers.
Human sacrifices?!
Yes. It must be her final experiment
to fully awaken the Life Fibers.
Gather a mass of people wearing
Life Fiber-laced clothing in one spot
and then instantly convert
them into Life Fibers.
That is the real purpose of the
Cultural & Sports Grand Festival.
Wait, so you're saying
that Mako's dad and mom
are gonna be eaten by their clothes?!
Put in simple terms,
I suppose they will.
Eaten by their clothes...
Screw that! No way am I
gonna let that happen!
Ryuko?
Ragyo Kiryuin and Satsuki Kiryuin...
I'm gonna take you both out!
Leap straight into
the jaws of danger?
Yeah, I'm gonna jump down its throat
and rip out its guts with my teeth!
Ryuko!
Don't worry.
I won't lose control again.
I won't make you shed
any more bitter tears.
One way or another, I have to
settle this fight with Satsuki.
Are you with me, Senketsu?
Of course.
This will be interesting.
Oh brother, I guess you
leave me no choice.
Let's hurry, then.
We don't have much time.
The Hyper Inner manufacturing facility
in Mozambique was attacked.
Militant extremists?
Yes, ma'am. It would seem that even
antiestablishment organizations are awash
with rumors that wearing REVOCS special
innerwear boosts physical capabilities.
That's fine.
It's exactly as planned.
We don't just
make people buy them.
There are some who are best tricked
into taking them for themselves.
Regardless of how it came into
their possession, the end result
of them being worn by REVOCS clothing
will remain unchanged.
What a beautiful world.
Not yet, we're only
getting started.
Tomorrow, we step
onto a new stage.
The next step to the
awakening of COVERS.
Lady Satsuki is most impressive.
She masterfully conquered
the teen demographic,
which has the highest resistance
to Life Fibers.
It was ingenious, negating their
resistance to Life Fibers
by getting them hooked on
the power of Goku Uniforms.
But things are so dull
if they're too neat and tidy.
Grand Couturier...
Oh, right. It was Matoi's daughter
that you were more interested in.
Yes. To think that she gathered up
the pieces of her Kamui
and stitched them together
all by herself...
There aren't many girls
who can be quite that rude.
"Fair is foul, and foul is fair," eh?
How very like you, Nui.
Yep!
Still, that's mere empty rhetoric.
There is only one truth.
Only those things that earn Ragyo Kiryuin's
approval may be called beautiful.
The Cultural & Sports
Grand Festival is tomorrow.
I expect you to dress up
for the occasion.
Enough to satisfy
even my sense of style.
Honestly, like mother,
like daughter...
Tsumugu.
What's this?
A Tailor's Dagger
and Tailor's Glove.
They're capable of
cutting Life Fibers.
You're at a disadvantage in
close combat with just
those sewing machine guns.
Sever the Goku Uniform's Banshi
and my opponent goes stark naked, huh?
Good. Very good.
Our targets are only Ragyo and Satsuki.
Ignore everything else.
Well, it's not like there's anything else
we can do with just three of us.
Keep Mako safe.
Sure.
I've asked our remaining
members to look after her here.
Don't ditch me here, Ryuko!
Mako...
C'mon, let's go home!
Dummy, Honnouji Academy
isn't safe for you!
But it's my home!
I've got souvenirs
to give to Dad and Mom!
Dammit, Mako!
If you're going, so am I!
Oh right, you don't listen once you've
made up your mind, either.
Tomorrow is the long-awaited
Cultural & Sports Grand Festival!
I want you all to set to it with
determination in your hearts!
Yes, sir!
I can't hear you!
YES, SIR!
Straighten out those lights a little!
Good, I want them
to wreathe the stage.
Tomorrow will be Honnouji Academy's climax!
Let's make it more dramatic!
Okay, right there!
Good, good!
Work fast, people!
We're in the home stretch!
How are things coming
down there, Iori?
It's the day that Lady
Satsuki has dreamed of.
We'll be ready come hell or high water.
Understood.
I'll be done here soon, too.
It looks like the naked apes
have taken the bait.
It was worth leaving those hidden
cameras where they were.
This will fill in the final
piece of the puzzle.
Summon everyone to the
Student Council Chambers.
All preparations to welcome
my mother are now complete.
I appreciate all your hard work.
Ma'am!
And so, let us toast the success of the
Cultural & Sports Grand Festival!
Attention, all students and families
of Honnouji Academy!
We have succeeded in conquering
of all the nation's academies!
All of the fools who dared oppose our
Goku Uniforms have been eliminated!
Today is a celebration
of those accomplishments!
Eat and drink your fill!
Praise the Kiryuin name!
The Honnouji Academy Cultural & Sports
Grand Festival begins now!
It's begun, dear!
Who cares?! Just eat!
Yeah! We'll stuff ourselves
and then skip out afterwards!
Hold on, Mataro, Now that I have
a good look at you, you're naked!
I sold off that stupid
dress uniform ages ago!
Damn, I wish I'd
thought of that!
And now, what you have all
been waiting for.
Let us offer a welcome
with the utmost respect.
I present to you this academy's
founder, Director Ragyo Kiryuin!
As grand an entrance as one would
expect from our director.
A ruler must shine
like the sun at all times.
It has been far too long, Mrs. Kiryuin.
Ah, Nonon.
How is your father?
Fine, thank you.
Are you still engaging in hacking
and stock manipulation?
Oh, I no longer indulge
in such things...
Oh, you don't? A pity.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I put a question to you.
What is the world?
The world is clothing.
Life Fibers are the ruler
of this world.
I, Ragyo Kiryuin,
know and carry out their will!
Honnouji Academy was created
for just that purpose.
The weak will serve as the foundation
for what is to come.
You should consider that
an honor.
What the heck is the Director
talking about?
She means that the day has come for
the pigs in human clothing to
be devoured by their clothing.
Now, let the celebration begin!
Dad! Mom!
Guts, too?!
What's that screaming?!
Sounds like it's started.
Let's hurry.
I'll use the DTR to jump us
to the stage in one go.
Come on, Tsumugu!
Ryuko!
You mean Dotonbori Robo?
DTR!
It's Dotonbori Robo, right?
He hates that name.
You're worried about that
at a time like this?
What about me?!
I slipped off!
There's nowhere to grab on!
Go and hide!
I'll give you snacks!
DTR, going airborne!
Have fun storming the stadium!
Such wonderful silence...
The cacophony spewed forth
by the foolish creature
known as humanity fades away,
and nothing but tranquil fibers
will fill the world.
The experiment is a success,
Lady Ragyo!
I'm putting an end to this,
Satsuki Kiryuin!
Turn everyone back to normal!
Oh, so you are Ryuko Matoi?
You're—
I see. And that is
Kamui Senketsu?
The fruits of Isshin Matoi's
last, futile efforts.
I must say, I didn't expect it
to be so beautiful.
So you're Ragyo Kiryuin, huh?
I swear, you Kiryuins love
to talk down to people!
I do. I am the one who knows
everything in this world.
I am the leader of the
Kiryuin Conglomerate, Rag—
What are you playing at, Satsuki?
The time for speeches
is over, Director.
As of this moment, Satsuki Kiryuin
and Honnouji Academy
are in rebellion against you!
What... the hell?
Oh, so that's her game.
You're trying to take
the throne from me?
No, I'm not!
People do not live
for the sake of clothing!
I, Satsuki Kiryuin, am rising up
to overthrow Life Fibers!
Honnouji Academy is the fortress
I created in order to defeat you!
Remember that, Ragyo Kiryuin!
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Pandemonium breaks loose on the stage.
THREAD
Whose are the fingers that tug
on the thread of destiny?
When the spinning wheel of destiny
spins and weaves the fabric of karma,
THREAD
SPIN
KARMA
FABRIC
who will it be that
smiles in the shadow?
WHO WILL IT BE THAT SMILES IN THE SHADOW?
Next time on Kill la Kill,
"Into the Night."
EPISODE 18
INTO THE NIGHT