STAFF ROOM
A meeting of delegates?
Apparently there's been such an
influx of clubs since Spring,
we've run out of club rooms.
Oh.
Is this the outbreak of Wizard War VI
for basal supremacy?!
How exciting!
Silence! And...?
And the student council
is gathering all of the
clubs  to hold a one-time briefing session.
They want your club to be in attendance.
Is the purpose of that meeting to take away
rooms from clubs deemed inactive?
I doubt it.
I'm sure of it.
The meeting is being held today after school,
so make sure your delegate attends.
Are you the club's delegate, Togashi?
No.
Isn't it you, Rikka?
CLUB
DELEGATES
MEETING
This is the Sabbath hall.
The universal decision-making body!
Is this where world-wide trends are created?
They all look so intimidating.
That's because each club is desperate
to secure a club room.
Can you do this, Rikka?
CLUB
DELEGATES
MEETING
Dekomori.
Yes, Master?
CLUB
DELEGATES
MEETING
From this day forward
starting now, Dekomori...
...I transfer leadership of the
Far-East Magical Society to you.
What?
It's a napping society!
I am a being of the Dark.
It is terribly perilous for one such as I
to appear
in such an overt gathering.
You don't wanna do it.
Yuta, if I should appear in such a meeting,
the overwhelming power of Wicked Lord Shingan
will inevitably affect every mortal in my vicinity.
So you're saying you don't wanna do it.
Hey.
Excuse me.
The meeting is starting.
Maybe you should have gone in
with her, Togashi.
There's no way I could do that.
Only one delegate from each club can attend.
Master, you are a shining example
of a Dark Being!
Just look at your all-enveloping
deep black aura!
No one can touch you now!
She's just nervous.
I call the delegate from the
Far-East Magical Napping...?
Society...
...summer thereof.
That is I. I am here.
Sure. Please describe your club activities.
Unfortunately I am not at
liberty to discuss that.
Those who have chosen to learn of our society
have done so in full acceptance
of the risks to life and limb...
...but with the guidance
of the fallen angels...
So you did write a speech for her.
Yes, because we can't let her do the talking.
We, the "Far-East Magical Napping Society
- summer thereof"...
...mumble, mumble.
Such commoners!
Those weaker beings were awed speechless
in the presence of Wicked
Lord Shingan. Victory!
My master! Your dark aura is
a force to be reckoned with!
So she was removed from the room
without saying anything helpful?
It's more like she removed herself.
Based on the historical materials
of magic and such...
...we explore the cultural
value and uses of...
Can you please speak up?
I feel ill.
What?
See?
Why didn't you go in there with her?
Because only one person
from a club could attend.
That is exactly the time to use
the fact that you're a couple.
For example...
Rikka and I are of one flesh!
Only together are we one person!
No one must ever...
...come between us!
That would be too embarrassing.
But you two are inseparable. Right?
Yeah, you're such lovebirds.
In what way?!
We really would be
ejected if we did that.
Good afternoon!
Teacher.
What brings you here?
A special news bulletin!
The student council?
Uh-huh. The gist was that you don't
appear to be active enough...
...to merit the use of a club room.
They asked me for my opinion as your advisor.
Well, that's no big surprise.
Hey! Give that back!
So what came of it?
I told them that I would confirm
your club's activities
and make a one-time report.
So, what do you guys do in here?
You don't know?
Uh-huh.
You are our advisor, right?
That's just it.
The student council person
asked me the same thing.
Oh.
But you have a magic summoning circle,
so I'm sure you do magic-type things.
Let go of that!
Mjolnir Tornado!
Or not.
True.
But I nap.
You're awake?
Yeah.
Nap?
Yes. It's even in the name, see?
"The Napping Society - summer thereof."
You're right. Does that mean
you're also a napping club?
Yes.
I doubt that classifying our magical society
as a napping society will help our case much.
You're wrong.
Napping Competition
(search)
Napping clubs are perfectly acceptable.
10 Ways to Win a Napping Tournament
The Napping Olympics Expo
There is such a thing
as championship napping?
Yes. In Europe, they even hold tournaments
as a competitive sport.
Registering Now
For This Year's Participants
How do you determine the merits of a nap?
Well, the total score is based on...
...speed of repose, sleep posture,
slumber depth...
...and time to achieve wakefulness.
You knew about this, Kumin-senpai?
Yes, because I am involved in nap studies.
Anyway, I happen to be acquainted
with a teacher at a school that has
what they call the Siesta Appreciation Club.
Siesta?
Magic?
Exactly, Master! It means "nap" in Spanish.
So, for example, if we
were to actively enter an
intramural competition with that school...
The council would be forced
to accept our club.
That's right!
To:      Momijigaoka High
School Siesta Club Advisor
Would you like me to send an email
asking the other school to compete?
Yes, please! Or at least I'd like to...
...but Kumin-senpai is the only one
among us who actually naps.
We can't jump straight into a competition.
Don't worry. It's not really that hard.
I'll show you how to do it.
You will?
Sure! Just leave it to me.
Darkness comes.
Yes!
Watch out for the trains!
I had no idea that napping was so profound.
It sure is. It's very difficult
to achieve an elegant nap.
The top, most active performers
achieve such elegant naps...
...it's emotionally moving.
Is that so?
Yes. Their posture and the
comfortable look on their faces...
The indescribably delicate depth of sleep...
...as they enter deep slumber.
Why, they look just like...
She's asleep!
After all we've heard, she's actually
starting to look impressive.
Yeah.
Excuse me?
Yes?
Are you the members of
Icho High's napping club?
We are actually.
I am Nemuri Sui and I represent Momijigaoka
High's Siesta Association...
President, Siesta Association:
Sui Nemuri
What? The Siesta Association?
What is this sleepy aura emanating
from her every pore?
She is drowsiness personified!
No, Master! You'll be sucked in!
Dekomori!
My advisor passed along
a rare invitation to compete...
...so I thought I should
introduce myself in person.
Thank you taking the time.
However...
However?
It appears it was unnecessary.
What?
From what I can determine,
you do not appear to be
seriously involved in napping.
I can only presume that you use your club
as an excuse to goof around.
She knows!
Do not worry.
Almost every club that claims
to be a nap club are like yours.
However, our Siesta Association is different.
We take napping very seriously.
Please refrain from making such
invitations for amusement.
I-I'm sorry.
Understood.
The competition is called off.
Please notify your advisor.
It is not for amusement.
Nor are we goofing around.
Kumin-senpai?
The Far-East Magical Napping Society
- summer thereof...
...always takes its activities seriously.
Isn't that right, guys?
Huh? Well, um...
Togashi!
Dekomori!
M-Master!
What? Um...
Uh, that's right!
Really? In that case...
May I accept this as an actual challenge?
Of course.
I swear on the Wicked Lord Shingan
that I always fight for keeps.
Failure equals death!
You're on fire, Master!
If we should happen to lose this battle,
at that very moment...
...I will disband our society!
What?!
How stupid are you?!
You have to learn to stop being so haphazard!
Battle is always waiting to pounce unbidden.
It's ready.
This is an official playing field?
Yes. Sanctioned by the Japanese high
school napping federation.
The professional version is a little bigger.
Professional?!
Team competitions are fought
with five people to a team.
Points are awarded for the speed of falling
asleep and for artistic merit and posture.
It's surprisingly complex.
Now let's give it a try!
Don't worry about posture for now.
Think only about sleeping.
I have Theatre Club to go to.
The moment you leave,
our club is as good as disbanded.
Oh, fine.
It's not all that easy to fall asleep.
Start by closing your eyes.
Is that Takanashi I hear?
Oh, Yuta.
What on Earth is she doing?
Yuta...
No way!
What are you doing?
You're wrong! I was just, uh...
Yuta...
I can't move.
She's sleep paralyzed!
Of course she is.
Master's mind is free of
the wicked and indecent
thoughts experienced by the likes of you.
I never said anything.
And what do you mean by indecent?
I meant...
Early bloomer.
What?! You be quiet, Fake Summer!
Knock that off!
Shut up!
Come on. Sleep properly.
Next, we will nap outdoors.
The ability to sleep the
same, despite a change
of environment, is a vital napping skill.
Here?
We have to sleep here?
Master! The light! The
Light Being is attacking!
Schwarz Shield Prototype...
...Mark IV!
Now let's swim!
Right now?!
Yes, because comfortable fatigue
is the best method to induce a good nap.
But why the pool? It's
still too cold to swim.
You're right. That's a shame.
Swimming really is the best way.
Because swimming helps you "crawl" into bed!
It was a pun?
Hey, come over here!
Is that Isshiki? What's he doing?
He probably followed Kumin-senpai to the pool
to show off to her that he can nap too.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Kumin-senpai.
Naps are a lot harder than I thought.
Because it's hard to ready, set, nap.
Don't worry. Wicked Lord
Shingan is all powerful.
That's my master!
Is now really the time for that?
If we lose, the club is gone.
We just need to win.
Win, Yuta!
Who, me?
Don't worry. I know we can do it.
Where does that unwavering
confidence come from?
Dekomori, nice timing!
Yes!
What are you rigging up now?!
Are we really going to make it like this?
Shouldn't we work out some sort of strategy?
What strategy could there be
in a sleeping competition?
Aside for learning how to sleep faster.
That's it! There is a simple way to do it!
The Night Before the
Competition
I will fight at your side...
...until the darkness vanishes with the dawn!
Naturally!
We just have to stay up all night...
...and we'll definitely be sleepy
in time for the competition.
I get it.
Although it isn't the most elegant
napping method.
We can't control our actions
after we're asleep...
...so it's more important to
start with falling asleep faster.
That's true.
Well, enjoy yourselves.
Right.
Good night!
But why? Why does this always happen?
Fork them over, Very Poor Man!
Take this! The Parallel
Pin Bone King explosion!
No! Not my fish paste factory!
50 combo!
Go! Go!
For I am...
...a sparkling monochrome monster.
Yuta.
Hero.
WHAT THE HECK?!
Morning, Hero.
Togashi, what did you do?
Huh?
Has the Dark Flame Master
turned to the dark side?
No!
So sorry. Old habits die hard.
I forgot that Hero and the Wicked Lord
Shingan are bound by the Lover's Contract.
I believe this is yours.
WHAT THE HECK?
Later!
Hey, wait.
She left.
Throw down salt! I need salt, Kuzuha!
But weren't all of you
supposed to stay awake?
Oh, no!
I failed! This was the
magical devil girl's plot all along!
No, it's our fault for falling asleep!
Hurry!
We will now commence the practice match...
...between Icho High's Far-East Magical
Napping Society - summer thereof...
...versus Momijioka High Siesta Association.
Hold on here.
Advance Guard: Fujiko Nasutaka
Second Guard: Barumu Ichiba
I don't think we have a hope in hell!
Center: Youko Tenbaku
Second in Command: Toromi Utsutsutouge
It's impossible to determine
if they're even awake at this very moment!
They are definitely dwellers
of the Dream World.
Danger.
As promised, you will disband if you lose.
I would be happy to obliterate...
...even one more farcical napping club.
What now?
There's no way we can win this.
We all got so much sleep,
our skin looks fabulous.
Advance Guard: Rikka Takanashi
Second guard: Sanae Dekomori
We have only one option left.
Center: Yuta Togashi
If we apologize to them now, just maybe...
Second in Command: Shinka Nibutani
You can't!
Captain: Kumin Tsuyuri
We will not lose.
Our club is not that irresponsible.
Kumin-senpai.
I remember thinking it
when I met Rikka for the first time.
Oh, really?
Precisely.
Our true goal is to locate
the invisible boundary line.
But our actions will not end there.
For that is our society!
I had a feeling back then...
...that things really could work out
if I joined her and her friends.
With her? But she has chunibyo.
Yes. But you know?
And I know nobody
really gets this about her...
...but she's very wholehearted and
serious about what she does...
...just like a napping club.
Kumin.
In our Far-East Magical Napping Society
- summer thereof...
...we nap hard,
we play hard...
...and we banish hard,
so we cannot lose.
We're invincible!
Yeah!
Be destroyed, real.
Blow up, synapses.
Banishment, This World!
This world of sleep belongs to us.
Leave here at once!
Avalon Smasher!
Mjolnir Hammer!
Disqualified!
I am the Dark Flame Master.
Be enveloped in the flames of darkness...
Disqualified!
Why does it always have to be me?!
I got a cramp in my leg!
Disqualified!
Who's left?
Just those two.
The Non-REM killer technique:
Circadian Rhythm Destroyer!
The Non-REM Killer Technique:
Circadian Rhythm Destroyer
Destiny Ring!
Destiny Ring
But why?
You could take that incredible power
and aim for the world title if you were serious!
The truth is, I like that place.
What is this?
That is why I must protect it.
Sleeper's Wake.
Kumin-senpai. Kumin-senpai.
Togashi, you're all here.
We did it. We won.
Kumin, I am grateful.
Really? What happened to Sui and her friends?
They went home. They said they accept defeat.
That means we don't have to disband.
But of course!
I will battle Fake Summer
once again tomorrow!
Why is that?!
What?
I had a funny dream while I was sleeping.
What kind of dream?
I was with all of you, and...
Was that really a dream?
I unleash this power.
Lightning Blast!
With this, the attributing
thunder technique is flawless.
I'll do it! Count me in!
Freshman, you messed with my costume again!
FAKE
There you are, Fake Summer!
It's very versatile.
Stay out of it!
Do not look away!
Ultimately nothing changed.
We still don't nap at all.
Yeah, but I'm happiest when I sleep here.
So, good night.
One more shot!
Yuta, watch out!
What was that for?!
Dekomori, sound the lightning!
To Be
Continued
Roger that!
Listen to me!