Miyagi Prefecture
Tokonami High School
It's official.
I got the pairings for the
Inter-High preliminaries.
At last.
Where's our first match gonna be?
Let's see...
Omisaki
Tokonami
Karasuno
Dateko
Tori... Torino?
Torino? Is that a British school?
It's Karasuno, moron.
Besides, Torino would be Italian.
Tokonami
I've heard of that school.
They're...
"Fallen rivals.
Unflying crows."
What's that? Some kind of idiom?
They used to be strong.
I think they even went to nationals once.
I hear they're not even
worth mentioning nowadays.
Which could mean, that just maybe...
They'll be easy to beat.
We won't lose in the first round
like we do every year.
But to make that happen, we have to train.
Captain.
Get running.
Yeah.
A guy from my junior high
volleyball club is at Karasuno.
Is it your first time
seeing him since then?
We've never played
against that school before.
He used to talk about how
unforgettable Karasuno was
in the spring tournament he saw on TV,
but he probably went there
because it's close to his home.
I wonder how he's doing now...
Sawamura.
Haikyu!!
Episode 14: Formidable Opponents
Block follow! Get in there!
Don't just stand and watch.
I'm sorry.
"This is my last chance."
Always tell yourself that.
Give it all you got.
If you don't, the one chance you wasted
could cost you the match!
Everyone, you all did a good job
in today's matches against Nekoma.
Inter-High preliminaries begin
next month on June 2nd.
There are no district
preliminaries in Miyagi,
so we go straight to
prefectural preliminaries.
Championship
Out of about 60 teams in the prefecture,
only one will go to nationals.
The winning team
Lose one match and the journey ends.
If you want to take revenge on Nekoma,
you must take first place in Miyagi.
There's no other way.
Second place won't cut it.
Of course, they'll have to win the battle
to represent Tokyo, as well.
Those guys can do it.
Yeah. They're strong.
Another match against Nekoma...
Again...
Nice, Hinata.
Get up quickly. One more.
Yes, thank you.
Front, front.
Cover.
Karasuno High School
Volleyball Club
You're right. That's amazing.
The picture's huge.
Yeah!
What, what?
What? What's that?
Look.
Boy's High School
This year, pay special attention to these three
GUYS!
"Shiratorizawa's Ushiwaka is among the
three most-noticed high schoolers
in the whole country."
Shiratorizawa! That's where
Kageyama couldn't get in.
Shut up.
What's so funny, you bastards?
Who's Ushiwaka?
We're not laughing.
You don't know?
You're full of it.
That's because you're only
a fan of the Little Giant.
Let me tell you about Ushiwaka.
He's unmistakably the number-one ace
of our prefecture: Ushijima Wakatoshi.
Overwhelming power and height!!
Super high-school ace!!
Miyagi
Shiratorizawa Academy
Third-year
Ushijima Wakatoshi
His goal: To conquer nationals, of course!
Hmm. He definitely has "ace"
written all over him.
Hey, why are you looking at me?
Kageyama, you were trying to get
into a place with guys like this?
And you were going to yell
at the super high-school ace,
"Move faster, clumsy oaf!" and stuff, right?
I wouldn't say that.
Monthly Volleyball
If we don't defeat him,
we can't play against Nekoma.
Hey, hey.
Shiratorizawa isn't the
only formidable opponent.
Would the others be last year's best four?
Yes, but there are other
formidable opponents this year.
Wakutani Minami
There's Wakutani Minami, which has
superior defense and coordination.
Date Kogyo
Date Kogyo is also known as
the Iron Wall, which says it all.
That team has the highest
blocking rate in the country.
If I recall,
we lost to Dateko 2-0 in the
prefectural tournament last March.
The match in March...
an iron wall of blockers...
Every single spike by Asahi got
blocked in this one match.
Was Suga-san talking about
the match against Date Kogyo?
I hear there's a second-year named
Aone who is particularly dangerous.
Dateko is as strong as
the other best four teams,
but they lost their third-round match against
the eventual champions, Shiratorizawa,
and only made the best sixteen.
That's why they weren't seeded this year.
In other words, depending on the match-ups,
we might or might not play
against them in the first round.
And the next one... Oh, yeah.
I heard we recently had a
practice match against them.
The team's top attacker is their setter,
and of course he's also a supreme setter.
Their team's ranks include perhaps the best
all-around player in the prefecture.
Aoba Johsai
That would Oikawa Toru at Aoba Johsai.
The Great King!
They were in last year's best four.
Last, but not least...
Shiratorizawa
The defending champions, Shiratorizawa,
and their super-ace Ushijima Wakatoshi.
That about sums it up.
I'll save the details for later.
Ukai-san, even though you're sloppy...
You guys are thinking something
disrespectful about me, aren't you?
Anyway, those are the top four
contenders this year.
However, if look up instead of straight ahead,
we could lose our footing.
There's no team that enters
a tournament to lose.
They all enter to win.
While we frantically train,
others will also be frantically training.
Weak or strong, they're all aiming to win.
Don't forget that.
And...
don't let them call us
"unflying crows" ever again.
Yeah.
I'm glad you're all still here.
Sorry I'm late.
The meeting went long. However...
Here it is. The match-ups for
the Inter-High preliminaries.
Tokonami (4)
Karasuno (5)
Dateko (6)
Ouka (7)
If we win the first round,
we might play against Dateko,
assuming they also win.
But that's not all...
Aoba Johsai (1)
Senkawa Kita (2)
Omisaki (3)
Okonami (4)
Karasuno (5)
Dateko (6)
Ouka (7)
Aoba Johsai is one of the seeds in our block.
Day One                         Day Two
For real?
Dateko and Seijoh...
Hey.
Don't forget what I just said.
If all you do is look up...
We know.
Tokonami
Karasuno
Which high school are
you going to, Sawamura?
Karasuno.
Huh? Where?
You know, the school that was
in the spring tournaments.
Oh.
And you, Ikejiri?
I'm going to Tokonami.
Guess we're parting ways.
Guess so.
Which means,
if I continue playing
volleyball in high school...
You should continue.
Maybe we'll play against each other.
And if we do, I'll smash you to pieces.
Tokonami
Karasuno
I dare you.
Ikejiri, let's get going.
The first round match...
I promise we'll win it.
Third-Year  Class 4
Sawamura.
What, Michimiya?
I got the pep rally schedule
for the sports clubs.
The volleyball club is up fifth.
Thank you.
Do you have a speech ready, captain?
Nope, I've got nothing.
The Inter-High preliminaries
are around the corner.
Yeah. The boys' team is doing well.
What was that team... the one you used
to do practice matches with...
Excuse me.
Nekoma?
Right, right. You played
against them again, right?
How are the girls doing?
I've been out of touch because
we have separate gyms.
We've been... well... as usual.
The club members stopped coming
to morning practice, as usual.
I'm not good at being stern.
We'll probably lose in
the first round, again.
Crap.
Michimiya, didn't you say,
"We'll definitely win next time"?
No matter how formidable and
unbeatable your opponent,
you'll never win if you don't
believe you can.
Whoops, I didn't mean to preach.
Well, you see...
I remember when you scolded me in
junior high. You said the same thing.
It was right after we got crushed
in a practice match before the tournament.
I figured we were destined
for failure in the real tournament.
Even if we're not confident that we'll win,
even if others tell us
we don't stand a chance, we...
"We must never tell ourselves that."
End quote.
I'm sorry! I have a bad habit of
losing confidence before a tournament.
I hope I'm not being presumptuous,
but since you and I are both captains,
I'll pretend I didn't hear any of that.
You're too easy on me.
All right, I'm good.
I'm good now. Thanks.
Because I...
want to pulverize my dear underclassman,
setter-on-setter, in an official match.
What's that?
Scary.
Third-Year  Class 3
Karasuno (5)
Dateko (6)
Dateko       Karasuno
Asahi-san.
Go! Club!
What's going on?
Is he training a dog?
Nishinoya.
Don't worry about me.
I'm not running away.
I know everyone's behind me.
This time, I'll stick out my chest,
and declare, "I'm the ace of Karasuno!"
Hinata.
Sugawara-san.
Perfect timing. There's something
I wanted to give you.
I'll give it to the other first years later.
My signals.
I'm not as accurate as Kageyama,
so I'll give signals to say,
"This is what I'm doing next."
Oh.
Though you might not like
memorizing things...
I don't mind. Signals are cool.
I'll memorize them.
We have to use them in practice,
or they'll be useless in the tournament.
I'd be grateful if you could
practice them with me.
Yes. I'll do it all you want.
I'll learn to spike any toss.
A back attack with three
vanguards feinting...
Keishin-chan.
Keishin-chan, dear, I need some mirin.
Sorry.
Foothill Store
Keishin-chan, dear, I need some mirin.
What are you looking all serious about?
The tournament's coming up, right?
Yeah.
Tournaments fire you up, don't they?
It's like getting ready for battle.
Yeah... sort of.
And then maybe, your cute
girlfriend comes to watch, and...
"Tomorrow's the tournament at last."
"Yeah, that's right."
"You were training so long for this."
"Yeah. I know it's been hard for you, too."
"No, I don't mind."
"I love watching you play, Ryu-kun."
"Honey..."
"I thought hard about what to give you,
and I made this for you."
"A good luck charm..."
"Ryu-kun. Do your best tomorrow."
If she said stuff like that to me...
I was thinking I'd get even more fired up.
Keep thinking that, and I'll
take your place as a regular.
Nice kill.
Nice, Azumane-san.
Azumane.
Yes.
Are you good at back attacks?
Hey. I need you guys here.
That's the idea...
We have to find the right
height for spiking.
It looks hard.
Let's do it.
Coach us.
Hinata, you jump in as usual.
Yes.
Good job.
Ukai-kun, you must be exhausted.
I appreciate you coming
daily at start time, but
I hope it's not affecting your job.
Yeah, I've been working at the
store exclusively 'til now,
but now I'm working on the farm as well,
so I've been working the
evening shift at the store.
It's our family business,
so I can't complain.
Thank you very much.
I'll bring you sake or something
the next time I visit.
Seriously?
I didn't realize there were
so many attack patterns.
Are we using all of these?
It depends.
I need those guys to focus on the match.
Hinata, A next.
Yes.
I can't overwhelm them before the match.
Nice, Hinata. Awesome, awesome.
Hinata and Sugawara's
quicks are taking shape.
Thanks!
That toss was really good.
Nice.
Azumane-san, how was that toss?
Was it too high? Too low?
How was it?
Oh, um... yeah, it was fine.
If you have a criticism, no matter
how minor, tell me everything.
I'll fix it.
I see... then... maybe a little higher?
And a little further away from the net.
Understood.
Ten more spikes, please.
What?
Is that not enough? Then twenty spikes.
There's no point in getting
that anxious before the match.
No, that's not what I meant...
Remember the timing
when you start running.
Yes.
Did you mean you want to
practice other patterns?
Hey, stragglers. Let's wrap it up.
Right.
Shimizu.
Daichi says he's buying us pork buns.
Sorry. I have stuff to do.
I see. Good job.
Good job.
One per person.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Daichi-san, thank you.
Let's eat and then go home.
Hey, Tsukishima.
Daichi-san bought us pork buns.
Oh, thanks.
Isn't Yamaguchi with you?
He said he has stuff to do.
Shimada Mart
He left before I did.
Sorry, we're closed. Oh?
I'm in the Karasuno Volleyball Club.
My name is Yamaguchi.
I knew you looked familiar.
Um...
Will you teach me how
to do a jump float serve?
Oh, yeah. I used it in that match.
But the Inter-High preliminaries
start soon, right?
It'll be hard to learn it in such short time.
Probably.
I probably won't be able to
play this time around, anyway.
There's no way a first-year like
me can replace a third-year.
But...
I don't want to be the only
first-year who has to sit out.
Tsukishima
All School Sports Clubs Pep Rally
Miyagi Prefecture Tokonami High School
Inter-High
Good job.
Go home and go to sleep early tonight.
Yeah.
Okay, that'll do it.
Just a second.
One more thing. Shimizu-san?
I'm not good at cheering, but...
Sensei, if you will?
Leave it to me.
Sensei, I can do the carrying.
Don't worry about it.
What's going on?
One, two...
Fly
I didn't know we had that.
I found it while cleaning, so I washed it.
I'm getting fired up!
That's our Kiyoko-san! Great job!
All right! Let's get fired up!
Wait.
She's...
...not done.
Do...
"Do"?
Do your best.
Fly
Shimizu!
No one ever did
anything like this for us before!
Even the captain?
Those guys... they're speechless.
They usually never shut up.
You're all out of control.
We're going to win the first round for sure!
Yeah.
We have the strength of a hundred men!
First one here! First one here!
You bastard! Stop, Kageyama.
That makes 31 wins and 30 losses for me.
And one draw.
That's not right.
It is right. I won.
I've won 30 times,
and that was my 32nd loss.
Around this time last year,
you defeated my team.
We got crushed.
Yukigaoka               Kitagawa Daiichi
If you're the king that rules the court...
"I'll have to defeat you, and
I'll be the last one standing."
I promise I'll defeat you.
Even if takes me ten years,
or twenty years, I will.
You plan on playing on the
same level as me, then.
Yeah, that's right.
Even if I'm the best in Japan,
or the whole world?
The whole world?
O-Of course.
And don't call me "King."
Ouch.
Ouch...
Let's go. Today we take our
first step toward that goal.
Yeah.
Next Episode Preview
Tanaka-senpai, why are you crying?
Kiyoko-san said, "Do your best."
But that was yesterday.
Ryu, don't remind me!
"I don't get you guys...
Episode 15: Revival
Next time on Haikyu!!: "Revival"