Haru!
Haru-chan!
He passed one!
He's in fourth!
He passed another!
Third!
Haru-chan...
Go!
And another! He's in second! Second!
He's closing in!
They're dead even!
Haru!
Haru-chan!
Haruka-senpai!
We
won!
Samezuka Academy
Iwatobi High School
Haru, that was amazing!
You did it, Haru-chan!
Haruka-senpai, that was truly inspiring!
Yeah, my heart was racing just watching it!
Same here! Mine's still racing!
We actually get to go to regionals!
I love you, Haru-chan!
Haruka-senpai!
Hey, you're heavy...
Nagisa!
We did it!
Stop it!
Despite being a brand-new club,
Hesitant Loosen Up!
our swimmers placed in
the top 8 at prefecturals
and qualified for regionals.
We hope that they're able
to advance to nationals.
That is all.
Congratulations to the Swim Club
on Making Regionals
They were really ready for this.
It's obvious that they reused an old one.
Swim Club
Judo Club
But it's finally starting
to sink in that we won.
Yep.
They'll treat us like heroes
when we enter the classroom.
Gou!
Oh, Hana-chan!
Hanging out with boys, huh?
True to your name.
We won?
Very funny.
I don't get it.
What do you mean, you don't get it?
I was talking about how
Gou has a boyish name
and hangs out with boys.
Enough of that.
Haru!
Haru-chan!
Haruka-senpai!
Where's Haruka-senpai?
He wandered off.
Did he go home?
Well, he does this all the time.
Anyway, we've accomplished our
objective of placing at a tournament,
so they should give us a bigger budget.
And we can use that budget to
swim at a gym all the time!
Yep.
How can you say that?!
Huh?
Weren't you listening to the principal?
Our next objective is to
make it to nationals!
Huh?
Always aim high!
Okay!
Let's do our best to make it to nationals!
Yes!
Fly...
...high!
Fly high?
I'll be the first one in the club room!
I don't think so!
You think you can beat a former
track and field athlete?!
Watch this!
Okay!
We'll mainly be running drills for now.
Rei-kun, you'll work on your kick.
You'll be training to develop
a faster and stronger kick.
Yes, ma'am.
Nagisa-kun, you'll focus on
strengthening your crawl stroke.
Okay.
Makoto-senpai, you need to work on
making your acceleration more even.
Got it.
Let's start warming up then!
Er...
Haru!
You were already here.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Haru-chan's really motivated.
How long have you been swimming?
Maybe he's upset about losing at free.
Not very long.
It's hot out today, so I brought
ice to keep your drinks cold.
Perhaps.
I appreciate it.
I'm happy to see you so motivated.
I'm not.
I was swimming because I
didn't know what to do.
I figured I should ask the water
about matters involving water.
What do you mean?
Well, everyone's here now.
Let's start practice.
Yes, you're right.
Then everybody should
start by warming up.
Roger!
Yes, ma'am!
Hey! No running!
Yahoo!
Senpai, you're swimming well.
I guess.
You posted a personal best
during the group stage,
so it looks like your decision to
focus on the 100m free paid off.
I wasn't able to make it to the final.
Yeah, too bad.
But you have to do your best!
I'll do everything I can to support you!
Senpai?
Is something wrong?
Not really.
You were so happy about
beating Nanase-san.
Yeah...
Then you can move on now!
Hey, hurry up. We're leaving.
Huh? Where are we going?
Weren't you listening?
We're off to pray for victory.
Oh, that's right.
Today is Hachiman-sama's...
Festival?
Yep, there's a summer
festival for Hachiman-sama!
Let's go, Haru-chan!
It'll be lots of fun!
But...
The shrine also hosts a festival
for the god of water.
We should pay a visit before regionals.
If that's okay with you.
Rei-chan's waiting for you to join us.
The four of us must go together,
or there's no point.
His words.
Was that supposed to be a Rei impression?
Okay.
I'll go get dressed.
Hey!
Rei-chan!
Did you wait long?
No, I just got here.
Wow! Good one, Rei-chan!
Mako-chan, Haru-chan...
If you arrive early for a date,
that's what you have to say.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's visit the shrine first.
Yes.
Well, let's go!
Iwatobi Station
I'm a fan of yukata.
We should have worn ours.
Oh, I believe you're familiar
with this area, Senpai.
I guess.
Oh, there he is!
You're late!
Sorry about that!
Hey, how much money did they give you?
I got a lot.
We have to try candy apples!
Huh? I wanna play shooting games!
We still can!
Candy apples come first!
Squid! Squid! Squid!
Candy apples!
Squid!
Wow, there's squid everywhere, all right.
Nothing's changed.
Just squiddy.
So where should we start?
Don't ignore me!
Squid Catching Heaven is about to start.
What kind of weird event is that?
And why are you looking at me?
Rei-chan.
I refuse.
You should participate.
No way!
It sounds so... slimy!
Give it a try!
Absolutely not!
Oh, the event's over there!
Let's get going!
Ah! Wait up!
Haru, we don't want to lose
sight of Nagisa and Rei.
Y-Yeah...
It went your way!
Don't let it escape!
Okay!
It looks fun.
You can still join in, Rei-chan.
Not happening.
What about you, Mako-chan?
I'll pass.
Hey, you're all here.
Oh, Gou-chan.
H-Hello.
You're wearing yukata!
You both look cute.
You mean just our yukata?
Not exactly...
Should we grab something to eat?
Sure.
I recommend the squid paella.
Sounds delicious!
Well, we'll be watching the
Squid Ink Calligraphy Contest.
Okay, bye!
What do you guys want to eat?
We have to start with fried squid!
I want squid tempura.
Let's look around then.
Oh, I could go for some paella.
Yeah, let's go through the stalls first.
Okay, dismissed.
You're free to walk around now.
However, don't get into any trouble.
Yes, sir!
Senpai, let's look around.
Wait for me!
Squid burgers!
I'm interested in trying out squid and chips.
Try not to get lost, you guys.
We know.
What is it, Rei-chan?
Rin-chan?
Bad timing, right?
Definitely...
Is something wrong?
Oh, we were wondering how many
bowls of squid we can eat.
Let's try a shooting game!
You're going to eat that much?
I'm not interested.
Oh! I'll go buy squid burgers for everyone!
How thoughtful of you, Nagisa-kun!
Hold on!
Can you wait in the rest area over there?!
Uh, I don't want one.
Er, but we do...
Let's go then, Haru.
We need to find space for all four of us.
Okay.
It's possible that Rin-chan and
Haru-chan will run into each other.
Definitely.
I invited Haru-chan to the festival
to take his mind off swimming.
But it may end up having
the opposite effect.
What? He might ditch the relay at regionals!
That would be the worst case scenario.
I want Haru-chan to swim with us.
I also want to swim with Haruka-senpai.
So we have to make sure they don't meet.
I believe so.
Rei-chan.
You follow Rin-chan.
What?
You tell me where Rin-chan is.
Then we can lead Haru-chan somewhere else!
Nagisa-kun, you seem to be enjoying this...
Okay! Go to it, Detective Rei-chan!
You bought a lot of food.
Huh? Where's Rei?
Oh, uh...
He ran into an acquaintance
and they're walking around
the festival together.
Oh.
A-Anyway, let's eat.
I'll go buy drinks.
Ah! You stay here, Haru-chan!
I'll go.
I'll come with you.
It might be more than you can carry by yourself.
Wait here, Haru-chan.
So what's going on?
Well, Rin-chan's here at the festival.
Rin's here?
Yeah, so Rei-chan's...
following him right now!
Target's height is estimated to be 177 cm.
Weight is estimated to be 68 kg.
He has red hair and pointy teeth.
Commence pursuit.
Captain Mikoshiba bought cotton candy,
chocolate bananas, and candy apples.
I wouldn't expect him to enjoy those.
Is something wrong?
No, nothing's wrong.
Not bad.
That'll be 500 yen.
Okay, I want that game console!
Man, I missed.
Mako-chan, can you hold this?
Sure thing.
The target is currently walking
through the stalls by the beach
and heading for the main road, over.
Roger that.
I need to go to the restroom.
The closest one would be in the
convenience store on the main road.
Got it.
Wait!
Can you hold it in a little longer?
Huh?
Oh, there might be a
porta potty over there.
It should be closer.
Fine.
Yeah, I'll come with you.
There aren't any stalls over here.
I know.
Let's go back.
You can go back.
Matsuoka-senpai...
It works better if you don't try as hard.
Hey, hey.
What?
Just like in real life.
Sometimes, it doesn't work
unless you try hard.
Right?
Awesome!
So many!
Lucky...
You can have them if you want.
Really?!
Yay!
We can show them off to
Ta-chan and everyone else!
Uh-huh!
Mako-chan, Mako-chan.
Rin-chan's in the park in the third district.
The park in the third district?
That leads to...
Iwatobi Elementary School
An elementary school?
Makoto!
Mako-chan!
Go, Nagisa!
Rin!
Rin-chan!
Faster! Faster!
Rin!
Haru!
Haru-chan!
Haruka-senpai!
From: Hazuki Nagisa
To: Ryugazaki Rei
Where are you now?
I haven't had candy apples in a while.
From: Rei-chan
Iwatobi Elementary School.
Thought so...
From: Rei-chan
Sub: Untitled
But I lost sight of him...
What?
Then Rin-chan could still be—
What are you up to?
Did you hear that, Haru-chan?
Rin is here?
Uh-huh.
Oh.
It's okay. Tell Rei to come back.
Uh-huh.
I'll go get Rei-chan then.
Here.
Thanks.
You know...
We didn't get to prepare for that
relay, so I got a bit frantic.
Swimming as hard as I could so
the next person could go...
But in the process, I remembered
what we saw that day.
I was happy to swim in a relay
with you, with everyone.
I'm...
not so sure anymore.
I don't need a reason to swim.
I just need to feel the water.
That's what I've always believed.
But...
When I lost to him,
everything became dark.
This means I'll never swim with you again.
Never.
I won't get to
swim with Rin again.
I didn't care about anything at that point.
Not the tournament or anything else.
But then I watched you guys swim.
I thought, "I trained hard with these guys."
I might end up being
nothing more than filler.
But
if you guys really wanted
to swim in a relay,
I would swim.
That was when I remembered
how it felt to swim in the
same lane together,
how it felt when everyone was
waiting at the finish line.
It made me
just as happy!
Haru!
Haru-chan!
Did you really mean that?
When did you guys get here?
You have your answer, Haruka-senpai.
Nagisa.
Rei.
Makoto.
I want to swim in the relay.
I want to swim with you guys!
Again!
Haru!
Okay!
That means we have to start training
hard tomorrow to make nationals!
I'm getting fired up.
We should head home so
we're ready tomorrow.
No, one last thing...
Huh? What is it?
I'm impressed, Haruka-senpai.
Can I really have these?
Yeah.
You're the only one who's
likely to take care of them.
I'll take good care of them.
Why don't you name them as well?
Name them?
Just go with Nagisa, Rei,
Haruka, and Makoto.
I don't know about that.
Mackerel, Bonito, Tuna, Jackfish.
What?
Iwatobi Station
Matsuoka, what are you doing?
The train's about to arrive.
Captain, we need to talk.
Big news!
My brother's swimming in
the relay at regionals!
What?!
Wow, that sukiyaki looks good.
Whose idea was it to have sukiyaki?
And why in the middle of summer
when it's over 39 degrees Celsius?
To build up stamina for the tournament.
Wait, Nagisa-kun!
That hasn't been cooked enough!
Just a little won't hurt.
Wait, Haruka-senpai!
You're not supposed to add
mackerel to sukiyaki!
That's enough! You guys stay away!
Next time: Irritated Heart Rate.
Irritated Heart Rate!
Calm down, Rei-chan!
You need more calcium!
Have some mackerel!