Yes. Yes.
Shinjuku Station
Kabuki-cho Ichibangai
Shinjuku Ward Office
This is the place, right?
April 1st
Shinjuku Ward Office
Main Building
Visitors during off-hours are required
to check in with security prior to entry.
#1 "Angels and Tengu Above the Shinjuku Skyline"
Um...
Yes?
I've been assigned to the Nocturnal
Community Relations Division.
My name is Miyako Arata.
Oh, you're their new kid, huh?
Sakaki-kun told me about you.
Come on in.
Holiday/Night Entrance
Follow the hallway to the end and turn right,
walk by the elevator hall,
turn at the corner with the closed cafeteria,
and then it's the first door on the left.
Storage #1
Here?
Excuse me...
Huh? It's not storage.
Jeez, that's weird.
Did I use the wrong stuff?
I had the sulfur, and the aluminum...
And the goat gallstones.
Did I get the proportions wrong?
U-Um...
Is this the Nocturnal Community
Relations Division?
Yeah, but who are you?
Well, I'm starting here today—
Oh, you're the new kid!
I remembered Reiji-kun saying
something about that.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Himezuka Seo, I work here.
Seo's written in katakana. Call me Seo.
Katakana?
I used to be British.
So make it sound British.
Seo!
You did it again, didn't you?
The smoke got all the way
out to the cafeteria.
You didn't use any fire, did you?
The one in the wrong here was...
you, Kyouichi!
You used my photo again, didn't you?!
As an excuse to dump a girl?!
You found out?
It's just so much easier to show them
a pic of you and say you're my girlfriend.
And because of that,
every day there's some angry woman
glaring at me from my doorstep!
Really?
Don't make me deal with the fallout
from your bad habits with women!
I swear,
if you do it again I'll make you regret it.
Oh, you're a woman, Himezuka-san?
I thought for sure you were a man—
I am a man!
And call me Seo!
S-e-o!
Okay...
How do you get that wrong?
Oh, hello there. It's Sakaki.
The new recruit is here. Miyako Arata-kun.
Should I send him in?
Roger. Introductions can wait, then.
That's Sakaki Kyouichi.
A former host who loves women and drinking.
He's the shift leader for the division.
Despite looking like that, somehow.
That's right.
Ask us if there's anything
you don't understand.
Th-Thank you.
It's 7:00.
Let's get to work, then.
Change into the outfit
in the far right locker.
We're going outside for your first shift.
Miyako
Our division spends most of
its time outside the office.
I'll give you a nametag for
inside the office later.
We work a different shift
from everyone else,
so you won't use it much.
Um,
what are we doing outside at nighttime?
What were you told?
Um...
"To build relationships with
people of various ages,
in various fields and social positions,
as well engage in planning and promotion".
That's right.
Shinjuku is a city where people from a lot of
different countries do different
jobs in different places.
So what do we do to make this
a better place to live for them?
Figuring that out is our job.
At least, that's what the paperwork says.
You ever see a youkai,
or an angel, or a devil?
Am I supposed to answer that seriously?
From the look of it, the answer is no.
But if you were assigned here,
it means you hit that little
trick in the employment exam.
He's probably the type who isn't aware of it.
So we'll need to do a rite of passage.
What are you talking about?
Shinjuku Gate
Imperial Gardens
April 1st
Where are we?
You've never come here?
The Shinjuku Imperial Gardens.
Shinjuku Imperial Gardens
I have but, um...
Isn't entry forbidden at night?
We're here a lot as part of our work.
So we have a key.
There's barely any lights
inside, so be careful.
Oh, okay!
We work in the Imperial Gardens at night?
What do we do, exactly?
I think that's a good spot.
Yeah.
Let's do it, then. The rite of passage.
Um, what is this thing
you keep talking about?
Don't worry.
Even if you scream and pass
out, I'll take care of you.
This job is easier to
experience than explain.
There.
There's a fairy right there.
Huh?
It's there.
You can't see it right now, though.
Youkai, angels, devils...
Most of the occult creatures
you see in fiction,
you can assume really exist.
That's the first thing
you need to learn, here.
Um, are we really talking
about work right now?
Of course.
It's an important discussion
about the job we do.
Seo.
Right, right.
What are you doing?
The Spray of Ibn Ghazi.
It's a helper item for people
who have trouble seeing them.
It's made from the soil of ancient tombs,
Amaranth flowers, and then ground ivy...
Oh, look in front of you.
What do you see?
What?
I see light... it's changing?
A little girl?
With wings on her back?
A-A fairy?
That was a pixie.
You can find them everywhere.
I can't believe it...
Believe what you see.
Otherwise you'll just have
to assume you've gone insane.
Wh-What is this?
You can see without help already, huh?
You've got good instincts.
This big boy is a Cu Sith.
It's friendly.
They all have their own unique names,
but they're what you might
call occult creatures.
Angels. Devils. Youkai. Fairies.
We have a name for all these non-human
creatures we use in our work.
"Anothers".
Huh? You don't seem scared.
No...
I'm surprised. Very surprised.
If that's all you are, then the
rite of passage was a big success.
We got a good one this time, huh, Kyouichi?
Most pass out after their first time,
or at least their legs give out.
But you're okay, huh?
Um,
what is our real job here?
Maintaining relations with the Anothers,
and if they get into any
problems with civilians,
taking care of it.
That's the job of the Shinjuku Ward Office
Nocturnal Community Relations Division.
Our job as public servants.
What's wrong?
Um...
I'm a little worried.
Don't worry.
Like I just said,
if you see an Another and stay calm
enough to talk, that's amazing.
Don't worry.
Just do what you're told, and
focus on the things you can do.
We won't ask for more just yet.
Okay...
Now, welcome to the Shinjuku Ward
Nocturnal Community Relations Division,
Miyako Arata.
Let's talk about our duties.
Tonight we're investigating
some loud noises that
have been reported in Shinjuku
Imperial Gardens at night.
Loud noises?
Yeah. There's no events being held,
March: Imperial Gardens Noise Complaints Graph
so we don't know where
they're coming from.
Then, when we were doing a patrol
around this area last night,
we found traces of two types of
Anothers at the tip of a damaged tree.
Analysis of both physical and
circumstantial evidence lead us to believe
that the cause of the noise was
a territory struggle between tengu and angels.
They fight? The Anothers.
Yeah, they do.
The Imperial Gardens have
more space and greenery,
so multiple types of Anothers live here.
Sometimes they fight.
So, how do we stop them?
Put up a barrier.
With like... talismans and
piles of salt and stuff?
No, that.
Tape?
Yup.
It uses the element of wind to slightly
adjust the area's dimensional phase.
It puts up a fairly powerful barrier
and can also block most noise.
Seo made it.
The other wards are using it, too.
Kyouichi, what about Sendagaya Gate?
Shinjuku Imperial Gardens
I already spoke to Shibuya's
Nocturnal Relations division.
I'm sure they've dealt with it.
The Gardens run into
Shibuya Ward, don't they?
Here.
Here you go.
We'll split up into two groups and
put up the barrier with this tape.
You can do that, right?
Yes.
All right.
I'll do the rest here.
You go do that forest over there.
Just run the tape along
the trees on the left side.
Got it.
Does this really put up
a barrier or something?
Oh, my beautiful wings! My beloved Adiel.
I feel so powerless, only
being able to meet you.
As long as you're safe, Taroubou-sama,
I don't care where we meet.
I want to fly in the great
sky above us, together!
Me, too! I want to fly with you forever!
Then, let's go!
The others will never accept us.
So let's...
I'm so happy, Taroubou-sama!
But, I can't leave my sister.
I'm sorry.
I have to go.
Taroubou-sama.
But think about it.
About our future.
An angel?
And that was a tengu, huh?
That's rare for the two of
them to get so close, though.
I see.
They were having a fight, weren't they?
But, that conversation...
I found you, Taroubou!
I am Folciel, and you are deceiving
my younger sister Adiel!
Tonight, I will destroy you!
Folciel-dono, listen to me.
You won't get away!
Hold it right there!
Dad!
Get back, Taroubou.
How dare you accuse the son
of Yotsuya Fudoubou of anything?
You're planning to kidnap him,
aren't you? We know it!
I hope they both calm down...
He's taking Adiel! You little...
What are they trying to do?!
Wait, Adiel!
Seo, they might be leaving the park!
What?!
How?!
Don't ask me!
Yes, this is the Nocturnal
Community Relations Division.
This is Sakaki!
The Anothers in the Gardens are taking
their fight out into the city.
We're going to follow them!
Thanks, Sakaki-kun.
Yes.
This is Shinjuku Nocturnal
Community Relations.
Some of our staff are
trailing some Anothers.
And?
They may be heading your way.
Wanted to give you heads up.
Nocturnal Culture and Environment Division
Adiel, get away from that tengu!
Stop this, Sister!
So you refuse?
Then...
This is the cause of the noise complaints?
Shinjuku Station
Look at them all!
April 1st
This is Sakaki.
City Hall!
The People's Plaza in front of City Hall!
They're fighting each other here!
Get over here!
Well? How's it look?
Small scuffles, and a lot of
glaring at each other.
This might continue until morning.
Wh-What is it?
Seo-san...
Is this really a struggle for territory?
Hell if I know!
Angels and tengu don't get
along, so I'm just guessing.
Huh?! Really?!
Then... none of them know?
Don't know what?
I just saw them at the park!
Taroubou-san and Adiel-san...
the two of them are lovers!
Who is Tarou?
The angel and the tengu.
Wait, wait. I'm not following this at all.
They were just close to each other, right?
How can you tell?
How? Because...
Run, idiot!
Miyako!
Are you okay?
Ow...
I'm okay.
So I got a human involved in this?
I'm sorry.
You want to fight us, too?
Forgive her.
She didn't mean to hurt him.
The angels are here, too.
We don't want to fight you!
They're not going to give up, are they?
Can you move, Arata?
I'm gonna hit them hard.
Why?
We don't need to go easy on them, do we?
Wait, we...
You want to fight, huh?!
Why?
Why is this happening?
Seo!
Right!
None of their words
are reaching each other!
What are you doing, you idiot?
They were apologizing!
Yotsuya Fudoubou-san and Folciel-san
both said they didn't mean to hurt me!
Y-Yotsuya Fudoubou?
You guys calm down, too!
Adiel-san's just fine.
What are you saying?
Don't tell me... you can talk to them?!
What do you mean?
You two can't understand what
the angels and tengu are saying?
Of course not!
They're Anothers!
How could we know what they're saying?!
It's the same as being able
to talk to a dog or cat!
Who is this new kid?
You understand our words?
Who are you?
I-I'm just an employee of
the Shinjuku Ward Office...
Sister!
April 2nd
E-E...
Elope?!
An angel?
And a tengu?
This is unheard of!
They're from different races!
What's going on here?
My sister...
I can't believe this.
I thought they made a wonderful couple.
And they say it's not good to interfere
with someone else's romance.
Right?
Let's talk about this again in a few days.
Agreed.
What did they say?
Is it over?
Ow! Ow! Sister, that hurts!
Quiet!
From now on, you tell me what's going on!
I'm sorry!
Taroubou-san?
What's your name?
Miyako.
Miyako Arata.
I'll remember that.
In the end, I never did figure
out what was going on...
Seriously, what are you?
I don't know myself!
That was excellently done!
Something else is here!
Your knack for languages
hasn't changed a bit,
Abe no Seimei.
Huh?
Wh-What's he saying? Translate!
He's calling me...
Huh...?
What's wrong?
Hey, you okay?
I'm feeling a little dizzy.
Um...
Wh-Who is Abe no Seimei?
#2 "The White Nekomata of Kagurazaka"