Matsuoka Rin
Hello, everyone.
My name is Matsuoka Rin.
I previously went to Sano Elementary School.
I have a girly name, but I'm a boy.
Looking forward to being in this class!
Wow, this tree is huge.
Is it a cherry blossom tree?
It is.
Irritated Heart Rate!
Yeah?
So come spring, there'll be a
whole bunch of blossoms
falling down into the pool.
I wanna try swimming in a
pool of cherry blossoms.
The water will be too cold.
You should wait until
summer before swimming.
I was just joking around.
You don't have to get so serious.
I have a question for you.
Oh? What's up?
Looking to shut down the
transfer student on his first day?
No.
I believe we've been in the
same tournaments before.
Oh, you remembered me?
What's with that scary look?
I just happened to end up at
this school when I moved.
Coincidences are scary, huh?
My name is Matsuoka Rin.
I previously belonged to
the Sano Swimming Club.
I have a girly name, but I'm a boy.
Man...
Coincidence after coincidence.
I transferred to your school and even
ended up in the same swimming club.
Yep, this is a surprise.
Right, Haru?
He's really something!
Man, that was a good swim!
Matsuoka-kun.
The bicycle racks are this way.
Oh, I'm running home.
Running? How many kilometers
is it to your home?
Around three kilometers, I think.
See ya!
Each team must decide the
kind of garden you will make
and the kinds of flowers you will plant,
and draw an illustration.
Okay!
Hey, Nanase. Did you reconsider?
Reconsider what?
Swimming in a medley relay.
You interested in teaming
up for the next tournament?
I said that I only swim free.
You're so stubborn, Nanase.
Fine, you can swim free.
That means Tachibana has
to swim breast or back.
So we'll need one more person for...
I said that I only swim free,
so don't include me in your relay.
I said you can do free!
Uh...
Free... I mean...
I'm saying we should all
write our own messages on
the bricks around the garden.
We'll do it our way! Be free!
That's a great idea.
It is.
Nice one, Matsuoka!
Lovely!
Matsuoka-kun's kick is really powerful.
He's so fast!
Where you going, Haru?
Our bicycles are over there.
I'm running home.
That's so cool, Nanase-kun!
Hey, can I run with you?
If you can keep up.
Wait, Haru. Your bicycle...
Hey, Matsuoka-kun.
Are you swimming in a relay with
Nanase-kun and Tachibana-kun?
That's the plan.
I'm still waiting for a response though.
Let me join you, then!
No way. We're serious about this.
I'm serious, too.
I'm really fast.
So please? Pretty please?
Fine then.
You can join if you place first in
the next breaststroke time trial.
Really?!
Nanase-kun, did you hear that?
I'm gonna work really hard!
Practice is about to start.
Okay! Wait for me!
Hey, why is Nanase so obsessed with free?
He always says that he only swims free.
I don't think it's because
Haru likes to swim free.
Why does he say that, then?
I've never asked him,
but I think being in water
feels the most natural to Haru.
So he wants to swim free.
I don't get it.
Is there a way to get Nanase
to swim in the relay?
And why are you so obsessed
with swimming in a relay?
Me?
I...
Well, I have my reasons.
Friends
Thanks
I won't be attending middle school here.
I'm going to Australia.
I'm going to a swimming school.
Smile
What are you trying to do?
I'm going to become an Olympic swimmer.
Why didn't you tell us?
What about the relay?
I'll swim in the relay.
I'm leaving the day after the tournament.
So this will be the last time
the four of us swim together.
I only swim freestyle.
That's why you have
to swim in the relay.
This is our last chance.
Let's swim together, Nanase.
If you swim with me,
I'll show you a sight
you've never seen before.
Hey! Put some more effort into it!
Nagisa, you're bending your knees too much.
You don't need such a
powerful jump for a relay dive.
Makoto, your form is terrible!
You're not using your shoulders!
I'm glad that Goro-chan agreed to coach us,
but his training regimen is tough.
That's why everyone called
him Goro the Demon.
Rei, if you can't coast into the wall,
throw in one more kick!
Not like that!
Haruka, watch your timing as you fall in!
No!
You have to watch Rei more closely!
Come on!
You guys don't know what you're doing.
You leave me no other choice.
How do you like this?!
I see.
This lets them check their
form from multiple angles.
Haru-chan's being very proactive.
Yes, that's the way!
What is it, Rei-chan?
His form may be perfect now,
but this isn't the way I like
to see Haruka-senpai swim.
It was more beautiful before.
Yeah, this place brings back memories.
The locker room hasn't changed one bit.
My message is still here!
Forever Iwatobi!
Goro-chan, you spelled it wrong.
I'm not that picky!
It doesn't affect his ability to coach.
That's true.
Goro-chan's helped us
improve our exchanges.
Yep.
Let's keep up the hard work,
so we can face Rin again in the relay.
Yeah, that's the spirit!
Then it's time for me to get serious.
What?!
I'll work you hard! Very hard!
What's wrong, Rei-chan?
I don't understand.
Don't understand what?
Gou-san's brother.
Why did he suddenly decide
to swim the relay?
I'm not entirely sure,
but racing Rin-chan again
has gotten Haru-chan motivated,
so it's a good thing, right?
What if he loses again?
Winning isn't everything.
You made me run around
the summer festival
to make sure they wouldn't meet.
Detective Rei-chan did great work.
Stop joking around!
Why does it matter who's
swimming in their relay?
Our goal is to make it to the
nationals as the Iwatobi Swim Club.
I know.
But everybody keeps talking about Rin-chan.
I don't understand.
Sasabe
Excuse us!
Oh, thanks for coming.
Why are we having a hot pot
in the middle of summer?
Because that's what sports medicine
recommends for swimmers.
Hot...
This is my special Sasabe Hot Pot,
with plenty of protein and minerals.
Can you at least turn on
the air conditioning?
No such thing.
Can we not do this?
Why would you say that?
I promise that it's good, so dig in.
Wow, it really is good!
See? We came up with this when
I was in the swim club.
Oh, this is a tomato hot pot.
Right, you're a former Iwatobi Swim Club member, aren't you, Sasabe-san?
Yes, and I was the last swim club member.
This really works up a sweat.
We couldn't find any new members
so it was abolished after I graduated.
We brought the swim club back,
so you should have been
coaching us earlier.
Hey!
I was busy with my pizza delivery job.
Here, there's rice inside.
Give it to me!
Sorry, you okay?
Oh, no.
What are these?
Really old magazines?
Oh, it's okay.
I'll clean it up.
Water Fairy
Marin
Coach Sasabe,
are you the type who doesn't
like to throw this stuff away?
Here you go, Sasabe-san.
Ma—
Marin-chan...
The crab's on fire!
It's lit now!
Look, Rei-chan!
Don't point that at me!
I haven't done fireworks in a long time.
Me neither.
I-I was told that your previous
job involved swimsuits,
but I never thought...
No wonder you looked so familiar.
I-I was a big fan, Marin-cha—
Not another word on that topic.
I'm sure you understand.
Y-Yes.
What's this, Coach Sasabe?
Huh? Huh? What's up?
Did you find something?
Hey, don't snoop around!
Wait, Matsuoka-san!
It's a photo album of the swimming club.
Oh!
These bring back memories!
There's Gou-chan!
This is when we had a
barbeque behind the club.
What? Nobody told me about that.
It was before Rin-chan transferred.
Nanase-kun looked so mature even then.
You're supposed to smile for pictures.
Haru-chan is always smiling on the inside.
This is from the summer tournament
when we were in fifth grade.
Award
1st Place
Haru-chan won then too, didn't he?
Huh?
Is that my brother?
We didn't know Rin yet.
Wow! We met before we
got to know each other!
Connected by the red string of fate.
Do you call it that when it's between boys?
Oh, this is where Rin starts showing up.
This was around when he transferred.
It snowed hard that day
and we all made snowmen.
This was when you were
training for the tournament.
Rin was really fired up.
That's so my brother.
That was fun!
We should drop by again!
The hot pot was too hot.
But it tasted good.
Hey, Rei...
What's wrong, Rei?
Just what
happened between
the four of you?
The four of us?
Are you talking about Rin-chan?
You were all so close in those pictures.
You all looked so happy.
Well...
Rei.
I don't know if there's any point
in talking about this now.
But if you're interested,
I can tell you what happened.
Please tell me.
I'm tired of being the
only one on the outside!
Rei...
I'm part of the team, too!
Rei-chan...
Okay.
Rin was obsessed with relays from
the moment he joined our club.
He didn't tell us why until
right before the final.
It's finally time for the final.
Thanks for doing this for me, guys.
We're not doing it for you.
We're here because we want to be here.
Right...
Of course.
I wasn't sure if I should tell you guys,
but win or lose, the next
race will be our last.
So I'll talk.
My dad was one of the first members
of the Iwatobi swimming club.
When he was in sixth grade, he was
part of a winning medley relay.
His dream was to become
an Olympic swimmer.
But he ended up becoming a fisherman
and died in an accident.
I've decided to go to Australia.
But I thought, if I could join
my dad's swimming club first
and win the medley relay,
I might be able to share his dream.
I don't know who was on his team,
but I'm sure they were the best team around.
I hope that we can also become the best!
I know I'm being selfish,
but I want us to be the best team around!
We won the medley relay,
and Rin went to Australia.
Rin said that he would show me
a sight I'd never seen before.
And after we won the relay,
it felt like I really did see it.
I also felt like I saw
something completely new.
Yep, same here.
So if you swam together
in the relay and won,
why is your relationship so different now?
During the winter break of my
first year in middle school,
I ran into Rin while he was visiting.
Haru...
You're back?
Yeah.
You could have called.
Well, it'd be a little embarrassing...
How are you doing?
Still swimming?
Yeah, I joined the swim
club at our middle school.
Makoto also joined.
The school has a pretty big pool.
Hey, Haru.
Let's swim together again...
...to see who's faster.
Oh, it's Rin!
You're back?
Yeah.
Hey, we want to do some swimming.
Sure, it's reserved for us right now anyway.
Set.
Wait, Rin!
What's wrong?
You've been acting strange today.
I quit.
Huh?
I'm done swimming.
I never knew that happened.
I couldn't tell anyone back then.
So that's why you quit the
swim club in middle school.
Haru stopped swimming competitively
because he felt guilty about
what happened with Rin.
But didn't your race the other
day put an end to all that?
You're free now.
You can swim the way you want.
So why are you upset about losing?
And why is he entering the relay?
I don't understand!
Rei-chan...
Haru?
I don't understand either.
But...
For some reason,
I'm looking forward to racing Rin again.
Want some ice cream?
No, thanks.
Well, there's no point in thinking about it.
It's all in the past.
And we don't plan on getting
you involved, so don't worry.
How can you say that when
I'm already involved?!
Damn!
Matsuoka-senpai, you're doing great!
We'll easily beat Nanase-san and his team...
Senpai...
What?!
Rei's not practicing?!
That's unusual.
Oh!
Maybe the strawberry milk ice cream
I gave him yesterday was spoiled.
Then why did you give it to him?!
Uh, I don't think ice cream can spoil.
But if he ate something spoiled...
Mackerel?
I didn't give him anything.
Anyway, there isn't much
time left before regionals!
You need to practice hard!
Rei-chan couldn't have...
Matsuoka...
Someone named Ryugazaki is here.
Rin-chan-san, yes?
It's you.
I need to talk to you.
What do you want, Speedo Glasses?
Speedo Glasses?!
The first time I saw you was
during our joint training.
You were wearing a speedo.
So in my mind, you're Speedo Glasses!
Very well.
I'll show you that I'm not
your typical Speedo Glasses.
Next time: Furious All-out!
Furious All-out!
Your pronunciation is horrible.
Furious All-out.
All-out.
Perfect body.