Ta-da!
Why are you dressed like that?
Vacation! Vacation!
Why "vacation"?
What?
Did you not tell the Vice Commander yet, Hana?
I did.
I told her there'd be no Orgone energy
movement for the next three days...
So we're going on vacation!
Aren't you always going to the pool
and eating sweets on the job?
Those aren't vacations... Those are breaks!
Lately, it's been nothing but hard missions.
And sleeping in a train car every
night makes my shoulders stiff...
Do you understand the situation we're in?
That's why.
We don't know what tomorrow will bring,
so we need to take a vacation.
Don't you agree, Captain?
Well, if we were normal students,
we'd be on summer break now.
But given what's going on...
True, you guys may need a break.
Fine.
I'll give the Midsummer's Knights
permission for a vacation.
Us, too?
But make sure we can reach
you at any time, okay?
Pitz, she says we're going on vacation!
All right!
They're ready to use.
You fixed them, huh?
They're perfect!
That was faster than planned.
We worked hard.
Don't forget to give us that data!
You were the one who said
we should leave the Machine Goodfellow
testing to Amara and Moco, Puck.
But the development schedule
is lagging badly behind.
The pilot's mental state
greatly affects the Neural Maneuver
System's capabilities.
The method we're using is the best
way to obtain the data we need.
When humanity goes to space
for the Kivotos Plan,
that system will be necessary.
Is it falling behind because they're slacking,
or because they're uncooperative?
I have no data on that.
We must do something.
Is there some system that would allow us
to control people more directly?
I suppose you're the only one at the
company I can truly control...
Don't forget that I have your
emergency shutdown switch.
Puck does not lie.
Even if the Machine Goodfellows are fixed...
...we don't have Setsuna's capsule anymore.
The new engine series is
finally nearing completion.
It'll be great to have a spare.
Once this new model is complete,
this and the Nebula Engine will be a great help.
But in the scenario you have in mind,
this will do more than simply enhance
the intercept system, correct?
What did Alonzo say about that plan?
They're still running the numbers.
Give them a little more time.
Jeez... For the first time in ages,
we get to sleep in big beds!
Well, just remember to exercise restraint.
You're in the room next to mine?
I can't believe I have this huge room to myself!
Hana?!
The rooms are connected? No, wait...
They're the same room?
This is just one room with two entrances!
I think they're called connecting rooms.
C-Connecting rooms?
Connecting rooms!
You set us up, didn't you, Akari?
I'm all sweaty.
What?!
I'm taking a bath.
A bath...
Calm down!
Calm down, Captain!
A Maiden's Tear That Sparkled
Through the Night
"Hey, Akari... This isn't funny!
Hana and me in the same room?
You can't do that!"
I was expecting him to come
and say that, but I guess not.
What do you do on vacation?
Captain?
Y-Yes?
Goodnight.
G-Goodnight...
Hana?
What's wrong?
Are you crying?
Well, how did it go?
How did what go?
I showed restraint.
Restraint?
Yes, restraint...
I exercised perfect restraint!
Really?
Really.
Are you talking about last night?
Did something happen?
"Not a thing," he says...
Why?
"Why"?
I'm not sure,
but I think she might hate me.
Hate you? Hana?
She hates you?
Miss, have you ever considered modeling?
No photographs!
Just one...
Come with me, Hana!
Wait...
Of course she doesn't hate you.
When you go to sleep before she does,
she often goes over to kiss you.
Hey, Hana...
You want to get some ice cream?
Sure!
Do you like ice cream?
Yep.
Do you prefer mint chocolate chip or vanilla?
I like both of them...
But I guess mint chocolate chip?
Then, mint chocolate chip or the captain?
The captain!
Yeah, I thought so...
Wait.
They're still underage.
Perhaps I overestimated you...
Another complaint came in from
Technology and Research Division 3.
You took out some Machine Goodfellows
without permission, and got them destroyed.
And you also used the Orgone
energy capsules, didn't you?
Those are a valuable energy resource.
A single one can power the latest
mobile weaponry for decades.
What did you use them for?
What do you have to do to
drain a capsule completely?
The two of us fought a mock battle.
It was part of our pilot training.
We thought improving our skills
would benefit the company.
You're wasting time.
The Neural Maneuver Systems need
to be tailored to a specific
individual, or it's pointless.
The Machine Goodfellows are not your toys!
From now on, you are forbidden
to use them without permission.
And you must obey Technology
and Research Division 3.
Understood?
Don't disappoint me.
Welcome, Malkin-sama... Amarok-sama.
I don't think we need Masaki Kube anymore.
He's obnoxious.
I estimate that we need
Masaki Kube a bit longer.
Eliminating him will make controlling
Macbeth Enterprises more difficult.
When a man who's only lived a few decades
treats me like a little kid,
it irritates my real self more than anything!
Masaki Kube can still be useful.
The Globe Tanegashima base's Independent
Attack Force is a bigger problem.
They've stopped every attempt at an
abreaction via Machine Goodfellow.
I know that.
I know!
I've got a great idea.
The satellite, Legacy, was made by the
Seton Company as part of Kube's plan.
The stock satellite Kube built
for the escape into space,
that's halfway between the Earth and Moon?
I'd rather not waste food...
But if we dropped the Legacy on Tanegashima...
It'd blow the island away,
and cause problems for Kube.
Two birds with one stone?
I like it.
You can do it, can't you, Puck?
Understood.
Did you know that there's a
total lunar eclipse tonight?
I worked so hard to arrange a
romantic setting for them...
I guess they're still kids.
Hana was born of my race...
So I think she has the same nature...
The same peculiarity, you might say.
When we kiss someone,
we can feel what they're thinking, to an extent.
A kind of telepathy?
Yeah.
A telepathic kiss.
Telepathic kiss?
It's true that I could see what she
was thinking then, for a second.
Come to think of it, doesn't Hana only
kiss the captain when he's asleep?
If Hana does have that peculiarity...
Why are you crying?
Hana?
I thought I should just kill you...
I...
I love you, Daichi.
I want to kiss you, Hana.
I can't...
I can't!
If you knew my real self...
You'd hate me!
An emergency call?
Yes? This is Manatsu!
Emergency!
Midsummer's Knights, get here now!
Sir! It's an emergency!
What's going on?
The Seton Company's modified asteroid, Legacy,
in halo orbit around L1, has fired its engines.
It's starting to accelerate toward Earth.
It's been a little over a dozen hours
since Legacy went out of control.
It's less than a hundred meters in diameter.
Something that small can't be detected
by the space guard's early warning system!
Legacy will crash into Earth?
Legacy sighted.
Verifying predicted point of impact.
I've got it.
The south end of Japan... Tanegashima!
What?
Less than 420 seconds to impact!
The Legacy satellite weighs around 100,000 tons.
If it crashes, the energy output
will be in the megatons.
This base... No, all of
Tanegashima will be destroyed!
Is this an attack by them?
The Legacy is our stock satellite.
It's where we've kept the materials
needed for the Kivotos Plan.
Who's behind this?
The Legacy appears to have been set
on a course to strike Tanegashima.
They're after the Globe base?
Likely, yes.
What's going on?
No one can stop it now.
The low-orbit Impacters?
Citronnier is the closest!
It won't be able to intercept it.
A 100,000-ton satellite is heading
straight toward Tanegashima.
Can we intercept?
It's already moving six kilometers per second...
With that much kinetic energy,
even if we destroy it,
it won't change the damage it does!
Commander...
Tell the staff in the underground
blocks to stay there!
Is there no way to evacuate the civilians?
150 seconds to impact!
There's no time!
Hana!
What?
I'm detecting a high-intensity heat source
coming from the Tanegashima coast!
The Blume?
The Legacy satellite has been destroyed.
The Blume's beam weapon?
The Blume?
Did the Blume do that?
Now you've done it, Princess...
Thank goodness...
That was the Blume's Orgone beam.
Then Hana did this?
Hana...
I'm not the girl you think I am.
Hana?
Stay back!
Hana!
Hana...
Hana runs away from us,
and by chance, finds Setsuna in the city.
Amara and Moco from the
Planetary Gears find her.
Run, Hana! They're after you!
Big changes are coming for Hana,
Setsuna, and Macbeth Enterprises.
Next time, on episode 15 of Captain Earth:
True Self
True Self.
Earth Engine, scramble!