Good morning.
The karuta club is looking for more members!
Let's start a competitive karuta club!
Please come see Ayase Chihaya in class 1-2!!
Let's play competitive karuta together!
Good morning.
We're the karuta club.
Would you like to join the karuta club?
Please hear us out.
We're the karuta club.
Please give us a try.
Oh, that person...
would look wonderful in a hakama!
Really?
Hold on!
Um, would you like to play karuta with us?
You would look great in a hakama!
N-No, thanks...
New Year's is enough for me.
Hey, are you interested in karuta?
It's a pretty intense sport.
You must be joking.
You'll understand if you give it a shot.
We need one more member
before we can become an official club.
I didn't think that everyone
would ignore us...
It'll be fine!
We'll find someone perfect!
This problem is looking at molecular mass.
When there are an equal number of
protons, electrons, and neutrons...
Hmm?
We'll pick up here next week.
Make sure you review the
material we covered.
Chi-chan, the Empress was
giving you the death stare.
Huh?  Really?
You were sound asleep.
What's going on?
I woke up early to recruit
members for the karuta club,
so I didn't eat breakfast...
Oh, it must be hard for you and Komano-kun.
First, you flip the cards
over and shuffle them.
Next, each player takes 25 cards
and places them on their side of the field.
Hundred Poets Competitive Karuta
The remaining 50 cards will not be used.
The player's field is 87 centimeters
long and three rows deep.
You're really enthusiastic
about this, Desktomu-kun.
I have to make up for lost time.
That's right.
We'll start practicing today.
Ayase, you should eat lunch.
Y-You could hear that?
The whole class could.
You're out of korokke sandwiches?
Can I get coffee milk?
Sure thing.
Thanks.
They're out of yakisoba sandwiches.
Here you go.
Ma'am, can I get two anpan?
Here you are.
Anpan
Huh?
It's Porky!
Porky?
You can buy your pork buns after I beat you!
Chihaya Furu
Verse 8
The
Sounds
of the
Waterfall
So basically, the player
who takes cards faster
and reduces the number of cards
on their side to zero, wins.
I understand what happens when you
take a card on your own side,
but what happens when you take
from the opponent's side?
When that happens, you can choose
one of the cards on your side
and send it to the opponent's side.
It's called "sending cards," right?
Right, sending cards is
a critical part of the game that
can turn the tide in a match.
You're also allowed to send cards
if your opponent commits a fault.
If you touch a card while the second
verse is being read, it's a fault.
If you touch a card on the opponent's side
when the correct card is
on your side, it's a fault.
The same goes for when you
touch a card on your side
when the correct card is
on the opponent's side.
However, if you touch the wrong
card on the correct side,
it's not a fault.
Huh?  Really?
Yep.  For example...
Taichi!
Pork!
I found pork!
Pork?
Look!
You're right!
He's a student at our high school...
Wait, that getup...
He's on the tennis team?
Looks like it.
So?  Why are we hiding?
Oh, just because.
I asked him to join the karuta club earlier,
and he ran away.
But this time...
Hey!
If you have experience,
you should join the karuta club!
Join!
If you have experience,
you should join the karuta club!
Chihaya!
What's wrong with you?
Huh?
Hey, long time no see.
Shut your mouth, fatty!
Chihaya's running late!
Oh!  You're...
Taichi's in the karuta club with me!
I really want you to join us, Porky!
My name is Nishida!
I already told you that I'm not
going to join the karuta club!
Nishida, did you quit playing karuta?
You were really good.
Being good at karuta doesn't mean anything.
Plus, it's lame.
That's not true!
I played tennis in middle school.
I plan on continuing in high school.
You look good.
I know.
Besides, if I wanted to play karuta,
I'd go to the Karuta Society.
There's no reason to join a club at school.
Please!
If Porky joins, our karuta
club can be really strong!
I'm sure you can also become really strong!
Won't happen.
I'm not interested.
You still refuse?
I need to go to practice.
And my name isn't Porky.  It's Nishida!
Bye.
Hey, wait a moment!
Just forget about him.
Let's go back to the clubroom.
Taichi...
Nice!
Way to go, Nishida!
Keep it up!
Yes!
Yamakawa, don't hold back on your serve.
Understood!
Wow...
Porky is really athletic!
Easy!
This is easy!
Nothing like...
Nothing like what happened back then!
My only thought as the!
Huh?
My only thought as I!
Is this...
The hazy early morning mist!
Karuta?  The timing for
multi-syllable cards?
One more volley!
Yes, please!
The world offers no escape!
Huh?
Okay, switch!
Go get the ball!
Y-Yes, sir!
I hide in the mountains,
only to hear the haunting cry of a deer.
Porky, you should play karuta!
Don't you know when to give up?!
But you're using tennis as
a substitute for karuta!
That's not fair to tennis!
Th-That's none of your business!
Stop bugging me!
We'll be waiting for you in the clubroom!
Nishida!
Your legs are slowing down!
Keep your eyes on the ball!
You're too slow!
What's wrong, Nishida?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I need to go home now.
Oh, I see.
The second-years are next!
Like I was saying earlier,
it isn't a fault
when you touch the wrong card but it's
on the same side as the correct card.
Yes.
So now...
Take these two cards which start the same.
"The world offers no change" and
"The world offers no escape."
They're called "like cards."
You have to wait until the fifth word
before you know which card to take.
However, if both cards are on the same side,
as soon as you hear "The world,"
you can take either one.
I see...
However, this also makes it
easier for your opponent.
When the like cards are on your side,
it might be a good idea
to send one of them
to the opponent's side.
Excuse me.
Porky!
It's Nishida!
Don't get the wrong idea!
I'm not here to join!
What?!
I wanted to see what you're doing here,
but it looks like you're
at a grade school level.
These two are beginners.
They have to start somewhere.
If you join,
our club will be much stronger!
No way!
It's pointless if I'm the
only one who's any good!
Is he really so special?
Number two in the country.
This was back when we were in grade school.
Oh.
Karuta is about talent!
It doesn't matter how hard we practice!
We can never beat Wataya Arata!
Well, give it your best shot.
I'll be giving tennis my best shot.
Bye.
Wait.
What is it?
Chihaya, play a match against Nishida.
Huh?
I refuse!
It's a waste of time.
You're gonna run away?
Chihaya never gave up on karuta.
Why don't you see for yourself
how strong someone can become
when they put in the effort?
Or are you scared of losing?
Come to think of it,
you struggled against
Chihaya when she was just a
beginner back in grade school.
Hard to say who would win now.
Hell no!
Porky, let's play karuta!
Promise me this...
If I win the match,
you'll never bother me again!
Plus, you'll have to buy me
pork buns for a month!
Bring it!
Memorization time is over.
Thank you for this match.
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
What is this?
Here comes spring, now the flower blooms
The introduction.
The match begins once he finishes reading this poem.
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
Feel the sorrow...
Though I prayed...
My only thought as I am put out to sea...
Amazing!
He's taken three straight
cards off Chihaya-chan.
I was worried that I might
have lost my touch,
but my body feels so light.
I guess all that tennis helped.
Come on, Chihaya...
You don't have time to be smiling.
That's right...
Whenever I won, people would praise me.
to tell the people in the capital
that I make for the islands
Long last we meet,
only for me to leave hurriedly,
for I could not recognize you, like
the moon hidden behind the clouds
Good job, Yusei!
You'll make it to class A in no time!
First, you'll need to win
the national tournament.
I started playing karuta because it was fun.
Big Helping
But at some point, I started playing to win.
National Champion or Bust
And then...
He showed me what a difference talent made.
That's why I ran away.
Ran away from karuta...
Chihaya-chan took another card!
Nishida-kun has 17 cards left.
Ayase has 15 left.
When did I fall two cards behind?
burning brightly by night, yet extinguished by day
No, I need to focus!
Turn the tide!
Since I could not hide...
He's good.
He targeted a card on the opponent's
side to turn things around.
Now, which card will he send?
He's going to send a card.
Yes.
is that I have no way to tell you in person
After I determined
She's worried about the like cards?
on a long September night, and then I saw a dawn moon
After I heard
Okay!
on a long September night,
and then I saw a dawn moon
Chihaya is too obvious.
He read her like a book.
Huh?
Chihaya-chan was ready to take the like cards
"After I determined" and
"After I heard" together.
Oh, I see.
The technique he just showed us.
people would always ask if
I was pining for someone
Though my hatred...
Since the dew atop...
Chihaya-chan...
Nishida-kun is making a comeback.
He's up one card.
Chihaya is usually better towards
the end of a match,
and she's still losing.
I'm starting to remember how this works.
Everything feels so familiar.
I'm so glad!
You don't hate karuta!
Don't forget your promise!
Uh-huh!
So I'm not going to lose!
it is as though pearls have been
strung across the autumn plain
Look—
—for the sound...
Impassioned was your...
She's fast!
Incredible!
In th—
—e sleepy spring sunlight,
Isn't that a two-syllable card?!
Were you camping it?!
She wasn't.
Then how did she move so fast?!
There are cards where Chihaya
can hear the next syllable.
She has incredible senses.
Hear the next syllable?
Five cards left on my side.
Four cards left on the opponent's side.
Those "After I" cards I split
should be read soon...
is that I have no way to tell you in person
After I determined
One on the opponent's side.
on a long September night, and then I saw a dawn moon
After I heard
One on my side.
Time to get pumped!
Read the one on my side!
The one on my side!
After I determined to abandon...
That's it!
What?!
She got it!
I was camping the card,
and I still couldn't take it.
Damn.
She's this much better than me now?
She just happens to really like karuta...
Was this how I used to play karuta?
Were my eyes so focused?
Good practice!
Yes.  Good practice, everyone.
Thank you very much!
That was an incredible match!
I learned a lot!
You're so good, Porky!
Bye.
Huh?
Nishida.
Hey, why don't you join our karuta club?
To be honest, I'm not good enough
to practice with Chihaya.
We need someone as strong as you.
Hey!
Taichi, it's okay.
Sorry, Porky.
I'll stop pestering you about joining.
But this was a lot of fun!
Thanks for playing karuta with me!
Nishida-kun!
Huh?
I thought you went home?
What are you doing here?
Don't tell me that you
were skipping practice?
Uh-oh.
Nishida-kun, explain yourself.
Coach, I'm...
quitting the tennis team.
Huh?
You're quitting?
I want to play karuta!
Porky...
Nishida-kun, are you serious?
Yes.
These guys are telling me that
they need me to start the club.
And karuta is still...
Tennis can never replace karuta!
I understand.
I expect you to submit
your resignation shortly.
We finally have our last member!
Thank you, Nishida!
But in return for joining, Mashima...
Make her stop calling me "Porky"!
Huh?  Why do you want me to stop, Porky?
Stop calling me "Porky"!
Fine, Porky.
Let's play another match!
Bring it!
I'm gonna get revenge!
Wait!  Stop calling me "Porky"!
Okay.
The karuta club...
My fellow players...
Ms. Miyauchi, We have 5 Karuta Club Members!!
Captain 1-2 Ayase Chihaya
Vice Captain 1-1 Mashima Taichi
Secretary 1-2 Komachi Tsutomu
Equipment Manager 1-8 Nishida Yusei
Treasurer 1-6 Oe Kanade
I'm...
...no longer alone!