Rule the Court
I'm sure you're sick of hearing this,
Seijoh!
but make sure you serve strong.
It can't be helped if their
#10 scores some points.
Seijoh!
Limit his path and pick up the ball.
Right!
You guys are strong.
Seijoh!
Yeah!
Fly
Just remember, don't let Oikawa do
whatever he wants with his serves.
Just get it up.
Get it up, no matter what.
Then, someone will connect.
Right!
If an enemy you must defeat one
day is called an archenemy,
then for Karasuno, Aoba
Johsai is indeed that.
You are going to be the ones
who are going to win this
battle against your archenemy.
Yeah!
The final set...
We're going to surpass Aoba Johsai.
We're going to surpass them with this team!
Karasuno, fight!
Yeah!
Haikyu!!
Episode 23: "Team"
This is finally it...
Yeah...
The set where they settle things with Seijoh.
Nice serve!
Go, Asahi!
All right!
Oikawa-san, nice serve!
Get it up...
Get it up, no matter what.
We can't let them gain
the lead this early.
Please! Cut them off with this one!
That speed...
It's past the net! It's coming direct!
It's right in front of me,
but my reaction's delayed.
Kyotani! Direct!
All right!
Great, great, Kentaro! Push it,
push it, Kentaro. One more time!
Good. It looks like Mad Dog-chan's
engine's still warmed up.
Oikawa's serves are definitely a problem.
Please... Cut them off.
Karasuno, fight!
Oikawa, one more! Nice serve!
All right!
It's up!
Cover!
Yeah!
Tanaka, nice kill!
They somehow managed to stop it.
Thanks!
Ryu, well done!
All right!
Tsukishima! You're serving next!
Oh, right.
Aoba Johsai                 Karasuno
Tsukishima, nice serve!
Got it!
Mad Dog-chan!
Yeah!
Great, great, Kentaro! Push it,
push it, Kentaro! One more time.
Nice kill!
Kyotani has a lot more energy
when he's on the front line.
Hopefully he'll be able to
keep it up until the end.
An ace with both power and technique...
Not only is his attack powerful,
but that #16 is also
a troublesome decoy.
And then Oikawa's serves
that rack up points...
If we can't counter those,
it's going to break us.
Both of us are high in ability.
The more we struggle for dominance,
the more fatal the consequences will be
when one of us loses our balance.
Rule the Court
Hang on and don't let go!
All right!
Aoba Johsai                  Karasuno
The final set's also really close.
But no one's taken a significant lead yet.
They've got to fight real hard
not to get left behind right now.
Asahi! Get this one!
Yeah!
N—
Nice course!
There's no way you could
have gotten that one.
We'll get the next one!
Aoba Johsai               Karasuno
Asahi, one more! Nice serve!
Yeah.
Nice receive!
Yeah!
Damn it...
And there he is again.
Oikawa, nice serve!
Yes! Now score and
cut off Oikawa's serves!
Chance ball! Tanaka!
Yeah!
A quick's coming!
Nice receive!
Kyotani, get the last!
Right! Right!
Tanaka-san...
Blocked out!
All right! They cut it off!
Yes!
Nice block!
Tsukki and Tanaka switched
up blocks just now.
Yeah.
Did they read that a straight was coming?
Great job, Tsukishima!
I knew it...
Tanaka was getting into
it with that #16, right?
You mean he was picking a fight?
Like in the second set,
he kept targeting their #16 and wiping.
There was no block for a cross,
so he went for the more narrow
straight... right by #16.
Seriously? I didn't notice.
It looks like their #16 is fighting back,
and hitting straights on the
side where Tanaka is.
I think Tsukishima also figured that out.
Great job reading that, Tsukishima!
How'd you come up with that?
It was nothing.
This is a chance to gain momentum.
Don't let it go to waste!
Got it!
Nice receive.
That #16's coming!
Get it back yourself.
Out!
All right!
Yes! Here it is!
Aoba Johsai                   Karasuno
Yeah! They turned it around!
Keep it up!
Yeah!
I think that they managed to
rile up #16 pretty well.
Don't tell me Ryu did that on purpose!
No, Ryu may have been challenging him,
but that wasn't his goal.
That's just his nature.
So it's like Tsukishima was able
to take advantage of that nature.
Now we see a crack in the
apparently infallible Seijoh.
This is our chance to break through!
We're gonna push forward!
Yeah!
Haikyu!!
Who's that? A high school kid?
Apparently, he just wants to practice.
I saw him in another
group on Saturday.
If he's in high school,
doesn't he have club activities?
He's probably the type that doesn't
get along with the rest of the club.
Is he going through his rebellious stage?
I'm surprised he's playing a team sport.
I'm sure he's playing because there's
something he likes about it.
Ah, Kiyoshi-san. Hi.
Otherwise, he wouldn't be
practicing here like this.
Japan! Japan! Japan! Japan!
W-Well, we always need people,
so I think it's okay.
Not to mention, he's better than us.
Wha?!
I wouldn't lose to him!
Aw, you're all mad.
Shut up.
Tsukishima, one more! Nice serve!
Got it!
Mad Dog-chan!
All right!
Aoba Johsai                  Karasuno
The time out didn't help, did it?
I don't think so.
Seijoh's got plenty of players,
so why don't they switch?
Switch!
Hey.
Go, Iwa-chan. Now.
Calm down if you want to
get back out on the court.
Hurry up and pull yourself together.
We don't have anything left after this.
Shut up. Like I care.
All right!
Yahaba, don't push him too much.
Sorry, but no.
You let the opponent provoke you,
got pissed off, and then fizzled out.
Talk about lame.
Ah?
You had the nerve to come back,
and then got to go right into a match.
Some guys who have a problem with that.
Like me.
But...
It's not like he caused a problem,
so I guess it doesn't matter as long as
we can use him in a match.
Will he be able to keep up at practice?
He'll have blanks to fill in.
Including communication.
Well...
Those aren't the moves of someone
who hasn't been practicing.
I thought he was pretty cold,
both to you and to us.
But that's not the problem.
Left!
The players we need in order to win
are chosen as regulars.
One-touch!
Cover! Cover!
Got it!
You were chosen...
So do your job right.
I think Yahaba's gonna get bitten.
Hope he's okay.
You go stop him.
Nope.
Well, that's just a front.
If you track dirt onto our senpais' stage,
I'll never forgive you.
You...
I thought you were more
shallow than that.
You're not wrong there.
I may be shallow,
but I respect our senpais.
As long as you're on the court, any
point won or lost belongs to the team.
So come on. Help us out.
Got it!
Center!
Kunimi-chan!
Kunimi's attack is... possibly...
A feint!
Ryu!
All right!
Aoba Johsai           Karasuno
Nice kill!
Good job reading that, Kageyama.
Thanks.
Huh? I guess he's back.
So he's coming back...
That was fast.
I'm sure it's a gamble for Seijoh, though.
All right!
Out! Out!
D-Don't mind!
Uwamushi Jr High         Minamisan Jr High
He's not doing well today.
What should we do?
No one's got more power
than he does, either...
But if the situation gets any worse,
he's going to get really annoying.
Let's see how things go.
Tanaka, nice serve!
Yes.
Nice receive!
Mad Dog-chan!
Oikawa's a total sadist.
Absolute trust with no words involved...
It's been a while since you started
coming here, Lone Wolf High School Kid.
I heard you were in Aoba Johsai.
That's a pretty strong school.
I actually couldn't get into that school.
Running away from the team,
and practicing elsewhere without rest...
You're sure taking the easy way out.
What?!
A team is reliable and
also annoying, at times.
They're strong allies,
yet cause a lot of stress.
You can't even deal with that,
and you think you're playing volleyball?
You need to face the team,
and have the team face you.
If you're able to do that, you'll
both clash and become even stronger.
All right!
And if you're able to do that,
just know that you're lucky.
Teams like that don't exist everywhere.
All right!
Looks like a great team.
Make sure you face them properly.
Sorry! I'll get the next one!
Yeah!
Aoba Johsai                Karasuno
Kyotani, you're serving next.
Nice hit.
Yeah.
If that #16 was in Karasuno,
I wonder what I'd do in this situation.
Oikawa...
He truly is amazing and terrifying.
All right, let's get this one!
Yeah!
With that play, it appears as
though their oddball #16
now fits in with the rest of the team.
That's not good.
We haven't lost
when it comes to our strength as a team.
We've only just begun.
Yeah.
Kyotani, nice serve!
Ryu!
Yeah!
Nice receive!
Watacchi, nice!
Counter!
All right!
Damn it...
Aoba Johsai               Karasuno
They're tied!
Seijoh caught up!
Kyotani, one more!
All right!
Chance ball!
Hit it, Asahi!
Damn it... Sorry.
All right!
You're awesome, Asahi-san.
It got totally knocked out.
Thanks!
Who's the senpai here?
With Hinata's spike,
if the course is narrowed or
read, it'll get picked up.
Yeah...
We have to use Hinata better...
All right!
Karasuno             Aoba Johsai
Geh, again?
I feel like my lifespan get shorter
Oikawa, one more! Nice serve!
every time Oikawa-kun's
time to serve comes around.
Oikawa-san, we're counting on you!
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
I'm sure everyone on this
side feels that way...
We're almost done with
the middle of the set...
Losing a lot of points
right now would be fatal.
Stop him now!
Bring it!
Daichi-san!
I can't believe he got that.
Chance ball!
Damn it!
A quick is coming!
Kindaichi!
Don't mind!
If you have a request, tell me!
If I tell Oikawa-san, he'll figure it out
and if I don't, he won't get it.
Say, Oikawa-san.
With that one, it's a bit
hard to sync or like, uh...
Okay, got it.
But try again without changing anything.
Again?
Your point of impact,
is about one ball's length ahead..
Great, great, Yutaro! Push it,
push it, Yutaro! One more time!
Yes!
A really sharp wipe...
Kindachi's movements are
different from the Inter-High.
Don't mind! We'll stop it with this one!
Concentrate!
Karasuno         Aoba Johsai
Break!
We're in the latter half and
Seijoh's turning it around.
It's now an all-out war
between the teams.
Yes...
And the one that brings the
whole Aoba Johsai team up
is Oikawa-kun, right?
Oikawa-san, one more! Nice serve!
Yeah, I know, Sensei.
Our team's even stronger than this.
Bring it!
Come on!
Oikawa-san, one more! Nice serve!
Sorry!
Tsukishima, get it!
Push through, Kindaichi!
All right!
Thanks, Tsukishima!
Tsukishima, you're serving next!
Go wild out there, Shoyo!
Right!
Cut it off with this one!
Yeah!
The Great King really is amazing.
Do you really understand that?
I can at least tell something
is amazing about him.
But!
If I'm here, you're invincible.
That's super awesome.
Seriously...
All of your spikes kept getting picked
up, so what are you talking about?
What'd you say?!
Baseless courage... Nice.
Th-There is though... there's base.
All right!
Nice receive!
Mad Dog-chan!
Nice one-touch!
Got it!
Bring it to me!
I flew too far forward...
The net's super close.
Isn't the toss a bit close to the net?!
It's basically right above the net!
No one's there!
Up front!
Slam it down!
We're playing the final set, score 17 to 16...
It's really close.
Yeah.
We're gonna win, no matter what!
Bring it all to me!
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"The Absolute Limit Switch."
Episode 24 "The Absolute Limit Switch"
Don't just ignore me!