Shiratorizawa
I haven't doubted once that we would win.
But right now,
I am completely sure
that I want to crush you.
All right!
Shiratorizawa                   Karasuno
One more point! One more point!
One more point!
Haikyu!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Episode 09: The Volleyball Idiots
Go!  One more!
Ugh, it hurts.
This seriously sucks.
Don't come in feeling like a decoy.
Stop, then jump up.
Oh, by the way...
Generally, when you're
one-on-one with a spiker,
rather than lining up
with their bodies to block,
if you line up with their
dominant hand...
Being too comfortable can be scary.
To think that the weirdo quick
that we thought was unstoppable
would be stopped...
Yeah!
Damn it! One more time!
Did you just change which course
you were going to close?
So you noticed? Not bad.
Tsukki! Jump some blocks for me! Okay?!
He's not just being calm.
He's concentrating.
Not on how the match is going...
he's probably thinking about what
he's going to do when he gets back.
Tsukki!
The glasses guy from Karasuno's back!
It's too late! It's all going
to be over with one more point.
It's not gonna end!
Tsukishima—
The bleeding has stopped.
They immobilized the part that
was dislocated rock hard.
Because it was my pinky, it'll
affect my play extremely little.
That basically sums it up.
To think a day would come
when he'd strongly express how
much he wants to be in the game.
Is Kei okay?!
Um... He hurt his pinky, so they taped
it to his ring finger and immobilized it,
and apparently he can continue playing.
But I'm pretty sure...
The pain hasn't stopped at all.
I bought you some time...
Though, to be honest,
Yamaguchi actually bought more time than me.
Well, thanks for your honesty.
Be Courageous Warriors
One more point! One more
point! One more point!
It's probably going to be a jump float serve.
We need to move up our defenses.
If we can stop them here, it'll
be Asahi's turn to serve next.
Yunohama, nice serve!
Daichi-san!
All right!
If they didn't have that guy, Karasuno's
defense would be more full of holes.
Nice receive!
All right!
He read me.
Looks like that's probably
not going to work anymore...
Shiratorizawa                 Karasuno
A dump right there?!
Good! Good! Though you guys are
taking years off my life, damn it.
We're counting on you, Tsukishima.
Well done.
Being able to play like you normally
do in this situation is impressive.
Right!
Tsukishima!
Look at you, showing up
like some hero, you jerk!
Um... about when we do a 3-person block...
Not phased one bit, are you?
Tsukishima!
We're counting on you!
All right.
Now both Tobio and Kei are back.
Now for the counterattack!
We're gonna get through this!
Yeah!
I doubt you would, but you
don't need to hold back.
If you don't think I'm going to,
then don't say it. And I won't.
Shirabu.
You remember our promise, don't you?
Will you be able to use me
mercilessly in any situation?
Yes!
Serving toward the end while
being at a disadvantage...
I really hate this!
Come on, please! Make this...
Don't be on your guard!
Give it all you've got!
Give it everything you've got, Asahi!
To think that the fact that no one's
looking this way would be so reassuring...
All right! Bring it!
Yes!
Yes! Yes!
Give it to me!
Again?!
Go! Wakatoshi-kun!
His right hand!
This is so stupid...
I'm not Hinata.
To think that I actually want
to fight until the end...
One touch!
They managed to stop it again.
What happened to Four-Eyes?
At the first practice match,
I thought he was just a tall guy
that was slightly intelligent.
Nice, Nishinoya!
Chance ball!
Ushijima-san!
Time difference from the right.
We're going to open it up!
Nishinoya-san's field of view.
Nice receive!
I'm surprised he's able to make
these decisions so quickly
and still be able to instruct others.
Asahi-san!
Tsutomu!
Nice! Get the last!
One more time...
He's planning to hit it...
Ushiwaka three times in a row!
The top of the net...
Yes!
This is our chance!
My legs are so friggin' heavy...
Don't give up, legs!
I'm going to hit it!
Tsukishima's doing a slide hit?!
He's faking!
He's figured me out...
But I managed to gain you a few seconds.
I-It's a break!
All right!
Shiratorizawa                Karasuno
We did it!
They're at a match point!
One more point, and they'll
beat Shiratorizawa!
I think they might just be able to do it!
We've been pushing them
ever since Kei came back!
Go, Karasuno!
I guess it's no surprise that
Shiratorizawa took a timeout.
Karasuno really is versatile.
I've never seen Glasses do a slide
hit... Even if he was just a decoy.
We can't easily abandon a near
perfect time difference attack,
and Shiratorizawa's not going
to change their style
of strengthening individual strengths.
That's why we're called
powerhouse schools now.
Who would've ever thought
you'd set us up like that!
But Karasuno probably doesn't have
a style they need to protect.
I'm so happy, Tsukishima!
They may have had one when
they were a powerhouse school.
Hey, sit down and rest on the
bench, even for a moment.
So they don't hesitate to try new things.
They even gave up that miracle-like
quick immediately and made it new.
The old and dependable Shiratorizawa...
The new and reckless Karasuno...
Either one of them winning
is going to piss me off,
so they should both lose.
You really are a crappy guy.
Could you stop calling me a "crappy guy"?!
Pick between that or a "shitty guy."
Well, then I guess I choose "crappy"!
Don't let up til the end!
I'm sure all of their legs are
at their limits by now.
It's obvious for Ushiwaka,
who's hit so many times,
but for Karasuno's offense,
they've done starting runs more than spikes.
That may look like a lot
of needless movement,
but that's the primary factor
in how Karasuno's offense is prying
through Shiratorizawa's blocks.
Since Tanaka, Azumane and Sawamura
have been playing the whole time,
I'm sure they're beyond their limits by now.
Nishinoya-san, are you okay?
Yeah. I've been able to
rest here and there, so...
Ushijima's scored about 40 points.
He was able to score almost
half the points all by himself.
Despite being thoroughly marked,
and a lot of the tosses
being harder ones to hit...
I knew that...
I knew that, but...
Ushijima Wakatoshi is beyond impressive.
Ushijima-san.
When you said to get tosses
up to you at any time,
you meant that for while
you're still of use, right?
Wha?! Hey, I don't know what's going
on, but how could you say that?
That's right.
Let's go.
Fire it up, fire it up, Karasuno!
Get it, get it, Karasuno!
If volleyball was a one-on-one sport,
we wouldn't be able to win
against Shiratorizawa.
We're smaller, and our individual attack
strength falls short in comparison.
But there are six of us on the court.
If we win, it's not because
a miracle happened.
Our concept won't change until the very end!
We're going to punch our way through!
Yeah!
We've done everything we can to this point.
Fight! Fight! Fight!
We've both used up all of our timeouts.
Let's end this thing!
Let's calm down and score that point.
The next time you leave that court...
Yeah!
...return as victors!
Haikyu!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Shiratorizawa                      Karasuno
Nice serve, Asahi!
Here comes that all-out serve again!
End it here. End it with this one!
Yes!
They did—
All right!
Such a waste!
Sorry!
Don't mind!
The serve toss was fine,
but I was a little careless
when stepping into the jump.
And now,
Ushijima-kun is serving.
Sorry.
Don't mind!
When we get back, you're
gonna be serving 100 times.
Neither side has any intention
of putting their guard up.
That's lucky for us, but also a waste.
I mean, it's all for naught if they miss.
But just by hitting
a powerful serve itself becomes
pressure for the other side.
Huh?
A jump serve is a very risky serve.
But a serve that's done by chance,
or a serve that's guaranteed to go in...
It's not about picking that,
but a team that's able to complete a
chance serve right now is a strong team.
A team that's able to choose
to do a chance serve right now
is a team that can become stronger.
Of course, it's better if they don't miss,
and of course it's great
if the other side misses,
but it's valuable just to take that chance,
as long as they're concerned.
All right!
Leon-san!
Don't jump at it. Don't jump at it.
Gimme!
Ushijima-san!
He's stopped!
From above the block?!
All right!
Nice kill, Ushijima!
That wasn't about height,
it was about timing.
Ushijima! Ushijima!
They jumped into that block a bit too early.
I'm sure the fact that everyone is
so tired and panicked is a factor,
but more importantly,
there's Ushiwaka's mid-air form,
which makes it look
as though he's floating...
If you have good form, it gives
you more of an advantage mid-air.
What the hell?
Does stress or being out of stamina
mean absolutely nothing to Ushiwaka?
He's definitely some kind
of monster or mutant,
but the name we're the most satisfied with...
is that he's a "super volleyball idiot."
Shiratorizawa             Karasuno
Nice serve!
Bring it!
Sorry, it's short!
It's plenty!
Bring it on!
Perfect!
All right!
It's rare to be so small
and be such a main force.
He's almost like the Little Giant—
Bigger will always be stronger.
That is nature's logic.
Nice serve, Kageyama!
Go, Kageyama!
Nice serve!
We're counting on you!
It's good...
This is it!
If we make this point, we win!
Chance ball!
Jump towards the direction
that smells like satisfaction.
I...
With my forty years...
I want to deny you...
Karasuno's #10.
I read it right!
All right!
Nice kill, Tendo!
Be Courageous Warriors
Tendo! Tendo!
Karasuno's #10 is being
a lot quieter than usual.
He's thinking.
He just got shut down
on a deuce on the final set,
and since he can't waste time being sad,
he's thinking about the next step.
Don't mind! We'll get the next one.
Right!
How disgusting.
Please hold up...
We'll have a chance in the next rotation.
Shiratorizawa            Karasuno
Go, Tanaka!
All right!
Yes! Just one more point!
Please! Make this one!
Here we go!
Leon-san!
Got it!
All right!
He wasn't able to jump...
Looks like #10's legs are about done, too.
You jerk!
Forgive it, Hinata.
At this point, Karasuno is basically
moving through sheer spirit.
Wakatoshi's on the front line now,
so this is our chance to break!
Here we go!
You want consecutive points so bad
that you can almost taste them.
The moment you obtain them
is not always dramatic.
I know...
I know that it's going to fall right there,
but my legs won't move...
Nishinoya...
Nishinoya!
All right!
Nice kill, Asahi!
What the heck was that?!
Wow...
Thanks, Nishinoya!
Karasuno can depend on me!
But... There are things
that I can't do, as well.
I know I'm asking for the
impossible when I say this,
but even if your thighs were to split open,
I'm counting on you guys
in the mid-air battles.
Right!
Yeah!
Shiratorizawa            Karasuno
I'm counting on you!
Right.
We've basically used up all our
options for switching out players.
But right now, the setter's on the back line,
Hinata, nice serve!
and there are three attackers in front.
Along with Hinata's super-fast back
attack, there are two attackers.
This rotation is 100% a
super attack-style rotation.
If you guys can find a chance to attack...
With Nishinoya out and Sawamura in front,
receiving is also really
light on this rotation, too.
Everything is riding on the blocks.
Fly
Hayato!
It went in.
Hinata, change positions with me!
Time difference attacks don't
work against Four-Eyes...
Then we'll get through the
center with sheer speed!
They're going for the center
at a time like this?!
When you have a brilliant ace,
their very existence is a brilliant decoy!
Go, Taichi!
Hear me out, Tsukki!
Kuroo-san yelled at me to read block again.
But don't you think it
feels better to be able
to shut out your opponent,
whether it's by luck or intuition?
That does feel good,
but I hate the ball getting
through even more.
If you go after the ball, even if
your reaction is slightly behind,
the ball won't completely make it through.
That sounds like something you'd say.
You probably think it's better
if you look cool, don't you?
You just don't get it.
This is the problem with you kids.
We're only two years apart!
Listen up, brat!
Read blocking is a block that consists of
restraint and persistence, but it's also...
The block where you laugh last.
One touch!
It almost seems like Tsukishima-kun's
reacting faster than in the first half.
The point of read blocking against a
quick isn't always to stop the ball,
but to touch it.
Glasses kid has gotten through this
whole time just by following the ball.
It's no surprise that he's gotten used to it.
Chance ball!
There's no other...
...choice...
...but to...
...attack!
A minus tempo...
Back attack!
Go!
Hey, stop making your knees shake.
They're doing that on their
own, so I don't have a choice!
You jerk!
You understand that since we came this far,
we can't let them take this chance!
Episode 10: The Battle of Concepts
Next time on Haikyu!!:
"The Battle of Concepts."