We made it back alive.
We made it back alive...
But...
can the Agency look past the
thirty-five people she murdered?
What am I going to do if she and the
Agency are at odds with each other?
Good morning.
Can you turn around once for me?
So cute!
What's going on?
Well, she looks good in anything.
No, that's not what I'm talking about...
Kunikida-san...
Don't look at me like that.
I tried to stop them, too.
I wonder if this is going to work out.
Maybe it's not such a good idea.
Even if everyone else is okay with it,
Rampo-san might be a stickler
about the rules...
Oh, don't worry about that.
I'm back!
I bought some!
Rampo-san's into it the most.
Mixy Mixy Mixy Mix
Grape Flavor
This is the snack I told you about earlier.
It changes color when you mix it.
Go ahead, mix it.
First, open the bag,
then put the two powders in the container,
and add some water.
They're like siblings
in elementary school...
Next, mix really well.
It's important to put your feelings into it.
Okay? Mix, mix, mix, mix, mix, mix, mix.
And look, how strange!
But I'm the one who gets to eat it.
How childish...
Rampo-san, you're a terrible person!
Well, it is just like him to do that...
So, who called her over to the Agency?
It was me.
President!
Any movement from the police?
Thanks to the Port Mafia's
attempts to erase her identity,
they haven't tracked down who she is yet...
But she'll be a wanted fugitive soon.
Please let me stay here.
What?
I'll do anything.
I don't recommend it.
It's not because you were
with the Port Mafia,
or because we don't have work.
But don't do it.
It's not easy, the world we live in.
Besides, if you stay here,
the Mafia will find you eventually.
Shouldn't you run somewhere far away?
He said...
that I could do nothing
else but kill people.
I want to prove to myself that he's wrong.
President.
I would also like to ask on her behalf.
Please.
Please...
Very well.
What?!
I'll take her in.
Sprain fracture of the lower jaw.
Avulsion of the frontal bone
and thoracic vertebrae,
damage to the jugular ligament,
rupture of the brachial
and femoral muscles,
and first-degree burns over the entire body.
To top it off, he's in a coma.
He's suffered serious damage.
It is the price he paid
for failing his mission.
I'm sorry.
He may not regain consciousness.
But...
Don't feel so disappointed.
You all did your best.
You did fail in attacking the Agency and
capturing the weretiger,
and you sank the transport ship.
But you did your best, didn't you?
Effort is what's important.
Results come second.
Isn't that right?
Oh, that reminds me.
The remnants of Karma Transit,
the group Akutagawa-kun crushed
during the operation,
are apparently coming together.
I presume they want vengeance
on Akutagawa-kun.
Listen, Higuchi-kun.
The Mafia are, in the end,
an act of commerce that employs
violence as its currency.
It is allowed to desire and
kill anything and anyone.
Retaliation in kind is a matter
of expenditure and liability.
But... liability?
Akutagawa-senpai has accomplished
much in his missions thus far...
Indeed, Akutagawa-kun is competent.
His propensity for violence is high,
even for our organization.
But what about you?
Higuchi-kun,
have you ever felt that you are
actually suited for this job?
Episode 11
First, an Unsuitable Profession for Her
I look horrible.
That's quite enough for rehearsals, Gin.
The Black Lizard.
Gin's often stuck with dark jobs like
infiltration and assassination.
It's not unusual for him to have
to slit the throat of one of our own
by the higher-ups' command.
When it's for real, you won't
even have time to be surprised.
You're saying the boss will terminate me?
Not at the moment.
But I don't know about tomorrow.
Are you here to mock me?
If I were in your situation,
I'd rethink my current position before
an assassin arrives at my doorstep.
You, along with Akutagawa-kun,
are a strike force under the
boss's direct supervision.
As such, you have the authority to give
orders to us in the combat squad.
In that sense, you are our superior.
But what makes us obey is not your authority,
Rashoumon
but fear and respect for the
ability Akutagawa-kun wields.
Higuchi-kun...
During the time Akutagawa-kun
is incapacitated,
do you possess something
that motivates us to obey?
I don't need your help!
Akutagawa-senpai!
Even for you, this would be suicide!
You're walking right into a
building full of security guards!
You didn't even give us subordinates
any orders about how to support you—
Shut up!
What would you know about any of this?
That's a beacon.
A beacon visible from anywhere in the city.
It is a powerful beacon that
will be seen by the one
who left without a word,
and without acknowledging my power.
But it's my job to help you!
I don't need your help!
I need no one's help!
I'm back.
Have you ever felt that you are
actually suited for this job?
Of course not...
Yes? This is Higuchi.
What?!
I urge you to reconsider.
Your actions are contrary to
what the brass would want.
Are you sane?
That's suicide!
Akutagawa was abducted by foreign mercs
hired by Karma Transit's remnants!
Not only do they have numbers on their side,
they're armed to the teeth!
The boss will eventually issue orders
to conduct a retrieval operation.
Wait until that happens!
There will be no order!
If we retaliate as an organization
against smugglers
who targeted Akutagawa-senpai
as an individual,
the ripple effect will trigger a
large-scale conflict with other organizations.
To avoid that,
the brass will turn a blind eye to a
personal dispute between individual members...
Akutagawa-senpai has been cut off.
But what can you hope
to do by yourself?
Nothing.
Still!
I can't stand by and do nothing!
I knew...
I knew I wasn't suited for this job.
I knew I didn't have my
subordinates' respect.
If I were in your situation,
I'd rethink my current position before
an assassin arrives at my doorstep.
It's not easy to leave the Port Mafia,
but it's not impossible.
I've thought about it many times.
Yet I didn't, because...
Crap.
I can't rescue Akutagawa-senpai
with this injury...
Yet I didn't, because...
Kill everyone you don't recognize!
Why is the Black Lizard here?
You are our superior officer.
If our superior officer is in danger,
we must act.
I guess we're about done.
Akutagawa-senpai...
Senpai...
Senpai!
Higuchi?
Senpai, you're bleeding.
Sorry about all this.
It's not easy to leave the Port Mafia,
but it's not impossible.
Yet I didn't, because...
It's my job.
You look after the girl.
What, me?
Of course.
You saved her.
Okay.
Excuse me.
We're from the city police.
Oh, welcome.
Oh?
You're Minoura-kun. Your subordinate
was arrested a while ago, right?
We're here today on a
different matter, detective.
We have a case.
Episode 11
Second, an Ecstatic Detective Agency
They left as soon as they
were done talking business,
without even having had tea.
I guess policemen in cities are busy.
Where you're from, do the police
have lots of free time?
Everyone knows each other in my village.
Our policeman's job would
be fixing the well's pump,
rescuing cats from chimneys,
and tasting the year's first watermelon.
What the...
What happens if anyone commits a crime?
The perpertrator'd get tied up
and thrown off a cliff.
Um, Kenji-san...
You can call me Kenji-kun.
Until two months ago, I was living
in a village called Ihatov
where there is neither
electricity nor telephones.
I was recruited by the president
and came to the city.
The city's full of new concepts.
I'm having a lot of fun.
New? Like what?
Isn't bartering
good enough?
First, I don't really understand
the concept of money.
I see...
Kunikida-san,
What should we about the request
from the city police earlier?
A car in motion blew up
for unknown reasons...
It'll be a challenge.
The police have given up on it.
Atsushi, want to give this one a try?
Shadow another agent and
quickly learn the ropes.
You can do this.
Got it.
What's going on?
What's that?
I heard a car was just going along
when it suddenly flew to there.
Another explosion?
I'm not sure I'm up for this...
The driver died on impact.
He hasn't been identified.
Why not?
Can't we identify people if their
fingerprints or teeth are intact?
Yes.
If they were intact.
What?!
Then...
It's all mush inside that car...
All right,
Rampo-san would be able to solve
the case right away here,
Yokohamabashi
but our task right now is
to gather information.
Oh, Ken-chan.
Oh hello, Miss Maeda.
Thank you for the boar meat the other day.
It was delicious.
It was extra sent from my home.
It was nothing.
"Miss"?
She'd be one of the
younger ladies at my village.
Hey, boy.
The vegetable garden I told you about,
it doesn't drain very well.
It must be the soil in the rows.
I'll come take a look tomorrow.
Thanks.
You're really popular.
Hey, Ken-chan.
You on a job?
We're investigating the car explosion
that happened on that street.
Do you know anything?
Oh, that...
There are... rumors...
I'm not really supposed to talk about it,
but the young'uns were saying
that before it happened,
backstreet folks from the
factory district bought a load of fertilizer.
Fertilizer...
I wonder if they realized
the beauty of farming.
No, they were apparently talking
about manufacturing something...
Then it was probably nitrogen fertilizer.
Nitrogen fertilizer?
It's an ingredient for building bombs.
What?!
Thank you as always.
It was very helpful.
I'd do anything for you, Ken-chan.
We already have a lead...
Let's stay friendly.
Kenji-kun's amazing.
The same goes for me.
I'll be counting on you.
Speaking of the back streets
of the factory district,
there's a meeting hall for the
Gojo Youth Association there.
Youth Association?
Put in city terms... a gang?
A... A gang?!
I wonder if they're the ones
who built the bomb.
Well, let's go ask them face to face.
Wait a minute!
Even if they were responsible,
I doubt they'd admit to it.
Won't it be risky?
If we are sincere in our
inquiries, they'll respond.
It's how things are.
I-It's how things are?
Is it?
It's...
I guess it is how things are!
Hey, Tanizaki.
Nikonikodou
Supermarket
Aren't you with Atsushi?
Was Off Purchasing
Eggs on a
Limited-Time Only Sale
Oh, Kenji-kun went with him.
What, with Kenji?!
Yes, they went to the crime scene together.
Kenji-kun's very competent.
He's solved many difficult cases,
so I doubt there'll be problems—
It's a huge problem!
Kenji's methods are too unique.
He's not a good role model!
But given how simplistic
and naïve Atsushi is,
he may easily take Kenji's
methods at face value
and believe them to be the gold standard!
Best and Worst Team
This isn't good...
Huh?!
Did you all build the bomb that
made the car go flying?
You're funny!
You guys cops?
Not at all. We're with the
Armed Detective Agency.
Oh, nice chain!
You must be keeping one on you
to use when you need to haul cows.
Don't touch me!
What's your play?!
Oh, I just wanted you all to tell me
whether you're responsible for what happened.
Huh?
Don't know anything about it.
Right?
I see!
I'm sorry to have bothered you.
Huh?!
Thank you for your help.
What?
H-Hey, Kenji-kun?
They were lying, no matter
how you try to look at it.
They're the ones responsible!
They might've used the bomb to kill someone
in an opposing gang, or something.
But they said they didn't know anything.
Well, sure, but...
Be it with a cow or a person...
Be it in a village or a city,
if you are sincere, you can
communicate with others.
I've never failed using this method.
R-Really?
Really.
I guess I can see that.
Shall we get back for now?
Yeah.
Grrrrrowl
Let's go by a beef bowl
place on our way back.
I'm starving.
Kenji-kun, you can eat beef
even though you keep cows?
I love cows!
I love having cows, communing
with cows, and eating cows.
The bomb was used to kill
an enemy gang member.
Who knew private investigators
would sniff us out...
Since you left without
really questioning us,
does that mean you found conclusive proof?
You're gonna tell the cops, aren't you?
We won't let you.
I see.
I'm glad you went through the
trouble to tell us the truth.
Huh?
I knew sincere conversation
would lead to understanding.
In all of my cases, everyone
confesses to me like this.
Oh, I see—
One down.
Crap!
We're surrounded...
What've I been doing?
Get 'em!
Ow...
Huh?
Phew.
Oops.
Ouch...
Oh, don't mind me.
This happens sometimes.
Out in the countryside,
cows often get in a temper
and refuse to listen to you.
In times like that...
Be not defeated by the rain.
Be not defeated by the wind.
Nor by the iron pipe.
Nor by the knife.
Nor by the metal bat.
Be of sound body.
Be without desire.
Never be angered.
Always have a quiet smile.
Miyazawa
Family Motto
That is whom I wish to be.
Should Cows Act Up,
Hit Them With
Whatever's Close
At Hand
This won't work.
I can't do things like this, Kunikida-san!
Calm down, idiot!
I commend you for realizing
that on your own.
Kenji is gifted with superhuman strength,
but he isn't invincible.
He can only manifest that
strength when he's hungry.
Beef Bowl
Huh?
Then what happens when he's full?
I can't eat any more...
He goes to sleep.
Meanwhile,
Dazai...
Sake
Snow Crab
I'll say I got away from
the Port Mafia tomorrow.
Episode 12
Borne Back Ceaselessly into the Past