Angelica, is that it for the orders?
Hugo.
Assuming his letter is accurate, yeah.
This is all is for his disciple?
Probably.
I guess you could call it an
introductory materials kit.
Really, though, a disciple?
For that half-baked guy?
Hugo.
Come on.
All right, let's start.
Okay.
Ready when you are, Angelica.
Yeah.
Dig deeper, dig deeper, droplet.
Forge, forge, steel.
Part the gold, cut the mortar, turn with...
Angelica!
What was that?
It should be around here...
Found it.
This is my gift.
I hope they like it.
That's why I asked you if
that was all for the orders.
I'd forgotten about this one.
A book from the land of disciples?
I found it at the used book store.
All right, Hugo.
Right.
Dig deeper, dig deeper, droplet.
Forge, forge, steel.
Part the gold, cut the mortar,
turn with those hands the
water wheel of the night.
Let what must go
flow to where it must be.
Now, take that to Ainsworth
and his disciple, Chise, please.
Those Awaiting a Star
Part 1
Morning, Ruth.
Morning, Chise.
Yes?
Is the medicine I requested ready?
The cough medicine, correct?
Elias.
Would you like Darjeeling?
Yes.
Please.
We're having a lot of
tomato dishes as of late.
We've got a lot of tomatoes,
since it's summer.
I see.
Ruth, you're having breakfast, right?
Yeah, Chise.
A gremlin?
I was making him fix something he messed up.
Time to eat.
Are you not eating?
Oh, it's not that.
Seems like he's in a bad mood.
Oh, I'll start eating.
You're spilling it, Ruth.
Chise.
Yes?
What are your plans for today?
I'll be checking on the field in the
back, to pick whatever is ready.
The herbs are maturing, too,
so I'm thinking of drying all of them.
Once I'm done with my morning tasks,
I'll be studying magic as usual.
What will you do?
There's a book I haven't finished,
so I'll read the rest of that.
Is it the one I gave you the other day?
Yes.
Chise, acquiring knowledge is fine,
but you need experience as well.
It seems kind of dangerous, though.
I thought I should learn it well first.
That's important, too,
but I'm your teacher.
You can ask me if you ever
want to experiment.
Yes.
I'll pick out a book suitable for you.
Let me know.
Coming.
S-Sorry.
All this stuff came crashing down on me.
I couldn't stop it.
That's fine.
Angie really stuffed it full, though.
Angelica-san?
I ordered some learning materials for you.
This is all for me?
Yes.
The books are still too advanced for you,
but I'll make sure you can
use the tools right away.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Oh.
Use this when you go into the forest.
Use this when you're gathering fairies.
This book's very easy to read.
This one's...
Now, Chise, let's bring this to the study.
The study?
Ah, have I not told you yet?
You haven't.
Stare...
May I finish breakfast first?
Good idea.
Aren't you going in?
Right.
What's wrong?
Elias, um...
May I tidy up this room?
I have a feeling it'll be difficult
to find things in here.
Well, I suppose I don't mind.
Ruth.
Okay.
I never even thought of
cleaning the bookshelves.
Even if I sort them, they tend to
end up elsewhere on their own.
Eventually I got sick of it.
I told Silky that she doesn't
need to bother, either.
B-But, maybe with enough diligence,
we can maintain some order.
If you think so, it must be true.
Chise, why don't we go for a walk?
Um...
Thank you very much,
for all the new learning materials.
I'm your magic teacher.
I'm just doing what anyone would.
I know, but why so many?
I simply thought you'd need it.
Nothing. Never mind.
The Lonely Little Star
This book...
What's the matter?
Angelica-san sent this.
A gift?
A Japanese book.
How unusual.
Looks like it's special.
Is it?
I guess.
E-Elias?
Um...
Tell me.
In what way is that book special to you?
Er, but we aren't done tidying up the books.
We can do that whenever.
I'm your magic teacher, but you're
my human teacher, aren't you?
I think it's important to answer your
student's questions as much as you can.
I know, but...
Tell me
about that book.
Please?
All right.
Our Slay Vega is telling a story.
The beloved child's telling a story?
I want to hear.
I read this book when I was still alone.
The Lonely Little Star
I shouldn't have had you.
Mom.
Mom!
She's way too much of a burden to take in.
And I hear she's odd,
talking to herself and behaving strangely.
Hey, I heard your mom left you.
No, her mom killed herself.
What's the difference? She's an orphan.
She didn't want you, did she?
Give it back!
No way!
Please!
Wait until I'm done.
No!
Please stop making a mess this early.
Take it if you can.
That's enough!
Okay.
Time to eat!
Thanks for the food!
Put your dishes away first.
Wait, I'm coming.
Hold on!
Daiki, wear your hat,
and take your water bottle!
See you.
Take care.
Again?
I'm cleaning it up if you won't eat.
Hey.
Say something, honey.
That girl won't warm up to us.
She won't even touch the food I made her.
What? I gave her the same
thing I gave the other two.
Come on, what do you mean
you're in the middle of work?
You were the one who
said you'd take her in!
I really shouldn't have accepted her!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
One second.
Here.
Th-Thanks.
Are you okay?
What was that for?
Where are your parents?
You're bleeding.
I'm sorry.
Hey, wait!
I'm sorry!
Is someone there?
Are you okay?
I-I'm sorry.
I'll leave immediately.
Don't worry.
Those creepy things can't come in here.
You can see them?
Who are you, Onii-san?
I'm the magician of the forest.
Welcome...
To the library of the forest.
The young man stood amidst
the huge collection of books.
What does the girl dream of in her nap?
Maybe I should just take her away.